[SPEAKER_10]: Tonight, February 5th, 2012.
[SPEAKER_10]: Could mature video games soon carry an extra sales tax?
[SPEAKER_10]: Game Gear games are spotted for the 3DS, and a creation kit is set to come for Skyrim.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello my friends out there on the internet and welcome back to another week of the show where every gamer has a voice, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: It is episode number 444, that's three fours, not four fours, for this February the 5th of 2012.
[SPEAKER_08]: We are live as we are every Sunday night at All Games Radio, www.allgames.com, where we tape live, 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern, right after the Bobby Blackwolf show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Although not tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bobby had the night off.
[SPEAKER_08]: Something about a superb owl.
[SPEAKER_08]: He was a superb owl or something he was doing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought he had to do a stupor or something.
[SPEAKER_08]: Something like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: So anyway, my name is Rob Roberts, and I'll be joining you over the next few hours with my co-host.
[SPEAKER_08]: First off, you already heard her, but it's Dark Sakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or maybe it was Super Bowels.
Ha ha ha!
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe that was it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It might have been.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Something like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also, say hello, of course, to the one and only Techmaster Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_08]: How are you, Loki?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, there's like a game that a lot of the live listeners like to play on the show, and that is, you know, where did Loki get his food tonight?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because you like to go to like fast food restaurants or you go to, you know, whatever restaurant you take out and you bring it to the show to munch on air.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because, you know, we do this show at dinnertime.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: So if we don't eat before or after, we're kind of screwed.
[SPEAKER_08]: So but you went to two restaurants tonight, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: I went to KFC and got some honey barbecue wings, and then I went to McDonald's and got some fries.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you had wings and fries for this superb owl day.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: I see.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's very appropriate.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I wanted to go to someplace else other than fast food, but the teriyaki place nearby closed, and the fish and chips place nearby, they're closed today.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's just like all the other places are closed.
[SPEAKER_09]: I got one at the Quiznos, I guess, but eh.
[SPEAKER_08]: I got food too
[SPEAKER_08]: Where'd you get food from tonight?
[SPEAKER_05]: Whole Foods.
[SPEAKER_08]: How healthy?
[SPEAKER_08]: You damn dirty hippie?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, it was delicious.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it had grapes in it.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, so obviously Pink Elephant in the room.
[SPEAKER_08]: We are live on a night where usually there's not a lot of stuff going on anywhere, not on TV, not anywhere, unless you're, you know, the network that's carrying the Super Bowl, because we are up against... I was going to say, I did hear something big happen today, and that was Madonna said, fuck you to everybody.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, that was MIA, I guess.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, MIA?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, because she had her whole little entourage with her.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, Madonna, you know...
[SPEAKER_08]: Can we take like five seconds to judge Madonna?
[SPEAKER_08]: Sure, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, I'm done.
[SPEAKER_08]: Chat.orangeloungeradio.com if you want to join us live in our chat room and talk along with the program and all that good stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I got to say, look, look, I don't want to keep ragging on Madonna because I do love Madonna.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, no, seriously, I'm gay.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have to love Madonna.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, it's like a requirement.
[SPEAKER_08]: She was pre-Gaga.
[SPEAKER_08]: She's been slipping.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, I don't even want to make a Madonna Gaga thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, that's not a thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: People need to stop making that a thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not a thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's an evolution of styles.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's an evolution of music?
[SPEAKER_05]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was clearly an influence.
[SPEAKER_08]: Here's the thing about Madonna.
[SPEAKER_08]: She's kind of slipping.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I don't know what it is, but that new song, not good.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just not good.
[SPEAKER_08]: But anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: Was there ever a Madonna video game trying to get back on topic?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think there was.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wasn't Ray of Light in something?
[SPEAKER_08]: It might have been like in a dance game.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Look, we do, of course, always invite our live chatters at chat.orangelounge.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: However, we do ask the live chatters, don't talk about the Super Bowl in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not that we want to like censor you or, you know, but it's just as I'm trying to look through chat room and read comments that are relevant to the show, I don't need to see a bunch of like woo giants, woo patriots, blah, blah, blah, you know, whatever going on in there.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Try to keep the Super Bowl chat out.
[SPEAKER_08]: However, Puppy Bowl chat is just fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you want to talk about the Puppy Bowl, we'll deal with that.
[SPEAKER_05]: What about that cute little lab that was drinking from the bowl when we were watching?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, this year's Puppy Bowl was all about fumble.
[SPEAKER_08]: It seemed like.
[SPEAKER_08]: The whole time was fumble.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I was a big fan of Oscar the Dashun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Happy birthday, Tiger Claw.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_08]: It is Tiger Claw's birthday.
[SPEAKER_08]: We should take a minute to acknowledge Tiger Claw because he does a lot.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, the network that we're on, allgames.com, like...
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: He's the P.A.
[SPEAKER_05]: The personal assistant to director.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: So he's the one that actually gets the stuff done.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's a very good way of putting it.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's a great way of putting it.
[SPEAKER_08]: He's the director's assistant or the one that's actually doing all the work because he's, you know, making sure that all the live shows are up.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like we...
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: Why?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because he loves the network.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or he's getting money that we don't know about.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it's the first one.
[SPEAKER_08]: So absolutely a special happy birthday to Tigerclaw.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because without Tigerclaw, I don't know if there'd be a network still going right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because if the power went down, probably people wouldn't notice until the next live broadcaster's like, where's my show?
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you know that our buddy Brad from PodCulture just got the first gong of the year?
[SPEAKER_08]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_08]: What did Brad do?
[SPEAKER_05]: He said he heard the puppy bull just went to the dogs.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: I went old school and went with the gong instead of the sad trombone.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, so I want to start off, since we can't ignore the big sports thing that's going on, I realize most people this week are probably downloading this via the podcast, because I guess it's just an American tradition or something.
[SPEAKER_09]: Did you know that Paula Deen was in Sacramento this week?
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_08]: From what I remember... Her personal hamstache!
[SPEAKER_08]: From what I remember of him, him being a big fan of Paula Deen.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is it coated in butter?
[SPEAKER_08]: Didn't he have like a little southern twang, if I remember right?
[SPEAKER_09]: He was a big fan of... Not Paula Deen.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's been like years.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was...
[SPEAKER_03]: Rachel Ray?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, it's a country music star.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's some country female country music star.
[SPEAKER_05]: Trisha Yearwood?
[SPEAKER_09]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm trying to think of the five.
[SPEAKER_08]: Shania Twain.
[SPEAKER_08]: Might be Shania Twain.
[SPEAKER_08]: She's Canadian.
[SPEAKER_08]: Even though she hasn't been around in about 15 years.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, maybe that's not it.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's...
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's not important.
[SPEAKER_09]: The important thing is that she looks like she's made of plastic.
Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: By the way, I have to tell you the sad thing that happened yesterday.
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: Becky and I were at the Crocker Art Museum for Free Museum Day.
[SPEAKER_05]: And we were standing next to this younger couple just looking at a picture.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the guy's like, wow, this looks like a Rush album.
[SPEAKER_05]: And she's like, what's Rush?
[SPEAKER_05]: And Becky and I turned around and in unison with her boyfriend said, what's Rush?
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: And she looked like she wanted to crawl into a corner and die.
[SPEAKER_08]: At least that didn't happen on 2-1-12 because that would have been a disaster.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, can we actually talk about video games?
[SPEAKER_05]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe possibly.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I thought that that was worth sharing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, it's fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: I played some Because they're ass Because I hate football
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I don't... Personally, I don't hate football.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, hate's a strong word, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, I think I'm just willing to admit I'm not very good at sports games because I'm not very knowledgeable about a lot of the sports.
[SPEAKER_08]: And for me, a lot of these games like Madden and stuff get really, like, detailed and stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: And when I look at all these, like, you know, maps of the X's and O's and things like that... And I'm sure, like, a lot of football fans, I'm going to sound like the biggest idiot in the world right now, but, like, you have to realize there's some people that don't really watch sports, you guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I can't really follow a lot of those new sports games But I thought, that doesn't mean I hate all sports games Because that's certainly not true There's some sports games out there I actually really enjoy So I thought we could talk a little bit about sports games that don't suck So DarkSakura, I know you say you hate football But are there any sports games you can think of that you really enjoy?
[SPEAKER_05]: The only football game I've ever really enjoyed was Super High Impact on Super Nintendo My brothers and I would play the crap out of that And NBA Jam
[SPEAKER_05]: and NBA Jam.
[SPEAKER_05]: NBA Jam's pretty damn good.
[SPEAKER_05]: That skiing game on the PC that I used to scream at that was on the old... No, on the PC.
[SPEAKER_08]: Whiskey.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, you need to talk into a mic or they can't hear you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, Ski Free.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ski Free.
[SPEAKER_05]: That game would piss me off.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, actually, I remember one that I really, really liked.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alpine Racer.
[SPEAKER_05]: I freaking loved Alpine Racer.
[SPEAKER_05]: And we had one at my arcade.
[SPEAKER_05]: I played the shit out of that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was super good at it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I liked... It's not really, you know, sports, but I'll count it as prop cycle.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: that's stretching it that's like saying DDR and taking the easy way out of this question I didn't say DDR uh some sports games that I've enjoyed in the past I used to play a game on the NES back in the day that I loved and I think it was like baseball baseball stars was that it you could like manage I have that game yes that game that game was awesome on Neo Geo
[SPEAKER_08]: But they had an NES version of it, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: I think they did.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe it was RBI Baseball or something.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, it wasn't RBI Baseball.
[SPEAKER_08]: It wasn't any other baseball.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I think that Baseball Stars was the... I think they did a Neo Geo... That wasn't on Neo Geo.
[SPEAKER_05]: The version of the Neo Geo one.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think, like, they did one on the NES.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then, like, you know, because that didn't... The folks at Neo... They made some games on Nintendo before they spun off to their own thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, anyway...
[SPEAKER_08]: Other stuff I enjoy, Blades of Steel will always be one of my favorites.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, I had Ice Hockey and Blades of Steel on the NES.
[SPEAKER_08]: Those are both great games.
[SPEAKER_08]: I really like a lot of racing games if you want to try and get a little more modern.
[SPEAKER_08]: I do like a lot of, like I like the, although I don't know if it's really sports borderline, but I like the Wangan Midnight Maximum Tune games.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's not a sport.
[SPEAKER_08]: Racing is not a sport.
[SPEAKER_09]: Drifting is not a sport.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, drifting, they have competitions, but it's not like a sport.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've played the NASCAR games and I've enjoyed them, like in the arcade, you know, like the big old simulations that you get in there and get into.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like those.
[SPEAKER_08]: So those are pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm trying to think if there's a... Oh, you know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: I...
[SPEAKER_08]: I really enjoyed, at least in the past, I haven't played a lot of them recently, but I remember when I was growing up, I used to love, on the Commodore 64, because you all know I loved my Commodore 64 growing up, I used to play the shit out of Winter Games and Summer Games 2, which were kind of like the Olympic, I mean there was a Summer Games 1, but we didn't own it.
[SPEAKER_08]: so I had those other ones those are kind of like their Olympic games where you could do like cycling and you know if it was winter games you could do I don't know like I think figure skating and speed skating and some of the other stuff they have so I like the Olympics like I really do like that as far as sports go anyway so I like usually a lot of the Olympic games I even played the demo for that Mario and Sonic 2012 Olympic game that's coming out later this year because they have the 3DS demo out right now
[SPEAKER_08]: I like the trampoline one because that was the only one where you really noticed the 3D.
[SPEAKER_08]: But the cycling one drove me bonkers.
[SPEAKER_08]: And some of the ones DarkSakura said.
[SPEAKER_08]: I used to play NBA Jam in the arcade all the time.
[SPEAKER_08]: I really tried to like this new NBA Jam that just came out, but I didn't really care for it.
[SPEAKER_08]: The new one that was on, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: I downloaded the demo on Fire Edition or whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: Didn't care for it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was not good.
[SPEAKER_05]: That sad face.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I tried.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, what was the game?
[SPEAKER_05]: California Games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh yeah, California Games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, that was originally an Amiga game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wasn't great at it, but it was okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it had the Unreal 360.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, they tried to keep... Actually, that's like a spinoff of the Summer Games and Winter Games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because they kind of ran out of stuff to do Olympic related.
[SPEAKER_05]: 720 and...
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, that was a different series, but yeah, 720 was awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyhow, Loki, what about you?
[SPEAKER_09]: I used to play some of the NFL Blitz arcade game back in, I don't know, when I worked at Roundtable.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then Co-op, it's running.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know, I don't play a lot of sports games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, I thought of a racing game that ought to count because everybody fucking loved this game when they were a kid.
[SPEAKER_08]: Iron Man, Ivan Stewart's Super Off-Road Racing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Every pizza parlor had that, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: I never played it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I actually never played that one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_08]: That had an awesome NES.
[SPEAKER_08]: I remember when the NES version of that came out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Super NES.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or was it NES?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, it was regular NES because it was one of the few games that supported the... Multitap?
[SPEAKER_08]: The Ultitap or whatever it was called.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Multitap.
[SPEAKER_05]: If I was going to count a racing game as included, then I would totally, totally just put in the original Ridge Racer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because that was a money sucker for me.
[SPEAKER_05]: If I hadn't worked at the damn arcade, I would have been broke.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, going to our chat room for some comments.
[SPEAKER_08]: If I got everything for Loki, sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just want to make sure.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_08]: Chat.OrangeLoungeRadio.com Kaijudo says, Baseball All-Stars was awesome and I had it on Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_08]: RDGSinge says, OMG, no one mentioned track and field.
[SPEAKER_08]: That one was okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know they had an Xbox Live port of that way back in the beginning when it was a bunch of old 80s Konami games were being ported over.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it's really... I mean, it's good, but it's really just button mashing.
[SPEAKER_08]: I did play Track and Field not even like three months ago, though, the last time I was at Electronica at Disneyland because they have the whole Flynn's Arcade and they had a Track and Field machine.
[SPEAKER_09]: I played it on my...
[SPEAKER_09]: Arcade Cabinet not too long ago.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, a few months ago.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it's really just like, you know, but I guess then again, the Commodore 64 games were no better.
[SPEAKER_08]: So what am I, who am I to judge?
[SPEAKER_08]: So, all right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyhow, let's move on and talk about our gaming weeks.
[SPEAKER_08]: We usually like to start off the show, talk about the video games that we've been playing this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dark Sakura, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: I played WoW.
[SPEAKER_05]: And something epic happened.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, I have to tell a story.
[SPEAKER_05]: I told you earlier, but I'm going to tell the newie.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: So this guy named LichRage on Blade's Edge Alliance, HumanDK...
[SPEAKER_05]: I was wandering around trying to finish the Love is in the Air crap, you know, they do for Valentine's suck.
[SPEAKER_05]: And there's this thing that you have to throw rose petals on certain race and class combinations, and one of them is a human death knight.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I just went in trade chat and said, is there a human death knight around?
[SPEAKER_05]: And this one said, yeah, ten gold.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I invited him into my party.
I
[SPEAKER_05]: and targeted him and then left the party.
[SPEAKER_05]: And he said, you lied.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm like, you shouldn't have been charging for something that's a free service.
[SPEAKER_05]: And he's like, I've only got 20 gold.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm like, so?
[SPEAKER_05]: Go out and earn it like the rest of us.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mining and herbalism are your friends.
[SPEAKER_05]: And he said, suck it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't do plenty of the herbalism.
[SPEAKER_05]: So he's like, suck it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I was like, ignore.
[SPEAKER_08]: You should have just put, deal with it, happy face.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I wasn't rude to him.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, I was like, you know, when I started off... You swindled him.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't swindle him.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe a little bit.
[SPEAKER_08]: A little bit.
[SPEAKER_08]: You swindled him a little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: He thought I swindled him.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you could, you would have had your character show her boobies a little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because my intention was the moment someone said, DK here, I was just going to find their name, target them, and throw the rose petals anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was the plan.
[SPEAKER_05]: Manny's like 10 gold.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's stupid.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't do that crap.
[SPEAKER_05]: Go out and earn your own damn money.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't help it if you keep buying every pet that pops up in the auction house.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's addicting.
[SPEAKER_05]: It kind of is.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've actually spent lots of money on pets.
[SPEAKER_09]: They should really have a series of hoarders where it's people collecting wild pets.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like MMO hoarders?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, MMO hoarders.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sure that exists somewhere.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: So she gave it to me because I think she already had it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then I'm also playing Bust a Move on my phone.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's still super fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: I really enjoy it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And also I have to make an observation before we move on to Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: On the can of Arizona Diet Green Tea is a prostitute.
[SPEAKER_05]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_05]: A taiyu.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can tell because her obi is tied in the front and her hair is over elaborate.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what I get for studying weight.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know whoever designed that had no idea.
[SPEAKER_08]: They were just like, we just need to put something.
[SPEAKER_08]: It looks like a geisha.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, we just need to put something Asian looking on this green tea.
[SPEAKER_05]: But they've put a whore.
[SPEAKER_05]: Granted, a very high class, talented, artistic whore.
[SPEAKER_08]: This writing here probably says, I am horse butt.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I mean, I just had to point it out.
[SPEAKER_05]: I looked at the can and it dawned on me that it's a prostitute.
[SPEAKER_08]: Isn't there some website of like bad Chinese text tattoos where you see people that got tattoos of Chinese writing and it says like really horrible things?
[SPEAKER_08]: Of course, I don't know how much of that's legit and how much of it's fake, but eh.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, if that's it for DarkSakura's Gaming Week, Loki, how was your Gaming Week?
[SPEAKER_09]: I played Skyrim.
[SPEAKER_09]: Only a little bit though, actually.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mainly this week was working on Grand Theft Auto modding.
[SPEAKER_09]: And thank God finished what I was working on because it was making my brain explode.
[SPEAKER_09]: Had to go back and learn or relearn some calculus stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: Mainly because during my actual calculus class, well actually pre-calculus because I never took calculus, I was too busy programming a Final Fantasy type game on my calculator.
[SPEAKER_09]: Skyrim I'm 123 hours now into the game and um
[SPEAKER_09]: I saw some things how Skyrim's won all these Game of the Year awards.
[SPEAKER_09]: That game is so fucking broken.
[SPEAKER_09]: It is just ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_09]: I literally have to now keep my iPod with me and pull up the quests as I do them to look at the bugs section.
[SPEAKER_09]: Known bugs for this quest so I don't run into them.
[SPEAKER_09]: I ran into two yesterday that were not really game breaking but one of them would have been pretty fucking annoying if it
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: Awesome!
[SPEAKER_09]: It's not... It was one I hired.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was a guy that was like, Hey, I'm the strongest guy here!
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm like, you die!
[SPEAKER_08]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_08]: You hired a companion so you could sacrifice them?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: So anyway, so I did that.
[SPEAKER_09]: And when she appears, when the Daedra appears, it's just like... It does this weird screen effect thing that gets all blurry and purple.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: But no, it's not for the record.
[SPEAKER_09]: The other one was when I was trying to become the Thane of Riften.
[SPEAKER_09]: Apparently, if you visit your house, you have to purchase a house in Riften.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you visit the house before you talk to the Jarl, you can never become the Thane of Riften.
[SPEAKER_09]: It just breaks the whole quest.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks for... There is no fucking way they bug tested this game.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, most of the quests they seriously must not have tested at all.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because there is no way that this would have been missed.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is just like... Completely obvious stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, what would happen if I visited the house first?
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, it breaks the fucking quest.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, no, we're not going to test for that.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's good.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, it worked the first time I played through it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sigh.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, and I cheated in... Well, not technically cheated.
[SPEAKER_09]: I exploited a glitch in the game to level my character up to 81.5, which is the cap.
[SPEAKER_09]: I capped all my skills at 100.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wait, the cap is 81.5?
81.5.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: It just happens to be that's the amount of leveling you get when you have all your skills at 100.
81.5.
[SPEAKER_09]: It didn't matter anyways.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm unkillable anyways, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just didn't want to have to...
[SPEAKER_09]: I wanted all my perk points right away so I could figure out where I wanted them.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I actually went back and started doing the actual main quest line.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I gotta say, man, that thing is short.
[SPEAKER_09]: It is a really short quest line.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, they usually are.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, the game isn't really about the main quest.
[SPEAKER_08]: Main quest is just kind of there to help you learn about the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: I am looking forward to the 1.4 patch so I can finish Blood on the Ice.
[SPEAKER_09]: Then I'm going to go kill everybody once I'm done with all that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Everybody will die in a bloody rage.
[SPEAKER_09]: I did see a video this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was great.
[SPEAKER_09]: Someone had changed their player model to one of the kids and then they had some spell on there that was dragon fire and it was hilarious.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: It made me laugh.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was a why kids can't be killed because they're actually dragons.
[SPEAKER_09]: And Call of Duty.
[SPEAKER_09]: Play more Call of Duty, of course.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, anything else?
[SPEAKER_08]: I think that's it, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: My gaming week.
[SPEAKER_08]: See, I actually played quite a bit of new stuff this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: A few games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Soul Calibur V, quickly.
[SPEAKER_08]: I literally played Soul Calibur V once, so I don't want to do a total review on it.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I did spend about an hour with it the other night when I got it.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I had a fairly good time.
[SPEAKER_08]: The fighting's a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: Creative character's great.
[SPEAKER_08]: I love creative character.
[SPEAKER_08]: and you know I was making some fun characters with that and story mode I noticed though right off the bat was was kind of weird because like you would have these full cut scenes and then like a storyboard like thing like you just see like a cartoon storyboard that transitions paint like it almost feels like it was like half done a little bit rushed and
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess the bottom line I noticed after you know the short amount of time I did play the game is that although the core fighter game itself which is what you're paying the money for is good I feel like everything kind of on the shell outside of that was a little bit like rushed or wonky except well creative characters decent the only thing that I'm disappointed is that you know because it's a game that didn't really pre-order anything do you know how they have that pre-order character that really weird looking guy no because I didn't pre wait no I pre-ordered on Amazon but they didn't give me anything
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, you're supposed to get this pre-order character.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's this guy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe it's only a GameStop or whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's this guy in a top hat or something like that that has some really wacky moves.
[SPEAKER_09]: But that would have been kind of fun to play as.
[SPEAKER_09]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think he may have been from 4.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or the PSP one, maybe, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, he might have been the PSP one.
[SPEAKER_08]: I wish the Lost Amel was in this one.
[SPEAKER_08]: I made a male Ivy.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: What, like wearing Voldo's gear?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, just wearing like a tight top and leather pants, you know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, yeah, Soul Calibur V. I'll tell you more about it when I have more time to play it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I've been on my PlayStation 3 mostly been playing and sucked into Final Fantasy XIII too, which came out the same day.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I've sunk a good at least seven hours, if not more, into that at this point.
[SPEAKER_08]: So...
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I'm really enjoying Final Fantasy XIII too.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm really surprised at how divided the internet is on this because there's just some people that really just fucking hate Final Fantasy XIII.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I really don't think this game is going to do much to sway your mind.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, it's to the point, like, this is how divided it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know that Final Fantasy XIII too is one of, like, what, less than 20 games to get a perfect 40 from Fumitsu Magazine ever, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: And then, like, Edge, I think in the UK, gave it a 5 out of 10.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, that's quite a difference between a perfect pristine score from Fumitsu and a 5.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, I mean, it's just...
[SPEAKER_09]: It's because these fucking reviewers go into this shit very biased.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, they're like judging games on shit that they never judged games on before.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like, this game is too linear.
[SPEAKER_09]: Really?
[SPEAKER_08]: All these other RPGs were too linear?
[SPEAKER_08]: I just want to give the disclaimer.
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't read either of those reviews.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going off Wikipedia.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was just really surprised, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was like, wow, this is really a diverse, you know, I would expect some, you know, not everybody's going to like everything, but just usually when it's all over the map like that, especially when Famitsu gave it such a high score, it just really surprised me.
[SPEAKER_08]: But anyway, let's not talk about what other people thought of it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's talk about what I thought of it.
[SPEAKER_08]: of course what they're doing is they're trying to fix a lot of what people bitched about with XIII there's definitely not a linear sense in this game whatsoever now you have this interesting map, the Crux, that you can travel to all these different time zones
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_08]: It's really like an entire season of Doctor Who scratched into a video game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or actually, in some ways, it reminds me of Quantum Leap.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, where are Noel and Sarah going to end up next?
[SPEAKER_08]: Wah, wah, wah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, but, uh, yeah, I mean, the, the, the really good thing about 13.2 is that the battle system is robust right off the bat.
[SPEAKER_08]: And, you know, well, maybe you don't really get the monster character and the monster trapping and all that till episode two, but needless to say...
[SPEAKER_08]: In 13, one of the big issues that people had was that it took forever before you even got to where you can flip paradigms and where the battle system becomes really interesting when you get the whole paradigm stuff, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: For the first two chapters, you're pretty much just button mashing.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's nothing else to do but auto-attack.
[SPEAKER_08]: but in 13.2 that paradigm stuff starts battle one which is good so um towns are back random conversations side quests that people want you to do for them uh Chocolina who's now the shop who shows up everywhere I love Chocolina she's like a Vegas show girl meets a Chocobo it's great and um apparently there's like a casino later on with tons of mini games and all that stuff so
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm really enjoying it.
[SPEAKER_08]: The story, although it's kind of confusing, I hate to make myself sound stupid, but the story is really confusing.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I gotta say, it is really cool to kind of see characters from 13 years later.
[SPEAKER_08]: And they do some neat stuff with that, so it's cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: The only thing about the characters that's a little weird is that your party only has two people.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I don't know if that's ever gonna change.
[SPEAKER_08]: I kinda think the whole game might be just the two people and the rotating monster.
[SPEAKER_08]: That might turn some people off.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think there's other stuff through DLC.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think you might be able to get more characters as DLC.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's a little bit...
[SPEAKER_08]: Side Eye and Judging Square for jumping on that bandwagon because I really don't like when so much stuff is behind DLC.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, it's kind of like now games are really costing $90 because it's $60 for what you would.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, a lot of that costume shit is paid to unlock content.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, of course it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: Of course it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's nothing to download right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: but I'm told that a bunch of zone areas are unlocked through DLC and I heard that Lightning and a General from the first game are supposed to be DLC at some point so I have to judge Square a little bit for hopping on that bad wagon you know especially when the series is a little bit vulnerable right now I think that especially when your game only has two characters in it that's a little bit...
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm judging you, but at least the game that you get for the money you pay for it is a robust experience.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I can think of far worse games to blow $60 on.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think this game is worthy of a 5.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know if it's a perfect 40, but it's really good.
[SPEAKER_08]: But not perfect.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that's what I think about Final Fantasy XIII too.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think if you like XIII, play it.
[SPEAKER_08]: And don't let that hurdle of, but I never beat XIII, stop you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because yes, the game will tell you what happened at the end of XIII, and you can even go through a mode that just, like it'll just walk you through the story of Final Fantasy XIII.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, albeit it's kind of like narrated text, but you get the idea.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, I didn't beat XIII, and I don't feel like it was really ruined for me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, I will know what happens right at the end of 13.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, you know, there's still a lot of stuff that it takes to get there.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know?
[SPEAKER_08]: So it's like, just knowing the ending, I don't think it's going to totally ruin 13 for me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I will have to go back and... Because I was on like chapter 12 when I stopped.
[SPEAKER_08]: I got a long way through it.
[SPEAKER_08]: But yeah, 13.2 is worth your time.
[SPEAKER_08]: One other game I played this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: So...
[SPEAKER_08]: Tangent for a minute.
[SPEAKER_08]: Orange Lounge Radio started, of course, for many years.
[SPEAKER_08]: For about, what, four years, we were a show exclusively about music games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because DarkSakura, Loki, and myself all met playing DDR at the local arcade.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the original concept behind the show was, let's make this kind of like show about what we enjoy doing at the arcades every Wednesday or Thursday night, whatever night it was we were going back then.
[SPEAKER_08]: and you know we also always used to go to Brookfield's the diner afterwards and kind of talk shit about games it was kind of like let's let's do that as like our show um so for a long time it was about music games we talked about DDR and the new songs are coming out in DDR we used to talk about guitar freaks and drum media and keyboard media para para paradise all these games that Konami did and when they first came out I think we were right on right I think we changed formats right around the time Guitar Hero was breaking and all that stuff um
[SPEAKER_08]: So, the bottom line is, we switched from doing a music game only show to a gaming show because there wasn't a lot of stuff in the music game world to talk about anymore, which was ironic because then about a year after we switched, Rock Band and Guitar Hero 2 and all that just made it huge.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, you know, we felt like there was more we could do talking about regular games.
[SPEAKER_08]: I haven't been following the music gaming scene as closely since then, but I do kind of like, you know, I like to, I check Bomani style once in a while.
[SPEAKER_08]: I checked DDR Freak when that was still running, you know, and I would just kind of like keep, I'd like to keep tabs on the music game scene.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I gotta say, I haven't really, really enjoyed a Bomani game in a long time.
[SPEAKER_08]: I haven't.
[SPEAKER_08]: I haven't really cared for a lot of the music in the newer Beatmania 2DXs.
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't think Jubeat was all that, or Ubeat, or whatever they call that game.
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't think, what else has come out since then?
[SPEAKER_08]: Poppin' Music, you know, the one they tried here on the Xbox was absolutely awful.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Wii one was really weird.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I can't say I've really, really, truly enjoyed a Bomani game.
[SPEAKER_08]: until I think this week I downloaded a game on Xbox Live that's out called Rhythm Party and I have to say it's actually pretty good now it's not perfect there are some things wrong with it but all things considered Rhythm Party is kind of the game that Dance Masters the Kinect game that came out last year on Xbox 360 that was like Konami's first like let's put a Bomani game with Kinect
[SPEAKER_08]: Rhythm Party is the game that Dance Masters should have been, I really think.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ironically enough, Dance Masters, or Dance Evolution as it's called in Japan, is an arcade game, or will become an arcade game very soon.
[SPEAKER_08]: Really?
[SPEAKER_08]: But Rhythm Party should, okay?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, here's the thing about Rhythm Party.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: Konami is setting this game up to fail, I really think.
[SPEAKER_08]: I kind of think this is just coming out.
[SPEAKER_08]: I went to Bomani Style to see what they were saying about it,
[SPEAKER_08]: There's nothing on it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I put it on Twitter, like Rhythm Party, and nobody's talking about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I saw one Major Nelson tweet.
[SPEAKER_08]: The only way I knew about this game was from following Naoki Midea on Facebook, who is, of course, one of the big guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: And we mentioned it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Remember, we mentioned it on the show last week, because we were like, oh, Naoki's teasing this game.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I remembered that, and so I'm like, oh, I'll download it and check it out.
[SPEAKER_08]: And when I fired it up, I noticed that the menu music was the music from Dance Dance Revolution 5th Mix.
[SPEAKER_08]: and I was like, oh, I loved Fifth Mix.
[SPEAKER_08]: I love this music.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then I went into the game and I was kind of like looking through the songs.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm like, okay, well, even though it's only 10 songs, this is a decent mix of songs.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like there's more stuff that's interesting to me here than there was in all of Dance Masters.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, and then I fired up the game and played it for a little bit.
[SPEAKER_08]: So let me tell you where this game's a little bit different.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not really like Dance Masters or Dance Central at all because you're not trying to mimic a pre-choreographed dance.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's actually a lot more like DDR or really Samba de Amigo.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_08]: But you also get extra points as you freestyle.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you jump, you get extra points.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you turn, you get extra points.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you hit balls with hands you're not supposed to, like you do crossovers and stuff, you get extra points.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you do poses and stuff, you get extra points.
[SPEAKER_08]: So there's really this emphasis on kind of making your own dance out of the balls that fly in out of that kind of pattern.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was entertaining, especially for somebody that really liked DDR, that was all about timing and hitting the arrows.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is truly a Kinect version of DDR, which I don't think Dance Masters was.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dance Masters, unfortunately, felt like Dance Central did this a little better.
[SPEAKER_08]: Better music, easier to understand the choreography.
[SPEAKER_08]: Whereas I think this is now a true, okay, it's not about the choreography, it's about the more music timing and doing all this.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, yeah, the song list, there's only 10 songs, which is a little eh, because two of them feature Vanilla Ice, but there are some good choices in there, Born This Way, Every Little Step, YMCA
[SPEAKER_08]: Every song, this is what really reminded me of old DDR.
[SPEAKER_08]: Every song has its own unique background, its own unique video, and its own unique kind of thing that your character does or turns into.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let me explain what I mean.
[SPEAKER_08]: When you're playing Born This Way by Lady Gaga, if you do really well, you suddenly turn into this electric peacock.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't even know how to explain it.
[SPEAKER_08]: But the cool thing is, it's still you.
[SPEAKER_05]: You look like a human pipe organ.
[SPEAKER_08]: YMCA
[SPEAKER_08]: Everything I used to really like about the DDR games is kind of in this game.
[SPEAKER_08]: But what I really feel like I'm playing here is the demo.
[SPEAKER_08]: for a full retail game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Where's the rest of the songs?
[SPEAKER_08]: Where's multiplayer?
[SPEAKER_08]: Where's anything?
[SPEAKER_08]: I really feel like they're selling a demo for what could potentially be a really good retail game.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I have this bad feeling because nobody knows about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I really feel like Konami just kind of...
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay Naoki, we know you have this idea.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why don't you throw something together?
[SPEAKER_08]: And like, you know, they threw together the demo and, you know, Konami was just like, eh, let's just put it out on Xbox Live and see if it sticks.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I just have this really bad feeling it's not gonna.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's room for the game to support DLC.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know if I trust Konami to handle the DLC appropriately based on other games where two songs ever come out as DLC.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to just cross my fingers and really hope that they get some licensed songs and they get some good stuff in there to really round out the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Rhythm Party is really not bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: and I'll be really bummed if it doesn't go anywhere other than this because it's not that bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know, Jamie, you just only got to watch me play it a little bit but I think you kind of went into it going, really?
[SPEAKER_08]: Rhythm party?
[SPEAKER_08]: But you kind of seemed like you were like, oh, this is cute, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want... Actually, I do want...
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, you've always been a vocal critic of Konami.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know you haven't really played it, but you saw me doing it for a little bit.
[SPEAKER_09]: It looked okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: But when I saw them announcing this, I'm like, oh, that's going to suck.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't even want to look at it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Right?
[SPEAKER_09]: And it was just all right.
[SPEAKER_09]: I remember my snarky comment on it was like, oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: I remember what it was.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was something about...
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know what happened behind the scenes, but it is worth your time to check out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, the way they may be treating it is like a retail game where they're gonna...
[SPEAKER_09]: and I'll see you next time.
[SPEAKER_08]: slap together a 10-pack of old DDR classics.
[SPEAKER_08]: I realize if you're doing custom backgrounds for everything, maybe that takes a little more time and art and so forth, but they could get away with fudging it a little bit.
[SPEAKER_08]: The old DDR games recycled a few things here and there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Recycle some of the art assets and just put out 10 other DDR songs for free, and then this game will have a really enhanced value.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it will.
[SPEAKER_08]: and then put some, like, if you get some decent licenses, like, they license Gaga.
[SPEAKER_08]: Somebody paid for that, like, you know?
[SPEAKER_08]: But unfortunately, it's one modern song and then two retro classics with Bobby Blackwolf, or Bobby Blackwolf.
[SPEAKER_09]: Bobby Blackwolf, uh, a.k.a.
[SPEAKER_09]: Vanilla Ice.
[SPEAKER_05]: I actually like the Vanilla Ice song.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bobby Brown, Bobby!
[SPEAKER_08]: And...
[SPEAKER_08]: That clip's going to end up on his show at some point.
[SPEAKER_08]: Watch.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bobby Brown and Village People were like the retro bigs.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's really it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Vanilla Ice, retro yet new.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: The songs, they're not terrible.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're not terrible.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're not like, I'm going to go run out and buy the CD tomorrow, but they're better than most of the stuff from Dance Masters, which was very unremarkable.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dance Masters was just frustrating.
[SPEAKER_09]: And the fact that they're making an arcade game now, it's just, there's no cues whatsoever to what to do.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, and I understand that, you know, para games and stuff like that,
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: How am I going to follow this?
[SPEAKER_05]: The only reason I was ever able to do anything good at Dance Masters was that I knew the Parapara routines.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's really only two Parapara songs in that whole game.
[SPEAKER_08]: There really are.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's five.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, there's two.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's Night of Fire.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought there were two others.
[SPEAKER_08]: I thought that they did Like a Virgin.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought Like a Virgin was in there.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_08]: But anyway...
[SPEAKER_08]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, I've spent a lot of time talking about that song, or talking about that game, but, you know, just as I've been a fan of music games for so, so long, I was just really surprised at what an unremarkable launch this game has had.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I think it's worth your attention, I really do.
[SPEAKER_08]: And if anybody from Konami, haha, is listening, you might want to consider making Rhythm Party the arcade game, because I think, but...
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe it needs a better name.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think Rhythm Party is the best name.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what they're calling it in Japan?
[SPEAKER_08]: Boom Boom Dance.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a better name.
[SPEAKER_08]: But there's no Boom Boom Dollar in it.
[SPEAKER_08]: And you know why I bet they didn't call it that here?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because of Boom Boom Rocket.
[SPEAKER_08]: Remember Boom Boom Rocket from EA?
[SPEAKER_08]: God, that was about five years ago now.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was an old-ass one with little arrows that would come up and you'd do the fireworks.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that was...
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm looking on here.
[SPEAKER_05]: It says that there's an achievement for playing three Parapara genre songs.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, maybe there's other songs that weren't in Parapara Paradise.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think that's what it was.
[SPEAKER_05]: There are songs that I knew, but they weren't in Parapara Paradise.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, I believe you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dance Masters wasn't, you know.
[SPEAKER_08]: But anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, so that's it for my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've talked plenty.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, housekeeping, real quick.
[SPEAKER_08]: Follow us on Facebook.
[SPEAKER_08]: Facebook.com slash Orange Launch Radio or of course there's Twitter.
[SPEAKER_08]: Twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's get into some news.
[SPEAKER_08]: And Loki's going to start us off tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: You got a lot of stuff about one particular company, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: And also, I was going to say, the song was for Dance Masters, so Night of Fire was one of them, Yesterday was the other Para song, and...
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know, it might have been one of these other... There's a lot of songs I don't recognize.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe Can't Stop Falling in Love Super Hero version?
[SPEAKER_09]: Because that did have a para.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, that was in para.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, that was a para para song.
[SPEAKER_08]: I bet that's it then.
[SPEAKER_09]: Mystery solved!
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_09]: If only it was that easy for companies to do well.
[SPEAKER_09]: THQ, on the other hand, has been having a rough... A boom boom fire of their own.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: First off, THQ received a stock delisting notice.
[SPEAKER_09]: And they basically have 180 calendar days until July 23rd to make the stock regain compliance for 10 consecutive business days.
[SPEAKER_09]: If the company can't comply, then they get taken off the stock market, basically.
[SPEAKER_09]: And, of course, their stock has fallen quite a bit down to about $0.70 a share.
[SPEAKER_09]: So that's not good.
[SPEAKER_09]: also the CEO they've taken a 50% pay cut
[SPEAKER_09]: And also the board of directors, they've taken pay cuts as well.
[SPEAKER_08]: Meaning $10 million as opposed to $20.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're going to see layoffs.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, the CEO doesn't make millions of dollars.
[SPEAKER_09]: He does make six figures.
[SPEAKER_09]: He dropped his salary from $718,500 a year to $359,250 a year.
[SPEAKER_09]: How's he gonna scrape by is what I want to know, man.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's some tough stuff right there.
[SPEAKER_09]: God, that's just disgusting.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then, of course, you know, some of the other, you know, they've cut from three times the highest bonus to, was it the...
[SPEAKER_09]: Just as high as bonus ever.
[SPEAKER_08]: At least he wasn't forced to take the, you know, Apple CEO at Steve Jobs used to get a dollar and then a bunch of stock options.
[SPEAKER_08]: At least this guy wasn't forced to take stock.
[SPEAKER_09]: The board of directors, they've decided to take 50% less cash compensation for a year.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um...
[SPEAKER_09]: Also, unfortunately, with all these cuts and delisting threats come layoffs.
[SPEAKER_09]: 240 people were set to be laid off, and it would be, I guess, across nine months.
[SPEAKER_09]: They said it should be, let's see here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Enough time to finish whatever game they were working on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't believe 240 is the correct number.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's up to 240.
[SPEAKER_09]: I want to say it was 172 or something like that is what it's supposed to be.
[SPEAKER_09]: They said that this isn't anything that they were trying to hide, that the cuts were described in their statement last week.
[SPEAKER_09]: and that no studios are a part of this.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's administration and publishing offices worldwide.
[SPEAKER_09]: And, you know, also...
[SPEAKER_09]: do the varying employment guidelines around the world and internal finance considerations.
[SPEAKER_09]: The restructuring will be completed by September 30, 2012, but most affected employees have already been notified.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then, on top of all that, they've revealed that they've lost $56 million in quarter three, which...
[SPEAKER_09]: That would, let's see, quarter ending in December 31st, 2011.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm kind of surprised that they lost a lot of money.
[SPEAKER_09]: I guess they were just in the hole so much that, you know, even though Saints Row III and WWE 12 did good, or well, I should say, it just wasn't enough to kind of make up for the slump in sales.
[SPEAKER_09]: And they actually had a pretty good quarter.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, I think we started off with, I don't remember if Warhammer, no, I don't think Warhammer was in that quarter.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think that was Q2.
[SPEAKER_09]: But anyways, regardless of that, one other game did come out in quarter three for them, and that would have been UDraw, and they're not putting out any more of those.
[SPEAKER_08]: All of this sad trombone stuff for THQ, is it all because of Udraw?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't think they could have invested.
[SPEAKER_08]: Could One Peripheral bring down a company like that?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, no.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or is it because their kiddie games are not doing too well either?
[SPEAKER_09]: but their kiddie games not doing well I don't think is a big deal because even this year they focused more on well not entirely more so on less on kiddie games more on their core franchises however though they did have a few games come out that were kind of kiddie that did not do well like for example they had Kung Fu Panda 2 which kind of bombed
[SPEAKER_09]: and you know what, it really is kind of their fault though, it bombed, I mean, let's see, they had on the PS3, which no one really buys kids games on the PS3, the Xbox 360 version was Kinect required, the Wii version was UDraw required, Wii right there, that is a problem, see, if they had it, you know, kind of, that is a prime audience right there, and you're really limiting it to people that buy your fucking tablet, which no one did...
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, it's just kind of annoying.
[SPEAKER_08]: DungeonBuster in our chatroom at chat.orangesponsorator.com says, Saints Row III and WWE 12 did well, but U-Draw crapped all over the good news for both games.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just, it's really shocking to me, like, that U-Draw's... It wasn't, I don't think it was that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think that that had a big... But, I mean, U-Draw was a huge investment for them, and I mean, nobody bought it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, the one on the Wii that came out, what, a year before, a couple years ago, that one got bought.
[SPEAKER_08]: But didn't they try to put that UDraw tablet on the PS3?
[SPEAKER_08]: It was on PS3 and 360.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was a huge mistake.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, it came out.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was what they were trying to debut, and they were trying to debut some other games.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would argue, literally, no one bought it on the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'd say probably close to no one bought it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, obviously, that's what I really mean.
[SPEAKER_09]: But then also, you know, they had the Penguins of Madagascar game and stuff like that that came out that no one gave a shit about.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is it maybe because if you tie into movies that aren't so successful at the box office, like, wasn't that... What Penguin movie was that?
[SPEAKER_09]: Penguins of Madagascar.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's all the DreamWorks properties is what they had.
[SPEAKER_09]: They had a Spongebob game that no one gave a shit about that came out.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just that stuff doesn't do well anymore.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, kind of it's run its course and no one really cared about Puss in Boots the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, it's just like, eh, whatever, you know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or the Penguins of Madagascar game.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, we're gonna get...
[SPEAKER_09]: We're going to enter in this market too.
[SPEAKER_09]: It seems like they're doing well with that U-Draw.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're going to put ours out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tanked.
[SPEAKER_08]: Does that mean we could expect something really awful to come to Ubisoft soon?
[SPEAKER_08]: Or do you think they had enough to keep them above water?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't think they're going to release anything else for it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Luckily, they still have Assassin's Creed and enough things to kind of... Oh, and they actually do quite a bit.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_09]: A lot less with kid stuff recently, but they do quite a bit.
[SPEAKER_08]: Didn't Rocksmith do a little better than folks thought for a really niche thing?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I know people on Facebook that are playing it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would not have expected to be playing any video games at all.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think it did okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, it hasn't really been a huge hit.
[SPEAKER_09]: It did better than, what was it, Six Strings, Rise of the Six Strings.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, yeah, that one kind of disappeared, didn't it?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, that wasn't very good.
[SPEAKER_05]: That sounds dreadful.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, that's too bad for THQ.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hope it doesn't impact Saints Row IV.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_09]: It won't.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sure they're going to do well.
[SPEAKER_09]: This year, kicking off things, they've got UFC 3, which will do well for them.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's in a couple weeks.
[SPEAKER_09]: they're going to have Darksiders 2 coming I think in May-ish then of course they've got the South Park RPG game coming out later this year there'll be another WWE game, WW13 I'm sure there's going to be some other big franchises that they're going to have um
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't think Saints Row the 4th would be coming out anytime soon.
[SPEAKER_09]: I would hope not.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, I think it's too soon for something like that, but they're going to have DLC for the 3rd coming out, and I think that sold well for them, but I wouldn't worry about THQ.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're going to be fine.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I would say, you know, that it really sucks that Nintendo didn't embrace the whole UDraw tablet, but you kind of see why they didn't because of the direction that they went.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, now, yeah, now with the Wii U, they, it's...
[SPEAKER_09]: or they're going to hold on to it for a little longer and make a Mario Paint game for the Wii U. That's probably more like it.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, well, speaking of the Wii U, Team Ninja has commented on the Wii U, talking about it, saying that it's pretty easy to develop for.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is from an interview with Nintendo Gamer Magazine where some of the folks from Teen Ninja said that they're finding it very similar to develop for Wii U as for Xbox 360 and PlayStation 3, which is no surprise if it's true what we've heard about the hardware in the past.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's very similar to just kind of an overdrived Xbox, basically.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's what Nintendo Wii U is supposed to be.
[SPEAKER_08]: They also said that the Wii U hardware keeps changing.
[SPEAKER_08]: That echoes statements that were made by Yoshinori Ono from Capcom last week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Apparently said something very similar, that the Wii U keeps changing some of the hardware.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're asking these developers from Teen Ninja what they want from the hardware and for feedback.
[SPEAKER_08]: They keep listening, making changes and so forth.
[SPEAKER_08]: The hardware keeps changing.
[SPEAKER_08]: What we don't know is what is changing about the hardware.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now my thought is, I wouldn't take the hardware is changing to mean suddenly this system is not going to have the tablet or any of that stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's here to stay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like that isn't going anywhere, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: I think they're either... They're too well, they've gone all in on that.
[SPEAKER_08]: So after last year's E3, they can't suddenly come out and say, well, we decided to scrap the tablet, ha ha.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: They're just changing what's inside.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because they don't fucking know.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're like, well, we've got this box that represents... Just imagine, if you will, a console that will do amazing things.
[SPEAKER_09]: Imagine it because we don't have one yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just this box that's sitting here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, it's about time to commit because in a couple months they're going to have to show that to the world.
[SPEAKER_08]: If they want to get that thing out this year, it's got to be at E3 and it's got to be good.
[SPEAKER_09]: It better be.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm telling you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Although if Team Ninja is developing for this, that means that you know where the next Dead or Alive game is going to show up.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I think it's Ninja Gaiden.
[SPEAKER_09]: They already said they were going to have a Ninja Gaiden.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, that's right.
[SPEAKER_09]: They did.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was basically a port of Ninja Gaiden 3.
[SPEAKER_08]: And Team Ninja and Nintendo have a little history.
[SPEAKER_08]: Team Ninja did the Metroid Other M game, which, although it didn't sell very well, it wasn't a bad game by any means.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was pretty neat.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: I hope they all fuck it up, I'm just saying.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, I think I'm hopeful that it'll be a good system, but... Just say the HG Mario and HZ Zelda game will be out this Christmas and it'll print money.
[SPEAKER_08]: It will.
[SPEAKER_08]: Keep our fingers crossed.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nintendo just has to put those key franchises on it and that's really what's gonna drive the system.
[SPEAKER_08]: And if you doubt what I'm saying...
[SPEAKER_08]: 3DS.
[SPEAKER_08]: That thing did not start selling until they put the Zelda remake on it and then sold a little bit and then when they put Mario Kart 7 and 3D Land on it, boom!
[SPEAKER_08]: Now it's selling tons.
[SPEAKER_08]: And when they dropped the price.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh yeah, that too.
[SPEAKER_07]: That helped.
[SPEAKER_08]: That did have a little bit to do with it.
[SPEAKER_08]: But well, then the price point is certainly important for the Wii U as well.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, if they get up on stage and say, Wii U is $599 US dollars.
$599.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ridge Racer.
$299.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's got to be $299, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: No higher than $299.
[SPEAKER_08]: It can't be higher than $299.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: You don't even want it to be $2.99.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't even see it being $2.99.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, by the time we get there, I mean, the other consoles could be lower.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to be sitting back and watching what happens because...
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why do they just say the games will only be $40 as opposed to $60?
[SPEAKER_08]: That would go a long way.
[SPEAKER_08]: That would go a very long way.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_08]: Breakman in our chatroom at chat.orangelandreda.com says, I hope they change the name from Wii U to something else that would be easier for me to make penis jokes for it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, there was some rumors last week that they are going to change the name.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know how much that will, you know,
[SPEAKER_08]: RDG Singenar Chatroom says, Anyway, it's probably three GameCubes duct taped together.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, so you were curious on Rocksmith sales.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: 350,000 copies in the US on 360.
[SPEAKER_09]: Basically a total of 610,000 copies.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's pretty... For what's essentially a really niche title, I really consider that that's pretty darn good.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: So...
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, anyhow, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, in other news, there is a proposition to put a 1% tax on violent video games.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know, stupid.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is actually coming from Oklahoma, which, it's Oklahoma.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oklahoma wins.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, it was introduced by State Representative William Forkiller Great name, Forkiller F-O-U-R-K-I-L-L-E-R That any title that's rated teen, mature, and adult only would fall under that spectrum That's the game that Team Ninja is making for the Wii U actually is Forkiller, go figure But you know what else that would include?
[SPEAKER_05]: Dance Central 2 And Final Fantasy XIII 2
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, because those games are rated T for teen because of, um, what, language and all that stuff, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, but he wants to donate- Somebody said hell in 13.2.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was like, oh, no, she didn't.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the, um, well, what about all the crap they said in 7?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, Barret said shit and- Well, anyway- Has anyone ever dropped the F-bomb in a Final Fantasy game?
[SPEAKER_08]: Final Fantasy fuck?
[SPEAKER_05]: Can I finish?
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, half of the revenues would go to donate the Childhood Outdoor Education Revolving Fund, which is basically making kids get outside and play.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the other half is the Bully Prevention Revolving Fund.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's got a good heart behind it, but I think that it's...
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, okay, actually here's a good quote on here.
[SPEAKER_05]: From the senior designer of Mass Effect 3, that's Manvir Hare, I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oklahoma proposes a 1% tax on violent games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can I propose a 1% tax on stupid fucking ideas that are also unconstitutional?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I mean, this is going to be a losing battle.
[SPEAKER_08]: We've already seen this stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: You heard us go off last week on the whole California has to pay the ESA of the Supreme Court thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I do get what you're saying.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it is like, you know, at the core of it, it's nice that he's trying to do something for charity, I guess.
[SPEAKER_08]: But this just speaks clearly.
[SPEAKER_09]: No one's asking him to do anything for charity.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, yeah, it's that.
[SPEAKER_08]: And if you really want to tax violence, put a 1% tax on guns.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, put it on something that's across the board.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have to say this.
[SPEAKER_05]: To say that guns cause violence is the same thing that says pencils cause bad spelling.
[SPEAKER_08]: Then put a 1% tax on pencils.
[SPEAKER_08]: Put the tax on a gun license.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: But the thing is, at least that's kind of constant.
[SPEAKER_08]: But to put a 1% tax on a subset of video games strikes me as very odd.
[SPEAKER_08]: Would you put a 1% tax on R-rated movies?
[SPEAKER_08]: Would you put a 1% tax on... Well, no, because we're afraid of the MPAA.
[SPEAKER_08]: Would you put a tax on 1% books that are not for young adults or children?
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, would you put a 1% tax on the, you know, I don't know, entire fiction section of Barnes & Noble?
[SPEAKER_09]: We're going to put a 1% tax on contraceptives.
[SPEAKER_08]: Would you put a 1% tax on parental advisory labels on CDs?
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, no.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is all  it's ridiculous in practice.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just  and it's somebody who  that just speaks  it's a big surprise, a politician who doesn't get video games, but it just really speaks to somebody.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: he's basically trying to do the same thing that all these other places have done to curtail the sale of these video games by making them more expensive by putting a tax on it and sugarcoating it with the oh but this is going to do all this good if this goes by he's trying to trick the gullible which unfortunately most of the public is sorry
[SPEAKER_09]: and you know those violent video games they pack on the pounds I'm telling you if I'm not like you know killing people in a game I'm just losing weight because um yeah I don't understand the argument that you know putting attacks on teen rated and up games is gonna somehow get kids to be slimmer
[SPEAKER_09]: I think you actually missed what I said about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: He said that the proceeds were going to be in half donated to services that get children to go outside and exercise.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that's the thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's kind of like it's indirectly for the children because I'm tying this nice little charity and all the money is going to go to good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why don't you tax them like 500%?
[SPEAKER_09]: Then they can't afford the games and they'll go out and exercise.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then the charities will get a ton of money.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, I don't understand, why do we need a program to get people to go outside?
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, is it that bad?
[SPEAKER_05]: Why don't parents do their fucking job?
[SPEAKER_05]: End of story.
[SPEAKER_05]: Parents, do your job.
[SPEAKER_05]: Your kids are fat, send them outside.
[SPEAKER_05]: The end.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what I did when I was bored when I was a kid?
[SPEAKER_05]: And I had a Nintendo?
[SPEAKER_05]: I went and rode my bike.
[SPEAKER_05]: Uphill.
[SPEAKER_05]: Twice.
[SPEAKER_05]: In the snow?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: We didn't have snow in Alabama, what are you talking about?
[SPEAKER_05]: In the swamp!
[SPEAKER_05]: Which is worse than the snow.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or even better, I mean, like, stop feeding your kids their sugary foods or whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, get them to go outside.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's a lot of contributing factors for people getting overweight.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's not because you're just playing video games.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's because you're eating like shit and you're sitting around doing nothing.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what, kids?
[SPEAKER_08]: If you want to lose weight, you just need to have more unprotected sex.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sexercise.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura's left the room
[SPEAKER_09]: But we were just talking about... So, let's talk a little bit about our favorite topic, at least it has been the last few weeks.
[SPEAKER_09]: And that is, quote, you know, online passes.
[SPEAKER_09]: and I kind of wonder if they don't understand what the online pass thing means because they're putting it on games that don't have online portions to them.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're not putting it on games that have online portions to them.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're not locking people out.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just don't understand.
[SPEAKER_09]: So first off, SSX, a big extreme sports game coming out from EA.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's going to have an online pass.
[SPEAKER_09]: Not a big surprise because they have a big online portion of it.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's kind of neat about it, though, is that the online pass, if you do not have it, will not lock people out of playing multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_09]: You just won't get any of the in-game credits used to unlock content while playing multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_09]: So that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can at least play with your friends still if you have it used.
[SPEAKER_08]: So...
[SPEAKER_08]: Wait, you mean to say that some companies find the value in not having an online pass?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, come on, this is the same company that just put an online pass on an offline game.
[SPEAKER_09]: True.
[SPEAKER_09]: And to be fair, that wasn't really an online pass, that was just, you know, free DLC that they labeled something completely stupid.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was like, you know, instead of saying, ooh, free gift, it was like...
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, pay money or get raped.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, it's like, you know, not... If you just called it a free gift, it wouldn't have sounded so bad.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why'd you call it get raped?
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, that doesn't make any sense.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why would you do that?
[SPEAKER_09]: So they're doing that for SSX, and so if you don't want to buy the game, or if you rent it, you can still play online.
[SPEAKER_09]: You just won't be able to unlock your little tokens or shit for your downloading or unlocking in-game things.
[SPEAKER_09]: Big deal.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um...
[SPEAKER_09]: However, what's kind of weird though is a co-op shooter, Syndicate, also coming out from EA, is not going to have an online pass at all.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just, eh, whatever reason.
[SPEAKER_09]: They say we want little resistance or barriers to entry as possible.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think a lot of guys say that too I had to come back in the room, didn't I?
[SPEAKER_09]: The co-op is equal billing in this We wanted everyone who owns a copy of the game to have access to the entire product
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, now, that's fair.
[SPEAKER_08]: If they recognize that, like, the core element of their game is the online part, you don't fucking gate it behind a pass.
[SPEAKER_08]: Right?
[SPEAKER_09]: But yet they do for Battlefield 3, for Madden, for, you know, NBA.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, they don't have an NBA game.
[SPEAKER_09]: But when they do have another NBA game, probably this year.
[SPEAKER_08]: NBA Jam might have one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, no, because the Xbox 360 and PS3 are already online only.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, so.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the Wii online.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ha, ha, ha.
[SPEAKER_09]: Need for Speed.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, all this shit had these online passes.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I do like the direction they're going.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I want to fucking have, every time that they have a goddamn online pass, the EA says, yeah, we stand behind this online pass.
[SPEAKER_09]: I want them to fucking quote what they said.
[SPEAKER_09]: We want as little resistance or barriers to entry as possible.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because that's really what you're doing is you're telling people, yeah, we only watch you, the player games, if you have the money to buy it new.
[SPEAKER_09]: If not, we don't really give a fuck.
[SPEAKER_09]: We want you to go away because you cost us too much money to run our servers.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I'll come back.
[SPEAKER_09]: There was something I was going to rant about this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just reminded myself.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, goody.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I think it was something along the lines of this online pass thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll get to that later.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, is there another story coming up later that's going to prompt that?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't think so, but it was something I posted on Twitter, and I had to refresh my memory.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just explode on the rant at a random point in the show.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was something about how used games steal money from developers, I think it was.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh yes, oh yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, look, well moving on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Old games still give money to the folks that own the rights to them these days.
[SPEAKER_08]: And old games will suddenly become new again on the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the old games are coming from the Game Gear.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Apparently, virtual console games for a non-Nintendo platform, of course, in this case Sega, have shown up for 3DS release by the good old ESRB, who has spoiled the releases of Shinobi and Sonic Triple Trouble.
[SPEAKER_08]: So those games apparently have been spotted.
[SPEAKER_08]: To be fair, the ESRB Remember that one of the things that they could do That the publishers could tell them Not to list their stuff on there So it's the fucking publisher's fault Yeah, they might have forgot to check that box in the forum, who knows Now, it's worth noting that at some point TurboGrafx-16 games Were supposed to be available on the 3DS But who knows if that's really going to happen anymore At some point, because there's no more Hudson Well, doesn't Konami Inherently own all their old licenses Or am I wrong?
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura is going to bitch slap me for this, but were there really any that good Game Gear games?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: Gunstar Heroes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Was that really a Game Gear game?
[SPEAKER_05]: I bought it for Dan for $30.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, that's right.
[SPEAKER_08]: I remember that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: There were really good... I think there was Puyo Puyo.
[SPEAKER_05]: There was Sonic Spinball.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Lion King game, of all things, was actually really good on Game Gear.
[SPEAKER_05]: So yeah, there were a lot of really good games.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Disney games on Genesis and all that stuff, like Aladdin and shit, were really good.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was like an interesting phase where Sega and Disney just kind of had this really great harmony going on.
[SPEAKER_05]: And if I do recall correctly, I think there were a number of Master System games that were converted for Game Gear use, so...
[SPEAKER_08]: All I remember are that those things were so fucking huge and just drained your batteries.
[SPEAKER_08]: But now, you know, the 3DS will drain your battery.
[SPEAKER_08]: It'll be about as fast.
[SPEAKER_08]: But at least you can recharge your 3DS without having to go buy AA batteries.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura is going to read us a story and then we're going to get to the release dates.
[SPEAKER_05]: Once upon a time, there was a game called Skyrim, and everyone was like, oh my god, the menu sucks, so people hacked it and put out little ads for it on PC.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, finally, the people at Bethesda were like, I guess people really don't like how we do this and want different stuff for the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, there is a PC creation kit coming out for The Elder Scrolls V Skyrim, and it will be on Steam on Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, uh, it's, uh, you can apparently just download it in the tools tab, so I guess people will be happy for it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm slowly starting to regret not getting Skyrim on the PC.
[SPEAKER_08]: I wish a lot of these cool things would come to the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_08]: I thought some of it was supposed to.
[SPEAKER_08]: I could be wrong, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: But Alan, he's in there playing Skyrim right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: He's hacked the shit out of that game.
[SPEAKER_08]: He's still playing by the rules, mostly.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think he's really cheated a lot.
[SPEAKER_08]: But his interface doesn't even look right to me.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it's really well organized.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just like he's done so many hacks to it.
[SPEAKER_05]: How many of us have WoW that look exactly like it did when we first got it?
[SPEAKER_08]: That's true, that's true.
[SPEAKER_08]: But that is something that Blizzard embraces, and that's part of why it's better than a lot of MMOs, by the way.
[SPEAKER_08]: But anyway, let's travel around the world and look at release dates and talk about games that you'll be able to hack soon in a store near you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, we'll start with the US dates.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's actually some stuff this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Not really a...
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: The Darkness 2 on PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, and PC as well.
[SPEAKER_09]: The Jak and Daxter Collection for PS3 will be coming out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Resident Evil Revelations with an extra I, at least on the packaging.
[SPEAKER_09]: And that's coming out on 3DS only.
[SPEAKER_09]: Kingdoms of Amalur Reckoning on PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, and PC as
[SPEAKER_09]: We also have the Zumba Fitness Rush on Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_09]: That'll be out on Sunday.
[SPEAKER_09]: And, yeah, that's it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, and as I remember, remind you, the 3DS Circle Pad Pro will be out in GameStop.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm irritated.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is there any chance if I wait it out it'll come to another retailer?
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess there's nothing I need it for right now, so I'm just gonna hold my breath.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm trying to see what... That hasn't come out over there yet?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I guess not.
[SPEAKER_08]: Surprised.
[SPEAKER_08]: It came out over here back in October.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think it's a price reduction.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, it's definitely not a price reduction.
[SPEAKER_08]: It might be like a localized version for them.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: So yeah, that's coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, sometimes they get the games a little later than we do, you know?
[SPEAKER_08]: Remember, the PlayStation Vita Vita Vegman's already out in Japan, so they have some new games this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Gravity Days comes out this week, and Sumiyomi, I think I'm saying that right, comes out this week on the Vita.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm trying to see if this is a game... I'm trying to see if this looks familiar to me.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm looking at a little trailer for Sumiyomi here in the studio to see if it's one that I recognized.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like the art style in this game.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a little bit like Okami.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've seen the... Oh, it's an ink game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sumie is a type of drawing with ink.
[SPEAKER_09]: I saw this when they were talking about Vita stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: I actually saw the video for it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't remember what it's being called over here, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: That game is coming out this week in Japan because they already have the Vita over there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Looking at the other handheld real quick, I'm just going to look really quickly at the Wii, see if there's anything worth mentioning.
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: How about the 3DS though?
[SPEAKER_08]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nothing until the 14th.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nude Love Plus comes out on the 14th with plenty of art book limited editions if you want to check that out.
[SPEAKER_09]: I thought for a second there you said Nude Love Plus.
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: That would be a whole different 3DS game right there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, that does it for Japanese releases.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_05]: In the UK, on the 7th, we have Combat Wings, The Great Battles of World War II, Gotham City Imposters, House of the Dead 3, and The Simpsons Arcade for PS3.
[SPEAKER_05]: On the 8th of February, we have more Gotham City crap.
[SPEAKER_05]: On the 9th, we have Cell Emergence.
[SPEAKER_05]: On the 10th, Catherine for Xbox 360 and PS3.
[SPEAKER_05]: That game is messed up.
[SPEAKER_05]: EA Sports Grand Slam Tennis 2, Kingdoms of Amalur Reckoning, Mario and Sonic at the London Olympic Games on 3DS, One Piece Unlimited Crew Special, and The Darkness 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alrighty, just a couple more stories for you guys, then we're going to get to the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_09]: But first... So, there's some talk saying, you know, Iwata is actually interested in doing some, you know, microtransactions with the Wii U. One of the pieces of technology that they may be incorporating for the Wii U is...
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_09]: or Skylanders.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're saying that it can provide a system in which consumers can use e-money.
[SPEAKER_09]: They'll find it much more easily to be able to make payments by entering credit card numbers or by purchasing Nintendo prepaid cards at the store.
[SPEAKER_09]: um you know of course they're you know trying to support DLC but they want to do it in a way that's not you know crazy
[SPEAKER_09]: Also, they're throwing out the idea that maybe Super Mario Land 3D or Mario Kart may get DLC, which I would be happy with that.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think they should do that.
[SPEAKER_09]: What if we could provide add-on content through the network?
[SPEAKER_09]: As I referred to before, for example... Like everyone else does?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, for example...
[SPEAKER_09]: this idea of supplying new stages to Super Mario users who want to play the game more but have completed the game and lost interest in existing stages this will not only give us new profits but then lengthen the life of the product and that it will never appear to be out of fashion and can keep attracting public attention as long as many people play no shit people have been doing this for fucking years now and you just figured this out oh my god
[SPEAKER_09]: That's fantastic.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I can't wait to see what breakthrough ideas will come with the Wii U. Hey, guys, we're going to have this thing called online.
[SPEAKER_08]: People can play without being in the same room.
[SPEAKER_08]: You have to admit, as behind the times as Nintendo is, there is almost that benefit to them being behind the times that you don't have this online pass garbage on any of the Nintendo games.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, you do.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do you?
[SPEAKER_09]: No.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, you do.
[SPEAKER_08]: Which game?
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_09]: You have the U-Pass that's on the... God, really?
[SPEAKER_09]: And the online passes do apply to the Wii games for Madden, for example, has online pass, I believe.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's just a lot of those core games don't end up... Well, then I stand corrected.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Unfortunately, they do have that stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: They are not exempt from it.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just that there's not a lot of big games that come out, so that's why you don't hear a lot of it.
[SPEAKER_09]: But yeah, I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_09]: They do these really amazing things sometimes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like the 3D's kind of cool, and the motion controls and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: At the same time, say, hey, we got this one cool thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, but we forgot to totally update everything else.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just like, oh, shit, you guys want HD graphics?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, we didn't fucking do that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, online?
[SPEAKER_09]: Nah.
[SPEAKER_09]: But hey, you got motion controls.
[SPEAKER_09]: Isn't that what you wanted?
[SPEAKER_09]: Something new?
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey 3D, it's got 3D, that's awesome, DLC, ah fuck, well we just didn't do DLC yet, we're gonna patch it in later, I'm sure, you know, we will eventually, and we'll support it someday, you know, maybe, yeah, we'll put out another system or something that'll have DLC in there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let me rephrase the point I made earlier since Loki owned me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because most of the stuff worth buying on the Wii is from Nintendo themselves and Nintendo's buying the times, we don't have any of this online pass garbage.
[SPEAKER_08]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: At least we can agree on that.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, congrats to Nintendo for getting on the DLC train, I guess.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just hope they don't go overboard with all this.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now we know how to charge people.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, sometimes your money just goes to these very interesting places where you just wish you'd never spent it in the first place.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I think that's what a lot of Mass Effect fans are feeling this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I'm not talking about the game, don't worry.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I am talking about the spinoff book series.
[SPEAKER_08]: A book came out, I guess, I don't know if it was last week or about a month ago, called Mass Effect Deception.
[SPEAKER_08]: And apparently the book has just got tons and tons of errors.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I'm talking like the type that, like if you're a lore nerd, are just like terribly bad errors.
[SPEAKER_08]: For example, oh, actually they have put together a document, I guess, online on Google.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's a pretty neat community idea.
[SPEAKER_08]: That has 80 errors.
[SPEAKER_08]: All together.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm trying to actually pull this up right now and see if...
[SPEAKER_08]: They talk about like the Citadel is the wrong state.
[SPEAKER_08]: One of the characters kills an alien by slicing into the back of its neck and severing the spine, but you can't really do that with this type of alien because they're not biologically set up that way.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it's like, it's almost like, you know how like when Star Trek kind of gets the canon wrong, the fans are up in arms?
[SPEAKER_05]: Like the whole series of Enterprise?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: so like 80 different errors they've all put together and stuff and yeah timeline errors and things like that so apparently it's gotten to the point where Bioware actually came out and said the teams at Del Rey and Bioware would like to extend our sincerest apologies to the Mass Effect fans for any errors and oversights made in the recent novel Mass Effect Deception we are currently working on a number of changes that will appear in future editions of the novel
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know how... So, in other words, it was all a dream, or alternate timeline, that whole book was an alternate universe, surprise!
[SPEAKER_09]: This is what happens when you write books like you write games.
[SPEAKER_09]: Can't fucking patch a book.
[SPEAKER_09]: You cannot patch a book.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can, apparently, you just print it later, but...
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh yeah, that's another thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, the Wii, can't patch anything, so we better get it right the first time.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or we'll have to put out, no, because remember what they had to do for the Zelda save games?
[SPEAKER_08]: They had to put out the Zelda save game patching channel.
[SPEAKER_08]: You have to admit, that's kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: Kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's kind of terrible.
[SPEAKER_08]: Always a hoot and a holler here on the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: The classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura likes to dive into the classic gaming vault every week and pull out a game that she thinks, hey, back in my day, you didn't have patches.
[SPEAKER_08]: You took your games glitchy and you liked it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: And if they were glitchy, they were collector's items.
[SPEAKER_08]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_08]: So here it is, the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is it a glitchy title?
[SPEAKER_05]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it's full of bugs, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Full of viruses.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, what's the classic game of the week?
[SPEAKER_05]: Dr. Mario.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's been a while since I've done a puzzle game, I think.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I had to do Dr. Mario.
[SPEAKER_08]: And stupid me didn't link the YouTube.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fail.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll play the QT music and I'll bring in the Dr. Mario music when I can.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, Dr. Mario... I need a patch.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dr. Mario came out in 1990.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was designed by Gunpei Yokoi, and it was produced by Takahiro Harada.
[SPEAKER_05]: It came out on the Nintendo Entertainment System, and it was super fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: You got to play as Mario, who became a doctor.
[SPEAKER_05]: Plumber to doctor, go fig.
[SPEAKER_05]: And his point is to eradicate really, really deadly viruses.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: and when you stack three of the same color on top of the virus then it destroys the virus and you keep going and oh my god I was good at this game I mean really good at this game I'm not kidding you had a max level of 20 that you could select and then you could just keep going from there and I could go into the I was really good at it and so humble too
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not gonna... A game's kind of hard not to be good at, you know?
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, unless you just have really awful reflexes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, there are all kinds of other versions, different ports and things that have come out, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was re-released on the Game Boy Advance as part of the Classic Nest series.
[SPEAKER_05]: And there were versions of it that was... There's a minigame in WarioWare Inc., Mega Micro Games, and Brain Age 2, more training in minutes a day.
[SPEAKER_05]: But let's see what else we have with this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because you also have... Your playfield is a bottle.
[SPEAKER_05]: And so he's throwing it into a bottle.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you've got as much space as your bottle allows.
[SPEAKER_05]: And honestly, on screen, it's fairly small.
[SPEAKER_05]: Especially, man, on the 13-inch TV that I played on...
[SPEAKER_05]: Go blind playing that thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: So let's hear about some of the people that probably had problems that this game was pushing pills to kids.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I'm sure I've heard that story somewhere before.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know you might not have it in front of you, but I know some fucking old ladies club probably complained.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dr. Mario teaches my kids about drugs.
[SPEAKER_05]: You see how many drugs will people pop?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, it also did have a multiplayer mode where two players could compete against each other to clean their different fields out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Basically, you just had to get rid of your viruses before they got rid of theirs, but it had more capsules fall on the opposing side.
[SPEAKER_05]: My little sister and I would play that hours on end.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course, it was done by Yokoi, who was the guy that gave us the Game Boy and the Game & Watch.
[SPEAKER_05]: and um uh Takehiro Harada who um was the producer was the producer on Metroid so and um a lot of the music actually that ended up um some of the music ended up in Super Smash Brothers Brawl
[SPEAKER_05]: was the guy that did that actually became one of the presidents of Creatures Inc.
[SPEAKER_05]: which owned a third of the copyright regarding Pokemon.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just to show that little correlation.
[SPEAKER_05]: Were you going to say something?
[SPEAKER_08]: Gotta eradicate them all.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dr. Mario in Puzzle League
[SPEAKER_05]: 2003, there was the release of a Nintendo GameCube preview disc that had you could download the NES version of Dr. Mario to your Game Boy Advance console.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: You do that little cable deal that came out.
[SPEAKER_05]: There was an enhanced version that came with Tetris on the Super Nintendo that was Tetris and Dr. Mario that came out on December 30th, 1994.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why not bring it out before then, you know?
[SPEAKER_05]: Christmas, blah.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was also re-released in Japan on March 30th, 1997 and was downloadable for the Satellaview.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was called Dr. Mario BS version.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because the Satellaview is the BS Satellaview.
[SPEAKER_08]: Can I play some music for one of the other versions here?
[SPEAKER_08]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to go to the Mario 64 version here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Kind of...
[SPEAKER_08]: Same song, but a little souped up.
[SPEAKER_05]: But yeah, it was also downloadable for the Nintendo Power Cartridges and Super Famicom and Game Boy.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then on the 21st anniversary of its release in 2011, the original Game Boy version was made available for the 3DS to download.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, basically, parents, this is what you were talking about, they said that there was a parent, parents had issues about the inclusion of medicine, and there was a review by Ace that gave it a 510 out of 1000 points because it said it reeked of plagiarism, and that it was worse than the games it was modeled after.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ace Games Magazine E-Map
[SPEAKER_05]: Amiga format and ST titles oh wow so yeah anyway keep going there were it was really just a good game a lot of people really loved it you know it was very simple graphically but it got it made its point it was fun and simple to play and that's the point of a game it was enough challenging to keep you playing it because I would play this game for hours I can tell you that
[SPEAKER_05]: But yeah, like you said, there were other follow-ups.
[SPEAKER_05]: There was Dr. Mario 64, like we're listening to right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: That other game modes too.
[SPEAKER_05]: And other characters, including Wario.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because at the time, Wario Land 3 was out.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it came out in Japan under the Nintendo Puzzle Collection.
[SPEAKER_08]: But Wario wasn't a doctor.
[SPEAKER_08]: He was just a nurse practitioner.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dr. Mario Online.
[SPEAKER_05]: RX, which I guess for prescription, came out in 2008 on the Wii, so you could play online versus the Nintendo Wi-Fi connection.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I do want to say to Alpha Cananigram in our chat room at chat.orange.com who says, Nintendo, release Dr. Mario 3DS online.
[SPEAKER_08]: Put it on the Nintendo Network.
[SPEAKER_08]: There is the Wii one.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, granted, you might be specifically wanting a handheld, but there is an online version available.
[SPEAKER_05]: and then there was Dr. Mario Express that came out in 2009 for the DSi.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Boo.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dr. Mario is a secret character in Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_05]: Melee and they actually had an attack based on it in Brawl and it had the chill music from the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, just lots of cool stuff and actually that music was arranged by the guy that did music for Magical Drop.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just all kinds of neat little crossovers there, don't you think?
[SPEAKER_08]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's it.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dr. Mario.
[SPEAKER_08]: There it is, your classic game of the week, Dr. Mario.
[SPEAKER_08]: For the NES, really, but available on pretty much every Nintendo system since then, in one way or another, including the Game Boy.
[SPEAKER_08]: I saw one there on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think I owned it on Game Boy, actually.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think I owned it on NES.
[SPEAKER_08]: I owned it on Game Boy.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to play the Satellaview version.
[SPEAKER_05]: The BS one?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: The BS, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: But we've actually got a Satellaview ROM of the Zelda game.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was really good.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I can imagine what the Dr. Mario one looks like.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, that's going to do it for part A of our show tonight, but we're not done yet, guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: We've got plenty more to come.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to talk about some other things when we get back from a quick break here, including some Xbox-related announcements and news.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is Sony possibly in trouble, according to somebody, so we'll talk a little bit about that.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then, of course, your Twitter topics at twitter.com slash OLR and your emails at mailbag at orangelaunchradio.com and...
[SPEAKER_08]: because it is a show where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's many ways to contact us.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Skype line at 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype, Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: We will be taking all of those calls a little later on right after a quick break.
[SPEAKER_08]: So stay tuned, guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll be right back.
[SPEAKER_08]: Welcome back everybody to Orange Lounge Radio live with episode number 444 on this February the 5th of 2012.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, there's this football game going on and Loki was mentioning that he was watching, he's catching up now on the good stuff, the commercials.
[SPEAKER_08]: And you just said, what, the Battleship movie might not be so bad from what you're looking at?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just really want that.
E5!
[SPEAKER_09]: You sunk my battleship!
[SPEAKER_09]: It just looked ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just like it could be Transformers 4 or whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, it's just pretty much... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm down with it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because, I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_09]: Look back at, like, Independence Day.
[SPEAKER_09]: How fucking cheesy was that movie?
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, it was so cheesy.
[SPEAKER_05]: I did see snakes on a plane.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_05]: In the theater at Disneyland.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did they get the motherfucking snakes off the motherfucking plane?
[SPEAKER_05]: It was me, Kristen, and Megzi.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wearing giant plushy snakes wrapped around us in the movie theater.
[SPEAKER_08]: You dressed up to go see Snakes on a Plane.
[SPEAKER_09]: We got the snakes at the Jungle Trader.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, we did something similar.
[SPEAKER_09]: We watched it actually at our work.
[SPEAKER_09]: They had a movie screening in our theater.
[SPEAKER_09]: We had rubber snakes that we were throwing during the movie.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: But yeah, the Avengers trailer is awesome.
That was a cool scene.
[SPEAKER_09]: I love Samuel L. Jackson.
[SPEAKER_09]: I like when the giant snake ate that one dude.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I gotta admit though, I would be all for them making a sequel where it takes place on a space shuttle with Samuel Jackson in it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Snakes on a shuttle.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you know that someone tried to do a knockoff called Snakes on a Train.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh yeah, that's Asylum.
[SPEAKER_09]: Asylum does fucking transmorphers and...
[SPEAKER_08]: I would expect them to do a GoBot scene How can we get in one of these movies?
[SPEAKER_08]: Damn it Don't they have a need for witty radio trio to be eaten alive by snakes or something?
[SPEAKER_09]: They may
[SPEAKER_09]: so many stupid movies and the thing is they do it intentional now I mean I don't know if they do it intentional as far as like they buy the properties for these and then they put them on like sci-fi channel or they purposely make them that bad I don't know if it's hard to tell like if are you doing this on purpose or you do you really just suck that much you know it's just I don't know
[SPEAKER_08]: Before we get into the rapid fire news tonight, DarkSakura, you mentioned you wanted to plug something real quick.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, I do.
[SPEAKER_05]: One of our fantabulous listeners, Ikuma JP, made an app for the iPhone, and I want to share it with everybody.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's called My Secret Garden.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's really beautiful, and it's free, so go get it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rob says he likes free.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't give Rob enough time.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's more than gorgeous moving pictures.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's beautiful.
[SPEAKER_09]: It has nothing to do with the My Secret Garden book series.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, that wasn't a series.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was one book by the same... Well, there was too many fucking books.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sorry, there's too many fucking movies based on that book.
[SPEAKER_05]: There was the same lady that wrote A Little Princess.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: The more you know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, I read them both.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love those books.
[SPEAKER_08]: But the most beautiful part of that sentence was free.
[SPEAKER_08]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that one of our listeners made him.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course, of course.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we demand he gets a top 100 ranking immediately.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's move on to some rapid fire news, Loki.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, let's talk a little bit about movies.
[SPEAKER_09]: We were just talking about movies.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ace Attorney, a movie I'm sure a lot of people might be interested in checking out, is actually going to be localized for worldwide release.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sure that's going to be a very limited release, but hey, you'll eventually get it on DVD and Blu-ray soon.
[SPEAKER_08]: As long as Samuel L. Jackson isn't saying, OBJECTION!
[SPEAKER_09]: He should be the judge.
[SPEAKER_09]: These motherfucking ejections out of my motherfucking courtroom.
[SPEAKER_09]: Objections in the courtroom.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sustain, motherfucker!
[SPEAKER_09]: You can put him really in anything, you know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Samuel Jackson really could just be in anything.
[SPEAKER_05]: Stance is sitting on the toilet at the movie.
[SPEAKER_09]: That'll be the movie we get offered to do.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then they're doing a Humble Bundle for Android, which is kind of unique.
[SPEAKER_09]: Mainly it's been PC.
[SPEAKER_09]: But now you're going to be able to get a few games.
[SPEAKER_09]: The new Humble Bundle for Android offers Android versions of Anomaly, Warzone, Earth, Osmos, and Edge with a bonus copy of World of Goo if you exceed the average payment.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, so that's kinda neat.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's neat that it's coming to mobile phones, so it'll never happen on Apple, but hey, yay for Android.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I guess, um, these games are cross-platform, so you get them on Android and Windows and OSX and Linux.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, it's pretty nice, I guess.
[SPEAKER_09]: Problem is, you know, really with a lot of these bundles, it's like if you bought one of these bundles, you probably have most of the games already in there anyway, so it's...
[SPEAKER_09]: How many fucking copies of VVVV do I need?
[SPEAKER_09]: Or World of Goo?
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, it's just really.
[SPEAKER_09]: Last but not least, Vita Games.
[SPEAKER_09]: They did mention a while back that Vita Games were going to be cheaper if you did buy them online versus a boxed game.
[SPEAKER_09]: However, you may consider still wanting to buy a boxed game because you're only going to be saving 10%.
[SPEAKER_09]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're 10% cheaper on the PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_09]: They will be day and day.
[SPEAKER_09]: So if it's a game that maybe you just want to go to the store to get it,
[SPEAKER_08]: and you can do it I guess but it's only 10% like two bucks on some of these games that's really interesting actually that whole thing because that's kind of how they're gonna try and combat used games is by making it cheaper to buy a new one that you can never sell back
[SPEAKER_09]: It's not much cheaper.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like a few bucks.
[SPEAKER_09]: Seriously, you're going to make back the difference if you sell a new copy of a game used.
[SPEAKER_08]: For some people, that's going to make the difference.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know it.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's 10%, folks.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now, if you want to play devil's advocate, you could say, no, it's not really 10%.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's going to be that plus tax, but I don't know if they charge tax on these purchases.
[SPEAKER_09]: Might depend on the state still.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: So you could potentially save upwards to 20%, but once again, you could probably buy it used and it'll be cheaper.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just don't know if there's a real need for you to jump in and get everything digital.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: And if you're not one to sell back games, then maybe?
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, moving on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Unfortunately, misspellings on box art will not result in any type of price reduction.
[SPEAKER_08]: In fact, it might make the price of these go up.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: But we talked about this a little bit last week, and that's, of course, Resident Evil Revelations or whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: It's missing the I and the T are backwards there, so that's what's wrong.
[SPEAKER_08]: But anyway, yeah, so the box art made it out there, so you might actually, if you've already picked up a copy... Doesn't that stuff get proofed?
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean... No, we were talking about this last week.
[SPEAKER_05]: But anyway... Seeing where that is now, I think the designer had very little to do with that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Capcom has stated that the initial shipment was sent to retailers in North America with a spelling error.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's being repackaged and will have the corrected spelling so you can actually order a new slipcover for it.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is the exact same thing they did when they put out Okami with the IGN watermark on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hilarious!
[SPEAKER_05]: I have all of the new ones and I didn't even know the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's even better because I have a poster that they've made up the box art.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just like, how'd you miss that?
[SPEAKER_08]: Somebody approved that.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, if Dance Dance Revolution with just yourself isn't enough and DDR in the arcades with two people isn't enough, well, I hope you're still in high school because DDR Classroom Edition is going to be a PC game that allows 48 dance mats.
[SPEAKER_08]: All to be linked together so that you can all play DDR.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's actually kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm actually, you know, as a gamer nerd who, you know, has been one ever since like high school where sometimes I was looked at as like the big old nerd for being into games.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is pretty rad that DDR really has kind of gotten into a lot of different PE programs.
[SPEAKER_08]: And so this is out there to try and basically get like an official Dance Dance Revolution classroom game.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, Konami already supports DDR and PE programs, but this is now just a whole, like, 48 people can all play the same game.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not sure how that works.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, I don't know if it's like, if the majority of people get it right, then you get points or whatever, but I think it's just kind of a, you know...
[SPEAKER_09]: Individual scorings, maybe?
[SPEAKER_08]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, if you fail this, you will get an F in P.E.
[SPEAKER_08]: The time has come for you to dance for your life.
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now's the time let's break and swim and dance!
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, I couldn't tell you exactly what songs are going to be in this new DDR game, but I bet if it's for schools, it's probably not going to be any songs by one particular musician who's been showing up in a lot of music games lately.
[SPEAKER_08]: And if recent rumors are to be believed, Ubisoft, who has made Just Dance, The Black-Eyed Peas Experience...
[SPEAKER_08]: The Abba You Can Dance The Michael Jackson Experience Guess what's supposed to come out for the Wii and the Wii U later this year The Lady Gaga Experience You know you're gonna get it Praise Gaga Oh my god Step aside lesser pop divas
[SPEAKER_08]: You too can experience Amazon discounting your album to 99 cents.
[SPEAKER_08]: Your fifth single not doing so well with a video that you directed nobody understands.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_08]: Look, Lady Gaga experience.
[SPEAKER_08]: There'll be plenty of people that'll pick that up.
[SPEAKER_07]: I may or may not be one of them.
[SPEAKER_07]: You will be one of them.
[SPEAKER_08]: I will totally fucking buy this game.
[SPEAKER_08]: I am not even going to try and lie.
[SPEAKER_08]: As long as it has all the songs I really like, I'll get it day one.
[SPEAKER_09]: Lady Gaga, the experience, all will be revealed.
[SPEAKER_09]: You will experience.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is she really a man?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, that was proven when she showed her twat.
[SPEAKER_09]: When did she show her twat?
[SPEAKER_09]: Telephone.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't remember that.
[SPEAKER_05]: She hopped up on the bars and showed her twat to everybody and it was all squared out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: I remember that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, they just had to pixel out her penis.
[SPEAKER_08]: She likes to make fun of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you know, if she had a penis, that thing would be like platinum plated and candy striped.
[SPEAKER_08]: when I went to her concert don't give her ideas for a new video I've seen her live twice in concert and both times she's joked about the rumors that she has a penis like she thinks it's funny so she likes the mystery I guess anyway can we please stop talking about Lady Gaga's penis and move on to more rapid fire news
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, how about Dance Central 2?
[SPEAKER_05]: Download content is going to have some fun stuff in it if you like the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: There is Say Hey, I Love You.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, by the way, this is on February 14th.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Milkshake, because that song's still, you know...
[SPEAKER_05]: It still brings all the boys to the yard All these years later And LMFAO featuring Lauren Bennett and Goon Rock's Party Rock Anthem That might be kind of cool Also on January 31st is Forget You Or as the version I like, Fuck You I just realized, do you even know what song Party Rock Anthem is?
[SPEAKER_05]: No
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, my favorite was when Alan and I were in the car the other day and we were listening to one station and Adele came on and we flipped to another station.
[SPEAKER_08]: They were in the middle of another Adele song.
[SPEAKER_08]: Go to a third station, they're in the middle of the song, the Adele song that the first station started playing.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm like, this bitch is everywhere.
[SPEAKER_08]: God, I cannot.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, if you bought your copy of Dance Central 2 from Best Buy, you will get a code to get Party Rock Anthem early.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whatever the hell song that is.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's a delayed DLC bonus right there.
[SPEAKER_05]: How about Just Dance 3 DLC?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because, you know, that game's relevant too.
[SPEAKER_09]: It is technically the number one selling game right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can get The Power by Snap.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because people still like that song.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you can actually get Bollywood, Kati Kallendal, I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: Love Letters, Y.O.Y.
[SPEAKER_05]: and Sweet Invaders, Skin to Skin.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you can get all those 240 Microsoft points apiece.
[SPEAKER_05]: and then last but not least which I kind of think I need to get this there's going to be the Pink Pearl 3DS available on February 10th and I want it the same way I wanted my pink GBA in a totally ironic way I was hipster before everybody else was no seriously I wanted the pink one because I thought it was hideous and I liked it and I think I would want this one too because it's equally hideous and I really want it
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, so tell me if you've ever heard this song before, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_01]: Are you ready?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, this shit.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm like, she's not the girl in the bubble.
[SPEAKER_09]: She has to have heard it at some point.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like pretty much avoidable.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can't, you know, you can't avoid that song at all.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like avoiding something.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't listen to the radio in my car.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know, but you go to Pinkberry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, that's probably, I think, where I heard it.
Shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know who does it, but I'm winning.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's LMFAO.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's the same band.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is?
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I think that song was hilarious.
[SPEAKER_09]: They also did that song that, you know, sine waves, you know, won a cage match.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, that's who opened for Kesha when my friend went.
[SPEAKER_05]: She said she was going just to see them and not Kesha.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm surprised she didn't catch the herps.
[SPEAKER_05]: The next day when she came into class, she still had glitter in her hair.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was so funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think Kesha's hilarious.
[SPEAKER_08]: I used to really hate Kesha, but she's really grown on me.
[SPEAKER_08]: And a lot of that is probably the influence of some of my friends.
[SPEAKER_08]: But now it's kind of like that whole guilty pleasure type of thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Some days you just feel a little bit trashy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Some days you want a trashy girl.
[SPEAKER_08]: Shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_08]: Can you imagine if Ubisoft put out Kesha the experience?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sexy and I know it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It would just come with a gallon of body glitter.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know, God.
[SPEAKER_05]: That would just be... That would make my soul hurt.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would play it.
[SPEAKER_08]: A jar full of gonorrhea and a used tampon.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would play it, but I would turn back in the gonorrhea.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can keep this part.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like my Kesha.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bathe that Kesha.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyhow, moving on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's get into some other news stories.
[SPEAKER_08]: And, of course, the mailbag is coming up soon, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Twitter topics, Skype line, all that fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: But first, some more stories, Loki.
[SPEAKER_09]: So yeah, you know the new Xbox and everyone's like, oh yeah, it's going to be announced this year.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_09]: Microsoft said nope.
[SPEAKER_09]: Apparently the Xbox 360 cycle is not at all finished.
[SPEAKER_09]: The proof is that we don't see the logic in cutting the prices here.
[SPEAKER_09]: And, you know, E3 is still premature.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's certain is that there'll be nothing new in 2012.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, um, and of course, you know, they put out another statement saying, you know, we're always thinking about the next and, you know, what is next and how we can push the boundaries and blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, yeah, you know, there will be another Xbox, most likely 2014 or holiday 2013.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're waiting to see what Nintendo does.
[SPEAKER_08]: I should have just been there lying because everybody would have believed that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I honestly think... I was going to tell them that for your ringtone.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wiggle, wiggle, wiggle, wiggle, wiggle, wiggle, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I did and it turned it back on.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyways, it's basically... I mean, their new system is going to be graphically... The Wii U is going to be graphically capable of what the 360 is right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I don't really think that they have too much to worry about right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: Especially if that whole tablet thing doesn't end up working out to be this innovative masterpiece.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think that they're fine right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: They can wait next year for the component prices to come way down and still beef up what's inside their box and put out some great games.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's in their box?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's Kesha.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um...
[SPEAKER_08]: Here's the thing, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: What does Microsoft show at E3 this year, then?
[SPEAKER_08]: Is it just going to be a repeat of last year's E3?
[SPEAKER_08]: Halo 4.
[SPEAKER_08]: Which they showed at last E3.
[SPEAKER_09]: They showed a teaser.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then what?
[SPEAKER_08]: The Tomb Raider game probably won't be out until this holiday, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: Tomb Raider's not coming out until holiday.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's Bioshock Infinite still holiday this year.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe Grand Theft Auto V holiday.
[SPEAKER_09]: Another Call of Duty game.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's going to be a bunch of new IPs.
[SPEAKER_08]: How much of Microsoft's keynote is just going to be rehashed of last year's stuff?
[SPEAKER_08]: I think they may still have a lot of stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: We haven't heard a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe they're keeping a lot of it under wraps.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I don't think they need to come out with a brand new system yet.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think they do either, but I'm still waiting for that Killer Connect hardcore game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Didn't we get a glimpse at one that was supposed to be some Greek fighting thing?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, that's the one from Crytek.
[SPEAKER_08]: That could be a big hit or a big miss.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's hard to say.
[SPEAKER_08]: That could be a hot mess when that comes out, so we'll see.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, there's that one.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't remember what it's called, but yeah, it's from Crytek.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's a lot of games coming out this year.
[SPEAKER_09]: And there's a lot of new IPs.
[SPEAKER_09]: I can't remember all of them.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I'm sure there's going to be some stuff that they'll be able to show.
[SPEAKER_09]: And obviously, there's a new...
[SPEAKER_09]: They're gonna show the new Fable game, which I don't give a shit about at all.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm done with that series, and done with Peter Molyneux.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, I think I paid more attention to what he said.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh yeah, there was that whole Fable connect, like, it's not on rails.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not on rails!
[SPEAKER_08]: It's on rails.
[SPEAKER_08]: Read the board, it's not on rails.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, listen, listen, you fucker, I'm not fucking listening to what fucking Peter Molyneux says.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's not on rails, it's fucking on rails, okay?
[SPEAKER_09]: It will be on goddamn rails.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anything he promises you is going to be underwhelming.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just the way it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: He's a snake oil salesman.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's what he is.
[SPEAKER_09]: He's a fucking snake oil salesman.
[SPEAKER_09]: He will promise you the world and it will be fucking Fable all over again.
[SPEAKER_09]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: Whether you're a fan of Fable that much, that might be a good thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe you're just looking for Fable.
[SPEAKER_09]: But it's not going to be this thing that's going to revolutionize Fable.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nothing will revolutionize Fable.
[SPEAKER_08]: Except maybe Kingdom of Amalur or whatever that game is called.
[SPEAKER_08]: Which is basically EA's Fable game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, it's Fable with God of War fighting.
[SPEAKER_09]: Which, that's not a bad combo.
[SPEAKER_07]: That doesn't sound bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not a bad combo.
[SPEAKER_08]: It sounds better than the demo.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyhow, big changes going on at Xbox.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is actually a pretty big change.
[SPEAKER_08]: I always say this guy's name wrong.
[SPEAKER_08]: Steven Toulouse?
[SPEAKER_08]: That sounds right.
[SPEAKER_08]: is one of the big guys at Xbox.
[SPEAKER_08]: He is the director of Xbox Live Policy and Enforcement.
[SPEAKER_08]: He's been working at Microsoft for quite a long time.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think about 17 years he's been working there.
[SPEAKER_08]: He is no longer going to be working there in a couple weeks.
[SPEAKER_08]: He has resigned effective on February 16th.
[SPEAKER_08]: for no particular reason.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's very interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: He's just said, on the 16th, I'm going to head down to Dallas to visit my family.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have no other plans beyond that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm a free agent.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is he a free bitch baby?
[SPEAKER_08]: He's not really saying he's jumped ship to go somewhere else, like some mega company or something like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: or what have you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Microsoft did come out and basically say that yes, he's leaving the company.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you for his service.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wish all the best.
[SPEAKER_08]: We don't have any details to share about a potential successor.
[SPEAKER_08]: We can assure you that the Xbox Live Enforcement Squad will continue their work to help ensure a safer, more secure experience.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, of course, the conclusion that many people have jumped to regarding this little resignation is that, oh, it's because of the hacks.
[SPEAKER_08]: Something's happening with the hacks, and he's stepping out because he knows something ugly is going to go down, and he doesn't want to go down with it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like all the tinfoil hat people come out.
[SPEAKER_08]: And to some extent, I've been one of the harshest critics of Xbox around here and the way they've handled that whole mess.
[SPEAKER_08]: You mean they handled it?
[SPEAKER_08]: well yeah exactly Rhythm Party is like the first time I've turned on my Xbox in a month so you know I'm just but I don't think at the end of the day it really has anything to do with that because his role was more about keeping the Xbox live environment a safe haven if you will or a family friendly environment you know what I mean it's basically a safe place I don't know whatever you want to call it
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just very possible that after... It's like the Thor of the Banhammer.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, let's be real.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know this guy.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know him personally.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't read his blogs.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't follow him on Twitter.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've heard he's very accessible, but I have not chosen to access him.
[SPEAKER_08]: Here's the thing, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you've been working at the same job 17 years, and so he's got to be, what, like almost 40?
[SPEAKER_08]: He's probably going through what some might call a midlife crisis.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I'm not saying it's necessarily a bad thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just tell him to buy a Ferrari and drive.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not saying it's necessarily a bad thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's probably just that moment a lot of people go through where it's like, is this what I want to do forever?
[SPEAKER_08]: And maybe he decided I want to spend more time with family or I want to do something else.
[SPEAKER_08]: And, you know, as a director, he's probably built up a little bit of a nest egg and he's probably okay to do that.
[SPEAKER_08]: so what I'm trying to say is that I really don't think this has anything to do with the Xbox hacks and just this guy wants to go have a life hooray good for him it's great so meanwhile Xbox really does need to do something about the hacking but I don't think this guy has anything to do with that let's move on shall we
[SPEAKER_08]: Some comments from our chat room real quick on this TigerClaw says he was a co-host for Major Nelson's podcast I think I've listened to one episode of Major Nelson's podcast and it was many many years ago so sadly I wouldn't know that but that's interesting to know so I guess a lot of the community knows him through that too Breakman says he's leaving Xbox Live because he's tired of Xbox Live kids calling him the n-word or questioning his sexuality in vulgar ways on a regular basis
[SPEAKER_08]: Kind of like how everybody gets treated on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, you know, if that hasn't been fixed in the past, how long has Xbox Live been around now?
[SPEAKER_08]: About nine years?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think it's going to get fixed anytime soon, I'd say.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not that it makes it right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe the Xbox lube or whatever the next Xbox ends up being called will have extreme anti-homophobe, anti-racist measures in it.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I wouldn't hold my breath.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's get to some emails!
[SPEAKER_08]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_08]: Every week you guys email us at mailbag at orangelawntrader.com We read some of our favorite emails on the air.
[SPEAKER_05]: And we stop the music.
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: I got one that says don't judge my grammar, but grammar was misspelled.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not going to say who it was though because I'm not going to bring attention to that person.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'm grabbing a random email and here's one that actually has fantastic grammar.
[SPEAKER_05]: I found this great website where you can play NES, NES, okay Genesis is misspelled, etc.
[SPEAKER_05]: games on your computer.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm writing this because I know DarkSakura is into old games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Keep up the good work and here's another 10 great years of Orange Lounge Radio and that's sincerely CD Thunder.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just want to point out in 10 more years we'll be as old or if not older than this guy who just resigned from Microsoft and we'll probably have a midlife crisis.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would like to point out that he didn't send the link.
[SPEAKER_08]: Really?
[SPEAKER_08]: He told you?
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, check out this great website.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's called Sincerely Me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Next email.
[SPEAKER_05]: This comes from... Oh, never mind.
[SPEAKER_05]: This was actually personally for us, so I'm saving it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now I really want to see it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's about mics.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm under an NDA, I don't know Am I going to love this as much as D2 or is there too much hype at this point?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think I'm under an NDA.
[SPEAKER_08]: If I am, oops, there's so much information out there.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, there's stuff on YouTube, people playing through it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It can't be under NDA.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not going to say anything that... I'll tell you what, the last time I played through it was in November.
[SPEAKER_08]: I probably gave it a more extensive review on one of the shows back then.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I enjoyed it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I enjoyed the older Diablo games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Some people call it, oh, it's just a click fest.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's nothing but click, click, click, click.
[SPEAKER_08]: but um no I thought it was fun I had a lot of fun like um Shane who has sometimes been known as Mikulatov on the show and I um he was in the beta too and we did some co-op online and we had a lot of fun just kind of playing it together and exploring the dungeons um it's very similar to what you remember in Diablo 2 there's a few quality of life improvements like I seem to remember oh god it's been a few months since I played it now but I seem to remember that like you don't have to carry around a bunch of town portal scrolls because like there's an item in your inventory that lets you just make one
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, just kind of like little things like that that help it, you know, feel.
[SPEAKER_05]: You said quality of life improvements?
[SPEAKER_05]: Does it make you sexy and you know it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, it does, actually.
[SPEAKER_08]: And some of the classes were really fun to play.
[SPEAKER_08]: I really enjoyed Monk, but there was another one I played I didn't like as much.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it was The Witch Doctor.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was The Chip Monk.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, The Witch Doctor I didn't like as much.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I liked The Monk.
[SPEAKER_05]: To continue with the email, any tidbit of info would be appreciated.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Your loyal turtle in Philly, Sirius Turtle.
[SPEAKER_05]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_05]: I heard that Loki secretly works for Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_05]: Boom!
[SPEAKER_09]: I secretly work for Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_09]: Boom.
[SPEAKER_09]: Blocks.
[SPEAKER_09]: I wish.
[SPEAKER_09]: I honestly wish I did because I'd be getting a lot more money.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you thought Reggie knew how to kick ass and take names, Loki would be in there.
[SPEAKER_08]: He'd flip a table the first day.
[SPEAKER_08]: I wish.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, would you flip a table if you worked for Nintendo?
[SPEAKER_08]: Fuck that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'd want to stay unemployed.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, so email, last email.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dear OLR, okay, recently I purchased a copy of The Elder Scrolls IV Oblivion Game of the Year Edition.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now I'm enjoying it for the most part with the exception of one thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Game of the Year Edition has a glitch in which when you're a vampire and you receive a quest to cure yourself.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, granted, I like being a vampire.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was strong, fast, didn't sparkle, but it made my character weak to fire and sunlight turns me into a crispy gritter.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm glad I'm not the only one that uses that term.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_08]: You mean an Elder Scrolls game is glitchy?
[SPEAKER_05]: Now on that quest, you talk to a witch and after running errands for her, she sends you out for ingredients for the potion to cure yourself permanently.
[SPEAKER_05]: But one of the ingredients will not be accepted now they patched this out of the original game.
[SPEAKER_05]: But when they booted out the Knights of the Nine DLC, the glitch re-arose and there's no way around that with Game of the Year.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now on another note, I've been playing a Japanese PSP demo for Final Fantasy Type-O.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to play that!
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm wondering if this will ever come into America and how it ties in with the Fabula Nova Crystallis.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you for reading my email signed Haseo Sumirogawa.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't believe it is part of the Fabula Nova Crystallis.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was supposed to be Akito.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was originally going to be the mobile phone one, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: But they just totally changed it and now it's the PSP one.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is supposed to be the Akito 13.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, but it's not now.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to play it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I really want to play it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's probably going to kind of feel like the same universe as XIII, but it won't be like any of the same characters.
[SPEAKER_08]: It'll be like Versus, because Final Fantasy Versus XIII doesn't look like it has shit in common with Final Fantasy XIII, except I'm assuming it takes place on Cocoon.
[SPEAKER_05]: No characters?
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's all different people?
[SPEAKER_09]: No.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't even think it takes place on Cocoon.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, so I don't know what the hell... I want to play it when you're done.
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't have Versus.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have 13 too.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's what I was talking about.
[SPEAKER_08]: If I get it back in less than a year this time.
[SPEAKER_09]: Honestly, 13 Versus has nothing to do with anything.
[SPEAKER_09]: 13 Versus looks good though.
[SPEAKER_09]: It looks really good.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, we got an email from PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's probably a hack email or a phishing email.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's not a hack email, it's that they're changing the PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_05]: Info at playstation.messages4.com Yeah, that's a... I did get one for the PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh yeah, they're merging PlayStation Network into the Sony Entertainment Network or whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Sony Entertainment Network of You Can't Sue Us.
[SPEAKER_05]: Watch us.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, hey, if they give us no reason for legal action, we're not going to say anything.
[SPEAKER_09]: For the record, I have not updated my system, so therefore I have not accepted the end user license agreement yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: I will still sue you if I feel like it.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I will get my southern lawyer.
[SPEAKER_09]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: Can we miss it?
[SPEAKER_08]: That's it?
[SPEAKER_08]: You're done?
[SPEAKER_08]: No more emails.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_05]: Where's the fork?
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, let's go to the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Every week on this show we like to get angsty.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because we can.
[SPEAKER_05]: F you to...
[SPEAKER_05]: God, you know, I had it in my head and I forgot what it was.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh yeah, the girl outside of Whole Foods today who was trying to get me to sign her petition.
[SPEAKER_05]: I normally don't have a problem with that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm all for political action.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I don't sign those petitions from people that are just standing outside the door because there's been a lot of issue lately with people trying to get your information and using it against you.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I don't really have... I thought she was legit.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I'm not going to make a judgment on her.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hate football!
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't stop me with- I mean, she didn't know that, but I was like, I was like, if I say I'm in a hurry, the correct response will be, oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not trying to start a conversation with me.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm still not gonna sign your shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Look at our website when you have a chance.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I would sign it through the website if I had credentials, you know.
[SPEAKER_05]: But that and how much my feet hurt yesterday, oh my god, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I had a really good time at museums with Becky.
[SPEAKER_05]: Lots of fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: Are they really crowded?
[SPEAKER_05]: We went to the Children's Discovery Museum with Julian in the morning.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't do it on the freebie day.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just get a membership.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's so much easier.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, he had a good time, but it was really crowded.
[SPEAKER_05]: But when we went to the Crocker, we got there right around like, I want to say one something.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it was busy, yeah, but it wasn't prohibitively busy, if you know what I mean.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright, that was it.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what they say, and I'm sure they've stolen this from somebody.
[SPEAKER_09]: If it ain't Baroque, then don't fix it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've heard that before.
[SPEAKER_05]: If it ain't Baroque, it's probably Renaissance.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was from Beauty and the Beast.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it was Lumiere.
[SPEAKER_08]: Lumiere says it.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, Cogsworth says it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Becky even quoted that when we were at the Baroque Art.
[SPEAKER_08]: You just quoted Beauty and the Beast, Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's be real, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: If this program were made up of dancing, you know, housewares, Loki would be the scene clock.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't want to be Mrs. Potts.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or the cupboard.
[SPEAKER_05]: The wardrobe.
[SPEAKER_08]: Clearly, I'm Lumiere.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because you're so French, Rob.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm on fire.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't even know if this is really an FU, but I guess it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm just very sick and tired of the whole argument that used games steal away from developers.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, let me fucking... I mean, come on, developers, you should know how this fucking works.
[SPEAKER_09]: You make a game.
[SPEAKER_09]: The game gets pressed.
[SPEAKER_09]: The publisher sells the game to the retailer.
[SPEAKER_09]: Therefore, there is money being exchanged there.
[SPEAKER_09]: It is up to the retailer to then sell the game so that they're not out the money that they paid for the game and they make a small profit on top of that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Then maybe, as an incentive, you may get some extra money depending on how well the game sells.
[SPEAKER_09]: That is the only money that is getting eaten up by used game sales and it's a very small fraction of that
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, so you can shut the fuck up because you still made your fucking money and used games didn't do shit for you guys.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sorry, it's just a stupid argument and I always hear people going, we're stealing money from the developers if we buy used games.
[SPEAKER_09]: No!
[SPEAKER_09]: It does not fucking steal any money from anybody because those games are already goddamn paid for.
[SPEAKER_09]: If they all sat on shelves, they don't fucking care, they have their money already.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's the whole point.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, well, shit, how am I supposed to follow that?
[SPEAKER_08]: F you to... I want pudding.
[SPEAKER_08]: F you to a lot of the same stuff that was bothering me last week, but I want to say thank you to the person who reached out to me on Twitter to talk about that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I thought that was very nice.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know who you are.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I want to say F you to the fact that oh my god, I went to California Pizza Kitchen last night, and granted there was a rather large party of us, but it took an hour and 15 minutes to get a table when we were quoted 30, and then even then they sat us at two separate tables.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll see you next time.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, Becky orders the salads every time we go.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's why they discriminated against you right there.
[SPEAKER_08]: The salads are really good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, they have a whole page dedicated to salads, and they have really good salads.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, you wouldn't know it, but... Yeah, I wouldn't know it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not California salad kitchen, but it could be.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what's funny?
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: Julian calls his bedroom his pizza kitchen.
[SPEAKER_09]: Listen, we know your type.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fresh Choice is down the street.
[SPEAKER_09]: Get the fuck out of here.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's where I had lunch yesterday.
[SPEAKER_08]: You fags are going to come in here and order salad?
[SPEAKER_08]: That's exactly what happened.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what that makes me think of?
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, Brack.
[SPEAKER_03]: And she orders something called a salad.
[SPEAKER_03]: That to me is love.
[SPEAKER_08]: The salt on the wound was watching all these high school kids coming in there all dressed up like it's fucking prom or something.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is it prom season?
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_09]: Winter ball.
[SPEAKER_08]: Have things come back so much that they're going to graduate next month?
[SPEAKER_09]: Winter ball, I guess, because...
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know, but there was a hell of people all dressed up and like all these kids and their fancy pants dresses because California Pizza Kitchen is the nice part of town where all the rich spoiled kids live What, Arden?
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: You went to the other one?
[SPEAKER_08]: We went to the one where Dave and Buster's is, the Fountains See what I mean?
[SPEAKER_08]: Go to Arden Don't give a shit at Arden Go hang out with the poor people like me at Arden Arden don't give a shit
[SPEAKER_05]: If I'm going to go over there, I'm just going to go to Mikuni, anyway, or Dave & Buster's.
[SPEAKER_08]: We had a party at 9, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's hard to find something everybody likes.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we went to California Salad Kitchen.
[SPEAKER_08]: We went to Dave & Buster's.
[SPEAKER_08]: I suggested Dave & Buster's, but I got shot down.
[SPEAKER_08]: They didn't want to do that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's be real, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: The food at Dave & Buster's is kind of mediocre.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the night before Super Bowl Sunday, we were kind of afraid it was going to be a mess.
[SPEAKER_08]: Of course, we didn't fare much better at California Pizza Kitchen.
[SPEAKER_08]: But anyway, can we please not turn this into a California Pizza Kitchen show and talk about more news, Loki?
[SPEAKER_09]: So, you know, not to be outdone, I guess, in Monkey See, Monkey Do, or whatever, you know, Sony is pulling another move with the Wii U type controllers.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sony has patented their own Wii U-esque device, and it looks like a tablet.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: What more is there to say?
[SPEAKER_09]: Tablet with buttons on it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, it looks like kind of a cross between a Game Boy and an iPod.
[SPEAKER_09]: And that looks really weird.
[SPEAKER_09]: It shows some augmented reality thing where this guy looks like his character through the tablet.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why do they need to do that?
[SPEAKER_08]: Didn't they just say two weeks ago that the PlayStation Vita was capable of everything that they're saying the whole Wii U will do?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: It looks weird.
[SPEAKER_09]: It looks like it's going to support multiple tablets and that it'll almost be some sort of augmented reality thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Basically, it's titled the very generic position-dependent gaming 3D controller and handheld as remote.
[SPEAKER_09]: Device would track its own location as input to video game and would render an
[SPEAKER_09]: Avatar on a mobile device such that it appears to overlay a competing user in the real world.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe it's something that they're going to implement to other tablets?
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe it'll be a cheaper option as opposed to getting a Vita, but then why would you kind of bite the, you know, take away from one to give to the other?
[SPEAKER_08]: It just seems a little weird.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know I do like how the fact that they're a little generic console that they use on there looks like the same console that they have rendered in Grand Theft Auto their like generic Xbox PS3 console it's kind of funny alright well let's move on and talk about speaking of the Vita and all that this is seriously the game that might convince me to get a Vita when the Vita's out which is what like next week or two weeks I think
[SPEAKER_08]: The early release is next week, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, Valentine's Day.
[SPEAKER_08]: Day after Valentine's Day.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're not that far away from the Vita launch over here, and I gotta say, this is the game that makes me... Sorry, I get so distracted because there's this giant Gotham City Imposters ad on the page, and it just makes me think about how this really disturbs Jamie.
[SPEAKER_08]: She really doesn't like what this game is doing, even though she's never played it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just don't like the concept.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It won't be fun to me.
[SPEAKER_08]: I downloaded the beta, but I just haven't run it yet.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, the game on the Vita...
[SPEAKER_08]: Luminous, Electronic Symphony I gotta say, the song list looks damn impressive There is 34 tracks in it, and a lot of it is really good licensed stuff There's stuff from Cascade, 4AM is in here, Bang Bang Bang, Mark Ronson Disco Infiltrator by LCD Sound System, Alan will like that
[SPEAKER_08]: Dissolve by the Chemical Brothers, Embracing the Future by BT, Flying High by Faithless, Good Girl by Benny Benassi, Hey Boy Hey Girl by the Chemical Brothers, an Air Song, Milo, Orbital, System F, 808 State, Gold Frap, Aeroplane, Deep Dish, Apex Twin, Pet Shop Boys.
[SPEAKER_08]: This looks fucking great.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, I'm really excited about this game.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, and a lot of it sounds really awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: So,
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, if you haven't seen the song list for this, you probably want to head over to the Luminous page on Facebook and check this out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because, yeah, I'm definitely, if I pick up a Vita launch day, which is looking very likely because I did my taxes, and I'm looking good.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I might be able to get one of these when they come out.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think my wife would let me.
[SPEAKER_09]: Aw, womp womp.
[SPEAKER_09]: I am considering selling my 3DS to get a Vita.
[SPEAKER_03]: To me.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thinking about it, huh?
[SPEAKER_08]: The only drawback to the whole Luminous thing is that I am still feeling a little bit bitter about the fact that I've bought Luminous like five times now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like what?
[SPEAKER_08]: There was Luminous, Luminous 2, Luminous PC, Luminous Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_08]: I never did get the PlayStation 3 one, but I seriously thought about it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm, I'm not in a huge hurry to get a Vita cause like, you know, the launch games are cool and you know, Konamari might be fun, but it's not a like, there's not anything that I must, must, must, must have on the Vita right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's kind of like, well, these are the ones I would pick, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's, I might want to wait, you know, wait until fourth quarter or something like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: I thought Loki was about to say I'm thinking about selling my wife to get it
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
No.
[SPEAKER_08]: Can't do that.
[SPEAKER_08]: She'd complain about that.
[SPEAKER_08]: She would not like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, just a few more stories for you guys, then we're going to get to the Twitter topics and the Skype line at 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: But first, a few more stories.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_05]: I actually have to stop and correct Bones006.
[SPEAKER_05]: The letters U-R do not spell anything.
[SPEAKER_05]: It spells er.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Y-O-U apostrophe R-E.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dear Lord, stop looking ignorant.
[SPEAKER_08]: When you have U-R, that's two-thirds of an earn, which DarkSakura will have you end up in if you don't change your ways.
[SPEAKER_05]: be nice to the listeners Jamie, be nice to the listeners I am being nice I'm doing them a serious favor that will help them get a job and earn the respect of people around them so fuck your Yankee Blue Jeans there was a part where you did video game news mmm
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh yeah, there was a comment by Kaz Harai who's going to be going in as CEO of Sony and he thinks that Sony's kind of in trouble.
[SPEAKER_05]: He spoke with the Wall Street Journal about their financial report.
[SPEAKER_05]: As you remember, they lost like 1.3 billion pounds because I'm going off a British site so in their last financial quarter and expect to report a loss of 2.9 billion dollars for the full year.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought turning around the PlayStation business was going to be the toughest challenge of my career, but I guess it's not.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's one issue after another.
[SPEAKER_05]: I feel like, holy shit, now what?
[SPEAKER_05]: and saying that his strategy for recovery basically means we're not going to rest on our laurels anymore.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to really push the user experience.
[SPEAKER_05]: He says that they need to buckle down and be realistic but people are coming around to the idea even though not everyone's on board.
[SPEAKER_05]: If they don't catch up, they're going to die.
[SPEAKER_08]: This just strikes me really weird that somebody like that would say, holy shit, now what, in an interview.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, I mean, I'm looking at the source in the Wall Street Journal right here.
[SPEAKER_08]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's just weird.
[SPEAKER_08]: That strikes me as odd.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, we can swear all we want, but we're not CEOs of Sony.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that kid is flipping somebody off.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow, he totally is in this little preview.
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't notice that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Trailer for what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Chronicle?
[SPEAKER_08]: Isn't that that movie you were talking about a few weeks ago?
[SPEAKER_08]: You really wanted to see?
[SPEAKER_08]: They came out in theaters this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did you know that?
[SPEAKER_08]: It was number one at the box office.
[SPEAKER_08]: You don't say.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did you go see it or did you see it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Just that ad makes me think, fuck you, clouds.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, look at the clouds.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're flipping him off too?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it's the cloud's fingers too.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, so back to the story at hand.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's weird that Sony... I mean, I feel like Sony's in a better place now so much more than they were four years ago.
[SPEAKER_08]: They were a hot mess when PlayStation 3 first came out.
[SPEAKER_08]: But now things are getting a little better, but there are still some big falls that they make.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just don't think the move...
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, as nice as the move is, I do think the move feels a lot better than the Wii, as it should.
[SPEAKER_08]: The technology's a little newer.
[SPEAKER_08]: But they never really came out with that must-have game for it, you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_08]: Everything kind of felt like a copycat of the Wii.
[SPEAKER_08]: and I think that's part of where a lot of their losses come from but at the same time I pretty much play games on my PS3 almost exclusively right now unless it's like exclusive on 360 or there's people I know on Xbox 360 that I can play the games with
[SPEAKER_08]: or a deliberate multiplayer game and all my friends are playing it on 360.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it's just interesting that Sony is losing all this money.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I guess, now, is this considering other arms of Sony too?
[SPEAKER_08]: Like not just PSP but maybe like, or excuse me, not just like PlayStation and that stuff but like movies?
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess turn that around too?
[SPEAKER_09]: I think it's mostly non-gaming.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think it's more of their electronics.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because their electronics are fucking expensive.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, just insanely expensive.
[SPEAKER_09]: As a promotion thing, we got a gift card to Sony, and their shit is so fucking expensive.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_09]: For stuff that's just half the price for something better elsewhere, it's just such a markup for the brand.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, maybe when they kind of take the JCPenney approach where they'll cut all their prices by 40%.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, not to say that, I mean, Sony stuff's all right because I have a Sony camera, a Sony camcorder, a Sony sound system, a Sony TV, a Sony PlayStation 3, a Sony PSP.
[SPEAKER_09]: Of course, most of that stuff was given to me for free.
[SPEAKER_09]: But it's not bad.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just really fucking expensive.
[SPEAKER_08]: JV Mon in chat says four years ago Sony stock was worth double than what it is now after 2009 it's been pretty much downhill since well yeah I mean I don't know I guess maybe just from the limited perspective where I think of Sony I think of PlayStation I think four years ago they were a mess and maybe there was excitement about the PlayStation 3 and all that but you know there were some huge missteps there for a couple years then things got back on the right track and then they just you know they had the move happen they had the hack happen
[SPEAKER_09]: and you know it's like they just kind of keep getting kicked down so mmm they get knocked down but they get up again all right anyhow uh let's do another story Loki um so let's talk a little bit about sales from a company that's struggling so hard to overcome used game sales
[SPEAKER_09]: I feel so bad for these guys.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, EA has got it so hard.
[SPEAKER_05]: So hard.
[SPEAKER_09]: FIFA 12 and Battlefield 3 only sold 10 million units.
[SPEAKER_09]: Only 10 million units!
[SPEAKER_09]: How do they manage?
[SPEAKER_09]: Madden, only 5 million units sold since August.
[SPEAKER_09]: Poor struggling company.
[SPEAKER_09]: I feel so bad.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm gonna go buy a new game.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm gonna buy all their games brand new.
[SPEAKER_09]: Tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just gonna go right out and buy all of them.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just because I think they're doing such a swell job.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or not.
[SPEAKER_09]: Star Wars The Old Republic has sold 200 million copies.
[SPEAKER_09]: And they already have... No, no.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sorry, not 200.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Two million.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm like, no way.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: Two million households.
[SPEAKER_09]: And 1.7 million are active each day on average per day.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's not bad.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, for user base, you know, especially when they talk like, you know, EA came out with their origin numbers where they said they have like 7 million user or is like 7 million user accounts or something like that, which I'm sure a lot lesser that, you know, than that percentage is active.
[SPEAKER_09]: But 1.7 out of 2 million is not bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: To be fair.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow has what?
[SPEAKER_08]: 10 million active subscribers right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: And at their peak, they had about 12 million.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know how many copies of the game they've sold.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's global.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it is global.
[SPEAKER_08]: 15 or 20 million, probably at some point.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I mean, everybody can't be on that game every day.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, some people do have other things they gotta do.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I am one of those people in the gap where I bought the game and I canceled after the first month.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just didn't really want to keep playing.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just think the game needs some tweaks and needs some improvements.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Some things happen in WoW and I'm playing WoW a lot more.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then, of course, EA's had the benefit of some DLC sales.
[SPEAKER_09]: And they've done well with certain types of DLC.
[SPEAKER_09]: In fact, in just three months...
[SPEAKER_09]: FIFA, FIFA 12's ultimate team, DLC, has generated $39 million in microtransactions.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's 69% more than it generated in the same period last year.
[SPEAKER_09]: Gee, I wonder why.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sorry, but when I heard EA gloating that statistic, I was like, that's insulting.
[SPEAKER_08]: That is insulting because you know where that money's coming from.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, like, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I kind of feel like in order to justify it, EA needed to say, oh, this is subtracting all the, you know, we didn't count the money that, you know, we had to give back because, you know, it was stolen or whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, it's just...
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was a really sore spot.
[SPEAKER_08]: I realize their need to gloat to appease the shareholders and all that stuff, but again, fucking stop denying that there's a problem.
[SPEAKER_09]: Stop it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is EA giving back that money or is Microsoft giving back that money?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who's taking the hit on that?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's all digital.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would imagine Microsoft takes back the money from EA.
[SPEAKER_08]: I imagine they have to.
[SPEAKER_09]: and then of course they're saying according to the Chief Financial Officer Eric Brown to put some rough numbers on this if we compare the total digital revenue from FIFA 11 Ultimate Team to what we expect from FIFA 12 Ultimate Team this fiscal year we're looking to see a 25% increase franchise to franchise
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I wonder where the 25% is coming from.
[SPEAKER_09]: Their overall packaged goods units sold is not increasing by 25%.
[SPEAKER_09]: and so we're expanding by a decent margin the microtransaction revenue per user of FIFA and then it's funny because you know like the people covering this it's like yeah we continue to receive complaints nearly every day of non-FIFA players having their accounts hacked to purchase Ultimate Team DLC
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh yeah, I still hear about it on Twitter and I hear about it, you know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hacked on Xbox, you know, they're still writing down a bunch of... Oh yeah, I forgot about that website.
[SPEAKER_09]: I check it all the time because I'm on their Twitter feed.
[SPEAKER_09]: I check it and they've got 30 stories on there right now and a lot more that get posted.
[SPEAKER_09]: She's kind of running behind on posting all that because she's getting a lot of emails.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_09]: And there's some that I saw that were so ridiculous that like,
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh yeah, you know, we were going to give you back your money, but we're not going to because you didn't put your full name on your account.
[SPEAKER_09]: It'd be like if I didn't put Matthew, I put Matt on my account.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's bull because my legal name I don't have on my Xbox and I still got it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, but see, they pulled that bullshit.
[SPEAKER_08]: Stupid.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, I guess I should be thankful that I didn't have quite the nightmare problem a lot of people are having, although it did take a month.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's the average time, 25 days is what I've been hearing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway...
[SPEAKER_08]: One more ridiculous story for you guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: Remember last week we were talking about the whole Zynga, the rip-off artist where they were making their own Dream Heights was a complete knock-off of Tiny Tower?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, Zynga finally came out and made a statement on the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it went along these lines.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mark Pincus, who's the head of Zynga, quote, you should be careful not to throw stones when you live in glass houses.
[SPEAKER_08]: When you pull the lens back, you saw that their tower game looks similar to five other tower games going all the way back to Sim Tower in the early 1990s.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bullshit.
[SPEAKER_08]: I knew they were going to make that comparison.
[SPEAKER_08]: The comparison of Tiny Tower to SimTower is a lazy, ignorant comparison that tells me you have never played SimTower in your life.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because SimTower was way... I mean, in a way, SimTower is a more complex...
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: But there is not nearly the level of micromanaging that there is in SimTower.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what those games have in common?
[SPEAKER_08]: They're both about skyscrapers.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_08]: And they have tower in the name.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, you don't really manage the people in SimTower.
[SPEAKER_08]: You manage your tower.
[SPEAKER_08]: You manage the escalators, the elevators, what type of businesses you're putting in.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just...
[SPEAKER_08]: Google didn't create the first search engine.
[SPEAKER_08]: Apple didn't create the first MP3 player or tablet.
[SPEAKER_08]: Facebook didn't create the first social network.
[SPEAKER_08]: But these companies have evolved products and categories in revolutionary ways.
[SPEAKER_08]: They are all internet treasures because they all have specific and broad missions to change the world.
[SPEAKER_08]: If that wasn't blowing smoke up their employees' ass, I don't know what was.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because seriously, how is that the same?
[SPEAKER_08]: How is that the same?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not.
[SPEAKER_08]: Google didn't create the first search engine.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's true, but they created the best search engine.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, so Tiny Tower didn't create the first tower game, but they created a really good one for iOS systems.
[SPEAKER_08]: And you fucking jacked it all and made new art.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Google didn't copy the code for Yahoo and change the name to Google on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Google actually has, it's like their whole search process is done by all kinds of different calculations too.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, it's really complex.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then they've taken Google and made a full spectrum product out of it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: Circle Space Circle Breakman in our chatroom says Zynga is currently making a podcast called Red Lounge Radio It will be on the More Than All Games Network He actually fooled somebody in chat Really?
[SPEAKER_08]: Frisbee says, Dear everyone who plays Zynga games, please stop being a person that plays Zynga games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Love humans everywhere.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jvmon brings out the harsh reality.
[SPEAKER_08]: Chat.orange.com saying, Zynga's stock doubled after the Facebook IPO this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, when you see how really dependent they were on each other, as if you didn't already know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, Facebook in their filing basically had to say a lot more about the internal workings of their company.
[SPEAKER_08]: And one of those things is that they kind of fucking rely on Zynga.
[SPEAKER_08]: for people to return visit to Facebook, just like Zynga fucking relies on Facebook.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because didn't Zynga try to make their own portal?
[SPEAKER_08]: I remember there was a time where Zynga was like, well, we don't really... Remember when Google Plus was going to murder everything?
[SPEAKER_08]: And Zynga was like, well, we don't really need Facebook.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to get everybody to come to our Zynga game, Zynga book, or whatever they were going to do.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I can see them doing that shit.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll make our own social network.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're just gonna copy-paste Facebook, and we're gonna call it Portrait...
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, one final note on this whole story.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nimblebit, who made Tiny Tower, did not let this all go by unscathed.
[SPEAKER_08]: The co-founder, Ian Marsh, talked to Touch Arcade and said, quote, It was a smart idea for Mark Pincus and Zynga to try and lump all games with the name Tower together as an actual genre whose games borrow from each other.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sharing a name or a setting does not a genre make.
[SPEAKER_05]: Agreed.
[SPEAKER_05]: For example, 13 Ghosts may be about a haunted house, but it's not the same kind of movie as High Spirits, for example.
[SPEAKER_09]: Jamie, is that like saying the movie Independence Day isn't really about the 4th of July?
[SPEAKER_08]: 1-877-GAME-OLR Our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio The Skype line is open now Give us a call if you want to talk about anything we've talked about tonight Or maybe there's something we missed that you wanted to bring up Or, hell, I don't know Just call us if you want to say hello We do have a reduced amount of live listeners tonight Because of, you know, football games and so forth But I do see there are some of you listening There in our chat room The few, the loyal
[SPEAKER_08]: at chat.orangelounge.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: So go ahead and call us.
[SPEAKER_08]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Meanwhile, we're going to do some tweets.
[SPEAKER_08]: And what?
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you have something, Loki, you want to add?
[SPEAKER_08]: Just real quick.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just thought this was funny.
[SPEAKER_09]: Apparently, there's a PlayStation Network update that just happened that has blocked users from accessing their paid content in the PAL territories.
[SPEAKER_09]: What?
[SPEAKER_09]: Apparently, it's those who have done the update are getting an error labeled as 800-231-02, which helpfully informs them that no content was found when the user tries to download or re-download PlayStation Network content they've already purchased.
[SPEAKER_08]: Going to our Twitter, twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not a lot of activities on Twitter either, although there were some nice tweets.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll read some of these nice tweets that are there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Breakman says, I might show up later for OLR.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll be pretty drunk though, so good luck to them.
[SPEAKER_08]: And CurlyKTK on Twitter says, putting the Super Bowl on mute to listen to OLR.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, we do have some calls coming in, so let's go to the phones.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_00]: Hey, it's the guy who's normally CD Thunder in chat, but tonight I'm God of Thunder.
[SPEAKER_00]: How are you all doing?
[SPEAKER_08]: Good.
[SPEAKER_08]: How are you, God of Thunder?
[SPEAKER_00]: Not too bad.
[SPEAKER_00]: I've got a couple quick things I'd like to talk about.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, what do you want to talk about?
[SPEAKER_00]: First off, quickly, I'd like to talk about Darkness 2.
[SPEAKER_08]: Darkness 2.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is this the one that's coming out, or is this the one that was out?
[SPEAKER_07]: This is the one that's coming out on Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, what do you want to talk about Darkness 2?
[SPEAKER_00]: well from what I've seen in the demo this game looks completely over the top and gory and sick and it just looks really awesome I wish I could actually play it but that's a man who thinks like this the game looks over the top and gory and disgusting and I love it that's like how I felt after I played the Bayonetta demo oh so are you going to pre-order your copy of Darkness 2?
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, as I said before, I don't actually have the system to play it on, but if I did, I would.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, you know what you have to do?
[SPEAKER_08]: You're going to have to steal one.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_00]: Don't steal.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, maybe, do you have a friend who might buy it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Sometimes we have a rich friend who has all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Growing up, I didn't get a Super Nintendo when they first came out, but my rich friend did, so I'd go over to his house.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, I don't know if anybody that I know would get it or not.
[SPEAKER_00]: I just really don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ah, all right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, that's all right.
[SPEAKER_00]: But the other thing I'd like to talk about quickly is I was talking to a friend of mine today and apparently can actually get a classic Nintendo Entertainment System controller USB and plug it into your USB port in a computer and use that to play Nintendo Entertainment System games on the website I linked to the chat room a few minutes earlier.
[SPEAKER_08]: What was the website?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because you sent us the email.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're the same guy who sent us the email.
[SPEAKER_08]: We didn't get the website.
[SPEAKER_08]: What is it?
[SPEAKER_00]: It's retrouprising.com
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, is this going to install porn bots on my computer?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because you know how some of these emulation sites are just, they carry porn bots.
[SPEAKER_08]: And, you know, one minute I'm playing Super Mario Brothers and the next minute, Vagina!
[SPEAKER_00]: No, I've tested out some of this stuff.
[SPEAKER_00]: A lot of it works.
[SPEAKER_08]: Extensively?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just checking.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, what retro games have you rediscovered through the websites?
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, they have stuff like Ice Climber, Donkey Kong, stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_00]: But some of the Super Nintendo games, you actually have to have an emulator, I believe.
[SPEAKER_00]: Which, unfortunately, I do not have.
[SPEAKER_08]: But you have the internet one, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Through the website?
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, I'm able to do the Sega Genesis and the Nintendo Entertainment System games, but for some reason it says it has a bar that shows the emulator is loading, then they get a black screen.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe update Java or try a different browser?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's what I would do.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or it's installing Vagina all over your computer.
[SPEAKER_08]: That could be what's happening.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm just saying, you've got to be very careful about some of these websites.
[SPEAKER_05]: You've got an infestation of Vagina.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_00]: But yeah, I'll probably get the NES controller and use that to play some of those NES games, which are pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Are you going to get one of those NES controllers that's like just a USB?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Gotcha.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, very cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, well, any other thoughts before we let you go?
[SPEAKER_00]: Hmm, well, I hope you guys continue doing what you're doing for quite a while.
[SPEAKER_00]: You guys keep all of us entertaining, me included, and just history of good health and so forth and so on, et cetera, et cetera.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, we appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's kind comments like that that keep us going because, you know, we don't make any money off this show.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's why I have to have rich friends.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, have a good one.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, you too.
[SPEAKER_00]: Later.
[SPEAKER_00]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_08]: Meanwhile, more Twitter topics.
[SPEAKER_08]: TigerClaw, always sending us a few stories that we may have overlooked.
[SPEAKER_08]: TigerClaw on Twitter tweets us this.
[SPEAKER_08]: Apple removes several iOS copycat games from one offending developer.
[SPEAKER_08]: So finally...
[SPEAKER_08]: This is funny that all the stuff we were talking about last week about the whole copycat crap is starting to kind of come to light and Apple's taking action against some of it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Again, I'm reading this story for the first time because TigerClock sent it to us.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's from Gamasutra.
[SPEAKER_08]: It says, Apple struck a blow against video game clones today by removing several offending apps from one rather prolific independent developer.
[SPEAKER_08]: The games were Plant vs. Zombie.
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_08]: as in the one plant against one zombie, Angry Ninja Birds, and Temple Jump, which is a knockoff of a game called Temple Run, which is funny because Temple Jump actually was having some success on the App Store, and yeah, we actually got all the way to the top of the paid app chart.
[SPEAKER_08]: The independent developer of the game is Anton Sinekov, and according to a Twitter post from another iOS developer,
[SPEAKER_08]: This developer had 68 iOS apps available this morning and now only 9 remain.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: One of the developers who was copied in this case, Imanji, says we were really happy with how quickly Apple responded to the situation and removed Temple Jump.
[SPEAKER_08]: The app was clearly a scam that traded entirely on the popularity of Temple Run and was packaged to confuse users.
[SPEAKER_08]: Booyah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mulkart's gone now, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, my question is, when are they going to start taking down the Zynga games?
[SPEAKER_08]: Probably never.
[SPEAKER_08]: But anyway, we're getting another call, so let's go to the phones.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_02]: Tesla.
[SPEAKER_02]: Log in and play.
[SPEAKER_08]: Are you calling to harass me to get me to come play WoW when I'm trying to do a show on the internets?
[SPEAKER_08]: Who told you how to find my show?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't even have to ask.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let me ask you some questions.
[SPEAKER_08]: First off, introduce yourself to the listeners.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who am I speaking with?
[SPEAKER_02]: For all four of you out there who are listening, this is Melodule.
[SPEAKER_02]: I play with your gracious host on a game called World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dude, I need a port I need all those things and a port
[SPEAKER_08]: He needs a port, so I have to sign in.
[SPEAKER_04]: Welcome to my life.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know, because this is the funny thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura plays an arcane mage on Alliance side, and now I have this arcane mage on Horde.
[SPEAKER_05]: Port, please.
[SPEAKER_05]: 5G.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I'll do that since that's like, what, 500% inflation?
[SPEAKER_08]: Now I've learned after your story earlier this evening, I'll never get paid for it.
[SPEAKER_08]: People will just swindle me like you did that poor death knight.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, you make them pay you, and then you open the portal.
[SPEAKER_08]: I see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Exactly Well look, Meloduel, do you play any other video games besides WoW?
[SPEAKER_02]: I, I, oh wait, I gotta turn myself down here because I didn't hear myself talking Yeah, it's always a little awkward, especially when there's a huge delay Right, even though I do sound pretty good on the radio Maybe I should have my own radio show Me too, me too, that's why I've been doing this so long is I sound great on the radio I'm just like listening to himself talk I do, I do
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, hey, at the risk of completely losing all of my sex life by admitting these things, I will admit to playing a little Final Fantasy here and there.
[SPEAKER_02]: What else do I play?
[SPEAKER_02]: I was a huge, huge EverQuest.
[SPEAKER_02]: R.I.P.
[SPEAKER_02]: EverQuest, R.I.P.
[SPEAKER_08]: There actually was a Final Fuck X in Japan.
[SPEAKER_06]: Perfect.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have this.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's basically just bad cosplay boinging.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it's basically just chicks dressed up as the characters in Final Fantasy X and they get fucked.
[SPEAKER_08]: But this weird thing about Japanese porn is that they have to blur the penetration.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then the guys aren't dressed up.
[SPEAKER_08]: The guys are just like, hey, I'm here to fuck Yuna.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, see, you've got to be careful because if you don't blur it, you could have an infestation of a vagina.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just like the last caller.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you're on a bad website, you just, you know, knock, knock.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who's there?
[SPEAKER_05]: Too much vagina is never a good thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: You want it in moderation.
[SPEAKER_08]: Never.
[SPEAKER_02]: Never.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, totally.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's that's those are the games that I played for a while.
[SPEAKER_02]: I loved Tactics.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was my big thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Final Fantasy Tactics was a great game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Final Fantasy Tactics was awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: They have the versions on what systems?
[SPEAKER_08]: Game Boy Advance had one and then they ported it.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's another one on... It escapes me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Didn't they make another port?
[SPEAKER_08]: It was a PSP.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, there was a PSP.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, that was the only one.
[SPEAKER_02]: I loved...
[SPEAKER_02]: Final Fantasy 2, the US version where it was like Final Fantasy 3 or something in Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: They couldn't get it right.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: I will stop harassing you and let you get to your radio show.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: I appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Totally cut it short because I need a port.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, you might have to buy one unless you want to wait until about 11 o'clock my time when I'll finally sign in.
[SPEAKER_08]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I'm really sorry that now you're not going to get laid for like six weeks because you admitted things on air.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll talk to you later.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_08]: 1-877-GAME-OLR Use the name on Skype as Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's very amusing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't let it fool you.
[SPEAKER_08]: He's a total asshole.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, I've actually been... I like everybody in that guild so far.
[SPEAKER_05]: They've been pretty nice people.
[SPEAKER_05]: Except for that Shane guy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, he's an ass.
But the first...
[SPEAKER_08]: The first, like I joined that guild because I knew that they were doing some raiding and that they were just starting.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I was like, all right, well, you know, because nothing's happening on Alliance.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to try this to work out my horde.
[SPEAKER_08]: The first night I went on the raid with the group, I was like, this might be a bit of a hot mess.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, you know, the next week, actually, we raided again last and it was really good.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I think like, you know, they made some tweaks to the group and it really worked.
[SPEAKER_08]: And we cleared like five bosses in one night.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it's a good time.
[SPEAKER_08]: On Firelands?
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: I want that on my mage because I have the tier 12 bonus.
[SPEAKER_08]: But anyway, sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: This discussion is getting a little too Horde House, which by the way is the other Warcraft show I do sometimes.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to be on soon.
[SPEAKER_08]: www.hordehouse.com I'm going to be honest.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's have some real talk for a minute.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know when there's going to be another episode of Horde House.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because like, Extifer is now like busy on the weekends all the time.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I don't...
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know if I should say this, but he's seeing... He's got an infestation of vaginas.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, he has an infestation of a vagina all week.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, he's seeing a boy, and I met the boy the other night, and he's really cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I don't want to, you know... So, you know, I don't know what's going to happen.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it's going to be really hard for us to kind of like coordinate our schedules and so forth.
[SPEAKER_08]: And plus, he's not playing WoW.
[SPEAKER_08]: So...
[SPEAKER_08]: So we have to get guests that can fill in the gaps and so forth.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll be more than happy to fill in if you want to record soon.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll work something out, but it's just don't expect Horde House every week, sadly, until we get some of this stuff worked out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Especially like a common date and time and all that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tiger Claw in chat says, I bet Rob is strict and mean in the guild.
[SPEAKER_08]: When someone underperforms, he'll yell at them like a drill sergeant.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't yell.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: What are you doing going to that side?
[SPEAKER_04]: We said this one.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, that's not Rob.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I don't really do that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like to think I'm fair and I'm nice and I'm patient.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm very fucking patient.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I get to these moments where I fucking snap.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is what Rob sounds like.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to do the, what was the boss in Blackrock?
[SPEAKER_03]: Nefarian?
[SPEAKER_03]: Nefarian.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is Rob on Nefarian.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, get to the platform.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, don't forget to interrupt.
[SPEAKER_05]: You interrupt, you interrupt, you interrupt.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, are you healing?
[SPEAKER_05]: What happened?
[SPEAKER_05]: What happened to your mana?
[SPEAKER_05]: Are you healing?
[SPEAKER_05]: What was that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Why did we wipe?
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, I think we wiped because this, this, this, and this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, let's try it again.
[SPEAKER_05]: Get to the platform!
[SPEAKER_05]: That's wrong.
[SPEAKER_08]: A little bit, a little bit.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Another story here from the Twitter.
[SPEAKER_08]: Twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tigerclaw sends us this link.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nintendo Zone to feature full episodes of Pokemon.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_08]: 3DS owners get free Wi-Fi access at 29,000 Nintendo Zone locations.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, that's that new channel on my 3DS.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can't figure out what it's used for.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nintendo Zone will offer much more content for 3DS owners.
[SPEAKER_08]: There will be a dedicated Pokemon section that will feature full length episodes of the Pokemon TV series.
[SPEAKER_08]: And yeah, McDonald's or Starbucks are both Nintendo Zone partners.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's actually kind of cool, especially if I can get like old school Pokemon episodes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like remember when I had all those Pokemon DVDs?
[SPEAKER_08]: I still do have some of them up there.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what I have, Rob?
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: Japanese Digimon DVDs.
[SPEAKER_05]: For the record, OLR has a one in three occurrence of vagina.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ah.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, our Skype line, unfortunately, isn't ringing anymore.
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess... They've come down with the vagina.
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess people just wanted to call and yell at me or talk about old games.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that's all right.
[SPEAKER_08]: They've come down with the cases.
[SPEAKER_08]: Our usual callers are at their Super Bowl parties.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: I understand.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, Loki, join the chat room.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's the artist behind Every Little Step, Bobby Blackpool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Speaking of the stupor bowl.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry, it's super bowels.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to wrap it up.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're getting out of here.
[SPEAKER_08]: But before we get out of here for the night, last minute stories.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, do you have anything you want to share for last minute stories?
[SPEAKER_09]: Just one small thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: I noticed that Joystick had posted a little thing about this game.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a free indie game.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's a really oddly named game called The Cat That Got Milk.
[SPEAKER_09]: The Cat That Got The Milk.
[SPEAKER_09]: Not necessarily what it sounds like, but it's a free game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Go check it out.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's pretty short, only 10-15 minutes, but it's thecatthatgothemilk.com and it looks pretty awesome based on the trailer.
[SPEAKER_08]: My final thought is Jigglypuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's going to do it, guys, for another episode of Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you guys so much for downloading and listening to our show, even if it was just to yell at me that you needed a port somewhere.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to do this all again next week.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what we ask.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you've enjoyed what you hear here at Orange Launch Radio, remember we don't have a big magazine backing us with millions of dollars.
[SPEAKER_08]: We don't have all these ads and stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: you know all we ask tell a friend about the show help spread the word of Orange Lounge Radio and we'll come back to do it all again next week so next week I'm hoping to talk a little more in depth about Soul Calibur 5 after I get some more hands on time with it I don't know what my co-hosts will be playing hands on maybe get some time in with Evita if I know anyone that gets one early we'll see I'll have to go find my rich friends but until then that's going to do it myself DarkSakura and Loki saying goodnight
[SPEAKER_10]: See you next week!