tonight February 12 2012 Blizzard files suit against Valve Mass Effect gets iOS
tie-ins galore and could the next Xbox also have a tablet controller?
Hello everybody out there on the internet and welcome back to another week of the
show where every gamer has a voice orange lounge radio we are live with the
445th episode of our show for this February the 12th of 2012 that's 2 12 12
alrighty my name is Rob Roberts and I'll be joining you over the next few hours
with my co-hosts first off the one the only dark Sakura Jamie Summers derp
herp derp herp it's gonna be like this tonight huh how are you doing I'm
actually a little sore you're a little sore in the hand oh in the handle region
well you've had the rain and I spent the last three days typing a renaming files
for the American River review we got we did our art submissions and I submitted
five pieces which this is like you know you're you're you are one of the stars
of NBC's community in a sense you're going to community college and you're on
yearbook right or what this I'll put it this way this makes a yearbook look like
a fanzine in comparison I was in your book in high school but I'm doing have
your books in high school yes oh by the way over there tech master Loki how are
you Loki they have your books in high school yes they did or not high school
out of college sure they could they did because my parents met at a Modesto
junior college I'll say it and they there was a yearbook yeah of course they
have your books in high school I I I was in yearbook at high school because it's
okay wait we got to go back to our Sakura story we derailed the magazine
basically it showcases all of the art the culinary the fashion that gets put
out through American River College and we win lots of big national awards we
beat out four year schools we beat out dedicated art schools and we beat
Harvard one year and you won the humility award apparently well now I'm
just really proud we put a lot of hard work on it and it's something to be
proud of fair enough but this is my last year being able to not for art selection
but it's my last year that I'm gonna be working on the design team so and no
time for games I've played some games someday though someday though you could
totally do designing for instruction manuals or you know I was at best I've
been applying for those types of jobs well I know I don't know how much I
should say it say on air but there's that company just down the road that
makes those strategy guides and I was just at Best Buy the other day and I was
really admiring there was a collector's strategy guide for Final Fantasy 13 to
I'm not usually the type to get strategy guides because you know you can kind of
get it all on game facts but I gotta say if you're a really big fan of a game
there's just some beautiful art and design in a lot of those books like
they're just they're they're good coffee table books for nerds I mean in this one
I was looking at with the collector's edition had like that that big thick
kind of pillowy cover almost to it I mean it was not your stand lost books I
guess I don't know what the technical name is for it but it was like you know
it was like the type that if you threw it on the ground it wouldn't leave any
marks because it's like push so they those are done with actually I think
foam and embossing mm-hmm so yeah I mean the thing is maybe I should save this
for my F use but I'll go ahead and say it right now the problem with a lot of
places that hire designers is they want you to have a four-year degree and it
doesn't matter really how much experience real-life experience you have
and just have an associates hmm it's stupid I've got tons of experience and
they knew in a four-year degree man I'm like well tell them to reduce the
tuition please do you know that I used to do design work before I worked at my
current company which I've been at for ten years this is a long time ago when I
was 21 22 I work excuse me I worked for a truck drivers magazine and I was just
kind of the dude in the office like we all worked at the publishers office it
was it was a great staff was a very small office seven people and I was more
like I guess you could say kind of an administrative assistant to the
publisher sort of but I really did a lot of just different stuff I helped with
subscriptions and one role I ended up taking on when one of the gals left I
started designing trade ads for the magazine so I mean that's something I
didn't I just fell into it it was weird and I'm not like I had yearbook and in
high school but let's be real that's I there's a lot more to it that I'm not up
and up on but that's just how the way the the market is right now yeah it's
it's crazy and I you know I I would have no problem finishing my four-year degree
if tuition was not so stupidly high and now you all know a little fact about me
yes it's true I used to work for a truck drivers magazine so but it's I don't
know if it's still around I think it is but anyway I got laid off because you
know not a lot of truck drivers read magazines they all listen to satellite
radio but anyhow let's move on video games techmaster Loki how are you these
days fine I gotta say this one of the popular games like to play here at olr
before we get into the game talk is what did Loki bring to the show tonight and
Loki brought with him Jack in the Box and one of the now Jack in the Box they
have almost everywhere in the u.s. right but not not in the Northeast I think they
don't have it that's weird yeah it's weird they don't have it like cuz I know
friends that live up in like Connecticut and stuff and when they come out here
they're like we got to go to Jack in the Box oh my god it's kind of like it's
kind of like me and Dunkin Donuts cuz we don't have Dunkin Donuts here in
California or Krispy Kreme coffee we do have a Krispy Kreme in Roseville yeah they're still yeah there's a Krispy Kreme where somewhere
there's one in Stockton too yeah but where's Roseville where in Roseville
though cuz I can swing out that way let me Google that for you anyhow Jack in
the Box right now they have the bacon milkshakes right now I don't know why I'm
giving them free advertising but whatever it's not on their menu probably
for good reason well okay I got to say when Loki came in and said I got a bacon
milkshake I'm like alright I have to try it that's why I brought it it's like try
that was so fucking repulsive I can't oh my god that was terrible I was I didn't
hate it and she's the Jewish one it's not real bacon that's right it's just
tastes like it just tastes like hickory and vanilla it did taste a little bit
like the cheeses that they have out at the mall with the Swiss ladies at
Christmastime was that the hickory farms hickory farms at it it did taste a
little bit like like smoked vanilla they made a bacon cheddar milkshake that might
be pretty good all right you know what though that has inspired me that you
know make my own bacon milkshake because this is it's the careful the grease and
milk don't hurdle Eric RPG says I want to go to a psycho donuts I've never heard
of that I wonder if that's like if you live in Portland there's a great place
called voodoo don't you surely you already know at this place it's legendary
up there but voodoo donuts which I had when I was up in Portland and that's
where you can get the donuts that look like penises and you can also get the
bacon maple bars Loki I've seen that on a I know actually no I've seen in that
and and no it wasn't that it was a what the hell it man versus food I saw it on
there all right video do weddings there to video games I want to want to get
into this off the top of the show Loki you sent out a tweet this week you are
parting with one of your video game systems what's going on I just don't
play my 3ds so I want to get rid of it and really it came down to just I'm was
thinking okay Vita or the 3ds you know normally I would get both but I don't
play my 3ds that often so I was like okay what titles coming you know soon or
this year or that have been announced or potentially would be announced that I
would be looking forward to on the 3ds
kid Icarus maybe another Mario title or a paper Mario or something like that
confirm a 2d Mario right yeah there well there's one learn another 2d Marba I
don't really care and then there's like maybe a paper Mario or something like
that but it's just it's a few and far between it's you know I picked up Mario
Kart and I picked up the Super Mario 3 land and I played a lot of Mario Kart I
didn't really play much of Super Mario 3 land but be tween those I hadn't picked
up anything says launch I mean it's a good you know nine months span basically
between games and and honestly the next thing I'd probably pick up would be kid
Icarus which is in March and beyond that yeah I mean this is not a whole lot
whereas the Vita I mean they're porting everything to that there's gonna be a
Call of Duty on that there's gonna be probably the grand theft next grant the
thought it will be on that I would not be surprised and just I think there's a
lot more games on there that I would probably play versus my 3ds and be
honest I mean the 3ds it's kind of a letdown a little bit because it's just a
DS more or less I mean with some 3d graphics that are just kind of like yeah
that's kind of neat but would you think about I mean one I see I'm not quite on
the same side issue but I'm also in a situation right now where financially I
could get the V because I just did taxes and I had a huge tax refund so I could
get the Vita without having to part with my 3ds and I can juggle them both I'm
not gonna feel like I'm losing something to gain something else but the more I
think about it from your perspective if you do sell your 3ds it's not like you
couldn't buy one later and they'll probably have the read is the inevitable
redesign that includes that second d-pad and we all know there's going to be some
redesign in the future I know that's Alan's thing you know he doesn't want to
get a 3ds until the end there there will be there's absolutely going to be a
redesigned 3ds at some point and and that's not even really a big deal for me
either because it's it's just like even the next console generation I was kind
of thinking about it and it's like I'm not gonna I don't think I'm gonna buy
all three again you know it was kind of cool with the Wii is like oh I got to
try that out because you know that is a completely different type of way to play
games and the ps3 I honestly wouldn't have picked up at all but I got one for
free so you know I'm not gonna complain there and and really I didn't play too
much of my I've played a few games on the ps3 but not a whole lot and I still
don't I hardly ever use it for blu-rays I use it for streaming movies but I mean
I could do that with my Xbox too I play a lot more Xbox but so interesting
because I'm the exact opposite ever since the hacking like I don't know what
it is but like I don't touch my xbox 360 unless it's specifically for something I
can only play on 360 which lately is connect games rhythm party I talked
about last week I'm really into I played that like every day this past week but
otherwise the multi console stuff has been all ps3 for me like 13 to have been
playing on the ps3 you know I just don't know if I will mainly it was before it
was going to be that it was money was going to be the issue where I just wanted
to be didn't even then I really want to be there I mean but yeah I do because
there's actually some games on there that I'd like to try out I'm going to go
crazy and buy like a bunch of launch games like I did you know with you know
the 3DS crazy there but I mean it's just that's kind of why I'm going that way
it's just I don't have a lot of I mean I don't play Kingdom Hearts so because
otherwise Kingdom Hearts is probably a big draw for me for the 3ds I guess but
you know they don't have a date for that yet it's still some time is here I don't
know I just think there's gonna be a lot of stuff that in that system seems like
such a step up versus the DS and the 3ds ds and 3ds I mean they're much the same
I mean the graphics dsi you know and even the 3ds in some regards is a step
backwards I mean I'm still team 3ds I really like my 3ds I'm not gonna part
with it but I will say those dsi XL's I mean when Alan got one of those those
screens are gigantic I love it like it's that's the best way to play DS games
right now I wish the 3ds screens were that big but I guess they have to save
that for the reason something I don't know well maybe it's more expensive
because of the technology and those screens I don't know it's a 3ds tablet
oh wait that's just a Wii U controller oh yeah all right Vida yeah have you
gotten your hands on a Vida yet I finally played one yesterday no I have
done I played one at GameStop yesterday which I know yes I walked into a
GameStop and I didn't instantly turn to ash but in my defense I was at the mall
and we were shopping at some other stores and so we were walking right by
and I was like oh there's the Vita right there on the wall damn it let's go in
and take a look so I did get my hands on the Vita a little bit and I gotta say I
first thing I noticed right away damn that screen is big like for a handheld
like that you know it's more like regular TV proportions and I was kind of
okay that's that's kind of neat like the analog sticks are tiny though that's
that was interesting and they're not thank God they're not like that little
nub that's on the PSP that would like hurt my thumb after using it for so long
like yeah how was that thing they're like little tiny tiny little nubs tiny
little PS nipples that you can use to you know for whatever but then it's like
I'm standing there like an idiot like how do I start the damn game I can't and
then I remembered oh yeah this thing has a touchscreen I have to touch the screen
to get it to do anything but I played um oh what is it the mod nation racers and
I played wipeout 2048 or whatever the wipeout game is it's on the Vita and
yeah I mean it's it's gorgeous looking the graphics you know when they say it
looks like a PlayStation 3 yeah I can kind of see that I mean you know again
it's it's a little bit of bait-and-switch because yeah it's really
high resolution but on a lower resolution monitor but for handhelds it
is it is pretty gorgeous looking I'm still kind of on the fence on if I want
one or not and funny enough it's it's kind of what's troubling Loki and that
is the games but Loki I got to say you do make a good point most of the big
franchises will probably inevitably come over at some point I know I want that
Final Fantasy 10 thing that they're gonna do down the line I absolutely like
if I were to buy the Vita at launch I'm getting that luminous game absolutely
hasn't yet but song list and everything and you know I always have this fanboy
boner for Q entertainment you know it was speaking it just I didn't decide
I was kind of ironic and funny Ridge racers no longer a launch title I wonder
if it didn't sell very well at all in Japan and they went back to fix it and
add tracks let's hope but didn't Ninja Gaiden get bumped up like there was kind
of a no it's just that the news is too they're they're behind in getting
release dates and stuff like that so it's been launched for a while it does
kind of concern me a little bit too that there's a lot about the Vita that's
still kind of a question mark even though the damn things out in Japan and
there's a lot of stuff that ought to be there that's not and I gotta admit one
of the things I know a lot of people are like well if you want to just go play
your PSP or go hook up your PlayStation 1 the ps1 games not playing on the
PlayStation Vita I mean why not I don't understand why that doesn't work if that
thing is supposed to be as powerful as a PlayStation 3 why can't it successfully
emulate the PlayStation 1 games I'm sure there's a highly technical answer but
from a consumer standpoint I'm like damn it I bought like Final Fantasy I would
like to play that I've got the emulator to work because they still have full
backwards compatibility with the PlayStation portable stuff and they are
working on that right it's me when Sony's like implementing all these
features as they go but then there's a part of you that watches what happened
with Microsoft because remember when the Xbox first came out it was like these
handful of titles will be emulatable from the original Xbox and they slowly
added more and more to that list and they said we're not gonna stop till
they're all emulatable and they stopped about a year you're into it and you
still can't play the old DDR ultimate games on 360 at the same time at least
they're not shipping that system saying oh hey look internet browser Oh
internet browser coming in the future you know patch what yeah I guess okay
Nintendo's guilty of the same thing hey look you're right I want to buy a game
oops sorry store coming in a future patch all right here I always the second
analog see you know that March release day for whatever reason or April what
what the hell month did it come out March March all right they sure were
married to that date oh yeah the because of the quarter quarter earnings are
you're yeah so I mean I get maybe it's the same thing with Sony I mean yeah
it's February but it's you know still maybe that's part of the reason why they
got to get it out now oh well I'm sure I'll end up getting one inevitably
because I really do want that luminous game I really want it and then when the
Final Fantasy 10 thing comes out I'm gonna be like I want that too so well
and just looking at like some of the other stuff like little big planet on it
I'm not you know I don't play enough of little big planet on the ps3 but just
showing how easy it is to make stuff using that touchscreen just like okay I
want to make a hill and I want to adjust it oh and I'm gonna pinch it to make it
a little bit smaller and I'm gonna rotate it and I'm just gonna poke at
this stuff and everything works perfectly fine it I mean it's awesome
it's just so easy to make stuff with so I'm kind of looking for that spin-offs
that they're gonna have let's go to our chat room we always love to be joined by
the chat room chat that orange lounge radio calm some comments in the chat
room let's see a suka and our chat room says Vita is worthwhile at launch only
if you don't own a PSP see I do oh yeah I do own a PSP yet I'm still kind of
like and what of one is the other thing too though and I don't know if you've
done this yet you remember back when they gave you those free PlayStation
Network games and the free PSP games as part of the reparations for you know the
network being down for a while I haven't used those PSP games so I actually have
ModNation racers waiting for me as soon as I you know get my Vita more comments
in our chat room at chat.org.com ahamkara says no HDMI port on the Vita
well that's kind of ass what if you want to play your Vita stuff on the TV who
cares me I like cooking up the PSP to the TV yeah but who cares you know why
because first off who's to say that you're not going to be able to stream
that stuff from your Vita to your TV in the first place and whoever fucking uses
stupid cable so you actually use the cables hook up to your TV you like being
tethered six feet away from your TV was that fun I mean because I actually okay
hold on hold on smarty pants when I'm in the bedroom on the TV in there and I'm
kind of lying on the bed that six-foot tether is just enough where yes I can
lie in bed and play Final Fantasy 4 and have a fat day where I am fat and I am
playing PSP in bed on my TV I mean the only one that was actually that would
make sense doing that would have been like the PSP go where it actually had
you know DualShock 3 Bluetooth support which hey there you go Bluetooth support
you know you could maybe do something like that later on but I don't care I've
got a big screen in front of me why do I need to hook it up to my TV to have some
weird resolution on there I just don't need that if I want to play on my TV I'll
use my PlayStation 3 or Xbox 360 spazz nator in our chat room says I don't want
to get a Vita due to the shit I've gone through with my PlayStation 3 and my
digital downloaded videos you know history can burn you and I you know I
know spazz nators called into the show before to talk about his his trials and
tribulations and I gotta say yeah I can see where he's coming from because it's
it's me and Microsoft right now I feel very apprehensive with like I don't want
to buy things on Xbox because my wallet will be you know stolen from yet again
I'm feeling a little weird about all that stuff whereas I'm sure some people
are like Rob you're irrational I don't buy a lot of digital content so it
doesn't matter to me I mean especially since they're like hey you get 10% off
maybe that's if we decide to discount it because uncharted it's not fucking
discounted or at least it wasn't it might be discounted now but still 10% all
right let's uh let's move on so Vida so Vida yes for you launch day um hopefully
Vida is strong like leaning towards yes but I'm really gonna wait for that first
week release thing that's Valentine's Day or whatever and see what the
feedback is on that dark soccer I'm pretty sure you said you're a no just
due to personal situations but any interest in Vita I want an iPad just
wait for an iPad three or whatever they're gonna announce one at the
beginning that's true yeah iPad 3 will be all HD and pretty I want one of those
two honestly I don't really give a shit about the Vida anymore why is that I
mean it would be nice to have one and I'm sure Dan wants to get one yeah are
you psyching yourself out of your like I don't want a Vida
Vida's are shit because I can't afford it no you know I'm saying I'm saying
this I really I'm still playing games on my DS and I can't play for very long
before I start to hurt so it's sort of like I play with anything that I want to
on my phone I only have to use my thumbs and bust to move is all I need bust to
move is all I need all right fair enough let's move on we're gonna talk about our
gaming weeks and the video games that we've been playing this week of course
you can always join us in the chat room to chat along with us chat orange
launch radio.com live on this Sunday evening February the 12th of 2012 if
you're listening on the podcast hey just a reminder we do tape live every Sunday
night right after the Bobby Black Wolf show at all games radio www.all games
calm and a big thanks of course to the chatters for coming out as always it's
it what did I say fucking last week when we were up against the Super Bowl we are
always against some damn national event on TV on Sunday nights and tonight it's
the Grammys but Adele's gonna win everything every star that gets on the
stage is gonna say something about Whitney Houston and that'll be pretty
much it I don't think I miss much any good performances will be on YouTube so
there you go now you can listen to us it'll be more spontaneous let's talk
about our gaming weeks dark soccer we'll start with you what types of video games
you've been playing this week best to move on my phone which I'm trying to go
back through and get all the medals now which I think I have most of them so I
can get like the proper ending of the game and I'm play well addict dealer
what's new with you in the world of Warcraft what are you been like your
goals lately holo dailies that's pretty much it I want pink flamingo it's running
around I go look at my pink flamingo and I'm playing my troll who cries in
size all the time and I have another horrid tune on Ravencrest to play with
other people good times but by the way Rob I did get the name today for the
death night alright be Whitney for you so just letting you know I I believe
grandpa war crafter as he goes by in our chat room salvellous would be proud
because he had what he had our IP Steve Jobs I have our IP Betty white just
waiting and I think he rolled he rolled another one when somebody passed away
recently I remember who was I'm actually because my one that's on the main server
I'm gonna be I'm learning how to tank on that one but this one other ones just
gonna be a DPS for lol so I can go in and go haha I begin some emails about a
Star Trek online and how they've added some new stuff and have really kind of
got behind the free-to-play stuff you've been able to check that out since when
FTP um well I haven't checked out the very new stuff I've seen some they they
have a really a lot easier way now to get some of the different costumes and
goodies and if you've got the cryptic points for it you actually just will
select it on the menu with all the rest of everything like if you're changing
your outfit and you want a certain piece of an outfit you can just select that
piece and pay your points then so I'm probably gonna be getting some cryptic
points in the next couple of weeks and really giving it a go because I miss
playing with my Scottish buddies but I still love us yo I went around and they
fixed a bunch of stuff on DS DS 9 Oh Deep Space 9 is in the game you can
actually now go in the office it's been in the game you did there were just
parts that were closed off now you can actually go you know in the commander's
office and the baseball is sitting there Cisco's baseball because you know he is
awesome tastic all right so I've had school and all this other stuff on my
plate so I still haven't sent out the game so sorry and we were gonna pick up
our lazy I know busy we're gonna pick up our duo today but we just didn't get by
there we had we were gonna go by Dan's mom's house but she had to go somewhere
else so we didn't get a chance to all right let's go to Loki tech master Loki
how was your gaming week I didn't play much I was writing for tutorials this
weekend I played very little bit of Skyrim I remember what I did in there
but something in Skyrim related I think it was oh yeah I checked out patch 1 4
which sadly to say even though it promised to fix the quest it did not
fix the quest I think the quest is too dead for me did they push out the
console finally yes it's a console now it was supposed to fix the fire on the
ice bro no not firing yes blood on the ice quest and I didn't none of mine it's
impossible so me whatever um let's see then some other miscellaneous quests I
did I also played the cat that got the milk which was the free game I was
talking about the cat that got the milk calm and it's this weird it's like a
puzzle game and it gets all kind of artsy and it gets pretty hard actually
so it's fun for like a few minutes that's about how long the game is and
called you played more Call of Duty and I'm starting to try to teach myself now
pronating which is throwing grenades in really specific ways to get them to
bounce off shit and hit people very far away from you that's pretty much the
only area I could improve upon right now I'm really frustrated how that my
co-workers they they really don't like playing with me you're just too good
because I because because I will purposefully run up behind them and
stab them I have the opportunity that's not a nice or they'll be or they'll be
or they'll be standing there or something like that I'm like and I'll
sit behind them I'm like okay what's something funny that I could do to kill
them hmm something funny so like one of my co-workers is prone under this truck
like trying to snipe at people so I went prone to and I crawled up right behind
them and they started seeing my gun in their screen because you know I had
clipped past their camera no like what is that and then they turned and that
shot him in the face god damn it you're sitting there the whole time just kill
me I'm so hateful that at your work you can do this like you always just it
sounds like you work at a frat house for God's no it's just our 15-minute games
we get to 15 minutes and then they ask you know what I do on my 15-minute
breaks like a walk yeah I could do that but now where's the fun in that exactly
walking for nerds Call of Duty is where it's at well they the whole thing with
Call of Duty was we hate getting our asses kicked in Grand Theft Auto we're
gonna play Call of Duty because he's probably not good at that so humble so
humble I hey I didn't know I was gonna be good at it because honestly I played
Call of Duty for once before I'd actually played with them and so I was
kind of at the same spot that they were in fact I believe that my boss at least
had Call of Duty 4 already and he's been playing online for like a while now so
that's why he thought he had the advantage but apparently I'm really good
at that game I also read up on everything it's it's good to be educated
in what you're playing all right anything else for your gaming week that's
it all right my gaming week I get pretty short because I didn't play a lot of new
stuff I've been playing when I'm not playing World of Warcraft just like Dark
Sakura Final Fantasy 13 to haters stay pressed step off it's great I'm loving
Final Fantasy 13 to it's it's so I it's it's such a different story than the
last one and kind of the way they they they split it up it's really it's really
interesting that you go into one time and then you can go into a parallel
timeline that's the same thing with a different result it's interesting and I
have to correct one little thing I said in my review last week and that is that
you actually do get more than the two characters in your party but they're not
really controllable like it's kind of like this extra characters just standing
off to the side and kind of fighting with me although I don't really watch
their hit points or anything but I just didn't want to be you know corrected in
my review last week because I played a lot further into it now I did check out
some of the DLC you can download right now the lightning and oh her her guy in
charge of the squadron dude I can't remember his name you can play against
them and I guess if you're able to beat them you can use lightning as your
summon summonable monster in battle but I can't beat them yet because I'm too
low a level as I guess I haven't played far enough so I'm still working away at
it I finally got to the casino in Final Fantasy 13 too so it was you know kind
of fun to see some of the minigames they're bringing back chocobo racing I
heard that the case if was in the game as a suitable well it but it's not it's
not the Kate Sith it's not the guy in the big moogle that you remember from
Final Fantasy 7 but it's a monster called Kate Sith in fact it's probably
the first monster that you'll get and probably hang on to hang on to for a
long time because it's a healer and it's one of the few healer monsters you get
and plus is a kitty and in the little special attack he goes wow and then
eats claw claw claw claw claw it's really funny so yeah I'm liking Final
Fantasy 13 too and I'm definitely gonna play this to completion that's pretty
much where all my gaming hours have gone when I'm not playing Wow or something
else I will say I randomly had an urge to play bit trip runner yesterday and
try to get further in that game that's the one you know it plays like the chip
yeah I know it's hard as hell it's like an older game it's on Steam it's where I
play it on PC I think maybe I played cannibal this week cuz I remember
yeah don't start Skyrim you'll never finish it um let's see I'm looking in
our chat room at chat orange launch rated calm hey Stan Stan says me too
loves Final Fantasy 13 to the use of enemies is the third character reminds
me of Pokemon mixed with dog fights it's an interesting way to think of that
jester Scott says by the way you need lightning I would love to get lightning
but I can't beat beat her yet Eric RPG says actually sky it's a 10% drop even
at 5 star oh my god I was able to beat lightning and tell her little buddy
joined in the fight and then I got wasted so I just I just need to level
further and grind and all that those of you that missed grinding in Final
Fantasy those of you that bitched about Final Fantasy 13 it's too linear and
there's no grinding it's too easy well guess what you got your wish prayers
answered enjoy grind grind grind away otherwise gaming a little bit Mario Kart
7 that's really it so let's move on and talk about some housekeeping tonight we
actually have some really big news in housekeeping tonight we didn't want to
promote this a little bit because not everybody's gonna see this is good news
I wish dark soccer was in the room but she's in the restroom right now but
that's alright we'll we'll move on anyway she can say her piece afterwards
if she needs to but it's it's pretty straightforward this is more of a
programming note and it's gonna be kind of a shift in in orange lounge radio it
is not going to affect anybody that listens to the podcast at all but it
will affect the live listeners the announcement is that we are going to be
ending the orange launch radio after birth and it's gonna be ending next week
next week will be the final after birth that we're gonna do and it's gonna
involve the ultimate cage match and we'll tell you more about that next week
why we're doing it I think part of us kind of creatively the the after birth
which which if you only are a podcast listener you don't know what it is the
orange on radio after birth it's kind of like after we tape the show live for
about 20 minutes afterwards we'll usually just kind of sit around and chat
and then we do this segment called the cage match where we play three songs and
it's more of a indulgence for the live listeners and we do this fortune cookie
message of the day and all this stuff and the cage match is a segment that
dates back to episode 20 of this program so we're on episode 445 and the cage
match dates back to episode 20 so it's it's very old segment and it's something
we kind of wanted to keep even after we made the shift to all games radio some
years ago but creatively unfortunately I think the after birth has lost a lot of
steam those of us here that hosts the show kind of feel like we got a we got
to get our cage match song we're stuck in the studio for another 20 minutes and
you know it's kind of it's kind of become this necessary thing we have to
do every week so and you know when creatively something's not working you
say okay we're gonna change it so that's what we're gonna do we're gonna change
it so we've decided to and the orange ones radio after birth and next week we
are gonna be saying goodbye to the cage match which has been a part of our show
for the past 425 weeks give or take a few so you know I realize our live
listeners may see this as oh well you don't care about your live audience
anymore hey that no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no it's not about
that at all think of it this way by doing that and ending the cage match it
opens the door for other possibilities and things we could better spend our
time with once this show is over more information on that in the coming weeks
but for now we hope our live listeners will understand this creative decision
and this longtime segment of our show that you know podcast listeners weren't
even hearing anyway so all right Kai's you know in chat says I'm gonna read
these Kai's you know in chat says just saying you guys are getting lazy after
birth is good times I think that comments a little bit unfair because you
know it's not a lazy thing to be doing a show for the past 10 years every week
but I think too you have to wait to see what the future holds I think we'll
prove you wrong hit stun says I think we need an official post show turntable FM
party I'd be in support of that I I have not logged on to turntable in quite some
time and I love the iPhone app and all that and I am totally in support of that
ahamkara in chat says play games after the show and stream it I've been
thinking about that as like a side project the whole twitch TV thing and
all that good times all right anyone want to chime in on this whole thing I
think I said my piece in the chat room but I'll say it aloud fuck you we do
this for free we do this as a service and we keep trying to think of new
things to make things even better so if we're getting rid of something we're
doing it for a very good reason not just because we don't feel like doing it so
fuck off but I can see well that's a strong reaction but I can see where the
strong reaction comes from in chat too is that you know we've been doing this
so long and then we're saying goodbye to it and it's like but wait why that's
well that's my initial reaction to uh just an accusation of overt laziness no
yeah and on top of that I mean Rob has a full-time job Loki has a full-time job I
go to school you know we give up our Sundays for you guys so there's nothing
I think wrong at all for us you know trying to think of something new some
way to innovate because nothing ever grows without a challenge and without
making small changes to it to make it grow so so just but there are no there
are some people in our chat that are like Brad from pop culture says
understandable and let's see Tiger Claw says so there won't be a post show of
any kind I didn't say that let's see active says nobody but one person is
complaining so you know I think I think for the most part people get it that
creatively sometimes you we don't not ending the show we're not ending the
show so don't know about that and there is there is something else coming yeah
so just deal with it all right I mean to be honest we don't have to do the show I
mean really but we do in the show we like doing the show in the show it free
up a lot of Skyrim time you know I've got design work that I'm being paid for
that I could be doing tonight but you know what I'm here doing the show all
right no worries guys all right let's move on and talk about something a
little more in gaming and we're gonna start with Loki with the video game news
Loki so we were talking a little bit about the Vita one of the things that
they offered in Japan was this cool UMD passport service basically if you owned
a PSP and some PSP games like UMD games and you downloaded this application or
whatever from the PlayStation Network that allowed you to kind of mark the
games that you had so then you could download them for a discount off of the
PlayStation Network store and be able to download them onto your Vita so it's not
a way to port your games for free from UMD but just a way to kind of offer you
a discount or an incentive to do that well that didn't just they just decided
hey you know what that's a cool service we're not bringing it over to the United
States or North America or Canada or anybody we're just meh you're not gonna
have it same with Europe Europe's not getting it either so unfortunately that
wonderful service they don't care I think they think that we're gonna abuse
it because we're you know the type of people to abuse that kind of thing
renting games or whatever I don't know how big rental is over in Japan but I
guess it's possible to be honest so not really anyone rents PSP games so oh it's
a little disappointing I guess it's disappointing it's you know there's gonna
be those people that are like but if you want to play a PSP game then you go get
your PSP but well then don't offer the service in Japan and not in other
territories there yeah there's that too um and then I'm also like you guys are
forgetting that that PSP didn't have digital distribution in the beginning so
those of us that were early adopters the PC or at least I'm almost positive it
didn't right it didn't for so you know longer than a year yeah it was a while
and like there was a lot of games I bought when the PSP first came out like
luminous which you know of course I'm always gonna go back to that cuz what
probably the greatest puzzle game to come out in a long time and yeah I'd
like to be able to have that on my PS Vita but granted the pain is numbed
significantly when you consider there's an all-new luminous game coming out so
it's gonna with some sounds well yeah I probably won't need the old one as badly
as I thought I did but okay what about Final Fantasy 4 the the collection on
the complete is great it's the original game and it's it's that PSP graphics
which are great and you couldn't download that on the marketplace at
first so of course I bought it on UMD and it's like oh damn I'd really love to
be able to have that on the Vita but I guess not so I want to buy it again so
they guarantee we'll go for the market value that it is right now exactly like
you know Final Fantasy 1 & 2 those are pretty awesome games I mean they're like
$9 retail now but they're probably gonna be like 15 bucks on the PlayStation
that's yeah that's that's kind of a bummer because now the PlayStation
Network kind of controls all that and you know hopefully they'll learn
something from steam about the deep discounting or maybe the whole
PlayStation Plus will throw in I think they already do right don't you get some
of those PlayStation do you get full PSP games free I know you get some PSN
Network games I don't think PlayStation PlayStation Plus is only on the
PlayStation 3 it's not a play oh it'll be it's a Vita thing you're gonna be
able to get the discounts on Vita I don't think I don't DLC certainly will
be discounted some of it so all right anyhow anything else on the UMD passport
system and all that good stuff there's ever a chance there'll be a drive no
there won't no they're not gonna make a drive and I don't think they should I
mean it's it's ridiculous you don't need to make a UMD drive for a PSP although
they did that with the PlayStation 2 memory cards remember they have the
memory card adapter that you can now do that before they you know allowed you
to use saves one thing that does kind of suck though is the backwards
compatibility games Grantha thought it was not one of the games is backwards
compatible that is so disappointing but ah but but I hope that that's because
that they're gonna go and fix the camera because before there was no camera
option it was one analog stick it was very difficult to play but I hope they
go back and fix that maybe some HD versions I'd be fine of that I can wait
I remember what it was I was gonna say earlier I got distracted by chat for a
little bit but I remember what I was gonna say earlier about UMDs notice how
in the complaining and the talking and all this stuff no one is talking about
the movies remember UMD movies no no one's feeling short change that the
movies are not gonna be playable or any of that stuff granted same thing they'll
playstation network certainly has its share of movies that they want you to
buy download all that well here's a thought how nice your movie's gonna look
like on that screen because they already look pretty because they have a lot of
digital downloads especially almost all the movies nowadays that come out like
on the blu-ray combo packs or whatever they have hey you can download digital
copy of the movie it's not bad isn't that all I always thought that was
restricted to the iPhone or no no it's usually it's usually iPhone they use
that Sony specially had the PSP ones but I think a lot of that they mean mp4s
kind of play on everything and they that's the format they usually use I did
not think about that so if I haven't cashed in my Tron digital Tron why is
the name escaping me right now the new one Tron legacy thank you if I haven't
cashed in my Tron legacy digital copy down the back of it because usually
it'll say PC you know PC iPod that kind of stuff and you may be able to convert
it if because a lot of the portable devices I mean Android phones and so
that they don't play you know the iPod stuff let's see I'm so glad we do the
show in the house Tron legacy digital copy of future feature film watch it
anytime anywhere on your computer and portable device works with iTunes works
with Windows Media Player I don't know you might be able to convert it somehow
but I mean there's a lot of stuff that you know supports that that's true
well Randy said F that UMDs it's all about GBA movie play our carts oh my
gosh remember those at e3 yes I do still coming to for the 3ds apparently
whatever happened to 3d movies on the 3ds that was a big thing they showed at
e3 I'm glad you mentioned that next week shut up really yeah okay there's been
like no press about it what 3ds movies just come out next it's not a movie it's
a game but it has the movie on it Tekken Tekken Prime or Tekken 3d Prime Edition
has the full Tekken animated movie on there in 3d that's weird that's kind of
cool though yeah it's just like and the good one too not the crappy live-action
Tekken movie hmm so that'll be something for next week that's pretty cool
well I just remember at e3 a couple years ago when we first saw the 3ds one
of the big things I remember seeing was the tangled trailer because that movie
wouldn't out yet and it was on the 3ds and I was like wow this is gonna be a
great babysitter system that you know kids and I'm and of course my mind I'm
like I want Tron on this thing yeah now haha now you're thinking about that 3ds
no I'm still not thinking about the 3ds I have Tron I'm five you have the
uber Tron with you know the original Tron on blue-gray and stuff but I don't
need three it 3d is cool in a theater 3d is cool maybe on my TV although I don't
have a 3d TV so I can't really speak for that I actually have seen our lobby TV
has a it's a 3d TV and that was alright but I don't need it 3d on the road I
don't need to watch the movie in 3d I mean it adds a little bit it's a little
bit more immersive but it's not like oh my god night and day so I'm fine without
3d that's why I like a lot of these 3d games I mean it's cool that the 3ds in
there like for the 3ds but I don't necessarily need it it doesn't add like
a ton of extra gameplay whereas you know that second analog stick does help quite
a bit just saying you know if I were the choose hey guess what we can make a
system with a second analog stick we're going to have 3d graphics yeah I'd
rather play with the second analog stick because that would be pretty useful all
right going to our chat room black will says about the Tron digital card says
check to see when it expires they expire after a few months great so I might be
screwed it's usually about a year and it's been about a year yeah Brad from
pot culture says fuck just torrent the movies well if I'm not able to get my
digital distribution that I bought fair and or a digital copy that I bought fair
and square I just might have to it is stupid that they expire that is kind of
dumb that it expires is that a whole is that like to prevent use bonuses I don't
what is the point of that it's them being assholes black will says I can't
wait for netflix to have 3d movies so I can actually see them in 3d I mean
wouldn't mind a 3d netflix after everything netflix has gone through this
past year I think a 3d version would be welcomed alright let's move on with some
more news we heard that Verizon is teaming up with I did did you also hear
that Disney is implementing the rental window I saw that on your Twitter
explain that quickly before we go on the next story what is the rental window so
to speak the rental window is basically that they limit all distributors from
selling copies to rental customers so blockbuster red box whomever cannot buy
copies for rent this is to prevent people it doesn't prevent people because
the first sale doctrine you can't prevent people from renting movies out
but it's basically to prevent them from having the movie on release date so the
people have to go so people go into you know their local video store ago all
sad face my neutron movies and I hear I better go buy it brand new instead of
you're renting it and so they go out will be not trying to try and you should
buy when it comes out but no like okay they don't have ours needs moms all they
don't have you know Mars needs moms to mom harder so I guess electric mama Lou
so I guess I gotta go buy it brand new so my kid can watch this so and and of
course you know the idiots that you make these decisions higher up hey look when
we did that look our our sell-through sales have just spiked they're just
going through there yeah because everybody's going to retail buying
copies and bring it back to the rental store so yes that is going to increase
the amount of sales you have in your sell-through copies oh but you forgot
all the other copies that you were selling for rental that aren't there
anymore so it actually evens out or is less but still that's the decision that
they make that's also the decision that Warner made a while back in there now a
60-day rental window I think and that's because they hate people that rent
movies all right ahamkara in our chat room says most of the Nintendo channel
3d isn't good you could turn it off and it's no different looking you know
that's kind of true like there's a have you ever Loki have you ever watched some
of the stuff on the Nintendo download stuff yeah there's some really bad sketch
comedy and some stuff on there this is I watch the animated shorts or I used to
have it you saw automatically downloaded I was like stop stop I don't I don't
want to watch this all right look we got it we we're like 50 minutes into the
show we don't one story so let's move on this is a big deal because this is to
gain companies people really love me I love both these companies and isn't it
rough when you see people you love fighting isn't that hard to watch well
that's what's happening now and it's it's a court battle blizzard filed a
notice of opposition with the u.s. patent and trademark office what they're trying
to do they're trying to block valve from using the term dota now for those that
don't know dota defense of the ancients long time ago was a Warcraft 3 mod that
was super freaking popular to the extent that it went on to spawn just all these
kind of I don't want to say clone games but other types of games in that same
vein League of Legends being the huge example of that now what's interesting
about dota is that because it was a Warcraft III thing how did it work like
there were two guys there was one guy that started dota one guy that continued
dota I think that I could guys I so apologize if I'm fucking this up but
it's like a soap opera storyline okay I think the guy that continued dota went
to go do League of Legends the guy that started dota got hired by valve because
that's what valve does they see things out there in the community they hire
that's that's where portal came from right the whole nevacular drop yeah
hired those guys so valve does that so now valve has dota 2 coming out blizzard
because defense of the ancients was a Warcraft 3 mod they're doing their own
thing blizzard dota for Starcraft 2 that's coming out at some point most
people seem to think it's gonna launch with heart of the swarm or it's gonna
require heart of the swarm to give the next Starcraft 2 expansion kind of
something that everybody's gonna really want well we've known that this has been
the case for almost a year and a half or two years but blizzard is now decided
now that dota 2 is in beta testing to take issue which I can kind of you know
if you really want to kick them where it counts do it after the games already in
beta testing so from that strategical standpoint I assume I can see that but a
blizzards case quote by virtue of that use the dota mark has been firmly
associated in the mind of consumers with blizzard including to signify a highly
popular scenario or variant of one of blizzard best-selling computer games
Warcraft 3 a lot of fans are up in arms about this because they're saying
blizzard you didn't make the mod yeah and I honestly never heard of the term
until a couple days ago but you don't really follow these types of games
either to be fair I don't see who wait I'm the lore nerd for Warcraft hold on
one sec Matt the dark soccer in your mind go back three days who did you
think own dota I was honestly I was I kind of glanced at it and didn't care
okay that thought didn't come to your mind fair enough
tiger claw on our charm says blizzards version is D OTA with the periods while
valve went around that by just calling it dota 2 apparently that wasn't good
enough for blizzard valve blizzard doesn't own the I can it was created for
one of their games and I can see the whole Association legally I don't know
what standing they have I mean I gotta admit legal but I'm not a lawyer also
I'm just a sick fanboy the only way legally that blizzard can stand on it is
if they had filed a trademark on it also valves game isn't dota it's dota 2 I
mean if I want to have a superb owl party can I get away with that are we
talking about this last week all right anyhow well and this to me this almost
reminds me of monster like monster cable suing monster mini golf because as the
word monster in it oh yeah or like I think monster energy drinks does the
same thing or they suit monster energy drink I'm sorry but just because a mod
was used on your game doesn't mean you have the rights to that and that doesn't
work it doesn't work that way unless they use some mod tools that you
provided them I don't see how they have the you don't have the rights to that
unless they gave you the rights what is this that our pal Bobby black wolf is
sending me right now he says this is the link to the dota song by bass hunter you
should play this for shits and giggles what is this
did end on a job dog on a seat that I haven't a low spell I don't thought we
see the heart event and spare money they don't stop I visit the heart event and
spare money they don't stop a few lawsuits off dance party instead can we
just dance our problems out somebody should sue this guy for being addicting
all right that same fucking melodies in like 50 goddamn songs I've heard come
out of various European territories moving I'm suing them for that melody
damn it dark Sakura save us from dance party I like to move it move it how
about some steam stuff speaking of valve yes well you know that whole business
with the steam hack it looks like they might have gotten some information for
transactions after all that happened between 2004 and 2008 so no incur
basically that was announced by Gabe Newell he said that the file had
usernames and email addresses and encrypted billing addresses and credit
card information but no passwords so I guess maybe your expired card might be
in trouble change your passwords anyway and to be perfectly honest it just said
he's he suggests using steam guard keep it on and my suggestion is don't put
your fucking credit card on steam I use PayPal for a reason the end but it's so
easy when you give them your credit card information I'll admit steam has my
credit card information so I'm a little nervous but also that credit card
expires very soon so yeah and honestly like my last credit card expiration date
was like 2010 yeah that's true I mean if they got information from 2008 whatever
credit card I was using then long since expired yeah so I mean as long as they
can't see what porn I bought on other websites between that time it never
hurts to be careful but don't panic in other words hey I like though that
they're being very upfront about it I mean the whole steam is awesome situation
really sucks but you know I've come to learn that the hacking is one thing and
you know PlayStation got hacked and Sony or Sony PlayStation got hacked and then
valve got hacked and you know other websites but then the information
actually being misused to steal money is another and that's Xbox which totally
denies that there has been a hacking of any sort so when choosing between this
or this I'd rather go with welp the information was hacked I know that
sounds really weird but think about it also use a different password on every
website that's really the best practice you have to use a different password on
every website you do and it's the only way to keep your information choice a
for the love of God your bank account password better be unique please tell me
your bank account password is unique and really your email password should be
unique too because to reset your password on any other website it usually
goes back to your email address so if any thing is going to have unique
passwords your banking and your email needs to have unique passwords right and
don't have any of your password saved yes and don't name passwords after your
kitty and don't be like who was it the president of Syria or whatever they had
their password one two three four five don't really that's the same multiple
people don't please don't do that but that's the password an idiot would put
on his luggage alright moving on
Loki so there's a big Kickstarter project featuring double fine they
decided to go ahead and put it this project on a Kickstarter to raise money
for a classic point-and-click adventure game using modern technology or modern
touch technology and it's broken all sorts of records they made their
forty thousand or four hundred thousand dollars in less than 24 hours that was
the original amount that they were looking to raise and it's already well
over a million dollars I believe 1.6 million as of today and they've still
got like 30 days to go on this it's just ridiculous it broke you know the records
on your Kickstarter and of course they're making quite a bit money off
that 5% cut they get kind of nice Kickstarter gets 5% they get 5% oh my
gosh hey they got a run they got a run their company yeah I know but I'm just
like do people know that 5% of their money goes to I guess they have to when
they click accept whether they read it or not yeah so yeah and so obviously
this game will be made there's lots of sorry I'm laughing because now I'm
thinking about that report I saw on CNN where the people at Kickstarter were
watching this double fine thing happening on the televisions and they
were like all around and they busted out champagne when it passed the million
dollar mark and like oh now I get why cuz they just made two hundred thousand
dollars in one fucking day or excuse me twenty thousand dollars it's still
really good yeah they've got 29 days to go and I mean you can still if you want
to pledge money for this and there's no reason I mean I can't fucking do math
50,000 yeah there's you know you can still pledge money if you want to and
they've got you know all the upper tier stuff sold out someone actually pledged
$10,000 or more to this there's ten people that pledge $5,000 100 to pledge
over $1,000 900 that pledges over 250 this is ridiculous but there's still the
bottom tier stuff if you pledge $15 you get a copy of the game and access to the
beta and steam as well as access to the video series and private discussion
community $30 or more you get HD download of the documentary series with
extras digital game soundtrack and all the other stuff before that and then 100
bucks you get the original double fine adventure poster an exclusive campaign
special thanks in the games credits and all the previous stuff so you should
well check out Kickstarter period cuz they need a lot of neat stuff on there
not necessarily just video game stuff but like they had it one time and I
almost considered doing it like you could buy a set of Catan tiles that were
like etched laser etched on wood nice nice that they're really fucking
expensive but uh oh my my favorite one which I've got a I can't remember it's a
card game it's just very inappropriate that's I can remember now dark to see
you in our time says last I heard they were almost gonna break 2 million 1.6
million when I looked earlier is where they're at now yeah yeah so that fair
chunk of money this just in by the way orange launch radio is starting a
Kickstarter if you want to save the afterbirth segment I'm kidding I'm
kidding I'm kidding but seriously now I'm like what could we give away and we
can honestly do that I mean no card against humanity not in it for the money
remember guys are not enough for the money cards against humanity is the
thing that was a Kickstarter project that it's basically this card game
that's really bad it's it's not appropriate for most ages um did you
donate to this or did you think about donating this why not I mean I didn't
either but we were talking about this with Bobby on his show earlier before we
started tonight and he did and so we were kind of talking about the last
thing I donated money for was that humble bundle and I've played one of the
games out of that I'm not gonna buy another digital game that I'm not gonna
fucking play so I do play the games in the humble indie bundle yeah that was a
great deal I've played only one of them I still have all the other like but you
did good for charity this has nothing to do with charity I understand nothing to
do with charity remember that I understand that and and that's the other
thing too it's raised money faster than Child's Play did think about it Child's
Play did not raise a million dollars in it well I take that back they may have
at some point but over the course of three months they raised three million
well it was great if I Child's Play then comes up with some cool perks you know
to give away and I know the guys behind penny arcade probably could come up with
some cool perks and then put a Kickstarter page up I'm sure they can
get quite a bit of tension and get money raised that way and I think it's a cool
idea crowdsourcing is kind of neat and you know I could think of some ways we
could utilize that but it's just I don't know like if we like they had another
game there was another one it was by the guys that did I want to say the Tony
Hawk game or something like that like one of the Tony Hawk games or something
and they were raising money for this really terrible looking Kinect Xbox Live
arcade game where you bounce your characters around like some Steve
Pachinko looking machine and it was just terrible but they love pitching but
they're raising money for that and it's like so you're gonna raise money for
this and then you're gonna put on Xbox Live arcade and make more money because
you're not investing really any of your money because it's you're making all the
money it must be nice I mean hell if I was motivated enough to program games
and stuff and I could make a convincing Kickstarter that would be cool hey look
I got all my seed money now I'm gonna make some money and all I have to do is
provide some people some free codes or some extra tchotchkes then that's it
here's my honest concern and I think this is a legitimate concern to have what
if the game's bad I mean I realize the whole community is gonna be
participating and in talking about this on the forums and you know watching the
development and that part's really cool I got to give props to somebody that's
willing to lift the curtain a little bit there and show you what's back there but
I'm also a little bit like you know some sometimes community isn't always right
in their decisions you know sometimes the hardcore gamers alienate the casual
gamers and I talked about World of Warcraft did that a little bit with
that's the same with like a pre-order though I mean you put money down for a
pre-order and you get the game and it could suck mmm thing again I'm not
putting $100 down for a game I mean I I could see putting the $15 down which is
basically a game purchase and don't get me wrong this day and age so $15 for
digital game is kind of kind of expensive so it you know it better be
pretty good I beg to differ that's average for a PlayStation or Xbox game
most of them these days are 1200 points it's 15 bucks I make it ever I we like
them when they're 800 points but let's be real there has not been a 400 points
game in like four years so unless you're talking indie games because I think
indie games can go as high as 400 points so so we'll see I don't know it's just I
just don't see myself you know buying this game I'm well yeah I'll buy it if
it if the folks that are watching it say gosh this is looking greater it's a
great game or when it actually comes out it's great reviews just like any other
game but I don't know like I don't know if I but see as I was you know
mentioning on this topic earlier I might not feel that strongly about this double
fine thing but if Nintendo came out tomorrow and said hey if we can raise
$500,000 on Kickstarter we'll do killer instinct 3 I'll be like take my money
take it here you go and you're part of the problem no I'm serious here you're
part of the problem then I or Konami says we'll support rhythm rhythm fever
if you know no no if they came out and said that shit I say fuck you fuck you
fuck you I am NOT paying you a dime for a fucking game you make the game and
then I'll buy it if it's good I'm not gonna you know I'm not gonna be like oh
well I'm not gonna make games until people pay me money first yeah that must
be nice you know I'm not gonna well Konami did that remember it was beat
mania 2d x7 style yeah remember they said they were not gonna do it until
10,000 people pre-ordered the game yeah and they're fucking assholes and you see
what their car see what that karma did yeah where's your fucking beat mania
DDR series now oh that's right where is your god of music now it's in the
shitter because you fucking sucked it it's just like you know what you know
what the chicken style is awesome you know the cherry on the top for that
karma pie was it's a fucking rock revolution rock revolution was just
like I'm gonna take a dump on this disc right here here you go I you know what
though if you want to ask the question when did Bamani die that would be the
best answer now thankful thank thank God Bamani's seemingly making a comeback
there's a couple new arcade games I still I still say I don't give two
shits what you say Loki that rhythm fever game is actually a lot of fun on
connect no don't get me wrong they're on the path they're on the right path but
it's just it's still a ways away and I'm sorry they just take a lot of missteps
and you know dark gray nope it's flowing down the screen against a black
background not the smartest thing to do let's go to the chat room because Bobby
black wolf loves to correct me loves to correct me and says there is a 400
spacebucks arcade game a few weeks ago the scrabble plus risk combo coral
member coral that I didn't realize that was 400 points I've heard a lot of good
things about that game I think I might get it
scrabble plus risk dark soccer doesn't that sound pretty cool sounds
interesting mm-hmm all right moving on let's talk Mass Effect I know a lot of
you kids really love Mass Effect and boy Mass Effect is going to keep on giving
you know Bioware has all these studios now I mean hell Sacramento has one where
we're at even as a Bioware studio so when there's a big Bioware event man
they can get all these properties out everywhere and that's what's happening
with Mass Effect 3 there is a Mass Effect 3 tie-in called Mass Effect data
pad it's gonna be an iPad app that works with the console or PC version of the
game and the reason why I sound sketchy on this is because there's really no
details beyond that just some type of iPad interaction that works with the
game I don't know if that's like Disney it will take a picture of a something or
other on the screen and do something that's pretty much I think what it's
gonna do like read QR codes or something like that I like something like that
like you at the but I don't know you know a lot of a lot of nerds have that
stuff handy so I don't have an iPad but you know on iOS which is the other story
so not just the iPad or whatever that is but there's also Mass Effect
infiltrator this is gonna be an iPhone iPad iPod touch game it's a third-person
shooter it features certain weapon and powers from Mass Effect the whole
storyline has to do with freeing prisoners from a hostile base you know
typical space sci-fi stuff you get awards for collecting evidence of the
crimes that happen that you catch in the mission and I guess it increases your
Mass Effect 3 galaxy at war galactic readiness rating so I guess things that
you do an infiltrator can actually affect what happens in Mass Effect 3 so
that's kind of neat that they'll work together like that I imagine you kind of
tie all your accounts together through the EA website and it'll work so that's
kind of cool tie your accounts all together through the EA website get FIFA
you didn't ask for it so I it's interesting I mean I'm not super huge in
Mass Effect but I know people that are and I can't deny that Mass Effect is a
huge franchise that a lot of people are really excited about so I gotta admit
there are certain games where if they had like the iPad app I'd be like that's
pretty awesome so I hope it enhances the experience it isn't just a cheap cash-in
I'm not gonna pretend if they had an IS app for like a Grand Theft Auto game or
something like that I'm I might have to pick it up or like an iPad Saints Row
the third somehow like like you could control your missiles on the iPad no
that wouldn't be worth it I don't think so yeah the UAV got they got boring
pretty fast it's just much faster to use the other weapons all right release
dates coming up right after one more story from Dark Sakura well how about
the Xbox the Xbox I've never played an Xbox the lube the ex you the ex you
explain yourself woman how about an Xbox tablet instead there in Xbox world for
April 2012 there was an announcement for a new Xbox at e3 that has a tablet of
course my thought is that this is the April issue hello it's a little early
for the April issue I think it says scans of Xbox world for April 2012
actually no because April ones are on the newsstand in March and we're getting
towards the end of February so we're getting towards the end of February
really this could be so well for the publisher we're approaching the end it's
way over there but we're on our way I shut up if I may this may also be
someone who happens to be with a publisher or something I don't know it
says April 2012 huh huh yeah but that's when Xbox world is okay well it says
that there is a matte black media hub that is gonna have a tablet and that
it's gonna be I'm trying to see where yes they're anticipating 399 pounds yeah
this is British of course but they said that it works as a remote control with
your TV as a browser when you're on the internet has extra buttons for playing a
game or a portable display when you want to take your game with you so yeah 600
bucks roughly it's it's a rumor I'm thinking it's a troll but it better be a
troll because I'm looking at that picture and it shows just a tablet with
no tangible buttons and when I see that and see Xbox wants to use this as a
controller I'm like nine nine nine nine nine tangible control no no no I think
what I think what it sounds like to me is that it's a little bit of an
expansion on what they had already talked about with I think you do this
window windows phones where basically you can browse your I don't even know
what the fuck they call their little dashboard you can browse around they're
using your windows phone and you can queue up stuff like that maybe that they
add that to a tablet that's running like the windows phone OS or whatever hope
they got it they updated to like Android or something and then they can you know
have some buttons on there so that you can play like different Xbox Live arcade
games or something like that on there I could see an app maybe but isn't it
funny that this comes up this story comes up right after we were talking
about Mass Effect and how it's kind of tying into tablets well here's the other
funny thing to precursor of things to come I have to find it but there was
also the same rumor for the PlayStation 3 that they were oh wait no we talked
about last week but they're gonna come up with a tablet member oh yeah the
whole it had been patented or something like that right yeah but though and then
the patent doesn't always mean reality my response to that is you already have
some of that with the PSP can tie into the ps3 a little bit and plus the whole
god they were showing it at e3 the whole Vita and that dungeon crawler game that
hasn't changed its name like three times now the dungeon crawler game that's on
the Vita that you know you can that's our game and then pick it up on the ps3
and that's a hunter's alliance I think because I think they're calling it now
right yeah so I mean theoretically you can already have that technology if you
really want to use it but it's expensive because that means you have to own a
$249 Vita and a $299 PlayStation 3 so $299 $200 it has a lot cheaper than it
used to be it is but that's that's where it's at now because blu-ray players are
very cheap to came down with that technology all right let's move on we're
gonna travel around the world and talk about release dates and see what's
coming out to a game stop or a Best Buy or Walmart or whatever you like to shop
Amazon near you actually earlier this week the Nintendo 3ds pearl pink came
out ooh snap those up right away before the new hardware revision comes out
Zumba fitness rush came out today that's definitely worthy of a Sunday release
that's on Xbox 360 for connect rhythm heaven fever comes out tomorrow on the
Nintendo Wii and only $29.99 they did a big push for that Adam there was like a
whole launch event in LA and all this stuff yeah I fucking hate rhythm heaven
it's a frustrating fucking game it looks interesting but it's not very fun I'm
kind of over the Wii the Wii's just kind of sitting sad in the corner B units
build it for Nintendo DS see hakuoki demon of the fleeting blossom coming
out on PSP I believe that's a visual novel game blaze blue continuum shift
extend on PlayStation 3 Xbox 360 and because this week you are getting the
early adopter edition of you know the first run PS PlayStation Vita although
they do say PS Vita so Vita it is also now coming out on the Vita as well also
on the Vita formula 1 2011 FIFA soccer Virtua Tennis 4 world tour and luminous
electronic symphony Rayman origins and that's right Vita games are now going to
hit stores because people have those early bundles and to be honest they've
already been hitting stores because there's no street dates on the first
party games those were already out for a few weeks now interesting nothing you
know I'm gonna go take this box home and just read the instruction manual if you
have a Japanese system it's useful because they're region free so that's
right uh-huh other stuff on other systems we've got of course UFC
Undisputed 3 on PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360 tales of the abyss on the 3ds the
Sims 3 hidden springs expansion for the PC twisted metal on PlayStation 3 this
week which includes twisted metal black Mario Sonic at the London Olympic Games
on the 3ds B units build it on the Wii Grand Slam Tennis 2 on PlayStation 3
Xbox 360 Tekken 3d Prime Edition that's the one that with the 3d movie in there
some more Vita games Dungeon Hunter Alliance on the Vita Michael Jackson
the experience HD on the Vita as fault injection ultimate Marvel vs. Capcom 3
Ben 10 galactic racing reality fighters although I thought that was supposed to
be next month sledgehammer for the Xbox 360 which is a weird racing game with
big rigs Mel you're solid through oh I'm sorry that's the next week getting
ahead of myself this is a big week on the Vita in it yes well also there's
obviously the first party stuff is missing on there because GameStop and
other websites and stores have had it out already but of course you know
there's the uncharted game is going to be coming out as well golden abyss
little deviants is definitely a launch title mod nation racers and hotshots
golf world tour or world invitational world towards the PSP one so the big
week for the via course so happens when a new system launches all right let's
go to Japan talk about what games are coming out in Japan this week on the
Xbox 360 binary domain and WRC to feel world rally championship those are
coming out on the 16th on the PlayStation 3 they also get binary
domain and the same game there WRC to feel world rally championship so both
those games on the main consoles checking out the PlayStation Vita in
Japan kyoko gen das shoots ooh a DV zenon shibo desu comes out this week I
have no idea what the hell game this is it looks like oh there's pretty anime
people on it and pretty anime creature oh there's a little there's a little
trailer here this is all about it looks like this might be like an
anime series it's kind of gone to game or something like that I don't know but
yet I notice in the actual little screenshots there is a game there
something this is just like an anime tie-in game as they do get a lot of
those out in Japan but that's really the only big release on the Vita this week
in Japan going over to the Nintendo systems real quick I want to see if the
weird 3ds has anything not so much on the we as releases are kind of drying up
there the regular DS doesn't have anything about the 3ds look in there
quickly oh this is a big one for the 3ds new love plus just in time for
Valentine's Day out from Konami new love plus makes its way out this week this is
where can I read the description for this this is great introduce your
friends to your girlfriend with the new functions on the Nintendo 3ds your game
life and your real life will be blurred makes use of the gyro sensor to take
pictures of your girlfriend find the angle that best captures her beauty now
that you can control the camera physically by beauty we mean her panties
you can also share photographs of your friends with her she will remember their
faces and integrate firmly into your life her attitude and her personality
changes as the two of you date see how she acts more familiar with you as you
know her better yes this is the new love plus series this is the girlfriend in my
pocket or Tamagotchi with tits I don't know what else to say about new love
plus but I love that it's coming out on Valentine's Day forever alone it's just
put that picture on the cover that would be awesome if you're looking for
something I don't know different on the 3ds you know maybe that other people
like people like you and me my hey you know what this is kind of oh sorry go
ahead I'll interrupt you the Tekken 3d Prime Edition and that I hate trying to
say this theater rhythm theater them theater rhythm that Final Fantasy music
game is on the 3ds you know how much that sucker cost to import you want to
buy this from your local import store seventy two ninety nine fuck it it's a
terrible looking game frisbee in our chat room says titagotchi gachi hey how
what were you gonna derail me with love I was gonna say that it would be cool if
they came up with some sort of like tower defense game with all those like
internet maims thrown in there you know like an internet maim tower defense
game yeah who owns the right I mean we were talking about copyright earlier
with Dota and you know this community made stuff who technically owns the
rights to forever alone I don't know and rage rage comics Nancat adventure came
out in indie games this week huh but didn't but see somebody made that Nyan
cat new YouTube but I where do you trace back the f you comics to do you give it
to 4chan do you give it to reddit do you give it to oh it's a tricky one I don't
know can you imagine if somebody did try to make a f you game alright forget it
let's move on dark Sakura how about in the the old country really states just a
few on the 15th is warp for Xbox 360 on the 16th is Alan Wake for the PC and the
17th is UFC and disputed 3 that's really it
Oscar in our chat room asks do the titagotchis live leave did you poop on
the screen too remember that on the old time of God cheese used to have to yes
push the button to scoop their poop my devi mon not my devi my my yeah it was
because I had the digimon ones remember the original digimon that was a direct
release from the Tamagotchi I don't know some guys might be into that in 3d and
all you never know devi mon was a big shitter alright just a couple more news
stories for you guys in the classic game of the week Loki so the ps3 did get
another firmware update this week it speeds up web browsing apparently
according to the notes for the 4.1 update also they change your account
from the PlayStation Network account to the Sony Entertainment Network account
and other things and improve display speed for the browser and I believe they
also added Dropbox support so you can use that for storing images online huh
I didn't realize that yeah it's pretty cool some other cool stuff of course
there was this whole play memories thing that they were teasing a little bit ago
it's a video editing app that's gonna be part of the PlayStation 3 as well as a
PC and mobile suite and they've included five gigabytes of storage as well that's
going to be on a cloud-based service and it does work with you know iOS and
Android devices and apparently you'll be able to you know edit images and videos
and stuff like that I can't imagine the image editing on the ps3 be very easy
this is the controller right everyone else all right real quickly speaking of
Sony things one of the big things that people are looking forward to on the
PlayStation Vita or the PlayStation 3 the Final Fantasy 10 re-release now this is
interesting because I thought we had a story on this a couple months ago that
said Final Fantasy 10 is is a complete redo they're building it from the ground
up and all this stuff it is it is a remake but this week it seems like
they've gone back on that a little bit let's see this was at a China Final
Fantasy event the Taipei game show because they were pushing Final Fantasy
13 to squeamix producer you know we always call Square Enix squeamix here on
the show producer Shinji Hashimoto was at answering some fan questions about
some of the Final Fantasy games and somebody asked about hey is the
PlayStation 3 and Vita re-release of Final Fantasy 10 is it a remake or is it
a remaster and Hashimoto said directly it is a remaster so think like the
Shadow of the Colossus HD thing that came out not too long ago I wouldn't
even say it's well that wouldn't be so bad hopefully it's not like the
Melger Solid stuff they look kind of blurry and weird now he also went so far
to say that the screen is much prettier than the original but he didn't really
elaborate on that whatsoever what can I do for you give me Final Fantasy 7 next
how about first that's what all the fans are saying but I I get it though it's
easier to do this I mean there was an excellent point that was made is that a
lot of the stuff that was in Final Fantasy 7 was still kind of sprite based
whereas everything in Final Fantasy 10 was full 3d so it's much easier to take
Final Fantasy 10 and just you know assign it to the new resolution give it
some higher res textures and you know maybe remake the menu and and go back
into some of the things you know I think they'll do some other little things to
sweeten the pot I'm sure maybe like a bonus summon or a bonus dungeon or
something else you know it's I think it'll I think it'll pay tribute well
enough to the original I'm so I like Final Fantasy 10 I know Final Fantasy 10
has a share of haters but I thought it was great it's still still to this day
in my opinion has the best summon of all time Shiva of course when she comes out
snap great so huh anyhow how about we travel down memory lane a little bit
sounds plan later we always on the show let's take a trip down memory lane in a
segment we call the classic game of the week where dark soccer is gonna reach
into the vault and find a classic game she says hey why don't you remaster this
bitches hmm back in my day we didn't have remakes and remasters we played our
games ugly ass pixelated and we liked it ugly they were cute all right so dark
Sakura what is the classic game of the week this week puzzle bobble yay it came
out in America as bust a move but puzzle bobble is great and I've been playing a
lot of it lately it came out in 1994 it's about as high as it goes this
YouTube I'm streaming things a little quiet I love this game anyway puzzle
bobble was a puzzle game that came out for one or two players put out by Taito
based off of their 1986 game bubble bubble and it has the characters from
that game you play as bub and or Bob and it's cute it's super cute I love the
game there were two different versions of the original there was puzzle bobble
that came out in Japan only in 1994 on a Taito B system hardware though and it
was originally called bubble buster and then down the line there was the neo-geo
version of puzzle bobble that was exactly the same except it was in stereo
and had a few different sound effects and translated text when it came out in
the u.s. it was called a bust a move and had anti-drug and anti-literary messages
ooh and the same title was wait a minute puzzle bottle was anti-drug are we
talking just an FBI warning in the beginning winners don't use drugs okay
and the title was retained for the u.s. Canada and Europe on consoles so
basically you have different colored balls for different reason they're
bubbles but they you have different colors and you have to turn the crank to
launch the balls yes turn the crank to watch the balls that's what they're doing yes
at any rate you have a little pointer and yes you does attach to a crank that
Bob and Bob move and you can bounce these bubbles little bubbles up to other
bubbles and when you get three in a row touching then they pop you may have a
bunch of one color already up there in a neat colorful pattern but it gets really
complicated trust me I noticed that when they touch the balls together they
explode so they go in the direct line along the pointer and as you do though a
few more in a row then the ceiling starts to drop down when your bubbles
hit the very bottom line then your game over if you don't know this game isn't
crawl up from under the rock no dipping your balls below the line I think dark
soccer is mad at me anyway which were your favorite balls the blue ones she's
trying not to laugh she thinks she's bad she's not shut up you're a bitch at any
rate it has really busting your balls there it has a different scoring system
it's exponential scoring so for each that you pop in the same color they're
worth ten points each but if you drop a bunch that are attached to that one me
like say that you've got at the top you have like two yellow one blue one green
you know I'll touch the yellow when you break the yellow ones everything that's
textural balls it's good balls drop your score actually will go to 20 points and
then 40 and then 80 so it's an exponential scoring system if you rub
and girls together their maximum is 50,000 points that you get for clearing
it within five seconds or less and then it drops down to zero over the next
minute you do have two player modes are not around you just each have the arena
and the same arrangement but when you get a large clump broken it goes on to
the opponent's side kind of the way that uh help you appeal works which is one of
another one of my favorites so yeah it's bub and Bob or as they were doing in
Japan baboon and baboon and it's their same animation from a bubble bubble
actually closer to bubble symphony and it also has all the enemies in it so the
red one is and I'll do both names the English name was super socket and
Japanese name was invader the yellow one is hello balloon or pull pull there was
a green is Willy whistle or drunk blue is bubble buster or Zen Chan purple is
beluga or Monsta orange is quietly or Bonnie bow black is incendo or hit a
konsu and white is stoner or my death who doesn't want to name their balls so
for all the games that came out there are a bunch of them and I will go
pretty much in order there was puzzle bobble puzzle bobble 2 which was called
best to move again in the u.s. puzzle bobble 2x which I believe is the one
that I had on Saturn puzzle bobble 3 in 1986 puzzle bobble for puzzle bottle
mini on leogeo pocket color super puzzle bobble in 1999 azumanga puzzle die-o
which was based off of azumanga die-o from 2001 super puzzle bobble to super
puzzle bobble all-stars puzzle bobble mobile which I am playing on my phone
puzzle bobble versus which was for the engage who remembers the engage best move
deluxe on PSP ultra best move on Xbox puzzle bobble DS he packed a puzzle
bobble which was best to move DS ultra puzzle bobble pocket which was best to
move deluxe in the u.s. and best to move ghost in Europe best to move bash on we
best move online best to move mobile for the newer mobile phones in 2008 space
puzzle bobble which was called space buster move or puzzle bobble galaxy
you're a bust a move yes balls in space puzzle bobble plus puzzle bobble live
puzzle bobble for iOS which is best to move puzzle bobble 3d which was best to
move universe on 3ds new puzzle bobble aka new best to move for iOS and puzzle
bobble online came out in 2011 there were clones who remember snood I don't
fortunately I have sold snood yeah my friend's mom was hooked on that stupid
game play the real thing this frozen bubble and bubble shooter you know which
I actually all those crappy Facebook games yeah yeah yeah and like jungle
quest was not one of them no jungle well and there's actually even a version of
it on that comes built in with Linux there's one on Google Plus to any
puzzle they pawn I love puzzle they pawn nothing to do with not like that there
are no balls and puzzles upon it's exactly the same thing so anyway that's
your game is a Tetris puzzle bobble okay everything one question I want to
ask it's very important that we didn't address what in the actual fuck it was
this box art on the PlayStation 2 for super bus to move it was redonk I'm
gonna I'm gonna post this link in chat it's from Amazon I apologize it's big
but that's the only place I need to find the box art for those listening on the
podcast just go to your favorite retail site Amazon whatever look for super bus
to move on the PlayStation 2 and tell me what in the fuck is that box art it is a
baby blowing a bubble and in the sunglasses you see glimpses of what that
is Saturn one was freaking creepy looking fucking scary who would buy that
no look at the sectors look at the Saturn version let me see the Saturn
version ah his face is melting no his eyes are being pinned open going that in
the chat room like Taito what kind of crack do you think Americans are on I
think that company or whoever they hired for marketing was the same one that
launched the PlayStation 3 a shitload of that game on Saturn like I would just
sit in front of it for hours and scream at it it's one of those games that you
see it in the arcade and if it's 25 cents you can't help but just check it
out you know like even to this day I've fucking creepy game even recently
fucking creepy all right but it was an awesome game it still is awesome all
righty there it is your classic game of the week puzzle bobble or if you want
bus to move but not that good the Japanese box art is so much better not
that creepy super bus to move look at that that seat that should be what it
was in the u.s. instead it was a stupid dude trapped in a bubble with his eyes
pinned open that gives me creep nightmares that's that is definitely one
of the monsters in Silent Hill on the box there all right that's gonna do it
for part a of our show but guess what we are not done yet kids we've got plenty
more show to come we got some rapid-fire news coming up some more news your
emails the F use of the week and no more topics and no more balls twitter doc
well I don't know about that twitter.com slash olr if you want to send in your
twitter topics and and and and the skype line will be open very soon Skype us at
orange lounge radio all one word but not just yet that's all coming up in part B
so stay tuned everybody
welcome back everybody to orange lounge radio with episode number 445 live on
this Sunday evening to 1212 is the date today join us of course live via our
chat room chat orange lounge radio.com quite a good show considering we're up
against the Grammys tonight got quite a good showing and I am very proud I have
to say this I'm very proud of the chatters tonight because despite
everything that's going on in the world right now there wasn't a single person
now of course now they're gonna say this everybody's gonna do this but there
wasn't a single person that came in to chat tonight and said hey did you guys
hear that Whitney Houston died because I was so waiting for that because
inevitably when something big happens in the world that really has nothing to do
with video games it'll get brought up anyway it's really been off and on like
even on the radio and stuff because like today I was you know driving my wife's
car and she has the radio tuned to be like it's not really like oldies but
it's like the R&B station or whatever and is it that V 101 or whatever you
want to say so I was driving to the park to take Josh to the park it's just you
know regular music you know that's fine I'll wait home for the park all Whitney
Houston solid Whitney Houston from like it was like three songs all Whitney
Houston it was ridiculous obviously it's a tragic loss that it up but they all
sound very the same it doesn't have to stop it it doesn't really have anything
to do with video games well she to be fair I totally have I want to dance with
somebody and sing star so she wasn't seeing star so tip of the hat to a
famous seeing star inspiration I guess if you want to say that all right but I
will give a big gold star to all our chatters tonight for keeping it on topic
you know even despite all of the unfortunate that happened with Miss
Houston there's not really a lot of talk about the Grammys either so I know you
guys are focused and I appreciate that all right let's move on let's get back
into some rapid-fire news we're going to do some quick news stories and then
we'll get back into the longer stuff so Loki start us off with some rapid-fire
news Microsoft finally or Microsoft or LucasArts I haven't really said who
announced this but they've announced the date for connect Star Wars I know let's
get excited it's coming in April and it's not joke it's on April 3rd that is
probably the closest date they could have added to you know get in there
April Fool's Day although actually yeah April April 1st is a Sunday I gotta say
that um that can the Xbox it looks like r2d2 looks pretty kick-ass oh yeah so
that'll be coming on the same day as well now here's here's the thing and I
know we've talked about this before but really really they're gonna have dancing
in there I mean that just looks stupid shut up they put dancing in there oh my
god that's Star Wars that is connects Star Wars that looks like dance masters
yeah exactly is that like cantina dancing or something they're gonna have
dancing I see Jabba the Hutt back there it's like you can be one of his sluts
dancing there dad's for me slut wasn't that a line that Lucas put back in
return of Jedi hey sure yeah so that'll be coming out and of course you are my
eyes in our chat room gives us the greatest line from the trailer
lightsaber on remember it's all about the voice commands and I'm telling you I
played this game and oh my god yeah you played it oh my god no no no no no I
think you need to see this as well no make it stop stupid like that that
little picture is not helping the rumors about c-3po sexuality because you know
that's out there in the fanverse I'm just saying I'm just saying just saying
all I gotta say is the one that they had a Disneyland dance-off much better than
this shit and you know he's dancing the gaga it's he was programmed this way
baby lol ah yeah anyways I just hope that God it's it's way better than than
the versions because those were not good but that is supposed to be coming out
April 3rd and so yeah some other stuff Super Mario Brothers crossover 2 is now
on the Super Mario Brothers crossover is definitely something that's infringing
all sorts of copyrights but hey it's a flash game it's been out there for a
while and people play it so if you want to check it out it's at exploding rabbit
com slash game slash Super dash Mario dash Bros dash crossover I'm sure if you
just go explaining rabbit.com they have a link on the front page and basically
what version 2 offers you is you know you still get the play as multiple
characters including Mario Luigi Link Samus Simon Belmont Megaman base Bill
Reiser Ryu and Sophia the third from blaster master yes blaster master and
then they all have alternate looks because you can also cycle through the
game or they cycle randomly through versions of the levels including NES
Super NES and Game Boy styles throughout the game as well also
apparently demon returns super demon returns and I guess the Super Mario
Brothers style game from the DS's retro game challenge 2 are different versions
as well so neat and there's also a picture that shows Dr. Wily in there so
I don't know if you could play as him that'd be weird so that's uh that by the
way quickly the chatters are asking for the question or asking for the Star
Wars dance party pictures see all Lincoln yeah Lincoln and then Rama can
get him up on the tumbler for the podcast listeners I want to see it too
disturbing it is a little disturbing just a warning don't click and then
finally apparently there's a rumor that certain and I mean this is probably
gonna be happening certain people that put stuff on the App Store are using
bots to automatically download their games and boost their rankings in the
App Store to get more people to download it I mean I don't even have to really
look into that to know that that's probably true I mean there's people that
put artificially high review scores to boost their reviews and stuff so why not
now is a great time to mention if you want to leave your totally legitimate
five-star reviews for Orange Lounge Radio on the iTunes Store we'd really
appreciate it by the way click the subscribe button four or five times
while you're there I'm kidding maybe I'm not about the five-star reviews though
so all right I I'm not I would not be surprised all by the way looking at some
of those games that are in the top 20 like you really look at like how did
this get here really this game is beating Angry Birds and where's my water
and the stuff you expect to see in the top 10 really interesting speaking of
games you expect to see in the top 10 on the iOS store tiny tower look hate on
this game all you want but it is really fucking addicting and how many addicts
are playing tiny tower 10 million according to a tweet from Ian Marsh the
tweeted this week that 10 million folks have downloaded tiny tower that's on
iOS that's not counting Android or I think that's it it's only also on
Android I believe it has a million daily active users I am no longer an active
player this game I finally quit I stopped the crack a few months ago how
tall is your tower um I know it pales in comparison years I won't say it was like
82 stories or something like that I still have to get the new shops well
actually no I did get the new shops last time I still have the oh that's right
there are new shops huh damn you don't say things like that let me look because
you asked I'm gonna fire up my tiny tower right look at this I haven't
touched this crack in a long time dark soccer did you ever get us sucked into
tiny tower for a little yeah I stopped you finally stopped I stopped it a while
back good for you let's see my tower is I do not want to get the plant game
leave me alone let's see 86 stories tall I was close and my 86th floor for the
record is the nerd cave apartments very cool very cool right above the 85th
floor volleyball because I don't know who puts volleyball on the 85th floor
but there you go huh Bahmani fans are looking forward to a new arcade game
called sound voltex booth this is gonna be playable at the AOU 2012 amusement
Expo it's kind of a new Bahmani game from Konami and there's some new songs
that have been announced for it called Zephyr remix so you might remember
Zephyr from one of the old DDR games a red zone remix and this is gonna be very
cool a vampire killer remix because as you know vampire killer is one of the
big songs from Castlevania so we like it when the Bahmani series kind of jacks
music from other Konami games because let's face it Konami music was awesome
also making its way to AOU an arcade version of dance evolution a new version
of you beat as well and I didn't know this series was still going guitar
freaks and drum mania xg3 I had no idea that series is still alive and kicking
but there you go lastly from me Nintendo of America has hired a new spokesperson
and following in the footsteps of what Carrie Underwood has been a Nintendo
spokesperson Beyonce has been a Nintendo spokesperson who could live up to those
great great musicians how about Oogie Oogie is a Jack Russell Terrier that's
right Nintendo has hired a dog to be their next pose person now to be fair
this dog is very famous because this dog appears in the movie the artist which is
like you know the movie they all say is gonna win the Oscar right I haven't seen
the movie it apparently the dog plays one of those like way too cute roles
that you know it's very memorable and what game will he be pimping guesses
guesses Nintendogs of course Nintendogs we have something to say about that a
second and and and the pearl pink 3ds Oh for the record I found in the
Nintendogs plus cats in the clearance Bennett fries nice how much 14 bucks I'm
not surprised they need to fucking sell those they probably have like tons on
their shelves hey this is just Nintendogs the end there's no cats yeah
all right dark Sakura well how about Sonic Sonic and Sega all-stars racing is
getting a sequel and it will be out it looks like at the end of the year so hey
fun I tried to play it I didn't really care for it and then there is and more
racing news little big planet karting that will be coming out and it was
actually announced via Twitter I think dark Tetsuya said this in the
destination PlayStations where people were at I think our Tetsuya said this in
the mod forums but isn't little big planet karting basically mod nation
racers it is and they actually do have a poster for it that is on the new games
are I think neo gaff forms I think and you know what though yes it is but I
think that this will be more fun I you know what as much as like I want to hate
on this but I can't be why because little big planet seriously is like the
best thing Sony has right now in my opinion I mean I fucking love those
games so the last bit of news has to do with rock band and it's the releases
that are coming out I believe around Valentine's Day so it's the gold star my
heart pack and here is what's on it it's a loan by heart which I freaking want
that song I I want that song are you gonna sing it in the privacy of your own
home I'll sing it with people around if you want to hear me try to break my
voice and there's to be with you by mr. big every rose has its thorn by poison
and the rick rollin song wait you mean I finally have an excuse to do this to the
listeners yes I've been waiting 10 years 10 freaking years never gonna give you
up oh to get trolled by an ad on YouTube oh yeah and for to be with you and every
rose has its thorn it's got pro guitar and bass expansions
delayed punch line
I've noticed that he still looks exactly like that
it's amazing what plastic surgery will do it's a vampire Alan just yelled he
does Alan has that yet he does look a little bit like our Pat he does look a
little bit by the way did you hate that you use that term that is did you know
that that was the most requested rock band song ever I don't care about the
others I went alone I would play that song I would be off what alone no not
alone fucking look I'm talking about fuck you heart is awesome we saw heart I
know we did see heart like two songs because we relate to the concert best
concert lineup ever heart and journey wait does not get it doesn't matter who
opened for heart but what cheep cheep but whatever all right anyhow well
there's been a cat sighting all right we're gonna get back into some longer
news here join us in our chat room chat about orange lounge radio calm if you
are listening live on this Sunday evening I think we finally had cats
seen during the show we had a very vocal Oh Alan says they could smell the lunch
meat there goes that tail there they go they're on out of here the chatters are
talking about the Rick roll Akuma JP says oh this is the end of olr that was
the moment we jump we jump the shark when we Rick rolled all the listeners
there let's see stand in our chat room says Rob should do a karaoke version of
the Rick roll song and use his re-recording as a soundbit for the show
when he wants to fuck sound with fuck around with the audience um no act
deaf in our chat room says forever alone see what he did there forever alone back
to some news Loki all right so the Skyrim creation kit came out this week
with the steam packs and stuff they have a high-resolution texture pack and also
there is a portal cameo apparently you can download an add-on that creates the
space core visiting your game it crashes into it really just goes to show glados
makes everything better and and space space core can be used to craft a helmet
that looks like one of the cores as well that is so awesome it really should have
a thing on the PC where then once you do that quest you get like a costume in
portal 2 for the little dudes and co-op you know there's also a rumor thanks to
someone that was digging around some of the console commands that there's a
quest that's tied to all that too that they haven't unlocked yet that's awesome
um some other cool stuff I want to see our eyes I saw on there they had a mod
that someone made that it was a giant horse and a bunch of people like you
know whacking at it with you know swords and stuff like that and they named you
know Bethesda and valve and stuff like that and it was the arrow and the knee
thing you know they're beating a dead horse huh
Wow okay that's some intellectual humor there right but one of the things so one
of the most popular mods that's actually available on this creation kit service
is something that removes that arrow in the need line from the game so that you
don't have to ever hear that brilliant now the interesting thing about this is
that modding was being done a long time before this even came out yeah now it's
like you know officially embraced but if I know this because I was playing I was
what I wasn't playing I was watching Alan play Skyrim and he zoomed his
character out I'm like Alan why is your person not wearing any clothes
whatsoever I can see her titties I can see her titties and I can see her butt
and Alan's just like no this was legitimately Alan's reaction oh I knew I
forgot to put the armor on I am playing possibly one of the sluttiest games of
Skyrim ever everyone is modded to be like not naked but just and they're in
you know Norway or whatever they all look very cold but yeah everyone's very
sexy and it's some of the some of the male armors that I have have the back
piece missing so they're just their asses hanging out and I'm like this is
hot and they're beating on the dragon like with this ass hanging out yeah but
there's a lot of like stuff that you could do but it required you to move
files and something that the creation kit kind of simplifies all that with
they have a launcher and you basically okay I want this this this this go and
that's why they for anyone playing Skyrim on PC you absolutely have to get
at least sky UI it's a complete UI an inventory replacer and also I think it's
called categorized favorites menu it completely changes the UI which I hated
originally and it's like a different game super awesome
all right unannounced Alan cameo thank you no don't be don't apologize it's
like the minute he heard Skyrim he's like I should come out and make a
sandwich I should take a break from Skyrim to go talk about Skyrim right hey
I heard you like Skyrim so here's some Skyrim while you're sky rimming I really
do wanna I want to get it for my laptop here but I'm playing it on my PC or my
PSR no kids read that 360 right now I love that they did the higher resolution
textures I wish I wish they had that like you know how the outfield through I
understand that for PC oh but I said yeah you know how like battlefield 3 had
a thing where you can install high-res textures to your hard drive I wish they
have that for like the 360 that would be pretty awesome I understand why they
don't but you know Tiger Claw in our chat room says I'm sure the furries are
messing around with the Skyrim mods you'd be surprised the stuff you can
find and it's not safe for work so basically someone has turned Skyrim in
his second life am I understanding this correctly
act-def says I want Skyrim so I can mod it with my little pony stuff I you know
they have that already as much as I I love having Skyrim on the PlayStation
3 is gonna use my controller and all that I have to admit I am somewhat
starting to regret not getting it on PC the minute I saw that macho man dragon
mod if you had a J tag you can do that well wasn't the PlayStation supposed to
get some of the popular community mods at some point yeah yeah they had that
whole steam integration think that they use for one game that was fucking awesome
I think though I think but we now that modding is officially embraced and now
that things can be officially signed off by Bethesda maybe that's a possibility
down the line I don't know maybe not gonna happen I don't know never say
never there'll be a fee but never say never and well the other thing I was
gonna say is you know I don't know if you saw but like they had a whole a I
don't know what they called it was a Bethesda kind of hey team members make
whatever you want during a week and then show us what you have for Skyrim so they
were able to make whatever mod they want and they came up with a whole bunch of
cool shit that they could have could have thrown in there but oh we couldn't
give them another week to do what they want you know because that would be you
know too awesome they have like Spears they had a giant enemy crab yeah and
giant enemy crab all sorts of you know improvements seasonal changes stuff like
that it's just amazing Lee there's some silence to one in our
chat room says Oda Ving is rainbow bright best mod right there what I guess
you can change one of the characters in a rainbow bright why have naked people
when you can have 80s cartoon nostalgia why not have both you're sick well I'm
not saying rainbow brain has to be naked but you can have naked people and you
can have rainbow bright I don't know I don't know I feel awkward this is an
awkward covers I want to be able to have all these different dragons like I want
to have a macho man dragon I want to have these you know my little pony
dragon I want to have I don't know what other dragons they have out there and
you know maybe you know maybe a family got Peter Griffin dragon or something
like that or I want to have a mod that makes one of my companions Loki and he
always just yells he's really like he always gets really irritated like why
are you doing that and then it kids like shout and they can shout and knock
people away I'd be awesome all right I don't know why Loki didn't have this
story because it's more relevant to his interest but I'll read it and then Loki
can react to it eat sleep play who is the developer behind twisted metal which
you know remember the series was like big back in the day and now it's all
nostalgic against I don't even know what they're doing with this game to be honest
there's a there's a new one coming out like what this week I do want to get it
but we'll see maybe I'll get it well according to the Salt Lake City Tribune
David Jaff is not with eat sleep play anymore he left the company and he's off
to pursue casual games yes that worked so well the last time he responded and
called it highly exaggerated but he didn't deny that he left so apparently
there's been reductions and all this stuff David Jaff did confirm that
following the release of twisted metal he is going to step away from eat sleep
play there have been layoffs these this affects the offices in Utah which is
interesting because David Jaff lives in California but he did mention that the
directing a game from a distance and all that did take its toll so that's not
good when the game I mean well I don't know I it's easy to sit here and say oh
that looks bad but at the same time it's also very common in the industry when a
game is done for there to be layoffs so but I guess this means they aren't
starting work on a sequel right away he said there's gonna be no DLC zero DLC
for it interesting I don't know if that's a good thing or a bad thing I
mean part of me is like well doing good it's all on the disc but then I'm like
oh wait maybe it's bad because that means they're just putting it out there
yeah there's gonna be aside from like I think the pre-order bonus that you can
get you know for me a prior in the game aside from that there is going to be no
DLC for twisted mill none they're just sticking around long enough to do like
any game balancing and bugs that may they've they may not have caught and
that's it once that patch is done they're done interesting all right well
there's that so we'll see what this game has in store I don't know I'm not
hearing good things about it which is kind of disappointing Loki you're still
gonna get in on it just because you love the old ones we'll see all right let's
go to the email email bag mailbag at orange lounge radio.com is where we
invite your emails each and every week we read them on the show dark soccer
dives in the mailbag headfirst again that's mailbag at orange lounge radio
calm dear llr crew after a long time of not listening and my only other podcast
bit the dust I decided to run back to you for my gaming news fix in the
college budget where I can no longer afford a subscription to magazines so
this is to you my new favorite number one podcast on my PSP I would say iPod
but some jackass dumb shit who took an arrow to the knee of their knowledge
stole that from me along with my 3ds ds light and FM transmitter the DS I had I
marked with my girlfriend's initials taped over with duct tape and had an r4
flash card with all of my DS backups and old old-school ROMs and my 3ds I had a
lot of these punctuation please I had a lot of 90s pop and DDR OSTs on the SD
card was super glued in and locked in with a flap of duct tape if he or she is
listening give me back my stuff you bitch
sadly it sounds like someone knew you had all that stuff in your case peace
out ds lover so I want to know who we bumped off to become number one ds
lover didn't say which podcast I want to know who we bumped off to be number one
next email all right yes stop it right now no she's gone to join her career
stop it read the next email dear dearlings with the non holiday holiday
coming up on Tuesday I was wondering if I could get some Valentine's Day video
game recommend recommendations out of you the game I'm looking for should be
one of the following a a romantic game a game with a realistic portrayal of
romance that is pulled off in a convincing manner not something where
the characters are driven by wanting to engage in hot monkey sex rather a game
where the characters are motivated by wanting to engage in a truly enriching
enriching romantic relationship or be a game to play while drunk a game that is
ideal to play while you are drunk drunk drunk drunk drunk not a game to play
while blackout drunk rather a game to play while borderline blackout drunk
stay black entertainment this message has been apricot hefeweizen from west
wasatch beers it's like fruit that gets you drunk sent from my iPad um and I
have a game love plus I was gonna say Catherine I was gonna say Catherine
actually or a girl gun gal gun if it's true love you can play rock band
together all night long get Catherine if it's single love then it's self-love
it's self-love then it's gonna be the guy game first oh my god I haven't heard
of that game in like six years wasn't that game banned because there was a
17 year old naked it oh yeah we don't know which one metal gear metal gear
solid cuz remember love can bloom on the battlefield they can all be under a love
is a battlefield no if there's a line snake can love bloom on the battlefield
rdg singe in our chat room suggests laser shoot Larry three that's a good
suggestion a boy the mansion get Catherine did okay is what was it self
love or was it duo love a game with realistic portrayal of romance that is
pulled off in a convincing manner really not where the characters are driven by
wanting to engage in hot monkey sex I'm trying to think of any like I got to say
hot monkey sex a lot there's there's like there's a the Tokimeki games donkey
Kong Final Fantasy 8 what can I do for you no just I don't just get Catherine
what was that really oh god was it on the PSP Brooktown and if you want to
play a game while you're drunk that's just gonna piss you off you'll never be
able to find that game no if you want a game that's just gonna piss you off
while you're drunk plate irritating stick move next email I like
entertainment the get the chatters are kind of agreeing with the Catherine
selection okay this is from the ECA put out a call to action to discover state
laws relating to EULA they used some of the verbiage from my previous inquiry to
Maryland's consumer protection office blows what appears to be another canned
response and only the first two sentences seem remotely related to my
email what makes this cool is letter I sent to OLR a couple of months which
Jamie read was used as a basis for the official ECA letter you see I confirmed
that they liked parts of the letter enough to include in their letter this
is the first time I ever influenced something so countrywide but also Canada
except of course OLR mailbag which is clearly worldwide the goal of this
letter-writing campaign is to establish what the current laws for each state are
and then maybe we can start talking about changing it I suggest sending the
ECA letter to your state legislators as well as the Attorney General of your
respective state this may boil down to actually having to hire a business law
lawyer to find out and that's from rubber so his email was used in the his
letter was basically turned into the form letter for the ECA go you you a
celebrity a winner is you you like Whitney I mean stop it right now party
fell okay we have two emails left two more emails shut up I'm the one reading
them I've been seeing a lot of forum members upset at Sony not bringing the
UMD transfer program to North America forgive me if I'm oversimplifying this
or misunderstanding something they're upset because they have to pay Sony to
repurchase the content they already bought on UMD as Vita digital contact
instead of having to pay Sony to repurchase the contact they already
bought on UMD as Vita digital content well they wanted the discount I'll be it
for slightly less in some cases if the UMD game has a digital version and the
publisher is participating as for me I'm not really in the market for another
handheld quite yet I did get a PSP for Christmas been on my list for a while
mostly to check out games that aren't on ps3 like the Powerstone collection and
before that replaced my iPod classic when it's hard drive gave out with a
touch so I doubt I'll be getting a Vita or 3ds anytime soon stay staying Robert
M all right and last email I have like two UMD games anyways because I sold the
rest off I'd have like some of the Grand Theft Auto games I actually have a bunch
yeah I have quite a few all my cue entertainment games every extend extra
but we also have a PSP so greetings olr it's your friendly neighborhood turtle I
have a somewhat odd question please don't take this the wrong way your show
is my absolute favorite among video game podcasts hence my question can you
mention any other video game podcasts that you like or listen to the caveat I
want to know about other shows besides what's on the all games network I used
to like Derek but there's way too much cursing for my liking why do I like oh
why do I ask all our this question wait a minute though I do like oh alert I know
I was gonna say hold on cuz we curse a lot on this show so that I okay okay I
need to step it up what the fuck is your problem dude well I'm a carpenter and
choose to work by myself all day and need good stuff to listen to which means
that every Monday morning I start out my week with olr but by lunch I'm out of
video game related material any shows that you'd like I'm sure to like keep up
the best podcast on air you guys are a great way to start out each week also
being on the right coast I never knew what pinkberry is but after looking at
their website I am extremely jealous you guys are awesome your loyal turtle in
Philly serious turtle it's sort of God we need to start charging for all the
product placement we just give away on this show thank me um well thank you I
mean that's that's quite the compliment I don't see that as a negative at all
that they're looking at us for recommendations for other shows because
I'm looking at my like the ultimate compliment see here's the thing I listen
to a lot of stuff that's not video game related whatsoever and the stuff that is
video game related is kind of all game shows yeah you mentioned Derek's dead
pixel a lot I think that's what he was talking about that because alive I you
know that's a good I like it I don't think there's that I like fantastic
forum uh-huh I I really like video game outsiders yeah and they they have a they
have a rhythm very similar to ours um not so much lately I think they I think
they've been challenged because I think the hosts are starting to kind of go
their own ways but when they're together it's a good time and John does his best
to keep it together I listen to Horde house well Horde house no comment right
now but there there's gonna be some things changing I think um let's see
other video game podcasts of course Bobby black wolf of course that's just a
given we like him but he has an updated podcast feed in a while
naughty boy so even if I told you to listen to him you couldn't get his
newest shows stuff that's off the all games network there's not a lot of video
game podcasts that I've actually see here's the thing are you well I try to
listen to others and I don't like them so I don't want to name them but there's
one in particular I really tried to listen to and I just and it's an
independent show so that's what I really want to support other independent shows
but we'll say it's a it was a very slickly produced independent show and
the person behind it does a lot of podcasts on iTunes but I just wasn't
in um it's a video podcast but I guess so that wouldn't really work but I like
occasionally watching episodes of the Ben Heck show well I'll throw on some of
the video game YouTube ones when I when I was at work I would check out the
angry video game nerd on my phone just by plugging in on YouTube and I like
classic game room that was one of my favorites let me give a shout out to a
few that I'm subscribed to that I actually whipped out my phone and I'm
looking at some others that I'm subscribed to of course I I subscribe to
under sedation live yeah which is you know sci-fi and stuff Travis you know
that's the show I started on our own Rama has a podcast of course anime jam
session if you're into that pod culture I got to give a shout out to my buddy
Brad over at pod culture if you like the sci-fi geeky stuff let me put it this
way the TARDIS shows up like in nine tenths of the artwork so you know if
you're if you're a Doctor Who fan you're gonna love pod culture couple people are
saying the bomb cast I haven't tried that one myself I know a lot of folks
are big fans of giant bomb though I really love smartest man in the world by
Greg Proops yes but if you're not into swearing I think it's still really funny
but just just warning you well there's two that I listen to and they're both
from I'm gonna have to look at look it up again but one of them is stuff mom
never told you that's really just interesting tidbits things that you know
you might not know and the other one is it's from how stuff works and one of
them is a things you never learned in history class and two others I want to
name real quick here of course girls gone Wow the lovely sill out of the UK
if since there is you know horde house is on a horde hiatus right now girls
gone Wow is a great place to get your fix girl on guy with Aisha Tyler but see
I love Aisha Tyler like you know I'm totally gay but Aisha Tyler she's pretty
hot and she's really intelligent a total geek so I've met her before did you
really yeah what'd you think of her she she's alright was she hot in person I
think she's real I think she's really hot she's attractive because she's kind
of got the she's got a little bit of the geez oh she's very geeky you know that
she plays like Gears of War and all that stuff and if you listen to her podcast
she's had some great episodes she had Greg Proops on she had Margaret Cho on
she had Chris Hardwick on she she came in pimping some movies she was in I
don't remember what it was yeah but she's interesting yeah so I did
podcat that's a good idea all right there you go I think we've given you
plenty of suggestions we could probably name a million more but I mean that was
the ones I named were off my personal iPod I do listen to all those there's
one other that I listen to it's not video game but you know me and my
history love there is history of the world through a hundred objects that's
put out by the BBC and the Museum of History in London actually if you like
history that was a really freaking good one and even though the the guy sounds a
little too posh for my taste but other than that it's a really good one you
know me I listen to all of the informational ones and the stuff that's
gonna teach you something that in video game ones so but hopefully this help and
that was last email all right anyhow let's move on past the mailbag this is
the part of the show where we get angsty sometimes we get a little bit angry here
at orange launch radio and we do a segment called the F use of the week so
here it is
fu to the increased cost of tuition and people who only want you to have a
bachelor's degree and fu to all the morons driving with their lights off in
the rain and not signaling in the rain
stupid not signaling in the rain signaling in the rain low-key your
nephews so my a few goes to Jack in the Box for pushing this milkshake that has
no bacon in it seriously I mean come on you can't even put like a little you
can't sprinkle a little bit of bacon bits on top you know because it is a
bacon milkshake and you know whatever it it is what it is I guess I'll have to
make my own bacon ice cream wasn't bad so milkshake the work
their sandwich looks weak to their like BLT sandwich I'm like yeah lettuce and
tomato and pickle and garbage I mean this is a regular burger sorry that the
chats a little bit behind you know that's too tense to happen there's a bit
of a buffer because you know we send the signal to all games who sends it to all
of you and there's time involved with that act after our chat goes blame it on
the rain I think that was in response to your F you dark Sakura who just had
desk alright you okay dark Sakura alright my a few of the week wait
where's the F you music alright my a few the week F you to that noise after all
these years I still hate that it's so old like saw the garage all right dead a
lot of people I bet we're getting to the point now where people were born after
that movie you know it's gonna know what you're talking about all right why she
sound like a creaky door I don't get it and no my real if you that do not
distract from my real F you of the week because this is serious business my F you
the week goes to parking lots I hate them oh so much no dude dude dude dude I
went to the mall Arden fair two o'clock yesterday yesterday Saturday that was
the dumbest thing I could have ever done in my life that mall was more crowded
than it is on Christmas like what is that Black Friday it was more crowded
than it was a Black Friday and just stupid people jumping in front of cars
driving slowly it got to the point we drove around the parking lot twice
couldn't find a place to park went up to the second floor of the parking
structure where nobody ever parks every space if there was taken and I said fuck
it and went home park across the street that's what I used to do we park at
Hooters oh no in that lot where nobody there's like fucking nothing there now
huh yep where they used to have the club the nightclub yeah exactly used to park
across the street right there next to the sidewalk hit the crosswalk by the
time you like cross the street and stuff you'll it seriously I used to go to
Virgin over there it was awesome I'm a mega store yeah sad
it's urban outfitters now it's all right urban outfit like some of their shirts
they sell Michelle's book do you know what you know what I bought huh at that
virgin what my activator nice for the Genesis with oh what was that game I
used to get import CDs at Virgin that's where I would go there for mm-hmm all
right anyhow and then the internet all right let's move on more news and
skype line coming up very soon Twitter topics as well tons of fun stuff coming
up very very very very soon Loki yeah I was gonna say fuck you to your parking
lot too cuz I have a park in like the mill nowhere the hike back to my car if
I remember where it is so call duty elite it's pretty popular for Activision
they've have 7 million users using the elite service on the 1.5 million have
actually paid the you know $60 for or $50 I think it is for all the free well
plenty of the paid for the download content so $50 times 100 or 1.5 million
times that's a lot of fucking money 75 million dollars and people thought who
would want to sign up for this service well to be honest if you're gonna pay
for the download content you're actually saving money with that service and if
you play a lot of Call of Duty that might be worth it to you I mean the
maps don't look bad I just don't play Call of Duty modern warfare 3 so I don't
use the service at all now I don't think it ties in with modern warfare so the
first one it does it looks like it's doing well for them they made lots of
money do you are they gonna do another one of those Expos this year like they
did last year they might I don't know this didn't that do really well for him
too because there's no BlizzCon this year but there might be the whole Call
of Duty con or what did they call that like the I forget the name somebody in
shadow yell it out but they did like a day long event remember so I could see
them I mean I could see them doing that so because it worked out you know pretty
well for them of course there's gonna be another call it yeah I saw yeah they
announced that they're gonna make another Call of Duty game you don't even
have to put that in the fucking you do not have to announce that at all that it
was part of their you know their financial report or something like that
that they're making new Call of Duty game of course they're gonna fucking
make a new Call of Duty game it's news when they say we're not making the Call
of Duty game we're not having a BlizzCon I mean it's just you know you don't even
need to report that people just make the assumption that there's gonna be a new
Call of Duty game coming out speaking of that Activision Blizzard earnings call
that happened this week very surprising that they announced there's no release
date still for Diablo 3 which we thought for sure we'd have that by the end of
next month but now it's looking like no cute summertime Q2 is what they're
saying if America will Starcraft not a Starcraft
probably buggy Starcraft I'm in the beta it's great well then I they just hate
you clearly Starcraft is you know launched in the end of July so that was
kind of an odd time for it I mean less yeah no no date well speaking of Diablo
3 my next story happens to be about Diablo 3 Bashiach who's the community
manager over at Blizzard was answering some questions and it wasn't about
Warcraft this time it was about Diablo 3 they say Diablo 3 it is still slated for
2012 but now they're saying that Diablo 3 is only going to support up to four
players even though there is five classes now that's four player co-op
they haven't said anything about a five player mode in the game Bashiach said
that Blizzard is not looking into it and they're not going to expand their player
cap no idea as to why they did that interesting because in World of Warcraft
you have if I'm not mistaken you have 10 classes and raids are 10 people or 25 or
you know but most you know the end game content is geared towards that although
you would find very very very few raid groups that have one of each class very
few Diablo 3 also will not have built-in voice chat at launch Blizzard wants to
make sure the voice chat is going to be worth it the wow voice chat leaves a lot
to be desired so it turned a lot of people to you know team speak ventrilo
mumble so Diablo 3 is going to have to do the same thing they're also one of
the thing Diablo 3 is not going to be getting any more visual treatment than
what you're already seeing there is no higher resolution textures in the final
game that's the official word from Bashiach I still thought the game looked
good enough on look in fact to look great on the beta so I don't think they
necessarily need to make it that much better you know again part of the charm
of Diablo is that you know be able to be played on a variety of systems if you
want to be able to find four people to co-op with I'm still really looking
forward to Diablo 3 despite all this I just wish it would come out already I
get a free copy because I signed the Blizzard blood pact for World of
Warcraft because I have problems few more news stories for you guys and then
the Twitter topics in the skype line dark soccer well did you ever watching
that pac-man show in the 80s I can I do that's where pac-man had legs right yeah
yes I do remember that well I also the pac-land game was based off of that too
and I used to also watch that in cupid but Hannah Barbara put it out well
they're four seasons coming out on DVD it's a two-disc 13 episode collection
where it has inky and blinky pinky Clyde and Sue and mesmer on who wants to take
over pac-land and has vampire pakula and all kinds of yeah I forgot about
pac-land that was a really interesting game it was kind of like a side
scroller pac-man I have it yeah no I've it's in those Namco collections like the
you know the ones that tend to come out on every system but I used to I also
remember the Christmas special where Santa came down they had no idea what a
human was yeah nice I had the pac-man board game growing up and it had like a
million marbles it was all these fucking marbles that were little pellets I have
the bedsheets awesome I bet it had remember miss pac-man was called pepper
and there was pac-baby yeah nice I like super pac-man dude the arcade game for
super pac-man is awesome anyhow Loki you know it's always great when you start
off the story with a sigh it should not be a surprise that they're making
another Skylanders game I mean really didn't you say this game was gonna tank
yeah it should have tanked I underestimated how stupid the average
consumer is my mistake and you know what if you bought this game you have
yourself to blame this is why you're gonna get fucking expensive down I do I
do not want to hear another fucking thing about oh those map packs are call
of duty are too expensive this is your fucking fault for buying
Skylanders this is why no more can you complain about DLC costs or the quantity
so yes Skylanders Giants because hey how can we make Skylanders better I don't
notice make larger figures that we could charge more for sounds like a plan bigger
is better people will buy them because they're consumer whores and how so yes
Skylanders Giants will be coming out later this year I think also for the Wii
U probably at some point and I gotta be honest by looking at the screenshots
which this game itself kinda looks like it could have been on the GameCube or
the PlayStation 2 I mean pretty cheap I've heard good things about the game
itself just the game not all this extra crap at the game itself I've heard
decent things as a decent dungeon crawler it looks pretty cheap anyways so
you can't go off the only the only thing they're changing is they're adding these
giant fucking characters that do stuff and their money but hey guess what
they're not going to force you to buy another goddamn portal you can still use
your old portal so they're just gonna be twice as many skews I got a fucking set
up thank God for that and it's so we're gonna have these giant fucking portal
characters that you have to use with your regular Skylanders characters and
I'm sure they're gonna have more characters go along with that and yeah
so that's fantastic and I want to say they were the number one accessory item
for games this month so congrats to you Skylanders for me I'm selling a lot and
then of course there's going to be some Toys R Us exclusive items because they
have signed a fucking blood pact with Activision to pimp these two children so
once again I hope you're happy because you you folks that purchase Skylanders
are going to be the downfall of the gaming industry when the inevitable
video game crash happens was by the way there's big rumblings we're headed
towards another video game crash because think about it if the Wii U and the Vita
don't do very well it could lead to another crash and if the Wii U and the
Vita don't do well people are just going to buy games the PlayStation 3 and the
Xbox 360 oh the world will end but I don't know things I'm reading I don't
think anything could ever happen to the extent that it happened with Atari but
if you look at the sales dude sales this January were way down compared to a year
ago there's nothing coming out in January I'm not surprised they had they
had one week of sales because all the game releases for January came out the
last still have holdovers and people using their gift cards and all that
but see normally January like last year January they had Darksiders which came
out like in the first week they had Bayonetta they had actually been under
my bed in the year before it was I think I think Bayonetta was a year before okay
well one of these January's had Darksiders and Bayonetta and you know
Alan was saying to me the other day why haven't they announced a sequel to
Bayonetta yet it's a very good question it did well then of course there's a
whole a Metal Gear game that now is basically no Metal Gear Bayonetta the
Metal Gear game will come out eventually rebooted it totally rebooted it alright
so yes Skylander Giants hip hip hooray one more story for you guys here and
then we're gonna go to the Skype line and this one is also going to start off
with a sigh sorry I gotta interrupt real quick here so yeah remember how I was
saying that they're gonna have some exclusive stuff some of the characters
they've run out of you know they have the legendary characters which sell for
a lot more on eBay that's how you know how they're special and also they have
now iridescent blue characters so they're like and we're not even gonna
paint this one we're just gonna make it clear plastic and people spend more
money for it alright I got one more story for you guys then we're gonna get
to the sky plane and your Twitter topics so just a reminder here's your last
chance to get those Twitter topics into twitter.com slash o LR this story is
about another sigh huge sigh Ubisoft I I can't with this this is the whole DRM
thing okay and you know they've gotten a lot of shit about this whole I thought
they I thought that Ubisoft got rid of this DRM when the people started being
up in arms about it but I guess that was just like moving forward and what I'm
talking about is the whole you have to be online to play the game and if you
get kicked offline you get kicked out of the game well what happened is that
Ubisoft had to do an online server switch this past week and it locked
people out of the games now granted they warned people you know this is gonna be
happening so you won't be able to play your fucking game for a day the game
that you bought it won't work for a day because we were too lazy to have a
backup server in place or however these technical things work meaning driver
San Francisco and so forth was unable to be signed into however driver San
Francisco was not one of the games that Ubisoft originally said you will not be
able to play so extra games got taken down on top of what Ubisoft originally
said some games were still okay like Just Dance 3 and settlers online via
Twitter Ubisoft says we apologize for the inconvenience it seems some of you
can't connect to games announced as playable during migration we're on it
and we'll keep you posted here in related news those that pirated these
games experience no issues I don't think Just Dance would be part of it because
that's not I think I think it was after the fact to no one gets to wiggle their
but how about Assassin's Creed revelations there you go I think it's
only PC tiles yeah so but but am I correct in saying Ubisoft does not not
do this anymore right they will they don't care you're still gonna buy the
next Assassin's Creed game people you're not gonna remember that they even did
this I'm not but then again I hadn't bought by any of the others like does
anyone remember the snafu with the whole like PlayStation Network where they
they forgot to calculate a date correctly or something like that and so
it knocked everything offline for like a day no one remembers that that's true
that's true I remember the big fuss people made about that I wonder how many
people forgot about the PlayStation hack by now I'm sure a lot of people have
already forgotten a whole little PlayStation Network thing all right we
are about ready to go to the skype line so go ahead one eight seven seven game OLR
or our username on skype is orange lounge radio we're gonna go to the skype
line it's already lighting up people are ready to call in and get through so
let's go to the phones right now hi you're on orange lounge radio who's this
hey this is Oscar what's up hey is it did you say it's a suka what
ask us it's Oscar and a suka it's kind of weird but I respond to both it's all
good it's a little bit of both well guys you never know what kind of folks are
gonna call into orange lounge radio now we've been chatting a little bit this
week so I think I think it's really cool that you're actually you're actually
listening to the show and calling in tonight yeah it's a good buddy stand if
it thanks for that he introduced me to OLR and I'm loving it so far thank you
so much thank you Stan now for those that don't know who you are is there a
place where folks may or may not have been seeing you this week yes um I
actually appeared on the new season of the tester on the PlayStation Network I
can't believe it guys after all this okay I I don't know if you know about
some of our running jokes if Stan feels you in about the tester but when I
originally gave my review on the tester season one way back when I talked about
the tester and I actually said the tester is not bad like it's it's it's
not like a great freakin show it's not like you know you're gonna be watching
The Walking Dead or something but right as far as reality TV goes as far as a
lot of the old g4 shows go the tester is not bad but as I'm talking about this
Jamie's cat because we were doing the show at her house Shermie took a big
dump all over the floor and so I think well there's Shermie's review well
actually it's quite fitting because for those that might have seen the first
episode Quajimonster gotten some deep shit literally because she started
talking about farting and shitting and yeah what works what is up with this
okay I gotta say I made a tweet right after I watched the first episode cuz
you I look I love video games and I love trashy reality TV so I'm not gonna lie I
did watch the tester all right judge me all you want I don't give a fuck all
right it's not as bad as being on the tester trust me wow we've got to get
into this a little bit but okay okay but here's the thing I'm watching it and I'm
like these they all have potty mouths it was like watching there was an episode
of South Park called it hits the fan where they hype up in the whole episode
dude they're gonna say shit on Chicago hope tonight they're gonna say shit and
then like it turns into they say one shit to now it's like mush shit TV and
they say the word shit like 200 times and I'm watching the first episode of
tester and I hear shit dropped like literally 1520 times during the show my
game you hear me go that's bullshit and there's there is an awesome story about
that it's in regards to what somebody said so might stop by next week to talk
about it it's a good story but yeah there's a lot of shit being dropped left
and right Wow but yet they bleep fuck I don't know sorry to the guy who didn't
like cursing I'm very sorry but you know it's just look they say it on PlayStation
Network all right yeah for real you you were actually on the tester and it's
funny because we joked about getting dark soccer to apply next year I applied
a little bit of a whim and I actually the reason I decided to go for the
tester was way back when sci-fi did WCG ultimate gamer I said why not I'll try I
made it to like the final 42 people and didn't make that show because apparently
I wasn't like cool enough so screw them and then the tester started applying or
started the application process for season three I said why not next I know
I'm getting a phone call saying yeah we're flying you out to Los Angeles and
you're gonna be on the tester like oh shit you just got picked like there
wasn't a lot of like screening and whittling down there's it's the whole
process starts in about there started about mid August I want to say and I put
up a profile really quickly I said you know I need to think of what what's
gonna get me noticed I figured okay how many people are the combination of a
chemist plays roller derby and has like a trophy level of 18 not many so I use
that and then within a day of putting that up I had a producer calling me say
hey you want to do some interviews with you check you out and then the Skype
interview had to wait a month of like no contact from them and then all of a
sudden mid-october I get a call from the executive producer saying yeah you're
still in the running here's a contract sign your life away once to do that
we'll do another interview and I found out I was flying to LA about mmm four or
five days before filming began so it's a long process but just a lot of
interviews and waiting but I get the sense that the whole process of
recording the show itself is really quick like you know I know there's a lot
of TV magic but you know I could kind of tell that they're probably doing like
multiple challenges in a day and the whole no actually no really no it's
every episode is literally one day of filming huh it's back to back to back
to back about like 15 18 hours worth of filming crammed into one little half
hour Wow there's a lot of awesomeness but they try to keep the drama and my
case a picture of a cockroach trying to go like ass to mouth to me which was
great now because I know Loki and don't start a dark soccer don't watch the
tester this week the challenge no no no I saw do you watch I was a night and I
had a joke ready too so basically I'm like say be glad that they're just you
know you know they're they're doing the analogy where it's you know you have to
keep your head in a case of bugs you know because you're squashing bugs or
whatever thank God you're not testing for Bethesda where you'd have to jump in
a fun swimming pool full of cockroaches well the thing is if you're testing for
Bethesda there would be no bugs because apparently they don't see them when they
test them they just leave them in the game you know my honest-to-god reaction
when I saw that on the show though I said dark soccer would have been first
out she would have been first out she put your hand no they had to they had to
have their head in this case full of bugs and they're pouring cockroaches
because because they wanted to see who can interview under pressure and I was
like dark soccer would have been telling that guy off like I put my head no bugs
well what's funny is like we have our this one guy Jay Titan he's this big
rough-and-tough trash talk and like knows the shit and then as soon as we
find out it's the roaches we go back into the loft as they're doing us they're
doing each person for the challenge one at a time he starts freaking out back in
the loft like scream I quit and he was probably one of the next to last people
to go and all of us are coming back oh it's fine you'll be fine he's almost
starting to like shake from nervousness he's that terrified of bugs so that
would have been me I would have been crying I would have been screaming I
would have been threatening calls to my lawyer but then I would have just done
it you know I would have been like alright just fucking get in the zone
don't think about it don't think about it don't think I'm fucking thinking
about it don't think about it like the hardest part was just well for me I the
way they fell down my hair started going in my face so I had like at one point
almost a dozen roaches just checking out my face like you know I'm gonna sit
right in front of her so she can't see anything you know it would freak them
out you start munching off actually actually we were totally weren't allowed
to eat them ah there was like this roach wrangler or this guy that owned the
roaches and they were his like precious little babies and we couldn't do any
harm to him what was his name Joe and did he have an apartment I wouldn't be
surprised if it's probably him the only one that remembers Joe's apartment I
remember Joe's apartment singing roaches so I I have to I I know there's probably
tons you want to talk about but of course I I'm gonna steer the
conversation but I'm take over I felt bad for the girl they sent home I get
oh I shouldn't ruin it for those that watched it my bad but I I like that the
person that they sent home seemed I don't agree with that I completely
disagree with sending the person they sent home she that person seemed really
nice to me and I was like that seemed I'm surprised that person's not
listening to OLR cuz like that seemed like the kind of person that would like
be like I would be friends with like for real so I kind of felt bad for them
she's like she was the one of the coolest cats in the loft I mean like she
just the first thing we noticed by her she had this giant like tail that she
brought with and okay you're awesome and actually we were aligned or we were
getting into the vans to head to the law for filming she originally had on this
Voltron t-shirt that they took away from her because you couldn't like have
copyrighted material that wasn't first party Sony cuz wah wah wah whatever but
I'm just looking at going I like her so we spent a good like our just talking
about Voltron and it's I was so sad to see her go and considering it was either
like the person that either didn't like wasn't memorable the person that talked
about shit the whole time but that's home the person talked about shit that
that's just me that's reality TV I'm kind of you know I'm kind of looking at
it going you know it sounds like you are the real deal you're legit your
intentions I mean am I correct you really did want to work for Sony right
like oh my god yeah they're in a later episode you'll see just how much I I
would have killed or I did I get my dream job it's like I can't really say
which way how or which way it fell but right sure no I understand and listeners
please do respect that she's under contract can't say if she wins or got
told to sashay away sued so yeah all five people that watch the show I mean I
don't know like it's kind of a joke that like no one watches the tester but yet
here I am I I I admit I watch it and you know I gotta say all joking aside what
they're doing there is interesting because it really is the only show right
now that I can think of that's produced exclusively for a gaming console you
don't have anything like it on Nintendo you don't have anything like it
otherwise on Sony you'd certainly don't have anything like it on Xbox especially
since one versus a hundred isn't around anymore which was a different kind of
thing anyway right but no it it's I mean like I said they originally did that
that the BC ultimate gamer but that kind of flopped after two seasons but even
then it wasn't entirely Xbox I think season two had some we crap in it that
no one cared about but yeah it's when I tell people that it's exclusively on
PlayStation Network you can't download the episodes on your computer via the
tester calm or crackle calm but yeah just the fact that it's produced by Sony
for Sony promoting Sony it's very unique in that sound so here's a question
though Rob is since you mentioned crackle calm crackle they have the
actual utility on or the app on the 360 so could you watch a tester on the 360
can actually watch the tester on the 360 I've tried it and it is possible so yeah
I kind of got a personal kick a lot of that zenacorn our term is do you have to
pay to see the tester no it's it's no we free trust me would you want to pay to
see the tester I love that you're deprecated I I don't know I again I know
you can't tell me which way but the way you talk about it sometimes makes me
think it might not a one just looking at the first episode there it's supposed to
be a double elimination but it wasn't a little bit of spoiler there but it was a
single elimination and with who was clearly supposed to go home when he or
she didn't that pissed me off like throwing a little shade Lee bullshit
what happened there so I'm getting I'm getting the sense that maybe you're
you're still kind of friends with some of these folks like maybe the person we
were talking about earlier who got kicked off before their time but maybe
not with yeah I we have this like yes I talked she's actually going to a like a
giant world cosplay competition so good luck to her but um yeah we have this
secret tester we call it the tester lounge on fake book as I call it because
Facebook is but yeah like people from all three seasons Brent go keys in it
Meredith Adrian side note Meredith knows her shit about games like it surprised
all of us how much she knew about it so that was awesome but yeah we we talk all
the time and as a matter of fact once the cast was announced Mo chocolate from
season 2 reached out to all of us it's like whoa what's up my mo nice to meet
you let's video chat on Skype and I'm just going oh my god you're you were
you're Mo chocolate and you're talking to me holy crap and we've become the
best of friends since then so it's pretty cool that is that is awesome what
sounds like you at the end of the day you know no matter what's happening on
the show you you good or bad you had a good experience and you met a lot of
great people out of it sounds like so oh my god it I it's something that I could
never like forget I mean I never thought I would be doing something like that
efforts I'm not the most outgoing person I'm a gamer I'm a little bit shy a
little bit of a closet dweller but it just blew my mind in terms of
awesomeness and oh my god I look on the TV that I've muted and it's Whitney
Houston changing that's why people watch the tester to get away from CNN and the
witness that's it we need to hang out I had to catch a predator on and then all
of a sudden it became Whitney Houston I'm like I can't see the sake but let's
turn on something equally that's what I have you know what's funny and I swear
I'm not just I I swear I'm not just saying this because I had no idea that
you were gonna read like I know Stan had told me like hey I know someone on the
show and I was like okay cool like I didn't I guess you guys must be pretty
close because here you are actually listening to orange lounge radio but at
first I was like oh neat it's kind of fun to know somebody who got to do you
know a rare experience like that but when when I saw you specifically on the
show I actually thought I was like that's the girl they have instead of
dark Sakura I really did I really think that because you guys kind of strike me
as having stuff in common so well maybe I'll do it next year if I don't have a
job I had a job or have have had a job as a chemist so they even asked me would
you be okay with giving up your current job I said hmm work in a lab or work at
Santa Monica let me think yes yes I would be okay with that okay thanks I'm
a designer so I was like I can do all of your booklets it's a good way to get
your foot in the door as I understand the the guy that won the very first
season was only like a tester for like what six months and now he's like in
marketing or something and I know that guy isn't the whole six months thing is
what they don't tell you is it's for a six month contract mmm it's so like
kicking the groin cuz after Meredith like tells about the prize that you
could win you're all excited and they cut the scene then this one random crew
member comes out and they go alright this is just a reminder the prizes you
got the ps3 the money the TV blah blah blah blah and just you know the job as a
tester is a six-month contract at which point somebody may or may not keep you
okay keep filming all going and the same thing for this season it's like the
Santa Monica thing six-month contract and then the cars for two-year lease all
right let's see some enthusiasm cars going funny Wow no stand in the chat
says I'm sure Rob thought I was making stuff up no I didn't think you were
making stuff up I just thought you know some like sometimes like you you might
know somebody like oh I knew I went to high school with that person and after
the six-month period we're gonna have your memory erased just look into this
pen let me put on my sunglasses oh god um let's god what else was I gonna ask
I know something escapes me I don't know it was just one episodes aired and I'm
sure there's plenty more you've really got to bite your tongue on but we'll
well hopefully you'll decide to keep listening to olr and we can get some
more dirt on the tester I look we're probably the only podcast that talks
about this show there's a few out there actually totally don't want to plug it
but kind of have to since Greg Miller was a guest judge this season sure he's
actually having all of the cast members as they're booted off the show on the
beyond podcast so all right whatever I get kicked off or when I win I'll be on
there and I'll I'll see if I can put in a well our show for you guys that's
awesome see you know you don't have to say the final thing that kept me from
applying really was that I don't want to live in LA except for being close to
Disneyland well I figured it would be nice to actually like enjoy non sub
zero temperatures like I am right now because I'm in Milwaukee not really the
best weather capital of the world so I think it'd be a nice change you live
relatively close to good friends of ours yeah you live right by these olr
lesbians located in Wisconsin in Madison in that case they should come to my
roller derby bouts I actually play for the Brew City Bruisers in Milwaukee so
if you guys are listening come to our fucking bouts I have a good a really
good friend of mine just recently got into that whole roller derby thing and
she's loving it you know actually a friend of mine from one of my classes
two semesters ago tried to get me into their league in Sacramento Sacramento
League yeah I could see however my bad ankle kind of keeps me from doing it
don't oh I I have like horrible ankles I actually tore my PCL on my left knee so
I have to wear this like Robo Bryce of death and I still do it it's it sounds
like you might make me to make quite the scene you know you could be the Android
of the scapes pretty much all right well unfortunately I gotta I gotta wrap
things up we've had you on for like 20 minutes it's way longer we have those
colors but you're you're special cuz you're you know you got the whole whole
tie-in does like something that's going on right now but um please do I hope
you're able to listen again and call us with updates so we can dish especially
when the whole thing's over then we don't really dish and we can really dish
yes I have so many fun stories so I can't wait can't wait I will make it a
point to catch the episodes so that it's not just one person now you have a
rosie's advance I do every now it's like someone from olr is on I mean in the way
it might have happened in the reverse order but so it's it now that she's
listening to olr she's she's kind of a member of the oil army here a few
minutes out of my week 22 minutes you can do it Rob takes that 20 minutes out
of his busy rating schedule okay I know it's like but I with all due respect I
watched drag race first then the tester so nice all right good combo you out
there all right well Oscar thank you so much for calling in I I hope to hell you
win but you know I I yeah I hope to hell you win let's just put it that way yes I
will definitely be coming back next week in the week after and you can't get rid
of me now I'm sorry awesome she's joining army we've used the olr me
duct tape just don't tell him Stan all right all right take care have a good
one take care bye you mentioning sure me now I'm gonna have to go home and clean
a big pile of crap up off the laundry room floor I cuz sure me has her in
bedroom y'all I love that she's so delts like self-deprecating about the whole
thing like the I and it sounds to me I mean I could be wrong but it sounds to
me based on the whole like Facebook group they've got going on or where fake
book as she called it that it sounds like they're all kind of in on the joke
like yeah you know it's the tester and that's that's pretty awesome you know
they they accept it for what it is so that's awesome but I'll tell you what
you know what again I and I do stand by this I said this before and I'll say it
now the tester it's not a TV show that's going to change your life it's not the
best thing on television but you know what for something in the background it
is probably more entertaining than a lot of shows that have been about video
gaming in the past so there you go 1 8 7 7 game olr or our username on Skype is
orange a lounge radio if you want to give us a call you can go for that right
now we've got time to take a couple more calls I know that call went on a long
time but we'll get at least one or two more other people on the show in the
meantime let's read some Twitter topics at twitter.com slash olr 13x4 ever sent
us a tweet this week that says hey olr how about five game music albums for
whatever price you wish to pay how about 13 plus albums for $10 or more and he's
referring to the game music bundle.com it's another one of those indie bundles
you know that whole thing's been very popular lately and yeah you can donate
their money and get soundtracks so if you're a game music fan it sounds like
they have all different types of games included in that and they add more
soundtracks as more people donate so interesting let's go to the phones
because we have more people calling in hi you're on orange launch radio who's
this yo what up guys it's Zina Korp from the UKC how you doing hey Zina Korp from
Oklahoma City unless OKC stands for something else what's up you're pretty
worried about money hey by the way just want to say the Thunder losing to the
Kings dude dude the Thunder lost to the Kings that's do you watch basketball who
the hell the Thunder never mind all right never mind that I'll pay tips of
that fucking team they paying me fucking let me just say the Thunder right now is
the best team in the league and they fucking lost to the Kings the Sacramento
King pretty funny everybody here in Sacramento is just laughing cuz like the
Kings suck and you guys anyway I won't make this about basketball what's on
your mind Zina Korp that much not much just been playing the hell out of League
of Legends for some reason you know it's funny you bring that up Twitter asked us
a question here about League of Legends so I can kind of tie this together
awesome her sent us a tweet said have you guys ever played League of Legends
it's an extremely popular free online game that I've never heard you mention
on the show which is funny because we did end up mentioning it at the top of
the show during the Dota thing but he's right I I personally have not played
League of Legends myself but Zina Korp sounds like you're a fan yeah I've been
playing it for a while now finally got my account maxed out so I can actually
compete with some of the other characters in the game like the whole
thing with the multiplayer online battle arenas at least that's the genre it's
been labeled as the MOBAs is it since it's all team based there's a lot of
rage in there more so than you might see in the first-person shooter so I can
only play it for about an hour and then a little 12 year olds get on my nerves
but other than that the game itself is pretty fun I can only imagine like the
League of Legends one of those games I think I would enjoy more if I just
played it with like only people I know but um one thing I do notice is that
it's a hugely popular game to be streamed on those video game streaming
websites like twitch TV I always see League of Legends stuff going on on
there yeah actually started playing Heroes of Newark just because it looked
this looks more polished you know cuz they acted the higher resolutions and
all this other stuff your interface was better but I couldn't find any like pro
content or even games being played so I could learn how to play it but there's
tons of League of Legends stuff so I started watching that here here and
there like pro coverage and just some guys casting their games because that's
how I got into Starcraft is when everybody was casting it during the beta
and I'd started playing it out and once I figured out how it worked it was
pretty fun it's the only really competitive game that I play so I'm
pretty much done with first-person shooters as far as I'm concerned let me
back up a minute because this is the question I should have asked you first
like for those that aren't familiar with League of Legends this ossifer kind of
insinuates we are in on the Twitter what what is what makes this game addicting
what makes you stick it out through the 12 year olds as long as you can for this
okay so you're familiar with the interface that Starcraft and them use
right so you got your your mouse control you're right-clicking on things moving
them around this one you're locked in a one single character alright so you play
one character there's about I think just under a hundred if not just a little
over a hundred characters to choose from they all have different abilities some
yeah think of your standard role-playing game party they have characters that fit
each role that's in the game your healer your magic user your Archer sure yeah
this one is this street attack damage you have your attack power which are
your magical abilities you have your tanks and you have your junglers of the
guys who don't sit in the main action of the game running around in the
assisting everybody else to sum it up here real quick and you just keep used
it's tower defense so you have three lines of towers and a large crystal that
you defend if you kill the other guys crystal you win or they can surrender
and give up okay it's not hard to learn but it takes patience to learn how to
play each character because they're all a little bit different there's like I
think right puts out a teaser video on each one of the characters they release
that tell you all about how to use their powers and just that any other thing so
just if you want to learn one there's plenty of resources to do so you know I
gotta admit part of what is scary to me in sorts about League of Legends that I
am afraid of of signing on there and that just getting owned by twelve-year
olds right off the bat cuz there's no way to practice like is there any type
of like practice learning curve like kinda way to ease yourself into this
game before you have to play against the hardcore people yeah well you can't
really play with the hardcore guys cuz they're mainly doing ranked matches
right matches you can't even touch until you max out your account they keeps
track of your players skill and how long you've been playing up to level 30 so
it'll take you about a good four or five months before you can even touch the
rank stuff so you don't have to worry about it and the matching is pretty good
so balances the team based off of the level base and how many wins they have
okay that's a little better so in the very beginning you'll see rookie stuff
happening left and right like when you think about it's like that doesn't make
any sense why is it gonna go close to that when he knows he's gonna die
because he's a rookie and he doesn't know any better they say exactly why so
you'll see that and as you your level goes up the quality of your games will
go up as far as who you're matched with and once you reach level 30 you're
pretty much like you can pretty much play any role because you've been
playing the game enough in order to do so and it's free you don't have to put
any money into it whatsoever I like free I do like free let me ask this um what
do you think about the whole dota stuff that we were talking about earlier in
the show with Blizzard and valve going at each other over dota I mean it seems
like you're kind of getting into these games now do you do you have a
preference on what you want to see happen with the dota name or well to
sum them all up dota and dota 2 and what blizzard I think is trying to do in
heroes a new earth follow the original model the original model is not newbie
friendly there's a lot of step game is very complex I mean you take just five
on five guys in the Starcraft environment fighting each other and you
add the crafting system and how you build bigger items you worry about the
concepts of feeding other players just running and killing so they get gold
because they're killing you off left or right which unbalances the whole game
and then everybody's screaming new bet you this that and the other thing
there's a lot of craft to remember for the all those but some people like that
complexity League of Legends is a lot simpler it's easier to get into and the
matches don't potentially don't last as long because there's a level cap during
the game your character can only get up to level 18 I think and all the others
and go up to 25 30 before they start capping out so the game is forced to a
conclusion usually one game will not go any longer than an hour even as a newbie
all right so it sounds like there's a lot of even though you know we kind of
say these games all have the same roots there's still a lot of mechanic
mechanical differences between them so yeah at the core of the same but one is
very newbie friendly the other one just let the pros deal with it don't even
bother all right xenocore anything else you want to share with listeners for we
take another call yeah actually now if you get it uh to go order from the Olive
Garden they give you a whole freaking roll of drumstick or breadsticks man
that's awesome I got five in the fridge go eat for breakfast I heard you know I
heard I heard a random story that that the Olive Garden is having image
problems right now I can't imagine why but they're gonna be like they're
actually gonna like change their restaurants they're going through like a
JC penny crisis right now or they're gonna like totally rebrand the Olive
Garden yeah it's weird cuz no one's really going there anymore yeah well the
Olive Garden's kind of like become a joke now like a freaking corporate man
you can go ahead and see some old Italian dude cooking in the back
speaking Italian than half these joints around here so I'd rather go there
exactly exactly all right well xenocore enjoy those
breadsticks but I gotta let you go so we can take a few more calls and good luck
all right your illegal I'm out of here thanks for having me on hey no problem
take care buddy all right one eight seven seven game
olr our username on skype is orange lounge radio let me get a few more
Twitter topics out of the way before the next call comes in let's see we have do
do do do do do dark to see you tweets us this is bad news for Loki guess who's
working on haptic technology Apple what is the haptic technology I'm oh it's a
ready player one reference touching stuff oh he tweets us a story about I
guess apples working on this right now good for them Apple is playing around in
the space now adding teeth to speculation it may soon launch high-end
TV sets with glasses less 3d god all you ever hear about are these Apple TV
sets that are all the rumor right now I don't know what an Apple TV interest you
in the least Loki no I'm not I'm not one okay listen I'm not your normal Apple
consumer that like oh I will release something I go out to the store right
now I go bye go bye go bye go bye I mean like that that is that's your usual
consumer I I am the other hand have a TV I have two TVs one of which I use one of
which I don't use I do not need a third TV all right I gotta wrap it up and go
to the phone because we have another call hi you're on orange launch radio is
this it's the one and only Rama hey Rama sorry you had to sit there on the line
and listen to more of Loki's ranting bad timing you have to I enjoy Loki's
ranting about Apple since my new roommate is Apple fanboy so you know
well what's up buddy not too much but Rob I have a bone to pick with you again
you have a boner to pick with me that's hot okay first we have balls now we have
boners okay what's up what's up what's up Rama
Rob you're a dick why what I do now talk about balls you are a dick talking about
balls man you got some nerve that's what I do here on the show is help it land in
the toilet yes but we should leave the talking of balls David Bowie since he
fondles them on a regular basis stop that all you really want come on my show
make balls jokes no I also want to compliment your hair so you look you
look like Riker look we don't have a webcam you don't know what my hair looks
like right now I've been napping why do I ask this question can we what hair
what since the studio is at your house can we get to all our cam back I've
thought about it I've seriously thought about it but it's kind of a pain in the
butt to hook up and we're probably gonna be moving in June anyway so probably
after that because we'll have a more proper studio set up at that point it's
like the studio is like a nomad isn't it maybe for your 10-year present olr
listeners because our birthdays in June too it plays Genesis games I have a
thing that plays Genesis games it's called a Genesis what am I gonna do with
you Rama all right anything else you want to I filthy up the show it tonight
how bad the beat is gonna fall flat on its face no now you're throwing some
shade this is good this is these are the types of calls I like why is the Vita
gonna fall flat on its face Rama I can't as much as I want the system I can't see
myself shelling out two hundred and fifty dollars for this thing I just
can't I mean Nintendo learned their lesson like pretty quickly with the
price drop Sony will just stand there all right just say that it's okay it's
a cop it's okay there's nothing wrong with the price for me for a year before
it falls if that all right let's look at let's look at the technology with you
know the DS and the 3ds I mean if you put those side to side and you know is
you give it to somebody like okay why are these the same thing so I mean
really all they added with the 3ds is an analog nub and 3d and the 3d is just
kind of it and their launch lineup was kind of meh so that's why the 3ds
flopped is because they didn't have a good launch lineup didn't have any big
franchise I'm sorry Nintendogs fucking porting Nintendogs I'm not even gonna
call it a new game and adding cats because some people have cats is not a
fucking launch game I mean that's just terrible and pilot wings is kind of ho
hum it was three three activities that you could do on woohoo Island that no
one gives a shit about woohoo Island is not fucking character Mario is a
character link is a character woohoo Island no one gives a shit I want woohoo
Island to be a fighter in the next Smash Brothers I would like to see that but
that's not gonna happen but um so that's why it tanked is because of that and I
know people think it may tank again because it didn't do so well in Japan
but Japanese people are fickle they they like some things they don't like some
things they like dating sim games we don't like dating sim games I don't know
it's just weird so um I think it has a good chance because their launch lineup
is fucking awesome I mean they've got a lot of games coming out and it's not
like hey look here's our launch lineup and then we have one 3ds game coming out
each month I mean we're talking like a lot of games and it's gonna be Vita Vita
Vita all I will say PlayStation does seem to have really good third-party
support out the gate as opposed to third-party support eventually and and
it's also pretty you know powerful technology wise I mean the screen looks
nice it's got dual analog sticks which is gonna be great for porting games over
or creating you know first-person shooter games and that kind of stuff
because you actually have some decent controls there except you know unlike
the 3ds where you're gonna force people to use the analog stick and then the
touchscreen and oh it's very fucking uncomfortable so let's throw in the
stand we're gonna have a kickstand on this fucker that we're gonna put out
with this game because it's just not gonna work well yeah that's stupid if
you've got to add accessories to your stupid system because oh I forgot to put
some buttons on there and oh this is really fucking uncomfortable to hold
then then you got a problem all right Rama he's made his case we'll see we'll
see a lot a lot of questions to be answered over the next month and see
what the numbers look like when the system comes out all right Rama anything
else quickly before we let you go I'm kind of floored because I actually
agree with Loki on that hmm I mean I do and I understand where he's coming from
I mean the Vita is a much more powerful system it it's there but the way I see
it is that the consumers can look at like I could do all this look at the
price put it down and they can go pick up a 3ds or something like that I think
that's what it's coming down to right about now it's all about the price point
yeah but people are comfortable in pain that's kinds of price points because
people are buying tablets and they're buying all this other electronic garbage
that's really expensive well the price point is not that big a deal anymore
well I don't know about that most people are buying tablets or iPad users because
they're buying because it's an iPad you know people people shell out that type
of money but you know but iPads aren't the only tablets out there and there's
definitely plenty of them being sold yeah but those are but those tablets
cost less or less expensive than the iPad I mean okay between a $500 iPad and
a $200 Kindle fire I'll I will drop 200 on the Kindle fire so you'll drop $200
on a Kindle fire but you won't drop $200 on a fucking via I see how it is no no
no no you get my words twisted Loki but I respect you for that all right I have
to put it into this we got to wrap up the show right all right Rama thank you
very much for your call good luck no problem take care later run John all
right well he didn't hear that he'll hear it on the air all right so really
the Skype was really you gotta buy a system that's less less expensive than
the other system that's how it is so I mean that's that's the argument me well
you know the iPads $500 so you know spending $250 on this tablet it's not
that big a deal wait what doesn't make any sense all right we got to wrap up
the show we ran long tonight but that's okay why it was worth it for the phone
call with Aska earlier on it was fun so I'm who I've been chatting but I knew
you would I need to be braiding each other's hair within minutes this is a
matter of time all right hitting each other with pellas on the party all
right anyway we got to we got to wrap it up we got to wrap up the show and be on
out of here for the night so let's go around and get everybody's oh I didn't
do all the tweets damn it damn it damn it quickly because there were some I
really wanted to read act deft says beat hazard ultra is now on iOS if you know
the beat hazard games which are actually a lot of I do love beat hazard on the PC
on via steam so I'm going to definitely check this out now that I know it's on
iOS I don't see a price here in the story but I wanted to say I read
somewhere it was like $2.99 and it will work with all the stuff that's on your
ios device that's pretty cool a couple quick ones from tiger claw I think the
sonic and Sega all-stars you mentioned during quickfire news let me read this
other one from tiger claw 305 on Twitter twisted metal promotion blows up sweet
tooth truck let's see I guess this is a promotion for twisted metal where you
get to destroy thing fans can sign up for a chance to remotely fire m249 saw
machine guns at the real-life version of the ice cream truck driven by sweet
tooth the game's fire haired clown faced antagonists they've hooked guns up to a
satellite so you can control them remotely from your computer what you
could shoot a real gun with real bullets at a real truck from your computer go to
shoot my truck calm for a chance to pull the trigger or it's just a video of that
trick it's a dirty trick all right that does it for the tweets tonight thank you
guys to the Twitter topics now we're gonna wrap up the show all right we're
gonna go around to your base final thoughts oh actually last minute stories
I'm sorry Loki I'm sorry I'm not doing your last minute story I think give me
your final thought I've got this song for cage match all right it's gonna be
awesome can't wait can't wait dark soccer your final thought tonight my
final thought tonight is the only downside to shows running along is no
pinkberry break I know oh well we'll get it during the week salted
caramel you will be mine that's gonna do it for another week here orange launch
radio hey if you like what you heard you know what we say please just tell a
couple other people about the show help spread the word about orange launch
radio we really appreciate it and you know we don't have a million dollar
magazine backing us up or a website or our own show on the PlayStation Network
or anything like that so all we ask just tell a friend or two about the show and
help grow the ol army like like Stan did yeah right Stan told his buddy you
happen to be on this little show that's going on right now to listen to the show
and it works so Stan gets a gold star this week but you guys definitely
everybody else can earn gold stars just tell a friend or two about orange lounge
radio really appreciate it have a great week everybody we'll see you back here
next week for more gaming news and discussion maybe some more Vita
impressions I don't know if anyone's getting the early one but have a great
Valentine's Day as well whether you're spending it with somebody special or
whether you're spending it forever alone or whether you're spending it with your
hand have a great week everybody see you next time you've been listening to
orange lounge radio orange lounge radio is an orange lounge production to join
us for a live show visit www.allgames.com Sunday nights at 6 p.m. Pacific
time the views and opinions expressed on orange lounge radio do not necessarily
reflect those of the entire staff of orange lounge radio or all games calm
but we're probably right anyway see you next week