[SPEAKER_31]: The following live program is a special presentation of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_28]: Orange Lounge Radio is presented in the TMI sound format.
Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_05]: Call me Daddy.
[SPEAKER_32]: Orange Lounge may contain adult content.
[SPEAKER_32]: Orange Lounge may contain many four-letter words.
[SPEAKER_32]: Orange Lounge may contain a scene of nudity.
[SPEAKER_32]: Orange Lounge may contain plenty of... Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_17]: Orange Lounge Radio will not contain any of that in this episode.
[SPEAKER_25]: Well, isn't that special?
[SPEAKER_32]: Orange Lounge Radio Live is a fully interactive program via our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com And now, here are your hosts for Orange Lounge Radio Live, DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_21]: We are live.
[SPEAKER_21]: This is episode number 116 for this.
[SPEAKER_21]: October the 24th of 2004.
[SPEAKER_21]: You're tuned in to the B-Money Scene's most pooped radio station of all things, the money.
[SPEAKER_21]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_21]: You might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_21]: Joining me as always are my awesome co-hosts.
[SPEAKER_21]: In that corner, the happiest bunny on the farm is Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_22]: You know her better as DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm happy.
[SPEAKER_22]: Also...
[SPEAKER_22]: What?
[SPEAKER_22]: The mic doesn't pick you up for some reason.
Ah!
[SPEAKER_22]: There you go, now we can hear you.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm actually in a good mood.
[SPEAKER_22]: Good!
[SPEAKER_22]: You looked really pooped earlier today.
[SPEAKER_16]: Good, and I'm still tired, and I still got some of the crap to do, but... I feel exhausted right now.
[SPEAKER_13]: Given what you were doing earlier, though, I wouldn't blame you.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, maybe we'll share that with our listeners a little later.
[SPEAKER_21]: Hold on, wait.
[SPEAKER_21]: Wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_21]: I have something to share with listeners.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes, burping wars and more on tonight's episode.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, but first, it's very, very sparkling water.
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't think you like this stuff.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, I don't drink soda.
[SPEAKER_22]: I drink Crystal Geyser sparkling mineral water.
[SPEAKER_22]: Why?
[SPEAKER_21]: Because I like to feign this diet I'm on.
[SPEAKER_21]: Anyway, also joining us as always,
[SPEAKER_21]: The third wheel of our program, our tech master, Loki.
[SPEAKER_20]: Oh, excuse me.
[SPEAKER_20]: Something in my throat there.
[SPEAKER_20]: Anyways, hi.
[SPEAKER_22]: Get the dick out of your mouth.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's time to start the show.
[SPEAKER_22]: I like gummy bears.
[SPEAKER_20]: That makes me sad.
[SPEAKER_21]: Also joining us tonight, we have a couple of special guests.
[SPEAKER_21]: They like to come to this show quite often here.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm trying to get them a mic here.
[SPEAKER_21]: DDR Angel's here.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hiya.
[SPEAKER_15]: Here again.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm starting to become a regular.
[SPEAKER_15]: Be afraid.
[SPEAKER_21]: Don't you have anything else to do on Sunday night?
[SPEAKER_21]: Don't you have villages to burn and convenience stores to rob?
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, I'm an angel.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not speaking to you like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, this is the show needed.
[SPEAKER_21]: Loki went and bought an Arashuka this week.
[SPEAKER_21]: Also joining us, say hello to RKDN42, also known as Bradley.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_21]: You have a car this week, right?
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, good to hear.
[SPEAKER_22]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_22]: I think your mic might be cut out.
[SPEAKER_22]: Grab the bottom.
[SPEAKER_22]: Why am I not hearing it?
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, hello then.
[SPEAKER_22]: Hello, hello, hello.
[SPEAKER_29]: That was weird.
[SPEAKER_29]: Yes, I have a car now.
[SPEAKER_29]: Very strange.
[SPEAKER_29]: And we'll get to tell the whole story after the break.
[SPEAKER_29]: Alright, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_21]: A little bit of Imani news.
[SPEAKER_21]: Somebody made an oopsie and we figured out one new Ultramix 2 song.
[SPEAKER_21]: So we'll be sharing that with you guys tonight.
[SPEAKER_21]: And I guess all that and whatever else we can come up with until the next three hours.
[SPEAKER_22]: But first, we're going to do a little bit of a break.
[SPEAKER_21]: And what kind of music should we do in this break?
[SPEAKER_20]: I feel like doing some 5K Beatmania stuff.
[SPEAKER_20]: So let's start off with this.
[SPEAKER_20]: And we will be back after this.
[SPEAKER_20]: Join us in our chatroom, www.orangeonsradio.com.
[SPEAKER_20]: Click on chat, we'll be back.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you for watching!
Thank you.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thanks for watching!
and many more.
This is the way we rock, this is the way we vibe, as we demonstrate, as we demonstrate.
Everybody wants a piece of the pie, most of it I miss the eye, cause I know that I know the vibe, cause I spy, let me try.
This is the way we dance, this is the way we rock, this is the way we vibe, as we demonstrate.
[SPEAKER_25]: I can leave all my cares behind now I'm out to play, gonna have me some fun In a world that is totally mine
[SPEAKER_24]: Gaming Radio, so uncensored.
[SPEAKER_21]: and even Tom Brokaw could get a job with us.
[SPEAKER_22]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_22]: We are back here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_22]: This lovely October evening.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm so tired today.
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't know if I've got three hours worth in me.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's going to be like squeezing the sponge to get the last little drop out.
[SPEAKER_21]: But I will do it.
[SPEAKER_21]: For the listeners, I will force myself.
[SPEAKER_13]: And if you don't do it for them, we'll force you.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_21]: We're going to start off tonight's show as we start off every week playing a little bit of How was your week?
[SPEAKER_21]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_21]: A chance for you to catch up with us and our personal lives.
[SPEAKER_21]: You can be nosy and invade our personal lives.
[SPEAKER_21]: And we'll start by opening up the file on Jamie.
[SPEAKER_16]: My week was all busy crap.
[SPEAKER_16]: Busy, busy, busy crap.
[SPEAKER_16]: Lots of stress.
[SPEAKER_16]: And yeah.
[SPEAKER_16]: That's pretty much my week.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_18]: No specifics you want to give?
[SPEAKER_16]: No.
[SPEAKER_16]: It was busy.
[SPEAKER_16]: And it's going to be even busier next week.
[SPEAKER_16]: And, let's see, Tuesday when I came home, the business that was going to cause me to cancel the show didn't happen.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_16]: And I was all stressing out.
[SPEAKER_16]: Well, you know about that.
[SPEAKER_16]: You told me.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh, that's right, that's right, that's right.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_18]: I thought it was something else.
[SPEAKER_18]: See, I have so many things going on right now that I'm just... It's like spaghetti.
[SPEAKER_16]: At any rate, I just said fuck it that night and had dinner with Dan and had a nice time and relaxed, but I'm still stressed as hell, and it's going to be that way until after Halloween.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's exactly how I feel.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_18]: Alright, well, I guess that does it for Jamie's week.
[SPEAKER_18]: Let's talk to Loki.
[SPEAKER_18]: You want to talk to us about your week?
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, I didn't really do a whole lot of stuff.
[SPEAKER_19]: What did I do this week?
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh yeah, I played Leisure Suit Larry all week.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's pretty much what I did.
[SPEAKER_19]: And other than that, I played a little bit of Final Fantasy this weekend.
[SPEAKER_19]: And then, what else did I do?
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't know, just kind of hung out.
[SPEAKER_19]: Just trying to stay out of the weather.
[SPEAKER_19]: And, yeah, that's pretty much all that happened.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, and I bought an Airzooka yesterday because I was at the mall.
[SPEAKER_19]: I had money.
[SPEAKER_19]: I didn't want to buy a game because I'm just going to rent it.
[SPEAKER_19]: And so, you know, I couldn't leave empty-handed, so I got an Airzooka instead.
[SPEAKER_19]: Virgin didn't have any echo image.
[SPEAKER_19]: Of course, why was I even looking?
[SPEAKER_19]: Because...
[SPEAKER_19]: What?!
[SPEAKER_21]: Explain what an airzooka is for those listeners that don't know.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's a giant thing that shoots a ring of air at you.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's like a giant, um... I don't know, it looks like a giant tube with a big elastic thing at the end and you pull it back and it creates like... You know how if you were to blow smoke rings?
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, it does the same thing.
[SPEAKER_19]: It creates like a shockwave of air that goes up through about ten feet.
[SPEAKER_19]: And it's supposed to be harmless, and you can, like, shoot at it, animals and stuff, and all that fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's what an Arizuka is.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's this giant thing that I wasted a lot of, well, not a lot of money, but I wasted money on.
[SPEAKER_19]: And, um, yeah, that's pretty much all that's been going down this week.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's been pretty boring.
[SPEAKER_19]: Pretty boring.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_19]: Wait, I already talked about my trip, though, didn't I?
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, I think I did.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, and I saw The Grudge.
[SPEAKER_19]: That was cool.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, I'll talk about The Grudge in a little bit, because I saw it too.
[SPEAKER_21]: But first, we'll talk to Arcadian, Bradley, and talk to him about his week, because I know he had a fun week.
[SPEAKER_29]: Oh yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_29]: And it started off really, really fucking shitty.
[SPEAKER_29]: About two miles from leaving this apartment last week,
[SPEAKER_29]: The fucking Folsom Police Department stops me, goddamn motherfuckers.
[SPEAKER_21]: After leaving this show.
[SPEAKER_29]: Yes, right after leaving the show.
[SPEAKER_29]: Two miles away, a fucking guy pulls me over and says, Oh, your registration's out of date, so it's over six months, so we gotta tow it.
[SPEAKER_29]: Fuck you.
[SPEAKER_29]: Don't!
[SPEAKER_29]: It really fucking sucks.
[SPEAKER_29]: At least he didn't get me for speeding, because it was right at a fucking place where it goes from 50 to 40, and he could have busted me for that, but he didn't.
[SPEAKER_29]: and so he went away and said, do you have money?
[SPEAKER_29]: I said, yeah, I do.
[SPEAKER_29]: I went down to the thing and called Rob.
[SPEAKER_29]: And so he came and picked me up and took me home.
[SPEAKER_29]: Thank you, Rob.
[SPEAKER_21]: No problem, because I was dropping off Angel anyway, so we're done.
[SPEAKER_19]: So sure, they can pull you over for fucking expired registration, but they never catch anybody that runs a fucking red light.
[SPEAKER_19]: makes a goddamn left turn when there's a right turn only lane and fucking just blatantly drives like assholes.
[SPEAKER_19]: You know, they just...
[SPEAKER_19]: I saw two people, and Rob actually passed me when I was stopped
[SPEAKER_19]: And it just frustrated the hell out of me.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, bitches.
[SPEAKER_29]: Well, then, once I got home, I called my manager, and he said, You better get it out tomorrow, because those fees for the tow yards go up astronomically, so they can take away your car after a number of days.
[SPEAKER_29]: They'll take away your car, put a lien on it, sell it off.
[SPEAKER_29]: So you want to get it out tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_29]: So, after that, I went and called... So I had to wait until like 4 a.m.
[SPEAKER_29]: in the morning, called my mom on the East Coast, and asked her to put in some money in my account, and she... She...
[SPEAKER_29]: So, in the morning I called my co-worker and she drove me over to the Carmichael DMV and 10 minutes after they opened I paid $319 and got my registration and temporary tag so I can get a smog check and so from there, since the bus wasn't coming for 30 minutes I decided, oh, I'll just go ahead and start walking towards ARC, the American River College that took about 45 minutes later I was there
[SPEAKER_29]: Even though my foot was hurting in the beginning, but it didn't hurt after a while, so that was okay.
[SPEAKER_29]: But, after that, I took a bus from there to Greenback, then from there to Orangevale, where the thing was.
[SPEAKER_29]: The co-worker says, hey, okay, let's see if we can get it out.
[SPEAKER_29]: No, you have to go to Folsom PD and get them to release it.
[SPEAKER_29]: So you have to go there and show them that you got your registration and everything.
[SPEAKER_29]: So, after that, I didn't know about the buses there, so I started walking towards Folsom, and I missed the bus that came next.
[SPEAKER_29]: So I said, ah, let's go ahead and walk.
[SPEAKER_29]: So I walked another mile and a half down the hill, which wasn't too bad.
[SPEAKER_29]: It was a nice day out and so on.
[SPEAKER_29]: Then from there, I walked across the bridge because I missed the bus there.
[SPEAKER_29]: I kind of just went on and then said, nah, let's go walk a bit farther.
[SPEAKER_29]: So here comes the stupid part.
[SPEAKER_29]: There's a, I got like a little, the person at the tow yards that gave me a map.
[SPEAKER_29]: They said, you should go to Natoma Boulevard or Natoma Street.
[SPEAKER_29]: I thought it was Natomas Street, and I thought it was like a right turn.
[SPEAKER_29]: So when I went to Natomas Street, I went to turn to the right, and thought, oh, the levers are going up.
[SPEAKER_29]: And I didn't think to go left and see if there was something up that way.
[SPEAKER_29]: I just went down this, kept going down this road miles and miles.
[SPEAKER_29]: Didn't ask any directions or anything until I got to the end, basically to a big cross street.
[SPEAKER_29]: That's the lady, last lady of the apartment there.
[SPEAKER_29]: Apartment company says, uh, where's the Pilsner PD?
[SPEAKER_29]: I said, it's Natomas, there's no Natomas Street, you idiot.
[SPEAKER_29]: She didn't say that, of course.
[SPEAKER_29]: She was probably thinking it was crazy.
[SPEAKER_29]: This crazy guy walking away, the long way.
[SPEAKER_29]: So, after that, I walked back to the next bus stop.
[SPEAKER_29]: That took me to Entomba Street, and I had to walk, like, half a mile or so down to the PD.
[SPEAKER_29]: They said, oh, okay, here we go, give me a ticket, and say, okay, oh, you gotta pay $20.
[SPEAKER_29]: Ah, fuck.
[SPEAKER_29]: Gotta go across the street, get money out of the bank.
[SPEAKER_29]: Oh my god!
[SPEAKER_29]: Then walked back across the street, paid the money, then gotta go back to the bank.
[SPEAKER_29]: So I walked back down to Riley, and then got on a bus, which was good.
[SPEAKER_29]: The bus took me almost there, then paid $175 to the fucking tow yard, and got it out, and yay.
[SPEAKER_29]: Then I went back to work for like three and a half hours, and then made it up the rest of the week.
[SPEAKER_29]: Basically made up my whole week, and that was it for that.
[SPEAKER_21]: Tough lesson learned, everybody out there.
[SPEAKER_21]: Register your car!
[SPEAKER_29]: Don't fucking drive in Folsom.
[SPEAKER_29]: Stay far away.
[SPEAKER_29]: And in other news, I got keys to work so I can stay late and lock up the place after everyone else has left.
[SPEAKER_19]: If you want to run through red lights and make illegal left turns, Folsom's where it's at because no one gives a shit.
[SPEAKER_29]: I'm not broke now because Mother gave me enough money so that I could do that and a little bit of extra money.
[SPEAKER_29]: Which is helpful because I can go and get a new chair mat because my other one has a hole in it that's been poking me in the foot for like three or four months.
[SPEAKER_29]: Then go to the Mall of Wart, the Mart of Walls and buy stuff.
[SPEAKER_29]: That's what I did today before coming here.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, wow, well, interesting week there.
[SPEAKER_21]: Let's talk to DDR Angel and see how her week went.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, uh, not much really, um, just school and work.
[SPEAKER_15]: Although, um, my instructor's becoming quite a flake.
[SPEAKER_15]: He almost canceled class on Monday.
[SPEAKER_15]: Nah, well, I suppose he has his own reasons.
[SPEAKER_15]: Um...
[SPEAKER_15]: Played a little Karamari Damasi and other stuff this week.
[SPEAKER_15]: Maybe like a couple hours worth of FFXI, which is not as bad as you guys, but hey, it's something.
[SPEAKER_15]: I also spent some time with, well, what, one-third of Orange Lounge?
[SPEAKER_15]: Not the hosts, of course, the other people that usually come here.
[SPEAKER_15]: Last night and spent an hour waiting to get into dinner.
[SPEAKER_15]: I can talk.
[SPEAKER_15]: Had dinner and watched movies and stuff last night.
[SPEAKER_15]: That was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_15]: Which I don't get to do that often, so that was kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_15]: And that's about it, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_16]: I have something else to add, but I think you're going to talk about it, so I'll let you bring that up.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay, I'll talk about my weekend.
[SPEAKER_21]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_21]: And then Thursday, I hung out with my friend and pretty much nothing interesting happened until Friday when I went and saw The Grudge with Loki and his girlfriend and my buddy Christopher.
[SPEAKER_21]: We went to this theater.
[SPEAKER_21]: My God, it was packed.
[SPEAKER_21]: Not only was the theater packed, but it was packed full of high schoolers because apparently these movies really appeal to the high schoolers.
[SPEAKER_21]: Boy, did we make a mistake going on opening night with all these high schoolers in there because every scary part of the movie, and there was a lot.
[SPEAKER_21]: The movie was pretty scary.
[SPEAKER_21]: Every scary part.
[SPEAKER_21]: All the girls were like,
[SPEAKER_21]: And like, even, it's, I don't want to ruin it, but there's this one part where the screaming became almost rhythmic.
[SPEAKER_21]: It was like, It was really funny.
[SPEAKER_21]: I can't, if you've seen the movie, you probably could figure out what part I'm talking about, but this is one part where it just was rhythmic.
[SPEAKER_21]: It was so funny.
[SPEAKER_21]: But then there was this guy in the back of the theater, he was being really annoying, and you know the type I'm talking about, he's like that high school jock type, he's sitting there going, like making those noises, because apparently other high school jock types find those kinds of noises funny, and their girlfriends or whatever, so he was kind of mocking how everybody else was getting scared, like, oh my god, I want my mommy, and apparently this is funny when somebody does this.
[SPEAKER_21]: Never mind that it's a sold out theater and he's getting on everybody else's nerves in the theater and just bugging the hell out of all of us.
[SPEAKER_21]: You can just feel the tension, like everybody just wanted to turn around and punch this guy in the face.
[SPEAKER_21]: Am I right, Loki?
[SPEAKER_21]: Uh, sure.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay, so finally, I don't know what came over me, but I just turned, and mind you, this is right at the climax of the movie, towards the end of the movie, he's still yelling and screaming, he's been doing it for five minutes.
[SPEAKER_21]: I turn around, I look right at him, and I yell in the crowded theater.
[SPEAKER_21]: I said, with the guy with the little penis in the back row, please shut the hell up.
[SPEAKER_21]: And everybody burst into applause and started laughing.
[SPEAKER_21]: And so that was kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_21]: And then he shut up.
[SPEAKER_21]: So he knew who he was by the way I addressed him, by being the small penis guy.
[SPEAKER_21]: My advice to you, don't be afraid to shout it out if people are distracting the movie, because chances are everybody else around you is finding them distracting too, and they'll back you up.
[SPEAKER_21]: They're just being chicken.
[SPEAKER_21]: They don't want to say anything.
[SPEAKER_21]: So I can credit my couple years, God, several years experience with Rocky Horror Picture Show for making me unafraid to yell back at a movie.
[SPEAKER_21]: Speaking of which, I ended up going to see a local production of the Rocky Horror Show, which the
[SPEAKER_21]: Broadway version
[SPEAKER_16]: The one that they played on Broadway in 2000.
[SPEAKER_16]: So that's where the difference... People were talking about, well, this isn't how the original play was because it actually was the redo for Broadway.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, Richard O'Brien went back and did the script for Broadway.
[SPEAKER_16]: I recognize it because I have the 2000 recording.
[SPEAKER_16]: And it was the same thing.
[SPEAKER_21]: Very good.
[SPEAKER_21]: So it was a good show.
[SPEAKER_21]: I liked it.
[SPEAKER_21]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_21]: And then other than that, I've just been doing a lot of rehearsal because there is going to be another production of the movie soon, which I'm involved with.
[SPEAKER_21]: So I've just been very tired going to rehearsals and things like that.
[SPEAKER_21]: And Jamie knows where I'm coming from with that, certainly.
[SPEAKER_16]: Amen.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm just glad I don't have to do prop crew this time around.
[SPEAKER_16]: I mean, I like doing prop crew and that's all cool.
[SPEAKER_16]: But I'm doing lighting.
[SPEAKER_16]: That means I'm going to just sit on my butt playing with the light switches.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's an easy job.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's good.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_21]: You have a lot of control in that little box.
[SPEAKER_16]: I don't mind the running about.
[SPEAKER_21]: If someone makes you mad, you just turn the light off.
[SPEAKER_16]: Well, I don't really mind doing the running about, putting stuff up on, you know, it was fun, but I was exhausted last time I did it, and you know what, I'm just going to sit back because I'm stressed enough.
[SPEAKER_21]: So, after next week, it's just going to be so tired.
[SPEAKER_21]: Which, by the way, reminds me, you guys, next week is Halloween.
[SPEAKER_21]: And so, on Halloween night, it's not looking like we're going to have a live show, you guys.
[SPEAKER_21]: Just so you know.
[SPEAKER_21]: Because it's Halloween and people want to go out and do Halloween stuff.
[SPEAKER_21]: We actually don't think there's enough listener base.
[SPEAKER_21]: Because you guys will probably all want to go out and do your own things for Halloween.
[SPEAKER_21]: What I think we might do next weekend, we might do some type of very scary marathon of old Orange Lounge episodes.
[SPEAKER_21]: We might fit that in next week.
[SPEAKER_16]: That means we definitely get to hear Loki sing.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, that means episode 69 for sure would be in there because that has to be one of the scariest episodes we ever did.
[SPEAKER_21]: We're going to work something out where we do a marathon of old episodes.
[SPEAKER_21]: So that's pretty much it for my week and my day.
[SPEAKER_21]: Nobody had anything remotely DDR related in their week at all.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's just... Yes, Angel.
[SPEAKER_15]: I was at Fry's and I met one of our local freestylers.
[SPEAKER_15]: Prestige.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_21]: I've never heard... What, is Fry's the place to play DDR in town now?
[SPEAKER_21]: Because I know that... What's his name online?
[SPEAKER_21]: I can't remember.
[SPEAKER_21]: Islander.
[SPEAKER_21]: I know his real name, I can't remember his name online.
[SPEAKER_21]: Islander plays a lot at Fry's, from what I hear.
[SPEAKER_21]: He plays a lot at DDR at Fry's, because I guess it's near his work, and then I guess Prestige goes there.
[SPEAKER_21]: You're going there, and you were playing DDR?
[SPEAKER_21]: Fry's must be the place to be now, all of a sudden.
[SPEAKER_21]: What happened to... Well, I mean, I know what happened to Golfland and all the arcades in town, but it's kind of sad when a department store becomes the main DDR hangout in town.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, I was just shopping for geek stuff, and, well, he was there, and so we just started playing DDR for, like,
[SPEAKER_15]: Good times, good times.
[SPEAKER_21]: So, it's getting sad, but you have to understand there's really not a whole lot of reason for us to go out and play DDR in this town anymore because really, nobody's really gotten anything new in six months at least.
[SPEAKER_21]: When did Guitar Freaks 9, 10 come out?
[SPEAKER_21]: What the hell version do they have anyway, 9?
[SPEAKER_21]: I could give a shit after five, really.
[SPEAKER_29]: They actually still have the same Guitar Freaks 8th Mix where they put in Percussion Freaks 9th Mix, I think.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_21]: Percussion Freaks 9th Mix and Guitar Freaks 8th Mix, which makes no sense at all.
[SPEAKER_21]: But that's the last new Bomani this town saw, anyway.
[SPEAKER_21]: Except the Statmania machine, but that thing was broken so fast that it never really got to stick around.
[SPEAKER_21]: So really, I think at this point a lot of us are just sitting and waiting in anticipation of Ultramix 2 because that's going to be the next big story.
[SPEAKER_21]: I actually did play DDR Extreme the other day though.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's still really fun to me.
[SPEAKER_21]: So that's one thing I guess I could say for it is that I was playing on the ignition pad trying to work some of my fat ass off because I've got a show to do next week.
[SPEAKER_21]: Poppin' Music and 2DX8 also Absolutely, it's going to be definitely a huge week, November 18th When Festival and Poppin' Music 10 and all that fun stuff, 2DX8 style come out too Oh, you know we had a trailer, there was a trailer for 2DX8 style that came out not too long ago And we completely forgot to mention it last week So I'm going to make sure to bring it up tonight In fact, I'm going to do that right now If I can find that, here it is
[SPEAKER_21]: Here's some audio here from a new preview that is out for 2DX8Style, and I'll show this here in studio.
[SPEAKER_21]: Of course, you hear a little bit of Guideca there.
[SPEAKER_21]: And it just shows the Konami logos here.
[SPEAKER_21]: It says, ooh, 2DX8Style!
[SPEAKER_21]: And it's showing a lot of the screenshots from the game and all these videos.
[SPEAKER_21]: You see, like, Alien World and a bunch of Japanese text.
[SPEAKER_21]: Something 50 and something 80 here.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm sure somebody in our chat room can translate that there.
[SPEAKER_21]: New song!
Very nice clip there of a Santa song.
This is a new song as well.
Yeah, it's definitely an LED song.
[SPEAKER_21]: Ooh, look at that.
[SPEAKER_21]: And it says there, November 18th.
[SPEAKER_21]: And it had some clips from the new videos in there as well, so.
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't even remember where I got that.
[SPEAKER_21]: I think somebody sent it to me.
[SPEAKER_21]: So I would totally pass along where you guys could get it, except I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_21]: They said 50 new songs over 80 songs in total.
[SPEAKER_21]: And they're confirming in our chatroom, DarkLionXVI says the last song is Nebula Grasper.
[SPEAKER_21]: Was that last song you heard a little clip of there?
[SPEAKER_21]: And the one before that was the Santa song that's in the new poppin' music as well, right?
[SPEAKER_21]: The one that she sang at Tokyo Game Show?
[SPEAKER_21]: Correct me if I'm wrong.
[SPEAKER_21]: I could be.
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_21]: Also on Bomani News this week, we have a little bit of Bomani News.
[SPEAKER_21]: The box art for Ultramix 2 came out.
[SPEAKER_21]: You might have seen this at your local store, actually.
[SPEAKER_21]: And the interesting thing about the box art, though, is that it has a little thing in there that talks about how it features dance hits.
[SPEAKER_21]: Like, remember how DDR Max said, Ooh, this features dance hits from Darude and Aurora and all the bands that were in there.
[SPEAKER_21]: And the Max 2 was, Ooh, it's Kylie Minogue.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, this one says...
[SPEAKER_21]: Featuring dance hits by Delirium, we knew that after all, right?
[SPEAKER_21]: Elvis, we knew that, Rubberneckin' Freestylers, which isn't ringing a bell with me So I don't think we know about what this song is And they've tried to do research, I think over on the DDR Freak thread But nobody's come up with what song that could be yet So maybe we'll hear more about that later But we have the Commodores, which we know is Brick House Nucleus, which is jam on it, we talked about that before Captain Jack
[SPEAKER_21]: I believe the Dream of Dream booty mix was confirmed previously.
[SPEAKER_21]: And now, Jason Nevins presents Holly James.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, guess what?
[SPEAKER_21]: Jason Nevins and Holly James, they only ever did one song together.
[SPEAKER_21]: So, that pretty much, no, that song was just announced recently.
[SPEAKER_21]: So, anyway, we're going to go ahead and play that song for you guys right now.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's Jason Nevins and Holly James.
[SPEAKER_21]: and the song is called I'm in Heaven and we'll play that for you guys now this hasn't been confirmed but it's kind of one of those things where it's like well unless it's a remix or something like that who knows so we're going to play that for you guys right now the assumed radio edit would be the version they'd use in DDR because we haven't heard if it's a remix again it's kind of unconfirmed but at the same time when it's on the box art you know duh so here it is Jason Evans
[SPEAKER_21]: With Holly James, I'm in Heaven.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't wanna be the one to tell you how I feel When these feelings I have really are for real The time is right for this, a love to shine on through But you gotta tell me what you wanna do
I'm in heaven with you I'm in heaven with you Heaven with you
[SPEAKER_06]: Every time you're near, I start to lose control When the thought of you, hits my very soul When you're lying in my bed, right next to me
I'm in heaven with you Only one for me
Thanks for watching!
I'm in heaven with you
[SPEAKER_32]: Warning, Orange Lounge Radio's Monty Music and More program might be dangerous for you to listen to in the kitchen.
[SPEAKER_32]: We have reported incidents where exposed listening to this program in the kitchen has caused people to bust out a Sharpie pen, draw arrows on the tiles, and start stomping away.
[SPEAKER_32]: A friendly public service announcement from Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_21]: We are back here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_21]: And that was a song that has not been confirmed, yet it pretty much has by the box art.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm in Heaven, Jason Evans, featuring Holly James.
[SPEAKER_21]: What did you guys think of that?
[SPEAKER_21]: Pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, did you realize that that's actually a former Cage Match winner from this program?
[SPEAKER_21]: I remember that song.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes, Loki picked that song a while back.
[SPEAKER_21]: Or at least, I don't know if it was necessarily that mix.
[SPEAKER_21]: I think it was one of your white label mixes.
[SPEAKER_21]: Very close.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, that was it?
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, my bad.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay, so that was it.
[SPEAKER_21]: So now...
[SPEAKER_21]: Jamie, you had picked Delirium After All in a cage match once.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_21]: Loki, you picked that one, which was in a cage match once.
[SPEAKER_21]: I want a song in Ultramax.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's not fair.
[SPEAKER_26]: No.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_21]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right.
[SPEAKER_16]: Sorry, Rob.
[SPEAKER_21]: Maybe one day.
[SPEAKER_16]: Chicks are for kids.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right.
[SPEAKER_21]: Maybe one day.
[SPEAKER_21]: So, what we want to do now, I actually want to go ahead and give somebody a call here on the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_21]: We tried to get him on the show here last week, but unfortunately the connection was really bad.
[SPEAKER_21]: So, everybody keep your fingers crossed that the connection is a little bit better tonight.
[SPEAKER_19]: So, everybody's got their fingers crossed, yes?
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay, so hopefully he's there and I don't embarrass myself here on the radio, but we're going to go ahead and give this a try here.
[SPEAKER_21]: I hope it works.
[SPEAKER_21]: One ringy dingy, two ringy dingys.
[SPEAKER_21]: Three ringy dingies.
[SPEAKER_21]: Four ringy dingies.
[SPEAKER_21]: God, I hope he's there.
[SPEAKER_21]: That would be pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_21]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_21]: Hi, is this frequency?
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh no, the connection's still kind of shy.
[SPEAKER_18]: Can you hear me okay?
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh no, we're still having a problem hearing him.
[SPEAKER_21]: He's very choppy.
[SPEAKER_21]: You only hear a couple seconds here and there, and then that's it.
[SPEAKER_21]: I hear you fine.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, there you go.
[SPEAKER_21]: I can kind of hear him.
[SPEAKER_21]: He says he can hear us okay.
[SPEAKER_21]: You might have something with your mic sensitivity settings.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm wondering if it's the mic sensitivity because I heard like a little bit there.
[SPEAKER_21]: Can you hold the mic up nice and... Hi.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay, so I'm going to try and do a conversation here.
[SPEAKER_21]: How are you doing this evening, Frequency?
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm doing okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just woke up from nap.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right, so tell us a little bit about this tournament that just happened on the East Coast recently.
[SPEAKER_21]: I was kind of curious about what went on there, because we don't get to talk a whole lot about East Coast events on the show, so I'm kind of curious what went on with this tournament.
[SPEAKER_12]: It was not so good, but not the main thing.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_21]: The connection, for some reason, we're not getting them for some reason.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm only hearing little bits and pieces of you.
[SPEAKER_21]: So, gosh, I'm really sorry.
[SPEAKER_21]: I guess what we're going to have to do, maybe we can try giving you a call later in the show.
[SPEAKER_21]: I have another idea.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm going to try getting back to you a little bit later, Frequency.
[SPEAKER_21]: I have another idea, okay?
[SPEAKER_21]: All right.
[SPEAKER_21]: Take care, bud.
[SPEAKER_21]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_21]: Ah, what a bummer.
[SPEAKER_21]: What a bummer.
[SPEAKER_21]: I do have another idea, though, but I can't get to it until the next break.
[SPEAKER_21]: But that does give me an idea.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay, so, I guess we have to shift gears here.
[SPEAKER_21]: Darn, because I have a lot of good questions I want to ask them too, and we don't get East Coast people on this show a whole lot, but that's alright, we'll give it a try later.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, moving on.
[SPEAKER_21]: I guess we could talk about other news going on.
[SPEAKER_21]: Didn't you find some news about Pump It Up that was going on this week, Loki?
[SPEAKER_21]: You got really bored and you found out that Pump It Up actually had some news going on?
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, there's two things going on.
[SPEAKER_19]: Number one being, there's another release that's coming out in November, I believe.
[SPEAKER_19]: And that would be Pump It Up Exceed on the JPS2.
[SPEAKER_19]: So that's going to be coming out.
[SPEAKER_19]: God damn it.
[SPEAKER_19]: Dude, our connection is fucking sucking tonight.
[SPEAKER_19]: Anyways, yeah, so Pump It Up Exceed, it's going to be coming out.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's going to be arcade perfect.
[SPEAKER_19]: So there's going to be 100 plus songs.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's going to be coming out one week before all the DDR stuff.
[SPEAKER_19]: There's rumors, though, that it's going to be coming out also for the US PS2 and the Xbox later on.
[SPEAKER_19]: Also, they've added a few different modes in there.
[SPEAKER_19]: They have a mode that's kind of like where you just watch videos, the background videos, that type of thing.
[SPEAKER_19]: and also supposedly the PC version USB pads that shipped with the old version, Premiere, I think actually are going to be working with the PS2 version.
[SPEAKER_19]: So that should be pretty interesting.
[SPEAKER_19]: Looks pretty cool so far.
[SPEAKER_19]: Other than that, starting, looks like this coming week in Korea...
[SPEAKER_19]: at Animero headquarters will be beta testing for Pump It Up Exceed 2, which they have really, really insane details on that.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm sure that will be coming next week as stuff leaks out from the beta test location.
[SPEAKER_19]: So that's your Pump It Up news.
[SPEAKER_17]: Exciting.
[SPEAKER_21]: I think it's very strange that Pump It Up could possibly come to the U.S.
[SPEAKER_21]: And then they're also saying, they're rumoring that In The Groove could be coming to the home versions as well, so it's going to be very interesting.
[SPEAKER_21]: I doubt that one, but I do too, but they're saying it, so I guess I should acknowledge it.
[SPEAKER_19]: I doubt that.
[SPEAKER_19]: But, no, seriously, McSeed, though, is doing extremely well, like in some of the other countries that, you know, non-English countries like Mexico is fucking hot over there.
[SPEAKER_19]: And, um,
[SPEAKER_19]: I couldn't, I mean, why not?
[SPEAKER_19]: Try releasing it over here, see how it does.
[SPEAKER_19]: Because I'm sure, I mean, most of the stuff they've got is in-house artists anyway, so you're not really, you know, going to lose money on licensing as far as music goes.
[SPEAKER_19]: Really, there's not much to lose there.
[SPEAKER_19]: I mean, other than, you know, oh, you have to make some new pads or something, but I think you'd do pretty well over here.
[SPEAKER_19]: You know, give it a shot.
[SPEAKER_19]: I mean, it can't be any worse than, like, say, you know, Britney's Dance Beat and all that crap.
[SPEAKER_19]: I mean, at least it's a step above all that stuff, so, you know, hey, why not?
[SPEAKER_21]: I think it would be very interesting if they did give Pump It Up a home release for this reason, because DDR, they've kind of stopped doing the arcade thing, and I think especially with DDR, or I'm sorry, with Konami USA, they've kind of given up on doing the arcade thing, there's not going to be a new arcade mix unless hell freezes over, so basically it is a possibility, but very low chance, low, low, low chance.
[SPEAKER_21]: So basically they've pretty much stuck to the home versions, and I think everybody understands that the home versions are where they make their money.
[SPEAKER_21]: and Konami of America, they push the home versions.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's their bread and butter for DDR.
[SPEAKER_21]: They see the future of DDR being these home versions, and that's why they never really threw a fit over the import mixes, at least as far as I can tell, because the import mixes of DDR Arcade kind of serve as promotion for the home versions.
[SPEAKER_21]: So everything works out.
[SPEAKER_21]: Everybody gets their share.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, now if Pump It Up ends up coming out for the home versions...
[SPEAKER_21]: Was Konami going to take issue to that?
[SPEAKER_21]: Is there anything they can do about it?
[SPEAKER_21]: I mean, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_21]: I mean, there were those rumors a while back that Andomero and Konami might have had it out in court, and that's why, you know, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's a bunch of rumors going on out there.
[SPEAKER_21]: You think Konami would take issue with that?
[SPEAKER_21]: What do you think would happen?
[SPEAKER_21]: Anybody have a thought?
[SPEAKER_21]: Loki, I'd especially be curious what you think.
[SPEAKER_21]: You always seem to have a strong opinion.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't know if they're legally able to bring it over here, actually, because of the whole lawsuit thing earlier, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_19]: They're
[SPEAKER_19]: You can't really... I mean, DDR hasn't gone after... Konami hasn't gone after any of these other games that have similar rhythm type things with them.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm sure it'll be fine.
[SPEAKER_19]: I mean, it'd be pretty cheap if they just went after them if they started doing well.
[SPEAKER_19]: I mean, oh yeah, well, now that they're doing well, I guess, yeah, we have a problem with it now.
[SPEAKER_19]: But, yeah, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_19]: To be honest, I really don't know.
[SPEAKER_19]: But,
[SPEAKER_19]: Here's my concern, okay, about Indie Groove coming to the home console.
[SPEAKER_19]: First off, I don't think it's going to happen, only because, one, it's going to be hard.
[SPEAKER_19]: I mean, making a console game is a little harder than making, you know, just the arcade, you know, ports and stuff.
[SPEAKER_19]: Because, I mean, hell, anyone can hook up a PC to an arcade machine.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's not that hard.
[SPEAKER_19]: Now, programming for the home console is a little different.
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, if it's fucking hard enough, they have 11 12-footers in the arcade.
[SPEAKER_19]: How the fuck are you going to play that on a softpad?
[SPEAKER_19]: That's never going to work.
[SPEAKER_19]: So that's my concern right there.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't think it's ever going to happen.
[SPEAKER_19]: I mean, I'm sure they'd like to see it happen, but feasibly, I don't think it's going to happen.
[SPEAKER_21]: Very interesting thought.
[SPEAKER_21]: Anybody else have a thought on In the Groove coming out for home or what Pump It Up may do for DDR?
[SPEAKER_16]: Well, Pump It Up actually did have a home release on PC.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's right, I forgot about that.
[SPEAKER_21]: Was that in the U.S., though?
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, yeah, actually, Red Octane sells it, and I don't think they sell the import DDRs, or do they?
[SPEAKER_21]: I could be wrong.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah, I saw that too.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, do they?
[SPEAKER_16]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_21]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm not sure.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, I completely forgot about that.
[SPEAKER_21]: You're right, Pump It Up did have a previous home release on the PC.
[SPEAKER_21]: Not that the dance market on PC is very lucrative.
[SPEAKER_21]: I believe the folks that created DDR PC found that out the hard way.
[SPEAKER_21]: You know, I saw those games going for like $10 a pop at Fry's not too long ago.
[SPEAKER_21]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_16]: I think I got mine for about the same.
[SPEAKER_21]: Do you think that Pump It Up coming out for the home version would help DDR, or do you think it's going to hurt it?
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, I think that after they compare, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: It can depend.
[SPEAKER_13]: There's different factors to consider.
[SPEAKER_21]: I think the biggest turnoff is that you have to get a whole other dance pad for Pump It Up.
[SPEAKER_21]: Because...
[SPEAKER_21]: Although it would be very easy, you would think, with the ignition pad, you could just use the buttons, the X, O, circle, square, which are in the corners, but there's no center button.
[SPEAKER_21]: The center doesn't do anything on those pads, as far as I know, so you're kind of screwed there.
[SPEAKER_19]: The pump-it-up pads not only do have the corner buttons, they do have the up, down, left, right buttons also, because those are for song select stuff.
[SPEAKER_19]: They use those.
[SPEAKER_19]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_21]: So theoretically, any DDR pad that has all the corner buttons would work, except the official Konami ones, because they don't have triangle and square in the back like most of the other pads do, except all the other pads are missing that center button.
[SPEAKER_21]: So, now you're going to have a whole new dance pad if you want to play Pump It Up at home.
[SPEAKER_21]: And how many people are that obsessed with Pump It Up where they're going to spend all the money on that?
[SPEAKER_21]: And how many stores are going to pick up those Pump It Up pads for commercial sale?
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_21]: It'd be interesting.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, I guess what we're going to do now is we're going to take another break.
[SPEAKER_21]: When we come back, we'll hopefully have everything set up so we can try calling frequency again.
[SPEAKER_21]: That'll be very cool.
[SPEAKER_21]: If not, I guess we'll have ourselves a cage match.
[SPEAKER_21]: That'll be some fun.
[SPEAKER_21]: And we'll talk about some more DDR, Bomani, when we come back.
[SPEAKER_21]: In this break, let's do... Well, you know what I kind of want to do, if I can find the music?
[SPEAKER_21]: Let's do some DDR Disney.
[SPEAKER_16]: We play fire.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, I think that's a good idea.
[SPEAKER_21]: Let's see if I can find the directory that has all my random stuff in it.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, shoot, not all the Disney stuff's in here.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay, we'll see what we can do.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, I do have the Mickey Mouse March.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay, well, we have enough to do a break.
[SPEAKER_21]: We'll be back after this.
Thank you for watching!
Mickey Mouse, Mickey Mouse, forever let's go, I wanna hide, hide, hide, hide Come along and sing a song and join the juggling, M-I-C-K-Y-M-U-S-E Come along and sing a song and join the juggling, M-I-C-K-Y-M-U-S-E Mickey Mouse, Mickey Mouse, we have fun with Mickey Mouse
Fire!
One, two, three, FIRE!
Thanks for watching!
and many more.
[SPEAKER_10]: and many more.
[SPEAKER_30]: And now, let's listen in to an Orange Lounge Radio staff meeting as they debate some of the new programming coming to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_21]: Jamie, I have a suggestion about some of the music in our Bomani Music and More program.
[SPEAKER_21]: Can we talk about that?
[SPEAKER_11]: No subject will ever be taboo.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, I was thinking maybe we should move Pump Up the Volume from Tuesday Nights.
[SPEAKER_21]: Except, of course, a subject that was just under discussion.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay, well, what would you think if maybe we cut back on some of the tack music we play on the station?
[SPEAKER_19]: I collect your fucking head.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just like this fucker here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh my god, why did you do that to Loki?
[SPEAKER_28]: The holic thing on episode 69 was just a joke!
[SPEAKER_28]: Now if any of you sons of bitches got anything else to say, now's the fucking time!
[SPEAKER_30]: Orange Lounge Radio, where everybody has a say.
[SPEAKER_21]: You know what I never understood, Jamie, is why does your voice sound so different in that promo?
[SPEAKER_16]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_16]: I was taking these voice acting lessons and decided to sound like Lucy Liu.
[SPEAKER_21]: I see.
[SPEAKER_21]: Maybe it was something like that.
[SPEAKER_16]: I think I did pretty well, don't you?
[SPEAKER_21]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_21]: Now, I got this new thing for Skype that allows us to dial phone numbers, so I'm going to try this real fast.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm going to do a test.
[SPEAKER_21]: I hate to do this live on air, but damn it, I want this to happen.
[SPEAKER_21]: Ooh, it worked.
[SPEAKER_21]: What the hell do you want?
[SPEAKER_21]: I think it worked.
[SPEAKER_21]: Hello, can you hear me on this thing?
[SPEAKER_20]: Yeah, there's a delay, but that's cool.
[SPEAKER_20]: I'm on a phone, and I'm here.
[SPEAKER_16]: You need to hang up.
[SPEAKER_16]: We don't want any.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, I'm hanging up on him.
[SPEAKER_21]: Cool, it worked.
[SPEAKER_16]: Okay, so maybe... Telemarket Loki.
[SPEAKER_21]: Hopefully we can do that and make it work.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's a little quiet, but maybe I can tweak the volume settings in there and get it to work.
[SPEAKER_16]: Would you like to take a survey?
[SPEAKER_16]: You're crazy.
[SPEAKER_16]: No, I'm not crazy.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm slightly strange.
[SPEAKER_16]: Loki's the crazy one with his portal to hell and all that.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right.
[SPEAKER_21]: How's it going there, Loki?
[SPEAKER_21]: You're trying to figure out what that Freestyler song could be, huh?
[SPEAKER_21]: You're trying to do research there.
[SPEAKER_21]: What were you doing there earlier?
[SPEAKER_21]: You were hacking that master file thing that... I don't even... I can't even remember what the hell this thing is.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's the master song list.
[SPEAKER_19]: I was looking at it.
Where does that come from?
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, this is from... It's a document that... Or it's a file that's in... Well, this one is in the DDR Extreme USA...
[SPEAKER_19]: CD or DVD.
[SPEAKER_19]: So I was looking to see, because there's a few songs in there.
[SPEAKER_19]: I see some from the new Dancing Stage game that's going to be coming out.
[SPEAKER_19]: Then there's a few that I didn't recognize.
[SPEAKER_19]: So I was just seeing if I could figure it out.
[SPEAKER_19]: Because in here, remember we reported a few weeks back about Superstar?
[SPEAKER_19]: That's in there.
[SPEAKER_19]: So, you know, just stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_19]: So I was just seeing if it might be in there.
[SPEAKER_19]: Because it might be.
[SPEAKER_19]: You never know.
[SPEAKER_16]: What is that you're... No, I found out... I had the microphone in my lap and people can hear me being IM'd.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_16]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_21]: I guess what we're going to do is go into the Orange Lounge Radio cage match for this week.
[SPEAKER_21]: You want to change your song?
[SPEAKER_21]: Do you have a new one?
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah, um... Hold on a second.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, we're going to get into the Orange Lounge Radio Cage Match tonight.
[SPEAKER_21]: Last week in the Orange Lounge Radio Cage Match, Echo Image won for the fourth week in a row, meaning they are retired.
[SPEAKER_21]: Goodbye, you're gone, you're out of here.
[SPEAKER_21]: But let's have one more moment to remember the Echo Image, the very first song ever to be retired in the Orange Lounge Radio Cage Match here.
[SPEAKER_21]: Let me...
[SPEAKER_21]: The song was called Come Back, and here's a little bit of Come Back for you to remember this song by.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, that's enough of the song.
[SPEAKER_21]: You've heard enough of it over the past four weeks.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, so you get three brand new songs in their entirety tonight, each host bringing one song to the table.
[SPEAKER_21]: And who's going to go first tonight?
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes, I will.
[SPEAKER_21]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_21]: I never get to go first because I hardly ever win this thing.
[SPEAKER_21]: So, I'm going to go first tonight.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm going to play my song.
[SPEAKER_21]: And, whoops, that's not the song I'm doing.
[SPEAKER_21]: My song is a song by Ian Van Dow, who is the guy who did Will I from DDR Max 2, and he has a new song out, and the song is called Reason, and that's going to be my cage match pick for tonight.
[SPEAKER_21]: So, enjoy Reason by Ian Van Dow, my pick, song number one tonight.
Together, or is it time to say goodbye?
Where is the love?
Give me a reason To hold on to what we've got There must be a reason To hold on to what we've got Time has come to set things right
is it worth another fight tell me the truth
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: Where is the love?
[SPEAKER_02]: Tell me, is there hope inside?
[SPEAKER_10]: Gotta read between the lines Where is the love?
Thank you.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, that was song number one in tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_21]: That was Ian Van Dow with Reason.
[SPEAKER_21]: Let's go around and see if they had a reason to like or hate this song in the studio.
[SPEAKER_21]: Jamie!
[SPEAKER_16]: It's chancy.
[SPEAKER_16]: Um, again, I'm really burned on chant.
[SPEAKER_16]: But it's not bad.
[SPEAKER_16]: I mean, I've heard it before.
[SPEAKER_16]: Um, just seven.
[SPEAKER_16]: Seven and a half.
[SPEAKER_21]: I actually thought Jamie would give it a lower score, because I remember her saying she was sick of Trance, but dammit, I'm out of songs!
[SPEAKER_21]: That's a new one that I happen to like.
[SPEAKER_21]: Bradley, what'd you think?
[SPEAKER_29]: I thought it was pretty good, I'd give it an 8.
[SPEAKER_21]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_21]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm not sick of Trance, but I'm sick of Ian Vandell, so I think it's a 6.
[SPEAKER_21]: I like it, it's happy, it's not my favorite Ian Vandell song, but I think it is worthy of a cage match title, I'd give it an 8.5.
[SPEAKER_15]: Uh, Infant Doll's cool.
[SPEAKER_15]: Uh, I'll give it an 8.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_21]: Let's go on to song number 2, which is coming to us courtesy of the lovely DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_21]: DarkSakura, what did you pick for us tonight?
[SPEAKER_16]: Well, I need to find the name of the song again because I remembered that you had it because you burned my CD.
[SPEAKER_21]: Let me give you a hint.
[SPEAKER_21]: The song is called Everybody Wants You to Emerge.
[SPEAKER_16]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's a mix of Emerge by Fisher Spooner and, uh...
[SPEAKER_16]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_21]: Whether you love or hate the show, it's got a great bouncy soundtrack to it.
[SPEAKER_16]: So, let's see if this... Basically enough, I don't like the opening song.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, that's kind of weird, huh?
[SPEAKER_21]: I know, the opening song is like too gay, but the rest of it's really good.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah, it's like 90s pop dance, you know?
[SPEAKER_16]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_16]: Like, I feel like... Oh, you should have heard the thing on Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_21]: I did a whole... Did you hear... Oh, I did a whole block of 90s dance.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm detesting you, I heard.
[SPEAKER_16]: And I need that, by the way.
[SPEAKER_16]: I remember being in Mobile and my friend's little Honda thing...
[SPEAKER_16]: If for some reason, heaven forbid, Orange Moms Radio ever went belly up and we weren't doing this show anymore, I think I would have to start an early 90s dance music station.
[SPEAKER_16]: That would be rad.
[SPEAKER_21]: Maybe we just ought to start one anyway.
[SPEAKER_21]: Compete with ourselves.
[SPEAKER_21]: Hey, there's somebody out there that I know we're trying to negotiate with somebody out there to do a new show on our network.
[SPEAKER_21]: But they're thinking of ideas for the show.
[SPEAKER_21]: There's a great one right there.
[SPEAKER_21]: And I know you like that kind of music, person.
[SPEAKER_19]: In San Diego, they have an 80s and 90s radio station.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's the best of both decades.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_20]: Popular when I get Grand Theft Auto tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right, anyway, anyway, we're getting way off subject.
[SPEAKER_21]: We're getting way off subject.
[SPEAKER_21]: Way off subject.
[SPEAKER_21]: Let's go to Fisher Spooner versus Billy Splyer with Everybody Wants to Emerge.
[SPEAKER_21]: Enjoy.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: You don't need to be much.
[SPEAKER_10]: From nothing you don't need to step away You don't need to emerge From nothing you don't need to step away Step away
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: You don't need to emerge from nothing You don't need to turn away Just one more, one more, one more, one more, one more, one more Everybody love me
[SPEAKER_03]: Feels good, looks good, sounds good, looks good, feels good too Feels good, looks good
[SPEAKER_10]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_21]: Song number two in tonight's cage match, Fisher Spooner vs. Billy Squire.
[SPEAKER_21]: Everybody wants you to emerge.
[SPEAKER_21]: Let's emerge our decisions on that song.
[SPEAKER_21]: Jamie.
[SPEAKER_16]: You know, I really like that mix of it.
[SPEAKER_16]: It wasn't quite what I had remembered it to be, but I still like it.
[SPEAKER_16]: So it gets an A from me.
[SPEAKER_16]: What do you think I'm going to bring you next time?
[SPEAKER_22]: I was going to say, it samples an old song in there, because I've heard that old song at the raids before, I'm almost positive.
[SPEAKER_16]: Well, Emergence is really cool, the song itself, but I mean, I really like that mix, because it's a lot different than the original.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, let's go on.
[SPEAKER_21]: Bradley.
[SPEAKER_29]: I had no idea what the hell they were saying, and it filled me with, eh.
[SPEAKER_29]: So I give it a five.
[SPEAKER_22]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_20]: I second the, eh.
[SPEAKER_20]: It was just like, it...
[SPEAKER_20]: It got annoying.
[SPEAKER_20]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_21]: Actually, when I heard that song, I kind of thought, this might be like a Guitar Freaks fun song.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's kind of funky.
[SPEAKER_21]: I like it.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was funky.
[SPEAKER_21]: Seven.
[SPEAKER_21]: Angel.
[SPEAKER_14]: That was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_15]: Seven and a half.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right.
[SPEAKER_21]: Remember, our votes don't mean shit.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's your votes in the chat room that really decide this.
[SPEAKER_21]: You got one more song that you can pick from.
[SPEAKER_21]: God help us all, it's Loki's.
[SPEAKER_20]: Ah, man.
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, I have a few things to win you over already.
[SPEAKER_19]: Not trance, and short.
[SPEAKER_19]: The other thing I forgot to mention I did this week was saw Team America World Police.
[SPEAKER_19]: And this is America, Fuck Yeah.
Team America
America, fuck yeah!
Coming again to save the motherfucking day, yeah America, fuck yeah!
Freedom is the only way, yeah Terrorists, your game is through Cause now you have some answer to America, fuck yeah!
So lick my butt and suck on my bone America, fuck yeah!
What you gonna do when we come for you now?
[SPEAKER_09]: Together, Fuck Yeah, Ramon, Fuck Yeah, The Gap, Fuck Yeah, Baseball, Fuck Yeah, NFL, Fuck Yeah, Rock and Roll, Fuck Yeah, Internet, Fuck Yeah, Levering, Fuck Yeah, Fuck Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Starbuck, Fuck Yeah, Disney World, Fuck Yeah, Porno, Fuck Yeah, Vallejo, Fuck Yeah, Reebok, Fuck Yeah, Fake Tits, Fuck Yeah, Sushi, Fuck Yeah, Taco Bell, Fuck Yeah, Rodeo, Fuck Yeah, Black Bath & Beyond, Fuck Yeah, Fuck Yeah
[SPEAKER_09]: Liberty, White Slip, The Atomos, Band-Aid, Las Vegas, Christmas, Immigrant, Popeye, Democrat, Republican, Republican, Bull
[SPEAKER_21]: All right.
[SPEAKER_21]: Gotta love Loki.
[SPEAKER_21]: Song number three in tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_21]: From the Team America World Police soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_21]: America, fuck yeah.
[SPEAKER_21]: Fuck yeah or fuck no, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_16]: It would be a humorous song for about ten minutes and then if you don't write... It gets fixed.
[SPEAKER_16]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_16]: I have no desire to see the movie.
[SPEAKER_22]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_22]: Arcadian.
[SPEAKER_29]: Fuck maybe.
[SPEAKER_29]: I give it like a 7.5.
[SPEAKER_29]: Alright, Loki.
[SPEAKER_19]: I give it a 10.
[SPEAKER_19]: I was specifically instructed by my girlfriend not to sing the song any longer, so I give it a 10.
[SPEAKER_21]: I hope you don't sing that while you're trying to have sex.
[SPEAKER_21]: Fuck yeah!
[SPEAKER_21]: That's beyond!
[SPEAKER_21]: I give that song the same score I'd give the movie, a 4.
[SPEAKER_21]: Angel.
[SPEAKER_21]: No, a four out of ten.
[SPEAKER_15]: Um, it was okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: I was just going to see the movie last night.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's what's important.
[SPEAKER_15]: Um, five and a half.
[SPEAKER_15]: Go see what?
[SPEAKER_15]: You could go see a good movie instead.
[SPEAKER_15]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_20]: Seriously?
[SPEAKER_21]: If you're going to go see a movie, go see The Grudge, but go on a school night where the kiddies can't go.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_21]: You've heard what we think, now it's time to hear what you think.
[SPEAKER_21]: You're going to decide tonight's winner from three brand new songs while Loki throws pens at me in anger of my score.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, let's hear a clip from all three songs you can vote for tonight.
[SPEAKER_21]: Song number one you can vote for tonight is Reason by Ian Van Dow.
[SPEAKER_02]: Time has come to set things right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Is it worth another fight?
[SPEAKER_21]: And song number two in tonight's cage match is Fisher Spooner vs. Billy Squire, Everybody Wants You To Emerge.
[SPEAKER_21]: And song number three in tonight's cage match from the Team America World Police soundtrack, America, Fuck Yeah.
[SPEAKER_21]: Place vote now.
[SPEAKER_21]: Send a private message to Sky in the chat room with your vote.
[SPEAKER_21]: Song number one, song number two, or Sky number three.
[SPEAKER_21]: Song number three.
[SPEAKER_21]: Your votes can decide it all.
[SPEAKER_21]: Now, you know the scary thing, though, about that Fuck Yeah song is it's actually, if you took out the lyrics, it kind of sounds like a Guitar Freak song.
[SPEAKER_21]: It really does.
[SPEAKER_16]: Like an old one.
[SPEAKER_21]: Wait, we're losing you there.
[SPEAKER_21]: Adjust the bottom mic there.
[SPEAKER_29]: Oh, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_21]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_29]: Especially with the speeding up, like, bass drum part.
[SPEAKER_29]: Or kick drum or whatever.
[SPEAKER_21]: Just like the little synthesizers and everything kind of make it... Yeah.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, it makes it... It gives it that sound.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right.
[SPEAKER_29]: You know what it sounds like?
[SPEAKER_16]: It sounds like PBR.
[SPEAKER_29]: It's like PBR.
[SPEAKER_29]: Like, the end of PBR, that's what it sounds like.
[SPEAKER_21]: Kind of.
[SPEAKER_29]: It sounds like PBR.
[SPEAKER_21]: God, I haven't heard Limousine in a long, long time.
[SPEAKER_16]: Limousine!
[SPEAKER_16]: Strong bad.
[SPEAKER_20]: Oh, boy, oh, boy.
[SPEAKER_21]: I can't believe that this is the first time we've had to retire a song.
[SPEAKER_21]: You know we've been doing the cage match for almost two years now, and that's the first time we've had to retire a song?
[SPEAKER_21]: We actually haven't done the cage match since episode one.
[SPEAKER_21]: It was something we added to the show when we went three hours on episode 20, I think?
[SPEAKER_21]: Because the show only used to be two hours.
[SPEAKER_20]: All right.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right, what we're going to do now, we're going to try and get that connection that we had earlier.
[SPEAKER_21]: We were trying to get frequency from the East Coast on the phone.
[SPEAKER_21]: You guys, I'm sure you know this guy.
[SPEAKER_21]: If you're on DDR Freak, if you're on Bomani Style, I think he's a mod on both those sites.
[SPEAKER_21]: And he's definitely out there.
[SPEAKER_21]: If you're on the East Coast, you definitely, definitely know who this guy is.
[SPEAKER_21]: So we're going to give him a call because we want to ask him some questions that were kind of spawned from last week's show.
[SPEAKER_21]: So let's have a look and see if we can get frequency on the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_21]: Hi, is this frequency?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_21]: Hey, how are you doing?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm doing okay.
[SPEAKER_21]: Fantastic.
[SPEAKER_21]: The week was fine.
[SPEAKER_21]: No problems there.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, look at that.
[SPEAKER_21]: There's an appearance from the guy next door.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_23]: The guy next door has a ham radio, and I'd like to interfere with all the electronics in my house.
[SPEAKER_21]: I guess so.
[SPEAKER_23]: The East Coast Tournament was... The tournament itself wasn't really a good tournament, in my opinion.
[SPEAKER_23]: A lot of the stuff just ran wrong and things weren't properly organized and things like that.
[SPEAKER_23]: And we, after the entire thing was done with, we realized what the problems were and we're going to fix those for the next years and things like that.
[SPEAKER_23]: But as publicity for DDR...
[SPEAKER_23]: It's skyrocketed.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, now this is... Now, we actually had a caller last week.
[SPEAKER_21]: Zachu called in.
[SPEAKER_21]: He said something about the crowds that had come to the DDR tournament were bigger than the ones for, what, the Blue Man Group and... Yeah, it's literally... You could literally pick any exhibition there.
[SPEAKER_23]: Blue Man Group was there for an hour, and Ludacris and some other Def Jam artists were there for a little while.
[SPEAKER_23]: Opie and Anthony were there for a little while.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, that's right.
[SPEAKER_21]: Opie and Anthony was the other one he mentioned.
[SPEAKER_21]: They're hacks anyway.
[SPEAKER_21]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_23]: because these people were representing, I don't know, XM Radio and other, you know, like Opie Ante was at XM Radio for like an hour or something like that.
[SPEAKER_23]: Obviously, they had a crowd for a little while, you know, but, you know, you can only stay so long and listen to Opie Ante, I guess.
[SPEAKER_23]: But, yeah, everyone was, everyone just stayed and watched people step on arrows all day.
[SPEAKER_23]: It was amazing.
[SPEAKER_23]: It was truly amazing.
[SPEAKER_21]: Even Perfect Attack?
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_23]: More so than Freestyle, actually.
[SPEAKER_23]: There was a lot of people watching Perfect Attack that were just like, wow, this is amazing how they do that.
[SPEAKER_23]: And half the people are like, even though they don't know what they're doing, they still want to know how they do that.
[SPEAKER_23]: But publicity-wise, Sammy, the person who put these two women together, and myself made them up.
[SPEAKER_23]: A whole bunch of contacts on Thursday because the press was the people who were allowed on Thursday.
[SPEAKER_21]: I was going to say, I bet a lot of press was at this event.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, we had a lot of press.
[SPEAKER_21]: So does this mean we can be looking forward to seeing DDR in the news anytime soon?
[SPEAKER_21]: Or in the press?
[SPEAKER_21]: Some big stuff?
[SPEAKER_23]: Maybe not in the news and the press.
[SPEAKER_23]: There's already been enough stuff in the news and the press that it's in the wrong angle.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_21]: I guess that's very true.
[SPEAKER_23]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_23]: The problem is that the angle is way lost.
[SPEAKER_23]: Everyone likes that way lost angle, and everyone jumps on that.
[SPEAKER_23]: I was at Fox News a couple weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_21]: I was actually going to ask you about that, the Fox News thing.
[SPEAKER_23]: I'll tell you exactly what happened.
[SPEAKER_23]: What they did was, on Friday night, I get a call from these people.
[SPEAKER_23]: And I'm like, yeah, sure, I'll come in.
[SPEAKER_23]: They just want DDR.
[SPEAKER_23]: I'm like, okay, I could do DDR.
[SPEAKER_23]: So I come in.
[SPEAKER_23]: Uh, next day, because that's when they want me for the interview, live, next day.
[SPEAKER_08]: Right.
[SPEAKER_23]: With no preparation, uh, I'm sitting in the briefing room, not getting briefs.
[SPEAKER_23]: I was actually sitting next to the person who was interviewing me, and I had absolutely no idea, until, like, I was actually called in.
[SPEAKER_21]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_23]: And once, when I got into the studio, the first thing the girl says is, well, you're not a kid.
[SPEAKER_23]: And I'm like, no, sorry.
[SPEAKER_23]: Someone should have probably informed you about something, too.
[SPEAKER_21]: They thought they were getting a 12-year-old?
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, they thought a 12-year-old was going to end up coming in and doing an interview.
[SPEAKER_21]: I remember that, because we were watching the clip here in studio during a show about a month ago, and we were having a little fun with how bad the interviewer was, the person who was interviewing you, and it sounded like she was talking down to you.
[SPEAKER_21]: A lot of the questions she was asking, I remember, didn't she say at one point in the interview, gosh, how old are you?
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, I was 21, but the thing that got me the most was when she said, you're part of the DDR freaks, and I'm like... Yeah, that bug does too.
[SPEAKER_23]: Are you serious?
[SPEAKER_23]: What are you doing to me right now?
[SPEAKER_21]: It's obvious they hadn't done any research.
[SPEAKER_23]: So, like, I mean, I'm doing it for DDR, you know, to get the publicity up there for it, so even though it's just the wrong angle for it, I mean, I tried to jump onto, you know, the competition thing, she just tossed it right off of that, so...
[SPEAKER_23]: Regardless, they're not ready for it.
[SPEAKER_21]: Right.
[SPEAKER_23]: But, you know, upcoming now... Wait, actually, I have a quick question for you.
[SPEAKER_21]: I have a quick question for you, though, before we change the subject.
[SPEAKER_21]: Do you think that part of that might be Konami's fault?
[SPEAKER_21]: Because Konami's kind of going the way Los Angles with this?
[SPEAKER_23]: Um... Konami hasn't done much.
[SPEAKER_23]: I'll tell you right now.
[SPEAKER_23]: They haven't done much in the publicity of DER.
[SPEAKER_23]: They...
[SPEAKER_23]: and they don't really need to because it just so happens that mixes keep selling, home mixes at least, keep selling.
[SPEAKER_21]: Word of mouth is a powerful thing.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, it just happens.
[SPEAKER_23]: People see these dance mats in the game stores and they're like, oh, what does that go with?
[SPEAKER_23]: And they go with this DPR game and they buy it and take it home.
[SPEAKER_23]: And there's a lot of people who actually play at home and they just don't know about the community behind it and its competition and how big this can really be.
[SPEAKER_23]: So, Konami really actually doesn't do much, but this upcoming year, you might see some stuff coming out.
[SPEAKER_21]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_21]: So I guess other little things you probably can't talk about?
[SPEAKER_23]: I can talk about them, it's just that a lot of the stuff is, you know... You don't want to say anything and then not have it happen?
[SPEAKER_23]: I'll say what we want to do, I'll say what we're planning.
[SPEAKER_23]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_23]: First off...
[SPEAKER_23]: First off, Sammy and I have a meeting with Ziff Davis Media tomorrow at 11 a.m.
[SPEAKER_18]: Aren't Ziff Davis Media the folks that run G4 Tech TV?
[SPEAKER_23]: They might be.
[SPEAKER_23]: I'm not too sure about the whole business.
[SPEAKER_23]: But I know that these are the people who put together the actual convention last weekend.
[SPEAKER_21]: Ah, okay.
[SPEAKER_23]: And they got Microsoft and XM and Intel and Best Buy and all those other companies to come down and, you know...
[SPEAKER_23]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_23]: They were so interested in our place that they want us to set up the next year's tournament now with sponsors.
[SPEAKER_23]: They want all these companies that came to the convention to help sponsor us in whatever way possible.
[SPEAKER_23]: We're looking at a really big grand prize at the end of it.
[SPEAKER_23]: No real dollar amount has been set.
[SPEAKER_23]: We're looking at something huge, something enough to get many more people to end up coming out.
[SPEAKER_21]: Correct me if I'm wrong, but this is coming off the heels of a $1,000 grand prize tournament, correct?
[SPEAKER_23]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_21]: And you guys are talking about something bigger?
[SPEAKER_23]: Right.
[SPEAKER_21]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_23]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_23]: The $1,000 was actually put up by Sammy, but if we have people like Microsoft who want to put up
[SPEAKER_23]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_23]: Another meeting I have coming up soon is with Fuse TV.
[SPEAKER_23]: I don't know if you guys get that out there.
[SPEAKER_21]: They used to be Much Music, right?
[SPEAKER_21]: Weren't they Much Music?
[SPEAKER_21]: And then they turned into Fuse?
[SPEAKER_23]: I think that sounds about right.
[SPEAKER_21]: I think it's a subscription channel out here.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_21]: But I've heard of them.
[SPEAKER_23]: So, I have a producer contact that I actually made.
[SPEAKER_23]: He absolutely adores the game.
[SPEAKER_23]: He just found it on Thursday when he showed up.
[SPEAKER_23]: And he absolutely adores the game.
[SPEAKER_23]: I have a meeting with him in a couple of weeks and we're going to pitch an idea, both together, to Fuse about a weekly DDR show.
[SPEAKER_21]: A weekly DDR show?
[SPEAKER_23]: Weekly, right.
[SPEAKER_21]: Not some kind of DDR special you're talking about like a weekly DDR show?
[SPEAKER_23]: Right, exactly.
[SPEAKER_23]: We're probably looking at, like the only idea was that so far that I've had was a weekly tournament.
[SPEAKER_21]: Is this the OMG DDR game show that people have talked about for years?
[SPEAKER_23]: I've never heard of that, actually.
[SPEAKER_21]: I see these threads occasionally on the message board where they're like, OMG DDR game show type thing, could DDR be a game show?
[SPEAKER_21]: Maybe it's just that it's a couple years ago, and I'm... I don't know, it just seems like I've seen these kind of ideas going around before where people are like, OMG, they should have a DDR TV show and stuff, and now you're saying that that's exactly what you're going to go pitch in a couple weeks.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's probably not going to end up being a game show.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's going to be something like... Do you remember... I don't even know if you guys have this out here.
[SPEAKER_23]: Do you guys remember when they had this thing called the WMCA Championships?
[SPEAKER_23]: It was a martial arts championship.
[SPEAKER_23]: I actually remember this.
[SPEAKER_23]: It was a lot like the WWF, except it was karate.
[SPEAKER_23]: I do remember seeing a couple episodes of this.
[SPEAKER_23]: It used to be on Channel 31, remember?
[SPEAKER_21]: I think I want to do something similar to that.
[SPEAKER_21]: You know, like, porno ends up meeting the real world in MTV kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_20]: and many more.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, we're not gonna, we're gonna, you know, we're probably gonna show how people train, and maybe do some interviews, and maybe some little cute skits in there, but a lot of it's gonna be in the, uh, in my, you know, my thing, we're gonna actually just end up doing, like, a weekly tournament, you know, like Red Team vs. Blue Team, you know, try to ham it up for a little while, maybe like a BattleBots kind of thing, where every, like, month we end up doing a championship, or every few months or something like that, and they get some kind of crazy trophy that we, like, you know, pass around.
[SPEAKER_21]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_21]: Do you guys think...
[SPEAKER_21]: Do you guys think you would run into any resistance from Konami?
[SPEAKER_23]: Funny you bring that up.
[SPEAKER_23]: Sammy actually got a call last week from someone from Konami who happens to actually end up being the VP.
[SPEAKER_23]: The VP is very, very interested in sponsoring the tournament in 2005.
[SPEAKER_20]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yes, and considering now that we have this contact here, which is going to be...
[SPEAKER_23]: and many more.
[SPEAKER_23]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_23]: EDR comes up on the television, maybe ESPN or whatever, and everyone knows what a great is and how many greats a JSB gets on this song.
[SPEAKER_23]: Everyone knows the stats and knows the players and roots for their favorite team, like the New York Blue Impulse versus the California Trip Machines or whatever.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's what we're looking to do.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's a hell of a goal, but that's a neat goal.
[SPEAKER_21]: Loki, you look like you want to say something here.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's what we're pushing for.
[SPEAKER_23]: I want to expect that there's going to be a huge jump in publicity in this next coming year.
[SPEAKER_19]: I hope so.
[SPEAKER_19]: But, like, you know, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_19]: It seems like it's going to be about as popular as Extreme Dodgeball or, you know, everything like that.
[SPEAKER_23]: It might end up being looking like that, at least for this first year coming.
[SPEAKER_23]: But with a lot of the more context that we're getting, you know, especially Konami, it looks like there might be more push for it.
[SPEAKER_23]: You know, considering it's a new genre of video game, it's already a sport in Norway, you know, so it's got potential.
[SPEAKER_19]: It reminds me though of like that webcomic that's 10K Commotion or whatever.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's just like, you know, with all the DDR drama and then you have the teams competing in a giant like tournament thing.
[SPEAKER_19]: It just, it seems a lot like that.
[SPEAKER_19]: Not that it's a bad idea, I think it's a pretty cool idea.
[SPEAKER_23]: Well, you know, there's drama everywhere.
[SPEAKER_23]: There's drama in Sublubrities and stuff like that, so it's not going to be, you know, more common.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'll tell you what, if you ever want to take the DDR drama angle with this show, like Degrassi DDR League or whatever, I could give you pages and pages of real-life fire drama.
[SPEAKER_23]: No, no, I don't have pages and pages.
[SPEAKER_23]: I think just about everyone knows I have pages and pages.
[SPEAKER_23]: You know, getting out of the tournament last week, I, you know...
[SPEAKER_23]: A lot of the people actually ended up thanking, you know, Sammy for putting together the tournament, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_23]: And to tell you the truth, Sammy screwed up a lot of things about the tournament.
[SPEAKER_23]: And there were a lot of things that if he was more prepared, he would have actually ended up, you know, doing a better work with it.
[SPEAKER_23]: You know, and I ended up trying to fix a lot of the behind-the-scenes and things like that.
[SPEAKER_23]: And a lot of people don't even remember me being there.
[SPEAKER_23]: You know, and it's annoying to one extent, and it's not...
[SPEAKER_23]: Too bad in another, because, you know, I kind of don't want to be attached to the tournament, because of the tournament being actually too bad, and I'm more attached to what happened otherwise.
[SPEAKER_23]: But, I mean, there was this one incident during freestyle where a team element from upstate New York came in to do the routine, obviously, to DICE.
[SPEAKER_23]: And what happened was, they went up for the first time, and Sammy wasn't ready with the camera.
[SPEAKER_23]: So Sammy says, wait, wait, wait, and tells one of the other staff members to reset the machine while they're at mid-play.
[SPEAKER_23]: Well, not mid-play, but they actually got into about 10 seconds of the routine.
[SPEAKER_23]: So Sammy goes, oh, I didn't know they started already.
[SPEAKER_23]: That would have been fine.
[SPEAKER_23]: Don't worry about it.
[SPEAKER_23]: Just start up again.
[SPEAKER_23]: So they're like, OK, fine.
[SPEAKER_23]: So they start up again.
[SPEAKER_23]: And the problem here was that they forgot Mirror.
[SPEAKER_23]: And we actually ended up forgetting to put Event Mode on.
[SPEAKER_23]: But that wouldn't have mattered if they wouldn't have failed.
[SPEAKER_23]: So what happened was they ended up actually failing
[SPEAKER_23]: Halfway through the song, you know, the fail screen comes up because they forgot to put Mirror on.
Bummer.
[SPEAKER_23]: You know.
[SPEAKER_23]: So then they go ahead and they're like, oh, what the fuck, you know, we had it right the first time, blah blah blah, and then we're like, okay, you know, we'll just go again and we'll figure out something later.
[SPEAKER_23]: So they went again, they finished their routine, you know, and we figured out, you know, I was, right in the beginning, I said they're disqualified.
[SPEAKER_23]: And the reason I said that was because
[SPEAKER_23]: When you do a routine, everything about the routine is routine.
[SPEAKER_23]: When you put options on, when you put your clothes on, when you do the routine, everything is routine.
[SPEAKER_23]: There's no real excuse of not putting an option on.
[SPEAKER_21]: So you're saying the second they turn the machine over to you, it's routine time?
[SPEAKER_23]: Right, exactly.
[SPEAKER_23]: Once you have the option of choosing a song, making your options, blah, blah, blah, blah,
[SPEAKER_23]: It's routine to you, and it's part of the routine that's going to come out on the show to us.
[SPEAKER_21]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_21]: I can see why you're coming from that angle, though, because a lot of what you just talked to us about, about this DDR TV show and stuff, you kind of were talking a little bit about kind of the hype
[SPEAKER_21]: There's also a lot of the problem that people just aren't prepared for freestyle anymore.
[SPEAKER_23]: There's no real big pot for freestyle anymore.
[SPEAKER_23]: You know, everyone wants the expert tech.
[SPEAKER_23]: No one really freestyles.
[SPEAKER_23]: No one really thinks they're good at freestyle.
[SPEAKER_23]: People think they're good at freestyle.
[SPEAKER_23]: They really aren't.
[SPEAKER_23]: You know, it's just like, there's not a lot of people that jump out there, get the job done, you know, and look awesome doing it.
[SPEAKER_23]: At least out here I've seen it.
[SPEAKER_23]: You know, people just, you know, don't put themselves together and make a good routine.
[SPEAKER_23]: To tell you the truth, when I did the Sports World Tournament two years back for Drifting Away, I actually was planning to do insertion for a month.
[SPEAKER_23]: I did this routine for about three, three and a half weeks, putting together every step, every arrow, how to move to a blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_23]: And at the end of it all, about three or four days before the competition, I scrapped the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_23]: I don't even know why, I think I just got sick of it, or whatever, and I ended up doing Drifting Away.
[SPEAKER_23]: The day before, I literally slapped together, won the whole tournament, and that was the story about that.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, you know, the practice of building the other routine, though, probably kind of helped in making the second routine, right?
[SPEAKER_21]: Did you end up taking elements of your insertion routine?
[SPEAKER_23]: Well, I don't know, like,
[SPEAKER_23]: There was more leeway with drifting away.
[SPEAKER_23]: Drifting away is such a trickle, no freeze.
[SPEAKER_23]: It has no arrows for the first half of it.
[SPEAKER_23]: You'll see me get off the pad and do whatever for a while.
[SPEAKER_23]: I had more freedom to do what I wanted with insertion.
[SPEAKER_23]: There was a whole lot of arrows.
[SPEAKER_23]: I just loved the saw insertion, but the problem was there were so many arrows.
[SPEAKER_23]: There was a lot of stuff to work with, and there was a big risk of me failing.
[SPEAKER_23]: I don't like the total big risk of failing, at least back when I was actually competing.
[SPEAKER_23]: Well, no, I might be competing soon because of the tournament last week.
[SPEAKER_23]: What happened was Sketch and Visor had a first place routine, and it was a phenomenal routine.
[SPEAKER_23]: They got inspired through a lot of my stuff, but I kind of got inspired to go ahead and beat their routine with something that I'll come out with later.
[SPEAKER_23]: And I have ideas in my head that are jumping around, and I can't really tell...
[SPEAKER_23]: Not because I don't want to, but because I'm not sure when I'm going to compete.
[SPEAKER_23]: But I want it to be in a place that we're going to tape it and show it online, unlike the dropout freestyle that's still sitting on my side and no one knows what it looks like, not even me.
[SPEAKER_21]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_23]: So that's my plans.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's a lot of video publicity and I guess some freestyle on a personal note.
[SPEAKER_23]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, I know we've been taking up a lot of your time here, but I do have one other question I want to ask you, because it has to do with something that the caller last week had brought up, about hearing something about, and I don't know if you can confirm or deny this, but he had said something about DDR maybe going out on tour with a rap artist.
[SPEAKER_23]: Is this a load of crap, or what is it?
[SPEAKER_23]: Well, actually, before we go to that, I'll tell you one thing that's up on Thursday.
[SPEAKER_23]: Spike TV came up to us and said,
[SPEAKER_23]: said, is it DDR Machine for Rentals?
[SPEAKER_23]: And we're like, well, yeah, because DDR Machine Rentals, that's one of the companies that was obviously Sammy's.
[SPEAKER_21]: Right.
[SPEAKER_23]: And they go, oh, because we have this video game award show that happens in California.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_21]: We talked about this on one of our other shows, the Spike TV's first annual show, yeah.
[SPEAKER_23]: Right, they want the DDR Machine at the after party.
[SPEAKER_20]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, so, but the problem is it's kind of out of the range, and, you know, because obviously that's the west coast, and the east coast, and it's a very long haul for that DVR machine.
[SPEAKER_17]: Right.
[SPEAKER_23]: You know, on Sammy's own, because Sammy only has like a coverage range, and outside the coverage range is a lot of, a lot of, you know, money involved to try to get it out of that.
[SPEAKER_21]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_23]: But on to the rap artists, so basically what happened was, we were in the middle of the tour month, out of a ludicrous and
[SPEAKER_23]: and the film label were there.
[SPEAKER_23]: And someone noticed it, obviously, because it was actually probably on the other side of the screen.
[SPEAKER_23]: Like, ludicrous, it was probably on the other side of the curtain from where we were.
[SPEAKER_23]: And I actually ended up seeing them.
[SPEAKER_23]: But someone, a representative from their production label, came up specifically to me, because it looked like I was doing, and they're like, and they asked me, is this, you know, for rent, or is there even a possibility of taking the machine on tour?
[SPEAKER_23]: and uh... you know, I was like, wow, you know, you want to have this thing on tour?
[SPEAKER_23]: That's pretty cool, you know, you can talk to Sammy.
[SPEAKER_23]: You know, so the person from Ludacris...
[SPEAKER_23]: production label is asking for the DDR Machine to be on tour with them sometime next spring or summer.
[SPEAKER_21]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_21]: Now, what I'd be curious about, though, is it on tour?
[SPEAKER_21]: Because you know how sometimes the big celebrities with their rock and roll lifestyle, or in this case, rap lifestyle, they've got all the stuff that they have in their trailer and stuff.
[SPEAKER_21]: Is this DDR Machine for him to be using in his posse, or is it something he wants to have out there?
[SPEAKER_23]: I have no idea what he wants to do with it.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's just the fact, you know, it's just kind of funny that he wants it, you know.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's the thing that, like, you know,
[SPEAKER_23]: You know, jumped on it, like, I mean, Sammy has that contact information, I don't know what they're doing with that.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, because when I think about famous pairs, I don't really envision Ludacris and DDR, but whatever floats your boat.
[SPEAKER_23]: You know what, you're going to see a lot of stupid stuff soon, I'm going to tell you right now.
[SPEAKER_23]: There's going to be people in the sporting industry playing DDR, I'm positive, it's just going to happen once it gets big.
[SPEAKER_21]: Good, we need more stuff to make fun of here on our little program, so bring on all the silly stuff.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh yeah, there'll be plenty of silly stuff coming, I'm sure of it.
[SPEAKER_23]: But like I said, people will know once the show, if it actually ends up happening, the weekly show, people will know.
[SPEAKER_23]: We'll both be on DVR Freak and be MontyStyle because I obviously am both affiliated with both sites.
[SPEAKER_23]: So you will find out through both of those sites that something will be going down at any point in time, whether it be the 2005 huge tournament or, you know,
[SPEAKER_23]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_21]: Definitely a lot of very interesting stuff it sounds like you've got coming up in the future.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, I'll expect something good is going to happen next year.
[SPEAKER_23]: There's even talk, I don't even know if I want to say this, people are probably going to jump out of their seats.
[SPEAKER_23]: Because of the media that we've received and this call from Konami that we also got, this big uproar that actually happened in only a week or so,
[SPEAKER_23]: We have the possibility of requesting a new arcade mix.
[SPEAKER_20]: I'm jumping out of my seat!
[SPEAKER_23]: You're right.
[SPEAKER_23]: No, we're okay.
[SPEAKER_23]: People are now like, the people are like, now they're like, wait a minute, wait, what did he just say?
[SPEAKER_23]: A new arcade mix?
[SPEAKER_21]: Honestly, here it is, though.
[SPEAKER_23]: You know what, though?
[SPEAKER_23]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm scared of this being wolf.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's not definite, okay?
[SPEAKER_23]: It's not something that's like, wow, okay, we're really doing this.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's a possibility because...
[SPEAKER_23]: America's now finding out about DDR, and it's a real big thing now that at this convention that happened, the public's like, wow, DDR?
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh, wow, this is an amazing game.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh, wow, let's put this thing on TV.
[SPEAKER_23]: We're going to push it, push it, push it.
[SPEAKER_21]: And they're going to be bootleg illegal mixes.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, right?
[SPEAKER_23]: Well, because Konami's going to notice this, obviously, because they called us, they're going to...
[SPEAKER_23]: We hope they're going to help us out and show us, here, look, we got a new arcade mix for you.
[SPEAKER_23]: You know, how does that sound?
[SPEAKER_21]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_21]: Loki is convinced it's not going to happen.
[SPEAKER_23]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_21]: Loki is convinced over here it's not going to happen.
[SPEAKER_23]: Well, you know what?
[SPEAKER_21]: Prove him wrong.
[SPEAKER_23]: Some of us gave up on thinking that another one was going to come out, and some of us were like, I hope there's something else that comes out.
[SPEAKER_23]: And then there's obviously people out there that are still steadfast, and I know Extreme 2 is coming, I know it's coming.
[SPEAKER_23]: So me and Sammy, because of the love of the game, want to push for the new arcade mix to come out, because the USA stuff is kind of like...
[SPEAKER_23]: Sleepy, and PutTogetherBadly, and Spell of Marvelous is with two L's, and things like that.
[SPEAKER_23]: So we want to see a new arcade mix put together, and even if it ends up being a home version like Six Fix was, still something else that's not in the group.
[SPEAKER_23]: Definitely.
[SPEAKER_23]: Here's my advice to you, though.
[SPEAKER_21]: If Konami's going to do it, make sure Hawaii's involved.
[SPEAKER_21]: Hawaii?
[SPEAKER_21]: Konami Hawaii, the folks that did Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh my god, no.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh my god, you've got to be kidding me.
[SPEAKER_21]: You're not a fan of Ultramix 2?
[SPEAKER_23]: Let me tell you right now.
[SPEAKER_23]: When Ultramix 1 came out, I thought it was all Tornamix.
[SPEAKER_23]: I thought Tornamix decided to go ahead and put together a mix from Hawaii and send it out to people.
[SPEAKER_23]: Looking at Ready Steady Go, when the thing speeds up to 280 BPM for absolutely no reason, you have all these songs in here that, you know, Quickening is a six-footer?
[SPEAKER_23]: How do you do that?
[SPEAKER_23]: How do you put Quickening as a six-footer?
[SPEAKER_21]: I'll give you that.
[SPEAKER_23]: You got a good point.
[SPEAKER_23]: How do you do that?
[SPEAKER_23]: So with Ultramix 2 coming out, what's on there?
[SPEAKER_23]: Is Maximizer on there?
[SPEAKER_21]: No, that's on DDR Extreme.
[SPEAKER_21]: So I was going to say, here's the other half of that.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay, now if KOJ does it, then you're going to have Marvelous with two L's, and you're going to have Karaoke Revolution crossovers.
[SPEAKER_21]: So it's kind of like Damned if you do, Damned if you don't.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's just that they need to be aware of what, you know, the people who want the game want.
[SPEAKER_23]: You know, I understand that they're trying to get another group of people, the people who play K-Round, you know, if they do get the long versions like that, or...
[SPEAKER_23]: You know, they're trying to get a different group of people putting U.S.
[SPEAKER_23]: songs in there like Move Your Feet and, you know, Afrika Bambaataa's songs.
[SPEAKER_23]: You know, they're trying to get, you know, the U.S.
[SPEAKER_23]: into their U.S.
[SPEAKER_23]: mixes, but it's not up to that.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's up to, you know, good songs like In the Arcade Extreme and good step charts and things like that that, you know,
[SPEAKER_23]: Push for people to play that are real hardcore players and people that aren't even hardcore players that are even actually into playing.
[SPEAKER_23]: I mean, the regular public doesn't understand that this mix, you know, has faults to it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Right.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's very true.
[SPEAKER_23]: They just play the game, they see arrows, and, you know, obviously once they get into it, they'll realize.
[SPEAKER_23]: But, you know, and that's all they want to really go for.
[SPEAKER_23]: If they actually end up getting the shit together, you know, then this will actually, you know, could be ending up being good.
[SPEAKER_23]: If we have some kind of affiliation with Konami, I mean, if I have an affiliation with Konami at any point in time where I can say what we should put on a mix, I promise you, you will not be disappointed.
[SPEAKER_32]: Very good.
[SPEAKER_23]: I can't see another home version song with some stupid step chart that looks like it's from... Yes, please, no hand plants in DER.
[SPEAKER_21]: Please, no hand plants.
[SPEAKER_23]: Listen, I can go on an entire different show right now with you next week talking about how much I hate In The Groove.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, actually, we're not going to be on next week, but I would love to have... Well, regardless, I could totally go on for hours and hours about how much I hate it, but... I would love to have you back on the show sometime and we can dish on In The Groove.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, man.
[SPEAKER_21]: Because I actually... I was on the East Coast not that long ago and I got to go to In On The Break and I got to check it out.
[SPEAKER_21]: And if I could sum it up in one word, interesting.
[SPEAKER_23]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's good.
[SPEAKER_23]: Um...
[SPEAKER_23]: Interesting is definitely a good word for it.
[SPEAKER_23]: But yeah, to tell you the truth, I know I'm on all these big forums and everything, but if you see me on itgfreak.com, you'll see me flaming everyone.
[SPEAKER_23]: All I do is flame.
[SPEAKER_23]: I actually, I think I just registered just to flame me in the group.
[SPEAKER_21]: See, now you're just adding back into this DDR drama, the drama thing that you were talking about earlier.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, that's all I do, because you know what?
[SPEAKER_23]: They just, they really didn't care.
[SPEAKER_23]: I can almost tell that they didn't care.
[SPEAKER_23]: Or the people out there that they're like, oh, I can make arrows and, you know, put arrows to the song, and no one cares what they look like.
[SPEAKER_23]: You know, it's really frustrating to look at that and have this be put out to...
[SPEAKER_23]: You know, arcades and have people play it, you know, or at least attempt to play it.
[SPEAKER_23]: I mean, when it first came out, it just, it didn't have a lot of, well, it had a lot of, like, wow, another, you know, dancing game, but now no one's playing it anymore over here.
[SPEAKER_21]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, we'll get more of your thoughts on In the Groove a little later.
[SPEAKER_21]: We've taken up, like, over a half hour of your time.
[SPEAKER_21]: Thank you very much for being on the show tonight.
[SPEAKER_21]: Keep in touch with us.
[SPEAKER_21]: Don't forget about us when you're off doing all these projects and stuff.
[SPEAKER_21]: You're welcome back on the show anytime to give us an update on what's going on.
[SPEAKER_21]: and best of luck to you, man.
[SPEAKER_21]: Sounds exciting.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right, baby.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right.
[SPEAKER_21]: Talk to you.
[SPEAKER_21]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_21]: Later.
[SPEAKER_21]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_21]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_21]: Lots of interesting stuff in that interview.
[SPEAKER_21]: Lots and lots of interesting stuff.
[SPEAKER_21]: I didn't realize what the hell they're cooking up over there on the East Coast.
[SPEAKER_21]: Don't we feel out of the loop now over here on the West?
[SPEAKER_21]: That's very interesting.
[SPEAKER_21]: So, Guy, how can we sum up that whole thing for people that joined us halfway through that interview there?
[SPEAKER_21]: Because we've been talking to Frequency for about the past half hour there.
[SPEAKER_21]: DDR going on tour with Ludacris next spring.
[SPEAKER_21]: We don't know to what extent.
[SPEAKER_21]: What did he say?
[SPEAKER_21]: He's talking to Fuse TV about some type of DDR show that right now could, could not be pitched.
[SPEAKER_21]: with a WWE-ish element, or actually that wasn't the analogy.
[SPEAKER_21]: What did he say?
[SPEAKER_21]: The karate show.
[SPEAKER_21]: The ultimate fighting championship.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, the fighting championship.
[SPEAKER_21]: He was saying maybe like a BattleBots type of thing, where it's like a tournament.
[SPEAKER_21]: Very interesting to see what happens with that.
[SPEAKER_21]: Lots of producer contacts apparently at that.
[SPEAKER_21]: DDR could be showing up a lot in the media in the next few months, and it won't be about weight loss.
[SPEAKER_21]: And that's great.
[SPEAKER_21]: And the more exposure that DDR gets in the media...
[SPEAKER_21]: I remember when we used to have new DDR Max came out
[SPEAKER_19]: You know, that show sounds like it needs like wacky, very informative commentators on that.
[SPEAKER_19]: Some people with like radio experience and some DDR experience and just, you know, someone that's been in the community for a while.
[SPEAKER_19]: Hmm, who could that be?
[SPEAKER_21]: Quit trying to whore yourself out to everybody, Loki.
[SPEAKER_20]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, damn, you know what?
[SPEAKER_21]: I need a break.
[SPEAKER_21]: Thanks to Frequency for spending... That was like... Looking at the little timer going on there, that was over 30 minutes of chat.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think a break is a good call.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, Jamie appreciates it too, because she's got a lot of work on her poster done over there, right?
[SPEAKER_14]: My posters are done.
[SPEAKER_21]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_16]: They're done.
[SPEAKER_16]: No, I was listening... No, I know you were.
[SPEAKER_21]: I know you were.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's just...
[SPEAKER_16]: I have this thing at work, but I have to have ten posters done, and I've got five done.
[SPEAKER_21]: No worries.
[SPEAKER_21]: And I need a moment to tally up those cage match votes, since it is.
[SPEAKER_21]: So we're going to tally up the cage match votes, and just take ourselves a nice little break here, because, damn, we need a break after that.
[SPEAKER_21]: So we're going to do a break here of some, um, how about some 2DX songs?
[SPEAKER_21]: I want to do a couple, a couple 2DX songs.
[SPEAKER_21]: We'll start it off with one of my, let's do one we haven't heard in a while here.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm going to do one from 2DX Fifth Style.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm going to do the cube first.
[SPEAKER_21]: and then we'll do Get On Beat.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'll try to get that in there too.
[SPEAKER_21]: And we'll be back in a little bit.
[SPEAKER_21]: We're going to do the FUs of the Week.
[SPEAKER_21]: We're going to let you know who won the cage match and who knows what else when we come back.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, we'll get to Loki as well when we come back.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yeah, I was just playing.
Uh, hey, guys, don't say me.
Don't say my name.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thanks for watching!
Thanks for watching!
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_27]: Hi, this is Mel B of RTF.
[SPEAKER_27]: And for an extra $1.99 a minute, my girlfriend Mel B can join us on all the fun together.
[SPEAKER_27]: But hey, if you're a broke ass like I am, why don't you come to one place that costs absolutely nothing to go to and still the fun is just as great.
[SPEAKER_27]: It's Orange Lounge Radio, Sunday nights.
[SPEAKER_27]: Kick it with me and you just might realize the best things in life are free.
[SPEAKER_21]: We are back here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_21]: We gotta get Mel back on the show at some point.
[SPEAKER_21]: You know, he was gonna be here a couple weeks ago, but something came up.
[SPEAKER_21]: So, we gotta get him back on the show.
[SPEAKER_21]: We need all our favorites back on the show.
[SPEAKER_16]: We'll have our people go get them.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, we'll have our people talk to their people, etc., etc.
[SPEAKER_21]: So, there's some other news going out there in the music and rhythm game world.
[SPEAKER_21]: We've just spent the past half hour edition on DDR, but there are other games going on out there.
[SPEAKER_21]: One thing I wanted to talk about, Taiko Drum Master, actually.
[SPEAKER_21]: We've kind of mentioned this a couple times in the past few weeks.
[SPEAKER_21]: Taiko Drum Master is going to have its release on Tuesday, we're hearing.
[SPEAKER_21]: Angel, you've been kind of reading about this one.
[SPEAKER_21]: Are you planning on picking this game up, or...?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yep, I'm going to try to pick it up.
[SPEAKER_15]: One of the sites I usually frequent to buy games says that the listed price is $69.99, and for PS2, obviously, you guys know that.
[SPEAKER_15]: However, it doesn't state that there's going to be a controller included, like they did with Donkey Konga for the GameCube.
[SPEAKER_21]: For $69.99, there damn well better be.
[SPEAKER_15]: I hope so, yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: There should be one, obviously, so...
[SPEAKER_21]: $49.99 is the most I've ever heard them charging for a video game, and that's for top-shelf games like Grand Theft Auto San Andreas, things like that.
[SPEAKER_16]: Right.
[SPEAKER_16]: Hey, but Rob, you remember how much I played for Samba de Amigo back in the day?
[SPEAKER_16]: Paid $80 for the US controller and, what was the game, $50 for the game?
[SPEAKER_16]: Back in the day.
[SPEAKER_21]: I think the only game I've seen more expensive to import was Parapara back when it was at its height.
[SPEAKER_16]: My DDR2 mix on Dreamcast, when Dan bought it for me, the game was $75, and he spent $80 on my dance pad.
[SPEAKER_16]: Damn!
[SPEAKER_16]: And I sort of acquired somebody else's dance pad.
[SPEAKER_21]: Now, if Namco's smart, they've got one song in Taiko Drum Master, they can be riding the wave of success off of one of their other games right now.
[SPEAKER_21]: Katamari Damacy, the Katamari on the Rocks theme, is in Taiko Drum Master.
[SPEAKER_21]: See, now that little green guy, I bet you anything that little green guy is going to become a little spokesman for Namco.
[SPEAKER_21]: Katamari Damacy is a huge thing.
[SPEAKER_21]: Of course, they've got their staple.
[SPEAKER_21]: The Namco is a pretty good company.
[SPEAKER_21]: They're allowed to have more than one mascot, just like Nintendo's got Mario, and Link, Luigi, and who the hell else?
[SPEAKER_14]: Not Mario, Wario!
[SPEAKER_21]: You finally got a chance to get your own copy of Kanamari Damashii this week, right?
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_21]: So, were you playing it at all, or you said you were watching?
[SPEAKER_16]: I was playing at some.
[SPEAKER_16]: I played, like, at 3 a.m.
[SPEAKER_16]: I was like, okay, these mushrooms are tripping me out.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm going to bed.
[SPEAKER_21]: But it's kind of like, it feels like it's become the internet's latest mail-forward type thing.
[SPEAKER_21]: Where it's like, it's really funny, but you're going to get sick of it in a month.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's like, shut up about that goddamn ball-rolling game already.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_19]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm sorry, but, you know, it is human nature to love smashing things with a ball.
[SPEAKER_19]: Rolling over stuff has been with us ever since the automobile.
[SPEAKER_19]: Since the automobile can smash objects like small squirrels and stuff, it's been our desire to find those small objects to roll over.
[SPEAKER_19]: And the fact that the ball is sticky and holds more objects to make an even larger ball, that's even better.
[SPEAKER_21]: That was beautiful, I think.
[SPEAKER_16]: I like running over buildings, and picking up cows, and the stupid dog that keeps trying to run into you.
[SPEAKER_16]: Okay, I was in this one part where this dog kept trying to butt into me, so I ran over the dog later on, and that was gratifying.
[SPEAKER_21]: Now see, in our chat room, here we go, we have one that says, I'm sick of it already.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's just like Super Monkey Ball, come on!
[SPEAKER_21]: Now see, Super Monkey Ball I never got into.
[SPEAKER_16]: Monkey Ball is cool.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's cute and all, but I never got into it.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's like the Parappa for this generation.
[SPEAKER_16]: Generation, what am I saying?
[SPEAKER_16]: This year, you know?
[SPEAKER_16]: Because you know how Parappa hit and then kind of blew over?
[SPEAKER_16]: We're going to have like, you know, Katamari Damacy 2 is coming out, and then there's going to be like, I think a theme.
[SPEAKER_16]: There should be like, like Katamari Party.
[SPEAKER_16]: Mario Party, just with the little prince.
[SPEAKER_15]: I was going to say that the game's got its little cult following now, so it's kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_15]: I was going to mention that VGCats jumped on it as soon as the game got released.
[SPEAKER_15]: For those of you that don't know what VGCats is... It took them quite a while, actually, to get on it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, but... Anyway, I was going to say VGCats is an online comic for video games and stuff.
[SPEAKER_15]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_21]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, okay, let's get back on topic to talking about rhythm and music games here.
[SPEAKER_21]: Loki had some things he wanted to talk about with you guys, some news that's going on.
[SPEAKER_21]: Now you, I guess there's some remix contests going on that just finished up.
[SPEAKER_21]: What happened with remixing?
[SPEAKER_19]: Both DDR, it's like DDR Remix, which is just DDR Maniacs' contest, which didn't have quite a turnout as, but my sales, Remix Contest 1.5 or whatever that was.
[SPEAKER_19]: But anyways, there's some pretty cool stuff that came out of those.
[SPEAKER_19]: First I'll talk about the DDR Maniacs 1, the Remix competition, because it's actually not done.
[SPEAKER_19]: They're in voting right now, but they have the...
[SPEAKER_19]: The songs that were out there, so I'm going to play a few of these here.
[SPEAKER_19]: Actually, let me adjust my volume here.
[SPEAKER_19]: There was actually only four people that entered this, which is kind of a little sad.
[SPEAKER_19]: A little sad.
[SPEAKER_19]: There was two by, you know, you might recognize DJ Potato.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm trying to find these here.
[SPEAKER_19]: What do I have?
[SPEAKER_19]: Um...
[SPEAKER_21]: DJ Potato
[SPEAKER_19]: There was only five entries.
[SPEAKER_19]: Two of them were his.
[SPEAKER_19]: They were actually... And I can play them for you guys.
[SPEAKER_19]: It was actually some work that he did, sort of, kind of, with the Bomani Rock album, but not... It's just a piano and saxophone sort of remixes of... What the hell?
[SPEAKER_19]: What the hell was that?
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, give us a little clip of one of these songs here.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay, well, let's see here.
[SPEAKER_19]: Um...
[SPEAKER_19]: We'll start off with... Let's see, these are old.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay, we're going to start off with... They had one of Kind Lady.
[SPEAKER_19]: He actually did a few of these.
[SPEAKER_19]: He has, like, D2R 1998.
[SPEAKER_19]: Kind Lady, there was another one, too.
[SPEAKER_19]: I can't remember what it was offhand, but... Anyways.
[SPEAKER_19]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay, this one...
[SPEAKER_19]: Right here is going to be DJ Potato Piano Concentrato Shut up!
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't need your fancy English-English talk, okay?
[SPEAKER_16]: It's Italian!
[SPEAKER_19]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_19]: European.
[SPEAKER_19]: We do not formally recognize European nations, okay?
[SPEAKER_19]: I just want you to know that.
[SPEAKER_19]: They do not exist to me.
[SPEAKER_13]: and your psychotic little universe.
Anyways.
Keep in mind, I played saxophone for like 12 years.
You're listening to KOLR Smooth Jazz.
[SPEAKER_19]: So that was that.
[SPEAKER_19]: Anyways, that was one of the songs that was in there.
[SPEAKER_19]: There were some other remixes, but not a lot.
[SPEAKER_19]: However, the Bomani Style remix competition was a little different.
[SPEAKER_19]: There was quite a bit there.
[SPEAKER_19]: I saved some of these really kick-ass ones on here because there were a few that were like, and even the judges said, what the hell is this?
[SPEAKER_19]: But, you know, there's always going to be something like that.
[SPEAKER_19]: So, some of the ones I'd like to point out, which were pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_19]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_19]: Some of them you've heard before on this show.
[SPEAKER_19]: Klunk Klunk 2004.
[SPEAKER_19]: Now, that was DM Ashura.
[SPEAKER_19]: And that was pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, anyways, that one.
[SPEAKER_19]: And then...
[SPEAKER_19]: We've got my personal favorite, Dazed and Destroyed.
[SPEAKER_19]: I loved this one before when it was only a clip of the song, but that's the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_19]: The second half is kind of, eh, it's okay, but I mean, it's pretty well done for, um, it's a remix of Hysteria, so, pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_20]: It's a really cool song, trust me with that.
[SPEAKER_22]: And he's making bitter beer face.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's different.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's different, and it's well-produced.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well-produced maybe, but of course they can speak to each other.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_19]: BUDDY BUDDY BUDDY BUDDY BUDDY BUDDY BUDDY
[SPEAKER_20]: I'm trying to think of some really cool ones that are out there.
[SPEAKER_20]: They sort of had an R&B version of Rainbow Flyer.
[SPEAKER_20]: Rainbow Flyer, the polychromatic algorithmic... Let's see here, we've also got... But the winner, the winner of it all was Saxon Pike with V1.
[SPEAKER_20]: No, wait, wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_21]: Correct me if I'm wrong, but isn't this the same contest you were complaining about because they wouldn't allow fusion mixes and what won the damn contest?
[SPEAKER_19]: Now, this was a little different now.
[SPEAKER_19]: They didn't want people just using acid to throw two songs on top of each other.
[SPEAKER_19]: However, there were some songs in there that were two songs thrown on top of each other.
[SPEAKER_19]: How that got in is beyond me, because I specifically remembered in the rules that that's why I didn't enter.
[SPEAKER_19]: But whatever.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_19]: The contest is over.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's a little late.
[SPEAKER_19]: But anyway, so yeah, that was that.
[SPEAKER_19]: You can find all these songs online.
[SPEAKER_19]: Under the music production forum on MyStyle, there's a whole list of songs you can listen to, good and bad, and they're all on there, pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_19]: One of the other songs that came out this week also was a remix of Vanity Angel by DM Asura, because he can do no wrong, it seems like, with these.
[SPEAKER_19]: So anyways, I thought I'd play a little bit of that, because that's pretty sweet also.
[SPEAKER_20]: But, yeah, it's just, you know, cool, like, long, trance, universal, and trance songs, so.
[SPEAKER_19]: But anyways, that was out.
[SPEAKER_19]: You can also find that in the Music Production Forum.
[SPEAKER_21]: Or you could listen to Monday Nights, Diversion, the Orange Sons Radio Remix Show, because we'll definitely be adding some of these songs into our rotation there on Monday nights from 7 o'clock to 9 o'clock Pacific Standard Time.
[SPEAKER_19]: Now, and the other thing I wanted to mention, and we mentioned this way back in the show a while ago, about, what was it, it was DJ Potato's Bomani Rock album that was going to be coming out.
[SPEAKER_19]: I have a few full tracks, actually, from that.
[SPEAKER_19]: So, there's a few I'd like to just preview real quick, and we'll also be throwing those in to rotation as well.
[SPEAKER_19]: Max 300.
[SPEAKER_22]: All right, all right, all right.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's well done, don't get me wrong, but no more Macs.
[SPEAKER_22]: I mean it.
[SPEAKER_22]: No more.
[SPEAKER_14]: Samsung keeps breeding.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's worse than Tribbles.
[SPEAKER_19]: This one's the one I like, Peer Drain.
[SPEAKER_19]: I can't go on.
[SPEAKER_19]: This one is a little harder to find.
[SPEAKER_19]: I believe this was in the 2DX forum.
[SPEAKER_19]: There's like a sample thing from the Bomani Rock album.
[SPEAKER_19]: You can find that also on Bomani Style.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's pretty much all that's like music news.
[SPEAKER_19]: Now, there's a little other thing I read because we're talking about, you know, new arcade mixes and the Step Mania machine and in the groove and all that kind of stuff that kind of coincides with this.
[SPEAKER_19]: Now, for those who...
[SPEAKER_19]: Frequent the DDRUK.com site, you'll know that they created a Setmania machine called DDX, or Dance Dance X, or whatever it is.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's basically a Setmania arcade game that they skinned.
[SPEAKER_19]: It looks really nice, and it was being played in a Namco, I think it was like a Namco cyberstation somewhere in England.
[SPEAKER_19]: And anyways...
[SPEAKER_19]: That's getting pulled out of there.
[SPEAKER_19]: Not because of licensing issues and stuff, but it fell the same fate that the Golf Land Machine was.
[SPEAKER_19]: And that is, it's not being fixed by them, and it's just falling apart and damaged.
[SPEAKER_19]: Everyone out there know that problems with little kids trashing shit, it's worldwide.
[SPEAKER_19]: There are bad parents everywhere.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, and you told me that it happened during break.
[SPEAKER_21]: I was hoping it was going to be a legal issues story so we could have a little fun with that, but you're just saying some fucking punks ruined the machine.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_19]: That is it.
[SPEAKER_19]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_21]: How boring!
[SPEAKER_21]: I wanted somebody to get sued.
[SPEAKER_21]: That would have been exciting.
[SPEAKER_21]: So no plans to bring it back?
[SPEAKER_21]: They're just going to let it rot?
[SPEAKER_19]: Maybe we will get a lawsuit story out of this after all.
[SPEAKER_19]: Hooray!
[SPEAKER_19]: Anyways, the other thing I wanted to talk about was there was a bootleg that came out a few weeks ago, Dance Dance King.
[SPEAKER_19]: It looked like a really crappy bootleg machine from China that featured gold colored pads and stuff and had, what else?
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, and it's basically a second mix consumer style machine that was running from a PlayStation machine.
[SPEAKER_19]: Literally, a PS1 was inside this cabinet.
[SPEAKER_19]: And that was quite interesting.
[SPEAKER_19]: I happened to contact these people.
[SPEAKER_19]: They want to... Now, it wasn't their idea, they say, to bring this bootleg over here, but the guy wants to make a legitimate mix.
[SPEAKER_19]: That was kind of interesting, I thought.
[SPEAKER_28]: Good luck!
[SPEAKER_19]: So yeah, that's all the miscellaneous Bomani stuff that's been going on this week.
[SPEAKER_19]: Next week, I have no idea what's going to be going on because I'm going to be playing Grand Theft Auto San Andreas.
[SPEAKER_19]: So unless there's Bomani in San Andreas, I have no idea what's going on.
[SPEAKER_21]: Fair enough, because we're not having a show next Sunday, remember, it's Halloween, and we're giving all the people a night off so you can go trick-or-treating.
[SPEAKER_21]: We will have a marathon of old Orange Lounge Radio episodes, though, a very scary Orange Lounge Radio marathon for you guys next Sunday.
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't know how long that's going to run.
[SPEAKER_21]: Stay tuned to the website for details and when your shows will air.
[SPEAKER_19]: You know, Nelly almost got me to buy Karaoke Revolution 2.
[SPEAKER_19]: Then my wits came about me, I said, fuck no!
[SPEAKER_19]: I am not buying that game.
[SPEAKER_17]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_21]: Actually, I want to ask you about this.
[SPEAKER_21]: Rai Chan sent me a private message.
[SPEAKER_21]: She linked me to this thread over on Freak that's showing this.
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't know if you've seen this, but it is a Stepmania computer put inside an 80s era ghetto blaster.
[SPEAKER_21]: And they've got the Stepmania logo painted over the speakers.
[SPEAKER_21]: And this is actually a computer.
[SPEAKER_21]: It looks like a boombox in the front, but look at the side.
[SPEAKER_21]: Look at that.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's a little computer.
[SPEAKER_21]: You see this, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_21]: Look at that.
[SPEAKER_16]: Old school.
[SPEAKER_16]: That makes me think of the Nintendo computer.
[SPEAKER_16]: You remember when they were building a Nintendo out of laptop parts?
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm sorry, building a computer out of a Nintendo shell and laptop parts.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, it's the nice case mod.
[SPEAKER_19]: I thought about doing one like that, but putting it in a Dreamcast.
[SPEAKER_16]: I still want one built out of a toolkit, a toolbox.
[SPEAKER_18]: Is that kind of thing hard to do, Loki?
[SPEAKER_18]: Now, when it comes to technical stuff, I don't know shit.
[SPEAKER_21]: I know how to put a radio station on the internet, but that's about it.
[SPEAKER_21]: So, Loki, tell me about, is this hard to do?
[SPEAKER_19]: Not if you have a Dremel tool.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's pretty much, even since that boombox was so big, that they probably wouldn't even need to get a micro ITX board.
[SPEAKER_19]: The micro ITX ones that they have now are really small.
[SPEAKER_19]: I think the specifications for that are 15, I think it's 17 centimeters by 17 centimeters.
[SPEAKER_19]: And looking at that, it looks like that is a micro ITX board in there.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, so it's a micro-ITX board, looks like a hard drive, power supply and everything.
[SPEAKER_19]: It looks like they had a P4 version that was in there.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't really know if that's the thing.
[SPEAKER_19]: They might have just added a fan to that just so it's cooled off a little bit more.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's hard to tell by the picture.
[SPEAKER_19]: It looks like it could be a regular-sized motherboard, but I'm thinking it's probably a micro-ITX.
[SPEAKER_21]: I like how they have the hard drive on top.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's very interesting.
[SPEAKER_21]: The hard drive's like separate from everything else.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't know if that's just the way they open it up or what.
[SPEAKER_21]: But look at this.
[SPEAKER_21]: It says it also includes a sound-sensitive blue LED rod that kind of goes with the beat.
[SPEAKER_21]: But those little things go a long way in ghetto fabulousness, don't they?
[SPEAKER_21]: Don't you think?
[SPEAKER_21]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_19]: I still wanted to do...
[SPEAKER_19]: I wanted to make like a mini portable console system for like, you know, Stepmania emulation games and just like a, not really, like almost like a laptop but not, I don't know, I'm never going to do that though because I start too many projects.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, well we're going to go to a break.
[SPEAKER_21]: When we come back from this break, we've got to do the FUs of the week, don't you know?
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, but shouldn't I announce the winner of the Orange Lounge Radio Cage Match before we get to that?
[SPEAKER_21]: Because that was about an hour ago that we had the Cage Match.
[SPEAKER_21]: Tonight's winner of the Orange Lounge Radio Cage Match is Ian Van Dahl with Reason.
[SPEAKER_21]: So there you have it.
[SPEAKER_21]: Just because Loki picks a funny one doesn't mean he wins it.
[SPEAKER_21]: So, too bad!
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm glad.
[SPEAKER_21]: I haven't won that in at least a while.
[SPEAKER_21]: So, at least a month.
[SPEAKER_21]: I know that much.
[SPEAKER_21]: So, cool.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, you'll be hearing that one again next week along with two other lovely new songs.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, no, not next week.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, yeah, by default it's going to win for two weeks now.
[SPEAKER_21]: So, we'll be back in two weeks to try and dethrone Ian Vandal.
[SPEAKER_21]: Ryu, I'm white, forgive me, we'll be back
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: Please subscribe to my channel!
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_28]: Hi-ho, Kermit the Frog here, informing you that today's broadcast of Orange Lounge Radio is brought to you by the letter V, the letter A, and the number 59.
[SPEAKER_10]: Can you tell me how to get, how to get to Sesame Street?
[SPEAKER_21]: We are back here on Orange Lounge Radio, and believe it or not, we're coming into the home stretch of the show.
[SPEAKER_21]: But no show would be complete...
[SPEAKER_21]: Without a little bit of angst.
[SPEAKER_21]: And that means it's time for the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_21]: Jamie, why do we have to do these FUs of the week every single week?
[SPEAKER_16]: Because we're full of angst.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, this is bad.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here is justice.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here is punishment.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here is... This is fucked up!
[SPEAKER_16]: First thing I do goes to my laundry...
[SPEAKER_16]: for not being dry yet, it's still damp.
[SPEAKER_16]: Another FU goes toward being exhausted, drained, worn out, you name it.
[SPEAKER_16]: FU to stress, big FU to stress.
[SPEAKER_16]: FU to people in minivans who drive 30 in a 50 mile an hour zone.
[SPEAKER_16]: and Distance, Time, Money.
[SPEAKER_16]: I don't really have anything specific.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, then we'll move on to Loki.
[SPEAKER_19]: First off, you know, it's like every week, you know, fuck you the drivers, because
[SPEAKER_19]: God, they're so awful and wholesome.
[SPEAKER_19]: I just don't know what it is.
[SPEAKER_19]: They just don't pay attention to any of the stop signs, lights, road signs, nothing.
[SPEAKER_19]: They're just stupid.
[SPEAKER_19]: So, fuck you, Zeb.
[SPEAKER_19]: Fuck you to my car, because the engine light came on the other day, and I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, actually, I do know why, because it was out of coolant, but I fixed that, and I hope it doesn't break down, because, you know, I need good karma around my car.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't want to have to, like...
[SPEAKER_19]: Have it great.
[SPEAKER_19]: That would suck.
[SPEAKER_19]: Then on more personal notes, and I apologize to any people that are listening from my work, because I think there might be one or two.
[SPEAKER_19]: Maybe one.
[SPEAKER_19]: Anyways, fuck you to BPD for firing Nelly from the mailroom.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's really funny because I do know the reasons behind it, and it was really stupid why they did it.
[SPEAKER_19]: There's a lot of people there that have done a lot worse
[SPEAKER_19]: and are still there, and it's just retarded, so, but whatever, she's probably going to end up getting something better in the long run, so that's cool, but there's just a lot of people I have lost respect for from that, and that sucks.
[SPEAKER_19]: Then finally, just, I'm sorry, fuck you to the rain, because it's wet outside and I can't work on my cabinet, not that I would work on my cabinet anyways if it wasn't raining.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm just tired, that's it.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, I'm going back to my old FU song, because the new one, William Hung, just wasn't working out, so I'm going back to my old song.
[SPEAKER_21]: Weren't we just talking about how we didn't really care for this song, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_21]: And yet...
[SPEAKER_14]: Why don't you pick another one?
[SPEAKER_21]: Nah, I'm feeling uncreative tonight.
[SPEAKER_21]: Because I just like the fact that it goes, all things keep getting better.
[SPEAKER_21]: And, you know, it's the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't wanna.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, maybe later.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm never that angsty though, and honestly, to be honest, this week is much different.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm just, I'm going to say F you to the fact that I've been really insanely busy this week, and I haven't had time to do all the things that I want to do, and F you to the fact that I haven't been able to hang out with certain people as much as I would like to be able to.
[SPEAKER_21]: Just because of the fact that, you know, they're working, and I'm working, and I got the radio stuff, etc., etc., so...
[SPEAKER_21]: That kind of sucks.
[SPEAKER_21]: There needs to be more hours in the day.
[SPEAKER_21]: And then people shouldn't have to work as much and then keep the same salary.
[SPEAKER_21]: I realize I'm living in La La Land, but I really don't have anything realistic this week.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's actually been a pretty decent week.
[SPEAKER_21]: Just really busy.
[SPEAKER_21]: Except F you to the people that went and saw The Grudge at 9.30 on Friday night in Roseville because you all were too damn loud.
[SPEAKER_21]: And F you to that guy I had to yell at in the middle of the movie.
[SPEAKER_21]: Although that did make me feel really good.
[SPEAKER_21]: I mean, just getting the applause like that when I told that guy to shut the hell up felt really, really good.
[SPEAKER_21]: There's just not a lot of rushes like that you get in the world, so.
[SPEAKER_21]: Just, you know, F you to that movie as well for making people scream and stuff.
[SPEAKER_21]: People were too damn loud with that movie and it was giving me a headache.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, F you to the fact, I know why, F you to the fact that the projectionist or something, the film was damaged or the projection was going on because for 20 goddamn minutes the movie was bouncing up and down like it was shaking.
[SPEAKER_21]: Like imagine if you were trying to watch something on a projection screen and it was shaking like an earthquake.
[SPEAKER_21]: I swear to God it was giving me a headache after like one minute of having to watch it like that.
[SPEAKER_21]: And we go and complain, Loki actually went in and complained and what did they tell you?
[SPEAKER_20]: Uh, yeah, it's only going to do that for 20 minutes.
[SPEAKER_20]: We got the defective reel from the studio, but hey, we're getting a new one to replace it soon.
[SPEAKER_20]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_22]: Uh-uh.
[SPEAKER_21]: No.
[SPEAKER_21]: Fuck you and your fucking bitch-ass whore cunt for fucking making me pay $9.25 plus a $1.25 Fandango fee because I don't like fucking lines at your movie theater.
[SPEAKER_21]: Fuck you for making me pay that.
[SPEAKER_21]: I want a perfect goddamn theater experience.
[SPEAKER_14]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_14]: You should have asked for the manager.
[SPEAKER_21]: I know.
[SPEAKER_21]: I should write a letter and complain.
[SPEAKER_16]: Do it.
[SPEAKER_21]: I just might.
[SPEAKER_16]: You should ask for the manager's boss then.
[SPEAKER_21]: Who knew?
[SPEAKER_21]: I had this rage pent up in me and I forgot all about it.
[SPEAKER_21]: I pushed it to the back of my mind and you people brought it out of me.
[SPEAKER_16]: Rage!
[SPEAKER_16]: I got a free ticket for complaining about them turning on the lights at the end of the credits for Matrix.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'll write a nasty letter.
[SPEAKER_21]: Because you know what?
[SPEAKER_21]: I think I had one other bad experience at theater and I can't remember what it was.
[SPEAKER_21]: But I bet if I went through the FU archives of the show I could find it.
[SPEAKER_16]: Mention the three magic words.
[SPEAKER_16]: Better business bureau.
[SPEAKER_21]: I mentioned these magic words.
[SPEAKER_21]: Fuck you, whore, for making me pay so much money for going to see a subpar production.
[SPEAKER_21]: I want everything in pristine condition.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's highway robbery.
[SPEAKER_21]: No wonder people pirate your goddamn movies.
[SPEAKER_19]: Here's my thing, okay?
[SPEAKER_19]: It was playing on like six to eight screens in there.
[SPEAKER_19]: Take out the bad film, play it less.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh my God, five screens.
[SPEAKER_19]: How will we survive?
[SPEAKER_19]: I mean, seriously, just play it less.
[SPEAKER_19]: Play another...
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm sure more people want to see a shark's tail, so go ahead and play that instead.
[SPEAKER_19]: I mean, they could have easily taken this out of rotation, but instead they're like, ah, fuck it, no one's going to care.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right.
[SPEAKER_21]: Let's move on and go to the other angsty folks in our studio right now.
[SPEAKER_21]: We'll start it off with DDR Angel.
[SPEAKER_15]: I actually have to burp right now.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: Um, just, FU to just being tired today, I don't even know what's up, everybody seems tired today.
[SPEAKER_15]: Um, I don't know, just, there's no reason for it, I shouldn't be tired, but I am.
[SPEAKER_15]: FU to that.
[SPEAKER_15]: Um, again, FU to the flaky instructor that I've got, because that sucks, but, whatever, he's still deciding to hold class every once in a while, maybe he'll get over it and realize, oh wait, uh, I have a job to do.
[SPEAKER_15]: Um, that's about it, I'm like, not 80, what the hell.
[SPEAKER_21]: You're not really ever that angsty, Angel.
[SPEAKER_21]: I've only seen you angsty here one time.
[SPEAKER_21]: And it took an act of God to make you angsty.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_21]: Bradley, Arcadian42, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_29]: Of course, fuck you to, uh, Folsom PD, and... Surprise!
[SPEAKER_29]: Yes, uh, Fakira, and all that, and all, fuck you to me for getting myself into that, and that situation, and all the decisions, and delays, and everything that caused it, and, yeah, so forth.
[SPEAKER_29]: Uh, what else, uh, fuck you to having to make up all that time, but at least my work is nice and will let me make up time.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let me in, let me in
[SPEAKER_29]: Fuck you to the honey-backed ribs or whatever the new thing at Applebee's for sucking.
[SPEAKER_28]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_29]: No, honey.
[SPEAKER_29]: It's like honey... honey barbecue ribs.
[SPEAKER_29]: Oh, it's actually a rib thing, but it sucked.
[SPEAKER_29]: Riblets are good, but it's like a new rib thing, but it sucked.
[SPEAKER_29]: It was like, bleh.
[SPEAKER_29]: Yeah, but at least it was free, because it was the free lunch day at work.
[SPEAKER_29]: So at least I didn't have to pay that money for it.
[SPEAKER_29]: And, uh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_29]: Actually, just ROD for the DVD, but...
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, let's move on to the chatroom FUs, of which I haven't gotten very many tonight, surprisingly enough, so if they don't get in in the next 30 seconds or so, they're probably not getting read, but that's alright, we have a few.
[SPEAKER_21]: Raichan says, F you to friends borrowing things and not returning them.
[SPEAKER_21]: F you to people that drive in the fast lane and are going 15 miles an hour under the speed limit.
[SPEAKER_21]: F you to loners.
[SPEAKER_21]: F you to people that continue to try to use you for all your worth and can't take a hint when I say no.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, and F you to taking a frisbee to the lip.
[SPEAKER_21]: Ow, ow.
[SPEAKER_19]: What, Loki?
[SPEAKER_19]: Said you're not a dog, you can't catch it with your mouth.
[SPEAKER_21]: Something tells me she wasn't trying to do that.
[SPEAKER_21]: You know what, though?
[SPEAKER_21]: You know what's a lot safer?
[SPEAKER_21]: What were those things?
[SPEAKER_21]: They're like frisbees, but they go further.
[SPEAKER_21]: Robies?
[SPEAKER_21]: What were those things called?
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, it's like throwing a giant saw blade at your head.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's the best thing ever.
[SPEAKER_16]: No, the Nerf ones, the plastic ones.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, the Nerf ones are the best ones because it just feels like you're throwing a fish at you or something like that.
[SPEAKER_19]: But yeah, the Robies are fucking dangerous because they go faster and they're more streamlined.
[SPEAKER_19]: Seriously, it's like a saw blade getting thrown at you.
[SPEAKER_19]: But they're awesome, you can throw them in the car.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_21]: Didn't they have aerobies that were shaped in, like, strange shapes, too?
[SPEAKER_21]: Like, diamonds and stuff?
[SPEAKER_21]: Right, right.
[SPEAKER_21]: DarkTetsuya says, F you to my cold, and F you to my computer.
[SPEAKER_21]: I only heard half of tonight's show.
[SPEAKER_21]: Unacceptable!
[SPEAKER_21]: Fired!
[SPEAKER_21]: No, that's fine, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_21]: He does good news for the website, so...
[SPEAKER_21]: Jazz says, F you to the fact that the projection people didn't turn off the lights for like 15 minutes into the movie and the fact that the grudge was more funny than scary and the rest of my audience agreed.
[SPEAKER_21]: I thought the grudge was scary.
[SPEAKER_21]: I thought the grudge was really scary.
[SPEAKER_21]: But that's it.
[SPEAKER_21]: He reminded me of the other thing.
[SPEAKER_21]: When I went and saw, I think it was, I want to say it was Kill Bill 2 over there, they didn't turn off the goddamn lights.
[SPEAKER_16]: That's what it was.
[SPEAKER_16]: It was Kill Bill 2.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, when I went and saw Kill Bill 2, they didn't turn off the goddamn lights for like 15 minutes.
[SPEAKER_21]: And you would think such a little thing would not be so annoying, but it was really, really annoying.
[SPEAKER_21]: Thank you, Jazz, for reigniting that angst within me.
[SPEAKER_21]: Lastly, Poto says, F you to writing a paper on two hours of sleep.
[SPEAKER_21]: Aww.
[SPEAKER_21]: I remember being such a procrastinator like that.
[SPEAKER_21]: Still am.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm doing my paper during my lunch break tomorrow, and it's due tomorrow night.
[SPEAKER_21]: Amen to that.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm not going to class tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, wait.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm not going to class ever.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_21]: I guess what we should do, let's open up the Skype line, because for God's sake, we haven't had it open the whole show except for that long chat we had with Frequency.
[SPEAKER_21]: Basically, Frequency took all your Skype time tonight, ladies and gentlemen.
[SPEAKER_21]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_21]: We'll open it up a little bit for the folks to talk to us on Skype.
[SPEAKER_21]: So Skype's open.
[SPEAKER_21]: If you want more information on Skype, head on over to www.orangeloungeradio.com and click on Interact With Us.
[SPEAKER_21]: We definitely would like your feedback to anything we've talked about during tonight's show, including lots of stuff that we had talked to Frequency about earlier, as well as, you know, other news, the Bomani Remix Contest, and machines breaking down, and kids in arcades, and projectionists that don't know how to tromp the goddamn light when the movie starts.
[SPEAKER_21]: Anyway, sorry.
[SPEAKER_21]: Getting a little bit off tangent there.
[SPEAKER_21]: Also, we will accept your Ask Orange Lounge questions over private message and chat if you guys have anything you want to ask us.
[SPEAKER_21]: We only have a couple minutes left, so we're not going to make it an official segment, but if you have some questions you'd like us to address, go ahead and send those in.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'd also like to add that everything Sam Raimi touches turns to gold.
[SPEAKER_16]: And his car ends up in all of his movies.
[SPEAKER_19]: Damn it, I didn't look for it in the garage, but I don't know if that really counts because he just produced the movie.
[SPEAKER_16]: His car might be in there.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm being told right now in our chat room that right now our very show is being played inside a truck stop.
[SPEAKER_07]: Awesome!
[SPEAKER_21]: So we'd like to give a big yee-haw to all our trucking buddies down there.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm totally kidding.
[SPEAKER_21]: Please don't beat me up.
[SPEAKER_21]: No, but I guess we have somebody listening on a network over at the truck stop right now.
[SPEAKER_21]: I think that's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_14]: I want a good truck stop.
[SPEAKER_14]: They have good food.
[SPEAKER_14]: I want hashbrown.
[SPEAKER_14]: They have good food over at the truck stop.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh my god, let's go get food.
[SPEAKER_19]: I want riblets.
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't think they have riblets.
[SPEAKER_21]: But I need to be watching my weight because I have a performance to do on Saturday.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, come on.
[SPEAKER_16]: Eat healthy food.
[SPEAKER_16]: Get some spinach with it.
[SPEAKER_21]: I've got to work early tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_21]: If I didn't have to work early tomorrow, I would totally do it.
[SPEAKER_16]: I have to work at 6.30.
[SPEAKER_21]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_21]: Anyway, we're supposed to watch the language because we're being broadcast at the truck stop right now.
[SPEAKER_21]: So, you know.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, I'll keep the mic away from Loki, if that's the case.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, I didn't even check the Skype thing to see if anybody called.
[SPEAKER_21]: Nope, still wide open there.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, I guess nobody wants to call us tonight, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's fine, we'll just talk to ourselves, we'll amuse ourselves here, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_21]: Any big Halloween plans for you, Loki?
[SPEAKER_19]: Just having a get-together over here.
[SPEAKER_19]: We're going to watch Shaun of the Dead because I got my lovely promo copy of that.
[SPEAKER_19]: And that's going to rock.
[SPEAKER_19]: Shaun of the Dead.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm going to try.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm going to try because the people are going to have alcohol.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm going to try to slip in one of my bad movies in there, but I don't think they're going to go for it.
[SPEAKER_19]: No one wants to watch my bad movies, and that makes me sad.
[SPEAKER_19]: I spend good money on those, and goddammit, if, you know, no one wants to watch, uh, what is it, uh, Blood Sisters of Lesbian Sin, you know, who will?
[SPEAKER_16]: I'll watch it.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'll watch it.
[SPEAKER_21]: Come on, make a plan for it.
[SPEAKER_16]: Just to see what the hell it is.
[SPEAKER_21]: I have a question.
[SPEAKER_21]: How many people are coming to this get-together?
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_21]: Where are they all going to fit?
[SPEAKER_20]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_19]: Sit on the floor, goddammit, because I'm taking... Language!
[SPEAKER_21]: Gosh darn it!
[SPEAKER_21]: Much better, much better.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right.
[SPEAKER_21]: Bradley, you have any exciting Halloween plans?
[SPEAKER_21]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_29]: Sit on my ass at home.
[SPEAKER_29]: Do nothing.
[SPEAKER_21]: Sounds like a plan of me.
[SPEAKER_21]: You know what I'm doing.
[SPEAKER_20]: I want to see the Arizuka kids.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's a fabulous idea.
[SPEAKER_21]: Let's take out the Arizuka.
[SPEAKER_19]: We can put candy in it and it launches the candy.
[SPEAKER_16]: I've got like three days of Halloween because we're doing the big thing at work.
[SPEAKER_16]: I have my cat girl costume.
[SPEAKER_16]: And then I'm having Rocky on Saturday.
[SPEAKER_16]: And probably Sunday I'm just going to sit around and watch Interview with a Vampire on Laserdisc.
[SPEAKER_21]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_21]: Also, what else I wanted to say?
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, remember the follow-up from last week?
[SPEAKER_21]: Remember we were talking about, in case you guys weren't listening last week, but we were talking about how we were going to do DDR on the big screen at some point.
[SPEAKER_21]: We were going to take that same movie screen and possibly have a Bomani night in the movie theater and possibly do a live taping of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_21]: Outlook is very good on that.
[SPEAKER_21]: We're hoping to get some help from other friends of ours within the Bomani community to kind of make that a success.
[SPEAKER_21]: But just like the
[SPEAKER_21]: TV show thing that had come up earlier.
[SPEAKER_21]: We're having a hard time figuring out exactly what we're going to do besides a live episode of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_21]: But we want there to be more to it.
[SPEAKER_21]: What?
[SPEAKER_19]: I said let's set a virgin on fire.
[SPEAKER_16]: Get set a virgin's pants on fire.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh boy.
[SPEAKER_21]: Let's set the ferret on fire.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's what we need to do.
[SPEAKER_14]: My baby's.
[SPEAKER_21]: Where's my baby?
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_21]: He's funny enough.
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't even know where the ferrets are.
[SPEAKER_21]: Do you want to see my baby?
[SPEAKER_21]: No, I don't want to see your baby.
[SPEAKER_21]: You have to get out and get it.
[SPEAKER_20]: No, don't do it.
[SPEAKER_19]: Don't be your slave.
[SPEAKER_29]: Don't be your slave.
[SPEAKER_21]: Let my people go.
[SPEAKER_19]: You've got to play Katamari Damacy on the big screen.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay, that's one suggestion that's come up, is that Katamari Damacy gets played on the big screen.
[SPEAKER_16]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_21]: Somehow, we'll have to have some kind of little contest.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, they have two-player mode.
[SPEAKER_21]: We can have a Katamari Damacy tournament or something.
[SPEAKER_16]: You can play as the cousins.
[SPEAKER_21]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm liking this so far.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm liking it.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, we're going to take a real quick break.
[SPEAKER_21]: We're going to do a one song break, then we're going to come back and wrap up the show.
[SPEAKER_21]: What song should we do here in this break?
[SPEAKER_21]: Let's do... Well, we did pop in, we didn't do a guitar freak song.
[SPEAKER_21]: What?
[SPEAKER_21]: Language!
[SPEAKER_19]: So, golly gee willikers, it would not, you know, upload to the, to the, um, server, and, um, so yeah, I couldn't make it available for people to download, that made me sad.
[SPEAKER_19]: Um, and you said it sucks, okay, that's what I want to say.
[SPEAKER_19]: But anyways, this is, um, Paranoia Revolution, um,
[SPEAKER_19]: be sure you put in the one that's just Revolutions and MP3 because I changed it a few times because I just did not like the middle of it so I had to tweak it a little bit more but CDTemp Loki okay anyways so yeah here it is and it's glory and stuff and it'll be available for download soon I'm sure just have to get it to upload
[SPEAKER_21]: All righty, here we go.
[SPEAKER_21]: Paranoia Revolution.
[SPEAKER_21]: Enjoy, and we'll be back to wrap up the show after this.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_21]: It's Paranoia Revolution here on Orange Lounge Radio, remixed by our very own Loki.
[SPEAKER_21]: You know what I realized?
[SPEAKER_21]: The bass line in that kind of reminds me of Suguru.
[SPEAKER_21]: Like it has the same rhythm.
[SPEAKER_21]: Listen to it towards the end.
[SPEAKER_19]: Actually, it has the part, you know in Paranoia where it's all... Has that throughout the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_19]: Um, yeah, so it's like a, what is it, uh, 12th notes and then, um, like some 4th.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, it's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's just, it's a little bit, um, tweaked off of that.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's in the background, I know, for most of it, obviously, because I made it.
[SPEAKER_19]: But, um, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's all that's done on the second thing right now.
[SPEAKER_19]: DDR Angel, what is your final thought?
[SPEAKER_15]: Katamari Damacy, because I can't stop playing.
[SPEAKER_21]: Final thought from Bradley.
[SPEAKER_00]: You go last, right?
[SPEAKER_21]: Arcadian42?
[SPEAKER_29]: Thoughts?
[SPEAKER_29]: I have none at the moment.
[SPEAKER_29]: DarkSakura, your final thought?
[SPEAKER_16]: I have games to play, like I have Katamari Damacy now, I have Sims 2, and you know what?
[SPEAKER_16]: Real life is taking up all my time.
[SPEAKER_16]: So I've had to focus on school, everything, so there is a world outside of video games, not much one, and it usually sucks, but there is one.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, and my final thought is, don't forget to listen to our other shows on Monday night, Diversion, Orange Zones Radio Remix Show, Tuesday night, Pump Up the Volume with DarkSakura, 7 o'clock Pacific Time, and, oh, I'm sorry, 7 o'clock for pre-show, 7.30 for show, and Wednesday nights on Orange Zones Radio, Outside the Box, with a special Grand Theft Auto San Andreas update!
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes, very special Grand Theft Auto San Andreas update.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's the show on this station where we talk about the other games, other than the stomp your feet and tap your fingers games.
[SPEAKER_21]: So, we'll get to all that on Wednesday, and Tuesday, Jamie, I'm sure, will have another fun show, and Monday, remixes.
[SPEAKER_21]: Thursday, Orange Sounds Radio Rewind.
[SPEAKER_21]: Another night of programming is coming to Orange Sounds Radio soon, that's all I have to say.
[SPEAKER_21]: Also, the Long Versions program is going to launch...
[SPEAKER_21]: Hopefully, sometime this week, but like next week at the latest.
[SPEAKER_21]: So, we're going to have a long version program that's going to be at lunchtime for an hour.
[SPEAKER_19]: Rob, real quick question here in the studio.
[SPEAKER_19]: What about the, um, CK or something?
[SPEAKER_19]: Eh, okay, never mind.
[SPEAKER_19]: Nothing to see here, move along.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, and, should mention, when you're, um, you know, not listening to Orange Knowledge Radio, New South Park coming to Comedy Central.
[SPEAKER_21]: Hooray, hooray.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay, the last word of this show, I'll give it to Loki.
[SPEAKER_21]: Loki, the last word of tonight's show.
[SPEAKER_21]: One word that sums it all up for our listeners.
[SPEAKER_21]: I can't do it in one word.
[SPEAKER_21]: Fuck yeah!
[SPEAKER_32]: That does it for another episode of Orange Lounge Radio Live.
[SPEAKER_32]: Orange Lounge Radio Live is an Orange Lounge Radio production.
[SPEAKER_32]: For more information about our station, visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com And now, here is your fortune cookie message of the day.
[SPEAKER_32]: Thank you very much for listening, and we'll see you next week.
[SPEAKER_21]: Orange Lounge Radio, the afterbirth, the part after the credits have faded to black, etc., etc.
[SPEAKER_21]: I thought that was a gospel song at first, and then I realized what it was.
[SPEAKER_21]: I didn't realize they sung the theme around us like that.
[SPEAKER_21]: I thought they actually had a little synthesized thing.
[SPEAKER_19]: No, because the show fucking rocked, and then they took it off air like they do everything that's good on Nickelodeon.
[SPEAKER_19]: they need to have Nick Retro with, you know, the old, um, shows like Salute Your Shorts, you know, um, fuckin', uh, Hey Dude, and all that stuff, you know, they need to put that back on there, cause they've got, like, you know, this stupid, uh, Noggin crap with, like, you know, Daria's cool and stuff, but Degrassi, oh my god, it's like, what the hell, I don't even know what's up with that show, that show's got some weird shit on there, it's like, uh,
[SPEAKER_19]: Fucking Melrose Place meets High School.
[SPEAKER_21]: Jamie's yelling from the back, remember Seventeen, that show on Nickelodeon?
[SPEAKER_19]: Ha!
[SPEAKER_21]: Ha ha ha!
[SPEAKER_21]: Show was fabulous.
[SPEAKER_21]: For some reason it makes me think... God, yes, you can't do that on television.
[SPEAKER_21]: Why can't we have reruns if you can't do that on television?
[SPEAKER_21]: Turkey TV!
[SPEAKER_21]: Turkey TV.
[SPEAKER_21]: Pinwheel, today's special...
[SPEAKER_21]: And we all Oh well You know, we'll just never get that stuff back He'll just die He'll come back when Exactly Thank God for the internet Because I'm hoping more and more old school You can't do that on television episodes Start showing up Because I found a couple online once Or somebody gave me some I don't remember what it was Did you give me some?
[SPEAKER_21]: Angel gave me some Oh, so great I need to get more That show was so freaking fabulous
[SPEAKER_15]: Dude, the dungeon scenes.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, you can't do that on television.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's all I gotta say.
[SPEAKER_15]: Or the arcades.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's all about barf.
[SPEAKER_19]: That guy rocks.
[SPEAKER_19]: Poor guy.
[SPEAKER_19]: I think, isn't he dead?
[SPEAKER_19]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_19]: Poor guy.
[SPEAKER_19]: He was awesome.
[SPEAKER_19]: So underappreciated.
[SPEAKER_19]: And PeeWee, you know, fucking PeeWee's play out seems to come back.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't care if he's a fucking pervert and child molester.
[SPEAKER_19]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_19]: This is a conversation I was having with my friend the other day.
[SPEAKER_19]: We're talking about Michael Jackson, okay?
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, the guy's really fucked up.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, okay, maybe he slept with some children.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, that does not make his music bad.
[SPEAKER_19]: Just because someone's a child molester does not mean that they cannot make good music.
[SPEAKER_19]: Just like PeeWee Herman.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay, so he's into child pornography and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_19]: Does not mean the show was bad.
[SPEAKER_19]: Some comments from the chatroom Danger Mouse and Count Ducula
[SPEAKER_19]: Duckman needs to come back.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, Duckman, definitely.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, enough memory lane stuff.
[SPEAKER_19]: Coming to DVDs soon, Fresh Prince of Bel-Air and Full House.
[SPEAKER_19]: For all you sick pedophiles out there like the Olsen twins.
[SPEAKER_21]: When do I get my Golden Girls DVDs?
[SPEAKER_21]: When are those out?
[SPEAKER_21]: They're already out.
[SPEAKER_16]: What?
[SPEAKER_16]: I need Wonder Woman.
[SPEAKER_16]: Bitch, what?
[SPEAKER_21]: What?
[SPEAKER_21]: My Golden Girls DVDs are already out and I don't have them?
[SPEAKER_19]: I think they come out Tuesday or I think they're already out.
[SPEAKER_19]: They were coming out in October.
[SPEAKER_21]: Stop the presses!
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh my god, I must get this.
[SPEAKER_21]: Sorry, but you know, Golden Girls was like the best TV show ever.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm so excited.
[SPEAKER_21]: Says it ships November 23rd.
[SPEAKER_19]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_19]: I was confusing it with October 23rd.
[SPEAKER_21]: God, you got me all excited for nothing.
[SPEAKER_13]: I need Danger Mouse episodes.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm bringing up Danger Mouse.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_21]: We're going to pull the plug on the show now, and we're going to go to tonight's post show.
[SPEAKER_21]: You guys seem to like the Dance Mania stuff, so we're going to do Dance Mania X7 tonight.
[SPEAKER_21]: There's a lot of fun songs on here including some fourth mix songs if you can believe it or not.
[SPEAKER_21]: Have a great night.
[SPEAKER_21]: Thank you everybody very, very much for listening tonight.
[SPEAKER_21]: We really appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_21]: Have a great night.
[SPEAKER_21]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you for watching!