Orange Lounge Radio
With your hosts, DarkSakura, Sky and Loco
Tonight, September 21st, 2008
Warcraft's expansion finally gets a release date
Could Metal Slug get re-released in high definition?
And Animal Crossing undergoes a strange name change overseas
Orange Lounge Radio
Hello everybody out there on the internet
Welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio
We are that podcast on the internet
Dedicated to video games, video gaming, gaming culture
And the gamer lifestyle
We always tape live on Sunday nights
At about 6 o'clock Pacific Standard Time
On AllGames.com
Although we're getting a little bit of a late start tonight
The show before us, The Bobby Black Wolf Show
Ran over just a smidge
But that's kind of our fault
Because we're always on at the end of his show
And then we had a little teeny weeny snafu
Transitioning between shows
So we're a little bit late start tonight
But we are live and running
And my name is Rob Roberts
I join you here every week on the program
And also join you every week
Say hello to the one and only
Happiest bunny on the farm, DarkSakura
Jamie Summers
Hi
How are you doing, Jamie Summers?
I have no voice
Did you eat a frog?
No, I didn't
What happened?
When it got a little bit cooler here
The wind picked up and blew all of the pollen around
And well, I'm very prone to sinus infections
And I'm trying to fight off one
You know what you need?
A SARS mask
You know what I need?
What?
Power thirst
It's made from lightning
Awesome
Alright, so also say hello to the one and only
Techmaster Loki
Yes
Knock it off
Sorry, Loki, not you
What's up, Loki?
Not much
I figured out why that song cut off pre-show
Okay, hold on
We gotta explain now
For the people listening on the podcast
Before we go live
We always like play a song
To kind of transition from the previous show
To our show
And tonight was
What is this?
A Funk to the Past
Was the song that we played
Yes, Ninten-sploitation
Uh-huh
Nintendo-sploitation
It's by
Lime Mutterplucken B
Is the name of the guy that does it
Unique
It all
They all flow together each song
So that's why part of the song is on another track
Gotcha, because I was like
Why is that song cut off?
That's weird, okay
But it's one of those CDs that transitions
From song to song
I get it
Alrighty
Well, if you would like to join us
And give your input on the show
What's going on
You can always join our chat room
Chat.orangelaunchradio.com
Or if you only have an IRC client or whatever
You can always point yourself to the Game Surge Network
At gamesurge.net
And our chat room is Channel Orange Lounge
It's not just a clever name
So we are going to get into tonight's show
We always kick it off with a little bit of insight
On our gaming weeks and the games we've been playing
DarkSakura, how was your gaming week?
Um
I played Ragnarok
Ragnarok
And um
No, I played something else
Here's my occasional question on
Where's Ragnarok 2?
Whatever happened to Ragnarok 2?
It's in beta still
Still?
Hasn't it been beta for like a year and a half?
Usually it's been forever
Do you know how long the first Ragnarok was in beta?
A long, long time?
I played the beta for about three years
Geez
Wow
Alright
So, no, no, not three
It was about
No, it was about two years that I played the beta
Because I started on the
The first closed beta
I think
Or before
No?
Yeah, the first closed beta
So a long time
Yeah
So, wow, geez
I'm sorry you haven't tried to get in on that beta
It's just something about you have to have a Korean
Equivalent of a social security number to get in
I also looked more into it
And the only thing that I'm really interested in is the soundtrack
It's done by Yoko Kanno
Oh nice
Yeah, I mean
As soon as I can find a reliable way to give it a go
I might try, but for right now
There's emulated ways
Alright, fair enough
Well, if that's it for your gaming week
Then, Loki, how was your gaming week?
Um, it was alright
I played
Not a whole lot this week
Mainly
I played a lot of things
Grand Theft Auto IV, of course
Trying to keep on my winning streak
But there was a day that I let it get away from me
For a game or so
But it's back now
So I'm still on my winning streak
And then, um
I played
Some more Mercenaries 2
And I swear
The more I play that game
The more broken it gets
But it's kind of entertaining
Just to see how bad
The glitching will get
And so I'm about
To get my way through it now
And then
I also played
Pure, which is pretty fun
It's an ATV off-road racing game
Kind of a little similar
To Excite Truck, sort of
Um
Controls aren't exactly as tight as Excite Truck
I mean, it's a little bit more realistic
But, um
You know, a lot of flying through the air
And doing tricks and stuff like that
And lots of nitrous, so it's fun
But, um
Yeah, that's pretty much it so far
Alright, well
My gaming week, I actually played something new
This week, I went out and got a copy
Of Warhammer Online
I decided I was gonna take the plunge and go ahead and
Start playing another MMO
So I went and grabbed myself a copy of Warhammer Online
And, um
I don't know, MMOs are really hard to evaluate
You know, it takes a long time because there's so
Much depth to them
That they can take a long time to evaluate
And I'm not sure what my full opinion of Warhammer Online is
I'm still playing it, so that must be a good sign, right?
I had a friend of mine quit after playing it for
About ten minutes
Saying it was garbage
So, I mean, I guess I was into it long enough
To keep going past that
So, you know
Here's the thing, I'll start with what I don't like
About the game
I actually don't care for the graphics
Even though some of the textures are very pretty
And some of the shadow is very cool
For some reason, Warhammer
Feels really clunky to me
Really clunky
There seems to be delay in some of the things I do
And, you know, you could blame my computer's
Performance, but seeing as I just got a new
Quad-core 6GB RAM computer
I don't think it's necessarily the computer's
Specs that are slowing it down
You know, it's just
The interface feels a little clunky to me
It's not so bad that the game
Really suffers because I still
Will play it and everything
But it's a little bit clunky to me
And, I don't know, sometimes I find
The interface to be messy, but it's highly
Highly customizable, which is cool
And they really encourage people to customize this, that's cool
Alright, so, some of the things I do like about the game now
I do like kind of the way
That the game seems to be kind of
Split off into these three
Different areas, you have your PVE
Stuff, which feels pretty much
Like Warcraft, you know, and it's
Go to
Guy with exclamation point overhead
Or in this case, a little book with
A green book, get quest
Go do quest, turn in quest
You know, it's very, very similar to
Kind of the
Warcraft, but what I thought was
Kind of cool was now the different branches
That the game would go down, and that was something
Called Realm vs Realm, which is
Similar, I guess you could say, to PvP
Like, for instance, one of the
Realm vs Realm things I got into was
This thing where it's
For those that have played Warcraft, it's very
Similar to Arathi Basin
But you only have two nodes, and for those that are playing
Warhammer, I'm describing Kain's Embrace
I think that's how you say it
But what's kind of cool about it, what I really liked
Is that, okay, so you have, you know, the order
And you have chaos, and you're trying to capture
Both the nodes, and when one
Team captures both nodes
What's really cool is that it sets off this
Giant, like, alarm, like you hear
A rrrrrrrrr sound, and then
After ten seconds, giant
Explosions happen at both
The nodes to kind of reset the board
So, like, you'll see one team captures the nodes
And then you'll hear the big horn
And then you'll see everybody start running away
Because they want to get out of the explosion
Because if you get into the explosion, you instantly die
And I actually had a lot of fun with it
It was cracking me up, and I thought it was actually
Really well done, so I can
Tell already that the PvP
In this game is pretty well thought out
And done really well, and I
Really like the fact that the game kind of
Gives you buffs, so that, like, let's say
This particular
RVR experience
Is a one versus ten
They call it ranks in Warhammer, but you notice
Levels, let's say it's a level one
Through ten, you know, RVR
Instance, everybody gets bumped up
To rank eight, so that way
You know, even if you're kind of lower
You get the stats of a rank eight character
So that way the playing field seems a little
More level, it seems like they've really
Kind of tested this out and really
Kind of tweaked the PvP in this
So I think if you're, like, a PvP player mostly
You're gonna be drawn to
Warhammer, I think, a lot more
Than WoW, and Warhammer does
Have some PvE elements in it
And the other thing, kind of the other road that Warhammer
Goes down that I thought was kind of cool was the idea
Of public quests, which is
Kind of neat, like, you can go into an area
And there might be an event going on, and again
To compare this to Warcraft, because that's what, you know
I just do that because that's what most you MMO players
Know, I would say, like, imagine
You could just walk into a 25 man
Raid and walk out as you please
That's kind of what a public quest is
You'll go into an area and there might be an event
Going on, like an early event that I played
Was one where you kill 30
Guards, then you protect 30 guards
Then you have to kill a giant dragon
And his Beastmaster, and like that
Whole event kind of goes on, it takes about 15
Minutes to complete, and you can run in and play
As much or as little as you want
But the more you participate in it, the better
Your role is going to be for the loot at the end
And then as you play it, your reputation
Kind of goes up slowly
Does Beastmaster have a pair of ferrets?
No, he does not have a pair of ferrets
He's the Beastmaster over, like, a dragon
There might be a ferret Beastmaster later in the game
I don't know, but uh...
Are they called Kodo and Podo?
No. But yeah, I thought that was kind of neat
That you could slowly gain the
You know, kind of the experience that way
So there's many different ways to
Experience in the game and different types
Of, you know, you have your
Renown is one
And then your experience
You meet the different things to accomplish
But, like, I haven't really gotten a chance
To tackle the crafting
So I feel like there's still a lot more of this game
For me to explore
And the MMO is early
So, you know, while I might be criticizing
The graphical interface and these sorts of things
Early on, there's gonna be
Patches that will probably fix a lot of the stuff
That bugs us. I mean, let's face it
Pretty much any MMO has a lot of issues
When it first launches. So that's another reason
Why I'm like, hmm, I can't really
Review this game in full yet
Because it still has a long way to grow
And develop. But I will say this
If you're a PvPer
You really like the player versus player stuff
I think you're really gonna enjoy Warhammer
Even if you're more of a PvE type person
There's something worth
Checking out here for you. Like, I'm usually not a big
PvPer, but I thought it was set up enough where
I didn't feel like
I was wasting my time
If that makes sense. Like, I was having a good time
And I was enjoying the game. And that's really what it comes down to
So I do recommend
If you like MMOs, check out Warhammer
Online. At least do your research
Check into it. See if it's something you like
Sadly there's no trial for it, really
And I think that's one thing they're severely lacking
And they need to get up and running in the next 60 days
Is get a trial for the people who really
Want to check out what this game's all about
Because they can get away with it for right now
Because the game's got a lot of hype and they're gonna have a lot of initial user base
But I really think if they want to
Really try to sway people
They're gonna need to have a trial similar to
What Warcraft has where you can experience the first
20 levels or so. I think that's what
Warhammer badly needs. Would you guys check out
Warhammer if they had something like that?
Where you didn't have to drop the dollars to check it out? No? Why?
I'm not at all interested in Warhammer
You're not really a big, big MMO player
I mean, you play Ragnarok, but you haven't enjoyed
A lot of the other MMOs you've played. You didn't enjoy
Warcraft, you didn't. That's different.
That's a space one. But I actually
I liked World of Warcraft until
It turned out that it just wasn't worth my time
Loki?
Yeah, I don't play MMOs right now
And even when
My wife joins Warcraft, I may not
Do that. Alright, fair enough.
Although when APB comes around
We'll talk again
Alright, well that's it for my gaming week, otherwise
Just pretty much Rock Band 2 and games you've heard me
Talk about before. So
Let's get into some housekeeping tonight
And tonight for housekeeping, Loki wants to
Talk about olrpsp.com
Well, I was just gonna say that I have a thread
Up in our forum right now
Basically
Allowing you guys to
Submit banners
Because if you notice on the
Olrpsp all games radio player
That there's a little banner
That keeps repeating, and you'll probably have noticed
That there's only three of them. One including
A banner for the PAX
Coverage, which is way old now.
So we need more banners
And it's real easy
Pretty much you can make a banner for
You know, either one of the shows
On the network, one of the
Inside jokes, something
You know, funny like one of the PSAs
Just anything. Just pretty much
Anything that's kind of show related
Or network related
Or indie production related
Yeah, and basically
Just 296 pixels
By 32, and
Why is it such a weird ass banner size?
That's just the size I made it
And there you go
And all the details are on our forums
And you can post your
Images there
Or email them to me
And if they're decent
Then we'll throw them up there
And you can see the awesome
Olrpsp.com, you can see this in action
On that great all games radio
Tuner on the PSP
Awesome
Speaking of please for stuff
You know, we've been having to recycle a lot of the
Audio bumpers we used during our free breaks
In the middle of the show
We haven't done any new stuff lately
So please if you have an independent show you want to plug
You host your own podcast or whatever
Please send me commercials
Fake PSAs, whatever you want to send
That's not for profit
We're looking for more stuff, we really need some stuff
I don't think you're going to hear a lot in tonight's free break
Because I don't want to recycle the same old crap over and over again
Sadly I didn't have time to create anything new today
So we really rely on you guys
For some of the extra stuff
Just send me an email or post on the forums
There's all that cool stuff on there
Rhetortainment is in chat
Reading some comments from chat, he says
I have the latest version of the PSP hardware
I tried to download the all games player on
OLRPSP.com and it didn't work
Any thoughts on what might be going on?
I have no idea
It should work, you just put it in this
It's probably the directory that you have it in
You probably set it in the wrong directory
Try downloading the official radio players
Off of Sony's website
If those work for you
Then I don't know
It's probably the same directory as those
But you test on the latest
PSP firmwares as they're released right?
No
Then again it shouldn't matter
They don't remove anything
From the PSP firmwares
To be honest I don't have any legitimate
Firmwares
It doesn't matter because they're the exact
Same thing plus other added bonuses
I want to read this comment
From earlier because I'm not sure
If it's on the right track or not
Jamie also has bad memories
Involving things like Warhammer right?
Is that true or not?
The Warhammer with the little models
Yeah
What happened?
I had an ex who would play Warhammer to the exclusion of all else
Yikes
And I would have to sit and paint his models
Do you think that he's gotten
Sucked into this thing beyond belief at this point?
Dude I don't know
This is 12 years ago in Alabama
It was worth asking
I don't care what happened
Was it Warhammer or Warhammer 40,000?
It was Warhammer 40k
Keep in mind
My review comes from somebody who has never
Touched a Warhammer model
Or done any of that stuff
I did get vengeance on him once
How so?
He had some sort of big figure that was
This hulking creature
And I painted it hot pink
Nice
That was pretty cool
Well also pretty cool
Some video game news!
Loki, start us off tonight would you?
Alright
This time
I think we may have talked about this a little bit before
But Rock Revolution
As if you needed more reasons
Why it's not gonna be that great
Well Konami says that they're not actually gonna put out
Any guitars for it
So you're gonna need to find your own guitars
Whether that be a Guitar Hero guitar
A rock band guitar
Or you're just gonna need another guitar
Cause if you don't own any music game
And for some reason you decide this is the one you
Want to start off with
Well all you're gonna be able to get is just the drums
And that's it. No guitars for you
You know what do you think of this? Because at first
I was kinda like laughing to myself
Going, well geez this just kinda goes to show
About this game
Then as I was thinking about it I was like
But at the same time I really don't need another freaking
Guitar in my house
So in a way I'm thankful
Not necessarily I mean they should
They have the option of buying the game by itself
Or the bundle
But the thing is they're just not gonna make a guitar
Whatsoever and that's fine if they don't want to do it
But I've had you know Konami reps
Before tell me oh we're not in the
We're not in the peripheral business
But yet you have peripherals bundled with
Your DDR bundles so
You're a liar
Basically
But yeah they're not trying to be in the peripheral business
Yet they're making a game with peripherals
So they're kind of
Well plus the fact that
It's not like Konami's never made a guitar controller
Before they just didn't do it
Here it's probably they just don't want to make another
One they probably have reasons
And it's maybe something to do with
You know the fact that they've licensed out there
Designed for guitars
To other companies or something maybe there's something
Legal
That we don't see
Yet I mean that's part of the lawsuit
Or something that's why they didn't do it
And that's why they only did drum controller
Maybe I'm thinking
That's got to be the reason because if you notice the drum
Controllers that they have out there
They're not exactly rip offs
Of the original
Drum mania controller
Except for Konami's which is obviously
It looks like kind of a rip off of the original
Drum mania controller but they can do that since it's theirs
And it sucked for the record
Yeah so
That's my thing is that maybe they
These people are paying to license
You know these guitars or something
And I don't know
Non compete thing or something I don't know
You know Bobby Blackwolf
Is in our chat right now and he obviously does the show
Before us here on All Games he says
I find it funny this is news when Konami has always
Said this Konami told me at E3 that they are
Only making a drum peripheral and really
It's one less plastic instrument you have to buy
And yeah I want to say Loki saw something
In the retail world that indicated this is going to be
True a while ago too but it's kind of
Interesting because you see the trailers for Rock Revolution
Hitting this week and there's really no
Hint at this whole thing
And what about the fact that people are going to be
Buying this game maybe expecting that there's
Going to be a guitar with it because that's what you see
In the other bundles
Well it will just have to be very clear on the box
That it's not going to happen
You and I both know it will be in tiny tiny print
Somewhere, guitar not included
Well I think it's also you know the guitar
Not included I don't even remember if they have
Vocals in this as well I think
No they don't have
Vocals in it before they were going to
But they accidentally
So it's just a guitar and drums
And
I don't know I don't think it's a big deal because
Shit you can buy used guitars like used
Guitar Hero 2 guitars for like 12 bucks
So
Doesn't really matter but
I don't know
Whatever do what they want to do the game is going to suck anyways
Are you sure?
And again
Having not played it what's your basis for this?
My basis for it is it looks cheap
All the videos I've seen from it look cheap
All the gameplay from it I've seen looks very cheap
It just looks like a cheap knock off
And that's sad because you know
They were the ones that pioneered this
But it's just a cheap knock off
What their problem was is they
Did it right to start with in Japan
But they didn't realize that their American
User base would be interested in the same stuff too
So it was they started way
Too late
And I'll quote Bobby that there is
One of the icons for the drum
Is actually a dark grey
Come on
That's retarded what were you thinking
You know and I've said this on the show before
I don't know if I want to continue to beat a dead horse
But you know in a way
If Konami is going to assume
You know what happens about assuming
That this stuff is not going to
Take off in America you know then they have
No one to blame but themselves for what's happening now
I mean and this
Sounds all conspiracy theory
Like but I really think
That they're making this so that it doesn't
Do well so that they can sue
Them so they have reason
To say hey look your game is causing
Our game not to sell
But
I don't think that that
Would fly in court and they know it
They'd have to know better
Alright well let's see what you guys
The listeners thought because OLR is the show
How long did they register any
Licenses for Guitar Freak
For Guitar Freak Surger Mania
They did Guitar Revolution a while back
Well they also had an arcade release of Guitar Freaks here
So you know that's years old
I don't know if that would count for a console
Well now that I think of it Guitar Revolution and Drum Revolution
Oh Rock Revolution here we go
Alright anyhow
Let's go to the pre-OLR
Twitter to see what you guys
Out there thought and we asked on our Twitter
Our username on Twitter if you're a Twitter user you should
Add us it's just simply OLR
Before every show we ask questions
This week we asked are you getting Rock Revolution
Why or why not
DGRamaS said possibly problem is
Real estate space but if the game works with
Guitar Hero Rock Band Controllers then yes
And I think it's been pretty well known now that
Yes it will work with both
So that's a yes
Picaruno says hell no because that's the answer I gave
Last time I guess during the show we must
Ask this before once
The SEG said no I enjoy the
Careful selection harmonics practices
In their set list they are game designers
Of music so kind of going back to the set list
K Rose
Says I won't buy it
I only like Konami games for the Japanese music
If it's localized I'll get a better
Rhythm band game like Rock Band
Interesting perspective that you know they didn't
Bring over anything from Japan so
There are folks that like that although I gotta say
Though you're kind of a niche
Market in that case you know
I think it would be nice if somebody would
Release a game that has some of the US stuff
And that but you're never
Going to see a game released over here
It's kind of retarded about this too
The game only version of this is coming out in early
October the
Actual instruments the drums
And those bundles aren't coming until like
Mid November
Well Rock Band 2 is the same way
Well they're just doing that now because they have the
Exclusive for it but it's still
Stupid because if you want to try their
Unique drums or whatever how many people are going to
Buy this game and just go eh
Whatever you know I'm not going to buy the drums
Now they're stuck with a bunch of drums
Alright going back to the Twitter question
Are you going to buy Rock Revolution
GS68 says I'm too ghetto to bother shelling
Out the moneys for it. Act Def says no
Because Konami failed to do this years ago and they
Should have and they're not even offering something
At the level of Rock Band Guitar Hero
Gold Anthro says no because if I was going to spend
The money for a game like that I'd buy Guitar Hero or
Rock Band. Marin Marvel says
No it's too little too late for Konami to try to
Jump back into the music game business in the US
They've already failed hardcore
Joosten says all covers in an
Archaic interface? No thank you
Plus the drums look like ass. Konami
Missed the boat years ago
I can never say this name
Giove Dea
I think
I got lessons on how to pronounce it last week but I
Already forgot. I think it's Giove Dea
As DJ Rama S said
Only if it works with the stuff I already have
Javier Altman says
Because we already have enough plastic
Instrument stuff. Konami is
Too late for their own good. The last Bossa
De Sanna has been played
Sponge Twang says I will wait out
Most likely into next year after
The dust has settled. I need to figure which
Plastic instruments work with which games
DJ Tyrant says depends on how good the
Execution is since it's compatible
With Rock Band 2 Guitar Hero gear
I might pick it up but they are very late to the party
And lastly Chad28 says
No because they are mostly songs
That have already been used in other Guitar Hero
Rock Band games and no Master Tracks
There you have it
Twitter.com slash O-L-R
And um
Yeah
So alright well we'll see what happens
I mean it's really hard to make an ultimate
Decision until the game actually comes out
I would just if you're unsure about it
Just wait cause
You know in the past there have been other games that haven't
Performed very well and the price drops
Come very quickly so
Alright we'll see what happens
Alright well let's move on talking about Guitar Hero
Since we're kind of on music game news right now
Very interesting story being teased this week is that
It was the CEO of Publishing
For Activision, Mike Griffith
He has actually kind of come out and said
According to Shaq News that
They might be looking at a subscription
Model for Guitar Hero
So where as you know Rock Band and Guitar Hero
To date function with their download content
Kind of like iTunes, imagine a system that was
More like Napster where it's more
Subscription based
Apparently 20 million individual
Songs have already been downloaded for Guitar Hero
Which is pretty impressive when you consider that
There's not nearly as much
As there is for Rock Band, I mean there's some good stuff
And not nearly as much
Just it could be interesting
If especially if the timetable is
Stepped up for the releases
What this annual subscription model could do
What do you guys think, is the subscription model a good idea
Bad idea? I don't think it's a good idea
Why is that? Because you don't know what's coming out
I mean that's
Kind of stupid, who knows what they're going to put out
What frequency it's going to be coming out as
I mean there might be a lot of stuff that you're not
Really interested in
I would say you'd have
I think the better deal is the way that Rock Band's doing it
Where you have a bundle of songs
That you can pay for
And if you want all of them you get it like a buck cheaper
Or something like that
Or you know you can buy individual songs
Because if you pay like say 60 bucks a year or whatever
For the subscription model or whatever
What if it's not worth it to you
Because all these songs coming out
And you have them and you're just like eh
What do you think, Dark Sakura?
What if for a subscription model
If they had it like
Okay you know how it used to be like if you did like
BMG music or something
How you would
They had their featured CD
And then you could refuse it if you want to
And picked what you wanted to order
What if they did something to that effect
Where they say this is our exclusive featured
Track, you can only get it this way
However if you don't want it
Then choose something else
And then also the other thing comes too
It's nice that they want to do this
But is this actual model built into
Xbox Live, Marketplace
Or Playstation Network
Now we know Playstation Network can do it
Because they obviously have their core subscription model
And you can pay for stuff that way
Why not? There's two MMOs on Xbox 360
That have subscription models
Fantasy Star Universe and Final Fantasy XI
Yeah but those are done through their own individual servers
But you still pay for it on Xbox Live
That's true, in the case of the
Fantasy Star Universe you actually pay for that on
Xbox Live, so it's got to
Be there
They actually have you input all of your billing information
Right before you can start
VXJ6V comes up with an interesting point in chat
Loki you don't know what music comes out in the real world
Either until it's about to or does
This is fundamentally nothing different from
Actual music subscription services
But at the same time I mean to kind of
But at the same time though it's not necessarily
Just
I mean what are they going to do? You have to pay
To this service to get
Access to all the download content
Or you're just going to get access to the new stuff
Like say if I'm on Rhapsody or
You know Napster or whatever
Napster's got to have, I mean I'm just pulling
This number out of my butt, but Napster's got to have
Hundreds of thousands of songs on it
Exactly, that's a little different thing
Guitar Hero has a bucket full
Maybe, not a room full
You know what I mean? Exactly
That's totally different
Unless they're going to start pumping out
20 tracks a week
Or something like that, then that's different
But I don't think they are
I notice a lot of people are kind of turning their noses
Up as subscription models, but I mean
That's pretty much how all MMOs work
And also the other thing you have to look at too
Are people really going to start
Wanting all this
Licensed music
Which is good, but at the same time
With Guitar Hero World Tour now you're going to have
All this independently made music
All the stuff through the
Song creator or whatever
That you can download for free
So
What I'm thinking might work
Is sort of, I'm going back to what I was saying before
About having the exclusive
Subscription only stuff
If they have like
Certain things that are available only
Through subscription and they have their regular
Bundle packs that everybody has access to
But there's only certain
Really good stuff available
To people who are in the fan club
What about like a
Just kind of really going off wild here
What about like a Guitar Hero magazine or something
Or a tie in with a rock magazine
Or something that would come with a CD with bonus tracks
Because I'm thinking rock bands kind of done that
Like the Xbox
What, official Xbox magazine had like three bonus
Songs on it at once so you could only get there
Well I think they came out for download eventually
But a long time later
And there was the deal about buying the soundtrack
That gave you the
Bonus songs
Alright well, we'll see, we'll see what happens
I mean, new ideas, never a bad
Thing to try new things, the worst that can happen
Is you fall on your face and fail
But hopefully they'll still keep kind of both
Options available, but we'll see what happens
Who knows
Well it looks like Activision's getting something right
In the UK and Ireland
They're actually stating
That there's going to be
A bundle pack called the Super Bundle
That is for, it's 150 pounds
It has the
Game, the guitar, the microphone, and the drum kit
But you also get a free bass guitar
Well, I mean
You don't have to at least pay the 50 pounds for the guitar
You just have, you just get it in your Super Bundle
It's going to be
The same Red Octane
One
That's the Guitar Hero 3
Peripheral for PS3
This is UK
Only, just to reiterate
And they're saying that there's a release date
Early November
So
That's pretty, pretty
Interesting, I think
But it would be available
To any retailer
And consumers can pre-order either online or in-store
I want free stuff
It's not fair
Yeah, but they're giving them old guitars
But it's free!
Oh, okay. I give you a kick in the balls
It's free
Now
Yeah, but unlike a kick in the balls
Which is somewhat entertaining
Sorry, Rob
How would you know?
I'm a girl, they're very entertaining to watch
And deliver
You'll never be the recipient of one
Exactly
But anyway
I think that
It's actually, first of all
It's a good way to get rid of some overstock
If that's half the case
You could never have too many peripherals
I love peripherals, I have a room in my house
Dedicated to peripherals
You are also a freak in that regard
You know what? You've seen the vault
No, I mean that with love
But you know you are a freak in that regard
Whereas I won't even get the fucking drum set
For Rock Band, because I'm like, I just don't need any more shit in my house
But I have a whole room
You know I'm actually getting
You have to get a vault, Rob
No vault, this is the vault
My freaking garage is now an internet
Radio station hub
There is room here for a drum kit
Do not want
Pinball machine, yes, drum kit, no
You wanna buy our Black Knight?
I'm poor
The Rock Band 2 drums are actually being delivered to my work
On Wednesday
Your wife is gonna punch you in the face
I'm getting rid of the old ones
I'm upgrading, whatever
What are you gonna do with the old ones?
Give them to my sister, I think
Anyways
Some other interesting stuff about Guitar Hero
And I guess this is a little bit of trivia
The Metallica mix of their brand new album
Is actually
Better in Guitar Hero
Than it is on the actual CD
In fact, the new Death Magnet album
Has been mixed too loud
They say
And is actually sacrificing audio quality
In favor of a louder
Sounding product
Well, Guitar Hero on the other hand
It's actually
A little bit more balanced
So you actually have a little bit more depth
Than the audio in there
So a lot of people are thinking
Hey, let's just rip the audio from Guitar Hero instead
Okay, wouldn't this be a matter of opinion though?
No, they actually
They looked at the audio
They actually ran it through
You know, a
Waveform editor or whatever
And it showed, you know, how they had it
Capped in there for the CD audio
Versus Guitar Hero
Which is significantly better on
Guitar Hero
Is this one of those things that only like
Crazy audio files would really notice?
Like, what about
Joe Average Headbanger?
You know, they get some Metallica CDs
They may not care, but you know
I actually did listen to some of the portions of it
When they were comparing it
It does sound distorted
Sounds like someone just recorded it too loud
But it's Metallica! It's supposed to be loud!
You know what I mean?
It's supposed to be loud, but you're supposed to turn up
Your radio to 11!
Okay, you're not supposed to record it loud
And then turn it up, because it'll sound all fucked up
They should know this! I mean, hell
I mean, come on! Hitstun agrees, Hitstun says
The CD has mad clipping, and Alpha
Kananagram agrees it's too much clicking
In our chatroom, chat.com
I think they should replace everyone's CDs
That's my opinion
It's that bad? Really?
Well, I guess so
Especially when the CD
In some regard, the old-fashioned CD market
Is struggling to survive in a way
This is a pretty big screw-up
This is what you get for buying CDs
I'm just telling you
See, this is what Metallica thinks of you
They're all, fuck you guys, we're gonna just record it all fucked up
Ah, you bought the CD
Now you're stuck, bitches
Somehow I doubt that
You should play Rock Band or Guitar Hero
Alright, well look, if you want to play more
Guitar Hero, especially Guitar Hero World Tour
You can use your
Rock Band drums with Guitar Hero World Tour
And this story's kind of making the rounds of the
Blogs, although I don't know, I thought I already
Kinda knew some of this, but whatever
Here's the thing, what happens
If you use a Rock Band
Drum set in Guitar Hero
World Tour, and this is kind of
Demonstrated a World Tour preview event that happened
Earlier this week
Basically what'll happen is that the pad
That's all the way on the right
On the five
Note chart
Will actually kind of go over
To the other orange pad instead
But sometimes there will be some other
Logic as well, like if there's
Already an orange note in there, it might actually
Move it to a blue note
So there is, it's not just necessarily
Eliminating the fifth one altogether
Like, and I think that's kind of where this is
Kind of resurfacing in news reports
Cause I think the early things we thought
Is that that fifth one would just get eliminated altogether
But no, those notes are gonna get moved
Basically to other drops
Which is kind of neat in a way
Which is also good for score comparison and everything
Does it truly keep everything on the same page
Or what, is this gonna be an advantage?
Using one controller over the other
Because one's four and one's five
I don't think it matters
But then again I'm not super duper into drums as well
Right? Yeah
So
So I got sent a link to a YouTube
That's supposed to compare the two Metallica tracks
You wanna hear it a little bit?
I've already listened to it
Okay
Here's the thing
I bet you, this is a radio show
You didn't get to see what we saw on our screen
Which would show you which clips were guitar hero
And which clips were the CD
I bet you people at home couldn't tell the difference
Now granted this show is delivered at a lower bit rate
But I think this is one of those things
And you can see it in the visuals
Absolutely, you can see, look at the waveforms
They absolutely look different
Where the guitar hero wants to prep
But what's the audio quality on
YouTube?
Not that great
So I think you're not gonna be able to tell
Until you actually have the two side by side
In person
It's like, okay, here's an example
When Symphony of the Night came out on Saturn
Dan and I actually did
A side by side comparison
Because we had seen one done
Online that we couldn't hear the difference in the music quality
But when we did it on our TV
We could
Have them both running side by side
Alright, some people in chat rooms say
Yes, I hear the difference, it's very clear
I don't know, sometimes I think people just want to argue
But alright, I'm gonna be honest
If I closed my eyes, I probably wouldn't have been able to tell you the difference
All I can tell you is the metallica
But I understand, I can see the difference
Okay, I get the point
I get what you guys are saying
I heard the new album is mediocre anyway
So what do we even care about it?
It's just like saying, you know
Barney is not in high def quality
You know, it's just in normal quality
What the fuck, you know
It doesn't matter, it's Barney, no one gives a shit
Hmm
That's my comparison there
Alright, well look, not only
Do we have that going on in the rock band world
That there is the news about
How you're gonna use the rock band drums on Guitar Hero World Tour
But, hey look, this is a much more
Important clip, because
Hey, coming to the rock band download store this week
Finally
After a very, very, very
Very long wait
The real Tom Sawyer
Hell yeah
The actual version of Tom Sawyer
One of my favorite songs
Kicking off the Moving Pictures album
Is finally making its way to a rock band this week
They swear, and of course, you know
Other songs like YYZ, Limelight
You know, those are all from Moving Pictures
Not a lot
Of songs on that album, considering
It was kind of epic, and the albums were
Only like 7 or 8 tracks back then
And that The Camera Eye is an 11
Freaking minute song
Epic release is very epic
And, as if this wasn't enough
You kind of get the feeling that this
Late delivery of this album was just added
On top of what was already going to be released
Because you got 6 other just kind of like
Kind of potpourri songs
Just kind of a hodgepodge mix
Of songs from Bad Religion, The Cult
Hot Hot Heat, Caspian
Caspian, Sleater Kenny
And Stone Roses all have songs
Coming out this week, so
Very cool
I may not get the whole album
But I do love me some Tom Sawyer, that was like one of my favorite
Songs in the first rock band, and I think the real
Version is much better than the cover version
I want to get that at least
Maybe YYZ or
Limelight, I don't know yet
11 minute song, do not want
Because that will show up in my random playlist
Guaranteed
So I don't want to get the whole album, sorry
Tom Sawyer
Is a really, really freaking good
Song, that's a great album in general
It is
Canada knows how to rock, is your proof
Alright
So, another
Interesting thing about Guitar Hero
And this has been kind of circling around
A little bit
Every instrument that G4 hinted to
It's not really an instrument at all
It's a MIDI sequencer
That's right
They're going to be adding a MIDI sequencer
That will allow you to
Import creations
Like
MIDI files from your PC
Into Guitar Hero World Tour
As well as
Allowing you to
I guess
At least on the PS3
To import different tracks
Including instruments
Rhythm lead, guitar, bass
Keyboards, and drum tracks
However on the 360 it will only be limited to drums
Due to hardware issues
Which, whatever
I don't understand what hardware issues they could be having
That would prevent them from doing this
But whatever
So yeah
I guess kind of interesting
No word on price or when it's going to be released
But
You're really hardcore into making
I guess
Tracks on there
That actually sounds kind of awesome though
I think I'd use it
I think it's a neat idea for an expansion
You know the results could be iffy
But I think that's really taken this franchise
In a different direction
I don't know how often it will actually be used though
Tiger Clawed Chat says
I think you could also create techno on that
Could you?
Could you make different genres of music and stuff?
You could make
Well I was telling them about drum and bass stuff
They said that yeah you can make
Whatever to your heart's content on there
So you could make a drum and bass
Track or a techno track if you're that creative
Interesting
That's the only thing that kind of makes me
Want to buy maybe just the game only version
Or something
Just to check that out
I don't know I'll wait and see
So Black Wolf and I are having a little bit of an argument
In chat room right now over the last story
And he says Rush is the only good thing
To come out of Canada
And I said wait a minute no no no no
Degrassi
Hello
You can't do that on television
He says I still lose
Degrassi is not a great thing to come out of Canada
And I think you're full of poop sir
And what was that show?
Out of Control
That show was great
Kids in the Hall
And what is that dish
With the french fries with gravy
Poutain or whatever
That stuff is good
That stuff rocks too
And maple syrup
Alright forget it
We love Canada come on
And hockey
Alright I think Black Wolf is just giving us a hard time
Now he's really starting to argue with us
Just for the sake of arguing
Alright how about some release dates
Do we gotta
Okay well coming out
For our friends in the UK
Pardon my death voice
On the 24th
Duke Nukem 3D for Xbox 360
25th is Pure
On some systems
26th is the rest of everything
Vampire Story
Baja Edge of Control
Brothers in Arms Hell's Highway
Don King presents Prize Fighter
Family Trainer on Wii
G1 Jockey 4
G1 Jockey 4 2008
Harvest Fishing on DS
R-Type Tactics PSP
Samba de Amigo
Sonic Chronicles The Dark Brotherhood
The Destiny of Zorro
And Wario Land The Shake Dimension
Yay Wario Land
Alright awesome
That game is gonna be great
Forgot that that's actually coming out
Anyways Nintendo's been doing a great job marketing that
Oh yeah
I mean not really
Yeah that's gonna be a
As good as the DS one fortunately
Who knows maybe there'll be an onslaught of
Marketing Blitz in the game itself
I hope so, the game's awesome
It really is better than I think a lot of people are expecting it to be
Well
Starting off this week in the US
We've got
The Price is Right coming to PC
And I think other systems as well
Baja The Edge of Control
Coming out on
PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360
Wasn't that Price is Right game supposed to be out last week?
This is the PC version
They may have delayed it from last week so
Oh
Let's see, same with the Hell's Kitchen PC game
So I'm guessing it came out last week
Kirby Superstar Ultra
On the DS which they actually did
Some pretty good marketing for that
They had like little Kirby clouds
Which is kinda neat
And I doubt this is coming out but apparently the
Symbol pack, 2 pack
2 is supposed to be out
I heard that it's supposed to be October
And of course you go to a GameStop and you ask them
Hey one of the symbols coming at your website says the 22nd
And we're like I don't know
So the hell with them
You can get a box set of
The Command and Conquer games
For Command and Conquer 3
Both Command and Conquer 3 and
Kain's Wrath
And a nice little box set there
Nancy Drew and the Hidden Staircase
For the DS
Let's see here
Also
There's some
EA08 Sports Collection
Ooh, a bunch of games from last year, awesome
SimCity Creator
For the Wii and the DS
Wario Land Shake It
Coming to the Wii
DeBlob, also coming
To the Wii
Dropcast, which is a puzzle game
Coming to the DS
Digatti Defenders, also
My Little Pony, Pinkie Pie's Party
Also on the DS
Yippie
Brain Quest, grades 3 and 4
And 5 and 6 coming to the DS
Hey, quick question
Does anyone give a shit about Brain Quest
Grade 3, 4, 5, 6
Cause I'm thinking we can make this segment
A little shorter
No we can't
By cutting out the games that not a single
OLR listener cares about, not a one
That is being
Biased right there
It is completely biased, but also true
Hey, we've got parents to listen, who knows
Maybe they want to get something for their kid
Maybe you're full of poop
Something that says, hey look, I know you like games, but I hate you
You know, that kind of thing
And they might also get them Barbie Fashion Show
Eye for Style for the DS
There you go
Dinosaur King, coming out for the DS
What better way to tell your child I hate you
Sing Star Pop Volume 2
Coming out on Playstation 2
Onimusha, The Essentials
It's a 3-pack collection
Of previous Onimusha games
Buzz, The Master Quiz
Coming out on PSP and also Buzz Quiz TV
Coming out on Playstation 3
Line Rider 2
Unbound on PC
And DS this week, I believe
Brothers in Arms, Hell's Highway
On Playstation 3 and Xbox 360
Also Dragon Ball Z
trilogy coming out on Playstation 2
We've also got
Time Hollow on the DS
Which is a Konami
Role-playing game
Pipe Mania is a puzzle game
Kind of like Pipe Dream
And also the hacking in Bioshock
That's on PSP
And I want to say the Wii also
Lego Batman
Pretty much on every single system out there
Playstation 2, 3
360, Wii, DS, and PSP
Lost in Blue Shipwrecked on the Wii
My Japanese coach
That moved to October
So that date's wrong
Bastards have incorrect dates on their website
Rebel Raiders
On the Wii
Although that game sucks balls
So I wouldn't recommend buying it
Lots of stuff this week, I guess
Cavella's Dangerous Hunts 2009
Coming out on 360, Playstation 3
Playstation 2, and Wii
Samba de Amigo
Coming out on Wii this week
And I believe the Maracas come out this week as well
Warriors Rochii 2
on Playstation 2 and 360
Uhhhh
I think we're almost done here
Thank god
Sorry
Hi Hamtaro Ham Ham Challenge
Cause it's a cute hamster game on the DS
And
Disgaea DS
Is gonna be coming out as well
And
God damn there's a lot of shit this week
Come on
Well while you're trying to figure it out
I looked up cause I was curious
What's on that Sing Star Pop Volume 2
And kind of an interesting
mix of songs
Nelly Furtado, Permisqueous
Jenny from the Block by Jennifer Lopez
This is definitely a top 40 mix here
Fergie, Big Girls Don't Cry
The Sweet Escape, Gwen Stefani
And uh
I don't know Dark Soccer maybe you'll like this one
Rihanna, Umbrella, Ella
Ella, A
I actually don't like that song
I like the remix
Under My Umbrella, Ella, Ella, A
I only like the remix
Alright alright enough of that
That's annoying seriously
Rhapsody a Musical Adventure on the DS
Rob
What?
Knock it out
Can I turn off her mic? How do I unplug her mic?
I don't know
Pitfall, The Big Adventure on the Wii
And that's it
Done
Finally, alright no I'm just kidding
Alright let's look at Japan release dates and see what's coming out over in Japan this week
On the 25th
The Japanese language version
Of Infinite Undiscovery and the English language version
Make their way to regions outside Japan
Sometimes I get some general
Asia release dates
Like I said this Friday for regions outside Japan
But in Japan you get a game called
Janline comes out in Japan this Friday
Also Madden NFL 09
And Tiger Woods PGA Tour on 09
Finally come out in Japan this Friday
Because they usually get localized versions of our sports games
Just a little later than we do
Also coming out on the
PlayStation 3
Aquanauts Holiday comes out in Japan
From Sony Entertainment
Also a new headset will come out
Madden NFL 09
Quest for Booty comes out
Again that's an Asia release not just Japan
But just Japan would be
Tiger Woods PGA Tour 09
Going to some of the other systems
Taking a look at the
Nintendo Wii
Bomberman comes out on
September 25th as does
Disaster Day of Crisis
SimCity Creator
The simple 2000 series for the Wii
The Table Game volume 1
So Loki you like the simple series on the
Game Boy Advance right?
So now they have these games coming out on the Wii
I used to check out some of the stuff on the PlayStation 2
The Wii stuff
I've gotten like a couple
But I haven't actually played them
They have all the kind of weird stuff
I don't play my Zhong
So a lot of that doesn't apply to me
An interesting looking game called
Soul Eater Monotone Princess
Also comes out from Squeenix on the Wii
So that's a Square Enix game
And it looks a little bit like
Action kind of mixed with the whole
Anime type of cutscenes
Going on so
Looks like it could be interesting if you're a fan of those types of games
That's it for the Nintendo Wii this week
Let's take a look at the
PlayStation 2 since they're still cranking stuff out for that
And I do want to point out
Secret of Evangelion is going to be
A best hit now in Japan
As of September 25th
So will Angel Profile that will also be
Getting a price reduction
But if you're looking for some new stuff
Anyway there's quite a bit
There's Super Robot Taisen Z comes out
As well as Sugar Plus Spice
Anoko no Suteken no Name no Kamo
Comes out as well
And let's see
Soul Cradle
Well that's another best hit
How about this one though
Nojizaka
Tsunku no Himitsu
Cosplay
Hajime Mashita
That is the game coming out
And all I have to say is that
It's got a girl dressed as a maid
On the cover of it
And some of the screenshots from the game
Some of the screenshots from the game
Topless Bathing Sun Beauties
Actually inside the game
And Women in Nurse Outfits
Sweet
Oh the name of it right there
Jamie's looking at the name there
To see if she can figure out
I see Secret Cosplay
Secret Cosplay
Looks like a lot of fanboy fantasies might come true
With that game so you might want to check that out
I think it's a fetish game
Nice
It's Secret Cosplay
Coming out in Japan on the Nintendo DS
Gobble Gobble Planet
Knights in the Nightmare
Princess Maker 4
Special Edition
And a game you might know from here in the US
Guitar Hero on Tour makes his way to Japan
On the Nintendo DS this week
Also lastly
On the Sony PSP
Taking a look to see if anything
Is coming out next week
Patapon gets a price reduction
Because that game has been very popular
Princess Maker 5 portable
It is a Princess Maker week
This week you got new ones on the
PSP and a price reduction on the DS
What a week
There you have it your Japanese release dates
Alright let's get back
Into some news
After the release dates
Well in other news
Sorry
And this is actually very happy for me
Because I love
Freaking Metal Slug
Don't we all know this already right?
I heard a rumor
Well
It looks like
SNK is going to be
Doing
A high def
Version sort of like
How some of the other old school games
Have gone
So that might be cool
I just want it to still play
Like Metal Slug
I don't want it to be 3D
I want it to be 2D
With very high res pretty
Pretty pretties
Well I think that's probably what they're going to do
Because they did the same thing with King of Fighters 12
Yeah
But I think
A lot of times
This has happened with a lot of different franchises
Originally
2D that they've put to 3D
Is that if they
Try to like
Okay remember the Street Fighter EX series
Now I liked the later EX games
But they still weren't right
Or
Fogger going 3D
Yeah something was always weird about that
Yeah so I think that they would be in their best interest
To keep the 2D
Or to go the
You know what I mean by the 2.5D
They're doing
You know where it's 3D but plays 2D
I'm all for the 2.5D
Like what was it
Fantasy Zone
The Sega Ages one that I have
It still played
Just like the 2D one
It was all cel shaded
You couldn't really tell it was 3D
Except it would do rotations in some places
It gave it a little bit more depth to it
I think that they should do something
Like that
In the high res route
Well we'll see if we get more information on this soon
Let's see
Well in other news
And this is actually pretty cool
Nintendo may actually have a chance to redeem itself
They're actually holding a media summit
In early October
Supposedly on the 2nd and 3rd
This has already been confirmed for Japan
But what they're going to talk about
Who knows
But the event also
There's supposed to be a US event as well
Taking place in San Francisco around the same time
Guesses of course
Would be the announcement of Disaster Day of Crisis
Since it's already been announced
For the Japanese market
Obviously since it's coming out next week
And for Europe
Because it's coming out in October
But no word on
A US release yet
And
Other rumors or thoughts maybe
That they're going to announce that
Conduit's being published by them now
Maybe some new games or something like that
But we'll have to see
Maybe a storage solution
Who knows
I would like to hear that
That would be a wonderful announcement
We'll see
Well you know it's almost kind of like
It was a fanboy story almost going around a while back
That Microsoft
You've probably heard this before
Nintendo
What if oh yeah Microsoft's going to buy Nintendo
Especially kind of back before the Wii was announced
Used to hear these kind of rumors
Remember hearing this like oh yeah
Microsoft's going to buy Nintendo and they're going to conquer the world
Well what's kind of interesting
There actually
Was kind of a little bit of truth to that
And that was explained by Peter Moore
Who was talking in an interview this week
He actually mentioned during the interview
Balmer wanted to know
And that was an individual that he worked with at Microsoft
Wanted to know how he was going to win
For Microsoft
How we were going to take on Sony
How we would compete with or acquire Nintendo
Those were the conversations in those days
It was a classic build or buy conversation
Interestingly we were just completely fixated on Sony
Nintendo didn't even come into the conversation
Notice that way he said that though
Compete with or acquire
Nintendo
But now after the massive success of the Wii
The world may never know what would have happened
If Microsoft and Nintendo had merged
Very interesting huh
But it might also kind of give some background as to why
Microsoft is a little more willing to put some of their
Stuff out on DS like Viva Pinata
Kind of has that DS game
And they're not really competing with Nintendo on that market
They really have their heart set on Sony
Black Wolf chimes in and says
Nintendo laughed at Microsoft
They actually did have a meeting
And you know when you've got a very
Very American company and a very
Very Japanese company in that regard
It kind of doesn't surprise me
You know what I mean
So I think sometimes our perspective
Might be a little skewed being over here
What's just a ginormous company
And what power Nintendo has
But it's interesting that in some
Regards in that way they've kind of worked together
A bit
Well
Other neat things
Nintendo of course they only
Teased us very briefly
During the E3 media
Event
Grand Theft Auto Chinatown Wars now
There's a little bit more details coming out from
Nintendo Power
And the game itself is actually
Going to be a cel-shaded
Isometric game
It is still going to be M-rated
Of course it's still going to be a crime drama
They actually had some screenshots to look
It sort of resembles I guess
A little bit like the
Old Grand Theft Auto 1 and 2
Just kind of shot a little different
Kind of
Grand Theft Auto cell phone games that they had
But it looks neat
It'll be interesting to check out
They said that the
So as a Grand Theft Auto fan
You're interested
I'm interested to check it out
Some of the artwork looks kind of weird
But it'll be interesting to see how the game plays
Be definitely willing to
Check it out because it's Grand Theft Auto
And I love Grand Theft Auto
They were saying though that
It's going to be a sizable
Or the game's going to take place in a sizable
Portion of Liberty City
The map has
Been altered from of course the console version
Which only makes sense
And the missions will also be shorter and can
Easily be restarted upon failure
The D-pad is going to be used for aiming
While the R button activates in
Auto-targeting
And there's going to be a subtle
Auto-steering built into
The driving controls as well so you can
Shoe out the window and stuff like that
But they're going to bring back the over the top weapons
Like the minigun, the flamethrowers
And pretty much a lot of the stuff that was in
Like say
Grand Theft Auto 1 and 2
So it'll be pretty cool
And it's still due out this winter
Which I think January is the month
Very interesting
I want to backtrack just a little bit going to the last story
Because sometimes our chat room is a little behind
Because of the delay from when we say something to when it goes out over the radio
But kind of a comment on
The whole Microsoft Nintendo thing and how
Microsoft kind of plays nicely with the DS
Tigerclaw gives an interesting comment in our chat room
chat.orangelsonshooter.com
Microsoft is sort of getting into the handheld
Gaming market with the release of the second gen
Zune which will play
Games so that's true this new
Zune thing they got does the games
But at the same time I kind of when I first read that
I saw it more of a response to the iPhone
I'm not so much
The DS but I mean it's an interesting
Point though it's not that like
Microsoft doesn't do handheld games of any sort
But I sort of see it more as like an iPhone
Type of game in my opinion
I have a feeling that
If they were to get into the handheld market
It wouldn't be with the Zune
And if they did I don't think they'd have trouble
Passing up the PSP
The DS on the other hand
The DS on the other hand though I don't think
They'll be
Well one game that probably won't find its way
To the Zune unless they find some way to
Have a spin off would be Halo
Halo 3 specifically and Halo 3
Is going to be getting a new title update
And guess when it's coming?
Tuesday September the 23rd so maybe by the time
A lot of you guys hear this
Halo 3 update will be there it's going to be an automatic download
You may have to kind of clear out the cash
First though before the download will actually
Happen there but once you get the new updates
There's going to be a brand new ranking system
Some changes to the playlist
Some brand new achievements which will be cool
A complete overhaul to Bungie.net
Which is pretty cool and the Bungie.net
Website is slowly changing throughout the next week
So pretty cool there
And I know some of you achievement whores are very excited
About new achievements so you'll be able to check that out
This Tuesday with the free update
To Halo 3
So there you go
Well in
Other MMO news
There actually have been some more details put out
About Star Trek Online
I know that a few of us have been looking forward to this
They actually said
On the website that there are going
To be more
Details coming out soon but for right now
The ships are going to be something
Like naval combat
Using traditional MMO game
Gameplay
Klingon ships are going to be
Different
A bit more reflecting of
Their culture
Everything will be very customizable
You can modify and customize
The uniforms of the characters but they still have to look like
A uniform
So the options are going to
Be things from the show and bring in some new things
So it's supposed to be cool
And is it supposed to be out in the next three years?
That's
A long wait
That sometimes means more towards
The end of that three years so like
2011 that's going to be a long wait
Whew
I hope it's worth it
Definitely
Well other
Fun PC games of course
Spore
One of the biggest complaints about Spore
Of course is some of the DRM restrictions
Well EA has heard your pleas
And they have decided to loosen them up
A bit so now
Some of the changes that they've had
And of course without
You know of course they were
Bitching and moaning about having to do it
But they did it anyways
They expanded the number of eligible
Machines that you can install the product on
From three to five
They will offer ways for you to
Request additional activations
Where warranted
And also developing a system that
Will allow the consumer to deauthorize machines
And move authorizations to new machines
And on top of that
As well they're going to allow you to
Log in multiple characters
Into each account
So you're going to be able to have I think up to
Five different
Players
On each
Of your activations
So that's kind of cool
I wish they would get rid of secure ROM though
That's the part that's kind of weird
But you know at least they're trying to meet you halfway on this stuff
I think that's the one component that really still needs to happen
Is that whole secure ROM thing
But at the same time it's kind of like you know
If you think there's going to be no DRM in these games
Whatsoever, dream on
I mean that's just the way it's going to be
This is the day and age we live in
This is what they're going to try to do to protect their games
Although it still does kind of suck that you know
Days before the release and the legitimate users
Have to suffer
It's just like having a car alarm in your car
I mean it's not going to prevent people from
Stealing stuff out of your car
It just makes it more difficult
And it's just like you know the secure ROM stuff
And the DRM stuff, it's just going to make people
Have to try that much harder to
Crack it to be able to steal your product
And make it as hard for them as possible
Although it's not very hard
And it's not
Too much of an inconvenience
It's not at all an issue
It's not as easy as say you know
Bob down the street gets a game
And there's no DRM and just copies it
For all of his friends
Well one game that's very hard to copy
Because you have to have your own individual
Account to play online
These are the games that are hard to copy
MMOs
Unless you have the whole private server and that whole stuff
But hey, World of Warcraft obviously
Doesn't have too big a problem with piracy
Because they've got what like 7 million people playing the game
And they are all looking forward to the brand new expansion
Wrath of the Lich King
Which finally got dated this week
November 13th, 2008
If you have some war crack addicted friends
Expect them to call in sick on this day
Because they probably will be
Working on heading up to Northrend
And some of the new areas up there like the Howling Fjord
And trying to level the characters to 80
Maybe playing some Lake Wintergrasp
Running some of the new instances
Leveling Inscription
Or their new Death Knight
Millions of different things to do in the new Warcraft expansion
I'm looking forward to the dance studio
Myself
You can teach characters new dances now apparently
Which is badly needed
And also you can get your characters some haircuts
So very interesting
How you can almost
Micro manage
Even more
That's the last thing our MMO needed
More micromanaging
Well there's a new add on coming to
World of Warcraft
And it's Bejeweled
Oddly enough this game started off
As a third party knock off
Bejeweled
It was called Becharted
And the developer from Willer
Actually
Kind of made it as a method
Of killing time during long raids
And farming sessions
But apparently
PopCap caught wind of it
And instead of having them
Stop making it
They actually
Wanted him to
Or they hired him on to create a more polished
Version of the application
That will be released for the game
So you'll be able to play
Bejeweled
And my wife was excited to hear this
So now if your wife gets sucked into
Getting World of Warcraft
Yeah she's just going to be playing Bejeweled
And they're just sitting there playing Bejeweled
I know
World of Warcraft is the best game ever
Cause it has
Bejeweled in it
So no you were telling this on Bobby's show
I don't think you told it on our show though
The wife is actually signing up for a Warcraft account
Thanks to Extifer
She's trying the 14 day trial
She may actually do
A month in 14 days because
Extifer wants to get I guess you get some
Recruitment bonuses or something like that
Kind of like the military or something where you get
Like a special mounts
Or triple experience or some shit
I don't know it's retarded but
So she may
Indulge him in that but
Yeah she's going to try it
I have to install it on this laptop that I'm using
Right now cause
You're that I buy her a new laptop
She wants me to buy her a Mac and I'm like
Fuck that shit
Oh my god
I think now the wife is purposely trying to get into
Things that you don't like just to
Piss you off I don't know
I don't think she
The thing is you have to know her
She doesn't have the patience for it
And she's going to quit like very fast
I will be very surprised
If she actually
We should take bets on what level
Nellie will quit at
How far she gets her character up before she quits
I'm down with that
What would the bet be?
I don't know
Like what does the loser have to do
Or what does the loser get
Or win or get
I don't know I don't even care
DarkSakura can you think of anything
That's not too extreme like no tingle dressing up
For a bet like this
We have to poop? Well I think everybody does that
On a semi regular basis if you're not
You might want to see a doctor
Alright
We'll figure something out maybe make a bet
In part B
I just don't think she'll have the time for this game
Seriously I think she'll probably
Level to about 5 and then stop
We'll see
Alright anyhow hey
Maybe there's some other games that Loki's wife
Should be checking out because there's a classic
Gaming archive that dates
Years and years and years that have
Hundreds and hundreds and thousands and thousands of games
In it and every week
Here on this program DarkSakura selects
One of them to highlight here
On this program and we call it the classic
Video game of the week
So what should the
Kids be playing this week DarkSakura?
For lack of a better
Game I picked Snake Rattle and Roll
Because I know it's a
A game that somebody I
Think is great really likes
So um
Oh me? No
I really like it
No I put it on there for
Sauce although I think it's been a while since
She's played it but it was a game that was
Made by Rare
And it came out on the NES
In 1990 it's one of the
Earliest platform games
It was a 3D isometric playing field sort of like
How Marble Madness was
They uh
Actually it didn't really sell all that
Great but it was actually kind of a fun little game
It was really difficult too
But the whole point is that you are two snakes called
Rattle and Roll and you have to eat these little things
Called Nibley Pibleys and race to the moon
So
That's what you play. There was supposed to be a sequel
Called Snakes to Snakes but
It was never made but there was Sneaky Snakes
For Game Boy in 1991
And it had a version come out on
Sega on the uh
Mega Drive in 1993
So that's pretty cool
I never knew there was a Mega Drive version of this
It's kind of neat
Huh. Well I like this game quite a bit
It's actually a lot of fun. I'm kind of sad we never got that sequel
And this is a Rare game
So yet again here's another great
Franchise that Rare could go back and revisit
Someday on I don't know Xbox Live
Arcade but I somehow think they never will
Which is sad
It makes me cry
Alright
Well it looks like that's it. That's your classic game of the week folks
Snake, Rattle and Roll
For the Nintendo Entertainment System
But also on the Mega Drive apparently
Which I just learned tonight
Alright on that note
We're going to take a quick break and we're going to come back
With more of Orange Lounge Radio
And yes we're going to talk about Mega Man 9
We'll also talk about a new sweet code and game
And we'll talk about Project Gotham Racing 5
It's all coming up in part B
So hey don't go anywhere we'll be right back
Having a bad day
Job getting you down
Are you looking for something to pick you up
Give you a laugh all at the same time
Then oh brother do I have the show for you
I am Brad Boyer
And join me each week on The Geek Spin
As I scour the net to bring you the best
In comedy music
Check us out
www.thegeekspin.com
Ladies and gentlemen
Rape isn't funny
Unless if it's clown rape
Rape of people is not funny
Rape of monsters is funny
Because monsters are bad
And when bad people
What I'm just not going to keep going
I'm digging myself a hole
I'm Brad
I'm Glenn
And I'm Christina
And we're from the Pod Culture Podcast
And podculture.net
When you're done here and you find yourself hungry
With some more geeky goodness
Head on over and check us out
At podculture.net
From A-plus shows to Grade Z movies
And everything else in between
Like comics and video games
Along with the occasional special musical guest
There's something for the geek in us all
And head on over to our little corner of the verse
www.podculture.net
Pod Culture
Equal Opportunity Geek Month
See you soon
Welcome back
Kids to Orange Lounge Radio
Here on this lovely Sunday evening
September the 21st, 2008
Five weeks to go until episode 300
If you can believe it
Yes, we've been on the air that long
To have done 300 weekly episodes
You know, and obviously we've missed a week here and there
So, you know, it's taken us a little over six years to get here
But quite an accomplishment
I don't know many other shows, if any, that have gotten to the 300 weekly show mark
So, yeah, now we're trying to decide what exactly we're going to do to celebrate
We're going to try to get some big guests on the show that week
I know that I'm going to try to start sending some emails this week
And just have a potpourri of big names on the show that week
But otherwise I'm not sure what other surprises we have in store
But if you have suggestions please email us
Or email me directly
You can get all our contact information on the website
Anyhow, we've got lots more gaming news to discuss
And only a little bit of time to do it
So let's get back to it
During the break we heard some music from the new Mega Man 9
Unfortunately folks on the podcast don't get to hear that
Because, you know, the whole copyright and all that stuff we can't offer it up for download
But the live listeners did hear it
And I believe Loki's going to start us off with some Mega Man 9 news tonight
Yes, in fact, if you liked Mega Man 9's music
You're going to like it even more when you can actually buy the game
Which comes out on the 22nd
Or tomorrow if you're listening to us live
On the WiiWare download service
If you do not own a Wii and you own a PS3
You'll be able to purchase it on the Playstation Network on the 25th
And if you want it on the 360
Well you're going to have to wait until October 1st
But it will be available soon
And that's awesome
Another thing that will be available shortly after all that comes out
Is some download content for Mega Man 9
And the first new playable character they're going to include
Is Protoman
And you're going to actually be able to use him
Some of the stuff that you get like the rush adapters
Actually change to proto adapters in the game
And including like the proto sled, proto coil, etc
I guess it's all just kind of
I'm sorry, it's just crazy that there's download content
For like an old school Nintendo game in a way
It's just kind of cool, I don't know why
It's just really really cool
Yes, so that will be available on October 6th
For $2 or the equivalent thereof
And by the way, even though we can't play the entire Mega Man 9 soundtrack
Or so on the live show
We can play a little clip
So here's what some of the music sounds like
Here's a clip from Tornado Man's stage
So you can see it has all that same retro goodness
Of the old school Mega Man games
Like you knew it was going to have
And some other cool stuff
If you happen to be all nostalgic
And love playing Mega Man 9
Well, I don't know if you remember that fake
Well I guess old school box art they had
Going out for Mega Man 9
The really human face for Mega Man
That was scary, yeah
You now can actually purchase the fake box
A fake NES cart
And I guess it may come with the asset CD
That they were handing out before
Because these were for press release stuff
They had screenshots and all sorts of stuff
But they are available on the Capcom store
So you can find those at capcom-unity.com
And they will be exceedingly rare
So if you're interested in getting it
You might want to put an order in as soon as possible
It's kind of neat
Yeah, how much do you think those things will start going for on eBay?
Who knows? Quite a bit I'd imagine
Anyone in here planning to get that game this week?
Yes
I think we're going to
Jamie of course having a little trouble with her voice tonight
Because of the allergies
But I think she just said she
They think they're going to get it this week
I want to because I think the d-pad on the Wii is pretty awesome
Whereas the d-pad on the 360 not so awesome
However, I love achievement points
So therefore I will be getting out of that too
Yeah, I think I'm going to be holding off on the 360 version
Even though the controller bugs the crap out of me
I'm kind of hoping that's one of the things Microsoft is going to fix in 09
Based on what we saw at the Leipzig show
At least I'm hoping
We'll see
Anyhow, other games and other big franchises that people are really excited about
Suikoden!
I know we got a few Suikoden fans in the house
A brand new Suikoden game was announced for DS
It's not a numbered Suikoden game
But a new game called Suikoden Tier Crease is the new game that's coming out
And this is kind of neat
What's kind of cool about this game
Again, the big niche of the Suikoden series
You could say is that it's a classic JRPG
But you have 108 characters in it
There's just tons and tons and tons of characters
What's kind of cool about this one is that
With the Nintendo Wi-Fi connection now
You can actually play where you're leveling one of the 108 people
But somebody else can level the other characters
And you can all participate in leveling up the different characters
So it provides a new way to level up characters
And creates a little bit of a community
And apparently when they say Nintendo Wi-Fi connection
They are talking the internet
Not just a local Wi-Fi connection
So that could be very interesting
I'm kind of curious to see how this plays out
So more information to come on that
Apparently this was shown at a Konami event
That we weren't invited to this year
Sad
But I heard it was in New York
That's probably why
Yeah
It wasn't on our coast
I'm sure it was
Oh well
They couldn't fly us out there
Even though they flew everybody else out there
Oh well
Not that we're going to be bitter much
But we can't really tell you much more about the game
Because we didn't see it
Oh darn
I couldn't play Rock Revolution
Maybe have a positive
Do you think maybe that's why you didn't get invited?
Well
No I don't think so
But hey
You know what
If the game stinks we're not going to hold back at the same time
It's more important we have integrity
Than you know
I could have
But see that's the thing
I'm only taking it based off of
You know screenshots and stuff
That's not very accurate
And with you know
Out playing it
I can't really give you my true impression
But whatever
Who cares
It's not important
So anyway
Sweet Coding looks interesting though
I you know
I've missed out on some of the more recent Sweet Coding games
But I did enjoy the ones on Playstation 1
So I might have a reason to check it out
I think the online component sounds neat
So Peter Molyneux
He actually of course
Has this little game coming out called Fable 2
And you may remember
There were some games released on Xbox Live Arcade
Called the Fable 2 Pub Games
Where you can earn gold to use in the actual game
Well of course people found you know
Exploits and glitches
To be able to make a lot of money really quick
And according to Peter Molyneux
That was intentional
And that they're going to be in for a surprise
When they actually start the game
And of course now there's
You know a patch being put out that fixes that
And all that stuff
Somehow I think he's full of shit
To be honest
And I don't think it was intentional
And I think maybe if you try it with this new patch
It will do trigger something
But I think
If you're doing it and besides you can also
You know clear out your hard drive cache or whatever
And erase these updates and cheat anyways
I don't think it's going to matter
I'm kind of curious to see what happens
I do claim bullshit on the fact that it was premeditated
But I think there is some legitimacy
To the fact that something will happen in the game
If you cheat it I think they will be able to
Enable that
Because sometimes even if you buy it
Like even if the game had already like pretty much gone gold
Or whatever and there wasn't time to add in
Something to you know get the cheaters
They could patch it in
When the release happens
Because how many times have you bought a new Xbox game
And it patches day one
Well I know that
I'm not saying something about the game
I'm saying that the Xbox Live Arcade game
Is going to have to be patched
In order for it to be able to detect the cheating
Because I think that you're going to try it
And you know if you try the same technique
To cheat now
Now that they have it patched in
That it's going to raise a flag or something
That's going to cause it to you know trigger in the game
If you're that worried about it
Just flush your you know
Your Fable 2 pub games file
And flush your hard drive
Exactly just do it offline or whatever
And the patch is actually already live according to Zushi
Yes it is already live
And so I haven't actually played the pub games yet
Even though I got them
Yeah I played them for like five minutes
And honestly they're I mean especially like
One of them is just basically a fancy slot machine
Which brings nothing new to the table
The other one is kind of like a weird version of roulette
The pyramid game was interesting
But it didn't hold my attention for long enough
Honestly
I think a lot of people were just getting it to exploit the hell out of it
For when the game actually comes out
But I don't know what do you guys think in chat
Do you think it was intentional the whole time
That they intended to have an exploit in there
I mean it does definitely kind of tie into the whole good versus evil thing
Yeah but it also makes it sound like he's
He likes to sound like a smarty pants
And just you know trying to
Oh I did all this stuff
Because I think outside the box
I think greater than all this
I don't think he thought anything
I think it's just a glitch
That now they're patching in some sort of
Reprecussion if you try it
So whatever
Big freaking whoop
Well who knows if we'll get a new Fable game next year
But one game we'll probably get next year
Is a brand new James Bond game
Right Activision has said that they are planning to put out
Yearly Bond games
Even though the movies only seem to come out every other year
They're going to actually be trying to crank out
Yearly Bond titles
Of course right now the game they're trying to put out is Quantum of Solus
It's actually based on the Call of Duty 4 engine
And you know obviously the movie tie in
They've got this year
But they may do these games even if there is no movie
To go off of
They haven't mentioned what the genre will be
They haven't mentioned who's going to develop them
What systems are going to be made for
They're going to be aggressive in milking this James Bond franchise
For all it's worth
And frankly I don't really blame them
People everywhere love their James Bond
It's not surprising at all
They're going to try to milk this franchise
And let's face it you know one of the greatest video games
On the Nintendo 64 ever
Was the James Bond game
GoldenEye
That game made me so sick
But you know sometimes
I know there was a James Bond game I played
That wasn't necessarily based off a movie
But there have been a few
Not that they've been wonderful
But who knows we'll see what happens
Anyway just really quickly I wanted to go over some of the responses
Was the pub games intentional or not?
James Patrick says
Peter M. isn't a typical guy
I think it could very well be intentional
Game Guru says
They should keep the cheat in
But have it make you more evil
So that yeah you can cheat but it's an evil act
Oh interesting
So we'll see what happens
So
If you want to comment on our stories
Chat.orangelaunchradio.com
We want comments
Well this actually is good news for our European listeners
Or anybody listening or not
But we hope you're listening
Actually the Xbox 360 is getting a price cut
On the 19th of September
The 360 arcade
Is going to
129 pounds
Excuse me
The 60 gigabyte pro
Is going to 169
And the 120 gigabyte elite
Is 229 pounds
So good news
Yay cheaper things
And I'm glad you know because Europe
Sometimes gets the shaft in a lot of our news stories
So it's nice to hear them getting a break once in a while
It's just too bad they didn't get it the same time
We did but hey better late than never
Right?
There's a big old rumor coming out about
Project Gotham 5 saying now that
It's being developed by the Forza
Development team
And that there could be an announcement for it
Next week
According to a website called Addict
Gaming
They have a reliable source
That the game
Will be unveiled next week
And also mentions
That this may be
This is supposed to take place during the new
Xbox experience announcement
Scheduled for next week which a lot of people have already
Debunked as being false
There could be this like 5 hour long
Thing on G4
I mean granted I can see how they could do that
Since there's nothing really plain on G4 except
Reruns of cops and cheaters
Haven't we already had a rumor about a G4 marathon
Of something that got debunked?
This is the same thing but this is saying that
This is going to be part of that announcement
So it could all be bullshit or you know
Heaven forbid
Microsoft and G4 could have been
Lying to us and it's actually going to happen
I mean but you know
Once again we'll see you next week
You know what don't you think
I don't know if I were G4 television and I had a big
Exclusive thing that I was going to be dedicating
You know 5 hours of programming to
Don't you think I would have started advertising it like 6 weeks ago?
No because if they want to be a surprise
Then this was the agreement with Microsoft
To keep it hush hush super secret
Until the very end you know
What's the point of a surprise?
I don't know I don't know
I'm just saying it's bullshit that's all
All I'm saying there's other stuff happening
And that may be completely bullshit
But there are other things
Including I think a story that didn't make
It was in show roll but didn't make
Our show roll
About how they had
That new Halo game or whatever
Is being teased on Bungie's site
And that there's an announcement
Coming soon maybe this announcement
Could come at the same time just saying
There's kind of smoke here
That maybe they're going to announce something soon
About something so
It's still I don't believe they're going to do
A 5 hour long thing on G4 but who knows
Maybe there's something
Somewhere in the middle ground that's coming
Just saying cause you know all those Microsoft rumors
You know they always seem to come true somehow
So I don't know
Well some people are very excited about this rumor
Acteft in chat says Project Gotham Racing 5
Developed by the Forza team do want
Could be very interesting
I'm kind of I want to see
You know what I'm actually more excited about
As sad as this is
What game Blizzard
Not Blizzard
What game Bazaar is developing
With Blizzard, Activision
You know that whole thing
I'm curious what the new thing is they're making
And I'm hoping you know I'm not as into the Project Gotham
And Forza games as much as I am
The more simple racing games so to speak
You know I'm not like super into cars
But I like the more need for speed burnout type games
But I love
Dumb simple like dumb dumb dumb
Simple racing games like F-Zero and Mario Kart
And I would love it if they would make
A next gen like dumb racing game
That's like F-Zero
I really want like a next gen F-Zero game
Can't you tell how many times have I said it on the show
I wish that would be what
They'd announce at Nintendo's press events
Coming up, wouldn't that be nice
Well meanwhile there are other games you can play
One of them is Grid
It's a game I didn't particularly care for it
But hey I do like I do support when games
Further extend the life
With some extra content and Grid is going to be
Extending its life with some new cars
And some new events
And some new download content that's coming out
It's called the 8 Ball Pack
It's supposed to be coming out this fall
There's going to be two brand new multiplayer things
And eight new cars, hence the name of the 8 Ball Pack
A McLaren F1 GTR
A Honda S2000
A 1971 Pontiac Firebird Trans Am
Are some of the new things you can look for
The expansion will be released for the Xbox 360
And Playstation 3
It's going to also bring some new achievements
Four new achievements, 100 gamer score
Of course on the Playstation 3 that would be trophies
So there's also going to be some new multiplayer events as well
It's pretty cool
Not quite specific on what the price is going to be for this
Or what the exact release date is
But just plan on it soon
As in this fall
If you're a Grid player
Well something else that's coming soon
Is the Playstation firmware 2.5
That's going to be likely later October
And supposedly simultaneously with that
It will be the release of Home 1.0
So finally the beta will be over
And you'll actually be able to participate in it
And it says they're waiting for a system software update
To the PS3 to deal with this
I guess some sporadic network issues
That they have with Home right now
And then they're going to
Reopen it sometime
I guess this week for thousands of new testers
But in October is when they're supposed to bite the bullet
And actually launch this thing that they've been teasing for a long time now
Wouldn't it be funny if they just came out in October and go
Yeah it's coming out spring of 2009
I'd laugh
Haven't they guaranteed that it's coming out this year?
It doesn't matter. They guaranteed that the Playstation 3 was coming out in the spring
And ended up getting delayed through the fall
So nothing's guaranteed
Fair enough
Are you looking forward to trying out Home?
No I don't really care
You don't really care?
I'll test it out
I'm excited about Home. I'll have PS3
I honestly don't think it's going to be that great
I think it's just going to be kind of eh
Look at what we can do. We're different
I mean great. It's a way to differentiate themselves
We'll see how they actually use it
Alright
Well hey, you know what's kind of funny we're talking about
We're just joking around in chat right now
And people were talking about racing games
And AlphaCananagram said there is a next gen racing game
It's called Crazy Woman Driver
Also known as Excite Truck
And I was kind of like, they should make a game called Crazy Woman Driver
But it should be like, not really
I'm not trying to say that with malice
Obviously I don't think all women are crazy drivers
But I think there should be a game based around
Crazy Women Driving
So then we get the sequel Small Penis Trucking
Sure
Sure fine by me
We can have Small Penis Trucking
Fair enough. Fair is fair
We can have both
Or how about this
Great Big Rims
Itty Bitty Penis
That could be a sequel
Would that work for you? I don't know
Anyhow
The reason why I'm saying that is
I'm tying this into a story about
The Power
Because the Tyra Banks show
This is a show that airs during the day
And actually I have to admit
I kind of like the Tyra Banks show
Because in one of those cheesy
Over the top type of ways
Tyra Banks is a very cheesy over the top host
Well do you remember the Wii Fit Girl?
I mean how can you forget her right?
She was the one on YouTube
That her boyfriend taped her
Doing the whole hula hooping thing
Obviously showing off her assets
And it was very controversial
Well Tyra Banks had that couple on the show
And apparently
Tyra
Helped this girl kind of get
Her revenge on the guy
And the guy was actually
The boyfriend was on the show playing
And
He actually had to take
His pants off
And play Wii Fit
In his undies to be a delight of the audience
And that was actually the
Audience clapping along there
And apparently that was done during a commercial break
Or something and released as a viral video
And in
Retrospect it's kind of stupid I mean this story
Is like how old like two months old
Listen Tyra Banks is trying to be
Edgy and trying to be all like
She's edgy like 90 days late
The only
Time I ever hear about the Tyra Banks show is when I'm
Watching the soup because they make fun
Of her because she's retarded
And I don't know
But she also was she did something
Way back with like World of Warcraft
Where they destroyed some dudes CDs
Or something like that
Yeah you installed the game you dipshit
You know I actually walked by at work
And I saw that Tyra
Was on because they have a TV at work and you know
They have different channels on during the day and I saw that the Tyra Banks
Show was on and I actually
Kind of looked up and I noticed they were showing
The YouTube of the Wii Fit girl
She was getting ready to introduce her and I was kind of looking
At it going this must be a rerun
This is like 90 days old
No it wasn't it was
It was a brand new episode
Too little too late
Too little too late so you know
Late stories I don't know about you
Guys but they make me a little bit angsty
So this is when we get into the FUs of the week
My FU of the week was towards
My sinuses my allergies
My lungs and lots and lots of mucus
I miss having a voice
I miss having to eat or drink something hot
Just to be perfectly audible
And um Rob
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
That's the only cool part of it
Old joke is old
Alright Loki
Um I guess
My FU of the week goes to the fact
That I have to wake up early tomorrow
Because I have to take my wife's car in
Apparently she was driving down the street
Or whatever um doing 50
year or something and then the car like all sudden stopped accelerating and the
check engine light came on then it started accelerating again so that's
usually not a good thing so yeah I hate waking up really um my a few of the week
goes to something I've been spending a lot of time on lately and my a few of
the week goes to Proposition 8 I don't usually get very politically motivated
on the show but amen seeing as this is something that directly affects my
rights and you know we've done this show for free for how long pardon me while I
get on my soapbox for a minute if you live in California even if you don't
live in California please tell people that you know that live in California to
vote no on Proposition 8 and Proposition 8 is basically an initiative on the
ballot that's looking to ban same-sex marriage which is already legal in
California thanks just a court decision a few months ago and I believe in
equality and fairness for all and you know despite however a person might feel
about gay marriage personally it's not gonna hurt you if two guys or two women
get married and you know go on with their lives and raise a family and I
think it's just I think the whole thing is so stupid and I can't believe that
people pour millions and millions of dollars into what I basically see as in
this opinion hate when I see people donating money to this yes on a campaign
I see hate because that's what it is a discrimination of the 21st century and
it stinks ignorance it's just ignorance it's ignorant I mean I know I know I
could go on for days no no I fully agree with you it's absolutely disgusting I
mean honestly I would love to see marriage made illegal to begin with no
no no I understand be strictly reduced to a religious institution separation of
church and state have that wall that you know Jefferson intended when he wrote
the damn phrase right now and have the government should anyone would think
that the government wouldn't love for there to be more married people it's it's
good for the economy tax taxes and think of other wedding money that goes in the
economy but anyway anyway look I could go on for days and days it's a video
game show I don't want to but you know just please you know this is gonna set a
precedent for the nation here and you know it's very very important that we
defeat proposition 8 on the ballot it just it pisses me off that they lie they
freaking lie when they call people they say that if this proposition is defeated
the churches are going to be forced to marry that Mormon churches the church
that don't want to do are going to be forced to marry that is not true it's
straight-up not true look like the Catholic Church actually they're very
strict they can and can't marry because they have both have to be Catholic as
far as I'm aware and all this other stuff is no you're absolutely right I
think it's stupid and ridiculous and those should dedicate a podcast just to
it oh god oh I could just go on for days and days days anyway you know what for
those folks to think that you know gay marriage is gonna ruin the sanctity of
marriage I've got three words for you Britney fucking Spears all right back to
video games hug hug kiss kiss I love everybody I really all right Britney
fucking Spears that's awesome you know what what that's another pocket we need
to do a political podcast someday you know I actually actually and I will go
ahead and say this on the air you know cuz you know me I'm very opinionated
about my ideas you know Rob I'm just messing but maybe maybe we should do
some type of a new sub podcast a political can we should do something
called I don't know if Loki's down with it I just like to pissed off nerds I
should call the show to pissed off huh I joined the ECA yeah there you get lots
of information from them why not maybe you know it's about time people put
their foot down and said screw you guys I'm going belly know what I'm pissed off
that podcast is limiting my bandwidth to 250 gigabytes a month you know what that
is something else to get pissed off that's a different political thing but
yeah that is angry I like that idea to pissed off nerds we'll see if there's
already a pot there's got to be I'm sure there's one called angry that's 62,500
songs at four megabytes per song that that's basically our 125 standard
definition movies well you know what I download that much actually I don't but
I do monitor my downloading now gs68 says pissed off nerds wouldn't that be
under sedation life that's a good point they might already have a corner on that
mark they also have an angry video game nerd who's kind of retarded he's awesome
that's different though because that's actually about video games awesome any
place he plays the games and talk shit about them and they usually are shitty
games I'm I don't know what I'm not gonna say my show Nintendo nerd didn't
begin the angry video game I'm a fan of independent productions we'll just leave
it up but let's do it well so we'll look into it when two twin powers activate
will love a bucket explore the possibilities all right video games hey
damn it guess what's coming out a virtual console overseas they're getting
the master system Sonic the Hedgehog isn't that pretty cool and then some
Commodore 64 games Rob Boulder dash do Boulder dash is awesome and guess what
there was like a million of those Boulder dash games I know what else
jump man cool jump man I'd love jump man why are we getting these over here I
played jump man standards I think they had it over here our jump man jump man
generous no I don't I know we had those I had jump man junior was the first game
I ever owned on my Commodore 64 well jump man if I'm if I'm right this is the
jump man that led to us getting Donkey Kong wasn't in a way yeah I mean it's
very similar the way they were laid out but the first hero in Donkey Kong was
called jump man before he became Mario remember yeah but it's not I mean the
games aren't related but I mean the but well they're they're not related in
design but they're related in the fact that they kind of are similar with the
ladders checks and ladders type of gameplay I always thought that they were
related but oh well I just beat me no different design companies one was
Japanese one was American yeah um this one says it was a pixie they did um
mousetrap didn't they uh yeah they did mouse trap I love that they did but I
thought epics did jump but then they did jump in junior um it is epic someone was
reading it wrong yeah dead epics did like summer games and winter games it had
a lot of great great games on clique of vision that's what I played it on is the
clique of vision yeah I got to play a little bit here of just some of this
stuff from jump man jr.
I know it's jumping jr. not jump man but it's the same same same freaking thing
I remember setting it up to go really fast funny yeah you could set your speed
in this game that was the amazing thing about it is that like you could have the
speed be so freaky fast it was like unreal
so where's some actual gameplay noise I love that game oh this game was so
amazing sorry we're living in a little dot oh yes you have to avoid that killer
dot anyway sorry okay we're done reminiscing uh me too I don't know that
was it that was a good virtual console update well it's not fair that they get
it there we don't get it I know even though I'm on my little boy I might
break my boycott for jump man honestly that's awesome I think that we will
though you know I think the tiger class said what the fuck is that sound it
sounds like someone jacking off at warp speed it was the sound of him running
you have to see that go go YouTube jump man jr. you'll see it funny or what's
faster it is it's super slow too you can choose the pace that you want to jack
off at a medium pace yeah anyhow oh yes we can only make that you know
transition from virtual console the porn anyways so from jacking off to
PlayStation 3 news yeah exactly Oh Sony how you make the funnies I seriously
wonder if they're trying this on purpose now but apparently the Sony PlayStation
3 just launched into the Malaysia region and during their little party that they
were you know talking about you know how great Sony is and stuff like that they
were introducing different speakers and stuff including one of which is now a
pseudo the managing director of Sony Malaysia and he was taken to the stage
with a very familiar not Sony related video game theme and it's absolutely
hilarious because they were playing the Legend of Zelda theme for him walking up
to the stage wow how did they not catch that I don't know but of course someone
just get the wrong CD in the mixer maybe that's a really wrong CD wrong platform
only that's something you shouldn't have even been in the building right exactly
so that was kind of funny they have the video on YouTube you know definitely
check it out because it's pretty funny so that is it and of course Kotaku ran
the story the or one of the stories is that even the Imperial March would have
been a better choice all right well every week on this program we like to
give you a chance to give us some feedback not just through the chat room
at chat.org.com or the phone calls which we'll get to later but through our mail
bag and every week you guys send us emails and we pick a few of them to read
on the show or in tonight's case we're probably gonna read a lot of them on the
show tonight actually it's a statement we call the OLR mailbag
wrong thing I know but I felt like singing anyway by the way I know I still
do that when I hear it I still hear it in my head. You've ruined me Rob, you've ruined me.
usually dark soccer reads the emails but as you know she's a little bit under the
weather tonight thanks to stuff in the air so I will be taking over since my
voice seems to be in good shape even though I was shouting most of the day
gay or straight no on eight anyway moving on we're gonna start off with an
email from Robway it's Rob with two B's I just got infinite undiscovery I noticed
the action RPG fights a lot like say Kingdom Hearts could this be an initial
run with a new RPG engine any thoughts hmm interesting theory but would Kingdom
Hearts be on the 360 I don't think so an infinite of discovery I think is a 360
exclusive but it would be a killer exclusive but I think most people have
kind of already chalked up the fact that in the rumors are saying the Kingdom
Hearts is gonna be on the 360 but if you remember they don't be on PlayStation
3 if you remember they develop all their games on PC so it wouldn't matter
anyway true so you know yeah absolutely it could be a cross-platform thing but
just something to think about by the way he also wants to add a PS if you haven't
yet played the game early on in the game is a village called new land this is
spoiler free don't worry in order to ensure you don't have to restart the
game save the game as soon as you find the save point do not overwrite that
save until you have completed the task they're a tip from Rob with two B's that
might save some of you guys some headaches we have another question here
this individual did not sign their email but I think it's spasnator because I see
it in the email address even though I'm not gonna give the whole email address
but we'll just say that hi folks I have some questions for you again I hope you
don't mind that most of them are of a semi quasi political in nature hey no
that's okay we're kind of on a political tangent tonight one given that we're
experiencing all this economic turmoil do you see this affecting the video game
industry in any way shape or form what do you guys think with the reset with
the current economy situation affect the video game industry well it's a lot of
banks that are going poor so it's not like I mean people really aren't seeing
a lot of people becoming poor because of the situation that's going on right now
unless I guess you're you own a bank and in which case you probably before but no
I don't think it's gonna affect anything if this continues on for a few years or
something like that then yeah it's gonna be bad and probably people will be more
conservative with their game spending so they won't buy as much in my opinion and
this is only the dumbest answer in some ways yes in some ways no yes because
people have less disposable income and video games are funded by disposable
income but no because video games are a global market not just made for the US
so I don't think they're necessarily gonna stop developing games because they
still sell in Japan they still sell in Europe and other countries and it might
not be experiencing the same thing we're experiencing so something to think about
number two with the election coming up not too long from now and given the fact
that both Obama and McCain are in a virtual tie currently in polls do you
think either one of them will reach out to gamers seeing as a good chunk of the
population or gamers most of which are old enough to vote honestly you want my
honest answer no because unfortunately there's still that stigma in the the
place out there and I'm not reading from the email this is my off the top of my
head I say no because there's still a big negative aura that goes with video
games thanks to people like Jack Voldemort and people that you know video
games are bad and bloody and violent and you know it's that old mentality that
Dungeons & Dragons makes people kill people in real life unfortunately that's
still around so unfortunately I don't think you're ever gonna see Obama McCain
siding with the gamers in that respect because I think it would for them sadly
would do more harm than good and it's sad don't get me wrong but that's why
it's important that gamers you know that's why things like ECA and so on are
important because gamers get a voice then gamers get their political clout
known etc etc this one isn't so much a question back to the email as it is a
random idea or thought I had and would like to have you guys be my sounding
board do you think it may be a decent idea if sometime down the road there was
a political post either on a volunteer basis or salaried that had two functions
advise the president on all things video game entertainment related and also did
some public education on video games basically dispelling myths
misconceptions stereotypes and anything Jack douchebag says about video games I
was thinking that if something like this was in place perhaps things will
eventually simmer down something like it is in place it's called the ECA it's
just not officially government sanctioned but that's you know you're on
the right track with what you're thinking about but again for the same
reasons I stated before you're not going to see the government just start to
embrace video games like that you know what I mean but I think what you're
talking about that's the type of thing that the ECA is looking to bring
awareness to so check it out if you haven't already because I think they're
looking for politically minded people like you agree disagree I think so all
right that was and I think so all right moving on to the next email this is from
I am a B hi olr I was wondering if you guys are still going to do pyramid head
rape appreciation day and if so when is it anyways keep up the great work and I
hope to see you guys in future cons you know I'm afraid we may have missed it I
forgot completely about it we haven't missed the other game hasn't come out
yet it's moved so I thought it was supposed to be the day after Silent Hill
2's release no I think we were doing this just to make it easy the release of
Silent Hill homecoming doesn't homecoming come out in like two weeks
yeah it's on the 30th see I always thought oh it's it's almost around that
same time anyway because September 25th so that would be like in four days what
is it yeah it's like the day no I'm sorry September 24th the Wednesday so
her 24th was the day that it was originally released on the PlayStation
2 in 2001 I just I don't know if it would be yeah just do it on the 30th it
makes it easy or for Halloween you know I don't think we have any officially run
events this year but I think what you should do you should if it's go see
the hard thing is I don't want to say run out by Silent Hill homecoming
because I don't know it might suck so what you should do is play a Silent Hill
game yeah play a Silent Hill game like Silent Hill 2 that's really good and
then wait for our review I'm after the game comes out and if it's good you'll
buy that too and that's how you can praise pyramid head but if you do want
to take little pictures of pyramid heads and send them in to us or creative
pyramid head usage in public then I would love to run them on the front page
of our site I think that would be fun so maybe just kind of like a general end of
September time frame I don't know about having a rape appreciation day people
would like that too much but the only rape of monsters remember not rape of
humans all right let's go on to another email that comes from see it's not
signed oh yes it is geek boy 2424 woohoo I finally got an Xbox 360 OMG it is so
awesome you can't even imagine the happy vibes coming off me right now anyway what
are you guys gamer tags I'll add you on live if you have any space on your
friends list my gamer tag is geek boy 2424 see you guys on live this email is
brought to you by me home of the endless amounts of happiness check out the
forums and the oil army thread there's a whole thread where we're exchanging
gamer tags sadly my friends list is full but if you send me a really nice message
I'll usually try to find somebody on there who hasn't signed in xbox live in
like 30 days and delete them to make room for new listeners or just somebody
who I've never exchanged a message with or anything so yeah send me a message if
you want but instead of giving you the gamer tags out over the air we're gonna
make it work for it so I head on over the forums and check that out or listen
to a previous episode where we did give give it out I think there was one other
email I wanted to read here and we're not gonna be able to get to all the
emails this week but I think we'll read this one and this will be the last one
tonight and it comes to us from Dan shadow hey guys Dan shadow here hope you
all had a great talk like a pirate day this last Friday I had my fair share of
grog I can tell you that hmm talk like a pirate day did you guys do anything to
celebrate I said our once I didn't are like a pirate you acted like one though
yeah I think I posted on my Twitter hey zero day leet where's coming to my site
check it out dudes that was my talk like a pirate thing some some things have
been on my mind lately it seems the only way developers can move forward is to
move laterally we have been seeing games adopt aspects of other genres to fix
some of their problems this has been incredibly popular so far look at look
Grand Theft Auto for instance when this game was went 3d all they did was to
take a crappy driving game with a crappy shooter put you in the big world to play
in it seems to me that if there's an abundance of things to do people will
overlook the quality of the gameplay retort not necessarily I think the
driving is good in it and it's not really a crappy game now however they're
crappy minigames that they threw in there like crappy bowling crappy darts
and crappy billiards yes that does suck and that does feel very tacked on and
this crappy but the game itself fun do you think that it's a so you don't think
it's a crappy shooter and crapping driving game kind of no not all I think
they I mean having played some of the other multiplayer Grand Theft Auto games
which were only on PSP unfortunately they fixed a lot of things there's a lot
of things they haven't fixed but you know they each have their own little
nuances my problem with Grand Theft Auto is now that I've finished the game
unless I play multiplayer there's not much for me to do in it it's not really
fun anymore there's not a lot of I don't know fun things to do in it I
guess I have more to this email from Dan shadow I just wonder if the developers
are having problems with moving a genre forward without having to distract the
gamer with aspects of more popular games this work so far but I don't want to see
RPG elements in every single game nor do I want to have a driver in my RPG on the
surface you'll see big-time shooters that are hardcore on the surface once
you go online you're riddled with customization experience points and
guild systems where do you think the genres are going do you think there's
room for more than one great single genre game each year yes but you know
what the problem is I think and thanks for your mouth I think a big prior the
problem is that because of the way like Christmas is a lot of games get
overlooked because they all come out between September to December I think
more great games we get recognized if they would learn how to evenly space
them out throughout the years starting to get that I I think a little bit yes
but my god I feel overwhelmed right now with all the games I want to play I mean
really the other thing too also is that I mean what they're trying to do is
attract more people to their game and the problem is if they keep putting out
the same game and not trying to incorporate these little elements that
maybe will attract an RPG player or maybe we'll attract someone who's really
into bowling or something that's really what they're trying to do to get they're
kind of trying to branch out a little bit I think the real problem comes down
to these companies but not games that aren't finished or aren't working
correctly or haven't been properly bug tested or anything I mean seriously
mercenaries to what the fuck that game is not done there is no way that they
can say oh yeah we've ironed out all the bugs in that one no they did not in fact
they probably will just look at it figure out what's wrong with it and then
later on they can go patch it because it made better business sense for them at
the time to release it when they did because there wasn't a lot coming out
around then and they figure they're gonna get a lot more sales that way at
the same time people say their game is shit interesting comment from Xenocore
in our chat room the problem is the same reason we all have these big-budget games
too many suits in the industry I'm kind of curious to see what XNA is gonna do
to all this you know you know I keep talking about I really think this is
gonna be a big freaking deal and I know I make a big deal about it on the show
but come on I mean it is a distribution platform for independent games to really
get noticed I'm very curious to see what this does to gaming if anything I could
be wrong it could have the impact of just a little pebble I think if they do
anything right they could be a big volcano too and I hate to say this like
the Apple App Store where a lot of people putting stuff on there and it
spreads like wildfire really quick and that's part of the reason why sorry
Logie but the iPhone is murdering is because you don't see that type of in
enabling on other phones that are out there like the instinct and all those
other things you know I'm and I'm sure some angry emailer who's anti Apple and
pro sprint or whatever's gonna email me telling me about things I'm not
considering but whatever Apple's doing a great job marketing their marketplace
and getting it out there that you know any idiot can make these applications
that you know some of them are very exciting like you know the whole built
in Twitter and you know just everything they've got it's great so that's part of
why the iPhones kicking a lot of button why everybody really wants one well not
everybody but a lot of people all right that was it for mailbag hey why don't
you send us an email for consideration to be read up next week mailbag at
orange laundry calm very sorry to those emails we didn't get to this week just
realized we didn't run out of time but we did read them all and we lulled at
your improper grammar just kidding but we also praised you when you had good
grammar let's get back some gaming news Loki yes well the big trend now is to
release movies based on games release talk about it so of course the next game
that they're talking about making a movie for would be Mass Effect and
apparently AV Arad I guess the guy behind a bunch of good comic book movie
franchises is has been rumored to be or to have optioned the game for movie so
we'll have to see if this actually ends up happening because you know like other
games like Halo it doesn't end up coming out so yeah I think great let's see if
there's a good quality movie made here but unfortunately so far track record
hasn't been too favorable I am I do have a little bit of I guess moderately high
hopes for Max Payne because that looks kind of cool and hit man I guess wasn't
that bad but I didn't see it so I can't really judge was not good well if one
movie wasn't enough there's another movie coming out is coming out in Germany
why Germany because that's right the man who brought you postal among with other
great cinematic fair label has made a new movie it's called far cry yippie
skippy and it's getting its German premiere on October 2nd so expect the
first reviews to hit the internet around them I call it a far cry from good now
now you can't hate it until you've seen it no I can hate it because it's doable
or available and yes his track record speaks for himself I'm sorry I'm waiting
for the fluke to happen where all sudden it's just cinematic you know mastery but
it's not it's really not going to be good by the way I'm Tiger Claw reminds
me of something I read on the internet this week he says oh speaking of label
he's also coming out with his own video games you hear about that yeah tunnel
rats when we interviewed him he actually talked about that a little bit I think
it's supposed to come out like next year and they had a trailer for the game which
looks okay I guess it looked kind of boring but the graphics were all right
because if ruining one entertainment genre wasn't enough or Zach deft calls
him way balls he really just he needs to find his niche that he's good at
obviously games aren't it and he just really wants to use games because it's
an excuse about meditating far away from here what's his name talking well he
just wants to make genre films but it's like kind of like oh I just want to play
around with making movies you know he's not even really that serious about it
frisbee suggests in chat room the wonderfully mature name of boob way balls
why not we give new people we give people new names on this show all the
time maybe we should officially call him boo boy balls you know what what why do
we give him press I don't know because sometimes you can't help it's like a
train wreck you know you don't want to look but you can't help but turn your
head and go because I wonder how bad it is because we have to warn people
because there are some people that are like ooh Far Cry Far Cry video game
movie you know sadly enough the thing is you know obviously we can't reach a lot
of people but the people that listen to us can reach their friends and their
friends will reach their friends and eventually more these movies will make
it less into the theaters more direct-to-video and less people will buy
them because unfortunately these sell like crazy on DVD and I don't know why
because people apparently are stupid well people like their bad movie
collection it's MST 3k syndrome right exactly it is I'm actually wanting to
know if the any of those riff tracks have been done to a new a bowl film
because I bet that would be funny anyway awesome moving on um for people who are
Sega fans like myself there are actually going to be a new game coming out it's
Harley Davidson king of the road and you know they did Harley Davidson in LA
writers not too long ago well like ten years ago but now they're going to have
it on a full-size Harley on a 62 inch screen and it's gonna have a very 70s
rock soundtrack with Deep Purple and Steppin Wolf and it's on display it was
on display the Tokyo amusement show so I want awesome
very cool uh Harley games that could be kind of awesome it could also be kind of
bad but hopefully not yeah I was gonna say there was another arcade game that
was supposed to be coming out that didn't make our show roll but uh
elevator action was getting a new arcade game with an actual elevator door on the
arcade cabinet nice and it's now a shooter game which is interesting so
kind of cool anyways another thing that's getting changed a little bit is
Animal Crossing for the Wii the name is actually changed a little bit in
Australia for some reason apparently city folk is not welcome in Australia
but let's go to the city is so Animal Crossing shall now be known as Animal
Crossing let's go to the city in Australia make it so why I don't know
that's the question of the day like is is I gotta know Australian folks is is
fault did I just insult you by saying folk I mean that's what I want to know
that's I'm very very curious about what is it so in insulting about city folk
folk you rub I don't think that's it I don't know the other thing I was gonna
say well I mean they've done this in the past with other games I mean another
perfect example would be in the Asian region Africa is no longer known as
Africa it's known as a kuna matata kuna matata I love it do we talk about that
last week yes we did Oh God that's a great now see if they'd called the game
that originally I would be all over that you know what I mean we wouldn't I was a
game coming I'll call her kuna matata how wondering if they don't do that
because Disney would be like you're sued yeah Disney will sue Xenocore says it's
now known as Jumbo Safari that's why they're gonna sell more copies of it I
wish I wish alright well one more story for you guys then we're gonna open up
our skype line and you can call us at orange lounge radio on skype or our
phone number one eight seven seven game olr and this is a story about EA
Microsoft and GameStop what did these three companies have in common well they
were recently awarded perfect scores for the treatment of gay lesbian bisexual
and transgender employees and that's by the Human Rights Campaign Foundation and
it's all in the 2009 corporate equity index here's a comment on this from game
politics comm a comment from the president of the HRC Foundation Joel
soul Moness the 2009 corporate equality index shows that corporate America
understands that a diverse workforce is critical to remaining successful and
competitive in the absence of a federal law that prohibits workplace
discrimination based on sexual orientation and gender identity or
expression it is up to employers to take the lead and implement policies that
ensure all of their employees are protected game related companies which
also receive perfect scores include retailers Best Buy and Target PC Dell HP
Intel eBay Google Yahoo and Apple so nice very nice you know it's it's kind
of sad but you know you might be thinking well why is this news because
sadly there are some companies out there where it's okay to discriminate based on
that stuff and it's time to get out of your cave and really to be honest it's
GameStop they just treat everyone like shit so but at least at least it's fair
everybody is treated everybody is treated like shit so at least it's it's
non-discriminatory that's the important thing and I'm fine with that as long as
everybody's treated like shit all right anyway we're gonna treat you like shit
now when you call us at Orson's radio on Skype or our phone number one eight
seven seven game olr just kidding we won't treat you like shit unless you
deserve it meanwhile while we wait for some calls you have any last-minute
stories Loki yes I do have a few some stuff that I didn't make our show roll
this week apparently there was a ISO loader being in development for the
homebrew community much to the dislike of the homebrew community and the
developer when it cocoa apparently it got leaked out which is not good and now
the developer said you didn't get the full version then so fuck you all
yikes alright let's go to the phone real quick we'll come back to the story how
you're on orange on radio is this you know what up guys it's in a corporate
quest
hey Zina core from ultimate quest what is on your mind my friend a few things
first of all ducked a new Knight Rider for public safety type thing you know
that get that get that get that did that premiere tonight or something
no but I caught it on Hulu and that's it's like how many sharks can you jump
in one show my god record or something it doesn't know how to do the show no
hassle Hoff equals instant fail I mean it doesn't take a genius to recognize
that the only cool thing I liked in there was even though I dislike the
whole mission support type thing going on the one Asian chick in there that
speaks my languages that's always throwing off one-liners is hilarious but
other than that that shows garbage potential for a good video game out of
the new Knight Rider series hell no too many effects they put ground effects on
kit for crying out loud he jumped over guys and there's shit glowing on the
bottom that said kr it's like what this thing run through the hood hood or
something get some rims like I missed spinning like good lord how much crap
can you bolt on him I mean and he transformed into an f-150 of all things
my god I got so much hate for the show all right well look I know you didn't
call in just to bash on Knight Rider what what's going on here what what
actually what from what I've seen of the new Knight Rider show I thought the
little of you know TV movie that they did that kind of like pilot the thing I
thought it was pretty good I mean I don't know all right look I did have
hope until I saw episode one okay like no spirit unless the hoffs involved I'm
not watching it anywhere but anyway I don't even talk just about Knight Rider
what's on the gaming world all right Rob have you played Warhammer online yet I
have I I don't know I think you came into the show late tonight but I talked
about during my gaming week in part a hmm yeah I kind of missed that I was
busy with some stuff no that's right yeah I'm like so far man what do you
what do you do you like it now here's my thing I had some likes I had some
dislikes I liked some of the new things that Warhammer brought to the table
especially in the PvP area like I really liked some of the RVR combat that I
played I thought some of the scenarios are pretty awesome and I like the idea
of the public questing but I thought the interface was very clunky I don't know
if it's just me I found the interface to be like really clunky especially
compared to some more fluid interfaces that I've used well the interface for me
I actually was able to manage all the information well I mean maybe it's
because I'm used to looking at cluttered screens but I saw everything I needed to
see in there I don't need to pull up at this it's like if they would have buried
it into like a window that you have to pull up nobody would really want to use
it I just want to just put everything up there just make the colors bright enough
so where you can still see the stuff even though it's just like one or two
pixels wide and it worked and you can still see a lot of the game and have all
the information that you need plus a lot of this stuff for the interface that
they include on the back end like highlighting quest areas and everything
else I thought was kind of brilliant so yeah that's kind of a nice plus is that
yeah it actually kind of shows you where to go for quests which you know you
might be thinking well it's helping you cheat on the game but you know what god
people do that with Wow all the time you know they're just looking up online how
to beat the quest so you know why not build it into the game a little bit it's
not like people aren't going to tell you specifically where to go or show you on
your app you know it works in the roleplay sense yeah but orcs are finally
done right this is the way orcs are supposed to be people blizzard stole it
from from games workshop this is the way they're supposed to be oh you know the
cut yes it fungus though you must be a chaos player oh yeah I am I just I tried
the the human side was like this is boring I do this and wow let me switch
over to the other one and you know like all the all the dark elves listen the
metal they refused to dance it's like that's the way it should be it's not
evil I've been playing a high elf it's been kind of fun because I feel like I'm
going around judging everyone it's fun yeah yeah I loved it every time I click
on slash dance like so-and-so refuses to dance it's like I should be right there
are you suggesting that your night elf is judge dread no she's more of a judge
Hershey actually but you know whatever isn't that the one on divorce court no
there's a judge Hershey in judge dreads just a female one oh god okay I'm
thinking okay I'm thinking a TV show I noticed a female once but whatever so so
you're like in Warhammer online for somebody that's never played an MMO
before in their life let's say they're just turned off by the whole MMO idea is
there anything for them in Warhammer that might change your mind well this is
a good gateway drug for a while like experience definitely especially with
the public quests you get to see what a large-scale battle would be like without
having to worry about getting ganked in the back and all this other stuff by
other players so that's the good entry entry level once they include the like
like a free trial or something for people to get in they don't be kind of
good that's a really good way of explaining is you know core I think it's
the best way you kind of explain it is like you're getting to sample what end
game is like at level five that's what's kind of awesome and also when you go
around versus realm like if you actually go into like the the closed like a was
it they captured a flag and stuff like that they they took a note from City of
Heroes and sidekick you up to those appropriate levels so that way you can
actually do something at level one if you wanted to that is so I brought up
the same point I thought it was great too I thought it was great yeah but
that's all I had guys so all right I appreciate it we appreciate your phone
call and appreciate the review on Warhammer online because you know
unfortunately not a lot of folks it sounds like I've checked it out yet real
quick plug for your show then we'll take another call Oh ultimate quest every
Thursday after video game outsiders give us a listen and give us some feedback
we need lots of feedback what topics on the show this week more Warhammer this
week are kind of on hiatus mainly due to real-life issues but we plan on doing
another show next week and hopefully I have some new content for you by that so
also tell your listeners we need more banners on the olr PSP all games radio
players we need an ultimate quest banner exactly I'll make it happen you guys
have a really good guess what he's done with this thesis I'll flog him and get
him right on it all right sounds good take yours in the morning later he's got
a great radio voice too so you know that you know that show is gonna be fun
because you can hear him calling in ours you can just tell like this you know
there's like certain people to call in this show they have a really good radio
voices like a there's Bobby one Rob D Bobby's got a great radio voice Bobby
has a wonderful radio voice stop being mean you're just mad because he sensors
you on his show I don't all right here and he and he wouldn't he wouldn't be
your friend on a PlayStation Network or something I'm just kidding all right
more calls 877 game olr our username on Skype orange lounge radio was there any
more to the mod story you were talking about uh no just not gonna finish it now
fine be that way I do have something real quick and this is awesome what show
or I should say what game had a show that was on PBS with a doo-wop group
there's now gonna be on the DS that would be where in the world is Carmen
San Diego coming to the yes does it have the doo-wop group no it does not have to
walk right if I find it but it's an adventure game with learning curve it's
got a you know a high-standing 3d graphics I've never heard that
description before but uh coming some time soon I don't know where ladies and
gentlemen I give you I want this fucking song in rock band yes I realize there's
no guitar drums I don't give a shit not just the show but the game itself was
actually she also had a cool cartoon series yes that that's the best theme
song to any game show ever love it we're not our phones not really ringing
tonight I guess we're very we have a very apathetic crowd and I at least one
more call I mean no offense to Xenocore but I don't want him to be the only one
that's on the show tonight apparently we are going to be harder to mod now that
they are being in case some of their drive I season are being encased epoxy
so you actually have to dissolve that ship freakin mod it or you can use one
of the contacts on the bottom of the board so it's not impossible but just
making it a little harder and if you're not into booting say backed-up games you
can still do import games with a bunch of new stuff including gecko OS version
1.07 which will now allow you to boot import games without a mod chip hello
Rama you're on orange lounge radio what's up not too much holy call cuz you
said nobody else is calling it hey that's alright we you know yeah that's
that's fine if there nobody else wants to call then you can you can be on the
show again we love having you on what's on your mind what's what's going on in
your game world this week although not too much on me and my roommate we're
kind of pissed at GameStop huh really hmm yeah what a shock why why what now
let's let's get off the list hey we should actually you know we should have
we should do that you know I want to do okay we need to do this how can we do
this okay in the studio I don't know if you see on Justin TV right now in the
studio there's a big blank I'm sorry it's better there's a big blank space
right here and I'm thinking what we ought to do is we ought to start over
here like a giant poster board and just a big list things that piss us off about
GameStop and we'll just have a list and start adding to it as people call in and
and what have you I like that maybe I don't know what do you guys think in
chat is that good good idea about it what do you guys think here to you maybe
it should be like put them on Arnold I think my notice putting them on things
on notice this week on the thing is real whiteboard I should okay I'm gonna go
target this we can get a whiteboard and we're either gonna do a game solvers or
a list of things on notice this week so we'll see all right well Rama sorry I
know that's not what you want to call about what what pissed you off about
GameStop well me and the roommate we were planning on picking up rock band
two and he loves the drums so like let's get the new drum kit so we I called over
to make sure they had it in stock that I asked him are you buying back the old
rock band one drum kit I'm like they should know like oh no we're not buying
them back and I'm like how come we're just not click Wow a wonderful customer
service yeah so we're probably end up putting them on Craigslist and going to
another place to buy the arm the drum kit what the hell yeah I know I remember
calling GameStop once and they were like I'm too busy to answer your question you
just have to come in the store and I understand that they might actually be
really busy but there's just better ways to say it you know what I mean like
working in customer service myself I'm kind of an ass saying when it comes to
things like that you know what I mean it's kind of like you know just just hey
dude just tell me you know unfortunately I have a line of about five people right
now could you possibly call back in a little bit or you know just you know
even can I take could I take your number and call you back you know or something
just I wish they would do something like that but I'm dreaming of a perfect world
both what else is going on in your gaming world Rama no I've just been
playing a lot more of my 360 and on a bit of a sad note to you Rob I'm not
gonna be able to do the game the game what the game fly audition oh it didn't
work out why why can't you do it more people got fired of my job so guess
who's covering shifts uh bummer yeah well you know you could still send in a
tape I don't think you should give up I think you should send in a tape well I
probably will end up doing it since I get a free moment cuz I had G of Diaz
camcorder here so we might be able to pull that off oh there you go thank you
for saying the name hopefully I'll remember it this time all right she
loud when um I told her you almost died trying to pronounce her name I'm trying
I'm trying look I have to how many different languages have I had to learn
on this program we have Japanese now Italian you know I'm trying all right
now I anything else you want to share tonight with listeners Rama
Pax 2009 a little army of New York in California getting together we're
getting a suite it's gonna happen holy fucking shit yes please yes please
that's all I have to say mm-hmm thank you very much oh yeah have a good one
Rama yes of Chuck hi no hearts on Friday with
journey yeah but by the way I need to have a voice by then you know you know
dark soccer loves her heart and I love my journey and they are touring together
they're gonna be here on Friday and we are going to the concert and I'm I'm so
excited I could I can hardly contain myself Rob is so excited he can hardly
contain his bladder she's coming right with because she loves hearts too oh my
god she should totally teleport out here we actually have an extra ticket right
now we're trying to get rid of the ticket it's funny she will find her way
out there one way or another even to me she has to pull a GT and steal somebody's
car and do it she better start driving she's got a long way to go all right we
gotta let you go yes see if any more calls come in have a good day all right
bye bye yeah if anyone Sacramento wants to come along that we know no strangers
please cuz you know that might be weird hi you're an orange launch radio who's
this hello orange lounge radio land it is Jason hello Jason land it's orange
lounge radio what's on your mind so speaking apart have you guys seen the
article that Hart published that had published in the magazine I believe it
was some time this last week about the Republican National Committee
specifically McCain using Barracuda in one of his ads yes I somehow had a bad
feeling you were gonna take this show back to politics what is it you guys
mentioned earlier you were talking about the tour I had to ask to make sure you
guys have actually seen it because it was priceless it's fine yes and for
those that aren't in the know Hart got their feathers ruffled big time because
one of the nicknames for Sarah Palin who's the vice presidential nominee
issued over the Republican Party one of her nicknames in Alaska with Sarah
Barracuda I can see Russia from my house Sarah Barracuda so they actually played
Barracuda at the Republican National Convention which is as you know a very
popular heart song where you gamers probably know it from Guitar Hero 3
because in that song in that game and heart was pissed yeah I think they're
anything but Republican yeah you know and you know a lot of musicians get
pissed off and that stuff is used because it makes it look like the
musician endorses that candidate when they often don't remember when it happens
both remember when Reagan used born in the USA and Springsteen threw a hissy
over that especially since the song was pretty much about nothing the American
the Republican Party stands for and I'm sure it works both ways like you know
there's a lot of artists like country artists and you know I think you've seen
people on the convention they that were Republican and they probably don't want
their songs being used and Obama's campaign so it's just politics what a
big mess I seem to remember when I was reading through the news that's actually
like the third time that artists have not been asked not been directly
compensated and through a hissy fit over it well specifically public inside of
the campaign whoever has been getting the music clearances over there needs to
be sacked and then whoever hired that person also needs to be sacked this is
quite possibly gonna be a very short answer I had to step out because I
really needed to get some food during the show but have we covered the epic
rock band crash and character transfer of doom tonight no what's this about
what's up I believe it was ssj 100 Matt published a put a link in chat like an
hour and a half ago pretty short shortly after the show started and apparently
for it looks to be I kind of skimmed but for local games characters created rock
band two characters would switch profiles that they were bound to like
they would be written out to the wrong gamertag so when one person goes back
and plays his characters completely gone and apparently band progress is getting
completely deleted apparently randomly perhaps when the console freezes up and
just really really poorly about 11 pages on the rock band forms to talk about all
these problems people have been having and quite unfortunately I kind of don't
want to play the game until I hear of a patch know what's funny is one thing I
did do is I signed up on the rock band forms or whatever you can link your
gamertag to the actual community it's only shown my rock band one stuff I did
that with you rock then I haven't done that since I've gotten to yet but they
don't have any of my rock band two stuff on there even though I've been playing
it online for like a while now it probably takes a while to catch up
because there's probably like tons and tons and tons of people that are all
playing this game online right now and that's probably what's causing the
crashes to is just like you know they're just probably overwhelmed me on one
hand you ought to think they know how popular their games gonna be but at the
same time you know you don't really know the strain until you put it out there
you know what I mean like you can test it test and test all you want but you
just don't know until it's out there again I'll restate that I only skimmed
it but I seem to remember that it was limited to local games and not quite
online in which case the whole comes the whole thing comes up of do people really
tested and such a narrow instance that they never had these problems when the
game was being developed it just really shocks me that the scores are just
resetting because I would think at least a backup copy saved on your local drive
if nothing else I would imagine the one thing that bugs me more than anything is
it is a you know progress and achieving further things in the game I'm already
kind of turned off just because of the fact that the initial songs are so
terrible in my opinion you know oh I might lay that about the exercise
there's a way you can unlock them all right off the bat you know right I don't
there's no button code out there I don't want to ruin it for everybody but if you
want to search the internet there's a button that you can do on the cheat menu
that will unlock all the songs automatically
well here's the thing isn't it not safe your progress when you use enables no
they disabled it this time it did well here's what it does
you can use it's the same code as in the first rock band game and what it does on
the cheat menu is it adds a toggle where you can toggle all songs off or all songs on.
And if you turn them on then you can't save, but it's more for like parties and that kind
of thing.
Right, I was just going to say, that sounds perfect for if I have a bunch of people over
really want to play and I just throw it in quick play or something.
Yeah, you can toggle it on and off once you've done it, it'll save that little toggle on
there and you can turn it on, off, or whatever.
It's under the game modifiers section under options.
So first correction, it was Sephiroth1215, it was an SSJ100 mat, and apparently, I don't
know if the forum is just overloaded or if they shit-canned this thread or something,
but I'm getting an error when I tried to browse to it again.
I posted it in chat in case anybody else was curious, but something tells me nobody else
is going to have any more luck than I am right now.
So...
You know, I was trying to load the thread too and I had the same problem, so yeah, something's
out.
Lovely.
Interesting.
So, alright, well, Jason, hey, we're going to let you go so we can go and wrap up the
show, alright?
Alrighty.
Have a good one, my friend, though.
Hi, guys.
And hey, wait, wait, wait, wait, before you go, you're a drummer, right?
You're a drummer, right?
Primarily, yeah.
You need to join the band that Shane and I have starting because we need a drummer.
What are you guys doing?
We have a band called the Emergency Kittens.
I'll contact you with more info later.
Sweet, sounds good.
Alright, later.
Thanks.
Alright.
Yes, drummer recruited.
I mean, I could have gone to Bobby Black Wolf, but he said that he's got like a million people
that he's playing with.
I'd always play a game with Bobby Black Wolf, too, if he wants to look me up.
And any drummer, really, that listens to Xbox Live.
Alright, real quick, one more call.
Real quick, one more call.
Who's this?
This is James Patrick.
Hey, James Patrick.
Quick question.
What's on your mind?
I haven't been listening to the whole show, but have you guys talked about Monster Hunter
3 Try, the information that's come out about it?
We have not.
Why don't you share that information with our audience?
Yeah, a bunch of screenshots and stuff from Famitsu has come out recently.
It's confirmed four player online.
The city will act as a lobby, apparently.
It will appear at TGS.
The engine has been completely rebuilt, apparently, for the first time since like the first Monster
Hunter game.
And yeah, it's just a bunch of screenshots out there showing the game and it looks like
Capcom is actually putting forth a lot of effort into this Wii game.
It looks pretty.
What is it that you love so much about Monster Hunter?
Haven't played it.
What is it that makes you highly anticipated?
I know people who've played it and they're very enthusiastic about it, but I think I'll
try it with this game.
What makes you so excited about this release?
Four player online.
If they use the Wii Speak, I guess that might be the thing that gets me to get Wii Speak.
Good point.
Wii Speak has the potential to be pretty cool.
We'll see.
It also has the potential to really suck, so I'm very curious to see how that kind of
plays out.
Could be very interesting.
It's got underwater battles as well, and you can go underwater and the monsters can go
up above and underwater too, apparently, and you can fight in a different environment.
That sounds like it might be interesting.
Huh.
Sounds like it could be a pretty cool game.
Well, James Patrick, thank you so much for the heads up, and we'll be counting down the
days to tell this.
Call us back and let us know how it plays out, because unfortunately, I've got so many
games I'm playing, I probably won't get around to this one.
We'll look to you for a review, okay?
All right.
Have a good one, buddy.
That's going to do it for the Skype line tonight.
If you didn't get through tonight and still want to talk to us, hey, there's always the
email bag or our chat room or our MySpace, our Facebook, our live journal, our Twitter.
There's like a million different ways to find us and interact with us, and you know we love
reaching out to you guys.
You guys help us make the show.
Any more last minute stories, Loki?
Yes.
In fact, you would have heard about this early on the Twitter, because I posted it on Twitter
before the news got out.
But Kingdom Hearts, chains of, or, Kingdom Hearts RE Chains of Memories is coming to...
To be fair, you posted it on your personal Twitter and not the OLR Twitter, and folks
may not know you have your own personal...
Yeah, whatever.
Anyways, so it's the remake that of course came out with Kingdom Hearts to Final Mix
is now coming to the US to PlayStation 2 in December on the 2nd for $29.99.
So that's not a bad deal, and of course they're adding some new stuff along with that, a brand
new voice cast, new minigames, but hey, 30 bucks, that's not bad at all, and apparently
Rockband's down, or Rockband.com's down right now.
Anyways, some other stuff, and this wasn't on show at all, but I just remembered it.
You remember last year how they did bundles with the Xbox 360 and you got free games for
no additional cost.
Well, they're doing that again this holiday, and I have what games in which consoles.
The arcade system actually is getting, I don't know if it's that great, but Sega Superstars
Tennis, and the Elite and Pro systems are both getting two games each, and those would
be Kung Fu Panda and Lego Indiana Jones.
So that's not bad for free, for the holidays.
I guess they're trying to target more of that family audience to fill that hole in their
demographic there.
Alright, and let's see here.
Lastly, I was going to mention that around the time when LittleBigPlanet comes out, they're
going to be offering some free download content, one of which is a spacesuit, so yes, you can
be a spaceman as well.
Is that only for pre-orders or something?
No, it's just, they're going to offer it for a limited time during the first week when
it comes out, and also you can get a rare t-shirt in it that says, I was there for week
one.
They're both going to be free to download, and the very last thing, this kind of goes
back to if you're listening live and heard our little funk remixes on there, you too
can check those out for free.
They're all free to download off of the guy's website, which is LIDBJORK.HOMELINX.ORG slash
Nintendo, and the website's called Sex, Drugs, and Nintendo.
You can also catch them on MySpace dot com slash H-E-N-R-I-K-L-I-D-B-J-O-R-K, and all
those are free to download.
B-J-O-R-K?
Bjork?
Bjork, yes.
Yeah, LIDBJORK.
Nice.
And those are all free to download.
He has Nintenseploitation, and then there's another album, Sex, Drugs, and Nintendo,
which when I was playing one of those AUG files, it crashed my computer, so I stopped
playing those.
But the first album that he has, Sex, Drugs, and Nintendo, is a lot of Mega Man stuff,
and some of the other games he remixes, Disney's DuckTales, there's a few tracks on there from
that, and Gunsmoke, and of course, oh there's one from Maniac Mansion, that's kind of cool.
Alright, very cool.
Some of them are good, some of them are alright.
There was one from Mario Brothers, or something that's kind of weird, or Link's Got a Bop
Gun, that was kind of a weird one.
Alright, that's it.
Awesome, awesome.
Well, DarkSakura, I'd ask if you have any last minute stories, but I know your voice
is not doing too hot.
No.
So, well, I hope you feel better.
In the meantime, I hope the allergies die down, and stop scratching at your throat,
because that's very rude when you're a radio person, to do that.
It feels like an undead bird crawled into my throat and made a nest.
You, you.
Fuck, fuck, fuck.
Alright, well I will ask for one more thing from you tonight, and that is, your final
thought.
Oh, that one's really easy.
You know what it is?
Dying of fire, immediately.
Loki, your final thought.
My final thought is the Baskin-Robbins, I guess their Heath Shake, has 2300 calories
in it.
Thank God I don't like Heath bars.
My final thought is Frozen Yogurt sounds really awesome right now.
That's what I want.
I really want Frozen Yogurt right now.
Hey, thank you guys so much for, unfortunately the Frozen Yogurt place closes at 9, and it's
now 9.05.
Thank you guys for staying up and listening to us tonight, and supporting Independent
Radio.
If you like what you heard, tell two friends about our show.
That's how we spread the word.
It's all via word of mouth, you guys.
Really appreciate it.
Or you could leave us a five-star review on iTunes.
We've had a few people do that this week.
Thank you guys so much to the new five-star reviews we've had left on iTunes.
Really appreciate it.
Cheeseburger messaged me with dongle.
Yeah, I saw dongle show up on Twitter.
Dongle.
Let's see, we had Mozart FX left a nice five-star review, and Skylark91 left a nice one, Warrior
Bob a few days ago.
They did the crappy review.
We call you out.
Dan Shadow, who emailed us, left a nice five-star review not that long ago, so thank you guys
so much who have left the nice reviews for us on iTunes.
Every little bit helps.
We really appreciate it.
Spread the word.
Have we got any one-star reviews on there?
If we did, I would not acknowledge them on this program, because we don't want to encourage
more people to do it, because actually one-star reviews really hurt.
Look, if you want to give the show a one-star review, don't do that.
Go give a show you like more a five-star review.
It's much more impactful.
Go help a show you do like then, because it's just kind of rude to leave a one-star review
in my opinion.
All right.
That's it.
We're out of here.
Have a good night, everybody.
We'll see you next week with episode 296 of Orange Lounge Radio as we inch closer to that
big 300 mark.
Yikes.
You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
To join us for a live show, visit www.allgames.com.
Sunday nights at 6 p.m.
Pacific time, the views and opinions expressed on Orange Lounge Radio do not necessarily
reflect those of the entire staff of Orange Lounge Radio or allgames.com, but we're probably
right anyway.
See you next week.