[SPEAKER_15]: Could a Wii storage problem solution finally be coming?
[SPEAKER_15]: The Mortal Kombat vs DC roster leaks thanks to its achievements, and the first details emerge on DJ Hero.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hello everybody out there on the internets and welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: We are that podcast dedicated to video games, video gaming, gaming culture, and the gamer lifestyle.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's where every gamer has a voice, including you guys when you join our chat room, chat.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: But the voices you'll probably hear most are myself, Rob Roberts, and with me as always, the one and only Dark Sakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_06]: How you doing, Dark Sakura, Jamie Summers?
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm here.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's almost like your new name, Dark Sakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not really, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just don't call me Bob Okay, Bob Alright, also joining us tonight You know what, Rob?
[SPEAKER_06]: Returning after being on vacation last week.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know who told him he could take a week off, but apparently he took it upon himself to take a week off after being so exhausted from Penny Arcade Expo.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's Techmaster Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_06]: So what was it?
[SPEAKER_06]: The day job kept you away, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I had to go to San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, you poor thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: You had to get bought fancy dinners by the company, I'm sure, huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: You poor, poor thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Any game-related things you saw?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, you probably can't talk about them even if you did, huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I didn't.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, everything there is just like...
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like company related stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: They, I mean, they mentioned a few like release seats for movies that, you know, it's, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: But nothing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's no game stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: They just like, oh yeah, we do games too.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's in more
[SPEAKER_04]: It's all movie stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: They gave everyone a $1,500 trip to one of ten locations.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that's just $1,500.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have to book your own trip, so that may cover your flight and that's about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: We could go to what, Fresno?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it's one of ten locations.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's either Hawaii, Hollywood, Seattle, somewhere in Arizona, I forget what it was.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can you save it for next year and go to Seattle next year?
[SPEAKER_04]: By the end of 2009.
[SPEAKER_04]: And no, I'm not going to PAX next year for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not using it for PAX, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's San Antonio, Chicago, Boston, New York City, and Orlando.
[SPEAKER_04]: Orlando.
[SPEAKER_06]: So lots of neat places.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, and Hawaii.
[SPEAKER_06]: You said Hawaii.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stop rubbing it in.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then I found out the other day, because this was originally only being offered to our movie sales, we're going to be probably getting a 42-inch Sony Bravia Plasma TV.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: Through some deal.
[SPEAKER_04]: Basically, our video reps are selling some Sony product, and the goals seem reasonable.
[SPEAKER_04]: So probably by Christmas, I'll have another TV.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let me know when they're hiring, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: A pillow shaped like a question block from Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I have it hanging to my desk just like a question block would be.
[SPEAKER_04]: They wouldn't let me hang it from the ceiling, so I had to put it under my shelf.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was going to say, when you get frustrated, would you just go boing?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, if I hit it, it knocks it off, but that's fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then I also brought, because I used to do and collect Gundam figures, they had armored core figures, so I picked up one of those and I'm going to build that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's kind of cool, but lots of game stuff there.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_13]: It wasn't, because I haven't had a chance to really play much other than Ragnarok.
[SPEAKER_13]: But I did open my copy of The World Ends With You, and I'm going to be starting it.
[SPEAKER_13]: So that's some progress, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sometimes opening the box can be a day-long chore in itself.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_13]: I played Salamander.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ah, how was that?
[SPEAKER_13]: Because I picked up the Salamander pack for Dan on PSP, and it was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_13]: Lifeforce was still kind of difficult.
[SPEAKER_13]: I wouldn't say it was our type hard, but it was pretty tough.
[SPEAKER_06]: Didn't it have a 30 lives code or something, or at least it had the up, up, down, down, like you could get all the power-ups?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that made it easier.
[SPEAKER_06]: GS68 wants to know, was it 1 or 2 Salamander?
[SPEAKER_13]: I got the deluxe pack.
[SPEAKER_13]: I played the first one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ah, there you go.
[SPEAKER_13]: The both games packs.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: well it stayed like that and so I was invulnerable and any vehicle I got in I was invincible in as well um until I turned the game off um
[SPEAKER_04]: And then they have a nice glitch with one of the little side missions you can do the bet money on to actually make money off of.
[SPEAKER_04]: Where they have a maximum where you can only make 5 million per bet.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the problem is though is the minimum is calculated off of the amount of money that you have.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the minimum doesn't have a cap to it.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you can keep playing this game until...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's kind of boring.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not too far into it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm to the tribe stage right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I haven't really actually played the tribe stage yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the cell and creature stages are quite boring.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I hope the rest of the game is not like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But so far I'm very unimpressed by the graphics.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm very unimpressed by the gameplay.
[SPEAKER_04]: It just looks like a game that should have been out like years ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then...
[SPEAKER_04]: Rock Band 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was lucky enough to get that a little early.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I've been playing quite a bit of Rock Band 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, we have a fellow worker.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mad Catz and Awesome in the same sentence?
[SPEAKER_04]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they were like the $20 dance pads.
[SPEAKER_06]: So everybody was like, yay, cheap dance pad.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, they would break after like a week.
[SPEAKER_06]: They were definitely made with $20 parts.
[SPEAKER_04]: At least with the Rock Band stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I know that these are officially licensed products.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Mad Catz is in charge of making the cymbals that are going to be optional for Rock Band 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: They are the only people that are making them.
[SPEAKER_04]: And this bass is something that they're starting to put out too.
[SPEAKER_04]: and it's actually put together a lot better than the controller is the normal guitar controller that you can buy so what makes it kind of unique though they have a thumb rest on it and a dual uh... strummer it's split down the middle so you can kind of um... strum it like you would a bass guitar the only thing i don't like about it and i know you can't really whammy on a bass guitar but the whammy bar is no longer a bar it's a knob and it's literally impossible unless you had a third arm
[SPEAKER_06]: to trigger it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I need to interject here because I want to do a quick poll in our chat room because I'm really, really curious about this before you finish this story.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, and this is for the longtime music game fans only, of which I know we have many that listen to Orange Lounge Radio because we've been doing this a while when we all started with DDR.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's my quick poll question for chat.
[SPEAKER_06]: Will you find it in your heart to forgive Mad Catz if this bass guitar thing is as awesome as Loki says it is?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's my quick poll.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you have it in your heart to forgive Mad Catz?
[SPEAKER_13]: I also do have a comment that I don't see what the difference should be in the strum bar or not because I always play the Guitar Hero ones strumming upwards and not downwards because you play bass strumming upwards.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's so that you can hit it faster if you want to.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I like that it's split in two.
[SPEAKER_06]: That is kind of cool because you can use like two fingers.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would take some getting used to.
[SPEAKER_04]: It does take some getting used to.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like it though.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's really good.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll read the reviews on it if you have any qualms about buying it.
[SPEAKER_04]: All the reviews have been extremely positive about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe it is a turn for the better.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then, let's see what else did I play.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wait, here's the results of our quick poll, alright?
[SPEAKER_06]: Can you find it in your heart to forgive MadCatz?
[SPEAKER_06]: Polled at chat.orangeontrader.com Here we go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fuck no, no, never ever ever, nope, probably, no, hell no, never.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm waiting for Hori to make a guitar con from GS68.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe, perhaps if the price is right, and that's because it has a better D-pad.
[SPEAKER_06]: I had a MadCatz GameCube controller and it was crap.
[SPEAKER_06]: There you go, the results of the quick poll.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Resoundingly negative.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'd buy a hoary one.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're also supposed to be making later on full wood controllers for...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like rockbanddrumsilencer.com or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're really cheap-ass, you know, foam shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, these are the official ones that they actually sell in the stores for $20, and they work pretty good.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you play drums a little bit, Rob?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I played drums at your little thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did they work pretty good, the sensitivity on them?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: It could have been a little better, honestly.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some of the pads were better than others.
[SPEAKER_06]: I noticed the red one.
[SPEAKER_06]: I had a lot of problems.
[SPEAKER_06]: Admittedly, it could be the way I drum.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not used to drumming.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't claim to drum professionally.
[SPEAKER_04]: It could also be my drum set because it's a first generation one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently, all the other ones they've made more sensitive.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought it worked pretty well.
[SPEAKER_04]: It beats being extremely loud with those because it bugs everybody.
[SPEAKER_04]: True.
[SPEAKER_06]: The volume is much more manageable with the little
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, I was trying to find the Rock Band 2 drum sets which were supposedly out today and apparently nobody knows that they're supposed to be out today so EA just didn't ship anybody because I went to GameStop which I might add, GameStop told me they were coming out today and they said, oh yeah, we have some coming in for our pre-order customers but we don't know how many extras they're going to have and then I come back to a different GameStop and they're all, what are you talking about?
[SPEAKER_04]: They're coming out in October.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm a liar!
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, he was an idiot, is what he was.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I went to the Fry's and they didn't know about it, and Best Buy said they're getting them later in the week, so I'm just assuming they didn't ship anybody, which, not surprising.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yeah, I need to get some of those new drums, because I want to plug in useless shit to them.
[SPEAKER_04]: And because my drum set will probably go to my sister eventually, so...
[SPEAKER_06]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Kind of a lot of the same things that Matt's been talking about, so I don't want to repeat too bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: One more thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, sorry, sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Castle Crashers.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've been playing mostly Spore and Rock Band 2 as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: Although most of my Rock Band 2 was early, early this morning because I went to a Walmart, which I usually don't shop at Walmart, but it was the only place that was doing it at midnight, so I was like, alright, I'll go.
[SPEAKER_06]: And so I went into Walmart and, you know, just bought it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I had to wait around because they didn't realize the game was coming out.
[SPEAKER_06]: But whatever, you know, I guess they're not used to games coming out on Sunday or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: Although, as Bobby pointed out... They're not used to working at Walmart at midnight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, no, actually, you know, I was going to try to defend them a little bit, you know, be devil's advocate.
[SPEAKER_06]: But you might be right because I was actually told they can't find the box right now because the guy's on break.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: and you know it's kind of fun to make a sticker and stuff and the online is much more comprehensive you can do these battle of the bands where you're automatically you know playing against your friends list in a Geometry Wars 2 stylish way of taking over their scores and you know on these set lists that could be up for a week or a few hours it's pretty crazy
[SPEAKER_06]: so yeah, that's more rounded out online mode but as far as graphics and some of that the interface hasn't really changed at all the models and everything are the exact same ones they had in Rock Band 1 the motion capturing was a lot better though
[SPEAKER_06]: It didn't even seem that different to me, to be honest.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's a little bit Rock Band 1.5-ish to me, but then again, this is kind of where we're going with music games, is it's a Madden all its own now.
[SPEAKER_06]: I say Rock Band 1.5 in somewhat ingest, because obviously we've been playing DDR for years.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're used to this crap, where it's pretty much the same game with new songs.
[SPEAKER_04]: But seriously though, if...
[SPEAKER_04]: The best feature, I think, in this game is actually something that's part of Rock Band 1, which is the song export feature.
[SPEAKER_04]: That, I think, makes it stand out from Guitar Hero easy because now, if it were like DDR, you can take all your songs from the previous mixes and add them in to your next... Rock Band 2, you take all those songs from Rock Band 1.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rock Band 3 is going to have 2 and 1.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you're just going to get this ever-expanding song list and...
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, no, I definitely agree.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that's cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that's one of the greatest things is just firing up a make-your-own-setlist type thing, and you have literally 150 songs to choose from because you have download songs, rock band one songs, rock band two songs.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's insane, but awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then playing a random setlist or playing online when you have to play random songs, you get songs you forgot you had or songs you didn't know you even had to play, so that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Other games I've been playing this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Spore, Spore, Spore.
[SPEAKER_06]: I bought Spore and I've been playing that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Moving the mouse in random directions, you can get these Picasso-style animals that aren't that bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I still feel like I'm crappy at animal design.
[SPEAKER_06]: But that's just something I guess is learned with time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I kind of like Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: You had a creature that has like one ginormous eye, like a scorpion, that showed up in my planet that was actually kind of cool looking.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was supposed to be like a dog-looking thing, and the eye was its nose.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because it was black.
[SPEAKER_04]: I called it Spike, and it had like a...
[SPEAKER_06]: My current creature that's like a carnivore that just eats everything, it looks like a velociraptor, but with a giant mouth.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it's like one of those like, hello, my name is George, like type of mouse, like, you know, old.
[SPEAKER_04]: PudgeyGuyMouth
[SPEAKER_06]: So either I see crappy things my friends made, or I can see the cool-looking Maxis ones.
[SPEAKER_06]: I should probably do that, because there's been some really stupid things that came in.
[SPEAKER_04]: How many penis monsters have you seen in sports?
[SPEAKER_04]: Zero.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: Zero penis monsters.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't made one, though, myself.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's pretty impressive.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, can't you, like, report it or something if it happens?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: See, that's the thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have to report it, because I was going to make a planet of penis monsters or something, because that'd be funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: The one other thing I've been playing, I've been playing World of Warcraft, Wrath of the Lich King.
[SPEAKER_06]: I got in the beta.
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't really read the user end agreement, so I'm not sure how much I'm allowed to say about it, although I'm pretty sure most WoW sites have been talking pretty openly about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to talk about everything about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Honestly, what is there to talk about?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's been extremely laggy and very hard to kill things.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was like, ooh, pretty new splash screens.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_06]: Pretty new graphics.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm on a pretty new continent.
[SPEAKER_06]: But that's about as much as I could see because it was very, very laggy.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it's a beta.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's free for me to play.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't complain nor base a review off it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So what can you do?
[SPEAKER_06]: I can complain.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'd rather not complain because I realize it's a beta and it's free and it's not the finished product.
[SPEAKER_06]: But all I can say is that it's hard for me to get a feel for it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I will say this though, the new achievement system is kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: I noticed that now you have to have a Blizzard account and I think that's how it's going to tie to Diablo and StarCraft 2 and the other Blizzard franchises.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the game does pretty much know with some hit and miss accuracy what achievements you've already unlocked.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it goes through your quest log and figures out what quests you've already done and therefore what achievements you must have beat.
[SPEAKER_06]: But like, my...
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: So anyway, that's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't want to drag out Gaming Week too long.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're already like 20 minutes into the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: We got gaming news to get to.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll really quickly say for housekeeping tonight, there's not an awful lot to say.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just a reminder, I'll be at E4ALL in a couple weeks.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sadly, DarkSakura and Loki will not be joining me, but I'll be there hoping to meet some of you in the LA area that are going to come out for E4ALL.
[SPEAKER_06]: Look at All Games booth.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's supposed to be right out there on the main floor.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to be pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sure they'll say more about that on AllGames.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that is the first weekend in October, the 3rd through the 5th, if I'm not mistaken.
[SPEAKER_06]: I will be there.
[SPEAKER_06]: in LA.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also, if you haven't already, check us out on Twitter at username OLR on Twitter.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a new one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or, of course, there's always our Live Journal at Orange Lounge, our MySpace at Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Facebook, our name is the OL Army.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's right, four different sites, four different names, just to confuse you further.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, let's get into the gaming news for tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll start off with Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's going on in gaming news?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, Nintendo has released a new peripheral for the Wii system.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it's not a hard drive.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a wireless router because I guess they phased out their little USB sticks that they had to use with your PC.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now this is its own standalone thing and will allow you to connect...
[SPEAKER_04]: to, it's basically, I guess, like an Ethernet bridge, and will allow you to connect your Wii to your router, to your wired network.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do we really need this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Is this a replacement for the dongle they had, the USB stick that you had?
[SPEAKER_13]: Rob, you just said one of my favorite funny words.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dongle?
[SPEAKER_13]: Dongle.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to make a spore creature and call it Dongle.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dongle.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll make one called Balls.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, you do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's an okay idea, I guess, to have a wireless router.
[SPEAKER_04]: or Wireless Bridge for whatever reason because say you know you want to connect your Wii to your wireless network well the problem is for 53 bucks it costs actually 5800 yen or $53 US which is about the equivalent there for 50 some bucks you could probably get yourself a wireless router and then all of your systems can use it oh and it also works with DS as well I don't know
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, my thought is, what exactly are you going to take your Wii Online for that badly?
[SPEAKER_06]: If you need one of these.
[SPEAKER_06]: To buy more virtual console games, I guess?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, are there that many games that support, I guess, Brawl and all that?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, this is just so your Wii can connect to the internet.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is basically a wireless router.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's Nintendo branded, and it looks like the Wii, sort of.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's a waste of time, but...
[SPEAKER_04]: There's cheaper solutions out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Say, for example, this is sitting next to your wired router, your Wii is.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have $20 USB wired dongles that you can get to connect straight to it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It beats paying $53.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't really think this is a problem for a lot of people to connect wirelessly to their network or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just buy a new router.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alpha Cananagram in chat says this does allow PCs.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a router for PCs as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that's awesome, but once again, I would rather that you bought just a normal router.
[SPEAKER_04]: Buy a Linksys or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: But is it pretty?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the important question.
[SPEAKER_06]: Linksys are not that pretty white with the blue lights.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's white, and they have a little stand that makes it stand up just like the Wii, but it... I mean...
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess this is going to appeal to the same people that like Max.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pretty but useless.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dongle.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_04]: This may never come out over here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, by the way, though, if you are interested in this and you want to get it and you live in Japan, it will be coming out on the 18th.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, moving on to more hardware, possibly, but not a hard drive, according to Reggie Fils-Aimé, who spoke to the Nintendo magazine Club Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's the Latin American magazine translated.
[SPEAKER_06]: Reggie actually said, quote,
[SPEAKER_06]: We have never said that it will be a hard drive, nor have we mentioned how we will fix this issue.
[SPEAKER_06]: We are going to deliver a better way to store the games.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: Why go the elaborate route when you can just go the easy route and make it so that it'll work with USB hard drives or USB flash drives or something like that?
[SPEAKER_04]: They're going to try to do something stupid like network storage where they'll just basically store the game on their server and you'll have a key and you'll have to download it every time you want to play it or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're going to do something retarded like this.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, here's my thought is that we too
[SPEAKER_06]: They'll release a, you know, just like they've done a DS and a DS Lite, they'll release a Wii 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: They should give us a dongle.
[SPEAKER_06]: The increased storage and possibly a dongle attachment.
[SPEAKER_13]: They need to have a dongle attachment that links to Bluetooth to a separate hard drive.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't get me wrong.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, they've got... They had some innovative ideas when they first put out the Wii, but all ideas since that haven't been that innovative.
[SPEAKER_04]: And actually have been kind of a step backwards.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: We had...
[SPEAKER_04]: Whoa, what are we going to do for shooter games?
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, let's release a plastic shell.
[SPEAKER_04]: What are we going to do for driving games?
[SPEAKER_04]: What are we going to do for storage?
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, let's do something stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, that's what's going to happen.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can just see Reggie at NextE3 coming out to introduce Wii Plus or Wii 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: Look at this, it's holographic storage.
[SPEAKER_06]: With his increased storage space and his massive dongle.
[SPEAKER_06]: Look at this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Come with it.
Ah!
[SPEAKER_06]: I can see it now.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Rob the Robot.
[SPEAKER_04]: He stores your data by stacking blocks or something really retarded.
[SPEAKER_13]: He shoves it all in his dongle.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_13]: Think about that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Wouldn't that be cool if they made a little USB storage device like Rob the Robot?
[SPEAKER_04]: It won't happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: I always thought they should release a miniature Rob the Robot that plugs into your DS and Game Boy Advance slot.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: That's something that people are familiar nowadays.
[SPEAKER_04]: People aren't like going, oh, it's a mystical device that connects through the internet via magic.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, people aren't that dumb.
[SPEAKER_04]: They do have a rudimentary understanding of how computers work.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: And to be honest, if they don't understand storage and stuff and what kilobytes mean, guess what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe they'll learn to figure out what this is via their Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, that's a great idea.
[SPEAKER_04]: Instead, no, we're going to make it.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're just going to pander to the idiots and figure out a way to do that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you, GS68.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wild, wacky action bike.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm waiting for that attachment to come out on Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm telling you, man.
[SPEAKER_06]: Whatever it's going to be, I'm just ready for disappointment.
[SPEAKER_06]: We need wild, wacky action bike Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: It would sell like crazy and you know it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's seriously, whatever they're going to announce at E3 is just going to be a disappointment.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_13]: But we are getting a dongle, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: We might.
[SPEAKER_04]: Seriously, they're going to be like, we've been working on this for years and it's a Nintendo branded SD card.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck yourselves.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, we'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't plan on ending my stupid little boycott just yet because most stuff I want that's been coming out on Wii lately, namely the Strong Bad games, have also been coming out on PC.
[SPEAKER_06]: Problem fixed.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, I'm still going to be downloading Cho Aniki behind my husband's back.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ooh, I like Shaoran's comment.
[SPEAKER_06]: A wild, wacky action dongle.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ooh!
[SPEAKER_06]: That could be like an OLR dream game.
[SPEAKER_06]: And by the way, I was gifted Cho Aniki this week.
[SPEAKER_13]: Someone should gift me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Heart.
[SPEAKER_13]: Gift me next.
[SPEAKER_06]: GIFs, I can't break my boycott when people give me GIFs.
[SPEAKER_06]: I forgot to remind you to take the Wii Fit.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, that's alright, I'll get it next week or something.
[SPEAKER_13]: More news!
[SPEAKER_13]: Mega Man 9, for everyone who has been happy and excited and getting a little bit flickery giddy about it.
[SPEAKER_13]: It actually has a Japanese release date now.
[SPEAKER_13]: Mega Man 9 is supposed to be out in Japan on September 24th for 1,000 Wii Points.
[SPEAKER_13]: We don't have our date here yet, or in Europe, but Capcom loves us.
[SPEAKER_13]: At least they better, bitches.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sure it'll be here soon.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, but seriously, seriously, seriously.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was actually reported, I do believe, by Dengeki Online, the release date, so not too bad.
[SPEAKER_13]: So I'm looking forward to it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I would honestly think that we'd probably get it close to the same day.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was going to say, odds looking good we'll get it around the same day.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hope so.
[SPEAKER_06]: Be nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, if you can't wait that long, you'll be happy to know that Strong Bad, Episode 2, Strong Baddie of the Free, will be releasing this Monday on WiiWare and on the PC.
[SPEAKER_04]: Woohoo!
[SPEAKER_04]: and I have no idea what's going to be happening in the game because one, I didn't play the first one and two, I don't really visit the websites.
[SPEAKER_06]: More of the wonderful humor that was in the first game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's episode two.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like you watch a TV series, this is episode two.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like you watch a show like South Park and episode one was funny so you tune into episode two.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then things get angsty in episode two.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, you know, characters start sleeping with each other and form these complex relationships.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I totally made that up.
[SPEAKER_06]: But that would be interesting.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think even watching too much daytime TV, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it's just 90210.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_06]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Something else is coming out on the Wii quite soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wii Music.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, you know, we've had certainly mixed opinions on Wii Music.
[SPEAKER_06]: But sometimes I kind of think that Nintendo does these kinds of things just to kind of impress us.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like try to get a certain niche audience.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's right, you are hearing in the background Cowbell in Wii Music.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wii Music is actually getting Cowbell.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they're actually demoing it there.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can actually check out a little trailer there.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's hit game trailers, but it's also on Nintendo's site.
[SPEAKER_06]: So insert your needs more Cowbell joke here because it's probably what got this in the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Somebody at Nintendo thought, joke, funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: or that the cowbell is actually considered a real instrument, which in some ways it really is.
[SPEAKER_13]: I actually went to this music store at Haight-Nashbury that has cowbells with features.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm like, dude, it's a cowbell.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, this one's got extra muting and this one has tone change and this one's got this.
[SPEAKER_06]: You bang it with a stick.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know, electric cowbell.
[SPEAKER_06]: That would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Amplified Cowbell.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like a cowbell that sounds like a gong every time you hit it.
[SPEAKER_13]: A cowbell doesn't vibrate like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you get to play gong in Wii Music?
[SPEAKER_06]: That would be kind of awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, but I will gong in Wii Music.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wii Music is getting more cowbell.
[SPEAKER_06]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_13]: All the others that are already there.
[SPEAKER_13]: Isn't that nice?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's wonderful news because Castlevania 3 is one of the best.
[SPEAKER_13]: One thing I hope, that it's like the Japanese version.
[SPEAKER_06]: I somehow knew you were going to go there and get into the whole discussion about the extra sound or whatever.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, that wasn't it.
[SPEAKER_13]: When you played Grant, you know the one who climbs on the ceiling and everything?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hell yeah, how can you forget Grant if you've ever played Castlevania 3?
[SPEAKER_13]: He throws his knife instead of just stabs.
[SPEAKER_13]: So he actually has a ranged attack.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, so he's actually useful.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I always used the one that had the fire, ice.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sypha?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: But what's the point in him throwing knives if he can have a sub-weapon of throwing knives?
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't think he can.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wasn't there something else, too, with Castlevania?
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's that the Famicom since it had an extra sound.
[SPEAKER_06]: Didn't it have an extra sound processor or something?
[SPEAKER_13]: I think it did.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think if I'm correct, it ran off the disc.
[SPEAKER_13]: and the disc system did actually have... Like, have you ever heard the Legend of Zelda for the Famicom disc?
[SPEAKER_13]: It had actually really nice music in it.
[SPEAKER_13]: So it was the difference in the sound processors too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Little known fact, the Famicom disc system had a sound channel for porno soundtracks.
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: True.
[SPEAKER_04]: False.
[SPEAKER_07]: Absolutely true.
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: Really?
[SPEAKER_06]: I wouldn't lie.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, you would.
[SPEAKER_06]: Absolutely true.
[SPEAKER_06]: GameGuru in chat says, JP will get JP version, US will get US version.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sad but true.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or if it's easier to not emulate off the disk system, because I don't think there have been any disk games that have come to Virtual Console, maybe JP will get US version.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it's going to be the US version.
[SPEAKER_13]: We got Excitebike, didn't we?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, that's true, we did.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, but Excitebyte wasn't the disc version.
[SPEAKER_06]: What did they do with the save load?
[SPEAKER_06]: Even here in America, though, remember we got the cartridge and it still had save load and it would just crash your game if you tried to use it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which I thought was one of the most hilarious things ever on the old school Nintendo, that they just left it in there when we didn't have the attachment.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, if I was right, the entire game was done in English anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: If only Nintendo knew they were setting trends with Excitebike that soon will be followed by large companies like EA.
[SPEAKER_04]: Releasing games that are broken.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_13]: DriverMite also had it, if I'm right.
[SPEAKER_13]: But no, it didn't because DriverMite was the one that my husband and I went through like 15 copies of when he had his used game store and took out the converter cartridge so that we could make our own converter.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow, there were actually that many copies of Gyromite in circulation?
[SPEAKER_06]: That many Rob the Robot sold?
[SPEAKER_06]: My friend had one.
[SPEAKER_06]: I knew one friend that had one.
[SPEAKER_13]: We have one.
[SPEAKER_06]: What did they really do?
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, nothing.
[SPEAKER_06]: They had the little spinny thing.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was a selling point.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It didn't do anything.
[SPEAKER_13]: You can play three games with this thing, and he's going to look cool, and then that's it.
[SPEAKER_13]: He looks like Johnny Five.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, a lot of people don't really understand what Rob the Robot actually did.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, basically, didn't he just, like, he had these little spinning discs that you would put down, like these little top things that you would put down on these giant things that just pressed your controller.
[SPEAKER_13]: Pretty much!
[SPEAKER_13]: Rob, it was a selling point.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was amazingly stupid in retrospect.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I realize that Rob the Robot is like pop culture cool, and everybody laughed when they saw him in Brawl, but if you think about it, Rob the Robot was really stupid.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, in all actuality.
[SPEAKER_06]: But anyhow.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rob the Robot just exudes awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what Rob the Robot does.
[SPEAKER_04]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, anyways, on PC this week, we've got Stalker, Clear Sky, uh, Cabela's Big Game Hunter 09, Legendary Adventures, and, uh, that's also coming out on the PlayStation 2 Wii, and I believe that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh, let's see here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Star Wars The Force Unleashed will be coming out on pretty much every system out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, not any retro systems, all current systems, and...
[SPEAKER_04]: Drun Life, Spongebob Squarepants Edition TNA Impact Crisis Warhead on PC
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's meant for lower end PCs.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Witcher Enhanced Edition on PC.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have Hell's Kitchen coming out on PC this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Armored Core for Answer on PS3 and Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have Igor coming out on PC, DS, and the Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: Line Rider 2 Unbound on PC and DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dance Dance Revolution X on PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Enchanted Unicorn on PC, Kid Sports Crazy Golf on Wii, Bratz Ponies 2 on DS, Dragon Quest IV Chapters of the Chosen on DS, Battle of Phantasia on 360, My Secret World by Imagine, and it's a diary.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pure on PS3, 360, and PC Super Pickups on the Wii Unsolved Crimes on the DS
[SPEAKER_04]: Zoo Hospital on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently it's like Trauma Center meets a pet hospital.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Red Bull BC One, that game I've been talking about for a while now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Check it out, it's on the DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: And let's see, there's some collections, retro collections coming out from Namco.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have the Naruto Ultimate Collection, which is...
[SPEAKER_04]: Naruto The Ultimate Ninja 2 and 3 and Uzumaki Chronicles and then the Namco Classic Fighter Collection which is Soul Calibur 2, Tekken 5 and... God, I can't remember the last one.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then Pac-Man Power Pack which is a bunch of Pac-Man games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nothing good, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think that's all the big stuff, at least.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, any price point?
[SPEAKER_06]: I know a lot of our listeners are probably into DDRX.
[SPEAKER_06]: Any price point for that?
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to say it's $40 for the game only, and for the bundle, it's probably $49.99.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would have thought maybe it came down a little bit in price, because PS2 is kind of, you know, the last... It may have.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just going off memory, and that's, you know...
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, so don't take that as the final word.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here, give me one second.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can tell you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, let me do the Japanese release dates, and you can kind of jump in whenever you find it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Going over to the Japanese release dates, Star Wars The Force Unleashed is coming to the Asian regions around Japan and on all those other consoles as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: As far as Japan, Japan itself is getting Unreal Tournament 3 on the Xbox 360 this week on the 18th for those folks that like the first-person shooters over there.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know the scene's not quite as big over there, but they've got some fans of it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some PlayStation 3 games getting a price reduction this week, including Def Jam Icon and Fight Night Round 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: Again, those are price reductions on the PlayStation 3, down to about $30 US.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some other games coming out in Japan on the PlayStation 3, G.I.
[SPEAKER_06]: Jockey 4 2008, and Winning Post 7 in a combo pack, or of course you can just get the game G.I.
[SPEAKER_06]: Jockey 4 by itself.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also, Trusty Bell, Chopin No Yume, you might know this here as Eternal Sonata, finally comes out on the PlayStation 3 this week in Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's $29.99 for the game only.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ah, much better.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good.
[SPEAKER_06]: Unreal Tournament 3 also comes out on the PlayStation 3 this week, so be on the lookout for that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also coming out in Japan on the Nintendo Wii, we have Biohazard Umbrella Chronicles getting a price reduction.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know that, of course, is Resident Evil.
[SPEAKER_06]: G.I.
[SPEAKER_06]: Jockey Wii 2008 as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: Kororimpa gets a price reduction.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bomberman comes out next week, so be on the lookout for that.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's actually on next week's list on the 25th.
[SPEAKER_06]: Moving on to the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: PlayStation 2 is still getting a lot of love.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hyper Street Fighter 2, the Anniversary Edition, and Vampire Darkstalkers Collection Value Pack.
[SPEAKER_06]: So for you old school 2D Capcom fighting fans, a little PS2 pack coming out for you guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's happiness.
[SPEAKER_06]: G.I.
[SPEAKER_06]: Jockey 4, 2008, also gets a version on PlayStation 2 and gets a combo pack with Winning Post 7, also on PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: And a game called Heart No Kuni No Alice is coming out as well on the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's take a look at the handheld systems, starting off on the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_06]: DragonBallDS comes out this week from NamcoBandai.
[SPEAKER_06]: LumiSlight, HikariNoPuzzle as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: LongVacation, IrukaTotoWatashi comes out.
[SPEAKER_06]: And OshishiKeiji, Keiji-san Watashi ga Arimashita comes out from Success.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: And we'll see if it will be a success over in Japan.
[SPEAKER_06]: Although probably not.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've never heard of it.
[SPEAKER_06]: On the Sony PlayStation Portable, Monster Hunter Portable, 2ndG Hunter, Leather Cover.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that's not a game.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just something to match all the Monster Hunter games that you have for your PlayStation Portable.
[SPEAKER_06]: But if you actually want a new game, you can get Samurai Do Portable.
[SPEAKER_06]: is the name of that game.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm not sure if that's a fighting game or what type of game that is.
[SPEAKER_06]: It looks to be an action-based game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think it's a fighting game, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's a hack-and-slash type PSP game.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's rated 15+, or 0C, so you know there's going to be some good blood.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hooray!
[SPEAKER_06]: Blood!
[SPEAKER_06]: Gore!
[SPEAKER_06]: That's it for your Japanese release dates.
[SPEAKER_13]: For UK, we have the 18th Warhammer Online.
[SPEAKER_13]: For the 19th is everything else.
[SPEAKER_13]: Destroy All Humans, Path of Furon, Hell's Kitchen, the video game, Play TV for PlayStation 3, SimCity Creator, Star Wars The Force Unleashed, also STCC, the game, The Witcher Enhanced Edition, and Tim Stockdale's Riding Star.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, and also Yakuza 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's it?
[SPEAKER_13]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, The Force Unleashed, we all mentioned that in our respective releases.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's practically a worldwide release this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: But one thing that's kind of interesting about it, one thing I was reading about on the internet, I was trying to see if GameStop was doing a Rock Band 2 midnight release.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I really just didn't want to go to Walmart, but it was pretty much the only thing that was open.
[SPEAKER_06]: And yes, I had to have the game at 12.01.
[SPEAKER_06]: even though I didn't get it until 1230.
[SPEAKER_06]: But anyway, apparently the reason why GameStop did not do a midnight release for Rock Band 2 is because a lot of them are doing midnight releases for Forced Unleash and they just didn't want to pay all that extra salary.
[SPEAKER_04]: A lot of people, I mean, I would see why they're doing that because the Forced Unleash is coming out on a lot more systems and a lot of people might not be interested in the game-only version of Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_04]: And there's a lot of rabid Star Wars fans.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, really.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, I mean, I can understand why they would do that.
[SPEAKER_06]: VXJasonXV played Hell's Kitchen the game in our chat room and he laughs ha ha ha and said I played Fox's Flash version of that it was silly yeah and you know what's funny is that Flash version of it is pretty much what you're getting on the Wii and the DS it's crap so Frisbee says bake that fucking bread now sadly I don't think the Wii version of the game will swear at you which is the only reason to watch Hell's Kitchen I don't get it like if you're not going to get berated by your Nintendo Wii what's the point
[SPEAKER_06]: Now you're just playing like Cake Mania with some fire.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's basically just like Cooking Mama mixed with American Idol.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rock Band 2 People that managed to get their copies early were welcomed with custom screens
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: And then, of course, for those people that have finally picked up their copy, you'll be greeted with some new tracks to download this Tuesday, including the Megadeth album, Peace Sells, but who's buying?
[SPEAKER_04]: And they've got, it looks like, about, I want to say...
[SPEAKER_06]: 7 songs available there for $2 each or you can buy the whole pack for $11 so you save a few bucks there remember back in the day when like 8 marathon songs was an album like you know you'd get 8 songs from a rock band but they would be just like effing epic rock songs like 7-8 minutes in length
[SPEAKER_06]: Megadeth.
[SPEAKER_06]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_13]: Megadeth was awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then also, if that's not your cup of tea, they have the Rock Band Tour Pack, which includes one of those nights by The Cab, Hands Down by Dashboard Confessional, She's a Handsome Woman by Panic at the Disco, and Natural Disaster by Plain White Teas.
[SPEAKER_04]: All those are available for a buck or 80 Microsoft points, or you can buy the whole pack for $4.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you're saving zero money.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: By the way, speaking of Rock Band download stuff, I know our one and only DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_06]: One thing she loves almost more than video games is gorillas, and therefore Blur, because, you know, the whole Damon-Auburn connection.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know!
[SPEAKER_06]: I did check out Beetlebum, which is available in the Rock Band store.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is a cover, if you weren't already aware.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not horrible.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's not worth having.
[SPEAKER_06]: At least you have the song, because, you know, ideally you're supposed to get someone else to sing to it anyway, but it is a cover.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you didn't know on it, already know.
[SPEAKER_13]: If you do sing it, you have to do the really extra thick accent that he affects for the song.
[SPEAKER_06]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I realize this is like the quintessential Blur song, but we have to have song two come out at some point.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_13]: Either that or There's No Other Way.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or Boys and Girls.
[SPEAKER_13]: I like that song.
[SPEAKER_13]: My favorite is.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like Coffee and TV too.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's a good song.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_13]: But they probably aren't going to have anything off of the later two Blur albums because they're very kind of melodramatic.
[SPEAKER_06]: At least in this country.
[SPEAKER_06]: This weren't as big here.
[SPEAKER_06]: 13 was a weird album.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow, sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Enough Blur dish.
[SPEAKER_06]: By the way, I love the fact...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: So, I thought it was funny that everybody's afraid to go online, like they're going to get busted and banned or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Harmonix really didn't seem to give a crap.
[SPEAKER_04]: We were playing that last night, and some of the vocal sections in the game were kind of easy to hit.
[SPEAKER_04]: I remember, was it...
[SPEAKER_04]: Jim Sabotage, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Not sabotage, what you want He was just like He's like drunk That's what he was literally saying He was just kind of yelling He was like, awesome!
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, I thought that was funny And then Irene If you've listened to this show long enough You know Rice Princess was making up new lyrics And saying something about my butt To all these songs Which was very rude, in my opinion Very rude
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow, thank God there was no video camera there so it can be on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, not only do you already know about the bundle, but now you know exactly what songs you're going to be getting in the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not going to read the entire song list.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can probably just Google Guitar Hero World Tour song list.
[SPEAKER_06]: You'll find the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I do want to point out some highlights of the song list, at least in my mind.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sure everybody feels differently.
[SPEAKER_06]: 311, Beautiful Disaster, Beastie Boys, No Sleep Till Brooklyn, Billy Idol, Rebel Yell,
[SPEAKER_06]: Blink-182, Damn It, Blondie, One Way or Another Bon Jovi, Livin' on a Prayer Coldplay, Shiver The Doors, Love Me Two Times The Eagles, Hotel California Filter, Hey Man, Nice Shot Fleetwood Mac, Go Your Own Way Foo Fighters, Everlong Guess Who, American Woman
[SPEAKER_06]: Jimmy Hendrix, Purple Haze, and The Wind Cries Mary Corn with Freak on a Leash Lenny Kravitz, Sweet Home Alabama Live
[SPEAKER_06]: Metallica, Trapped Under Ice, Michael Jackson, Mews with Assassin, Nirvana with the unplugged version of About a Girl, No Doubt with Spiderwebs, NoFX, Ozzy Osbourne with Crazy Train, Pat Benatar, Heartbreaker, R.E.M.,
[SPEAKER_06]: Smashing Pumpkins, Survivor, Eye of the Tiger, Sublime, Tool, 3 Songs by Tool,
[SPEAKER_06]: I like Tool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Parabola, Schism, and Vicarious.
[SPEAKER_06]: Schism.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't listen to Tool.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't like them, actually.
[SPEAKER_06]: But that's just... Well, whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Van Halen, Hot for Teacher.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was a song that got played over and over again at Penny Arcade Expo.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Wings with Band on the Run.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because you know we needed some Wings in Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_06]: Guitar Hero World Tour Guitar Hero World Tour Guitar Hero World Tour Guitar Hero World Tour
[SPEAKER_04]: I wish they would have more songs like Beat It and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: We need a pop band or a pop hero or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not even necessarily have to do that, but some download packs.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't understand why there isn't more Michael Jackson stuff in there because Beat It works and you might even be able to do Thriller and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just stuff that had a lot of guitar and stuff in the background.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dude, Thriller needs to be download content.
[SPEAKER_06]: Make it happen.
[SPEAKER_06]: Lovely folks.
[SPEAKER_04]: And also country stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's that one song, Rockstar, that would work pretty well.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just surprised there's not a lot of that stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: It may not be enough for its own game, but at least throw some download content out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure people would appreciate appealing to a broader audience, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, well there you have it.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Guitar Hero World Tour set list and a lot of guitar fans very excited about this game.
[SPEAKER_13]: and other exciting news.
[SPEAKER_13]: Actually, I think it's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: Rob, do you ever watch Comedy Central?
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love Comedy Central.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's where I get South Park.
[SPEAKER_13]: What's your favorite show besides South Park?
[SPEAKER_06]: My favorite show besides South Park?
[SPEAKER_06]: The Daily Show.
[SPEAKER_13]: The Colbert Report
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes, Charlene is going to be available as a free download for Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_13]: So everyone has to go get it right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, it is actually available now.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it's one of those blink and you miss it things.
[SPEAKER_06]: Get it!
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, because if you go into Rock Band, you won't see it in the new releases.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's only in the library.
[SPEAKER_13]: And if anyone wants to familiarize themselves with it, while they already should be, except that I'm not really all that familiar with it, you can actually watch the video on YouTube as well.
[SPEAKER_13]: Go watch it after the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: The song's only like a minute long and it's not that difficult either.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've heard people are getting their achievements with it.
[SPEAKER_06]: The lyrics are very funny.
[SPEAKER_13]: It enables the players to achieve more.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, we can play a little clip from Charlene.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's only like a minute long.
I love the synthesizer in this song.
[SPEAKER_10]: Aw, nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: Reminds me of my ex.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh my god, that's so wrong.
[SPEAKER_13]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's so wrong.
Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_06]: There'll be a couple people listening to the show that understand that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's move on quickly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, speaking of appealing to a broader audience, SingStar is releasing a country version which will be coming to the PlayStation 2 on October 28th.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you can find...
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess songs from Kelly Pickler, Keith Urban, Montgomery Gentry, and among others.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, they're going to be localizing SingStar Legends as well, which is supposed to be coming out the same day.
[SPEAKER_04]: That has a bunch of pop legend stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can probably guess all your favorite stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: How dare you, Loki?
[SPEAKER_06]: How dare you talk about SingStar and not talk about the most important announcement of all time?
[SPEAKER_06]: This is the greatest moment in video game history happened this week around SingStar, and Loki just somehow missed it.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's a decider who wins the console war, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: The console war has been won this week by Sony PlayStation 3, and it's all because...
[SPEAKER_06]: Waterloo
[SPEAKER_06]: This was one of those moments and then God spoke.
[SPEAKER_06]: And he said, let there be Abba.
[SPEAKER_06]: And there was.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Sony won the war.
[SPEAKER_06]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, let's just end the fucking show because there's no other news that's going to top this.
[SPEAKER_12]: Does that mean we can go home now?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, we could try, but it's just going to be pathetic.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: I still think that my story was the best story ever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, Stephen Colbert is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: We'll try, Rob.
[SPEAKER_13]: Try to find something fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: I will find something fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's talk about DJ Hero.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a lot of people that are very excited about DJ Hero because they think it's going to be Beatmania 2DX.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to be like, you know, the answer to Beatmania 2DX by the folks who did Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you'd be kind of like half right because it's not really going to be like...
[SPEAKER_06]: Beatmania 2DX
[SPEAKER_06]: So if you imagine one of these things, you could hit this little turntable and there's actually going to be little effector buttons on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like a version of one of those type of decks.
[SPEAKER_06]: You use these little effector buttons and a crossfader to actually drop samples.
[SPEAKER_06]: So if you ever thought like, hey, Beatmania isn't really like DJing, now you have a game that is actually kind of DJing.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_04]: If we take the scratch and replace it with strum and we turn the effector buttons into fret buttons, we have Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_04]: So really, it's just re-skinning Guitar Hero to put different music in it.
[SPEAKER_06]: But in a way, think about this.
[SPEAKER_06]: This does sound kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: They say the wireless controller apparently is actually grooved to fit in your lap.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_13]: The Grey Album was Jay-Z and the Beatles.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, never mind.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry, Jay-Z.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I'm thinking Metallica's Black Album.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know it was like a black album mixed with a white album.
[SPEAKER_06]: But think those types of things.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's supposed to be mashups.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is going to be the whole song list.
[SPEAKER_06]: You like mashups, don't you, Loki?
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought you loved that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think this game is going to be... People will probably buy it because it's...
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, something that Activision is putting out, but I think it's going to be, if you're thinking it's going to be 2DX, you're going to be sorely disappointed.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, we'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it's not going to be 2DX, but it sounds like it could be cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't necessarily need a copy of a game that's already out there and still selling in Japan, you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_06]: I like the fact that it's kind of different.
[SPEAKER_06]: and they're also saying that they're supposed to be like guitar co-op as well I don't know it's we'll have to see how it actually plays out but I'm not too optimistic yet what's interesting and possibly related is that almost within the same breath Activision announced this week that they have acquired Freestyle Games it's a UK based developer and they made the game B-Boy which you know was on the PSP I don't think it really sold like crazy but it was a rhythm action game that was available on the PSP and it's apparently what they're doing is they're developing a new music based IP
[SPEAKER_06]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_06]: B-Boy?
[SPEAKER_06]: DJ Hero?
[SPEAKER_06]: Connection?
[SPEAKER_06]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_06]: But it certainly is interesting that Freestyle Games was sucked into the Activision collective this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: People will eat this up.
[SPEAKER_04]: As long as you do something innovative with it, you know, if you can mix actual MP3s or something like that, that might be kind of cool, but somehow I'm gonna set the bar a lot lower than, you know,
[SPEAKER_06]: I would like it to be.
[SPEAKER_06]: By the way, B-Boy was not just available on the PlayStation Portable.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is available on the PlayStation 2, also in the United States.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it got released here a couple weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it was probably one of those, again, kind of blink and you miss it sort of things.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was an alright game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Was it?
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't played it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: I had never even heard of it.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's why I say blink and miss it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I played the UK version of the PSP game a while back, and it was alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: It wasn't a lot to hold my attention for a long time, but it was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, well, there you have it.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see more information on DJ Hero.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe made by these guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, Sony is not happy.
[SPEAKER_13]: Not happy at all.
[SPEAKER_06]: They should be elated.
[SPEAKER_06]: They have ABBA.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, but the PSP people aren't happy.
[SPEAKER_13]: They want it all.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I mean, as if ABBA wasn't big enough, they want everything.
[SPEAKER_13]: They want third-party support for the PSP.
[SPEAKER_13]: They're not very happy with it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Basically, the boss of Sony Worldwide Studios, Yoshida Shuhei, is basically saying that they'd like to see more third-party support on the PSP and that they're jealous because other people are getting third-party support and not them.
[SPEAKER_13]: He's quoted saying it's really, really disappointing.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, it's so disappointing he had to use really twice.
[SPEAKER_13]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: It did get the point across.
[SPEAKER_13]: and it's a lost opportunity for the third parties they should look at what the PSP can do for their titles and the potential for the business that their IP has they say though that Sony's got a whole bunch more things ready but they are really wanting Capcom maybe but you know the PSP 3000
[SPEAKER_13]: is on its way!
[SPEAKER_04]: Not even that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wouldn't even go that far.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just there's a lot more people that own the DS because they're suckered into buying multiple colors for it or God knows what.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, I like the PSP a lot better than the DS, but I... Well, but if you go back to that rule that a system is only as good as the games that are on it... Exactly, there's better games on DS in general, so people are going to go where the good games are.
[SPEAKER_06]: And in a way, this is what Sony's complaining about, is that the third parties aren't giving them what they need to sustain.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, maybe start supporting the third parties a little bit more.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe do some innovative features to the PSP, like make voice chat a lot easier.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now that they have the microphone built in, they can do some stuff with that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Touchscreen, that might be kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tilt sensors.
[SPEAKER_06]: I always kind of thought that the PSP's strength over the DS was that it was more of a kind of all-in-one type system.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was like part iPod, part game player, part web browser.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just a little bit of everything for a relatively low price.
[SPEAKER_13]: For me, I have absolutely no reason to really play a PSP much except for a couple of games, really.
[SPEAKER_06]: If I was in high school, though, all over again, I would be all over this PSP.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, this would be a great thing to take to high school, I think.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because you got it all right there.
[SPEAKER_13]: When I was in high school, it was the Atari Lynx.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow, if that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't have one of those.
[SPEAKER_06]: I had a Game Boy Brick.
[SPEAKER_13]: Actually, it was the Turbo Express.
[SPEAKER_06]: I had a Game Boy Brick in a brick gray case.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hauled it around and it got stolen.
[SPEAKER_13]: I had a Game Boy Brick and a friend of mine had a Turbo Express.
[SPEAKER_13]: I was like, cool, I want one.
[SPEAKER_13]: But anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, there's some other good things, though, coming to the PSP, and I know we don't talk about it too much, but they actually have a lot of games now on their PC store that you can download the full versions of.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's almost like a digital version of it, kind of like what they do with the PS1 Classics.
[SPEAKER_04]: Included, you know, this new lineup of stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're going to have Cube...
[SPEAKER_04]: Puzzle Quest Challenge of the Warlords for $14.99, which is not bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Work Time Fun for $10.
[SPEAKER_04]: You get PQ, PQ2, that one game that's kind of like IQ.
[SPEAKER_04]: The first one for $9.99, the second one for $14.99, and Deadhead Fred, which is kind of a sleeper game for $15.
[SPEAKER_04]: So they are releasing quite a bit of stuff on the PC store.
[SPEAKER_04]: I kind of think it's funny, though, that they have digital copies of it now, because, I mean...
[SPEAKER_04]: People have been doing that before in not such a legit way.
[SPEAKER_04]: But now they're encouraging it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And by the way, if you're listening to this show on a PSP, which a lot of our emailers and so on have told us that they do, you need to pause the podcast right now and you need to go to olrpsp.com in your browser and check out the new Orange Lounge Radio All Games Tuner that's available on the downloads page there because it's quite awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it will allow you to listen to the All Games Radio live feed right there from your crossbar without having to hunt around for it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like one-click access to the show, which is great.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Hmm, interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Moving on to another Sony-related story.
[SPEAKER_06]: And this is the type of game a lot of folks can get into.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's Kingdom Hearts.
[SPEAKER_06]: And a lot of people have kind of been wondering, when's the next Kingdom Hearts game going to come out?
[SPEAKER_06]: Where's our information on Kingdom Hearts 3?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, sadly, we don't have that.
[SPEAKER_06]: But what we did get from this week's GameStop Expo, which is kind of a meeting of all the important people at GameStop, happened this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently, a little piece slipped out about Kingdom Hearts Chain of Memories.
[SPEAKER_06]: You might remember that this was a Game Boy Advance game that got released on the PlayStation 2 in Japan as part of a Kingdom Hearts 2 Final Mix type thing that came out.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was like a bonus disc, and it kind of was forgotten about and never was released over here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Until now, apparently, Kingdom Hearts Chain of Memories, it is going to be coming to the U.S.,
[SPEAKER_06]: There was a small mention of Kingdom Hearts Chain of Memories at Square Enix's presentation.
[SPEAKER_06]: When they were asked if it was the same one that was Final Mix 2 in Japan, they did confirm it with a nod.
[SPEAKER_06]: There hasn't been an official announcement through Square, just this small mention.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I guess you should take it with a little bit of a grain of salt.
[SPEAKER_06]: But apparently, if you tie things together, back in July, Squeenix was hiring an English voice cast.
[SPEAKER_06]: So probably to go for this game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Although that could also be for Final Fantasy 13, but who knows.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would think, why not release this game here?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, certainly there's an audience for it.
[SPEAKER_13]: But, you know, they usually don't pay attention to everybody, do they?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, who knows?
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_13]: The classic game of the week came out on Super Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_13]: It is one of the Mario franchises, and it is Mario Paint.
[SPEAKER_06]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_13]: Mario Paint uses the SNES mouse that came with it, and it basically is a little drawing program for the most part.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, it basically is like Microsoft Paint, but I don't really want to go too much into the more...
[SPEAKER_13]: in a structured part of the game.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's go into what's playing in the background.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is a little clip from F-Zero that somebody has put into the little music maker in Mario Paint.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, right.
[SPEAKER_13]: It did actually have a music program in there, and you could actually save things onto... I do believe that you could actually tape them, but it was very weird.
[SPEAKER_13]: A lot of these are more... These days are done through an emulator now.
[SPEAKER_13]: But there was... Going back to the art side of it, you could actually make stamps, and it came with stamps in it, too, and that was cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: 30 different colors, 60 different textures and patterns, 75 different stamps, 15 customizable stamps, battery backup, and special erasers like the fade erase, water erase, where the picture becomes a grayscale and vanishes, timed erase, rain erase, split image erase, pixelated erase, blinds erase, rocket erase, and abrupt erase.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm just imagining.
[SPEAKER_13]: But here in the background... Turn it up a little bit.
[SPEAKER_13]: We have Dragon Force.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think this cheated a little bit though.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is using one of those external Mario Paint emulator things.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, but still.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, same idea.
[SPEAKER_13]: I know.
[SPEAKER_13]: I included basically a lot of those just because I thought they were fun.
[SPEAKER_13]: But yeah, there were the mini games called... A fly swatting game called Coffee Break or Nat Attack.
[SPEAKER_13]: And you played as the Glove Hand, which as we all know was the boss in the Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_13]: games, right?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: and it holds fly swatter and it has to swat things.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love Nat Attack.
[SPEAKER_13]: There was also a little mini-game on the title screen where you could click the letters to have a certain sequence of actions go on.
[SPEAKER_13]: And then you could change the music.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'd have Yoshi show up and paint the background.
[SPEAKER_13]: And also, this is a game that has a particular... Yeah, I put Power Rangers on there too because it's funny.
[SPEAKER_13]: But have you ever heard of a Totoka song, Rob?
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_13]: Kazumi Totoka was the guy who did a lot of Nintendo music.
[SPEAKER_13]: And there's a song that is basically his little 19-note song that shows up in all the games he does stuff on.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's a little Easter egg.
[SPEAKER_13]: And it shows up... Oh, I have heard of that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have heard of that, yes.
[SPEAKER_13]: But for anyone who doesn't know, on Animal Crossing, it actually was K.K.'
[SPEAKER_13]: 's song.
[SPEAKER_13]: In Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, that's when it... It was actually...
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: This is the song, um, uh, Airman, uh, La, Taos and I, I think, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't want to point out, this one is done in a legitimate Mario Paint.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, that one was.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I thought it was very well done.
[SPEAKER_13]: Um, but anyway, um, the first episode of Homestar Runner was animated in Mario Paint.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's so awesome.
[SPEAKER_13]: There have been sequels.
[SPEAKER_13]: There was one on the Nintendo 64DD called Mario Artist, which was a launch title, and it brought out the mouse for the Nintendo 64, and it was to make 3D polygonal models, and you could actually insert images onto these 3D models using the Nintendo 64 capture cartridge, and then share your work with the communication kit online.
[SPEAKER_13]: Although we didn't, of course, get that over here, but Mario Paint did have a sort of appearance in WarioWare Touched as WarioPaint.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_13]: And you had the turntable and the toy room and all that.
[SPEAKER_13]: And the Fly Splitting game was in WarioWare Mega Micro Games.
[SPEAKER_13]: And Wii Photo Channel has an editing system that's similar to Mario Paint.
[SPEAKER_13]: And then, like we were mentioning before, there have been standalone applications of the music program.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I had to put that one on there.
[SPEAKER_13]: You've been paint rolled.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, the game is Mario Paint.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is your classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mario Paint!
[SPEAKER_06]: Available on the Super Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_06]: With yet another one of Nintendo's famous peripherals.
[SPEAKER_06]: The mouse.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was only on one game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to say there was one other game that you could use it with.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think you could also use it on the gun games.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to say, couldn't you use it on, was it Lemmings you could use it on?
[SPEAKER_13]: Lemmings, Lemmings you could.
[SPEAKER_13]: Lemmings was one.
[SPEAKER_13]: In fact, I think I remember that actually being sort of a feature of it, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_06]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_13]: Lemmings kind of irritated me, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, that's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Classic Game of the Week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, that's going to do it for Part A of our show tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: But stay tuned.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's plenty more to come.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're only halfway there.
[SPEAKER_06]: In Part B tonight, your phone calls and more news, including some updates on Mortal Kombat vs. DC Universe, Batman Arkham Asylum, and some news about Capcom, and some more Xbox bundles coming soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we're going to take a quick break, but we'll be back in just a little bit with more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_17]: So you've got a bunch of websites and podcasts about anime, manga, or video games, but you just don't have the time to read and listen to them all.
[SPEAKER_17]: When are you actually going to find the time to play games or watch anime?
[SPEAKER_16]: That's why there's Anigamers.
[SPEAKER_16]: Not only are we a comprehensive anime, manga, and video game blog with news and reviews, but we've also got a podcast.
[SPEAKER_00]: Tune in to hear our insightful conversation about your favorite geeky topics.
[SPEAKER_00]: We do news, reviews, con reports, debates, and even recorded convention panels.
[SPEAKER_16]: Plus, you can expect something different from the Antigamers podcast every time.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's because we always bring in new co-hosts, including our own staff, other podcasters, and industry insiders.
[SPEAKER_00]: To subscribe, visit www.annagamers.com or search for us in the iTunes Store.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Annie Gamers Podcast.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because we all need another anime and gaming podcast.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, this is your buddy Rob Roberts here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Recently, I have become appalled at some of the language that people use on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_01]: Please, stop spewing hate speech on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_01]: It doesn't make you look cool, it won't get you any friends, and at the end of the day, you still have an incredibly small penis.
[SPEAKER_03]: Welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a little old school bumper bringing us back there.
[SPEAKER_13]: That was my Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: That is like a million different people yelling out acronyms.
[SPEAKER_06]: I still don't know what they mean to this day.
[SPEAKER_13]: That was Megumi doing GGPO.
[SPEAKER_06]: What does that even mean?
[SPEAKER_13]: Good game, peace out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, so yeah, those are our friends in StepSquad.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is there still a StepSquad that plays DDR?
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm sure StepSquad is still around.
[SPEAKER_13]: Although, honestly, the last time I saw Jahi, every time I ever see him is like randomly in Japantown.
[SPEAKER_13]: Like when I'm not even trying.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I ran into Wendell at Faname last year.
[SPEAKER_13]: I've seen him a few times recently.
[SPEAKER_13]: And once at YaoiCon.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think he was working security or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, very cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: VXJ6V's in chat and says, I asked that four years ago when I was on the show and I guess I forgot what GGPL means.
[SPEAKER_06]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: What, Loki?
[SPEAKER_04]: Before we started the second half here, I wanted to mention something I mentioned to you yesterday.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_04]: We all got 14-day trials to World of Warcraft from PAX, and my wife wants to try Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh my god, the rapture is coming.
[SPEAKER_04]: Start praying.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow, is she really going to do it?
[SPEAKER_06]: I think she is.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was going to say, she hates games, but she's going to start playing WoW.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, she's going to try the 14-day trial.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow, amazing.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm going to go ahead and jump the gun a little bit for emails.
[SPEAKER_13]: We got one from Sakura Max.
[SPEAKER_13]: This is from my cell phone.
[SPEAKER_13]: I survived the hurricane.
[SPEAKER_13]: No electricity.
[SPEAKER_13]: Minimal damage to my house.
[SPEAKER_13]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, thank you for reminding.
[SPEAKER_06]: There was that horrible hurricane that happened, and we hope any listener who is potentially impacted by that is doing okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: From what I hear, it's a lot of really, really bad damage, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Last time I checked, I hope I don't make an ass of myself, but last time I checked, it didn't sound like the fatalities were nearly as bad as the last time we had a major hurricane in this country.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I guess that's progress.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: And to respond to the chatroom, I'm not necessarily encouraging her to play.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's something she wants to try because everyone keeps talking about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: She feels left out.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if I would start playing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know if I want to.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sharan in chat has a very strong opinion.
[SPEAKER_06]: If Loki wants to help Nelly with World of Warcraft, he should just get her a real RPG instead.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ooh, burn.
[SPEAKER_06]: She doesn't have the patience for that stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: For the record, I actually, I'm not going back in the chat room because I keep getting dropped.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, we're having some network problems here in studio.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's annoying!
[SPEAKER_06]: Just another night here at OLR, so I guess maybe somebody will be buying me a new router soon, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to get into some gaming news tonight here at Orange Launch Radio, some more.
[SPEAKER_06]: We haven't even talked at all really about Xbox 360 news, and I think that's where we're going to start tonight, right Loki?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_04]: There was of course some rumors coming out of PAX about a possible new...
[SPEAKER_04]: Halo game coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then people realize, oh, it's just the map pack and there was new achievements that got leaked out and all that fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, those new achievements have been confirmed as actual achievements that will be coming to Halo 3 and they're coming to Halo 3 later this month.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you can expect for, I guess, I don't know how many new points they're going to add to it, but a whole bunch of new achievements.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess they'll come out with a new map pack.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that'd be kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_04]: and it's part of their title update too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, hooray for them doing a big update.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be free?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: We hope.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: The update will be free.
[SPEAKER_04]: So the new achievements will probably be free, but map pack, probably not.
[SPEAKER_04]: But remember, and not to discourage people buying it, but remember all those other map packs that they had out there?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, those eventually become free anyway, so... Dope.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it's a rental.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: Big Dumb Fun has been ruined this week thanks to a leaked list of achievements.
[SPEAKER_06]: Xbox360achievements.org, hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: They were just doing their job.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what they do.
[SPEAKER_06]: They uncover achievements as soon as they find out about them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, it turns out the achievement list spoils the entire character roster for Mortal Kombat vs. DC Universe.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_06]: So now we know who's in the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Midway kind of danced around this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Obviously, you know someone was pissed.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know somebody's head was rolling after this.
[SPEAKER_06]: They initially said, we have not officially released it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then they came back and said, yeah, okay, it's true.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dongle between our legs.
[SPEAKER_06]: Run away.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yipe, yipe, yipe.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, so here's the characters from Mortal Kombat.
[SPEAKER_06]: Baraka, Jax, Kano, Katana, Liu Kang, Raiden, Scorpion, Shang Tsung, Shao Kahn, Sonya, and Sub-Zero.
[SPEAKER_06]: DC Universe
[SPEAKER_06]: DC Universe, Catwoman, Darkseed, Deathstroke, Darkseid,
[SPEAKER_06]: Flash, Green Lantern, The Joker, Lex Luthor, Shazam, Superman, and Wonder Woman
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, but that's what they're going to refer to him as in the game, probably, I guess, because if they're pulling this off the achievement list, they must be referring to him as that in the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I'm excited.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now we can finally throw down Wonder Woman vs. Catwoman.
[SPEAKER_06]: That'll be awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Looking forward to that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, this game comes out soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: Be on the lookout for it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It'll be out before the holidays.
[SPEAKER_06]: and, uh, there you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: November 19th, if I remember correctly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just in time for Thanksgiving.
[SPEAKER_13]: I just wish they'd have, like, other unlockable characters later on.
[SPEAKER_13]: That would be neat.
[SPEAKER_06]: They may, and they may have pay-to-unlock characters.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, this is the first Mortal Kombat on the next-gen system, am I right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, so who knows?
[SPEAKER_06]: They might have the downloadable characters.
[SPEAKER_06]: That'd be kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: DC Universe, DC Universe
[SPEAKER_13]: Mark Hamill is the one.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_13]: When I think Joker, when I'm not thinking of the comic books, I'm thinking of animated series Joker just because he's so goofball.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think it's cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: You don't think about the movies, Heath Ledger, Jack Nicholson?
[SPEAKER_13]: I have not seen Dark Knight, remember?
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm going to see it in IMAX.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was pretty impressive.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's here.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know.
[SPEAKER_13]: When I go see it, it will be in IMAX.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have fun.
[SPEAKER_13]: But this makes me very, very, very, very giddy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actdeft agrees in chatroom.
[SPEAKER_06]: Chat.orange.com says Mark Hamill is the Joker and Solid Goomba simply says, fuck yeah, Mark Hamill.
[SPEAKER_06]: What is it about Mark Hamill that makes him so fucking amazing?
[SPEAKER_13]: He does the best Joker.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_13]: Then he was, what was it in Jay and Silent Bob Cockknocker?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, he was also in Jay and Silent Bob Strikeback.
[SPEAKER_13]: But there's more news.
[SPEAKER_13]: You could appear in the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Really?
[SPEAKER_06]: Me?
[SPEAKER_13]: There could be Rob in the game.
[SPEAKER_13]: Little me?
[SPEAKER_13]: There is a contest right now from GI that will allow the winner to become an Arkham inmate.
[SPEAKER_13]: And you get your cell decked out with personal photos and wall scribbles.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's more of a Loki role.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't you think?
[SPEAKER_13]: I would be all over that.
[SPEAKER_13]: And all of my graffiti would be, Hi Mom, I'm in jail.
[SPEAKER_13]: I like it here.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think, and I don't know if Travis still does this on Under Station Live, but maybe my voice could be something like, I've been here for seven years, the medication doesn't work.
[SPEAKER_06]: Does he still do that on Under Station Live?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't even know.
[SPEAKER_06]: That sounds weird.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, there was this old soundbite he used to play all the freaking time of this guy going, I've been here for seven years.
[SPEAKER_06]: DJ Dark Knight says, I can't see Jamie being in jail.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, how little you know Jamie.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've been in jail before.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alabama, they make you either sleep or read the Bible.
[SPEAKER_06]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_13]: And then my mom came and got me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: I never knew that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Six years and I never knew that Jamie was in jail.
[SPEAKER_13]: There's quite a bit about me you don't know, Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now the internet snows.
[SPEAKER_04]: It wasn't real jail.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: It wasn't real jail.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: We all did dumb shit as a kid.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, of course, with the announcement of the price drop last week, the Xbox sales numbers are apparently doubling, according to Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I guess we'll have to see when the MPD numbers come out at the beginning of October.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that's pretty promising.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, not a big surprise that, I don't know...
[SPEAKER_04]: It's selling well when it's cheaper.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, that's, I guess, a shocker to a lot of people.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, wait, no, it's not.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is it Christmas yet?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it's going to be interesting to see what happens with this.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what I'm curious.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is this a trend that's going to continue through Christmas?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are Xbox 360s now going to sell because everybody got a Wii last Christmas?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_04]: I still hear, and it really irks me, not that I'm picking sides or anything, but
[SPEAKER_03]: But you are.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really, I'm not.
[SPEAKER_04]: But when Sony comes out and says, oh yeah, we're winning.
[SPEAKER_04]: How are you winning when you have a quarter of the market?
[SPEAKER_04]: Abba.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: Listen, Abba ain't gonna do shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bite your tongue.
[SPEAKER_04]: Abba ain't gonna do shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what I'm saying.
[SPEAKER_04]: No one buys SingStar.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, nobody.
[SPEAKER_04]: Unless you're in Europe.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hate you.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know you anymore.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just own you as a friend.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought Mamma Mia sucked.
[SPEAKER_04]: Get out of my house!
[SPEAKER_04]: It just irks me when they say that they're winning, but it's like, dude, listen, you're not even close to winning.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, if you were like, you know, the Wii back in June when you were like 10,000 units away from becoming number one, yeah, that's close to winning.
[SPEAKER_04]: When you're millions of units behind, that's not close to winning.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, so don't talk that you're going to do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're going to do it by like year's end.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're not.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're not going to do it by year's end.
[SPEAKER_04]: 2011, okay, so stop it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, are you saying that SingStarAba's not going to sell well?
[SPEAKER_06]: Would you care to make a little wager on SingStarAba selling well or not?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I'm not.
[SPEAKER_06]: It doesn't have to be Tingle.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can think of far better punishments.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it's not.
[SPEAKER_06]: Damn.
[SPEAKER_06]: Everybody make chicken noises at Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll think about it, but I'm pretty sure it's not.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, he said I think about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I gotta do my research.
[SPEAKER_13]: Rob, I will totally play Singstar with you.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know.
[SPEAKER_13]: You're getting the ABBA one, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: The chat room is demanding it on Justin TV when it comes out.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see how the Xbox 360 sells after the price drop.
[SPEAKER_06]: Moving on into Christmas, I think they're going to continue to sell pretty well.
[SPEAKER_06]: The question is, will they overtake Nintendo or will Sony answer them?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's another one.
[SPEAKER_06]: A lot of people seem doubtful, but who knows?
[SPEAKER_06]: Another game that a lot of folks have been playing on their Xbox 360s as well as their PlayStation 3s, Burnout Paradise.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the long-awaited motorcycle download is coming on September 18th.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's actually a new patch, basically.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a free download update.
[SPEAKER_06]: 38 new clock race events, dynamic weather events, effects...
[SPEAKER_06]: Dynamic Weather Effects, a day-night cycle, meaning the game goes up from day to night, 70 new challenges in the Freeburns thing, and motorcycles.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that's pretty cool, but when are they adding the airplanes?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what I want to know, because they're talking about adding airplanes.
[SPEAKER_13]: What about giant enemy crabs?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, I want to be able to drive a giant enemy crab.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um...
[SPEAKER_06]: This is one of those games that I played for like three days and I never played again, and I keep thinking I need to go back and play it again.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is giving me the incentive to do so, so I'm definitely going to have to check it out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sounds pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have you been playing any Burnout Paradise, Loki, or is this kind of put it away?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I just noticed the other day that I still have my copy of Burnout Paradise sitting on a shelf.
[SPEAKER_04]: um it just came out at a bad time from what I remember I need to go back and look look at it again it was better than the last one but I don't know it's just when the next big game came out I forgot about it and sadly enough you know with like Rock Band 2 and stuff when Saints Row 2 comes out I'm gonna forget about Rock Band 2 never I'll never forget about Rock Band 2 hey they're doing a pretty good job trying to extend the life of it with the challenges and everything but anyway let's move on
[SPEAKER_13]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, please.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, you know one of my favorite ever companies is Capcom, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_13]: They were nice to me.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know why they were mean to you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do we have to go back there again?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because don't get me started.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do not go there.
[SPEAKER_13]: Capcom is planning on doing all of their major titles on multiple platforms to maximize their impact in the United States, especially outside of Japan.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's actually quoted as saying basically where the consoles are practically waging war on one another.
[SPEAKER_13]: and their annual report.
[SPEAKER_13]: It said, completing implementation of multi-platform development on major titles means that all major titles launched during the next fiscal year or thereafter will be developed as multi-platform games.
[SPEAKER_13]: So that's why we should be, that's why Devil May Cry 4, for example.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or Mega Man 9.
[SPEAKER_13]: Mega Man 9, exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: A lot of us assumed it was going to be WiiWare only and then suddenly it's shown up everywhere.
[SPEAKER_13]: MT Framework is actually supposed to be for PC, Xbox 360, and PS3 development Resident Evil 5, Street Fighter 4 are among the list and so they're also thinking about including a few more casual games like for Wii and other more casual game systems
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you talking about Man of Power Battles?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it was an actual side-scroller in the vein of the Nintendo games, but with better graphics at the time, because it was on PC.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, maybe somebody in the chatroom knows more about this and can remember.
[SPEAKER_06]: I actually bought this game way back when, in the early 90s, and it had three boss monsters, so it was short.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I remember one of them was electricity-based, as you remember.
[SPEAKER_06]: It wasn't based on... They were new Mega Man monsters.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was a completely different Mega Man game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not crazy.
[SPEAKER_13]: well in other news they also are they stated also again in their annual report Capcom did that there are more western focused titles in development one of them named Dark Void if you know we remember that and they plan to aggressively acquire partners and other studios especially independent developers the ones that will share their vision so I think that that's
[SPEAKER_13]: Sounding to me like a potential good thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I found the information on Wikipedia.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you now?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, it was by Hitech Expressions.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was released in 1990.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was just licensed by Capcom.
[SPEAKER_06]: There were three robot masters, Voltman, Sonicman, and Dynaman.
[SPEAKER_06]: And there were only two levels in the Wily Fortress.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it was a short game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I'd say.
[SPEAKER_06]: And there were other versions on PC, I guess, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: I never knew about those.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just had the first one.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think the PC versions were very good.
[SPEAKER_06]: They were cool when I was a kid, but I don't think they're cool now.
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_13]: Thanks to you.
[SPEAKER_13]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_13]: The Airman Can't Be Defeated song.
[SPEAKER_06]: Whose fault is that?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yours.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, some things that are good come in threes, I guess, including a bundle that's being released by Microsoft coming out later this holiday.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a brand new 12-month live gold kit, and it's going to come with Project Gotham Racing 4, a 12-plus-one-month card of live, and the Xbox...
[SPEAKER_04]: 360 Messenger Kit and it's going to run you $69.99.
[SPEAKER_04]: This was rumored to be coming out from the GameStop Expo although it's on their website now and I personally know it's coming out so it is coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of a good deal.
[SPEAKER_04]: There was some other bundle that they were talking about coming out as well that I haven't heard anything on but I know this one for sure is coming out.
[SPEAKER_06]: RedRingsOfDeath.com
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: apparently he went on and talked about these two different Red Ring of Death scenarios a reproducible crash that could happen in NBA 2K6 was one game that you could reproduce the crash in and apparently some dashboard update bugs in Dead Rising apparently he's being very standoffish about it he doesn't care that the former employer of his wants to sue him and says if they want to come after me, bring it on
[SPEAKER_06]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, you know, he did probably violate the terms of employment that he had with Microsoft and all these companies that he was working through.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, you do kind of don't talk about the products like this, especially on a website.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a little... I hope he knows what he's talking about because he's going to have to prove, well...
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I guess he's going to have to prove that he's telling the truth.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkTetsuya says, wow, the cojones on this guy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, for real.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ranma says, didn't he sign an NDA that forbade him from saying this?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sure he must have.
[SPEAKER_13]: If he didn't sign the NDA, unless it was specific, or I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe, but even still though, I mean, they can get him on that, but at the same time, I mean, he's hoping to open like a whole other can of worms with, you know, Microsoft knew about these defects and they didn't do anything about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ah, I see, so he's trying to be a hero, basically.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, we know what happens to heroes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: They become martyrs.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, let's hope it doesn't get that bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, well, there you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll keep you updated if we hear anything else in the adventures of this guy and his soon-to-be legal troubles.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, something that might not be soon to happen.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, they're talking about it, but I'm still thinking that it'll be out when another title with its name comes out.
[SPEAKER_13]: There's supposed to be a Duke Nukem movie.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: Scott Fay, the one who's doing Max Payne, was saying that he's working on a movie scenario that he thinks will do the character and the series justice.
[SPEAKER_13]: But
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm honestly really expecting to see it more along the lines of when Duke Nukem Forever comes out.
[SPEAKER_13]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_13]: But he also says that Depth Entertainment will be doing with trying to work on a few other cross-media franchises going into games and film.
[SPEAKER_13]: And
[SPEAKER_13]: They actually are still at work at doing American McGee's Alice.
[SPEAKER_13]: And Sarah Michelle Gellar isn't doing that anymore, by the way.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know she changed her last name officially for her husband?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's one of those Hollywood relationships that has actually stayed together, so good for them.
[SPEAKER_13]: As an anniversary present, I thought that was really sweet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, if you want to hear something even more ridiculous, there was a rumor coming around about a Craigslist entry that said they were casting for a Rock Band 2 TV show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, apparently it is true, and it's going to be officially launched next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rock Band 2, the show, and...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: And what exactly will be on the Rock Band show?
[SPEAKER_06]: Just watching people play Rock Band?
[SPEAKER_04]: Basically, you're going to follow... I guess they're going to set up some band teams or whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a 30-minute commercial for the game is what it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Basically, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, when you're MTV and you put out the game, you can kind of do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Besides, you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't see this being much worse than some of the other programming on that station.
[SPEAKER_04]: True, I guess it would be better than The Hills.
[SPEAKER_06]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you know, I don't know about you guys, but when I hear about one of my favorite music games, Jumping the Shark, and becoming a half-hour commercial TV series, and reminding us why MTV is a little bit poison for this series, or a lot of it poison, I get very angsty.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know about you guys, but it makes me just want to get out the angst in a segment we call the FUs of the Week.
[SPEAKER_13]: My FU goes to bullshit and the mouths it spews from.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: My FU goes to EA for saying that the Rock Band 2 drums are supposed to be out today and not actually shipping the Rock Band 2 drums to anybody, so it's a big clusterfuck.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: My FU goes to whatever little animal decided to crawl under our house and die.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because it happened on, I guess, Friday when we started noticing that something smells like death.
[SPEAKER_06]: So now the animal control people aren't going to be able to even come out until Monday because we think it's a cat.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because there was a cat that was sometimes in our backyard that just looked like hell.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's not around anymore.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, you know, although I am sad for little kitty, F you to deciding to die under our house and not in, say, the neighbor's pool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just gross.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's it for the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_06]: But boy, we get into some FUs of the century when we talk about some of the gaming industry's biggest controversies they've ever had.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is on a website called MCVUK.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: They ran a top ten list this week of gaming's biggest controversies.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, if you want to get your website on Digg, just add a top ten list.
[SPEAKER_06]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's all you ever see on Digg are these top ten lists from these sites I'd never heard of until I see the top ten list.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, there you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow, here's a quick rundown of what the controversies are.
[SPEAKER_06]: Number one...
[SPEAKER_06]: Night Trap with Dana Plato
[SPEAKER_06]: Caramageddon Caramageddon
[SPEAKER_13]: Caramageddon!
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, you know, in Summer Showdown for the U.S.
[SPEAKER_13]: one they put in, well, I think it was the U.S.
[SPEAKER_13]: one they had sweat instead of blood like in the Japanese one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, a little silly.
[SPEAKER_06]: And in the German one, they had robots.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not even people, but robots that you ran over.
[SPEAKER_06]: America's Army is number four, and it has to do with that, you know, the game was developed and is being used as a recruitment tool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ubisoft kind of has gotten itself in a little bit of trouble for publishing the console version of the title.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently, there was like a demonstration outside of their offices after this whole thing, because they actually went and published a console version, and that was...
[SPEAKER_06]: Really bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's basically a giant recruitment tool, which in a way is controversial in itself.
[SPEAKER_06]: Number five was something called Murder by PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently it was some type of story that was actually released.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, it was a headline that was actually in a paper on the Daily Mail.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it was actually a story about a 14-year-old kid who was murdered by a 17-year-old kid.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the newspaper claimed that the kid was obsessed with Manhunt.
[SPEAKER_06]: And by the way, police did say there was absolutely no link between the game and the killing.
[SPEAKER_06]: But yet that headline, Murder by PlayStation, giant bold letters, still exists.
[SPEAKER_06]: Number 6 on the list, The Guy Game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Remember The Guy Game, Loki?
[SPEAKER_06]: We covered The Guy Game on this program.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Guy Game was awesome, except for the 17-year-old that got in it.
[SPEAKER_06]: That caused the game to get pulled from shelves everywhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dude, seriously.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, yeah, because tits on a 17-year-old really change a lot in a year.
[SPEAKER_04]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's gay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I don't... Actually, no, it wouldn't be gay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I don't... Unless you're a woman.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because that game screws another of the same gender.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was just... I mean, obviously, it's a big no-no and very irresponsible.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's her fault anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: She lied about her age.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just irresponsible.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dumb bitch.
[SPEAKER_06]: But the game... They could be having Guy Game 4 by now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, if you cut this little element out of the game, we'd be on, like, Guy Game, you know, on Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_06]: It would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hell yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Uh...
[SPEAKER_06]: Number 7, Hot Coffee, All I Need to Say.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you don't know enough about that by now, where have you been?
[SPEAKER_06]: Number 8 was when the BBFC tackled Ban Hunt 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course, there was all the controversy around that, and then that got banned, and then it wasn't, and then the game sucked anyway, remember?
[SPEAKER_06]: Number 9 was Goat Gate, which is another way to refer to, remember the Greek god launch party for God of War 2 over in Europe?
[SPEAKER_06]: And they actually slaughtered a live goat.
[SPEAKER_06]: Remember that?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think that... Marketing genius over there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dot, dot, dot.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's all I have to say.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then the last controversy on the list, because I know you're all loving this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sony versus God.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it has to do with the fact that the Church of England was actually used, Manchester Cathedral, its church, was actually used in Resistance Fall of Man, and they were not happy about that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I remember that we covered that on the show a little while ago so there you have it the top 10 biggest controversies according to MCV UK so it is a little more UK based hence why we had a couple of those in there but I would say UK or not those are pretty good entries on the list very controversial anything you think they left off
[SPEAKER_06]: Remember the PSP ad that was almost racist because it had the white and the black and it was bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: Remember that?
[SPEAKER_06]: That was somehow left off the list.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just another brilliant Sony marketing scheme from the day.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anything else you guys can think of?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think they hit most of the good ones.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see in chat.
[SPEAKER_06]: Chat.OrangeLaunchRadio.com if anybody thinks of anything.
[SPEAKER_06]: No Custer's Revenge either.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's usually a Custer's Revenge that shows up on a list like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, let's see what you guys have to say in our mailbag.
[SPEAKER_06]: Every week you guys email us, mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com and we read your emails here live on the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: So let's open up ye olde mailbag and see what emails we've got.
[SPEAKER_13]: First email comes from Cheeseburger and it says, I'm sorry I got you mad last week.
[SPEAKER_13]: Can you please tell me more about Gatchaman, please?
[SPEAKER_13]: Did I spell that right?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes, you did spell it right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Gatchaman is awesome!
[SPEAKER_13]: 1972 anime character designs done by Amano.
[SPEAKER_13]: Just go look it up on Wikipedia and then go watch all of it.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's the only way you'll appease me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hey, OLR crew.
[SPEAKER_13]: This next email, by the way.
[SPEAKER_13]: After listening to last week's show, I figured it right in to clarify on what the Rob D was saying about me shaking while at the mic.
[SPEAKER_13]: It wasn't while at the mic that my hands started to shake, but after.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was a bit of a rush being on the air with a bunch of internet celebrities who are too humble to admit they really are celebrities, however minor.
[SPEAKER_13]: I am not.
[SPEAKER_13]: I am actually egotistical enough to admit my celebrity-dom on the internet.
[SPEAKER_13]: Curse you, Adrenaline!
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyway, it was great meeting you all at PAX and was very glad that I made it to Wild Ginger that night in one piece as the food and conversation were awesome.
[SPEAKER_13]: Who knew mango could make pork taste like beef?
[SPEAKER_06]: This is talking about the Chinese restaurant all us all games people went to, yeah?
[SPEAKER_13]: As I ordered the mango pork and it was freaking fantastic.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, the food I had was good too.
[SPEAKER_13]: Plus I had to be the best stand pad thai I've ever had.
[SPEAKER_13]: It made being lost in the scuzzy part of Seattle at night totally worth it.
[SPEAKER_13]: That was really good pad thai.
[SPEAKER_13]: I agree with that because I had some too.
[SPEAKER_13]: I didn't just write to reminisce and sing praises though.
[SPEAKER_13]: A few episodes back you guys were talking about Dragon's Lair and Space Ace and they should be put on PS3.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well good news, not only are they playable on PS3, but any Blu-ray player...
[SPEAKER_13]: I've actually had them in stock where I work for quite some time now, and I'm kind of shocked they aren't on shelves with the games at other stores as well.
[SPEAKER_13]: You can put links on Amazon.
[SPEAKER_13]: Actually, I think the reason I didn't get them is because I've already got the HD versions for PC.
[SPEAKER_13]: But I hope I passed the grammar Nazi test here.
[SPEAKER_13]: You almost did, but for right is W-R-I-T-E, not R-I-G-H-T.
[SPEAKER_13]: I can't wait until next year's PAX, assuming I can go.
[SPEAKER_13]: Cheers, Decipher.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_13]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_13]: This email was brought to you by the OLR Mailbag, home of the never-ending Olive Garden references.
[SPEAKER_06]: I actually haven't had an Olive Garden reference in a little while, but there you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_13]: Rob, let's go to Olive Garden.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dude, I really want Olive Garden.
[SPEAKER_13]: We have to.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know where I went this week?
[SPEAKER_06]: It was Carino's.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: I've never been there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nom, nom, nom.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'd take you to Pasquale's, but I don't think they have anything light, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or we should go to a little... They have a little joint here in Sacramento called Español, which is the Italian place with a Spanish name.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's really good.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have a very yummy minestrone soup.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mmm, Orange Lounge Foodio.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hey, OLR.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just have to say, I love that on this show when we're not talking about video games, we're talking about food.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_13]: I have gushy foods.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ooh, Rob D says Never Ending Pasta is going on at Olive Garden right now.
[SPEAKER_13]: Dude, we are there, okay?
[SPEAKER_13]: Hey, OLR, I read this on the FAQs of EA's new Sports World site, which is their online community for their sports games.
[SPEAKER_13]: One of the questions is why there's no female avatar option.
[SPEAKER_13]: Their response was, quote, question, why is there no female avatar image?
[SPEAKER_13]: In an effort to align EA Sports World with our primary user base, the decision was made to use a male avatar image for its launch.
[SPEAKER_13]: However, a female avatar image is planned for future releases soon.
[SPEAKER_13]: is it just me or are they making an assumption about who plays their games?
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm not a female but I think that it is kind of sexist to gear a sports game towards males only and assume that all the women are playing Barbie Island Princess or bake cakes although cakes are great
[SPEAKER_13]: Maybe I am completely stupid and don't see why this is okay, but I'm sure many women across the world play sports games and other types of traditionally male games like GTA, other FPSs, etc.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, thanks for reading this, and remember, if you are in the All Games chatroom, DMN can't kick you.
[SPEAKER_13]: The cake is light, PKJr92, Yaris sucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you have to understand that until EA Sports releases, you know...
[SPEAKER_04]: DinnerMaking09, you know, they're not going to have female avatars, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_06]: TheRobD says in chat, translation, their response was, girls don't play games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is this true, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_06]: Do girls not play games?
[SPEAKER_13]: I beg to differ.
[SPEAKER_06]: I had a feeling.
[SPEAKER_06]: I bet we have some more listeners out there that beg to differ as well.
[SPEAKER_13]: Remember though, Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_13]: Remember me telling you that there was a football game I actually liked?
[SPEAKER_06]: Tecmo Bowl.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, it wasn't Tecmo Bowl.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was...
[SPEAKER_13]: Great, now I can't remember, but it had a cool name.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was that one football game that was on Super Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_06]: Must have had a lasting impression.
[SPEAKER_13]: I can never remember the name of it, too.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was the problem with it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Was it with the four-player thing?
[SPEAKER_06]: Was it Super Tecmo Bowl?
[SPEAKER_13]: No, it wasn't Tecmo Bowl anything.
[SPEAKER_06]: High Impact High Impact, thank you, it was super high impact I just had a feeling, and I said that before I saw DarkTips to be a Satan shit I was gonna say also that, um, yeah, girls don't play games and EA doesn't release games that aren't buggy That just means that girls play good games You know how I feel about sports games, you guys Look, I respect those of you guys that choose to play them, but for me, Tecmo Bowl or GTFO No, it's all about that hockey game on Saturn
[SPEAKER_06]: or Blades of Steel.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hockey is fantastic too because blood bounces on ice.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know NHL 09 came out this last week.
[SPEAKER_06]: We should check it out just for fun.
[SPEAKER_13]: I used to watch hockey regularly.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's get into sports games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wouldn't buy NHL 09.
[SPEAKER_13]: I want a rugby game.
[SPEAKER_13]: I want someone to send me a rugby game, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: apparently it's got some sort of memory leak in the cache file on the on your hard drive and will stop working after a while oh shit can you imagine if we came on the show one week and during how was your gaming week suddenly it's like Jamie's talking about yeah I played NHL 09 this week I'm like yeah I played Madden Loki's like I played Hello Kitty Island Adventure and then we never mind no it would be like I was gonna say then we'd be AGI but you know
[SPEAKER_13]: If you wanted to do the complete role reversal here, I would be playing Imagine Babies, and Rob would be playing Yaris, and Matt would be playing the Tingle game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a tangle game, seriously.
[SPEAKER_04]: For April Fool's Day next year.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, next email, next email.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hey guys, Dan Shadow here.
[SPEAKER_13]: I've been meaning to email you guys for quite some time, but I've been very busy lately.
[SPEAKER_13]: Welcome to the club.
[SPEAKER_13]: If this email seems long, it's because with every new episode, there's a new subject to talk about.
[SPEAKER_13]: This segment goes to Rob.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hi Rob!
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi me!
[SPEAKER_06]: Who's this from?
[SPEAKER_13]: Dan Shadow.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi Dan Shadow.
[SPEAKER_13]: A while back you mentioned going out to Long Beach and visiting the Queen Mary.
[SPEAKER_13]: I laughed when you mentioned that because I currently live in Long Beach and next year I will be getting married on the Queen Mary.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a big boat.
[SPEAKER_13]: My wedding will be booze themed.
[SPEAKER_13]: Chew on that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Aww.
[SPEAKER_13]: I also wanted to point out that I am your Brazilian listener.
[SPEAKER_13]: I haven't been there in 10 years because, well, it's just better to live here.
[SPEAKER_13]: However, I will return next summer to have my new wife meet my family there.
[SPEAKER_13]: Brazilian listener!
[SPEAKER_06]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've been craving Brazilian grill.
[SPEAKER_06]: You don't even know how long.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what I'm talking about.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like the Espatuse place in San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've never been there, Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, they have a thing like it in Sacramento now called Taste of Brazil or something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: And basically that's where they bring the big slabs of meat on the swords and just slice off a slab of meat.
[SPEAKER_13]: Do we have to order in Portuguese?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I don't believe you do.
[SPEAKER_06]: You don't order at all.
[SPEAKER_06]: You just pay.
[SPEAKER_06]: You have a little dial.
[SPEAKER_06]: Green means go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Red means stop.
[SPEAKER_13]: Sweet.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm so there when I'm eating meat again.
[SPEAKER_13]: Thinking about playing Warhammer Online?
[SPEAKER_13]: Do it!
[SPEAKER_13]: I've been in the closed and open beta, and I can tell you right now it's worth it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Here's an example.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's say you're a squig hunter, and you want to drop aggro.
[SPEAKER_13]: You don't feign death.
[SPEAKER_13]: Instead, you will piss yourself, and the enemy won't touch you after that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, the orcs and goblins are on the comedic side, but if you want to be serious cool, then play as the high elves.
[SPEAKER_13]: I will be in the head start, so if you decide to get it, let me know and we can play on the same server.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, on the head server, sorry.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, it says I will be in the head start, so if you decide to play, blah blah.
[SPEAKER_13]: On another note, I can't wait for LittleBigPlanet.
[SPEAKER_13]: That seems like a game that can't possibly get old.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, and Rock Band 2 equals Party Night.
[SPEAKER_13]: This email is brought to you by StrongBad.
[SPEAKER_13]: Keeping my Wii alive with his never-ending style.
[SPEAKER_06]: I played Final Fantasy XI
[SPEAKER_06]: Star Trek Online!
[SPEAKER_06]: No!
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't do it, Rob!
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't do it!
[SPEAKER_06]: If you can level by yourself, then it's better.
[SPEAKER_06]: you can level, like let's say you're level 12 and your friend is level 70 your level 70 friend can cap himself to 12 and level with you and you guys both still get experience so you can level at any level, kinda neat I will stay level 1 forever seriously I will not be playing this bullshit Final Fantasy bullshit unless it's Penn and Teller's Final Fantasy bullshit then I'll play that
[SPEAKER_06]: I somehow don't see that happening.
[SPEAKER_13]: That should be a bullshit game.
[SPEAKER_13]: That'd be cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: I do see myself going out, at least checking out Warhammer for a month or two before I see myself going back to Fafixi.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, next email.
[SPEAKER_13]: Star Trek Online!
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, and then there's that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Star Trek Online!
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm hoping that gets delayed to 2010.
[SPEAKER_13]: Star Trek Online!
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, shut up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Read the next email.
[SPEAKER_06]: Shut up and read.
[SPEAKER_13]: Jeez, Rob.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, well, bite my big bloody left toe.
[SPEAKER_13]: Sorry, that's my right toe.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hey guys, I've been listening to your podcast for about the last year.
[SPEAKER_13]: Even though I can't listen to it live because I have school.
[SPEAKER_13]: You guys are my favorite podcast and I never miss your show.
[SPEAKER_13]: I haven't been able to get a 360 yet.
[SPEAKER_13]: It sucks because my mom and dad won't let me get one.
[SPEAKER_13]: They think that I shouldn't get another system even though I want to trade in my PS2.
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyway, since I have nothing to do and want to save money, I've been...
[SPEAKER_13]: I have been playing free MMOs.
[SPEAKER_13]: Here are a couple and what they are.
[SPEAKER_13]: S4 League.
[SPEAKER_13]: This game is a third-person shooter that has anime-style graphics and these make it so you can do flips and other cool stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_13]: And that's at S4League.com MapleStory.
[SPEAKER_13]: You've probably heard of this one, but if you haven't, it's a platforming MMO that's kind of like Super Mario Bros., but you use weapons.
[SPEAKER_13]: And that's at Nexon.com
[SPEAKER_13]: Again, these are all free and really fun.
[SPEAKER_13]: Thanks, guys.
[SPEAKER_13]: Keep up the great work.
[SPEAKER_13]: This email is brought to you by my Wii, PS2, GameCube, and any other system that I don't want anymore.
[SPEAKER_13]: Homes to the never-ending dust that collects on them because they're outdated and my parents don't let me trade them in.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alrighty.
[SPEAKER_13]: I also do have to commend you on your...
[SPEAKER_13]: Fairly decent sentence structure and grammar.
[SPEAKER_06]: Gold star for this listener.
[SPEAKER_13]: You get a smiley face.
[SPEAKER_06]: By the way, Rob D, I was snickering during that email because I read this comment in chat from Rob D talking about Penn & Teller's Final Fantasy XI bullshit.
[SPEAKER_06]: He says, wait, so you want Final Fantasy Desert Bus?
[SPEAKER_06]: Dude, you know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: Sometimes running from one end of the map to the other when you're not a high enough level to have a chocobo feels like playing Desert Bus.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not even fucking with you.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know what my whole thing was when I did play the game and was too low to actually make it across the desert without dying?
[SPEAKER_13]: I skirted the wall.
[SPEAKER_13]: I was doing maze business.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what you have to do.
[SPEAKER_13]: You skirt the wall and you hide.
[SPEAKER_13]: Like, oh my god, it's going to kill me.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, last one.
[SPEAKER_13]: Ready?
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: Dun, dun, dun, from J-Rod, who originated that joke.
[SPEAKER_13]: So we have to give him props.
[SPEAKER_06]: Props.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hi, OLR.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, I've been waiting all year for TNA Impact to come out, and now it's finally released.
[SPEAKER_13]: I see nothing but terrible reviews for it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Bad grapple system, only five slots for creative wrestlers, only a handful of moves, and so on.
[SPEAKER_13]: I really hope the other games I'm looking forward to this year, Dead Space and Silent Hill Homecoming, don't suck.
[SPEAKER_13]: How can a Silent Hill game suck, okay?
[SPEAKER_13]: So I'd like to ask, what was the biggest disappointment that you guys ever had to face with games you were highly anticipating?
[SPEAKER_13]: This email is sponsored by the Olive Garden Home of the Neverending Salads and Breadsticks.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, I have to say, one of the first ones that jumps into my mind was Nintendogs.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hate to say it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not that Nintendogs is a bad game, but I just got so hyped for it at E3 that the bar got set so high that the game just couldn't live up to it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It really couldn't.
[SPEAKER_06]: I tried.
[SPEAKER_13]: I remember one time Dan and I, this is when Dan and I were playing a lot of wrestling games and we rented at the time WWF, or was it?
[SPEAKER_13]: Rumble Roses
[SPEAKER_13]: Rumble Roses was great.
[SPEAKER_13]: But at any rate, Dan and I decided that we were going to rent the... No, it was Thunder.
[SPEAKER_13]: That was it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think it was WCW Thunder.
[SPEAKER_13]: We rented it, got it home, played it for 10 minutes, and called the Hollywood or blockbuster that we got it from and took it back.
[SPEAKER_13]: And they let us take out another game.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was that bad.
[SPEAKER_13]: I just remember that that has been the one... Even Spice World didn't disappoint me that badly.
[SPEAKER_06]: At least you knew what you were going to get with Spice World.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, shice.
[SPEAKER_06]: I got a night of endless laughs with Spice World.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess we were drunk, but it was really funny.
[SPEAKER_13]: There is one game that disappointed me, but it was Japanese release only.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was Super Producers.
[SPEAKER_13]: Super Producers was a game where you manage a pop idol's career.
[SPEAKER_13]: And it just disappointed me because it was a lot more language intense than I was prepared for.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gears of War, Halo 3, Bullet Witch, and... Oh, there's one more, I know it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um...
[SPEAKER_04]: Halo 3 Halo 2.5
[SPEAKER_06]: Rob D in chat says Mega Man X5 disappointed me a lot more recently that Infinite Undiscovery although I'm hearing if you can get past the first couple hours that suck it gets a lot better so I'm trying to force myself to play it more but now I have Rock Band I just won't play Rock Band all day
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: And no other emails then, huh?
[SPEAKER_06]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mailbag at OrangeLaunchRadio.com if you have some mail you would like to contribute for next week's show.
[SPEAKER_06]: In the meantime, a little more gaming news and then the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a couple hacking and cracking stories we have.
[SPEAKER_04]: The first one is a modification someone made using the Xbox 360 Messenger kit, and they turned it into a keyboard for the PSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: N.E.S.
[SPEAKER_04]: into a toaster
[SPEAKER_04]: and why?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because it's funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_06]: They made a Nintendo out of a toaster or they turned a Nintendo into a toaster?
[SPEAKER_04]: They have a toaster and they put a Nintendo inside of it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it actually has apparently some LED lights in the case that light up.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not sure if it lights up red like it's cooking because that would be pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yeah, NES toaster.
[SPEAKER_06]: The National Science Foundation gave $100,000 to do a study for World of Warcraft
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's a quote from the study or from the lady involved with the study.
[SPEAKER_06]: At least they mentioned them in more interviews.
[SPEAKER_06]: They talked more about color schemes, animations, architecture, and so on, more than American players.
[SPEAKER_06]: She goes on to say that the Chinese players, they actually don't really play with add-ons and modifications.
[SPEAKER_06]: They like the challenge of the core game, whereas in America we like to mod our game to hell.
[SPEAKER_06]: Kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: She's getting paid $100,000 to finish this research.
[SPEAKER_06]: She's doing it along with a student going after their doctoral, and will be doing some type of final paper that I'm sure will be published all over the internet when it's done.
[SPEAKER_06]: $100,000 to study WoW.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can really get a job doing anything.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I guess that's neat.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just kind of like, wow, there's a lot.
[SPEAKER_06]: But then you think about the complex layers, I guess there is a lot to study.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I'm just kind of curious, what will be contributed to society from the results?
[SPEAKER_06]: Is it a way for us to better understand each other through games?
[SPEAKER_13]: Why don't people just actually socially interact?
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, that's right, because people are scary.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: People are scary!
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, how about some more news?
[SPEAKER_06]: How about it?
[SPEAKER_13]: Would that make you giddy, Rob?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, speaking, because we did have an email earlier regarding... Warhammer?
[SPEAKER_13]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_13]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_13]: I stopped working.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, it was Warhammer.
[SPEAKER_13]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_13]: There was an announcement put out that there are actually server types and server names for Warhammer Online Age of Reckoning.
[SPEAKER_13]: There's a core open RVR, which is Realm vs. Realm, roleplay, and roleplay slash open RVR.
[SPEAKER_13]: So that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's going to have the standard gameplay, but you've got unrestricted PvP combat on the core server.
[SPEAKER_13]: And then on Realm vs. Realm, you have to be flagged for combat to do PvP stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: You can also permanently flag people on the open Realm vs. Realm servers.
[SPEAKER_13]: And of course, roleplay servers are basically getting into your character, roleplaying.
[SPEAKER_13]: We know this.
[SPEAKER_06]: which hopefully they actually enforce unlike in WoW I mean I guess you can file tickets in WoW but it seems like you always get a bunch of a-holes on there and they're like haha RP and it's like dude you signed up for an RP server what the F were you expecting I know right I've done a roleplay server before for World of Warcraft I had a lot of fun I played a real bitch like that's you know any different that's not roleplaying Jamie that's real life you see this ferret I do
[SPEAKER_13]: BendOverRob.
[SPEAKER_13]: No.
[SPEAKER_13]: No ferrets.
[SPEAKER_13]: But anyway, those are the type of servers that are out, so that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I don't know which one I'm playing on yet, if I get the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: If.
[SPEAKER_05]: If.
If.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was fascinated by the fact that apparently they changed the name of Africa in Japan to Hakuna Matata.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Akuna Matata
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm seriously thinking about buying this though.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is the fucking raddest name for a game ever though.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's only $54.90.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_06]: But it's coming out here eventually, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Eventually, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like things I can get early.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways, back on topic here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bioshock.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a PS3 game now.
[SPEAKER_04]: At least it will be in October.
[SPEAKER_04]: And as with most PS3 games, it will require an install.
[SPEAKER_04]: But don't worry, that'll be an entertaining 10 minutes as you watch Rapture-related advertisements and music.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks.
[SPEAKER_04]: He found his aroma like a certain appeal.
[SPEAKER_04]: He could clear the savannah after every meal.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm a sensitive soul, though I sing thick skinned.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wonder if this game is in English.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it too much to get the freaking chorus?
[SPEAKER_06]: I just wanted the freaking chorus, but the little samples on iTunes have the little chorus pre-verses there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Lame.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hakuna Matata.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, Harry Potter!
[SPEAKER_06]: Hakuna Matata, Harry Potter What do they have to do with each other, Rob?
[SPEAKER_06]: and instead they're getting Twilight out in the movie theaters this Christmas.
[SPEAKER_06]: But Harry Potter got pushed back to next summer.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, this should be kind of a duh, but the game got pushed back as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's right, EA confirmed this week that Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince, the game has been delayed.
[SPEAKER_06]: And even though I would think the game is pretty much done, but maybe they'll take some time to go back and tweak it.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's kind of sad about this, though, is that EA now is not going to get the profits from this game until their next fiscal quarter.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a loss.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oops.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince will be out in video game form when the movie comes out summer 2009.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm sure a lot of you kids can't wait.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are we getting a Twilight video game?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what I want to know.
[SPEAKER_06]: No?
[SPEAKER_06]: Where's that tie in?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's, uh... I want my sparkling vampires in a video game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Vampires that sparkle?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's too cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, our Skype line's open at Orange Lounge Radio or our phone number, 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_06]: Real quickly, though, some last-minute stories.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, I know you had something about EA and Take-Two, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: The final nail in the coffin.
[SPEAKER_04]: Breaking news.
[SPEAKER_04]: EA gives up on Take-Two acquisition.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's official.
[SPEAKER_04]: They will not buy them out.
[SPEAKER_04]: of other due diligence materials provided by Take-Two.
[SPEAKER_04]: EA has decided not to make a proposal to acquire Take-Two and has terminated discussions with Take-Two.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really, could it be all those times that they said, no, no, no, stop bothering me, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_13]: Maybe it just took them going, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't see you.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't hear you.
[SPEAKER_06]: La, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la.
[SPEAKER_06]: Skyblind's open, 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_06]: His name on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to take some calls.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll start here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_14]: My name is Zaku.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, Zaku.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's on your mind, my friend?
[SPEAKER_14]: Not much.
[SPEAKER_14]: Just chilling on a boring Sunday night.
[SPEAKER_14]: Except for you guys.
[SPEAKER_14]: We're just making it all better.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, are you getting DDRX this week?
[SPEAKER_06]: You're a Ditter fan.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, I'm on a wait-and-see right now, and since I'm unemployed and I need work right now, I need to hold off on spending splurging money on luxuries such as video games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, that's definitely understandable.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, you know the location test happened last week, right?
[SPEAKER_14]: Actually, throughout the better part of last week.
[SPEAKER_14]: It just ended today.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, yeah?
[SPEAKER_06]: How'd that go?
[SPEAKER_14]: I...
[SPEAKER_14]: Dude, from what I've known, from what those folks were able to test out there, it's shaping up to be a pretty good mix.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, I have a real quick question.
[SPEAKER_04]: DDRX, isn't that supposed to be coming out soon in the arcades?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, they tested the arcade machine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that's what they were testing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rob, you remember that... What?
[SPEAKER_04]: You went into that store Gamers Empire with me, remember, by the Folsom Theatres?
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't go into it, but I... You know of it, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know of it, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're converting the front of their store into an arcade now, and they have told me that they are probably going to get DDRX.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well...
[SPEAKER_04]: That'll be fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_14]: It all depends on whether or not they just buy the full cab or the upgrade kit.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's gonna be the full freaking cabinet.
[SPEAKER_04]: They said it's really expensive.
[SPEAKER_14]: Remember, that cab that was used in the location test is not final.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's kind of like a prototype right now.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's basically a test pad for what Konami's trying to do.
[SPEAKER_14]: According to what the rep said over there.
[SPEAKER_14]: And they're ditching Betsy.
[SPEAKER_14]: Which is great news since now Konami's restarting their arcade division.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I didn't know they were restarting it.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, because that's what the, you know, the folks, the guys who were running the test, you know, the folks in the arcade, you know, Konami's arcade division, that's what they were telling the folks who were at the test.
[SPEAKER_14]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_14]: They said we're starting over.
[SPEAKER_06]: We are starting over.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, indeed.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, and that's how they mean it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Does this mean we might get Silent Hill arcade game over here finally?
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, if it means that no, you know,
[SPEAKER_14]: Unfortunately, we won't have that American incompetence holding back certain, you know, basically tainting the good name of DDR with shitty cabs and just piss poor service.
[SPEAKER_14]: It means that Konami is actually doing something right.
[SPEAKER_14]: They're actually doing it themselves this time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, any other thoughts, Zaku, on your mind before we get to another call?
[SPEAKER_14]: Um, just the fact that Securom and EA is just killing PC gaming.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ah, yes, the whole DRM.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sure you can't run away from this discussion somewhere on the internet.
[SPEAKER_06]: We were just talking about it with Bobby on his show a little bit when we were doing the little toss-over that he does at the end of his show.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, it's...
[SPEAKER_06]: It's unfortunate that the people who are actually selling out the money to get the games are the ones that are getting punished.
[SPEAKER_14]: See, I was going to buy Command & Conquer, you know, I was going to buy Red Alert 3 until I found out that it was basically boiled down to something almost akin to a rental.
[SPEAKER_14]: And that's something I'm not cool with because I don't want to be, you know, first and foremost, there's no way I'm going to be treated as a criminal first and then have to prove my innocence.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's not the...
[SPEAKER_14]: You know, it's innocent until proven guilty, not the other way around.
[SPEAKER_06]: It does make me wish that the game would come out on consoles, you know, because it's sad for PC gamers.
[SPEAKER_14]: I would want to use my keyboard and mouse instead of the controller.
[SPEAKER_06]: Technically you can use the keyboard on 360, it's just there's really only one game that necessitates it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Will the game support those two peripherals?
[SPEAKER_14]: That's what I want to know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wish it would.
[SPEAKER_14]: If not, then I might as well just skip it until they ditch the...
[SPEAKER_14]: and the protections on the PC version, which is the one I wanted to buy in the first place.
[SPEAKER_14]: It just sucks it had to be like that, but hopefully we'll hit EA where it hurts, in their wallets.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, Sakura, we've got to let you go to get more calls, but have a good one, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, you too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you currently a Warcraft player that's considering leaving for Warhammer?
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's some of the responses we got via Twitter.
[SPEAKER_06]: GS68 says, I don't play MMOs, except the real occasional Albatross 18.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I apologize if I mispronounce your names, guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dustoise says, I'm actually waiting for Champions Online.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love City of Heroes villains and would love an updated, better version of that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tiara says, nope, still waiting patiently for Star Trek Online.
[SPEAKER_06]: Peker Uno says, simply, hell no.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dark Tetsuya says, I'm just waiting for Diablo 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: DJ Tyrant says, no and no.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've seen the war beta and it looks very similar to WoW and I'm not a huge PvP player.
[SPEAKER_06]: If I were, I might leave.
[SPEAKER_06]: Giavdea, sorry if I mispronounced that name, says, I'm waiting for Guild Wars 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: Misty OLR says, yeah, I'm with GS68, who said I don't play MMOs, 100% on this one.
[SPEAKER_06]: My damn attention span doesn't help things either.
[SPEAKER_06]: Quiltipo says, will there be bards?
[SPEAKER_06]: If so, yes, give me a damn bard already, people.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hate to say it, but Fafixi has bards, and it's actually a pretty awesome class to play.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actdeft says, considering that I was never into MMOs, Warhammer, even though it looks good, I won't be picking it up.
[SPEAKER_06]: MMOs are never-ending repeat cycles.
[SPEAKER_06]: Meowfrog says, I'm not buying Warhammer.
[SPEAKER_06]: I may later on.
[SPEAKER_06]: However, I do still play WoW.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have friends who have canceled their account for Warhammer.
[SPEAKER_06]: I actually know people that have done the same thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: We used to do a big rating alliance to do the 25 mans, and a bunch of them have quit to go to Warhammer.
[SPEAKER_06]: Something else.
[SPEAKER_06]: Lastly, here's another one I'll probably mispronounce.
[SPEAKER_06]: Spongetwang says, not buying Warhammer online.
[SPEAKER_06]: currently playing WoW sparingly as is, using spare and spare time for DDR.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I'd like to point out, out of those 12 responses, not a single person said they're buying Warhammer.
[SPEAKER_06]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_06]: But we did have people saying that their friends are getting it, so maybe it's not going to be a huge game.
[SPEAKER_06]: And certainly we have a very unscientific sample, but there you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Geovay Day Paradox Vincent
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, not much.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just wanted to give a big shout out to you guys for playing I'm Having Trouble Beating Airman from Mario Payne.
[SPEAKER_09]: I really liked that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I'm pretty much obsessed with that song.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just...
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I found it on YouTube a really long time ago, and I just kept listening to it and kept listening to it, and it's just a nice little Japanese rock song from some Japanese indie band.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's about Mega Man, and I can't go wrong with that.
[SPEAKER_13]: It sounds like you could go in a Mega Man game, though, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe Mega Man 10.
[SPEAKER_06]: They should have a best-of, Mega Man All-Stars, as the best monsters from all the games.
[SPEAKER_13]: Do you like watching the videos that they make for these?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know if you heard that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you like watching the videos that they make from these?
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, that's my favorite part.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's one of my favorite parts of those, the little videos.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't exactly know if they just hand animated them or if they're all pixeled, but yeah, that's one of my favorite parts about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, very cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anything else you've been playing lately?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, and... Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, actually, well, I mean...
[SPEAKER_09]: I haven't really been playing it, but... Well, I guess I have.
[SPEAKER_09]: A few weeks ago, I went over to a party, and I really started playing on my friend's PS3.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I used to really bash the PS3, but, you know, lately... And he sat me down, and... Can I do a really quick plug here?
[SPEAKER_07]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's my friend's website.
[SPEAKER_09]: His name is Frank Castle, and he's...
[SPEAKER_09]: He runs this community called Arizona Hobbyist Paradise.
[SPEAKER_09]: What?
[SPEAKER_13]: He's not the Punisher, is he?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: Frank Castle is the Punisher's name.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, so he runs a comic thing in Arizona?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, well it's called Arizona Hobbyist Paradise and it's at hobbyistparadise.com
[SPEAKER_09]: and it's just for like AZ Arizona people who like gaming, anime and comics but I was playing on his PS3 and then he sat me down and then he's like you know the PS3 is starting to really gain a lot of ground in the gaming industry and I obviously disagreed with him but then he showed me this big list and I mean I'm looking at the PS3 exclusives right now and it used to kind of be like the big joke of gaming but I'm really thinking about picking up a PS3 really soon
[SPEAKER_06]: I do want one for LittleBigPlanet and Home definitely has me curious, but I think Sony still has a long way to go.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's kind of been a theme with them lately, and that's kind of worrisome.
[SPEAKER_06]: They were allowed to do a little bit of a slow launch with the PlayStation 2 because it was really the only thing out there, if I remember right, when it first came out.
[SPEAKER_06]: But with the PSP, there wasn't a lot of must-have games on the PSP, and a lot of those patches that enabled the internet and all those things came out
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm wondering have you ever heard of The Last Guy?
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it's the last guy that's that one that was like that game in Work Time Fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: The one where it uses like the Google Map-esque stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, okay, yeah, I think I remember hearing about this on a previous show, yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: And also, uh, Pain, Pain looked pretty, it looked interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Uh, I hear it's a little silly, but okay, I mean, it's different.
[SPEAKER_09]: and I just think that, and Pain, if I'm not mistaken, isn't that a title that you buy on the PlayStation Network?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's one of those games I think that you can now get on your PSP as well through the whole little... No.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it's not?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought it was.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because you know how some of those PlayStation Network games are coming on the PSP, like Flow was one of them, I know?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Echo Chrome?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, well, anything else, Paradox Vincent, before we let you go?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm not all that much.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, have a good one, buddy.
[SPEAKER_09]: You too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for listening.
[SPEAKER_09]: Next time I see you, I'll break your arms.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, ow.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why would you do that?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's mean.
[SPEAKER_09]: Zongief would do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why would someone threaten to break my arms?
[SPEAKER_06]: Now if my arms really do get broken, I have it on tape and I can sue.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you want to give us a call, 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio, all one word.
[SPEAKER_06]: We've got time for maybe like one more call, I think.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll probably do tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, it's SSJ100 Matt from New York.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, hello SSJ100 Matt from New York.
[SPEAKER_06]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm good, thanks.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was just thinking the other day.
[SPEAKER_06]: I miss New York City.
[SPEAKER_08]: You should definitely come.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to come back and visit.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just don't know when I'm realistically going to make it happen because I'm very likely taking two trips to LA.
[SPEAKER_06]: There is a very small chance I might be able to pull through and do BlizzCon after all, but more on that when I find out for sure.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't want to jinx it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, first off, I wanted to profess my love to Castle Crashers.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think everyone who has a 360 needs to get it now.
[SPEAKER_06]: What is it about Castle Crashers that you love?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: It just brings back my old love of the classic beat-em-ups like Turtles in Time.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not saying it's like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Turtles in Time is great.
[SPEAKER_08]: It just reminds me of that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know though, the demo kind of got a little old for me, but I do like, I mean, I need to get the full version I think, because it does look like the little other aspects of upgrades and roleplay-esque elements they put in there look kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't want to review the game based off a demo alone, especially when everybody else is saying such wonderful things about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also, I've been playing the game by myself, and I imagine it's the type of game that's much more fun with more people.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I hear online is broken.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, online's broken.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what, I haven't really been playing online, um,
[SPEAKER_08]: Mostly my friends have been bugging me to come play.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm actually getting texted right now asking to come over and play it.
[SPEAKER_08]: But yeah, you know, it's lots of fun, and it's kind of a good party game if you kind of have a group of people who are all about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sure, sure.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Rob D kind of sums up what I'm thinking.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's in the chat right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: He says, I'm enjoying Castle Crashers, but I'm not really digging the combat gameplay.
[SPEAKER_06]: I do like the art style and the music, but I'm not liking the characters or the attacking.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I mean, the game's got a certain quirkiness about it that's very cool that piques my interest, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: The...
[SPEAKER_06]: Old School Ninja Turtles Arcade Game gameplay kind of got old a little while ago.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe it's not completely fair to say.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's just one of these more fun and big groups.
[SPEAKER_08]: It got old when you wasted all your quarters on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, true, true, very true.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, the other thing I wanted to talk about is, you guys kind of mentioned this before, is NHL 09.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I managed to pick that up yesterday and I, you know what, I'm a big hockey fan.
[SPEAKER_08]: If anyone listens to Under Sedation Live, I was calling about that.
[SPEAKER_08]: But,
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I think this is, you know, one of the better hockey games because of the whole online interaction that they have.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's so special about the online interaction, real quick?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, basically what it is, they kind of made hockey into an MMO where you create a player and you can take him on to a custom team where, you know, you can have a bunch of friends or like what we have with...
[SPEAKER_08]: All games, we've decided to make an all games team.
[SPEAKER_06]: Does everybody play as one character on the team, or how does it work?
[SPEAKER_08]: You play as one position on the team, or player.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you can either play goalie, you can play center, you can play any position.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can all play at once, and it's lots of fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: So yeah, we're trying to rally every show...
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: NHL 09 Online
[SPEAKER_06]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, well, we've got to let you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to start to wrap things up, but thanks so much for your call, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow, I think we've talked more about sports games tonight than we have in a year on Orange Lounge Radio, but that's okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: We want to give an equal opportunity to all games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to wrap things up here, but I did get a private message I wanted to read here.
[SPEAKER_06]: James Patrick says...
[SPEAKER_06]: Dragon Quest IV Dragon Quest V
[SPEAKER_04]: Rob cheated.
[SPEAKER_04]: I did not cheat.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had help.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was officially sanctioned.
[SPEAKER_06]: It wasn't one of those things where, like, for a while, if you bought the game, you got the stupid thing free, the guidebook, which I always thought was a little weird, but I'm pretty sure you did through, like, Nintendo Power or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um... It's been a long time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't even try Dragon Quest VIII.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was cool!
[SPEAKER_06]: Dragon Quest VIII is actually really fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to go back and beat it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was actually a lot, a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was like an old-school Super Nintendo role-playing game, but with, like, 3D graphics.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not my thing, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, I still have to go back and finish Lost Odyssey, so, I mean, shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: I am not buying any more RPGs until I finish Lost Odyssey.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it may be a while.
[SPEAKER_04]: In all these Square Enix offshoot games, like Last Remnant and Infinite Undiscovery, I don't know if I should even try those.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, I'm being persuaded by a listener that Infinite Undiscovery may not be as bad as the first two hours make it seem.
[SPEAKER_06]: But boy, what a crappy way to start the game is just running from things.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just kind of frustrating.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I'm going to try to...
[SPEAKER_06]: Try to suck it up and try to get a little further because I like the part that I played at Penny Arcade Expo and that bugged me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why isn't the game as cool as I remember?
[SPEAKER_06]: Was it just that whole con?
[SPEAKER_06]: You know how games always seem better at a con because you're caught up in the moment of a convention?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if this is exactly a good...
[SPEAKER_04]: I like Final Fantasy VIII, it was alright Like I can get on the internet
[SPEAKER_04]: So, in case you were wondering if Rock Revolution for the Wii is going to be good, apparently it's not.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just, you know, throwing it out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kotaku actually got to preview the game at a Nintendo party last Friday, and apparently the game itself on the Wii, there is no peripheral support whatsoever, even if you happen to do own...
[SPEAKER_04]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's kind of lame.
[SPEAKER_04]: And of course, kind of on the topic of Nintendo here, they will not be at E4ALL.
[SPEAKER_04]: And yeah, apparently they just didn't want to go.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not in their plans.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do remember if I heard correctly that they're going to be showing off their games there anyways at like some Target booth or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess they actually sell games at this expo, which is weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: and Namco Bandai has said that they're planning on making more Xbox Live Arcade remakes of classic arcade games, much like they've done with Pac-Man Championship Edition and Galaga Legions.
[SPEAKER_04]: No word on exactly what they're planning, but more games.
[SPEAKER_04]: One suggestion, I guess, says that the team is working on a Pole Position remake, which is interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: And this little bit, I thought I'd throw this out for you, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not exactly news, but there's a Dreamcast console available on PlayAsia.com that's the Hello Kitty Special Edition.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_06]: I've actually seen that in a store before.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's been out a while.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: But they're hard to find.
[SPEAKER_06]: Really, really hard to find.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, that's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Team Ico is revealing a new game, The Queen, apparently.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Queen of what?
[SPEAKER_04]: England?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just called The Queen.
[SPEAKER_04]: France?
[SPEAKER_04]: It says Tokyo Game Show teaser website calls the game Ico 3 The Queen.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which begs the question what was Ico 2?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't remember a night go to maybe Shadow of the Colossus I don't know but apparently it's going to be Tokyo Game Show so that's kind of exciting and also my final thought is that I got to the bottom of why those Rock Band drum sets weren't out there apparently they released a press release on the 10th saying that they're coming later in the week I somehow missed that so that'd be why no one has them yet
[SPEAKER_06]: My final thought for those of you in chatroom discussing this game right now is it's Treasure Hunter, not a thief.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, that's going to do it for tonight's show.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to wrap up and get on out of here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just let us say thank you very much for tuning into our show and downloading us and checking us out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Remember, if you like what you hear, please tell two other people about our podcast because that's how we slowly spread the word.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's by word of mouth.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're not cool enough or rich enough to have broadcasting and a really big corporate website backing us, but that just lets you guys know that we're unfiltered.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're the real deal.
[SPEAKER_06]: Real gamers just like you guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll hope you tune in live next week or in podcast if you can't join us live and talk more with us about games on the show where every gamer has a voice, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see you next week, same time.
[SPEAKER_06]: See you then.
[SPEAKER_15]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_15]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_15]: To join us for a live show, visit www.allgames.com Sunday nights at 6pm Pacific Time.
[SPEAKER_15]: The views and opinions expressed on Orange Lounge Radio do not necessarily reflect those of the entire staff of Orange Lounge Radio or AllGames.com, but we're probably right anyway.
[SPEAKER_15]: See you next week!