This week No Man's Sky's first landing was more of a thud than a splash, but the waves
made over time have become more impressive all without any post-purchase monetization
to this day.
This is just one 3 year survival story, stay tuned for the rest of the week's gaming news
starting right now on the show where every gamer has a voice.
Orange Lounge Radio Hello my friends out there on the internet
and welcome back to another week of the show where every gamer has a voice it is Orange
Lounge Radio live tonight with episode number 800 that's right 800 finally an 8 in front
of all those numbers for tonight December the 1st of 2019 my name is Rob Roberts and
joining me in studio as she has for the last 800 weeks give or take a few say hello to
DarkSakura or Jamie Summers hi hi how are you I'm a little under but I'm okay yeah you
have sounded a little bit sick tonight so sorry to hear that but respectfully don't
get me sick no I'm over here I actually I'm wearing half my pajamas I found in digging
through the closet the hoodie that I bought at the Skywalker Ranch before episode 3 came
out and it's an episode 3 hoodie yeah and I'm never getting rid of it even though it's
like five sizes too big for me now because number one it's warm and number two I bought
it at the fucking Skywalker Ranch well and being bigger is not always necessarily like
a bad thing that just makes it like comfy like loungewear you know show wow I didn't
think you would show on cam since we do tape live every Sunday night at twitch.tv slash
vog network the voice of geeks network vog network we are of course live right after
the bobby black wolf show at six o'clock pacific nine o'clock eastern not only are we celebrating
really 800 episodes orange launch radio but this month I mean give or take a couple weeks
one year on twitch actually so yay for the record my wearing of this is in no way an
endorsement of the film yeah understandable quite understandable also joining us tonight
say hello to tech master loki hello hi loki how are you I'm fine yeah all right yeah it's
fine uh some mr smoosh is wanting to execute you know oh he he I don't know what it is
about the three of us starting to talk that all of a sudden like wakes him up that he's
just like I want to be in there I want to but I mean he he could he's welcome to channeling
jerry blank he's welcome I have something to say he's welcome to come in here the viewers
love it did he really he's he saw jamie coming and he walked right into kitty jail I love it
anyway how are you tech master loki I'm fine yeah yeah yeah just fine yeah I'm just fine you
were talking about I felt I fell down earlier yeah she's sick you injured yourself it's just
a minor injury oh it's only a flesh wound it pretty much yeah it's only a flesh okay what
happened we all want to know oh my kids wanted me to take them to roller skating so they went
roller skating and I I used to roller blade like a ton like all the time and the last time we went
rollerblading which was not that long ago I my one of my straps on my blades broke so I had to
rent a pair today and so they had like a speed skating in session which I like doing that's fun
so I tried to go around the corner you know I usually crisscross the kind of go faster
over around the corners and because they're profiling the wheels is different than what
I'm used to it slipped inside I hit the ground on my knee rolled to my elbow and then got back
up so it's it scraped it a little bit but it's like I'm like ow but I'm gonna get back up and
just keep going I mean it's not like I broke my leg or something congrats you're old it's not
all this is what I used to do like all the time I've done this I've gotten this injury so many
times at least it was in a rink and not on like asphalt which is typically the case true I have
a sun-bleached spot on the sweater do you oh well oh well well you've had it a while episode 3 was
out so you know episode 9 is coming out soon I was at the movies yesterday we will get into gaming's
but it just wouldn't be an episode of orange entre do if there weren't tangents you know no it's
funny though when we were in the rink sorry how a tangent to the tangent November because we had
talked about like we should do something like like stupid for like one of these like big like
numbered episodes or something and I was like suggesting like hey we could rent out the roller
because that's dirt cheap huh and so I thought about that again well our live on roller skates
yeah why here's the thing let me let me loan you some sage advice for having done this for 800
episodes why do we have to do it for 800 episodes why can't we celebrate 823 like every you do
whatever we want every episode should be celebrated every every every olr is a blessing every week we
don't kill each other is a success story is it not it's a toll-free episode anyway going to wait
what was my oh yes I went to the movies I went to see knives out which you know I want to see that
because it's like clue it what I hear like clue dark here's a lot of my friends really loved it
I liked it I didn't love it but I liked it and I don't know if it was really clue I don't know if
you can be clue when you reference clue in the film however it did have Jamie Lee Curtis who's
a gamer we all know that right and she was great there just wasn't enough of her like I think there
was a lot of people in it where I was like we hardly got to see him but anyway that's all I
don't want spoil too much anyway so anyway um I also want to say I I am looking at chat because
again we tape live over at twitch TV slash vog network and I you guys are really donating biddies
tonight and I see you guys doing I don't usually call out all the bit donations because they go
across the bottom but I will at the end of the show when we're not recording for the podcast but
I see several of you are doing 800 biddies for 800 episodes and I know that's no small amount
of biddies so I really want to just acknowledge that and say thank you that is very very kind and
you know we wanted to at the top of the show here you know even if we've done 500 episodes
and 200 episodes and 700 episodes and we've done 10 years and 12 years and so forth I I I didn't
want to toot our own horn too much but I didn't want to take this opportunity at the top of the
show to just say thanks I mean you guys are truly what keeps this going gives us that energy to do
this show every week even when maybe we're feeling a little sick or we've injured ourselves earlier
in the day and maybe we don't necessarily always feel like coming in showing up to doing it it's
like by the time we're here and you guys are here and interacting with it and bringing that
enthusiasm that you guys do it really means a lot and obviously if we haven't broken it big by now
800 episodes and 17 years in we're probably not going to but I think we all made peace with that
a long time ago and still even with our small audience we have a very loyal and great little
family here and that's okay I like small families I don't I mean like when I used to go to the
extended family for holidays that's what all the messes happen that's all the drama and political
start small family gatherings awesome so we like the small family that we have here and I still you
know this show has afforded us many opportunities still even with its you know smaller size than I
think I would have ever gotten otherwise we were just talking about on Bobby's show before we went
live tonight a cameo that we had in a video game like that would have never happened if it wasn't
for this show we got to go to e3 back when it was cool like in its most heyday years you know that
was something because of this show that you know we got to do and and there's been other industry
events I've I have been an acknowledged professional at a very large convention every
year for the past couple years that is an amazing feat that I'm so thankful and humble for with this
show so thank you guys so much for showing up every week and giving us that motivation we need
to keep doing this show every single week thank you thank you thank you and yeah I let swung tongue
gave a donation and said happy 800 that's all I got that's okay you know we the the bits are
an extra thank you we'd never expect them but they are very very much appreciated and help us
to keep vog network as a business and do business II type of things that we do want to continue to
expand on yeah swung tongue said you were on TV that's true we thank you for reminding me yeah
there was a couple times and on in the newspaper which I still have that somewhere yeah I had it
it's really yellow though yeah it was it was early on in the life of the show when we were in the
newspaper because that was right when podcasting first broke and if you search for like Sacramento
in iTunes you got us like there wasn't you know now there's probably shows about Sacramento in
there and you know there's other that Sacramento has a number one gaming podcast now that comes up
in the results and all this other stuff that wasn't there back when we started so yeah like
we were what came up so the newspaper came out to do that and then the news station came out and did
one story at my place about podcasting but then what was really cool is that they remembered us
or something because when Guitar Hero came out the first one they would I wasn't there it was just
you and Loki so maybe hide on my bimani stuff oh yeah oh because the Guitar Hero guy the like PR
guy for a red or was it red octane at the time so you went as well to like he gave you guys a
personal demo of the game we have all the fun with it yeah no it's cool it was very very very
cool appreciate that and we had that nice big TV in the living room at the house in is a few
houses ago for me yeah but you know that house oh no I do yeah I do nice and shiny in there
I'm a necessary 100 Matt and chat says it's so much fun yeah that's where that quote came from
it's still on YouTube there's an orange on radio YouTube channel and you can still see that old
story it's an old story at this point yeah well what my god how many years ago to Dave Walker
retire and he's the one doing the the news anchor thing introducing the story I don't know also
here's the other interesting thing about that story they never name our show they never cuz
they're assholes they know I don't know if it's because they can't endorse it or whatever but
they never name our show um to be fair they also say at one point in the news story governor
Schwarzenegger just started a podcast because again it's that old so they said governor
Schwarzenegger started a podcast but they never named that program either because remember they
had the kid on the skateboard yeah I was like podcast listener you young person do you know
what podcasts are why yes sir I do it's funny that it made us such a niche thing back then
and now it's like now podcasting is that stereotype thing where it's like you know
you've all heard those jokes and I why don't you have a podcast yet or I hate these jokes
but I hate them but we've all heard them the one you know what do you call three white dudes in
their 30s in the basement a podcast you know that that whole thing and I'm just like the podcast I
I don't like that joke because I really really want podcasting to be for everybody I heard that
one yeah I have it's it's it's stupid I've seen it on Twitter I've seen a lot of really dumb
podcast jokes on Twitter and I that's one thing that like really irks me is that podcasting is
like because I think those jokes reinforce that it's only for one particular audience when it
really isn't it's really for everybody like everybody should be able to get their voice
out there and be heard and it's not just podcasting because now we live in this era of YouTube as much
as I don't like YouTube as a business and twitch where you know you can get on and have your own
streams and stuff they're really it's really really easy to have your voice heard when you
know again back in 2006 when these news stations featured us it was a little bit more of a novelty
wasn't it anyway all right anyhow sorry I it was a little bit of a tangent but we wanted to say
something here at the top of the show for episode number 800 so again thank you all for being with
us let's get into some video game news because I know that's what we're really about here at
the show what I was watching the video of my DDR pads are in the background oh yeah oh yeah that
was pretty funny yeah for sure oh my gosh Matt you look so young all right anyway let's get into
our kickoff topic tonight which has to do with pokemons so Loki you want to start us off here
with this kickoff topic about what's going on with the Pokemon Pokemon company so apparently arrest
you they're gonna they're gonna come and find you they have a specific set of skills that they're
gonna use to find you and kill you or something but anyways so yes apparently the Pokemon company
hired some outside forensic experts who are trying to locate I guess some people that leaked
information about Pokemon so they had been able to identify for discord users one who was the
source and a few others that were helping him spread the images through 4chan and reddit and
with that of course they've since they found their usernames they don't know who those people are so
now they've gone to the district court in Seattle to try to get a hold of that information from
discord and 4chan to try to track down who the people are under those usernames so that's
interesting I don't know this has been done like but is it really a crime to leak information about
something I mean if you're not under an NDA and somehow you came across that information is that
really a crime well that's the problem is that somewhere along the line in NDA had to be broken
like if I just happenstance accidentally came across something then somebody still broke an
NDA to get the game but then that person be in trouble but like if I if I like how do you find
that out but say I broke an NDA but they know one person but like say I broke an NDA and gave
information to somebody else and then that person didn't spread the information out but now you're
hunting after this person that doesn't make any sense to me because it's not a crime it's an
inconvenience for your marketing campaign but it's not a crime it's not a crime as in you can't go to
jail per se but they would have a case in civil court and I think I kind of think they have a
right to protect themselves in that capacity because you know it's just like if the new Star
Wars movie leaked to the internet tomorrow you know three weeks before it's supposed to be in
theaters would it necessarily be the person who leaked its fault if it was something that was
given to them no but it's still going to financially damage the results of the film that's copyright
theft that's that's not say that'd be like if you leaked a copy of Pokemon Sword and Shield to the
internet and then people based played that and they're like oh here's all the secrets that's
different versus like here's some information I've heard about like say that would be the equivalent
of somebody leaking the script for Star Wars the new Star Wars movie or the bits of the script of
the new Star Wars movie I don't know I still think it's a slippery slope but I guess they got to try
Elliot B in our chat says detective Pikachu on the case absolutely why we are in chat says argument
I own this physical copy of the game I can do with it as I please counter argument you don't
own the software your license to use it and doing this is a violation of the license agreement I
don't think anybody's going to jail over this but I think Nintendo wants to figure out where is the
leak so we can plug it up you know and potentially go after somebody in a civil court now I I had
heard a story about this but you can take it with a grain of salt because I don't have the article
or the receipts to back it up so maybe this is full of shit and I'm fully admitting that but I
had heard that there were live streams of Pokemon days before it was released that were somehow
altered or edited or maybe pre-releases or something that made the game look worse than it
actually was when it came to things like loading times yeah things of that nature but that's kind
of bullshit like and this was this was angry Dex it you know people that just wanted to bag on game
that's still though I mean you're gonna have a hard time proving damages for something like
that because you can say well this one video got out there and we suffered you know X number of
dollars in damages yeah but like if you sign an NDA that says if you spill you are it says in that
NDA you will pay one million dollars and I'm thinking in my mind today there was just some
article going around Facebook today because this was a ridiculous use of an NDA but um a comic one
of the guys from Saturday Night Live the young guy that was with Ariana Grande for a short time
what the hell's his name the kid from Davidson him okay he was doing a stand-up show in San Francisco
he was making people sign NDAs and the NDA said in it somebody posted it online like you uh would
pay one million dollars if you even like talked about the contents of the show online and people
were saying how ridiculous that was because you couldn't even criticize or critique the show I
mean it's one thing to be like you can't have your cell phones out during the show because that is
pretty bullshit when people record stand-up comic routines and put it on their own YouTube yeah that
is that's that's joke theft you know it's it's it's not that's copyright theft exactly um so
that's you know not okay but to take it to the extremes of an NDA where you can't even critique
it that's a little bit like you're not really within your realm here anyway the reason why I
bring that up is because it showed the NDA and it said you break this you pay a million dollars so
you know in Nintendo's NDA and any NDA um if you go on a reality tv show like survivor where
they know who won survivor whatever the next one is they already know because it's already been
filmed and done I mean okay technically they don't know who wins wins until they reveal the votes
but they know they know generally who gets voted out when and who's in the fight right but and it's
in their contract you break this you're paying like four million dollars they don't it's up to
that it's it could say you could fake you could face penalties of this whereas I still think
though even if there was a contract like that I still have a hard time believing that they can
prove damages on that okay but counterpoint who has the better lawyers Nintendo or 4chan kid
just saying Nintendo's gonna yeah but but to that though Pokemon company so to that though
like I don't know where 4chan is necessarily located is but it's not the site they're only
trying to get the site to reveal who it is but like if they're but if I understand that though
but if they're in a foreign country if they're look central in a foreign country they can say
fuck you and your stupid you know court order we're not gonna follow it if Nintendo doesn't
have a presence in that country but remember Nintendo has established in USA Canada Japan
many parts of uh you know overseas in Britain and surrounding countries I think they're gonna
have better luck with discord but but even still though that I don't know I think it's a it's a
slippery slope because then then what then you're gonna like start saying oh well these people they
they had bad things to say about our game let's find out who they are I mean like you could argue
that they cause damages because of their negative critique I understand that they should be
protected but but I'm Nintendo and I can fucking sue people so I don't know I go ahead just the
thing is is that with any kind of tech company be it software hardware you name it they're
part of their financial security lies in secrecy it lies in having something be locked to your
self as a proprietary secret so that when you release said item to to quote a term from another
company your customers are surprised and delighted by it to have anything sneak out about it
beforehand is going to impact that it may you know chase people off of buying the product it may
affect those upcoming sales and I think that what they're doing is not over reactionary at all
I think that it's like you said they have a leak to plug just because it happens now does not mean
this will not happen again right and so I actually I think even just by pursuing it the the simple
pursuit of it will set a precedence that companies are going to take it seriously
I think for the most part like I don't think it's a big deal that like final evolution you know I
realize for hardcore Pokemon fans it is a big deal but I do agree with Loki in a sense that like you
know certain types of information getting leaked is not a big deal oh no you saw what Grookey's
final form looked like you know like like how would like let's just assume that like nothing
got leaked how would people be taking like this Dexit stuff like because I don't think they
announced like here's the Pokemon well you're you just walked right into what my follow-up point is
is I think that's what actually makes this a little bit different and why Nintendo wants to
go after it because of that hard negativity about Dexit that was online which ultimately didn't
matter when it came to sales because it really is selling thing yeah but it still leaks showed you
who was missing and that was something Nintendo was trying to protect and I think that might be
the key difference here is that I think it's that specifically where that kind of crossed the line
for Nintendo was that they knew this was something that was negative and all the ramp up and they did
not want it out there who specifically was cut until till the final minute I just kind of think
that's what was going on now if and I'm gonna say bold if underline if if okay circled it's true
that somebody was streaming it and they were streaming a misrepresented fully copy of the game
then I think Nintendo should take that person for everything they got honestly because I think
that is fucked if they're streaming though they should be able to find them through
Twitch or YouTube or whomever so again that but that and that's if that was even true which might
not have been this is just something I was told so but I think that is way past the line of what's
acceptable and so forth and I think especially if you're you're streaming a game you're misrepresenting
what that game even is which is so weird that we live in this world where you have to talk about
that but I mean y'all have heard of in fake news and I was trying to think of another name for it
but I can't it's fake news and what you know the social media does in the spread of that type of
you know heavily partisan one way or another type of news and so forth I mean here we are where
video games are now kind of walking down the similar path we have we have fake video game news
maybe but I imagine we're not that far away from that being a reality so anyway but I think the
DeXit thing at its core is what you know Nintendo was was trying to protect now at the end of the
day you know and I've said this on a previous episode of OLR whereas I think the DeXit thing
is like oh man that would have been like that would have been the icing that would have been
like the that would have been that sweet glaze that extra thing that would have made this a
perfect fucking dessert Pokemon Sword and Shield is still a really fucking good dessert and I'll
get into more of that later on I think it's it's a great game personally so I mean is the DeXit
thing noticed yeah is it does it damn the whole game I don't think so I think there's still plenty
of variety and things to do then why hide it like I don't understand like if it's such it's if it I
it just seems disingenuous to me is the whole point it's like oh we want to hide it before
so we get all those pre-sale copies out there and then it's like oh now you can find out about it
like I don't know based on the social media and that negativity on social media there was probably
a legit concern within Nintendo that it would impact sales I mean now do you just say oh well
it didn't impact it uh sales all harm no all harm don't you want to have your in consumers be well
I guess you don't want your consumers to be well informed when purchasing your products you don't
want to know like what intricacies there are so they can make a you know educated decision in
their purchase I mean I guess that should be expected from a company that sells two copies
of their game every year so why not I don't know I just I have a hard time giving them a bit here
Loki and say you know what Rey is Princess Leia's sister enjoy episode nine now that's not a real
spoiler I don't know shit about what goes on that movie and I don't think age-wise that would work
anyway I made that up so don't worry exhale it's a fake spoiler but let's just say I did I just
blurred it out I just want you to be informed before you go see that movie here's the big
here's the big spoiler about the ending I mean isn't that kind of fucked up and like wouldn't
I mean wouldn't like you know if I'm advertising on my website you know like oh here's the big
twist at the end of episode nine it's like IGM publishes this headline no I guess in the sense
if you're trying to say that that's different than the expectations I would have for the movie
then that would be a huge um spoiler I picked something ridiculous so you all wouldn't panic
so no my my under see what I'm saying is so is it's drastically different from other pokemon
game whereas the other pokemon games they have they continue to add to you know the full um
list of pokemon they keep adding to it whereas this is the first one where they have taken
some away and then added some to that as well so that is what I'm saying about being well
informed because most people going into it having not known that might think oh hey cool I'm gonna
have all my favorite pokemon in there plus I'm gonna get some new ones and then they go there
and wait a second where are these pokemon oh they were taken out of the game I didn't know that that
kind of sucks you know and that that is what I'm talking about being you know well informed about
a games if you're taking something and you're drastically changing something to be fair they
weren't that shifty about it they announced like as far back as e3 that not all the pokemon were
going to be in it because they were asked that question very directly is every pokemon in this
game and they did say no and that was what started the whole hubbub then finally somebody got a copy
of the game and said oh I I have the answer here find out if your faves made the cut here's the list
and then here cue the reddit post once a day here is one pokemon family that has been eliminated
from pokemon it's so fucking dramatic jesus christ jigglypuff well she dead so
enjoy pokemon
anyway rest in peace jigglypuff with the you know all forever in our hearts with carnations
tombstone I mean come on loki some people are really fucking dramatic about this dexa thing
it's not again it's not that big a deal would it have made would it have made a nine and a half
game of 10 probably I mean I don't know I don't know I don't even know if I'd say that all right
technical issues aside too but you know yeah well yeah I would say the internet issues and the uh
wild area like how it fucking chokes when you're online I would say those issues are a way bigger
deal than the dexa thing but anyway all right um let's move on so we're gonna move on past
pokemons and talk about how was your gaming week which I left off the sidebar tonight isn't that
convenient all right so I guess I'll back it up how was your gaming week folks what types of
video games have you been playing this week dark soccer why don't you start us off I didn't really
play a whole lot um just because I had to bake five batches of cookies on Tuesday night after
work the holidays were this week so you know I had to yeah I had to because they were for three
different events that I had obligated myself to um and then actually I know I take that back because
we did have a lot of virtual racing going on in my house on Wednesday night like they stayed up
for hours playing fucking virtual racing I'm like it's virtual racing I don't give a shit
and play a bunch of pinball and then um actually I did get to play the jersey jack pirates of the
caribbean on Thursday because we went to a friend's place for thanksgiving and I got to play that and
I got to play um a Jurassic Park the new Jurassic Park stern pinball and I played a little bit of
Star Trek because it was there um there's also a uh an iron maiden but I don't really care for the
iron maiden table I still really need to come over and play that Elvira table while you still
have it yeah I played Elvira and Alan needs to play it too it's his table Alan's the one that
messaged me he's like I had no idea about this I'm like I told Rob he's sleeping on the couch
you know virtual racing has just about enough polygons for the Tesla Cybertruck in there so
we have a story on that later actually but um I guess I did do some gaming I just I didn't play
Pokemon which I thought I would but I also played my usual phone shit and then then I got like the
plague and so I didn't play much played a lot of solitaire all right well I play solitaire every
day at work why not solitaire so it's one of those standby good classics it's like my brain
D I'm more of a mind sweeper kid but you know I look at it as the the the frying pan of my brain
solitaire is the deglazer for the font the fond the bottom of my pan
all right let's move on Loki how was your gaming week I don't know did the holidays get in the way
of your gaming I didn't really play a lot of the games during the holidays I played Minecraft Earth
a bit and very little Pokemon go that's pretty much it I've been mainly just trying to work on
my game so I've been working on the procedural level generation portion of it and I got I got
it pretty much done I'm just dialing it in now because I want it to look a certain way
and it's just deciding between like different settings so that I get it to be just how I want
it without because you know I had I had done it in a certain way where it was just like getting
ridiculously meandering everywhere I was like no not quite what I want so it's just dialing that in
right now and then once I get that done I have to find a way to traverse the room so that I can make
the doors one way in a certain way so that I don't get trapped in a dead end because there's
no backtracking in the game so yeah that's what I've been working on most of the time that's why
I did not play very many games and didn't really buy that many games either because you know it's
all the sales and everything I looked at stuff I don't think I bought anything all right maybe I
will I wanted to get beat saver but oddly enough that is not on sale most of the sales go through
tomorrow which is you know cyber monday so well I mean a lot of the big sellers they don't really
discount because they're so it's uh death stranding you know I was hoping there'd be a black friday
sale on it nope still too new there was no black friday sale anywhere on it so um and I'll get to
that here shortly but I ended up paying the full 60 bucks in order to be able to play it so whatever
I knew that was probably going to be the case but I thought maybe there'd be a discount who knows
all right anything else you want to talk about that's it all right let me talk about my gaming
week here a little bit so um unlike my co-hosts um probably because I didn't do a lot for the
holidays it's just myself Alan and my dad and we had a great thanksgiving dinner though but we go
out to eat because you don't want to eat what I'm going to cook and like nobody wants to cook so we
go out so thank you to the folks at restaurants that that stay open on thanksgiving so that folks
who you know don't really aren't going to cook a great dinner still have a place to eat and I
will say we went to a great place we went to the brazilian steakhouse out in roseville which uh so
we had the meat on the swords and what was cute was that for their um like you know how they have
the food the salad bar right yeah and usually they'll have a selection of hot foods there like
soups and things what they did is they replaced all the hot food with turkey mashed potatoes
cranberry I thought they had like the turkey on the swords too no they didn't have the turkey
on the swords turkey was over at the salad bar oh that's lame yeah so not quite the same but um
believe me there was no shortage of amazing meat I just felt bad for my dad because he kind of
filled up on all the traditional stuff but I think that's what he wanted he wanted to have more of the
traditional stuff so he didn't get to try because he was already full by the time all those stuff
where it's like Alan and myself were like let's let's split half a piece of turkey and a scoop of
mashed potatoes and then that was like all we ate and it was like let's not fill up bring on that
bacon that's that's what my wife always says she's like don't fill up on the garbage don't
fill up on the salad fill up on the meat it's what we're here for you're paying for the meat
you eat the meat he's absolutely right all right but so that was great so thanksgiving was great
but outside of that we didn't have a whole lot going on so I played like a shitload of games
honestly um I was out playing pokemon go since you brought that up uh a friend of mine took me out
who plays the game a lot and was trying to help me along with the team rocket stuff to get Giovanni
for this month for the shadow articuno I didn't get all the way there but I did purify 15 pokemon
and like I did a lot of those team rocket fights but then like if it hadn't been raining these past
couple days I probably would have finished it but the rain starting here kind of like you know you
don't want to go outside as much so I didn't end up finishing uh that up but um you know I made a
lot of I've done a lot more of those team rocket fights than I ever have since it started I probably
did like three times as many in the past three days I have since that whole thing started so
there's that um bonds 006 says I detest those damn tr fights so much yeah they're not my favorite
thing but you know my friend made a good point about it was that it kind of gives another thing
to do in the game like another reason to craft these pokemon a certain way and have other pokemon
have the spotlight that maybe were monopolizing in the gym battles so it's like you have this
other thing to kind of work for and do besides just oh I have to catch shinies or oh I have to
catch you know perfect hundred percent the ones that you get though the purified ones or when you
do purify them they're not very strong they're they're really not they're kind of hit and miss
like those articuno's are crappy now I would think what you do is you save them for a lucky trade and
then trade them but I'm told you can't trade purified pokemon I don't know if that's true or
not but I would think that's the way to get around the low IVs but I did I fought a Bulbasaur um over
at the park not by my house but the other one I fought a Bulbasaur and after I purified it it was
15 14 14 so I evolved at once to a Venusaur and then before I evolved I'm sorry I evolved at
once to Ivysaur and then before I hit the button to do it Venusaur I heard my friend in the back
of my mind say you don't want to evolve that yet because community day is coming up and all those
moves will come back and I was like oh shit that's right so I held off and I didn't evolve it all the
way to Venusaur so wait for community day so I have that purified pokemon that's high levels
that'll be fun so anyway um I also played um so this is fun I have a little bit of b-roll of this
oh yes b-roll yay b-roll so um unfortunately it's not going to be great for those of you guys in the
podcast uh so I apologize but I will talk through this here a little bit so um earlier today I took
a some b-roll of myself playing destiny 2 on google stadia so uh this is what you guys are
going to see watch now is I'm firing up google stadia and I kind of wanted to show you guys what
it looked like so like the process and uh the green screen effect was horrible I didn't have
a chance to tune it so just uh please especially as the the monitor my main monitor gets bright and
dark the green screen screws up more and more so um sorry about that so anyway uh how did I get
google stadia did I buy it no those buddy passes came out where you can give it to a friend and a
friend can get three months so our pal Bobby Blackwolf who's on before us here Sunday nights
at vog was a buddy and gave me his buddy pass so I could check out with google state so I could do
impressions here on the show just like he did his a little bit uh except and and Jason did a fabulous
job here on this show and him and Bobby both talked about samurai showdown so I was like
well I'll play the other game I don't I don't mind I mean I know not a lot of first-person shooters
people want to play but I don't mind destiny too I think it uh the destiny series is one of the
better uh first-person shooters so why not so you'll notice for those that are watching I'm
still trying to get into the game so spoiler alert it still takes a good two minutes to launch the
game now that's because I'm counting the time of you gotta wait for the game to load up stadia then
you gotta get to the start menu and then it does all the security checks after the start menu and
then you gotta pick what you want to do and then here in this phase I'm waiting for two other
people to join my fire team so I can go down and do this random thing I don't even I haven't even
been paying attention to the stories I've been playing um but I can go I'm waiting patiently so
I can go down uh on the fire team and go to the planet and uh do what I need to do it's like
Final Fantasy 11 all over again yeah waiting for group now quest buster in chat says wow I'm behind
on light levels the game starts you at 750 I have not played the game that much on stadia's but so I
started off with like um 750 so it was pretty pretty high when I started off so anyway uh how
did I like it how was the experience of playing on google stadia well I wanted you guys that are
on twitch to be able to see some of the visuals so you could kind of see what it looks like and
honestly I think the visuals look fine it looks like you're playing a youtube basically I mean
there is a notice because I actually bought destiny 2 um on battle net way back when when
they first launched on battle net I bought it there and I've been able to play that in 2k mode
on my monitor um and it looks really sharp when I'm playing it in 2k mode um so um I don't think
it quite looks that good uh the colors get just ever so slightly washed like when you probably
watch youtube's of your favorite game um online you probably notice there's a little bit of a
wash over the screen a little bit and that kind of holds true when I'm playing in stadia and again
I'm playing on a web browser I'm not playing on my television because the buddy pass didn't exactly
give me a uh chromecast or anything like that uh and as Bobby points out in chat remember Rob is
playing the 1080p version too and yes that's the other point is that I'm used to playing in 2k but
when you are playing destiny 2 in the browser you're actually only getting it at 1080p wait a
minute I thought stadia did 4k yeah me too but I guess developers have not yet enabled the 4k
streaming or they're not officially supporting 4k streaming at this time um so I'm not actually
playing it in 4k but when it comes to how much bandwidth am I actually using to play this the
answer ends up being and not that much it's not that bad because I'm uh in 1080p and you have to
remember that is further being downsized to the 720p that you guys are seeing in a smaller than
720p window here so it actually probably looks even better uh for you guys um that are watching
it on twitch right now um me being really bad at shooters but very satisfied that I shot that
rocket and blew that guy up so um now prince bright star asks the very important question
how is the lag and I'm gonna say that is where I was most impressed with stadia I didn't notice it
like you'll notice I'm just plunking away playing my first person shooter the only thing I'm getting
frustrated at is how bad my aim is I'm not actually frustrated at oh why am I shooting
that ship I have no idea anyway it has a health bar it can be damaged it has a health bar shoot
it out of the sky anyway um but yeah honestly like the lag pretty good like it's not noticeable
like I was able to successfully you know do what I needed to do while I was playing this um
so there's that uh and yeah I mean even though I kind of tease it for taking two minutes to launch
I realize that it is an online game and you know you have to find a party and so forth
so for the most part a lot of that is understandable I'm not having to wait for
it to install patches or anything like that I was able to just kind of get up and running
so what did I think of google stadia not too shabby honestly like as far as the technology
goes especially if I wanted to just keep playing in 1080p like this here's where I think google
stadia is going to run into a problem the I'm not it's a lot of it's to do with the pricing honestly
like I'm playing this because it's free for me for three months thanks to bobby having paid for
it uh and I'll probably try out those other games that are gonna be free as well but that's only a
handful of games I'm gonna have for 9.99 a month whereas in contrast xbox game pass has a ton of
stuff on it right now yes you have to download that stuff to your computer right now how much
exact how much longer is that going to be a thing as we get closer and closer to xcloud being a
reality so I kind of think google's implemented something you know technology that's pretty nice
um but I think microsoft's about to throw them under the bus in about a year uh that games pass
man that that's gonna really do it next gen I think even this generation but like it's a really
nice offer and I mean I keep looking at xbox ones I'm just like no I'm gonna buy the next one but
I don't know it's it's uh because I know with being in this generation uh mainly playstation
you know I have a huge library of games I got with playstation plus I don't feel so bad
losing out on that being that um I'll get it all back with games pass anyways so anyway that's me
playing uh destiny 2 on stadia so just wanted to I wanted to have a little bit of the visual for
those of you guys on twitch you can see like what does it look like what does it actually look like
when you boot up how does it go into the game so I wanted you guys to be able to see a little bit of
that I have something else to talk about that's a little bit unrelated sure why not just go ahead
and sum up I was um I don't know if there's a lot else to say on it it's again it's one of those
things where I think the technology is not I mean with as much as we're complaining about bandwidth
caps and all that stuff like if I'm still just streaming things at 1080p I don't know if that's
really going to become an issue for me I mean maybe I want to try some things in 4k later maybe
that is going to be an issue later on I'm not trying to deny that that is an issue but 1080p
is good enough just like a lot of 2k gaming for me is good enough right now and I'm enjoying it um
I think I think stadia has more of a struggle on its monetary structure it's kind of the same thing
Jason said last week it's more the the structure and and how they want you to pay for games when
you look at what some of the competition is doing and especially how they're positioning the chess
pieces like we're talking about with xbox that's where I fear for stadia but if stadia can put
together something real quick that can rival game pass in a way it might be more tempting anyway
before I get to my next game Jamie you had a different thought I just wanted to go ahead and
mention that today is also uh world aids day excuse me um and so I just wanted to make sure
that I put the mention out there for everybody just have the awareness of it and keep those
that we've lost in mind so that is an important note thank you for that and I think it's very
important everybody know their status and your sexuality has nothing to do with that everybody's
know their status everybody should know yeah so so um it's very very very easy to get tested
and uh you know in fact it's not the death sentence it once was if you catch it and treat
it there's ways to um you know uh basically suppress you know I mean not that we should
overlook it by any means but you know there's also this uh saying that undetectable is
untransmittable so if you get it treated and you can get down to levels where it's undetectable
in your system you still have a lot of options I will you know kind of leave that out there but
there's many many many ways you can kind of get treatment for that that weren't there when people
were first talking about this in a lot of the media and stuff in the 80s and 90s so definitely
look into your local resources check and see if you've got like an LGBT center in your town
look for you don't even need that I mean yes it is resources sure resources and you see if you've
got sisters in town you know sisters will always help you with resources and education but
definitely just make sure that you take care of yourself and it doesn't matter if you what gender
you identify with what your body is like who you like sleeping with or not at all if you've had
contact with and I'm not just gonna say you know coitus or anything like that but even if you've
had injections recently if you have to say you know if you've had a blood transfusion I know
the doctors are very careful with it but I mean that's how Ryan White got it in the 80s for a lot
of that is tested and different now it's different now there's no excuse you should know your status
exactly so so I'm saying you know I never take it for granted yeah so and one of the quick thing
I'll say it's really easy like when I go to my doctor and my doctor is like I want to do blood
because doctors want to do blood tests all the time right I go in I'm coughing too much let's
do a blood test and I'll usually ask if it's been you know six months since last time I'm gonna ask
I'm gonna say hey since I'm going to lab anyway can you throw in this HIV test as well the worst
I've ever gotten from the doctor response is do you have a reason to be concerned I'm like no I
just want to know my status okay that's that's it they're gonna throw it in they want you they
want you to do that test too so anyway good life lesson from dark soccer mixed in here with the
gaming stuff all right um other games though I will mention uh for my gaming week pokemon shield
so here's here's the update on pokemon shield I beat it that's right I got all eight gym badges
I fought uh the championship and I became the champion and I caught the um legendary uh
that is integrated in the story so I don't know how much I should say into that not the sword and
shield legendary that is the post game so that's the one that's at the beginning of the game yeah
the very very beginning of the game that is the post game legendary um so I have not yeah I have
not done the post game content yet I'm sure I'll get around to it at some point but then I got
derailed with another game that I'll talk about in a moment um but honestly you know I know we
were just kind of talking about pokemon the controversy and everything I really enjoyed
gen 8 I really really enjoyed gen 8 and I think some of the major differences for this I've never
beaten a mainline pokemon game before I've never gotten this far in a mainline pokemon game
shane was shook he might not show it because he's shane but he was shook definitely that I beat the
game um but uh here's some things that made this generation different number one getting to be able
to play it on my television versus being forced to do it on a handheld I think there's just something
about that experience I've always enjoyed gaming on the tv more being able to kind of plop on my
couch have the big screen and the sound bar and everything um that was really cool number two I
think the wild area was a pretty good change because I don't feel this need to grind every
pokemon that I miss on a route because I kind of know like a the pokedex shows you what you're
missing from a certain route so you know you can kind of always go back and get it later um and you
don't feel the need to like oh I gotta go check this online reference I used to do in some of the
older games and most of them are available in the wild area number three which I think is the
biggest one raiding dynamax rating changed it because now I don't have to grind battles over
and over and over again to raise the experience level of my pokemon if I do enough of those
dynamax raids you get candy from those raids and you feed the candy to your pokemon and the candy
levels them up and it's a great alternative to grinding and I think that was a huge part of it
and it's funny because I hear this game get a lot of shit because people go it's not as long as the
prior games well how many of those hours in pokemon blue were you fucking grinding on a certain route
over and over again to either catch this pokemon that only showed up five percent of the time
or to over level your pokemon so that way the next gym fight would not be that big of a deal
like so I kind of think there's that I'll need to consider when you're talking about the length
of the game is how much of the game was actually interesting sorry not sorry anyway that's a good
thing for pokemon gen 8 in my opinion and yeah I mean those are some of the big things I'm trying
to think what else I said when I wrote this post on twitter because somebody like directly asked
me the question why did this gen stick when the other gens didn't but those are some of the
biggest ones right there that you know just made this a lot of fun the end game did kind
of keep going and going like I thought I was ready to beat it and it's like no you have to go here
and there but I don't think that's a bad thing at all I mean you know because this game's gotten
crap for its story too I suppose I will say I saw a critique about how the game felt like you
weren't an active participant in the story that the story was kind of happening around you for
the most part and I will say I do see truth in that critique and I can see where that bothers
some people I don't think that's to say you don't actively participate at all no certainly there's
very important things that your character does in the game but I can get the sense that there's a
lot that happens that you don't see or you're not involved with that feels a little weird so I do
think that's a valid critique there but it didn't really bother me to the level that it's may bother
some other people in that so anyway Bobby in chat says not as long as a positive for me I'm
debating on getting it especially because it's not as long as it only has a subset of all Pokemans
it's it's a good one to start with I think there's a good reason why they put it on the switch
I think all the Pokemon will come back when they do probably a remake they'll probably do a remake
of gen four I don't where did they leave off I can't remember Pokemon Uber and Pokemon ultimate
there there is a part of me that wonders if they won't just do since everybody's whining if they
won't just do like a Pokemon ultimate that has every Pokemon today in it that's just a side
Pokemon world traveler yeah maybe something that takes you through all the regions but like an
abbreviated they should have a collection collect them all no like a collection like a few games in
one you know like a few generations and then just one continuous Pokedex that you can use between
them those are all great ideas so but I hope they'll never do any of them I hope there are
conveniences from this generation and quality of life improvements that they do look at implementing
um in any remake or future generation so uh Elliot B says I don't think I've gotten past the third
gym on any Pokemon games in Sapphire same uh I just get bored around the 10 hour mark same
but this time when I got bored I just went and did dynamax ratings uh and uh can you start off
with those because I've got those little pink areas to look yeah if you can see the pink areas
I would say once you get your Y-com which is before the first gym you can raid um you don't
want to necessarily jump in all the five stars but you can you can raid well the last thing that I
did was the um uh the the mines on the way to the first gym so I might do it after the first gym
yeah so after the first gym is a good time and honestly if you get the first gym the second gym
is just a hop skip and a jump over the first three gyms are all pretty easy to knock out
and then you kind of have a wait before you get to the fourth gym but anyway um so that is uh
that is my thought on Pokemon Gen 8 I think it's great um I think a lot of people who are talking
bad about it probably haven't played it yet that's not to say none of the criticisms are valid and
it's not a perfect game but it's pretty darn good and it made a great impression on me needs better
fashion sense I mean white shorts with white leggings no girl you do get to redress him
that's one of the first things terrible yeah I so is that your gaming week uh one more one more
okay so one more game I said it was a busy week sorry guys so one more game so um I went out
on Thanksgiving and yeah I was one of those people who went to Target on Thanksgiving but I did as
well I was really nice I didn't spend any money yeah so I I went and um you know what the reality
is like Alan and I were going stir crazy we were bored like we have nothing to do on this holiday
what do we like is anything open so we're like let's just let's just go to you need to play
ingress listen no no god I'm like over that anyway so like I was like let's drive to target if the
parking lot is a shit show then we'll just drive somewhere else we'll go on a drive uh but the
parking lot at Target wasn't that bad it was just like a really bad Saturday morning pretty much and
we went in and um there was a ton of people staffing and they had a system and it was fine
and I just was very polite I was asked to go stand to one line versus another and I'm just okay I
talked to the guy about video games so I just you know tried to you know if I'm going to be a monster
and shot the Thanksgiving then at least I can be a nice one um so anyway I got a copy of Death
Stranding that's the that's the point and so I've been playing Death Stranding I'm probably about
six hours into Death Stranding um or as I called it what did I say in that text message I sent to
um Shane I said Death Cake Stranding yes or in the opening of the show tonight let's see I said
Reedus's baby fetus no there's all of that too this might be the strangest game ever I'm carrying
a dead body on my back across these scenic landscapes constantly having to use l2 and r2
to shift weight while hipster music plays in the background yep girl learn to crouch and uh dark
Tetsuya says I still like Dark Souls of walking here's the that description is completely accurate
it really is the Dark Souls what do you do in the game you walk how do you know where to walk you
press r1 and it shows you where the dangerous terrain versus the non-dangerous terrain is
so you can kind of plot plot out carefully where am I going to walk and you do you have to adjust
your weight you have to l2 and r2 to kind of like grip the ground and one of the places where
I was really struggling was that there's these kind of like again I don't want to spoil story
too much but there's like these ghosty things that'll chase you and come after you and they're
trying to like basically kill you although well I don't want to spoil but they're basically trying
to kill you so um like I was getting really frustrated because the thing would go off the
baby would cry and it would say press r1 to hold your breath and so like okay I'm holding my breath
well the fuckers would still get me like every time and so I actually went to twitter and I
made a tweet I'm like what the hell am I doing wrong and somebody replied and said are you
crouching and I'm like oh oh yeah that's a thing it taught you in like the first 20 seconds of the
game isn't it but it never to my to my credit the game reminds you to hold your breath it never
reminds you again to crouch so I remembered then thanks to twitter to crouch and I was like okay
this is a lot easier but the thing about crouching is then you move even slower
so it's like you are slowly going through these landscapes and don't leave corpses behind
oh well no and that has explained you very much in the story in the beginning well yeah but people
still do that shit but you know how like the very first mission in the game is moving a corpse
that's where I was at so um but anyway wait till you get to carry live people oh god
why do I have to carry live people they have legs they can walk on their own
no you gotta carry them just like the dead yeah so anyway um but I don't know it's it's weird like
the story is very interesting it's very cinematic it's very well done I didn't realize that Lindsay
Wagner played that part that she played and then it was like oh this by the way Lindsay Wagner
and she voiced the oh the the the I know you can't yes the the other character will just say
like that I know there's so many like spoilery things I could say but I'm trying to be good
she voiced 1.0 and not 2.0 yes yes that is and she but she provided the likeness for 2.0 yes
okay so um anyway so um where was I oh Lindsay Wagner was on this television show in the 70s
called the bionic woman and the main character in the bionic woman was Jamie Summers
it said spelled differently spelled differently that's where I took my stage name from yeah
uh quest buster says most weapons are non-lethal for a very good reason yeah I noticed that when
I would tackle people you weren't killing them and that does make sense because the story explains
why dead bodies you won't leave them around um so you had to basically tie people up and that
was it you incapacitate people just leave them on the ground squirming because you have to do that
one of the early missions which would suck if an actual BT did come by for them yeah um but then
questmaster says most weapons are non-lethal okay but the weapons there are are pee pee poo poo
that's the weapons in the game are pee pee poo poo like and I was like this game is infatuated
with pee pee poo poo because there's this whole there's this whole thing like when you're like
you are sitting in your little dorm room or whatever spoiler to say that the main character
special yes the main character is special and uh has special pee pee poo poo and it can actually
and his blood you're making a face but it's true no no I'm I know but the it was actually to me
that was an interesting concept you know then they they rationalize it completely in their
own weird way why pee pee poo poo is effective yes you learn more though about him as a character
than the reason why his bodily fluids and excrement are powerful you see this is why this
is why they warn you that drinking too many monster energy drinks is a bad thing it does
eventually kill the undead so I mean game of the year contender death stranding is infatuated with
pee pee poo poo and it actually it tries to it rationalizes everything it rations this is why
I am obsessed with pee pee poo poo here's the whole my thing like if they're collecting blood
from him every time he stops to rest how much of his blood do they have like there are so many
depending on how often you rest in the game or how many days passed it's just although the there's
one have you had the dream sequence yet with uh with uh BB yeah a couple I don't know I don't
know if there's a particular one crashing through no the head butting no okay okay first of all I
absolutely love the bridge baby I don't I don't like BB I don't like the usage of a baby in that
and especially when they start explaining how like that was just really the still mother
yeah that's just that was a bit much for me I think it's the side of me that doesn't care
for horror films I was like do they do they really have to do this but I like bridge baby as you get
to know the bitch bridge the bitch baby did you really as long as you learn more about the bridge
baby as you go along so I really like the bridge baby as a character as a conduit to all these
other things that went on in the game yeah and I'm gonna leave that again like that again they
explain why a baby like they explain it all why pee pee poo poo they explain it everything is
logically baby pee pee poo poo no there's no baby pee pee poo poo it's pee pee poo poo and baby
because baby because bridge baby is still living in in bridge baby sack but anyway anyway did you
meet mama yet no because that's what I'm planning on is one of my cosplays next year okay is mama
well I've seen mom but mama oh oh yes I've met mama yes yeah oh you meet her in like the first
opening sequence of the game right but that's like I'm good I'm planning on cosplaying mama
and I'm trying to figure out how to do her um accessory interesting so anyway yeah and then
the one more I swear only one more thing I have to say about pee pee poo poo but since it's so
central to this game when you are in the dorm room and you press the button to make Norman Reedus
poop which I think is the x button which yes is a thing you can do push button push x to poop
and you push it and he gets in he gets at the end it doesn't it's not showing you anything nasty
it's one of those like screens it's it's not the south park you know game where there's like a
little mini game the at the poop no it's there's this screen that comes up with the frosted glass
so you can't see anything advertising some show there's a fucking advertisement for a real show
in it's Norman Reedus's actual show on AMC and I was like what Rob what what on earth is this
when he's sitting downstairs his crotch repeatedly I've you know I tried did you get punched I did
not get punched but he did the thing he's done a few weird things the thing that weirded me out
was after the press x to poop and then he got the frosted glass when he gets out he sits back down
he looks over at me and winks and I'm like why are you that are you Norman Reedus are you hitting
on me that's not the time to be hitting on me number one this is the crazy thing I never
thought he was attractive until this game seriously but no it's not until you see a man defecate
you truly no attraction pixel paka says I just pooped winked yeah that's kind of what it is
I pooped it's like in the silent earth for mst 3k did you make faces in the in the mirror
yes and do the selfies and stuff yes I did find that okay but just stare at his crotch
like he does different things if you stare at his crotch a lot yeah yeah I heard so anyway um so I
don't know so so then the the 50 million dollar question in chat swung tong asks should I say the
$60 question in chat uh is it worth $60 I don't know yet I I still have more to traverse in this
game before I truly know if it's worth 60 bucks I will say this for a I I think it is an excellent
fucking troll on behalf of Hideo Kojima I don't know if this was planned or not but there's all
these people on twitter that love to bash walking simulators right it's like walking simulators
aren't games they're just they're just this there's a story that plays out while you walk
and I feel like Hideo Kojima was like hmm walking simulator I'm gonna make the ultimate walking
simulator and that's what he's done he's made the ultimate walking simulator game and yet nobody's
complaining about it I will say this though I do think the way it incorporates the online is pretty
fucking clever like uh I don't know if you guys know this but you can actually kind of edit the
terrain so like not like dig holes and stuff but like let's say there's a particularly nasty part
of the river to cross you can build a ladder or even a bridge to help you cross the river
and other players will see that in their games and they can send likes which help you in your game
so that was kind of fascinating and lends itself to this very like in your face theme to the other
big question what the fuck is Death Stranding about the fact that we have a need to be connected
that is what Death Stranding is about and at least early in the game where my head is that from what
we have a need to be connected but if you're also looking at it from the perspectives of the people
that you need it could also be involved with the dangers of being too connected that's true it's
very End of Eva for me yeah have you seen End of Evangelion no of course not well shit yeah the
whole game just strikes me as I think that Kojima like got really drunk one night and watched End of
Evangelion on repeat and then decided to make a walking simulator out of End of Evangelion without
giant robots appropriate so much in common with the Evangelion mythos but I did think you know I
will say this from for for all the pee-pee poo-poo jokes for all the weird baby things that happen in
the game for all the Guillermo del Toro appearances except it's not really Guillermo del Toro doing
the voice somebody else no it's not him it's credited in the very beginning it's um yeah
it's the it's the voice of LeFou from the original Beauty and the Beast oh okay yeah I thought that
they said that it's his likeness but it's not his voice all right well at any rate um I like his
character oh yeah he has a he's a great character when he showed up so early I was like oh I thought
this guy just had a cameo but no he's he's plays a pretty big role in it yeah I like I really this
is one of the few games like this that I've truly liked all the characters except for like one of
the bad guys yeah but um because he was just nuts anyway but I even liked one of the other
reoccurring quote bad guys and I like I even like the big quote bad as well I do not like 1.0
version but I like 2.0 version I like the um the mule was that their name the guys with the gold
skull masks and the I think that's a really rad look and I think who also has a really rad look
is that guy who has like a black plastic mask on over his face oh die hard man yeah die hard man
I think he's got a really rad look he I'm still kind of of two minds about that character
but his actor did like one of my tweets that was cool oh that's cool um I love the look like yeah
I would say there's a lot to cosplay in this there really is he's actually a handsome fellow
by himself anyway I want Loki to cosplay um Sam Bridges Porter uh carrying 200 kilograms of cargo
because it's ridiculous but kind of awesome all right but no one of my favorite characters in
the game could be considered uh an antagonist hmm right we'll leave it at that there's more like
six hours in and I feel like there's still so much more to uncover but I will say the whole like we
are connected and the way so my point I was getting at for all the peepee poo for all the
baby stuff the the fact that the theme of the game is around connection and the need to be connected
to people and so forth or maybe not the fact that then he built this online component that
allows you to be connected in the process of playing this game I was like aha that is art
and that was my review of Death Stranding
what'd you think Loki are you gonna buy the game no I don't know I like I yeah I don't
know I think some people will love it and some people will hate it um that's and isn't that the
isn't that the great part about video games I don't know anyway but I I I would still though
I think that even though that's one of my favorite characters I'm actually gonna go and say that
both Mama and Lochna are probably my favorite I could see you cosplaying Mama yeah they're my
they're really my favorite characters in the whole thing yeah I like the concept between them
all right well let's move on uh let's talk about so we've only been here talking about our gaming
weeks for like an hour sorry that was mostly my bad but I like I said I played a lot this week
what can I say so we do have some video game news we want to get into um quickly some housekeeping
uh we should be here every week through uh December because um the holidays this time are
on weird days so they shouldn't interfere with our show the next show we will be gone will be
Martin Luther King weekend January 19th I believe it is so here's the thing and you guys actually
don't know this you're finding this out for the first time uh Allen bought us an anniversary gift
today so we're going because January 19th actually happens to be our anniversary so we are going to
see um Dear Evan Hansen that night here um because um I was kind of complaining about wanting to see
it on Broadway I was like oh I want to see that so he made it happen so we're gonna go see that
that's Disneyland week for me well oh that's right you weren't gonna be here anyway right
well no I would have been because we don't leave until that Monday but all right well
but it's gonna be Disneyland week for packing for Disneyland week so all right yes exactly
all right what do you wanna say something before we get into this I'm not doing anything special
but do a stream well I might well if my computer would stop shutting down every five seconds
remember I'm still trying to get my computer or not being a shithole oh yeah there is that
because I've been needing to work on a website and do logo work every time I open my fucking
photoshop to do to piece more on our logo my computer shuts down so I think I'd need to
actually replace all the ram in my system and maybe update my bios I don't know but it's it's a
pain in the ass um but I did have just a small little thing that good that happened to me that
I just found out about yeah I told you when I got in okay so that podcast that I really like called
uh stuff mom never told you you know one of my letters got right out and we got some shout outs
for the show I got another shout out on that podcast for Muppet Babies when are you guessing
I don't know if I'd go to Atlanta and volunteer just because I think that uh you need to go to
Atlanta for Dragon Con and then do they go to Dragon Con maybe I've met them yeah Annie goes
to Dragon Con I've probably met them and I didn't even know who they were I don't think Samantha
Samantha doesn't cosplay but um because I think this Dragon Con was her first one from listening
to the show okay but um Annie does cosplay she does a Winter Soldier cosplay Bobby do I know
these people but in any Bobby does Atlanta better than I do but at any rate um I I've I would
actually I mean I don't know if they're listening they said they'd check us out but if I would love
to guest on their show and just talk about video games and women in podcasting they the one I'm
listening to right now is their episode on fan girls but they've done some great ones about
toxic fandom gatekeeping all kinds of things I totally would say check out the one the fandom
specific podcast of theirs uh Bobby says I have to see him I'm terrible with names Bobby's like me
like I'm so visual like you could tell me about a person I'm like I what do they look like what's
her face like and then I'd be like oh sure I've met this person um anyway uh it's horrible for
a podcaster I know uh I just tagged the both of them in one of my last tweets so sweet um one
thing I want to ask real quick what was the Muppet Babies thing before we get into okay so they were
they did an episode about puppetry and women in puppetry and so um Samantha was talking about
Muppet Babies and they got on a little tangent about Muppet Babies and you know are they like
there's the reboot of them and I happen to be at Target literally after listening to this podcast
and I saw Muppet Babies toys so I just snapped it and put it on Twitter said hey Samantha look
what I found and so she replied back like yeah I remember when Muppet Babies were first in the
Muppets Take Manhattan because not everyone knows that that's the origin of Muppet Babies
and so she mentioned it on the podcast I was like hey my my trivial knowledge is not as
trivial you can be hosting your own damn thing for 800 episodes and it's still fun to get mentioned
on a podcast that you like and respect you know yeah it's still fun I still remember when you were
on Greg Proops' podcast yeah a few years ago and he went off on my question yeah you were in a good
way in a good way yeah um this was and he's still doing that show right yeah I haven't
listened a while we went to the punch line here and I was absolutely just and he actually signed
the back of his show notes for me and gave it to me and it's framed somewhere in my house he just
told me to keep being awesome I was like that's pretty cool because I asked him if we were heading
for a repeat of the French Revolution or the Bolshevik Revolution because of the way our
economy and society is moving and that he just went off on that one and it was beautiful.
Swongtong in chat says I'm pretty sure I met Rob but was too scared to say hi years ago at PAX lol
I'm bummed to hear that I wish you had said hi but let me let me tell you like a secret so if
I seem like I'm really like in a zone or like off-putish or something like that when you see
me in person or whatever I seem like I'm I'm in doing something else or whatever like trust I am
just as nervous as you are like that's some tea so just you know especially at PAX it had to have
been packed I can't believe I wouldn't believe this was PAX08 in Seattle because we were all
there so it would have been one of the PAX East that they're referring to and so those shows to
me were like I was in a town I'm not that familiar with I was at a show that I didn't really have an
agenda for because especially the most recent packs they like well what the fuck ever obviously
say it I think Bobby said it on his show too they fucking invited us to do a panel then said never
mind we don't want you to do the panel because we got bigger names to do the panel essentially
that's the message that I was heard so I was kind of like in that one of those moods where I was
like I don't even know what I'm doing at this con except oh I'm having a good time being here with
Bobby and running into some of the people I do know back here but I had like no agenda or things
to do there so I was just probably like kind of like off of my own little zone or whatever so um
yeah please say hi I promise I don't bite unless um consent is given uh sg100 matt says rob's a
pretty cool and fun guy in person thank you for that I appreciate that so all right anyway uh
Bobby says they invited us to be on a panel then they took the panel off the schedule then we
applied as media and they declined us so we had to bypass this from a listener true true and true
and the only thing that I added is that that they took the panel off the schedule to replace
it with one with bigger people that's what it was anyway anyhow let's move on we have other
gaming news to talk about Loki's gonna start us off yes and so we've got apparently dev p
a playstation 5 death kits spotted in the wild so there is a photo that leaked out to the internet
of apparently two of the playstation 5 dev kits and we know these are
allegedly playstation 5 dev kits based on the filing that we saw with um you know a story on
that a few weeks ago yeah the patent office and it looked fucking weird they are like this weird
v-shaped system uh with all these vent holes and stuff on it and yep that's what it looks like
some weird v-shaped system with a bunch of vent holes in it so I don't know I mean that doesn't
necessarily mean that that's what the final system is gonna look like but at least we have
an idea of here's what the dev kit looks like and that they're out there um I hope the final system
doesn't look like that but it's an odd shape I don't really understand the the purpose behind
all the vent holes and the way it looks it's I don't know it almost looks like something you
would see like you know someone trying to kick start their own like game console or something
like the phantom system or something like that I'm trying not to read too much into it because
it is a dev kit and I highly doubt this with the actual no it's not sleek looking at all so um a
logical uh conclusion in our chat from prince bright star who says it'll help with airflow
if people try to stack things on top of it that could be like if you had these units kind of
stacked on top of each other if you're trying to test something like multiplayer but I mean
I I can't imagine that this is the final thing since I mean that thing is thick remember when
we were looking at the original xbox one and it was everyone kept comparing it to like a vcr I
mean this thing is huge it's super thick so I don't know I think it's just one of those this
is funky because it's not like a vcr looking thing or it's not a big box it's a very distinct
kind of shape u shape where the airflow is all around in that u um and it's it's just it's a
little weird and I think that image is jarring and kind of like what you said what makes this
newsworthy is that here we go we have a reddit post that basically confirms those you know what
we saw on the patent site some time ago so this appears to be the real deal now granted
we know fake news is out there we know it would be easy to fake these things because I'm almost
positive we've had fake system pictures before right and people fake them so you should take
this with a grain of salt as you should everything but on the other hand this is a dev kit and nobody
should be putting that much stock in what this thing looks like anyway yeah the playstation to
fake this is like you're playing yourself the playstation 4 dev kit anyways didn't look anything
like the playstation 4 when it finally launched anyways so it doesn't necessarily mean it's gonna
look like this it would be weird though if it is so I don't know yeah I guess we'll find out later
on yeah we will um and it'll be interesting too the repercussions how did an image like this even
get out like you know we had all those talks with ndas and I don't know if you read through the
comments but which I know you're not supposed to do but oops I did it I was doing some investigative
journalism and I went through the comments and some of the popular theories is that it was
possibly a cleaning crew that took the picture even though cleaning crews would still have to
sign ndas of their own you know I was kind of thinking well right now it's the holidays and
a lot of the usual people probably are not there so you probably have like other people in and they
may have signed ndas but maybe they're not as used to seeing this type of stuff or working with this
so I don't know my my tinfoil hat is that you had some type of holiday crew in there that was
not as familiar with the ins and outs so when they saw it they did something that they should
probably know they're not supposed to do but they haven't been tested with that before and so that's
where we're at because yeah um somebody else pointed out you can if you were to do some
photoshop fucking around you'd be able to see the reflection of the person in that tv
that's in maybe as well these have a pretty good idea what they look like
I mean you can sort of see a shadow of a person but like I don't know if there's enough light to
actually yeah do anything with that yeah uh dark to see who says you know like the lead up to the
switch reveal oh yeah there were so many fakes then well remember when the nintendo revolution
was going to project holograms on your wall like that was the legit story which I remember that
was the story we talked about on this show I still think that was actually kind of a rad
concept or the the one that nintendo on that was like supposed to go on your head or something
that is like vr um and then there was the xbox light room but I think that really was that no
that is a thing the light room is they never did it they never pushed no that that was actually
through microsoft that that that wasn't like a rumor thing that was a luma room was remembered
they were showing a luma room light room yeah that's that's an adobe product yeah well what
better to talk about more rumors might as well hey you know what y'all it was a slower week because
the holidays so rumors and this show isn't just about reporting game news it's about talk about
talking about news and sometimes these big rumors are the things that people are talking about
especially when you consider the source of this rumor the source of this rumor is on twitter
leaky pandy um because this particular leaker has been right about other nintendo directs in
the past so this is a leaker with a with a with a resume basically so the tweet says
excuse me guys sorry for all the coughing noises and stuff but things happen um leaky
pandy says nintendo is planning two new metroid titles that will release in the next two fiscal
years respectively one is a re-release of metroid prime trilogy hd the second one is a
super metroid remake that mimics samus returns in style and scope well because i love me some super
metroid that second part i mean the first part kind of strikes me as a of course that has to
happen at some point it would be weird for them to come out and announce metroid prime 4 when we
haven't had a metroid prime game to reference in quite some time and granted we haven't even had a
metroid game to reference save for that 3ds relaunch remake or whatever in quite some time
so i i kind of feel like nintendo kind of has to do something to like remind us about metroid or
or put metroid back out there and make it current again so i feel like something especially like a
metroid prime hd or whatever remake collection it's it's got to be a legit you know they're
gonna want to have something that kind of leads right into four so that makes a lot of sense
the part about super metroid that's the part where i go okay now that's a little different
though that part i wasn't expecting yeah and although i i'm not i'm like you can't touch
greatness at the same time greatness is already available to play on the switch it's in the super
nintendo library you can go in and play super metroid assuming you have nintendo switch online
which i imagine many of you do um so it would be weird of them to just like re-release super
metroid if they don't make some pretty significant changes to it so i think a super metroid with
changes in the style of you know samus returns on the 3ds i i think is going to be different
enough where i don't think i will necessarily have to have this live in the shadow of the original
i'll be curious what they do with it if it's true you know and there is that big if that goes with
it what do you guys think it'd be cool to see them do like kind of what they did with was a
zero mission or you know something like that where they had kind of the extended super metroid thing
oh yeah like with the the more extended end and really the map was a little different too they
made some very subtle changes that kind of changed everything yeah um prince bright star in chat says
i have to wonder if that second release might support randomization which has become pretty
popular in the metroid and zelda communities you know i brought this up last week or the week
before about metroid maker how i was kind of getting into those made one of those ones like
randomizer type of things um i i would think it would be a beautiful thing for nintendo to
embrace that to an extent um you know i don't know why nintendo won't be willing to put their name on
it i mean i guess they feel it has to be of a certain quality and sometimes you can get certain
seeds that aren't great quality but i i kind of think nintendo really ought to try chancing it
especially with their classic nes library of just i mean sniping a zelda randomizer essentially
i mean it's for their game anyway and making it their own where you can generate seeds play
against other people online do your own speed runs like i i'm not sure why nintendo doesn't
try to embrace this a little more i mean maybe they just are okay with it happening organically
because you'll notice as far as i know they haven't ceased and desisted any of the randomizers right
which is kind of surprising they've just i mean the randomizers don't you have to have your own
rom so like the randomizers are in an interesting legal area in that regard they're not exactly as
touchable um but i'm still surprised nintendo's like not never tried to go after them so there
must be some benefit they're seeing to it i don't know so anyway uh it would be very curious to see
if this uh all ends up being true about uh the metroid and you know if they really did reboot
metroid prime 4 earlier this year then we've still got a couple years to go before that game
is out so i think if this buys us more time and creates more of an awareness or whatever you want
to say on hold another hardware by the time that game comes out um maybe i mean because it depends
if you want to believe there's going to be a switch pro or a switch plus oh isn't that supposed to
happen next year allegedly allegedly so we'll see we got switch light so we've already had the switch
minus although some people would say they love the switch light because they do mostly handheld
gaming and it is a nice looking thing especially if you have like some of the artistic clam shells
and stuff is a pretty nice looking device so um some people would say the switch light is not
necessarily a downgrade although um you know from the pure technical perspective of the fact that it
doesn't dock it is but that's okay they're charging you less for it so all right well moving on we do
have some more news for you guys dark sakura well now i will go ahead and before i even go into this
i will preface it saying that metacritic can be a little bit questionable um you know it's been
used to to hurt games it's been used to hurt people uh who are fans of games so with that
being said um metacritic published uh the 15 highest rated games of 2019 uh with exclusion
of certain ports um as so to go from the list the top two number one is resident evil 2 with
a score of 93 second is uh second uh shadows die twice followed by final fantasy 14 shadow bringers
rob i think you'd be happy with that um monster hunter world and disco Elysium which i'll be
honest i've never fucking heard of have you heard of disco Elysium yeah i haven't i'd have
to see a screenshot again the visual thing right that is really cool about shadow bringers though
um yeah number three yeah um after that is f1 2019 then devil may cry 5 fire emblem three houses
slay the spire apex legend as regards wrath super mario maker 2 with a score of 88 baba is you
the legend of zelda links awakening and astral chain so but the top three then being resident
evil 2 sekiro and uh final fantasy 14 just with final fantasy 14 is just seeing how much that
game came back from the garbage it was before they fixed the things i'd say that's pretty impressive
yeah and honestly the recent expansion is is stunning and um you know a lot of people
are missing out i think um though square enix is an interesting predicament where they need
a better catch-up system like so that people can just jump right in to the expansion i mean you can
buy like a potion that lets you story skip and level skip and all this stuff but like i don't
know you shouldn't have to buy that at the same time um they might want to consider giving one
away like they do with world of warcraft or um i i have heard the developers say they are working
on the story problem but it probably won't anything won't be in about that until the next
expansion so we'll see yeah and prince bright star says in chat they're redoing the 2.0 story
yeah i have heard that that they're gonna kind of redo that so um we'll see but anyway all that
aside uh shadowbringers is is excellent um kind of surprised to see it so high with all the other
games that have come out this year honestly so that is kind of an interesting treat if again you
put stock in what metacritic has to say having the resident evil 2 remake though at the very top of
it just seems a little bit questionable to me i mean it's really good please don't get me wrong
i think it's very well done it definitely improves on the original and ads i think it
actually changes some of the dynamics for the characters in the game um but it is a remake and
it is a fairly quick play so Sekiro has a much higher challenge level and it's actually about to
match i think the highest of the dark souls games um for its overall revenue um
but i am pretty happy to see those as the top three not super surprised yeah interesting of
those three i don't believe resident evil 2 is a game of the year nominee but Sekiro certainly was
and i think it was very pretty one of you guys said that one hard as fuck has a real shot at
maybe winning so we'll see what happens i think Sekiro absolutely does have a shot i mean it's
it's involved it's in depth it's hard as shit the challenge is real um but it's also got a
pretty good story and quite the amazing like introductory uh bit of uh that's what i'm
thinking of bit of the game uh prologue uh yeah opening chapter opening but i think that that it
definitely deserves to be on the list all right do and let me ask let me ask this follow-up question
how much stock do you put in what metacritic has to say and we'll throw rotten tomatoes in that you
know all those uh meta review type of sites i'm asking those in the room and over in our chat room
at twitch tv slash vog network my view of it is sort of a generic litmus test of what people
are going to think but again it's been quote weaponized as far as damaging certain material
that's come out especially the uh the little incels out there like to use it to damage
games with a strong female protagonist or things that try to that might challenge their little
male-dominated view on things we've seen it happen before those are user reviews though and
i always throw those out i especially on those sites i do not pay attention really i thought
there were just critic scores maybe i'm thinking rotten tomatoes i don't know but um well some of
the other ones out there so i don't really put the stock in reviews unless it's some like if i'm
watching like say a a webcast that i like like something like um game sack i really i dude just
did a review of shanmu 3 and i thought that his review sounded pretty good it was about what i
expected of the game and i've trusted his opinion in regards to sega and you know former sega
franchises and things like that so um i trusted his opinion but it's getting a generic score when
it's going all the way across the board from people who may not necessarily be the gamer that
i am i may look at the score and then go look for reviews but for most of the case i'm gonna form my
own opinion on it the the numbers are in the end just numbers they're not going to speak to my
personal enjoyment of something granted i greatly enjoyed resident evil too it was really really
good i made dan take me in my pajamas to target to go get it and we had a great time with it
um there's other games on that list that i thought were really great like you know mario maker 2
and you know uh links awakening of course being on that list uh but overall i mean really i think
that the scores shouldn't be oh all these people thought it was great i should get it to no this
is why i miss game rentals outside of the red box i miss going to like a blockbuster or something
and renting the game and talking to the employees who might have also tried out said game and just
getting like an in-person thing i miss you know game stop is okay for that now i missed going into
some of the stores like that and having those talks with people i like to see what my friends
in the real world thinks like one of my friends crystal um you know there was a game i was super
excited about and they were all hey you know i don't this has just been getting pooped on by
this this and this and everyone says this about it and i'm like but they're not my opinion i want
to try it and see what i think yeah or people be like oh all these people think this movie is crap
and blah blah blah but i like xanadu yeah no it's kind of like it's kind of like i was joking or not
joking but talking about the walking simulators earlier and like a lot of people shit on things
like everybody's gone to the rapture because they say great there's not a game there but i'm like no
i fucking love that was one of my favorite things i played all year you know so there was a goal to
accomplish what makes that not a game yeah so there was there was something i enjoyed there
animal crossing doesn't have a game that you win there's more to do after you pay off your mortgage
right so but what's to say that that's not a game yeah you know what's to say that you know
reading a book and then playing a narrative game it's the difference between that you've read
something versus the fact that you have observed something let me quickly ask loki what do you what
is your stock in metacritic um i mean sometimes i'll kind of look at it just to get a general idea
of what a game's being reviewed as so like if i see some negative reviews in like like for death
strand or something like that where people are just hating on it i'll kind of look at general
consensus to see is everybody share that opinion does you know is only a couple of critics that
don't like it um stuff like that but usually like i have certain people that i will listen
to for their critiques on stuff because they have similar tastes than i do so um yeah i i will look
at maybe the broad stroke on metacritic like if something is reviewing particularly strongly or
particularly negatively that wasn't what i was expecting or you know wasn't on my radar i might
kind of look like oh what's what's this noise all about and maybe look a little more into that but
i think for some of those reasons the dark soccer kind of outlined that i just jumped on with that
you know what one just what a critic's perception of the game might not be my own i think for me
i put much more stock in things like twitch streams where i can kind of really watch people
play the game youtubes would be something like that as well but i like the live nature twitch
and all that so uh yep uh let's see some uh comments in our chat sg100 matt says comment
sections and game reviews is the reason i stopped reading the comments and game articles honestly
are you missing anything though no so good for you stopping uh metal mayhem says i never pay
attention to metacritic if anything i pay attention to what people on my miscellaneous
friends lists are playing good call um and bonds 006 says i don't care one damn what they have to
say in reviews if it's a review about a huge breaking feature of a game then yeah beyond that
so yep all right some good thoughts from you guys in our chat room over at twitch tv slash
vog network meanwhile let's move on to what's next on our list loki so yes unfortunately 2k
is going to be shutting um down or i should say gearbox is shutting down um battle born so they
stopped doing updates quite a while ago almost two years ago and now uh basically 2k said as
of january 2021 the battleborn servers are going to be deactivated cue the cynic in me that says
it was still open um right but you know one of the things if you do buy a game like this that is
only online it is now either your copy that you have is completely useless although to be fair
it is free to play now so that's not such a big deal but it still kind of sucks if you did end up
purchasing it at one point or another didn't one of these articles or one of the talk about it
talk about how like wow what's that steam website people use steam spy or something like that yes
and i did look at the steam spy numbers and yes all 12 of you that are playing the game right now
or you actually have it up right now so 12 p even in spite of this news that it's closing soon that's
been everywhere it has gone up so like so the average number of players is about 12.6 for the
last 30 days peak being 42 players okay okay so but that's in the world in the world at one time
yeah that's and and by contrast name and is there any literally any other recognized game that you
could give us for con context like uh versus battleborn like dota how many people are playing
dota 2 let's see i'm just trying to think uh i was gonna say totally accurate battle simulator
um not battle simulator uh totally accurate uh battle royale simulating spy won't show you
things like fortnite and um you know blizzard based games like overwatch and things like that
so you have to bring up something like dota or um uh what about oh paladins is that on steam uh
yeah i think paladins how many people are playing paladins compared to battleboard hold on i was
just gonna pick this one because this is an indie game and i know it's pretty um
no they don't have okay let's see paladins we're just trying to get a comparison here so 42 people
at its peak we're playing battleborn this month all right we don't know i i don't like this let's
yeah let's try this here we go so like if you want to go down like something that like for example
dota 2 would have uh 314 000 concurrent players yeah um okay here's a much older game terraria
has 40 000 um concurrent wow terraria wow yeah okay um okay so 42 not that impressive of a
numbers that's sad and again we're not trying to like kick kick a horse when it's already down or
whatever i mean that's unfortunate and some of you guys are hitting the nail on the head in chat
um tiger class says ever since overwatch came out games like that were like it were struggling
ironically paladins though seems to still be kicking along and you know since i named that
one and bobby says hi rez and atlanta represent yeah but i've actually played paladins it's you
know it's a similar concept although they do different things as here i'm trying to go down
the list to get down to like some of the um lower doom 2329 like which doom the doom the original
do oh the original not even the 2017 remake or whatever i well it just says doom i don't know
if this is the uh remake one or not um because it doesn't really give me anything uh uh this might
be the remake actually i can't i can't really tell all right quest buster says it doesn't help
since uh that overwatch released a few weeks after battle born no it certainly doesn't
so all of that certainly comes into play so i was trying to find something that was like
really ridiculous um to compare it to that with just kind of go hey see you know this game is
kind of garbage and i don't know all right well moving on let's uh talk about xbox scarlets and
the oh here you go this i'm sorry i'm sorry this is the perfect example uno has 1075 players
concurrently versus yeah the 12 all right we we get the point we get it all right moving on let's
talk about what the future might hold for project scarlet which is the name of xboxes or microsoft's
next system uh there was an interview with games radar where uh the uh head of xbox game studios
gentleman named matt booty uh talks about the plans for scarlet's first party support uh saying
we feel really good heading into 2020 we've got a goal of being able to deliver a game
roughly every three to four months so that's kind of an interesting and honestly is anyone
surprised after hearing how many studios yeah i was gonna say with all those studios i mean that's
like surprising again i've been saying this i've been saying this for like a year and a half ever
since that news came out microsoft has been laying the chess pieces under phil spencer's direction to
not let their next console go like how xbox one's launch did and i am really here for it because
i think this type of competition they're going to bring to the table for the next generation of
games is going to be really exciting and i hope to fuck sony's ready for it um or we're gonna
or we're gonna flip-flop again and this you know this has happened every time right when the
original xbox was out playstation 2 was still ahead of it then sony fell on their face with
the playstation 3 reveal and the 599 xbox 360 was everywhere and then it flip-flopped again
playstation 4 yeah just just like just smack the shit out of xbox one live on stage with those
really like frankly smug commercials that were hilarious uh and all that stuff i i really hope
sony does not allow themselves to get crisscrossed again because sony or excuse me microsoft is
setting the table they are setting the silverware this is going to be and now you have to add this
whole cloud stuff into it too like even if you're one of those people that's like i never buy xbox
xbox isn't really my thing and you need to wake up and take notice to what's about to happen because
everything that's going to be xbox is going to impact the pc gaming world too where maybe you
do game so microsoft's going to really come out swing in 2020 i'm adding a little bit of editorial
to the real news piece there sorry uh which is uh the uh matt booty from xbox game studio saying
a goal of being able to deliver a game roughly every three to four months so um obviously halo
infinite is going to be one of those a big launch title um kind of piggybacking on this a little bit
cyberpunk 2077 um we know that game is coming out in march but it probably will not make
scarlet or playstation 5 right around launch and that is uh according to a new earnings call from
cd project red they are developing for the new console but they're not going to be able to
release this at launch it could be a cross-gen title but they don't want to target anything as
soon as holiday 2020 and i suppose that makes sense because who knows how much time they've
actually gotten to play with these new systems or anything like that so um bonds 006 in chat says
i was saying similar to a few co-workers earlier this evening about xbox and how it will impact
pc gaming absolutely and look i realize there's many of you out there who don't follow microsoft
because you're like eh halo not my thing and they don't have a lot of first-party franchises i'm
into and i get it i've been very much the same way sometimes but you have to understand phil spencer
ever since he took over he has been laying this plan out that you're gonna notice next year and
if your problem is their first party titles well this is why they acquired all of these new studios
to try to combat that problem if you don't really want an xbox because you're kind of like i'm over
buying all these different consoles well that's why we're gonna have streaming or we're gonna
have these features for pc like if you're a gamer don't sleep on microsoft i'm not even saying that
as a fanboy like i i like all games i'm just i'm excited for this competition and what this next
generation is going to bring like 2020 i think it's just going to be an exciting fucking year
in that regard right yeah like you know you guys don't really follow microsoft but you have to admit
like there's there's something to what i'm saying right yeah it looks interesting they're gonna
be because i haven't really bought i haven't really bought in on like a lot of the playstation
exclusive stuff so like uh for example you know god of war was all right death stranding
the strand is okay but like i don't know like like horizon's pretty fun last of us just doesn't
really do anything for me and same with uncharted and i don't know i even like on the microsoft
side like not necessarily force is kind of cool but i i just don't really know like i'm looking
a lot of multi-platform games and like especially you know deep down your favorite is nintendo it
still is all these years later we know it's still your fave i mean i guess all right well
it only took 800 episodes to get that all right all joking aside let's move on uh dark sakura
you love these types of stories so i know you want to talk about this tonight yes i indeed do
okay so i i'm sure people remember the legend of rod caliber right where we beat soul caliber
on dreamcast with fishing rod so and of course we've tried to use our ddr pads to play games
and things like that well someone and this is probably one of the few times i'm going to bring
up halo stuff on purpose someone beat halo 3 on legendary with the guitar hero controller
that is impressive um so and i mean we're talking about you know roughly a 10-hour game
but someone went in and did the thing with a guitar hero controller um there is a d-pad on
that thing now that i think about it like you can do it it's just like yikes that's that's wow
wow that's so he put a video up on it there's no analog sticks the username is super lewis 64
and um yeah there's a whole video up i'm sure they have a way how he did it um and he's using this
the strumming and using the uh the standard fret buttons and he actually put in there his mapping
with the fret buttons for how he had everything you know what they were what all the buttons were
set for and that the uh the the strum bar is for moving forwards or backwards and then left and
right or action you know uses a different modifying aim left aim right we're also set on
the empty so i'll um i'll find the video and link it in chat for everybody sorry i didn't know there
was a video i would have put it up as b-roll but that's all right for our podcast they're gonna
want to find it too so right and but the but it's put up by a super lewis 64 i'll i'll go ahead and
put it in the chat i'll make sure you get a link to it that's silly but fun yeah i wonder if that's
because like accessibility things that you know you can map anything to anything sure yes the
accessibility controller can do all sorts of crazy stuff with so all right uh this isn't quite the
same i think is using the rod cap uh doing rod caliber um sj100 matt in chat says i remember
hosting a party where we played mortal combat on ddr pads back in college with enough alcohol and
drive anything can be played on a different controller oh yeah for sure i thought didn't we
play something silly on the dreamcast ddr pads at your house i seem to remember that was a thing
those dreamcast dr pads were so weird too because they had that weird like plastic layer on top of
them that was kind of funky yeah it was super funky um i mean and mine like completely separated
so it was like you know a dance dance slide revolution fall on your face and die yeah um but
uh but boom boom dollar y'all right fucking boom boom dollar and i passed i mean that's the first
place i passed paranoia was at home yeah on the dreamcast i didn't have this vivid shit when i
was playing ddr fucking kids all right let's move on low-key all right so valve has uh taken a
thousand games off of steam that have been abusing their tools mainly a lot of these games are
actually from a specific uh user on actually i think a specific developer or several developers
are actually one developer so what they're doing is it's this uh publisher called uh
degstan technology had 48 games on the platform and um apparently there's um some other ones
yet they've lost their entire library but i think a lot of these could be that they're just like
re-release they're releasing games changing they're kind of abusing the system by just
spamming games on there like for example i've seen some videos before where they're showing
some of the games that they have where they'll just kind of change what the character looks like
and just republish the game over and over and call it something different or release a game
four times on the platform they try to get you know steam card sales um stuff like that there's
a whole a lot of it's made off of the steam card trading stuff where they you know anything that's
easy card earnings people will sell it and they get a portion of that and they make their money
that way and they give out the keys for free type of thing but um yeah they said that some of the
games though that were on there weren't necessarily um just put up there for a quick buck there's a
game called electric highways that had been on steam since 2015 had 1300 positive reviews so
i don't know why that one got banned but that's kind of weird um sometimes you make a broad
stroke like this you're probably going to catch a few that maybe were more of an on the bubble
sort of thing like maybe yeah without looking at like the exact games that were banned maybe that
person like put up a legit game and maybe start spamming games i mean who knows um but there's
a lot of um they said basically they said a handful of partners are abusing some of steamworks tools
um they didn't really specify what exactly they were doing or yeah all right well moving on
let's talk about um man you know earlier we talked about like final fantasy 14 and how that game has
really um come a long way uh since the beginning and now it's on these metacritic lists and so
forth well how about no man's sky this is another one of those games that has managed to really
reinvent itself and yet again uh they've put out a pretty major update it's not a major major update
but a pretty big update uh the synthesis update uh which includes a new upgrade system that will
allow you to go to one of the starship outfitting terminals to spruce up your spacecraft so you can
upgrade one of your ships all the way up to an s class and then you can add inventory slots to
a spaceship hooray that's good uh there's also a new salvaging system that or i should say the
salvage system has kind of been reworked a little bit so you can break down ships that you no longer
want into actual materials so that's pretty cool um a lot of quality of life improvements to this
as well hello games redid the inventory systems that's kind of interesting now you can just drag
and drop things uh into your inventory so that's yeah that wasn't there before so that's pretty
cool uh and you can do different outfits within the customized menu so you can switch between
outfits because dress up is a very important part of any multiplayer game so that's pretty cool uh
the update is out this week uh so it already came out i should say 300 bugs squashed in synthesis as
well and uh you know what a turnaround story again for this game you know our voiceover guy
jason and i were texting a little bit i still haven't played it since they've done all these
updates i really need to go back and i think if i remember correctly i did also buy it on pc so i
i really need to go back and these updates are for vr as well as non-v yeah i still haven't played
in vr yet either um so uh vr will let you ride creatures and do new no man's sky photo mode
so that's pretty cool cool yeah so um lots and lots of uh little changes they say over 300 bug
fixes uh and that was all out within this past week you know and i'm sorry a voiceover guy jason
and i were talking about how does this game kind of continue to make money because he was asking
me he's like do they have a storefront or are they selling like premium currency or something nope
they don't they don't sell any of that there's no uh further cost continuing sales i guess
games service there's no continuing service besides well they they released on two more
platforms so pc and xbox sure but that's a big difference from what anthem is doing to make money
right um so uh yeah i mean i the only thing i can come up with is that when they do these big
releases they tend to not put the game on sale they're still charging full price for the game
but i think full price for no man's sky is down to like 30 bucks and you're only paying that full
price if you buy it like you know right around one of these big patches otherwise you can usually
find it during a sale for a lot cheaper and i don't know with this being i didn't really look
because i already own the game on all the platforms i won it on but um i would imagine
like is there a um i don't know is there like a a sale going on right now for black friday that
maybe you can still pick this up cheap i don't know well cyber monday yeah and that too this
whole this whole kind of weekend i think a lot of websites just kind of put something up for
the whole weekend friday to monday yeah i was actually checking epic just to see what was there
and actually rayman legends is free right now oh is that their free on and that's their freebie
right now wow uh nifty 805 in our chat says i want a baby yoda sidekick it's not yoda yeah
it's yeah so i was gonna say it's it's not supposed to be yoda right well yoda's been
dead for like by because this is after return of the jedi uh-huh and yoda died in return of the
jedi uh-huh so spoiler i'm just kidding fucking a but it said in between um return of the jedi and
whatever the the new ray movie was um but it's they never did come out and name yoda species
there was another one in uh uh the the prequels that was named yaddle rattle something like that
but they never did mention the name of the species and for all the people out there by the way
who are saying that it's biting off of gremlins first of all fuckers empire strikes back came out
in 1980 or 81 80 something like that yeah it came out in 1980 gremlins came out in 1984 i
actually don't see the gremlins resemblance at all besides the pointy ears which is you know
vulcans had pointy ears come on little damsel like look at the eyes and be like it looks like
look at infant humans how big their eyes are on their faces right look at kittens how big their
eyes are on their faces it's a thing that happens with babies and it's roughly a toddler of its
species so stop it with a stupid meme it makes you look like an idiot bobby black wolf and chat
said boomer okay you know what i'm gen x all the way so you can bite my butt nobody didn't like you
i know forget it all right it's a meme i've seen the meme that meme's clever all right bobby says
it's baby yoda and tell the creators tell me what to call him or her or it yoder nifty 805
i'm calling it kiddo i know that it's not yoda but the internet um you know it's stupid too all
right quest buster says someone is working on modding baby yoda into battlefront too well
because the internet of course they are of course they are beyond two souls is 15 bucks all right
let's you know what let's travel back to a simpler time we're gonna travel back to a simpler time in
gaming where there was no baby yoda there was simply just yoda uh it's uh once uh once a week
we like to step into the gaming vault and find a game that dark soccer thinks hey you ungrateful
brats you should be checking this game out but in a 2019 twist once a month she likes to spotlight a
soundtrack for the month and i bet you guys have no idea what it is so i didn't tell you about my
fuck up earlier do you want to know about my fuck up dark so do you know how i i capture b-roll
every week so what i did is i clicked the button to start recording and then i went off to take a
shower the only problem is i clicked the button above the one that starts recording which is the
one to start streaming girl so anyone who went to my personal channel probably knows what's coming
so sorry about that but it was an honest mistake i'm more worried about the fact that
i broadcast a game that wasn't really the game and it was somebody else's playthrough
like i was like oh shit i don't want to get in trouble no nintendo is going to be sending
lawyers out well luckily it's not an internal game it doesn't matter they're gonna do it anyways
luckily i i tried to delete it all and and make no trace it was an honest mistake i think people
understand so anyway all right so uh i i apologize if it was spoiled for you but what is the classic
classic soundtrack of the month i picked fantasy zone but i specifically picked fantasy zone
for this sega mark 3 because first of all i love i fucking love this
you mean i'll turn up the sound a little bit here just for a moment yeah let's listen for a sec
this is on the strong part right that's really good this is an eight-bit uh system so for me
to get into this i'm gonna have to get into a little bit about the sega mark 3
the sega mark 3 is roughly considered the precursor to the sega master system
but the mark 3 was also marketed as a home computer of sorts physically it looks actually
kind of not unlike the atari home computers of of its era it is um an 8-bit uh an 8-bit system
but it had the plug-in fm uh music unit so um now built in it was just a ti sn76489
chip but you could like i said go into and attach the uh an fm module to boost up that sound quality
and that's what we're listening to here um as far as that fm sound unit on its own um
it would plug in it was its own little box to it um it was sold uh it starting in 1987 for 6800 yen
and it used a ym 2413 fm chip that built above the built-in uh ti chip texas instruments chip
and so when the sega master system hit the japanese market that fm sound unit was built
into the japanese version of the sega master system and of course not all the games released
supported this one but fantasy zone sure as fuck did and fantasy zone is great so um you know and
i've done fantasy zone for the classic game of the month too it came out in 1986 um and then it had
an international uh release after the arcade game um it was the first of its series and um it just
you know really keep gaming music's happy i can listen to this music all freaking day
but at any rate um its first port was to the sega mark 3 and the master system um and then of course
it got other reports um but the uh the music on this one in particular and of course with the fm
for the uh master system is that it opened up so many more channels if you listen to
the soundtrack from say the american release that doesn't have the fm sound
it is kind of dinky sounding but you get this and it's on par like i was saying earlier with the um
with the arcade um and i know i had the the all right there's the composer on here i had that
so the composer for this is um a kaguchi hiroshi um who has worked on a lot of of games for for
sega and this is actually one of the earlier games he worked on the first one was called
girl's garden and he worked on it with yuji naka he did uh hang on space harrier alex kid the lost
stars ghost house outrun enduro racers both afterburners uh other things that people would
know about turbo outrun sort of vermilion um trying to pick some other things rent a hero
outrunners and um he did like some other games too like some he did virtual fighter uh 3 tv
he did derby derby owners club online rob that's one of ours so he did our horse whipping game
and um he actually i fucking miss derby owners club more recently going back to our music game
roots worked on my mind in fact there's some really good remixes of fantasy zone music in
my mind but yeah the this really and i feel like i really missed out not having this as my first
home version of fantasy zone my first fantasy zone was i think the the tangen one um which it
wasn't very pretty i'll go ahead and just tell you that right now but um but i can't do our last
soundtrack of the month without doing such a classic that had such a beautiful you know
bright soundtrack for a home release and also to let people know that while we were sitting here
with our dinky dinky you know four channels our friends in japan had this and it's so completely
unfair all right there it is now i need to have my own sega mark 3 just because the classic
soundtrack of the month fantasy zone but specifically on the mark 3 so that that
system can be acknowledged at some point yeah and of course then the fm uh
uh i got my brain went to no my brain was going to say fm towns but i'm at the fm uh capable uh
japanese master system oh yes it is okay so and i think that there were versions of fantasy zone
for the towns but there was fancy zone on everything like you said somehow a sega game
like fantasy zone even ended up on the nes thanks to the whole you know tangen bottle so
it's it's it's uh quality is questionable so i don't actually think it did come out on on
towns oh well then super fantasy zone with sega mega drive which if someone can find me a legit
okay people in japan or somewhere in asia if you can find me a super fantasy zone for the mega
drive i will um i'll bake for you i will ship it to to your country all right so it and it
can't be a repro it has to be legit old school uh super fantasy zone for the mega drive
all right all right there it is the classic soundtrack the final one for the year 2019
so that's it so yeah next we should probably uh take a walk down memory lane and recap for the
year what all the classic soundtracks were but um in the meantime uh what what's coming up next year
pinball oh that's right classic pinball so i am gonna do things that are i'm gonna start with the
the ones that had a dmd so you know this got the animation on it not just like
and this actually does exclude one of my favorites rob it excludes black knight 2000
but it's going to be any of the era of games pre-pinball 2000 but starting with some of the
with whatever the first ones to have the the full dmd is so um if people have suggestions
go ahead and throw them my way or else you're just gonna be getting you know world cup soccer
every month kidding um but you know these and i'm trying everyone knows that like my freaking
favorites are like world cup soccer and theater of magic and all that but i want to go to some of the
other ones that might not be as well known but on a month you're feeling uh last minute you might
see one of those well and the the thing is is that there are good games that are pre that dmd area
that i think you know like swords of fury for example go fucking listen to the soundtrack
for swords of fury that is phenomenal it's great you know black knight 2000 also good but i want
to get some of those ones that people might have had a chance that they've seen while they were
new out in the wild all right well stay tuned for 2020 in that segment now to recap 2019 and
the classic 8-bit soundtrack of the month uh in january we had the guardian legend because of
course we did in february we had journey to sillius march we had avadox april we had jackal
may we had wonder boy 3 the dragon's trap june we had r-type july we had quartet uh august we had
blaster master september we had akumajo densetsu and october we had ducktales and november we had
metal gear and closing it specifically the msx msx 2 metal gear and closing out the year
specifically the sega mark 3 because it wouldn't be a jamie segment if she didn't like no no i
want to use this to spotlight the soundtrack and the system we have fantasy zone specifically on
the sega mark 3 um i honestly think the fantasy zone is one of those games that really did just
show off um the power of the fm unit yeah so if you're a little newer to orange launch radio um
dark soccer has been uh screwing with the segment for a couple years now we had in 2018 the classic
peripheral of the month and in 2017 it was the classic console of the month that was the one
that kind of started it all so um and you can uh visit all of that if you want if you're curious
has this game ever been picked uh go visit our wiki it's like a it's an unofficial slash official
wiki unofficial because we don't touch it or edit it because i literally don't know how like i have
to ping dark tetsuya on twitter and say help like i did that today i said help this is wrong can you
fix it do the thing um but also official in the fact that we we look at it and like the reason
why that all came up is because dark soccer and i were having an offline conversation and i was
like wait the wiki's wrong so we actually look at it and i couldn't tell you what happened on
the show last week and i kind of like had a feeling i did but i didn't see it on there i was
like well shit i'll do no i've had if i have a good idea what happened well i don't care i was
gonna pick duck tails again and i was like i remember cutting this video like just like weeks
ago yeah uh but no i and then rob's like are you sure and then we looked at the wiki together like
we're missing a month what the fuck happened and then i actually thanks to the twitch archive
i looked at episode and thanks to the sidebar on the side it made it really easy to find okay
where's the classic game where aha here's where duck tails is in the missing the episode that's
missing in the wiki so yeah so but at any rate um you know and for folks if you just want to
message me on the twitters it's at dark sakura you've been using that more i have not just for
cross-posting i have been but um just because facebook is shit um i got my finally got my
invite to uh wt social i did too and i don't like it live journaling i've been trying to use like
live journal all right i'll be i'll check out yours see if i get inspiration but anyway but
anyway um so if you've got uh you know that era of pinball if there's particular games you like you
know if you really want me to do the getaway you know i don't know if i'm going to do the getaway
i don't really care for it but you know send me a message of the pins that you like and there's a
very likely chance that i might say hey that is a good one let's do it um bobby is kind of subtly
asking for his page to get updated because it's been about eight years uh saying the wiki says
something about the ferret and clicky the pen and wow that's a joke we haven't referenced in forever
well i don't know if you want to remove it but yeah you probably want to change the
tense to like it was a former joke it was an old joke it's in a box in my house but looking up
old jokes is is part of the reason why the wiki is there but i i'm i support a uh i support a
freshening up i support renovations on bobby's profile to make it current i remember that
shermy was the best foot warmer ever yes yes all right um let's see swang tong is asking is shaking
and crying dead um no i no but it may change um but i don't want to make any promises that i can't
keep all i can say is that victoria went on that trip to new york city with me when we went to go
see broadway plays which doesn't that sound exactly up the alley of what shaking and crying
is all about and so we definitely talked about like what we want to do when it comes to podcasting
but while we were there we kind of came up with a different idea that we were both really into
and then thanksgiving happened and we got completely derailed because she's been out of
town and you know i've been busy so and i still had that idea i know well and this is the one
victoria and i have is completely different it's not what you think so um we will um it'd be
exploring that in the near future that's all i can say so yes bobby knows what it is near near i have
to tell bobby because i'm like bobby i'm gonna be inviting all this traffic onto the website that
you weren't expecting is that okay and then it's like what traffic lol well you never know i i
might have the next big idea all right then you might appreciate what happened a couple weekends
ago for a sister stitch and bitch session sure quickly because we're almost to 8 30 we did break
out into show tunes part b of our show to get to we fully broke out into show tunes all right one
of these nights i'm gonna come to the bar when you all are there and do that all right what
happens yeah bobby did approve the idea it's on it's on me and victoria we haven't got up off the
ground to do it yet i i think you guys will like it if you said uh nifty says that podcast was
cute to me we need to hear you two theater queens geeking out i think you'll like the idea we have
in store it's a little more free form i i don't know how to explain it without making promises
then be expected to deliver on all right so for now let's go to rapid fire news let's uh travel
around quickly and check out some quick headlines from around gaming world loki all right so we've
got your new free games that you're gonna get with your paid subscriptions to xbox and microsoft
starting with our i'm sorry xbox and sony um playstation so we're gonna have with the
playstation side of things with playstation plus for december titanfall 2 and monster energy
supercross the official video game are going to be your free games and those are available from
december 3rd through january 6th because the monster energy subtle plugs and death stranding
not very subtle wasn't enough and titanfall 2 is an excellent game so go play that i did buy it a
long time ago still haven't played it but here it's excellent and everybody says it's it's an
amazing campaign it is i mean if it wasn't for that we wouldn't have apex so something to think
about on the microsoft type of our side of things with uh games of gold on xbox one you're gonna get
insane robots and then jurassic world evolution and then on the xbox 360 front you've got toy
story 3 and castlevania lord of shadow mirror of fate hd all right some of the early impressions
of the witcher's netflix series are starting to leak out onto social media technically it's
embargoed until december 20th um but i guess some critics uh who have seen the first few episodes
have uh written some tweets and so forth uh one critic critic said i'm quite liking it in a tweet
i'll have more to say when the embargo drops uh one other one says i've never really been thirsty
for henry cavill uh i've seen a screener of the first episode of the witcher and i think i'm
pregnant uh the fight choreography is insane first fight is beautifully savage uh the witcher's cast
both lead and supporting are beyond exceptional amazing cast all around um so it sounds like
there's a lot of actually pretty good feedback on the witcher series which you know usually shows
that are based on a video game don't do so well but oh it's not actually based on a video game
it's based on the books that the video game were also based off of if y'all were starting to type
the correction in chat i know it and i guess to be fair i say that uh a lot of games haven't made
good shows but uh the castlevania anime has been pretty well received from what i understand yeah
the ingress anime was mixed i i could not get into that and uh what else what other games about a
show that i'm not thinking of in the moment um i feel like there was another big one i'm like
neglecting in the moment obviously 14 is supposed to get one i'm really excited about that i'm
curious how that'll go there's actually something else kind of along with the show ish thing is that
animal crossing new horizon is getting a manga oh fun yeah they've got i can talk more about
they've sort of got minecraft story mode as like an interactive okay minecraft yeah yeah yeah yeah
sort of okay anyway uh moving on uh i did not know this game was getting like an expansion but it is
the stanley parable remember that it was at e3 yeah it was a few years ago so no actually that
was this year no no no the original game all right a few years ago the expansion was this year yeah
the stanley parable ultra deluxe a remaster slash expansion that will take the original game and add
some new content and new endings uh it's been delayed till next year womp womp but at the same
time delays aren't bad news anymore so if that's what they it's not like you don't have the and
that was how they prefaced it with like they're reading fan mail and all the fans are like we
want to be perfect and we don't care if you delay it well there you go challenge accepted so they've
delayed it uh till next year and honestly my plate's been pretty full this year so
a delay to next year is not the end of the world dark soccer what do you have for rapid fire news
um capcom is going to be releasing a new game in december um according to some listings for
japanese game expo um gamatsu uh there's actually a translation from gamatsu that um says that the
capcom's jump festa 2020 exhibit um they are going to showcase four titles at the event two are known
to be mega man zero slash zx legacy collection and a monster hunter world iceborn it could also
be possible that uh the devil may cry collection could take one of those but there's one more
that's unknown so we will find out uh the fest is going to run between december 1st to 22nd
in cheeba i don't suppose it's a dino crisis hd collection no well one of the other things
though is that of course they are working on a resident evil 3 um remake to follow the
resident evil 2 remake so uh they're really wanting people to leave some feedback on that
one are we gonna get a resident evil 8 because 7 is supposed to be pretty good i feel like they're
kind of stuck in the fuck out in the remake thing uh and eight i mean seven kind of had that whole
vr and non-vr stuff going on so i don't know what they've decided to do with eight at this point
i think it'll happen but these remakes are serving them pretty well for now
rob it's up to us to take down umbrella i don't want you to end up in a jamie sandwich
right anyway um there's gonna be um a update for death stranding to tackle some common requests
including improving the font size now keep in mind when i was looking at this i was looking
really tiny font on really tiny screen and i was fine but not everyone has super jamie vision when
you take off your glasses and everything's huge yeah if you're sitting next to a monitor you can
probably see it okay but yeah it's it's like the subtitles are all right i was like oh why are
people playing but then i saw like in the quest menus and stuff i'm like okay damn that is some
tiny ass text wow um um but also um there um there's gonna be another thing that addresses
a request to be able to dispose of individual vehicles so they're looking about patching that
in for the mid-december patch um and hold on just double check to see if there's anything else i
don't even have a vehicle yet i will say where i'm at in the game and i don't think this is spoilery
vehicles were in trailers um i i have the quest to because i just got the ability to build like
a power source in my structure so i have a directive to go build one of those next to a bike
that's run out of power it's been sitting there for a while so that's so for those of you that
played death stranding that's exactly where i'm at in the game well there's they did with the
last update um had some performance improvements and uh worked on some network functionality um
but yeah there you go so that's our current quick stuff all right so let's travel around the world
and check out what is coming out this week in world release dates i imagine it's a pretty slow
week being that the holidays just occurred but you never know i do you think so and you're right
you never know what's right around the corner in fact we have several things coming out this week
so we have blair witch coming out on playstation 4 we have halo reach um on pc i believe that's
just being added to the master chief collection uh life is strange episode 5 on pc playstation
4 and xbox one never winter nights enhanced edition on nintendo switch playstation 4 and xbox
one phoenix point on pc and mac saga scarlet grace ambitions on pc nintendo switch playstation
4 android and ios uh scale boy on nintendo switch terminator resistance on pc playstation 4 and
xbox one alien isolation on nintendo switch uh we have dark siders genesis on pc and stadia
uh raging loop on pc star ocean first departure r on nintendo switch and playstation 4 and last
but not least ancestors the humankind odyssey on playstation 4 and xbox one all right so it's
pretty still a pretty busy week i thought i would have thought it would be a dead week but not
really um it's starting after this week it'll start to slow down a bit and then really die off
about the second or third week in december fair enough well japan since things are a little
different holidays are kind of a different perception over there uh it's a very different
kind of week uh we got some big names out this week in japan on the playstation 4 including yokai
watch 4 plus plus on the playstation 4 so that's you know a a disc or a non-handheld release uh for
yokai watch that's a pretty big deal i i wish that series hadn't kind of disappeared here i was into
it in the beginning so i wish they would try a playstation 4 or switch release also something
in a high tv show oh yeah that's true all right so but anyway still pretty big over there though
oh no it's still huge over there so i'm not too surprised to hear i kind of wanted to sit and
watch the anime just because i love uh the folklore of yokai um also out in japan this
week the dark pictures man of madan um gets its release in japan this week they are saying it is
an english version it hasn't been localized for japan um but that is out if they want to check
that out uh and then a game called citadel is out this week as well and what is arguably the
biggest release in japan this week no just kidding it's definitely yokai watch but you know this one
caught my eye oni chambara origin is out on the playstation 4 this week oh that's right if you
don't know oni chambara you should check it bikini samurai that's right it's all the the ladies
wearing very little clothes i really wish more of the simple 1000 games or 2000 games actually ended
up coming out um aside from just you know earth defense force and on chambara i mean like they
had ambulance versus zombies and that's really the only other one i remember but uh more simple
series games or games like that all right well looking at the nintendo switch of course yokai
watch 4 plus plus is out on that system as well but then we have another couple titles we have
a game called moto new pus osumatsu san uh which comes out from d3 it looks like it's like just
a match 3 type of game but like there's two different versions of this game and everything
so it's yeah simple controls match 3 i guess there's a story that goes with it i don't know
seems like kind of a big deal for a match 3 game um always a big deal though is a pretty princess
game that's right pretty princess magical coordinate is out this week on the switch as
well where you get to decorate over 1300 castle excuse me castle rooms with 1300 items you can
customize your character and feel like a princess you can do princess training lessons and mini
games so you can perfect your wave i'm sure as the decorating thing sounds kind of fun um and
then you can have your princess make poses and take pictures of the finished rooms how about
that it's a one to four player four player game so i guess you get to decorate together
so there it is so japan japan's still a pretty fun week right see there's lots of stuff coming out
that's right how about europe uh a decent amount so on the second we have life is strange 2 for
xbox and playstation farming simulator 20 for switch never winter nights enhanced edition for
the three um we also have red dead redemption 2 for pc off-road oh that's sorry on december 4th
more on december 4th is offered racing for the big three um on the 5th we have dead by daylight
nightmare edition um it doesn't say what's coming out on though and then also on the on the 5th oh
yeah that's right there's a bunch uh battle wake for playstation uh assassins creed the rebel
collection for switch gang beasts on um for xbox and playstation and last but not least
narco's rise of the cartels for the playstation and xbox
so that's it all right there it is release dates from around the world um still pretty pretty busy
this early december but yeah probably because we're right in that gap where it's like okay
now's your last chance to get the game out before the end of the year uh before christmas and all
that stuff so all right well let's move on uh every week we invite your emails that participate
at orange lounge radio.com and we like to read some of your emails here on the show so again if
you want to send us an email for a future week please do participate at orange lounge radio.com
and dark sakura is going to jump in the mailbag and read some stuff okay um so uh we have one
from robert m which is sort of a follow-up from the bunch of other operating system questions but
i will go ahead and read part of this too um just uh just keep going um is citing older versions of
mac and ios systems from the last time the older games lost support and catalina that is correct
catalina no longer supports 32-bit applications and games so um um and then he asked is super
multitasking plus ultra is it 64-bit yyr that would be a yyr question i don't know please let
us know if it's a 64-bit app um the discussion of half-life alex as valve's first game in a
long time reminded me of the recent forgotten uh card game artifact i assume if it's still
uh being supported it probably is not going to see as much of an uptick as magic games are as
the hearthstone alternative so how about that like magic yyr is in chat thank you so much
buddy uh saying it is 64-bit on mac 32-bit on windows so it's where it needs to be to run
so there you go all right so yeah if you're gonna play it on a mac upgrade i mean you can know you
can do it on the current os's so yeah sorry brain went around okay and then um i got a two-part
email from flaco jones oh important footnote from yyr but future mac support is up in the air will
be determined over the coming months i wonder if that has to do with um sales so mac fans get on
that super multitasking i'm making that up he didn't say why i imagine it's probably difficult
give me an app store link and i'll make it fly well i don't think it's on the app store yet
it needs to be in the app store yeah i don't know there might be there might be a problem with steam
green light in the way that was all put up i don't know i don't know that's a that's an oh and and
the leaderboards are built into the games that would be a whole undertaking for him so i can
understand why he wants to focus he wants to focus on his expansion first i'm sure anyway hey i just
wanted to pop in with a little correction on your game rewards talk so that you have the right info
on how they work this is flaco jones by the way while fans do get a vote and how these awards go
it only accounts for 10 of the vote the voting jury composed of 80 media and influencer outlets
from around the world accounts do the other 90 of the vote so unless the vote is really close i
don't think fans have much of a sway over who actually wins if they did i doubt a small game
like overcook 2 would have beaten all those much more well-known nintendo games for best family
game last year also over half of those outlets are from outside the united states which makes
them less predictable based on how those games are received from our perspective here in the us
the jury isn't entirely made up of critical publications like i mentioned earlier if it
was just based on critics control probably wouldn't have a chance as it was the lowest
metacritic score of all the game of the year nominees you definitely hit the nail on the head
about the ongoing game category though it was a big shock that overwatch wasn't nominated as it
had been for the last two years and it won the category in 2017 i think final fantasy 14 has
shot over fortnite fortnite already won last year and again fan vote doesn't really mean anything
i was a little surprised that blitzchung didn't uh get a nomination for best esports player i
thought that would have been interesting but i don't really know how he did outside of the
tournament he won where he spoke out and got suspended have a great rest of your stream
flaco jones um very good points yeah i'll let you read that in a sec um i just want to say you know
oops we got it wrong sorry last week so um thanks for correcting how that all is um judged he makes
a really great analogy in the next email but i wanted to quickly say on um control and metacritic
and all that and you mentioned that final fantasy 14 has a shot um since we just talked about
metacritic earlier in the show it does seem like the barometer may be tilting in final fantasy 14's
favor so uh the blitzchung thing though i mean there was a part of me that was like well what
was the deadline for this maybe but i i would have thought nah i'm sure this that whole incident
could have happened before the deadline so um who knows why that didn't end up happening perhaps
um they were nervous about putting that in the spotlight i don't know anyway um let's hear the
other email though because he makes a great comparison in this email second email because
i forgot to mention one point i wanted to make about the game awards personally i find them to
be more like the golden globes of the game industry since the winners are determined by a global jury
of media and not game makers themselves i put more stock in who wins at the dice awards in february
which are actually voted on by peers who work in game development and publishing a lot more like
the oscars if we're still comparing it to movie awards but since they come out later and don't
have the media outlets attached they don't usually get as much buzz okay that's it for the award
emails flaco jones i just wanted to call out what a great comparison that is when many people are
saying that the game awards should be the oscars of gaming in a way um very interesting to call
out but the way they're voted on oscars are voted on by industry peers and people that are you know
within the film industry and so forth so really it's the dice awards that are kind of the barometer
there whereas the way this is voted on by media worldwide that is how the golden globes are voted
on it so the golden globes doesn't have the fan part of it but i mean still the comparison i think
is is pretty good what you're getting at there um and golden globes was always supposed to be the
more informal one the more party atmosphere right um the golden globes used to be the laughing stock
of the film industry like people didn't even want to be seen there but they really kind of
started turning it around what was it probably like the 90s the late 80s or the 90s i think a
lot of people with the golden globes probably remember one of the first big things that
contributed to that party atmosphere of the golden globes was when christine lottie won that award
for whatever tv show she was on at the time but she was in the bathroom so robin williams jumped
on stage and just started doing this improv live and was like paging christine lottie and stuff
and it was this really funny because you know robin williams could pull comedy out of his butt
and it was hilarious right he was great in that regard um and i think that really made a lot more
people start paying attention to the golden globes being like the party one and then they then the
golden globes kind of billed itself as that and they had ricky jervais host those few years and
they they loved him for a while because he was so unpredictable and so forth that was the one that
tina fey and amy polar hosted which i don't know why they don't do it every year they prob they
probably turned it down because they have other projects they want to do but they're hilarious
and so forth so you know especially because the game awards i think are definitely the showier
show whereas the dice awards are more the you know industry thing but we just don't really see the
dice awards they don't televise that so it doesn't feel as oscary and so forth so i'm glad they don't
have celebrity hosts doing it because like i know like several years like different not necessarily
award shows but like presenters joel mchale or even uh uh conan o'brien it has to not it has to
be the right presenter like for example i consider aisha tyler a celebrity presenter but like she
knows her shit because she plays halo and shit in her downtime like she she knew her games you know
she was an authentic voice in the celebrities i think i say was because i haven't seen her
do anything in gaming in a while but you know when she would talk about gear is a war on her
show or whatever because she was on the talk for a while i don't think i don't know if she ever
brought it up there but it's like she she knew what she was talking about she was being told
let's say she knew what she was talking about yeah you know and even though conan o'brien makes it
funny i still feel like he kind of really does play games but it's it's he his job is to not
make it serious um i still don't think he's funny uh well jimmy fallon then we'll go with that
because he's brought more video game exposure to the tonight show which is always kind of like
i mean you want to talk about okay boomer the tonight show is always that show that you kind
of associate with like a much different generation jimmy fallon love him or hate him has kind of had
this responsibility to try to make this show more accessible to a wider audience because let's be
real jay leno never did that and when conan o'brien swung that pendulum too hard in the
other direction he lost his show in seven months so jimmy fallon's been in this very hard place
where he's kind of had to walk the line and make a show that's accessible to the legacy of the
tonight show but also one that is going to live on you know with newer generations and he's done that
in part by having um oh what's her name captain marvel playing uh beat saber brie larson thank
you brie larson playing beat saber was it was it her i was somebody that one of one of the marvel
girls was playing beat saber with her on uh with him and you know he was one of the first to show
the switch that that gif or gif whatever you want to say of of um um oh my god miyamoto in the
audience where he does that whole like thumbs up thing that whole gift of him out there that was
from the tonight show you know so anyway i'm sorry i don't remember where i was going with
this but i was just kind of pointing out like you know oh media and having to embrace games
and celebrities and that whole sort of thing so um swang tong says whatever happened to conan
he's been on tbs this whole time yeah um i and they he doesn't need to pull in the same type of
numbers on well nowadays like it's i don't know how well these like late shows are really doing
because most people watch consume these through clips on youtube that's how i do it i mean i
don't watch like i don't watch uh any of these guys but i'll just watch the clips i don't think
i would ever watch one of these late night live shows i used to back in the day i i remember
watching johnny carson in my bedroom okay like i'm dating myself i know that towards the end of his
run and i was probably 10 or 11. i used to watch the reruns of conan o'brien though like when they
would rerun them during the day we used to gather up in the dorm room and watch late night with conan
o'brien like yeah he was like his target audience i think i i love well i saw him live i went to his
live tour and it was fantastic the one here in sac i did san francisco yes and i loved it it
was great yeah i thought it was funny i had a great time but i have to admit i haven't been
following the tbs show as much because i just don't watch a lot of late night stuff and you're
right it's all consumed in bits and honestly you know who you know who i see more than anybody else
like the youtubes i see more than anybody else that i probably watch more than anybody else
jimmy kimmel and i would have never thought that would be the case because jimmy kimmel reminds me
of the man show which was fucking ridiculous but his late night show he's got a lot of good viral
clips i usually watch uh late night with seth meyers or uh i'll watch the clips also of um
uh steven colbert i like samantha b and john oliver yeah john oliver i'll use watch that
like good like thinky stuff um i i what i want to say about um jimmy kimmel oh i think the best
clip that i saw him do was when he manufactured that viral clip of like the girl twerking on the
door and then the door opens and it falls over and they show that went that was a legit thing
that they put on youtube it went viral and then on his show they revealed that when the door opens
it's jimmy kimmel on the other side of the door and like he kind of showed like we made this clip
go viral and this is how we did it and i just thought it was very interesting so anyway and
then they brought on the girl that was twerking it was like a stunt stunt woman or something from
motion pictures so anyway i just thought it was interesting so um and bobby does point out the
good thing about oliver and b is that they're weekly and not nightly and you do see a lot of
shows kind of going that way as a result i used to love the daily show but i don't the clips that
aren't as great as they used to be i don't know if i just don't care for the new guy as much as
you know john stewart or what it is i don't know i used to love letterman back in the day i think
when letterman first took over at cbs that was like the heyday of late night television anyway
because i always thought leno was lame i never cared for him leno is a shithole but he has a
great car collection he had and he has a die-hard fan base of sorts i don't i don't get it anyway
he's just not a good person i think i don't think he's funny at all like anyway anyway it's not about
late night i don't think he's funny in the same way i don't think that rodney dangerfield was
funny that whole well i'm an asshole what are you gonna do but yeah like but bianca del rio
does that same shtick and it's funny yeah but bianca del rio is actually smart yeah i guess
that's true all right anyway let's move on and joan rivers did a lot of that same shtick but she's
smart she was a genius right all right let's move on um and full of preservatives let's talk about
more stadia news i talked about stadia earlier in the show yes so stadia pro they have that
subscription service which they're supposed to be giving new games uh each month and you know we
talked about last month how the only game that's really free right now is stadia probe was destiny
2 well that's actually going to change because now they've added a few more games for december that
are going to be available as well so um those being tomb raider and farming simulator 19
which um are available but apparently though anybody that bought those games now will actually
be getting a discount because they okay i'm sorry they're not free i guess you get a discount on
those um no they are free so they're giving you i guess a discount of 10 on tomb raider and 50 on
farming simulator 19 which i'm assuming is just the list price for those uh but yeah so those i
guess are finally live and i guess that i i don't know they need to do a better job of actually
communicating which games are free with stadia pro each month i guess they do have it now where
they're showing you know the december and i guess oh samurai showed that was another one that was
free as well chat was correct you on that but yeah sorry they added simmer i forgot the samurai
showing out like the last minute it was in there yeah but like you know it'd be nice to know like
what um like say for example january is going to be and stuff like that just i mean i get it like
it you don't really do that necessarily with um you like the playstation plus stuff in that but
if you're paying for stadia pro i mean there's such a small library right now that you would
think that they would kind of say hey oh shit i didn't even okay so here's the fun this is why i
said oh shit so i was actually bringing up the stadia app so loki could kind of see this firsthand
what it looks like in the app that they do actually have a section that says stadia pro
games is right there so and these are the ones that are all free and why i went oh shit is
because tomb raider and farming simulator are already there they went apparently they went
free today yeah because it's december i i well yeah but you know like playstation plus games
aren't live until like the first thursday in december it's not always december 1st so i just
oh shitted because i'm like oh tomb raider and farming simulator farming simulator fuck yes
you know actually i will say that euro truck simulator and those those games are actually
like in a zen sort of way like really relaxing and fun so i'll try for free free well yeah free
because bobby gave me his buddy pass thanks bobby i can't murder me anybody in those games i'm not
really necessarily so i'm sorry i guess well you can murder him in tomb raider i was gonna say i
had to leave all my murdering to me him yes to uh tomb raider so neat neat i had no idea um that
those games were um actually out so i'm good to know i'll be checking that out a little later on
i wish i could stream it but obviously you see the problem i can't stream while i'm streaming
i guess i could but it would affect the quality of both one or the other uh but i could record it
and i've thought about doing this would you guys even care what if i recorded like a long play and
just debuted it on twitch during the day um on a random night when there's no live vog programming
what would you think would you would you care about that or would you just be like eh
kind of a question for you guys because or they may think i go where i want to go rob's gonna be
like all wolf which is fine but i'm just curious like if i were to record stadia stuff and they're
gonna be like this isn't a pinball game do i have to play pinball no because you you accidentally
broadcast your footage from the b-roll oh shut up all right moving on uh let's talk about this
i just thought this was you know it's a bit of a slower news week so i thought this was like oh
interesting um and this has to do with minecraft um and it has to do with the vatican um so we have
a news article about a priest that is going to be launching a vatican minecraft server
um and so it's fr what's fr short for for france france friends god damn it what are the france
no it's the title in the church oh not deacon not pope not what's fr
father father oh that's our friar that's way too easier than father's father probably works
well you're you're saying this to the the nun i know father robert balacer um who is a jesuit
priest who studied engineering in silicon valley is wanting to introduce the vatican's minecraft
server as a place where players can express themselves in a environment that is not as toxic
as maybe other things that you're running out to out there so like i guess if you will a safe space
um then you may find in other games oh pot culture points out he's from this week in tech i didn't
know that okay so this guy's kind of involved with tech stuff before so the project started on
twitter and he polled the followers on what game do you want to do a test server rust arc team
fortress 2 or minecraft and 64 of the votes went to minecraft yeah i don't know if russ didn't
necessarily be the uh the best choice for don't don't you hang dong in that game so like i don't
know if that's he took a vote of sorts so anyway uh father robert balacer uh says in a quote rome
reports uh it's not about the technology it's not even really about the gaming it's about getting
people together who can then maybe move those relationships to the real world at first there
were a lot of people who were very hesitant because you see this guy in a collar talking
about the latest offerings from google or how you run fiber optics across the atlantic and they
didn't understand they said wait a minute these two things don't go together but after a time they
realized okay he knows what he's talking about he just happens to be a priest and ultimately that
was the ministry i was trying to do you know despite however you might feel about the church
organized religion and that sort of thing i you have to admire what this guy's trying to do
this is smart this and it's it's funny because we were just talking about like late night and having
to bridge the generations and when i i don't know about you guys when i think about the vatican i
think about the pope i think about a lot of these fathers these people you know who i think about
fucking old people really old people well right and and i and i think what he's doing is a great
thing i'm just worried that this is going to be a beacon for like trolls it's just like hey let's
this this is a good place to focus our energy like and yeah you know i think they can accomplish it
it's just it's gonna take a whole hell a lot of moderation if he's done this work with this week
in tech and worked in silicon valley before i think he well knows about that and the way i've
kind of seen this approached before is that you know usually if trolls come in um you pray for
them you you try to reach out through prayer and that sort of thing you know again i'm not i'm not
gonna speak on behalf of the church i'm not trying to say this but i'm just kind of in my experience
of watching this you know you try to still build a bridge even if somebody is a troll um they still
took a minute to walk into your church so to speak so what are you gonna do you're gonna preach at
him right so he may still be trying to build a bridge maybe again i don't speak for this guy
but i'm thinking he may be trying to build a bridge with trolls and so forth as well
um so who knows anyway i just thought you know honestly it's funny because i was reminded of
the movie sister act and what's one of the key plot points in sister act you have the old school
versus the new school right you have maggie smith playing you know the the mother mother hand or
whatever or mother superior right of the of the um nuns and she wants to do things very old school
she wants everything to be traditional she wants everything to be very you know by the book i
became a nun so i could live this particular life and then when whoopi goldberg comes in because
she's being hidden there by the cops she has this whole different approach to it where she's she
brings her lounge club experience into it where she's like we could put some butts in these seats
if we were to actually like modernize what we're doing and at the end of the day the priest in a
way or the the deacon of the church or whatever kind of sides with whoopi's character whereas
he's still trying to um be respectful to the history and what's happening by trying to um you
know be respectful of maggie smith's character so yes i just took a gaming story and compared it to
sister act but god damn it it works because the plot of that movie was about how they were
reaching out and making more people um interested in faith and religion by making it accessible
yeah and doggone it that's what this guy's trying to do in a way so you know again say what you want
to say about organized religion and all that but i i have to admire this guy's approach this guy
gets it in i think a way that a lot of his peers in the church don't so props to you dude best of
luck i hope it works out for you i think we all want to create a space sometimes for like-minded
individuals and sometimes that might be like a lgbtq plus and so forth safe space that might be
a place to talk about religion and so forth you know and as long as you're not kicking other
people down while you do it go for it so anyway bobby blackwolf and chat now that's funny bobby
blackwolf and chat with an excellent like troll ish but genuinely funny comment that says is he
building the bridge with wood or cobblestone minecraft this is about minecraft minecraft joke
cobblestone it's much more readily available all right let's take the conversation back to satan
uh dark sakura you have a story about a scary thing right me i made might have been scary um
so there is a uh a series of tweets that were going out trying to get the uh writer and producer
alana pierce to ask just basically deliver anything about silent hills that's a quote
that we didn't already know now that it's you know never coming out and so um the post reply
was i heard that silent hills would require you to sign a waiver before playing because it would
somehow interact with your real world self like by sending you emails or text messages as characters
from the game even when you weren't actively playing that is nuts can you imagine and that's
totally doable in this you know if all you have to do is give that game facebook access
and it'll pull from your facebook it can pull your phone number and your email and this type
of stuff and there's going to be people that blindly hit the button and do that
like remember remember hadeo kachima made that game metal gear solid that did something really
like psycho twisted when it would read your memory card i see you're a fan of konami games
exactly and it would like actually it mentioned games like that hadn't come out yet so or just
you know it would read like sweet koden you have a sense of adventure or things like that like
you would read the save files that were on your ps1 card sweet koden wasn't out yet yeah something
and so if you played it after sweet koden came out and it read the save file for it and then
get your comment but yeah they had a couple games on there that hadn't been out yet yeah
so uh just i mean so the fact that hadeo kajima potentially if this is to be believed
kind of was taking that to the next level with like what else do i inadvertently have access to
in this day and age that i could really scare the shit out of someone with like can you imagine
you are done with this game like you had to turn the game off because you were too scared
and then one of the you you fucking get a text message on your phone that pretends to be one
of the characters in the game i would die like that is that is that's awesome though that is
like wow what would you think if you were suddenly being texted and harassed by characters
bitch i'm at work do not disturb that would be me or just reply stop yeah which if you get marketing
text messages you can reply stop to get removed from them just letting y'all know yeah but the
the thing is is that you know we know we know kojima is looking to do another as as he says
the scariest horror game so maybe we're gonna eventually get at least a spiritual sequel to
the silent hill franchise i think maybe it'll be called like like uh quiet mountain it's just
it's gonna take all the ideas he had for silent hills and just put them in a new universe i'm sure
and nova has norman reading it read us in it maybe and his butt if he's available in his butt
i wonder if he's got a nice butt i wonder if he'll still team up with guillermo del toro
wow i i want this and i want it to have the fish man in it yeah i just people do need to
let the silent shape of water i mean honestly if konami wanted to earn a lot of points i don't
ever see them doing this but i'm just gonna say it they could just let him have the franchise
and i realize there's been a lot of bad blood between him and konami but a few years has been
a shit to a few years have passed at this point and konami you notice has been slowly trying to
turn the wheel in a new direction and get some positive press and i would say if konami wanted
to get some real positive press then all they would need to do is just say hey look you can
make you we will license the silent hill to you for a five percent cut a ten percent cut or
whatever and you can make the game you wanted to make or whatever i think would get a lot of stock
back in konami but that's to say if kojima even wanted to do it because kojima would have a right
to say no fuck them and you know make his own thing that had many of the same ideas and that's
that's he has the right to do that there's a really good video about pt and about the things
that he was putting references to that when the nda got lifted that make a lot of sense like
certain numbers that you would see in there or like the commentary of the fetus in the in the
sink how it was talking about something it goes back to how konami was treating him and you know
getting pushed out of his positions and whatnot it was a very interesting theory interesting that
the talking baby was a common theme between those two things baby doesn't talk oh i guess
he doesn't he doesn't talk does he okay there are all kinds of ghost babies
all right well moving on just a few more stories for you guys then we'll quickly check in on
discord and see if anybody wants to call in for tonight um over at uh uh vog network dot com slash
discord in our green room so there was a rom hack for fire emblem called midnight sun that was in
development but then canceled uh back in 2017 uh but now the folks that were behind that
have a new game called path of the midnight sun and it's kind of a spiritual successor to that
it's now more of like a visual novel but it also has some tactical combat like fire emblem in there
and they even have some of the same voice actors from the fire emblem series and even pokemon
that are lending their uh talents to the game itself and if that sounds like something that
you might be interested in well they have it up on kickstarter now and it's supposed to be
out by the end of next year on pc mac and the switch so you can go check that out path of the
midnight sun and it looks interesting definitely um it reminds me a little bit of fire emblem just
based on the animation and everything but that's always fascinating when um like a mod it kind of
spins off and becomes its own game because this isn't the first time this has happened hello dota
right why is there why is there no dota 1 there's only dota 2 because dota 1 was a warcraft 3 mod
so you know mods do spin off and become games sometimes it's uh and that's that's not all uh
team fortress was originally a quake mod you know a lot of that valve stuff you know they acquired
big modders and then helped them make their own games so it's kind of neat yep yeah all right
i'll have to check that out at some point even though i'm not really super into the tactical
rpgs but i think it's kind of a neat neat thing anyway um i'm sure a lot of you guys have been
following what's going on in other news and the announcement of the cyber truck did you guys see
the uh unveiling from elon musk of the cyber truck uh with the the shatterproof windows and all that
stuff anyway uh a lot of people commented that wow the cyber truck looks like something i would
have seen like in a 90s uh virtual racing type of game like a low polygon type of game
and now guess what's happening that car is being hacked into many different video games
including it's so hard to to recreate the model of the truck golden eye 007 is one of the more
prominent ones out there where you can actually uh have a mod you know for your golden eye game
that will put the cyber truck into the game which let's be real that truck does kind of look like
something out of a james bond film so this one makes the most sense so yeah it does kind of look
like a um stunt fx or what was hard driving hard driving car from hard drive well i thought you
know when um yeah when uh jamie was talking about virtual racing i'm like yeah i can see that yeah
for sure so that's cute that that truck has been hacked into everything and that's uh that's the
type of thing that modders do for the lulz so there you go all right um we are going to make
our way to discord so we can try to grab some calls tonight so let's see if we can actually
uh get that call here because we do have somebody waiting hello you're on orange launch radio who's
this hey uh this is mel mayhem how's it going hello hello metal mayhem and happy uh black
friday shopping weekend to you i'm sure you are uh having a great time of it did you know that
that's also the name of a pinball heavy metal mayhem oh no i wasn't aware of that i thought
for a second there she was talking about black friday shopping weekend i thought i was like
there's a black friday pinball machine what i know black hole all right anyway what's that what's on
your mind tonight buddy oh since you brought it up idly enough it's more or less the topic of my
you know you know a call in a very broad sense um now um since it's um you know black parties
you know cyber monday weekend and everyone's on buying guests either from themselves or for
others or what have you i would like to ask you this um not just during this weekend but
over the course of 2019 have you bought you know defeat any of you uh but uh bought some
games for yourselves or for others you know you know during a major sale you know did you
particularly love they're getting out the game doesn't necessarily have to have to have been uh
released this year just hit had to be on make uh available during uh during a sale and sure
sure i get what you're doing with that um what do you guys think is there uh a game that you've
bought in a sale this year um that you particularly enjoyed and and thought was a good deal um i did
say i didn't get death stranding on sale i was hoping it would go on sale this weekend but it
never did i did buy a music sequencer program on steam um because i was watching some how-to videos
on youtube and it looked pretty um relatively easy to use um and i was i liked that it made chiptune
songs and things of that nature so i thought it was relatively cheap it was probably like 14 bucks
for the program and the suit and i'm sorry i forget the name in the moment um if i i haven't
made anything with it yet so if i do i will let you know what it was called um but um yeah i
thought that would be fun to toy around with because you know i've been looking for some
new musical interludes here at olr and um i know jamie has a lead as well but maybe we want to have
other musical interludes as well so it depends on how difficult it is to use
um i used to do music stuff many many many many many years ago i don't exactly have a resume i
was in marching band so i can read sheet music but that's about you know the extent of it but
um yeah i'll be curious to tinker around with it and see what i can do so um that was one thing
i picked up this weekend as far as like all year in a sale or anything like that oh i remember i
know i'll say horizon zero dawn um i picked that up a couple months ago they were having a pretty
deep sale on playstation and i got the entire collection for like 20 bucks and that was one of
those series that i wasn't sure if i'd be really into it but um it was a it was a good game i i
didn't beat it because i never seem to beat games but i sunk plenty hours into it and i enjoyed what
i played um it's kind of you know that open world action type of thing like breath of the wild tomb
raider-esque type of thing um yeah i enjoyed that so i would say that was a pleasant surprise i
picked up a really good deal i think 20 bucks for that whole package was really good anything that
comes to mind for you guys not really i didn't buy anything this sale um the last game i bought
was black future 88 and still haven't gone around to playing it yet um by the way horizon zero dawn
is now down to fifteen dollars on this black friday sale so i mean if you're looking for
something on playstation 4 uh it's a pretty good one you don't want to pass up although
imagine if you wait long enough it's going to be a playstation plus game but well i want to say i
think super beat zonic was 99 cents at one time oh it was and then i picked that up so that's a
pretty good deal still haven't played it because i don't really get access to my switch anymore but
um yeah that's really it i buy a lot of weird stuff i buy a lot of um courses in udemy i was
disappointed that some of the expansion music for dj max uh respect weren't on sale because
i didn't realize that game was still doing expansions because they recently did a crossover
with groove coaster and i was interested in picking it up but the music the music expansions
in that game are pretty pricey and also just on a random tangent i saw a news article that dj
max respect is apparently coming to pc later this year um which is exciting but at the same time i'm
like that's going to be too much money they're going to want way too much money for it so i
hope they charge the right price for it so we'll see oh yeah pixel pocket says is it really rob
yeah i saw i saw a news article on that just a few days ago they just announced it like maybe
six days ago or something that there's going to be a dj max respect on pc if you look up if you um
excuse me if you go to like news.google where you can search for news trends just look for dj max it
should be one of the top stories that comes up so you can read they haven't said a lot about it
like we don't uh it's steam it's gonna be on steam that's all we know um but there's no page on steam
for it yet or anything like that so uh we're getting some answers from our chat uh quest
buster says valkyrie chronicles 4 for the ps4 is just 20 bucks really fun strategy game so there
you go um uh dark soccer anything that comes to mind for you i don't know if there's been any
fun deals that you've jumped in on not really yeah i mean i um i've just been basically grabbing
stuff and waiting for detroit to come out oh yeah better than that like i don't have any real games
coming out that i want to play until animal crossing okay so i'm not i haven't really been
deal hunting i've more been looking on the practical side of of gifts all right uh anything
else you have for us tonight middle man no they'll be it uh i'll try to clear up the line because i
can see two other people don't want to call in yeah yeah you too thanks so much for the call
yeah i definitely want to squeeze some other calls in but thank you buddy take care all right let's
get to some more calls here i'll go to this one next hi you're on orange launch radio who's this
hi it's yyr hello my friend yyr how are you oh pretty good how you doing i am great what's on
your mind tonight i'm trying to get you in the next caller in here so we can wrap up so not to
but maybe a little what's up no i uh i won't take up too much of your time i just uh first off want
to say you know congrats on 800 etc etc appreciate that my friend if you guys still have fun doing
this in a little over two years we'll be back to say congrats on 900 but uh i digress uh i did want
to mention something uh follow up to robert m's email earlier about uh you know the mac os support
basically what's happened is uh apple is trying to raise the security of mac os uh i'm not sure
if it's just because they want to protect their users from any and all uh avenues that malware
could get in or if they're just looking at iphone and ipad and saying well we get a a 30 cut of
everything they sell on there why not mac os too but for whatever reason they have a new thing
called notarization and starting uh with this new version of mac os that came out recently in
october uh all new apps have to be notarized uh which is a process you have to do directly with
apple otherwise they will not run now the thing is they temporarily relaxed these restrictions until
this coming january and one thing we noticed is that you know developing a mac game and running
it through steam it doesn't seem to go through some of the restrictive checks that other you know
applications do like if you had just distributed it say on your website uh so for all i know in
january my two games are going to stop working if you have the latest version of the operating
system i have no idea apple isn't saying anything valve has no clue either so i uh
yes yes i know how to notarize i see dark sakura put the link in chat but here's the kicker if you
want to be able to notarize your app you have to have an active developer account with apple which
means 99 a year yeah i i can tell you right now there is no uh i i am not making 99 a year on my
mac stuff you have a you have a baby to consider in that stuff so you gotta you know all those
costs uh certainly add up um well there are a lot of mass developers who are just not happy about
this for what it's worth the show computer is running catalina so i'm happy to test for you on
january 1st what happens um for what it's worth um but what's interesting is that um i think we've
run into a similar error i'm not sure if it has to do with security but like obs has some issues
i have to launch it from terminal in order to be able to get it to work um there still is not a
workaround on obs's front so um i don't know what is going on um so thank you for some of that
insight i mean i can you know i can certainly get where you know apple has a reputation of
being a safe platform where um pcs are usually the ones that get targeted by like viruses trojans
etc and so forth so um you know apple wants to kind of protect that because i think we've been
hearing in the past year we hear of it happening a little more on the mac platform still not yeah
you know the same ratios pc we've been hearing about it more so i think apple may have kind of
really clamped down on that in an effort to stay kind of that pristine clean little platform that
it is but unfortunately some more of this independent stuff is getting a little bit
left out in the cold as a result so um fingers crossed that it'll work i'm messaging you on
facebook about something so uh okay i'll make sure to log into facebook then okay yeah yeah
that's why she's gonna tell you all right but yeah i'm uh you're gonna see probably over the
next few months a lot of independent developers drop support for mac unfortunately uh simply
because you know they don't want to have to maintain an active subscription but i could be
wrong but we'll see yeah we'll see what happens it'll be interesting to see uh what develops but
i did not realize january was as soon as that was happening so that's less than a month away so
could be interesting and i don't know if it's january 1st january 30th nobody's saying anything
so we'll just figure it out all right we'll keep an eye on it well thank you for the follow-up
yyr and appreciate again everything you've done for you you've literally made our dreams come
true over the years um so we just want you to know how much you're appreciated and you're a
big part of how we got this far so thank you so much my friend i don't know if i would have gotten
this far without you guys either so thanks for that and uh have a great week we help each other
out take care my friend bye-bye see you later all right let's try to get one more call here before
we call it a night uh hi you're on orange long training who's this hey what's going on everybody
it is ron it is good to hear from you rama but i'm going to have us keep it quick tonight what's
on your mind first off i want to say happy 800. thank you my friend um to also touch back on
reference to jimmy fallon i can say i have seen some of the tech that they talk about on the show
that's the most i can release it okay meaning you know something bringing like newer tech and gaming
and so forth let's just say i've been in areas where you know they put stuff that they had on
the show up in store i've seen some of it so yeah all right good to know you probably have
observed a lot of interesting things over the year but we'll leave it at that cool and lastly i have
a switch i'm sorry say that again mr smoosh was trying to be heard over you i have a switch oh
congratulations of course yes because i got the friend request on the switch and of course you
picked luigi as your icon thank you um so um yeah congratulations what are you playing on it
right now mario kart 8 i picked up um starlink because it was like 10 bucks and i also picked up
a collection of mon those are some really good choices because you have a little bit of old
school you have a little bit of deep discounts you have some new school in there as well and i
also i also picked up links awakening i forgot yeah uh did anything in particular finally sway
you into the switch like now was it the free game of mario kart that finally got you in or what
what swayed you from e3 seeing a collection of mana because one of the games uh secret of mana
got me through a real rough time in my teenage years which is part of the reason why i picked
up a snest classic but this along with links awakening which was one of my personal favorite
zelda games so i'm just like god damn it nintendo here's my money have you touched trials of mana
or second sense of three yet i have not be sure to get in on that i was uh very pleasantly
surprised with that i need again on my list of games i need to finish but i did it i did
a pretty good decent amount of streaming like probably good four or five hours into that game
and uh it was great i had a good time i'm looking forward to a little redo i hope they learn some
things from the secret of mana redo same here but unfortunately i can't play the game i can't
play my switch as much because when i was coming back from mako channels i accidentally left my
charger behind oh no well the good news is it's a universal like for once nintendo is using like
universal stuff so as long as you have like a usb-c cable i think it is um you can charge it
with like anything so um you should say that because i'm doing that right now and according
to my switch it's not enough power so i think i have to go out and get another adapter so we
will see damn well best of luck to you i hope uh you're able to find the magic thing that gets a
chart yeah it probably needs to put out a certain amount of voltage that maybe whatever you're using
isn't doing but then again i also picked up another tablet while i got myself the certain
8 gig surface go which has a surface charger it also charges my usb-c so i do have to pick up
another charger so well there you go so maybe maybe that'll work so just make sure it's a
yeah if you're trying to do it like through a computer or through a plate it probably won't
be enough juice to enough voltage to do it but i bet if you get a pretty decent brick
um that can really pump some voltage through it i bet it'll i bet it'll work
that's what i'm thinking so you know for the time being i'm just letting it be until mocotron
ships it to me you know so i can because i am enjoying it i i can see the difference between
playing on a small screen and a large screen which i enjoy but since i'm kind of disappointed so
oh bobby also with an excellent suggestion suggesting a bypass the dock the dock is
going to require a higher voltage than just the system itself so uh if you plug directly
into the system you might be able to get away with it on whatever you're using now
yeah but you know but i will have to use the regular charger so i can actually play it on
the tv so of course understandable all right my friend i'm gonna let you go so we can wrap up but
thank you so much for the call hey no problem y'all take care stay awesome take care my friend
bye all right so i think with that we're through everything in the uh discord channel so thank you
lots of calls tonight thank you so much for that uh we do want to start to move to wrap up here
though since this is close to 9 30. i do have to ask if there's any last minute stories just
yeah i don't want to leave anything out all right yes i have a couple things so the first one being
that um the company beat games who as the developer of beat saber i think this news broke
during the show last week i feel like but maybe maybe not i thought it was a thing that broke
during the show but go ahead they were acquired by facebook yeah so now if you want to get that
beat saber action you're gonna have to do it on through oculus i guess well well they're gonna
no because i remember talking about they're gonna continue to support all the platforms that are
out there now so they're not gonna like pull it from whatever yeah but if there's a beat saber 2
or you know who knows but you know minecraft is a microsoft product and they still
runs great on nintendo there's still a playstation 4 version yeah but microsoft versus facebook
fair i'm not the biggest facebook fan but let's let's wait until something actually happens before
we say doomsday and then in acquisition news as well we have slightly mad studios uh the
developers project car is being acquired by code masters which you know code masters has a lot of
their own uh driving franchises so like i said it kind of makes sense yeah that's it money money
money all right so that's it for last minute stories so it brings our show just about to a
close uh we're gonna go around and get everybody's final thoughts but again here on this 800th
episode of our show just want to thank you guys for being here whether it's live whether it's on
the podcast you know you guys really make up this show and keep us going um so i really can't thank
you enough thank you for your participation and uh you know it's funny because why we are set on
that call if we do this for two more years we'll be celebrating 900 and i'm thinking in the back
of my head if we do it for four more years we'll get to a thousand we should do it wouldn't that
be something we'll try Guinness we'll try yeah hey Guinness do the thing and then you know what
if we get to a thousand i'll fucking call Guinness but i'll do it before that well here's the thing
there's other shows that have hit a thousand episodes but they do more than one a week like
i can think of a couple podcasts that like during e3 week they'll release like 20 episodes we've
been around longer than everybody that is still yeah that's still going regularly weekly yes i
think there is a show that did something then stopped for a long time then came back
but i shouldn't count it yeah i'm not counting that we're the longest continuously weekly show
without a major break so all right anyhow yeah uh dark diseases 2022 is 20 years yeah that would be
that be yeah that'd be about three years i mean it doesn't line up you would think oh there's
about 50 give or take weeks in a year shouldn't you be on episode it would be what like 850 by
now but just you know shit happens like we miss two weeks here and there we go on vacation things
happen you know so we don't but most of your shows out there like you know if you're watching things
on netflix what you get like 10 episodes of stranger things a year uh and even regular series
shows you get what like 26 episodes maybe yeah i might have to wait until 2020 for the end of
um the good place damn it oh oh did they go on a break i i'm still time to catch up on season
three i'm really behind oh you're on season three oh so swung tong says vgn is just this
long-running issue but they all go on hiatus a lot no disrespect to those hard-working fellows
over there but um as you pointed out they do go on hiatus a lot so um i think they went like a year
at least uh with a break um also we did start on life 365 just before i think they got started
in 03 or 04 uh our first episode was june of 2002 again i mean no disrespect um and i think
everything that they've accomplished should be celebrated as well it is not easy to keep your
show going one year let alone 17 so anyway um bobby blackwell says they claim to be the oldest
video game podcast well unfortunately um that is i want to see the receipts show me an episode
that you did before june of 2002 that was branded that same way because i don't think it exists
sorry and again even if it did as been pointing out there's been been a lot of long breaks so
all right and also sorry again i'm gonna sound like i'm being rude and i'm really not but i do
believe at one point the name of that show has changed because they weren't about video games
for a while um so just kind of just have to say that sorry anyway um let's see did i get final
thoughts no i was i was ramping up and saying thanks for all that stuff and all that good stuff
so let's go around and get everybody's final thought um dark soccer we'll start with you i
know you've been under the weather and and not feeling it as the show's been going on so thanks
for for persevering you have final thought tonight um i'm gonna go to brooke fields and get my
favorite soup which is the avago lemono it's like greek penicillin yeah i'm gonna get two
containers of it i'm gonna take that shit home and i'm gonna stay home from work tomorrow and
fall into a coma and do nothing but sleep and eat soup i hope they're still open they're up until
10. better get over there all right oh shit i'm gonna have time yeah it's almost 9 30. all right
well then i'll be going to whitey tofu house all right uh and then let's see uh my final thought
tonight you know i'm just in a very thankful uh mood so thank you everybody who's um supported us
um through the years and so forth and um yeah i played a lot of video games this week i even beat
one and i am fucking proud of that accomplishment so i'm gonna keep on trucking through death
stranding and who knows whatever else i decide to get into this week last but not least loki your
final thought i'm just gonna be working more on my game and that's it all right good luck i hope
we really do get to see something with that so that's gonna do it for another week here at
orange lounge radio for the 800th time thank you so much for tuning in and uh we'll see you next
time we'll do this all again 801 next week bye everyone good night you've been listening to
orange lounge radio orange lounge radio is a production of olr studios to join us for a live
show tune into fognetwork.com sunday nights at 6 p.m pacific 9 p.m eastern the views and opinions
expressed in this program do not necessarily reflect those of the staff of orange lounge radio
or vog network but you know they were all still true
see you next week
you