What, uh, what should we expect from your routine today? Is it a big secret? No? Can you give us any details before you go?
One word. Shades.
Message for you, son!
Attention!
Do you want to hear the most annoying fan in the world?
You're listening to Orange Lounge Radio, the Monty Talk, and then some.
Orange Lounge may contain adult content, Orange Lounge may contain many 4-letter words.
Orange Lounge may contain a scene of nudity. Orange Lounge may contain hot-monkey sex.
Just kidding, Orange Lounge will not contain hot-monkey sex.
In this episode...
What's your favorite scary movie?
Showgirls.
Absolutely frightening.
What's yours?
There are no stupid questions.
Just stupid people.
Don't torture yourself.
That's my job.
Now's the time on sprockets and we dogs.
I'll get you my pretty and your little dog too.
For no good food.
I'm sorry but all questions must be submitted in writing.
Why did they have to take the word game?
No!
Why did they have to take the word gay?
No! Nobody expects us, finally takes the position.
It's kendo.
Hey!
Dark Sakurai.
Shut up!
Where's my gun?
This is my boomstick.
Sky.
Come on girls, it's time to drop the bomb.
Loki.
I can't, for the life of me, get the hooker to have sex with me.
What kind of working and being would find that funny?
Orange Lounge Radio.
We are live!
And this is episode number 28 for January the 12th of 2003
You're tuned into the BEES!
Manisine's most shade-sy radio station of all things
My name is Rob Roberts, you might know me as Sky. Joining me, as always, are my
awesome
co-hosts, well one's invisible at the second. He isn't here yet. That would be
Loki
within your yet
the others right here and she's she's perky as always right
i'm wanting to do this particular show and michael jack
say hello to dark chakra
and some of these at the door
did you bring hot man sex with you
yes hot man sex is a bad person ok we'll get to that later
uh... this episode of the twenty-eight will be doing the fremont
attorney wrap-up, and you'll have to excuse us in advance. We're all a little out of it today.
Two of us have had headaches, one of us has been coughing, and one of us is late!
Say hello to Loki, there he is. Does that mean I'm having a baby?
Only if your water
breaks, I don't know. We're just really freaking tired after yesterday.
I'm feeling better, though. I was in a really pissy mood,
but I saw destruction on the way here, so I was happy.
always fun.
only $1.99 and actually what's kind of funny is this says that this is a baby
coyote now to my knowledge coyotes do not look like ferrets I don't understand
how this is a coyote or whatever at that um that long so we went to the yes the
fuck my diet at the Walgreens at the longs that we went to in Fremont they had
gigantic ones of these. I almost got one.
And don't forget, yesterday there was a horse, and we'll hear about that in the interviews
a little later. Oh, what, you mean Hot Man Sex?
No, not Hot Man Sex, the actual horse that Corey had that was, you know, made for a man
but pH balanced for a woman type thing. Yeah.
Anyway, yeah, it's going to be one of those shows. Darkticity summed it up right there.
Happy 24th, by the way. Where's my donut?
Let's say hello to Maureen's studio guests before we get to the first break.
Wow, there's chaos going on here. I feel like I'm in the middle of Gumby's routine. Jesus.
Say hello to Brad.
Another step has entered the game.
Say hello to Irene.
Hi guys!
And Dave is over there too. Dave, say hi.
Hi.
Dave, you look like a monk.
You know it, baby.
All right, baby.
All right.
We better go to break right now.
Now's a good time.
Let's do a break with some, we'll do a break with some songs from Extreme, because Extreme
is spreading across the country like a bad case of herpes.
It's extremely extreme.
Soon to be in your neighborhood.
Yeah, Rob spread it.
Hi guys, you're listening to Orange Jones Radio.
you
Oh
I don't want to lose you
And I don't want to lose you
Here's one of my favorite tracks.
by request, this is V, the Xtreme Edit.
Hi everybody, this is DSCS.
Make sure to visit SoCalKicks.com and you're listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
We finally accomplished ultimate evolution just now.
And then you make the horses have sex.
Oh, wait, are we live?
Yes, I just turned the mics on.
And then you make the horses have sex.
You pick your horses and they breed.
They go off into the distance.
You breed the horses for real?
They go off into the distance and there's a dramatic fade out.
And I see you see the mommy horse and the baby horse.
And the baby horse goes, hi, I'm the baby horse.
You get to name me.
So I named my hot man sex.
All right.
Mommy, where do baby horses come from?
Yeah, we're talking about Derby Owners Club.
Virtual horses.
I'll own you.
That game is crack.
Breathe.
Um, I'm...
My horse is...
And then I name mine Takumi, and uh, yeah.
No, you don't have any horses.
I know, I just...
But then, but then you train your horses...
I thought that Ryosuke could own Takumi easily.
You train your horsies, and then...
It's like that code.
And then you make them run around, and then you drown them, like Matt did.
I drowned my horse three times, and I was being mean.
For those that are completely lost right now...
My horse likes bananas.
talking about a new game, a somewhat new game, called Derby Owners Club. Now this game, it's
worse than DDR. It is a bigger drug than DDR ever is. It's kind of like, it's kind of like
DDR is like, DDR is kind of like, I don't know, like, DDR is kind of like pot, and Derby
Owners Club is kind of like just straight up smack. Because like, the straight up smack
is way more expensive, and there's not as much to it, you know, you just kind of take
the smack, you know, you don't have to worry about...anyway, the point I'm trying to make,
what the hell is Derby Owners Club? It's like these big, just giant seizure buttons you
use to beat your horse, and you throw $2.50 into the machine each time, and you just beat
them and you bond with them. That's all Derby Owners Club is. And yet, I find myself strangely
We're going to tell everybody our horses, but mine are last. Rob, what's your horse's name?
My horses are out on the car still, I believe. Or, I don't know, but my horses, I have Miss Thang, which I made in Irvine.
And then I have Beaver Fever, which I made last night in Milpitas.
Okay, I've got BJ, the horse I made in Irvine.
I have Cloud, the horse I jacked from the little girl in Irvine.
And then I have the two horses I made in Milpitas last night. We have Big Black Cock and Mr. Spanky.
And Mr. Spanky's being an ass, so I beat the shit out of him.
He wanted the coconut, but he wasn't good enough, so I gave him the hay.
So that's it.
We're being corrected in the chat room. Derby Owners Club at Milpitas Golf Line actually costs $2.25 a game. Sorry, Milton!
Not that you're making any horse, then it's three.
haha
uh-huh
it being a quarter of peace
yeah anyway
anyway my life it's expensive anyway
i have my first sources of Slytherin chaser is all black and he's really
he's a naughty horse
then my next horse
uh... by the way Slytherin chaser likes oranges
and then my next horse is i like cheese
and then next one is hot man sex
That was my best horse. I won third place with that one.
Then my next horse is Mmm Fajitas.
And my fifth horse is Jin Kazama.
So you spent like thirty dollars on this game or something?
Twelve.
Twelve? Wow, wait. You had like five cards though.
That's three dollars times five is fifteen.
I had two of my games paid for and then Matt lent me money.
Thank you.
Oh great, now you have other people buying you drugs.
That's when you know you're addicted.
Pretty soon you're going to be going to meetings.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
Anyway, well, Jamie has left the building.
Oh, and I get the chair.
Let's just go around the room and talk about our week.
Because we don't really have any structured Orange Islands Radio.
I know we've got a lot of new people joining us tonight.
They're tuning into here tonight's Fremont interviews.
interviews, and we will get to those in just a sec, but welcome to Orange Lounge Radio.
We're Bee-mani Talk Radio, we talk about DDR2DX, Big Black Cocks, masturbating with cake mix,
and all sorts of various random things, basically, that have nothing to do with each other. No,
we try to talk about Bemani, but obviously, if we were able to actually talk three hours
every week about Bemani, we are in really sad shape and have no life, so things get
really random on this program, so enjoy the randomness, and come into our chat room.
makes the ratings go up. Yes, and randomness makes ratings go up. Go to our website, orangelounge.skie.cx
and join in the chat because our chat room is insane. And play nice in the chat tonight,
kids. Play nice. Or we'll beat you. Or we'll whip you just like Mr. Spanky. We'll whip
be like a pony
we have ecstasy
without robs dr ads from the ecstasy cigarettes from two weeks ago show when
the official lesbians were lost in the house
with a dang
about two weeks ago it's nice to meet you guys and make you horny
anyway those things have catnip in it is not cool
they have to have to know i'm not a cat
I'm allergic to snacks.
Damiana makes you horny.
Hey, you know what we oughta do?
Let's all go run out and smoke an ecstasy cigarette and come back and do the show and
see what happens.
It smells like my mom's lasagna or something.
You are a dick.
These are yummy donuts.
Smells like old antique store.
It does.
Ew.
The ingredients are Damiana, Wild Lettuce, Catnip, Passion Flower, Mint, Love, and Light
What's that?
And uh, manufactured by X-Men Z Incorporated.
What is love?
Baby don't hurt me.
In Beverly Hills.
Don't hurt me no more.
And these are made by hippies.
Let's have some, some um, crack.
If I try out these cigarettes and I get horny, is anybody gonna help me out here?
Don't look at me, look at Irene.
She's not in here.
Don't look at me like that Brad, you're scaring me.
Joke.
Ew.
I thought I left the insects in the other room.
OK, so anybody else want to talk about their week,
something that happened this week?
Yes, Dave.
Dave.
I have finals next week, and it is crap.
Ha ha.
And I was like, mom, let me go to the show.
She's like, no, you have to study.
And I was like, dad, let me go to the show.
And he's like, OK, but you have to study later.
So my dad is cool.
But when I get home, I have to study for an hour and a half.
Study means open the book.
And have it in the music.
comic book that's really inside the book.
No, no, no, not that. Just open the book, stare into it blankly.
I'm just going to listen to Orange Lounge and just be like, hey, it's music.
And then I kind of wake up later and be like, yeah, I've been studying the whole time.
In high school, I didn't study, and look where it got me.
That's exactly why I am.
That's exactly the reason I am studying.
Why are you dressed like a monk?
Because I'm wearing...
I know it's not because you want to remain virginal for the rest of your life.
life wait wait wait look look look what I'm wearing oh what's that say it says
boo-boo oh I'm black now no no no no no I I have the big black cock now what is
this the Jewish boo-boo is that no jubu we will offend everyone you know that's
funny because there was a guy yesterday at Fremont that did a routine his name
was the Jew, made me think of you. That's not a good thing.
Well, Rob, I feel touched right here. I have to say, this guy did some very original
things. I have to commend that guy for having the balls to do what he did on that machine.
Very homoerotic original things. I bet when you watch the video, when you watch
the video, you're going to notice I'm the only one laughing at that routine.
Okay, keep in mind, keep in mind everybody had balls there yesterday.
yes for everybody at balls but this guy had really big balls to be doing back
stuff on everybody else to a normal day at a big black cock to go with them can
you show us rob
shows what he did
i'm stopping uh... u s bb ask an excellent question which relates to last
week's discussion did he with his cock out at the end of routine is i was
saying last week
nobody's done that yet and somebody needs to
and be the ultimate thing
no he did not with his car contracts are some people but i did almost a hit i did
almost get hit with his shirt. I had to kind of pick it off the table with my pen that
I was judging with. Speaking of shirts, you had a Twinkie yesterday. Ah, fuck. Ok, Nikkari,
if you're listening, you a bitch. No, seriously, Nikkari's great. He's a good guy. I like him
a lot. But I get to the tournament and I think I'm hot shit because Jamie and I, we ordered
shirts from the Engrish store, and I have my shirt that says, I hate myself and I want
to die, with the little rainbows and the stars.
I get there, I'm walking in, I'm wearing the shirt, and Jamie does this way better.
What's the first thing Nikkari does?
He runs out the door, he can't say it, he goes, oh no you didn't.
And pretty soon, here are Nikkari and I, and those of me out there that happen to know
me a little better than just the radio, and no Nikkari, know that Nikkari and I have something
in common that a lot of D.R. people don't have in common.
So it's just kind of, it made it a lot funnier that, hey, we happen to be wearing the same
shirt.
Too bad that exhibition didn't happen.
Yeah, we were supposed to do an exhibition P.A., but it didn't happen because he had
to go to work and I had to go get batteries to do the tape stuff.
Was Nikkari the Jew guy or was that different?
No, no, no, no.
No, no, completely different guy.
Now what did you rate that guy?
Did you give them like a 100?
I'm not allowed to reveal how I rated people, but if you want to see the judges' towers,
you can look at the results.
They're linked with the DDR3 thing.
I don't want to know about the judges' towers.
I don't need to know this, I'm an innocent, pure-hearted, oh fuck.
You're having to resort to Barry Propel.
You've got to tell, because the listeners that listen to Orange Lawn's radio know about
your love obsession with propel and yesterday what did you find next door to the tournament
berry flavored propel has been um dethroned as my favorite flavor of propel they have
peach flavor propelled because everyone knows i can drink a peach for hours actually i don't
remember what line that movie came from that i can eat that would be face off that's dan's
favorite movie which he actually broke by stepping on the laser disc so um but yeah
Yeah, he says that all the time with our Animal Crossing town, because we have peaches. But
I can drink peaches now. And look at Dan, seductively, go, I'm drinking a peach. Who?
Shut up. Okay. We're going to get to those Fremont interviews
in just a second here, but I wanted to have a serious moment here at the beginning of
the show. No, I want to have a serious moment here, because people died this week, and it
kind of sucks uh... one of the bt's passed away today
uh... maurice maurice hits i believe was the bt that has to wait a long
okay i don't even know the difference between on it
i have a saturday night beaver soundtrack thank you have two copies on
final
i like to be
i don't think it is a noble drop
besides um...
being a band
have no idea what the bt's are so maybe you could enlighten me
i'm too young
they did that song stand alive
uh... you are such a baby
uh... that's it i'm gonna bring you a beat of the best of the bgcd do it
that's right that's right david shit you know i find it very funny that this is a
very serious thing i was looking at your yahoo thing
and i see how you have movies stars and
all this
and and mike
Excuse me.
How unladylike.
Congratulations.
And my yahoo, that one tasted like my dinner, and my yahoo has like world events, and when
the next Harry Potter movie is supposed to come out, important things, yeah, it has my
horoscope, it has my comics, but it has world events, important things that are going to
affect my children's children's children when the magnetic layer decides to erode and everybody
dies.
But your children shouldn't be having kids. I mean, they're so young and they shouldn't have sex.
I don't even have them yet!
I don't want children-
Ew! Fetal sex!
Ew!
No, I don't want children because they'll play with my toys.
It doesn't matter. You have to understand that the world has really nothing to fear because all the world's problems can be solved with nuclear weapons.
I mean, that's what we've learned from the movie The Core that's going to be coming out later on.
We learned, oh hey, if the Earth's pole stops rotating, and I honestly didn't realize that the core of the Earth was rotating,
I guess it is, so the movie said so, it must be true, so...
Hey, are you drunk, Matt? Your face is really red.
No.
He's not Asian, so pay for space to be red like that.
He's so excited, and he just can't hide it.
He's about to lose control and he thinks he likes it.
I'm just so excited.
What is this, the gas episode? Jesus.
Where?
Also, no, also seriously, another famous celebrity that died this week that's very, very sad.
Roxette?
No.
Damn it.
No, no.
She has cancer, but she's not dying yet.
No, this is bigger than that.
This is bigger than that.
Oolong the bunny died, ladies and gentlemen.
Oh my God!
Oolong the bunny, the bunny that balances-
Oh, it's JWTF!
The bunny that balances shit on its head.
I mean, Oolong was a pig, by the way.
In Dragon Ball.
Okay, now you even got me on that one. I think I'm too young for that one, too.
It's an internet joke. Maybe somebody would be so kind to post the link to Oolong the Bunny so I can show some folks the pictures here.
I want to see the pictures of the dead bunny with all the little bunnies.
No, that's horrible!
I want to see it! I want to see it!
You're horrible! You're a horrible woman!
I want to see it! See, see, see!
Hopefully somebody in the chat room knows what I'm talking about when I talk about Oolong the Bunny.
Ah, bunnies just arrived at the cotton ball shoved up its ass.
My God!
You two know that you're the most popular host on this show in the chat room.
You know, that's from, I actually have a quote from a movie, that was from the movie Table
One I was talking about, a really shitty movie about these guys who wanted to open this restaurant
lounge.
Doesn't anyone understand that restaurant lounges don't survive?
In the movie, it didn't survive, so they turned it into a strip club, and that's why the movie
rocks.
This guy's going to talk about movies all night long, he's just like, so, yeah, um.
The president died and, oh man, this movie I saw the other night sucks, man.
Anybody? Come on.
And also, another thing that died was this segment.
And Charlie's Angels 2 is gonna suck ass. Duh.
The first one sucked ass. Why? Okay.
Okay, here's the trailer, okay?
They're on this bridge in this Russian, like, cargo truck thingy.
And there's a tank on one side, and a guy with an RPG on the other side.
So what they do, they're going to drive the truck off the freaking damn rocket-propelled grenade.
Dragon Warrior?
I can tell you why the second Charlie's Angels movie is going to suck.
Demi Moore's in it. Her career is over.
She belongs on the surreal life right now.
And they also took out, um, freaking, um...
What's his name?
The comedian?
Bill Murray.
Bill Murray's not in it, so that's why it's going to suck.
bernie mac is pretty funny
i don't know man
well it doesn't matter he doesn't really have a major part of the movie anyways
dave would know this uh...
don't be a menace
while drinking your juice or whatever
what? wasn't he a menace?
i have no idea what you're talking about come on you're our local ghetto jew
hi back to bemani hello yeah bemani
jamie's gonna go blow her nose okay that's fine
I've been given some lovely advanced MP3s from Cory the Sultan.
Cory the Sultan has given us some MP3s.
World premieres here right here.
You're not going to be able to hear them.
Can't download them.
Can't hear them anywhere else.
We've got them.
We're going to play them in this next break.
But I wanted to ask you guys that have played Extreme now this week.
It's been out for a week.
What do you guys think of Extreme?
Well, you know, I really, really, really, really liked it at first, and now I'm like kind of, eh, it's cool and all, but I'm getting bored pretty fast, and that's bad. Bad that I'm losing interest this fast, and, you know, and we haven't even gotten ours yet, and I'm like, eh, whatever.
Rosalind doesn't count, fuckers!
Well, the game itself didn't suck, because I could...
It seems a hell of a lot easier to PA stuff, because I was...
Let him finish, we'll get back to this.
It's the pancake, buddy!
Let Black Lab finish.
Yes, let me finish! God, people!
Okay, yeah, so I played it, I didn't hear the songs, and I was still double A-ing stuff, because I was...
All I could hear was the Max2 net right, like, 10 feet, or 10 inches away from it, so yeah.
It's easier to re-PA stuff on it.
Yeah.
You wanna know how I feel about Max?
Uh, I mean, sorry.
Extreme? Extreme?
Max 2+.
Jamie's out of nuts.
That's, uh, that's how I feel about it.
Okay, so back to this, what we brought up on the internet here,
I was given a link in the chatroom, thank you very much to yosfbb,
to the We Love Oolong page, which has Oolong the bunny balancing pancakes on its head here in the corner.
Please, can we have a serious moment, please?
Hokkaido, Japan. Oolong, the friend of children, bounds across the snow.
You bitch!
That verb was bumpsy, but very flavored Propel.
Go back YouTube, I'll be serious, I promise.
You'll be serious? You promise. You promise.
Happiness is a Japanese rabbit who rests pancakes on his hand.
Alright.
Oh my god, that's such a cute bunny.
He's a fucking gorgeous bunny and you all are really rude. You are rude people.
I don't know why I let you in my house. Okay.
So did he try to balance, like, say, I don't know, a ten-ton safe on his head, and is that what did him in, you know?
How did he die?
Let's, um...
We're gonna read another one? Hold on, hold on, here's another.
I don't know if I can trust you with reading these. All right, all right, here we go.
Shh! Shh!
Where is murder?
that's not what that's the person who wrote it
with big black
i'm still trying to figure out how this rabbit died it's like it had heart
failure or some shit like that heart failure my ass
it's a cover-up i say he's trying to balance the tenth unsafe on his fucking head
are you saying it faked its own death to sell more albums
yes
it's like the elvis of the burrito like to pop i think hiding when the secret
i'll be waiting for his return logan to block
but the hell
all i think it was an untighted embarrassment we're having to
don't pancakes on his head
cut this is our u.s.f. people you know it's a bb actually posted since i was a
picture of the uh...
the uh... al-qaeda having the big picture of us on the bin laden with the
bird is evil thing there
and if you look very carefully towards the middle left
there's a lot of the body with pancakes on the ten
you guys are sick
i want to see the picture of dead bunnies
you cannot see the picture of dead bunnies
i don't have the picture of dead bunnies nobody's given me the link yet
somebody says that they have a picture of uh...
um... adults a picture of the uh... pancake bunny
now it's become this new like
it's become the uh...
the tourists guide a new tourist guided
guy that was on you know it's worse i was the guy that was in that picture of
the supposedly the plane hitting the building and then they put him all these
pictures
okay this is this is really bad radio i'm not going to go through with all
these pictures right now um oh no we have ferret nookie but oolong the bunny is oh look
look here you go a little picture a little avatar you can use halfling pancake bunny
i want a bunny you can't have a bunny all right all right now's a good time to take
a break i believe i cry for humanity we're gonna take a break as promised as promised
some brand spanking new EX songs, and when we come back, that Fremont coverage, let me
load up those songs, and we will be right back. You are listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
Our apologies. We're going to start this off with Graduation. After that, Sync for Extreme
and tears will wrap up this set.
Remember, all brands make a new Xtreme.
we love dead bunnies
I'm a
I'm
Orange Lounge Radio. We put your thing down, flip it and reverse it.
Um, is that a ferret in your pocket or are you just excited about the show?
It's actually a baby coyote in my pocket.
Whatever.
Don't mind me for a second. You guys have to fill while I get the tape queued up here.
Fill or fill or space. Fill or fill or space.
On the next episode of Dragon Ball Z, Goku gets a real gun shoved up his ass and he lives.
Wow!
And he goes like super duper say at level 28 and kills people.
You know what I don't understand is why they didn't bury the bunny in the pancake on its head.
That would have been funny.
Yeah, but they didn't even put a pancake on its head.
It had an orange on its belly.
So?
Not a pancake on its head.
It's famous for things on its head.
Not its belly.
He has dirt on his head.
He's balancing dirt.
And pushing up the daisies while he's at it.
Well, good for him.
I was a cute bunny, though. I had a sniffle.
See, now you see how mean you all were
while I was trying to read those haikus.
It was hilarious, all those random pictures were pretty funny on that site.
Do your dead bunny thing. We miss you terribly and hate that you are dead.
Oolong died but apparently came out to life in Animal Crossing because your new guy Coco or whatever looks like a dead bunny.
Did somebody leave for Coco to show up? Who left?
Maddie.
Maddie left. That makes me cry.
a webcomic.
Um, FYI, I tried one of those ecstasy cigarette things, and I don't feel at all the least
bit, like, aroused. I just have halitosis now.
I'm glad I can't smell it.
Well, let one of us jerk you off, then you'll feel, then you'll feel aroused. No, in fact,
I feel like I gotta take a fat piss. If anything comes out along with it, then I'll let you
guys know.
I can smell, you walked in and I can smell that cigarette on you.
For the life of God, and all that is holy!
Brad, smoke five of them, see if anything happens.
Eat them!
You could probably eat them, though, safely.
Yeah, except for the filter.
You could open the filter and make tea out of them.
Seriously, you could.
No, SoCalKicks, I did not just volunteer to do that favor for Brad. He has a girlfriend.
Oh, stop it!
Stop it!
I think now is a good time, because we've got a lot of people tuned in.
They want to hear this. This is the Fremont coverage. This is where all of us were at yesterday.
Let go of it!
Oh my lord.
How does it feel to want?
Alright you can want in one hand and shit in the other and see which one fills up first.
Okay here we go with the Fremont tournament coverage.
This is going to get very crazy you guys, I just warn you.
We'll butt in with our comments.
I'm going to leave the mics hot so we might be butting in and out with our comments.
So here we go.
This is us yesterday.
That's just horribly wrong.
us yesterday
yesterday at fremont i hate this show
i touched it
tell them where we're at sweetie
we're at checky cheeses
i mean pan-tied pizza
omg wtf
i'm eating nuts
Okay, this is really random. Okay, for real, this is Orange Town's radio live on, um, what's
today? I don't know. The 11th. The 11th. 111. 111. 111-03. And we're here for Fremont, for
Fremont 2 tourney. And Rob kicked, um, ass on accident. I wasn't even supposed to be
here today you traded places with me and i'm eating nuts next and i'm not saying anything
and standing back here in the corner right here let's let everybody assembled out here say hello
hello everybody what's up let's uh let's talk to her too over here how you doing i lost you lost
what happened bud you took my power i'm so it was the shirt i swear to god i hate myself and i want
want to die
i'll give you the shirt off my back now i'm just getting a one i i don't walk
around naked it's like see you got a course or you have panicking
what exactly is panicking ink is
quality software for your apple micro computer is that like the organ trailer
yes i'm like that
without who's this
who's this over here what's your name
i'm sorry
hey how you doing
brings you to fremont today
Cory, I love Cory so much, I'm gonna bow down and kiss his shoes after he's done, but, you know.
You're a Cory fanboy?
Yes, I am.
Did you go, oh my god, it's the Max 300 King?
Yes, I said, oh my god, it's the Max 300 King.
All right, now anything you want to say to our lovely listeners out there on the radio?
Cory actually really sucks, I just pretend like he's really cool so that he'll like me.
Secrets revealed.
Don't worry, everybody does that. No, I'm kidding, I'm kidding.
Cory's gonna beat me up.
I want to say hello to one of my favorite guests to have on any radio program ever.
Give it up, ladies and gentlemen, it's Jahi.
I love this guy.
He always puts me on the microphone, especially when I'm drunk.
It's really great.
How are you doing?
How are you doing, Ski?
What have you had to drink today?
I'm actually completely sober and I gave up pot smoking as a New Year's resolution.
What the hell happened?
That's not right.
I didn't say I gave up drinking or eating pot, I just said I gave up smoking it.
So having it in the brownies is okay?
Yes.
your friend, rise your friend. All interaction at Jockey, www.mystyle.com. www, what the hell
is wrong with you, dot com. www, I didn't even pay for that dot com. Alright, I'll let
Jamie talk to some folks over here. I have the microphone. Anyway, first interview that
I do, say your name for our listeners. My Hypergirl. And you sure are. So what have
you been doing here at the thing all day with that bit of leather oh well last
year at Fremont one I'd worn a leather vest for routine so this year I'm
continuing the tradition I'm referring to the leather that you've been wrapping
around all the guys here oh that's the leather whip that's just randomly
wrapping it around people so how many victims have you claimed today well
Well, let's see. There's Cory, Nikkari, Nado, um...
I think there were a couple others, but I can't remember right now.
I must have threatened a whole lot of other people with it.
So I'm, are you competing in, you are competing in freestyle today?
Yeah, I am.
Very cool, best of luck.
Thank you.
Do you have any special words for our listeners?
um I'm turning 18 in a month and a half so I will thus lose my jailbait status
by summer should be able to legally buy porn yeah I don't have a gangbang legally
be in porn don't give her ideas it'll basically make my routines legal to watch
yeah it'll be in and download on the internet I did that before I was 18 you
You heard it here first on Orange Lounge.
I'm sorry, did anyone else just hear Jahi in the background scream,
NO MEANS NO!
Yeah, I fucking love Jahi. I love that man. Alright.
We are watching Rob get his ass beaten with a whip.
Thank you sir, may I have another?
This one violent hyper girl was beating me up with her whip. It was cool.
Ah, I see why all the boys like her.
At this point I was sitting inside playing GameCube and I was distracted by that.
All of a sudden I see Aaron...
Did you like the image of me getting beat up?
No, I was horribly horribly scarred by it because I look out the window and see Aaron with her whip and see you sticking your ass out waiting for it.
Hey, could have been worse. Could have been my bear ass, okay?
Twitch.
Moving on.
Interviewing you.
Hi guys, I'm DCB.
And what makes you special?
I'm running the tournament, or at least I was.
You're also being pelted with nuts.
It's raining nuts.
Hallelujah.
Stop throwing nuts in my head!
Don't throw nuts in your head!
Hi! So how's the tournament been so far?
It's been hectic.
Because the wrong directions were given out to very many people.
And so that's probably why there's not a lot of people here today.
Stay tuned for the FUs of the Week. We'll be getting into that later.
Yeah, a fuck you goes to MapQuest, indeed.
Um, by the way, tournament running is not as much fun as it looks, is it?
I thought it would be fun, but it's hectic. It's crazy.
It's hell. But, you think it's all worth it?
In the end, yeah.
So, do you have anything special to say for our listeners?
Hi, guys.
Hi, Dad. I'm in jail. I like it here.
All right. I have another interview here with the one, the only, the infamous, say hello to Kyle Snyder, ladies and gentlemen.
Hello.
How are you doing today?
I'm doing all right.
What brings you to Fremont, sir?
This is my hometown. I'm competing in this tournament to show my greatest, one of my greatest routines ever.
I can't say it's my greatest because flashing tonight is my greatest.
What should we expect from your routine today? Is it a big secret? Can you give us any details before you go?
One word.
Shades.
Cryptic.
Gets a reaction from the crowd.
Kyle, is there anything you want to say out there, listeners,
Orange Lawns Radio, Bomani Internet Radio?
I sure would.
To all those that are freestyling,
you are about to see a routine that you possibly have never seen before.
It is a Michael Jackson routine,
And I guarantee you, you are in for a show.
I am moist with anticipation.
How about everybody else?
Good luck out there, Kyle.
All right.
I'll see you soon.
You got many fans out there rooting for you.
Good luck.
All right.
That'd be a pretty cool name.
We're going to talk to these guys.
You want to talk to these guys, Jamie?
Or you want me to talk to these guys?
All right.
Who is this guy over here in the green?
Okay.
My name is Alex, aka La Saca Puntas for this tournament.
And for all you people that don't speak Spanish, that is the pencil sharpener.
Yes, that's right, I said pencil sharpener.
I thought Punta was whore.
No, that's the Saca Puntas.
Oh, my bad.
Yeah, so it's like the whole other word before it.
Yes, I know, I took Spanish.
So you're not a whore sharpener.
No, I'm not a whore shop.
I'm sorry.
Do I do support it?
No.
Anything you want to say about tourney today?
I don't know, actually.
This is my first time, so I don't know.
Virgin.
Virgin, yes.
Yes, that's right, um, I don't know, I was actually convinced into doing this, so this
is my cultural freestyle, best of luck to you, good to meet you, thank you, you too.
And uh, this is the, one of the co-runners of the tournament here, what's your name,
sir? Pete, AKA Henry. Alright, and uh, what makes you decide to do a tourney here at the
uh, lovely uh, where the hell are we? Funtime Pizza! Uh, I decided to make some money, I
I don't know.
Do you actually make money off a tournament?
That's unheard of for me, but...
Not much, no.
But it's fun.
All right.
Anything in particular you're really looking forward to seeing today?
Kyle Snyder.
It's the reason why we do this, right?
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Must see him.
He's my hero.
Must see.
DDR, ladies and gentlemen.
All right.
I had to ask one more question to DCB while I got him.
What's up with the Kirk Cameron and the milk thing?
Chaos, John.
he ripped it out of his cooking textbook
and i don't know if you just said hi guys and stuck it in my face and it's
kind of caught on ever since
wait a minute
a cooking textbook does that mean he's in home ec
a guy in home ec
i took a home ec in seventh grade and i got a pleasure because i can cook without burning
things
i took home ec in seventh grade
and i fail wait no i didn't see
macaroni is not very hard to make guys bunch of fags
I never took home macaroni, I just took anyway.
You took woodshop, didn't you?
Wait, no, we didn't even make macaroni.
That's too complicated.
I was in the gifted program and I got to take whatever the fuck I wanted.
Wait, no, we didn't make macaroni.
That was too complicated.
We made the little, like, biscuits where you, like, open up the can and then you just kind of put them onto the pan.
They made spam.
No, I'm sorry, maybe the school was a little bit too cheap for spam.
You made treat?
My home ec class, I actually cooked things.
We actually made pancakes from scratch, and I was the only one that could cook them without
burning them.
DCB's telling me that home ec is the cool thing to do at their school.
Well, at my school I just liked it because I got to eat food, and they gave this cool
thing to me.
I like to eat food.
I LIKE FOOD!
than eating faeces. That's funny, because I took it because I don't like to eat food,
you know, I just, oh my god. Okay, EOSFB just summed up high school in one sentence. Fuck,
I thought high school was going to be like Saved by the Bell, but I was wrong and disappointed.
Okay, you want to tell me what I learned in high school? Amen. Amen. Amen. Amen. I learned
how to either annoy or avoid people, and that a mole is 6.02 x 10-23. I'm so excited! I'm
I'm so excited! I'm so excited! I'm so scared!
Never mind.
Back to the back of the tape.
We'll let DCB finish the story now.
You can't stop time and talk to the camera?
No, unfortunately not.
Aww, back to the story, back to the story.
That's the joke, if y'all were wondering about inside jokes.
Yeah, it's all over my banner, all over my website, yeah.
It's about to die soon though. We need a new mascot for hi guys. He's so dreamy. Oh hell yeah
Right on oh, I didn't ask there's anything else you want to say any other shoutouts you want to give today, or what?
What's up? I?
Want to give a shout out to all my azm peeps all around the world
Peace out Bo. I was waiting for the acronyms. I've been waiting all day
day
virtues back with them
are you doing freestyle
unfortunately not
why not
i'm white
uh... i forgot
that gets me on your head again
i don't have my spinners
and i was just destroyed
yes
what's up
i'm just trying to remember what the hell johnnie was screaming about that
he's randomly hear him
i i i threatened to quit the show just like johnny takeover and i think all
three of us were agreement
the job he just needs to do the show
we've given his own show on yours on network at the degree to that
the johnny our way that way that i just come in and we're not even there yet
we're not even there yet
as they do it
i'm good hi guys
could show that there is that very nice
thank you
you know
that's all right
i don't know how that
I got off the machine and said, I'm not even supposed to be here today. What the hell is going on?
GLC Prize. Explain the horsey you've got here. It has a push button.
It's not just your average horse toy.
It's a sex toy for both boys and girls, you see.
Because
its beautiful face
gives great head.
And then I see you're caressing that face right now.
Yes, yes. Me and Eve have a lot of fun.
And then, if you flip a-
Eve is in Summer's Eve.
Over.
That's the girls' side.
This is just like the Harry Potter broomstick that vibrates.
Yeah, those are banned in Australia
because 12-year-old girls are riding them for more than an hour.
You must be this tall to ride.
Yeah, does that rule apply to, uh, Eve?
I can stand up and then give me head.
fair enough all right
i think that's better than the parent i think we've got some competition for the
fair in europe where jamie go
all she's up to no good
i think that's what's going to go cause some havoc
oh my god it's initial d live
it's initial d live
the reason why i don't think that's what he has left about it
We're, we're, we're, I've decided that at the next convention, on a big convention I
guess I'm gonna cosplay as Ulog.
I'm doing that.
Any fan of me, man.
Back to Fremont, hello.
Back to the topic at hand.
The reason why I'm yelling initial D live, you had all the step squad walking out towards
the cars, the race track.
I didn't know that they were actually going over there to take a group picture.
I thought they were actually all gonna get little go-karts and race.
No, we were gonna take a picture.
So I was like, initial D live!
I thought you were talking, oh what about like, the one that drove by in the big car
with the whole of the muffler. There we go. Oh my god, your cock's so big!
God, I hate guys with big cars. Anyway, moving on, interviews.
All of Step Squad hates me right now, it's all good. Alright, I'll be back later.
Alright, this is the portion of the show where we just give the microphone to Jahi and watch what happens.
Oh God. They keep doing this.
I don't know why. So now I'm walking around and I have a mic.
I think he just really doesn't give a rat's ass at this point. He's just, he's just letting me go.
He's just letting me go. I'm like the, like, man on the street host. I don't know.
Alright, so right now I'm walking around the front of, uh, Game Zone
Fremont. This is my old stomping grounds right here. Good shot to my friend, uh, Walter Williams. We used to walk here all the time. It's a nice arcade. And we're here with, um,
Natto. Natto, how's it going, man?
Yeah, pretty good, man. How's it going?
Cool, cool. Yeah, so you're here with Final Hyper, girl?
Yes, yes I am, yeah.
I'm assuming you're, like, happy today because she hasn't whipped you.
Well, yeah, oh, yeah. Like, I'm very fortunate that she hasn't whipped me yet, but she's, like, kicking the crap out of me right now.
VHD being the SSA or she is, she's kicking the shit out of Natto right now. They're probably going to have to edit that out on the show.
I got tons of people out here. Um, Khan's here, DCB's over here with his Kirk Cameron photo, which has traumatized me a lot.
oh god it's the man the myth the legend the RTF representer no skizzle Mike no
how's it going dog nose coughing right now he just smoked a
ten-sack he's okay how's it going man he's drinking Aquafina he's about to say
a few words as most of you guys should know today is my birthday to start I no
longer want to be addressed as Asian innovation for today I want you all to
call me the big party I've got my groove on you should too oh I think Mike I
think Mike had a fun birthday the video should be on the internet in a few days
All right, we're going to get run over, so I'm going to move. Fuzzy's drunk ass is driving
to hell with AORI, so I'm about to interview them in a minute.
How are you two gentlemen today? Are you competing in the tournament today?
Yes, I am.
Great, great. What's your name?
Robby.
Pete, I'm the one that's running the tournament.
Okay, so Pete's one of the staffers here that I haven't met yet, and he has, what does that
guy think, bubbles? I believe from the Strong Bad site. Go to homestarrunner.com, they own
you. So what are you going to be doing with the guitar here today?
I'm gonna be playing long train of run in my freshman's freestyle.
Wow. Okay, so we actually have somebody here with guitar skills, so we're not gonna hear Stairway to Heaven, right?
Uh, correct.
Thank you. Thank you, God. So how's the tournament been running today?
It's good. Yeah, at first, no, it was not good. There's like five people showed up, but then, yeah, everyone showed up.
Cool. So how many people do you think you have here today?
Uh, maybe like 80.
Wow. No, no. I don't know.
We'll find out later if that's...
How many tournaments have you run? This is my first one.
Is this the, from the tournaments that you've been to in DDR, is this like the average turnout for a tournament about 80, 100 people?
Yes it is.
Good turnout for the most part?
Yeah.
Everybody makes their money back and...
Yeah, everything's good.
Okay, he looks like he's scared as hell because I have a microphone right here. Don't worry, it's Orange Lounge. Everybody's half drunk anyway.
Orange Lounge owns you, go to that website. Okay, we got another person over here. This is...
I so can't read that, that's Chaos. Okay, how's it going, man?
What's up, man?
How you doing today?
I'm pretty good.
Did you already compete today?
Yep, I got third place in PA.
Wow third place in PA and he's getting he beat me at PA sniff. That's okay. I wasn't even supposed to be there
Anyway, you beat me
Miracles happen, I don't know. I just I just remember everyone that sounds like oh, yeah
it's gonna be this this and this and as always the top three they always mean but I
Don't know it's just I I woke up on the right side of bed, I guess
but I was able to go due to some reasons.
really because of emphasis and of course Tigger
I still fear emphasis and Tigger I'm like you know like a newbie when it
comes to the whole PA thing
so Cory's stealing his money so but yeah but
so how did you feel about third place what song did you play as your last song when you competed?
we played... what did we play? we played Kakamei
Heavy. Oh but the listeners after this tournament did take place on a DDR7 mix
so Kakamei is just nasty anyway
I did not.
Why not have a cock?
We got nuts.
We got balls.
We got cock.
It's a regular gay porno out here.
I think I see Ken Stryker walking in right now.
And Hanzo just ran out when he heard about the nuts.
FYI, it's Jeff Stryker.
Not that I know these things.
Balls and cock.
How you doing, Hanzo?
Oh, hey now.
Hey now.
I don't be getting down like that.
I'm going to leave that up for you.
But, hey.
Hey.
for you, but hey, I'm not down with the whole nuts and cocks thing. I don't swag. I'd rather
be down with that than be down with what R. Kelly was down with, though. You're right,
that is all bad. That whole yellow shower thing? No, no. Anybody here like the yellow
shower thing? No. Exactly. Scott wanted to play a song. We're going to let Scott play
Alright, I'll go play Long Chain of Runnin' from 7th Mix.
Alrighty. Let's do it.
Go.
Eric clapped me in the house.
Clap, dammit!
I clap with one right.
one right which are he says clapping fucking clap
so he's it's not as a threat he actually has to go with this thing is not like
is not
robin
i don't know i called and i know too many people robin is actually still at
this thing what is the source of the other things
i'll be wrong
robin's got
it's robin
yesterday i get robin okay robin was the other other favorite like songs
also my other fair songs on my like playing
buying a house of the rising sun
uh...
but your life on by santana
and then anything by the beatles are a smith
well he has good to see it
even salmon and that's good
that's good
kick those gonna interview fuzzy and i already but they just walked up an
interview that
dancer back here
my name is alex
they care about soccer put us
last stock up with us
but for the bilingual impaired at the pencil sharpener
well we've got
aren't from
No, I'm not. I'm from San Francisco.
Cool. Wow, you had a long trip coming out here. We're in Fremont, California today.
I know we are.
That's exactly right. Good job.
Where part of San Francisco are you from?
I don't live there. I was from there. I was born and conceived there.
Okay, where do you live now?
I live in Newark.
Okay, so he's right down the street practically here.
Yeah, I'm right down the street. That's cool.
This is like mild stomping grounds. Do you like it here?
Oh, yeah. This is very gravy, I believe is the terminology.
You like being able to walk home at night and not get stabbed and stuff?
Oh yes I do, yes I do.
Or not get held at gunpoint for my gay porn.
I mean, wait.
Axe is a busy, busy man.
So did you compete today or are you waiting to compete?
I'm waiting to compete. I'm going to be doing my cultural freestyle to La Seorita.
I couldn't believe I said that as well as I possibly could.
Now just so I don't have a bunch of people who are pissed off, shoot me later.
Are you part Mexican or Latino?
Yes I am, I'm half.
I celebrate single-to-mouth till noon, then I'm done.
Alright, so remember, this is Oxus Freestyle.
If you are mad at the cultural freestyle, if you see it on the internet, do not shoot
me.
I did not endorse this.
I think Dark Stalker wants the mic back because it's like a cock.
I don't know.
Oh, baby.
No.
It's, I believe, time for Freshness Freestyle.
Yay!
Time for Freshness Freestyle, where everybody can do knee drops and hand slaps.
Newbie Freshness.
Oh, yeah!
My big apologies to Chubbs and Maple because I told them we would interview them after
lounge and then we're gonna do your F use of the week how the knee drop
without bloodying your knee so send your F use over private message to want that
sky I'm in the chat room orange lounge s ki e dot CX click on chat what are you
talking about I know I know all the freestyle moves I can do the the knee
drop I'm I'm sorry you suck you know you know why you can't freeze out because
you're white.
No, no, no.
Okay, I can re-style.
It's all about the nut-chop.
Wait, wait, wait.
Am I white?
Wait, what am I wearing?
What am I wearing?
The FUBU.
Yes, the FUBU.
I'm not white.
Now, wait a minute.
A white girl tied for the winner yesterday at the competition.
No.
Yeah, we have our first place winner.
The first place team was half white.
Yep.
Oh, yeah.
All right.
Yeah, it was half white.
That's why.
Because first place, it was actually one of the best routines I've seen in a very, very
long time.
Well choreographed.
It was a good routine.
It was a good routine, yes.
But like 99% of the time, white guys don't freestyle at all.
Well...
Oh, I mean...
Give us some credit. Dave over here can do the grapevine.
What are you talking about, Dave?
White guys don't freestyle.
Look at Kyle Snyder!
Can we go to break now, please? We'll come back and we'll finish talking about freestyle.
So send me your refuse. If you don't want to come in the chat room and do it, you can send us an email.
Jamie, give us that address.
Um, words. No. It's orangeloungeradioatyahoo.com.
Alrighty, so we'll be right back.
Sorry? Oh, bitches. I thought you said and then.
And then?
And then? No, and then.
We'll be right back after some more happy fun MP3s from Xtreme.
I can't wait to see you in the next video!
I'll see you in the next video!
Give it to me good Give it to me good
Are you ready?
Yes, it's love we share
You are a super dancer!
Yes, we only stay together
Lashing hands, dancing and turning
Turn away
What a great feeling!
Awaken more than only letting you go
I, I have to let you go
I just want you to know
Can you hear the cheering?
The one, the one I love
Super performance
I, I have to let you go
May you remember me
Let me forget you
The one I love, is, I only have to let you go
I just want you to know
You'll always be the one I love
Please listen to Orange Lounge Radio, because real radio makes Captain Jack cry.
I want to see Captain Jack cry.
We're back.
Mommy, sing me a fast trip machine.
My phone's going off.
In that set we heard Love on a Trip Machine and Memories.
It's a polytary song!
What the hell happened?
It is a Polteri song, however, it's a good Polteri song where she can hold a key.
That's right, you'll all come around eventually.
I've been listening to Polteri since way back.
Yeah, but she's not holding up on her head between her ears, okay?
Like that friggin' bunny.
Is she balancing pancakes on her head?
She should be.
Okay, yeah.
So what's up next, Rob?
I wanted to talk about Freestyle, because we've got Xplizit.
Let's talk to Xplizit.
He's somebody who we haven't had on the show before.
the mic, how you doing? Alright, I'm doing alright. You missed Fremont yesterday, what
gives? I have some family stuff to take care of. Ah, family crap, I know how that goes.
So, what do you think about freestyle today in the DDR world? How's it going there? I'm
working on it very well. I'm trying to get better and better and better as well. As y'all
know, I used to be explicit alpha like last year and everything. I'm on the beta stage.
We gamma coming soon?
As the beta dies off.
I want it to die off after MGL.
And later on we can call you Explicit Pie.
Oh my gosh.
And speaking of freestyle, I got
routines already planned.
You like an extreme?
So far so good.
Very freestyle-able stuff in there?
Yeah, there's like a lot of good songs in there.
A lot of variations.
That song was like, We Will Rock You.
That was like one of the most off-picks.
The Ballbox!
Oh my gosh!
I'm wondering what that Ricky Martin song was, I was like, oh my gosh.
I'm waiting to see someone do a routine to Bag.
I'm waiting.
You know, I would even be half tempted to take the Cup of Life and bring out my Samba de Amigo maracas.
I'll do Bag, I'll wear the kilt, commando style.
Come on everybody, you know you want it.
Then I can get the, you know, cock-whipped-out thing, you know, done.
Dot, dot, dot.
Anyway.
Yeah, why is it that nobody whips their cock out at the end of a routine?
That's what I really want to know.
Why have these freestylers done that?
Just at the end, go, duh, duh, duh, duh, duh, yeah, there it is.
Why hasn't anyone done that explicit?
It happens.
Well, they've got planned routines, they do whatever they want.
I can say something very mean right now, but I'm not going to do it.
Say it!
No!
I can't, I'm going to get killed.
Fine.
Save it for next show.
Oh, okay.
What's the next big tour you plan on competing in, locally, here?
Well, probably the one in Sacramento that's coming out in March, because I've heard all
about it.
Right.
And B3, which is in April.
Ah, it's going to be big.
Actually, from what I understand, it might be postponed until May, but the details are
Actually, I'm pretty sure that the confirmed dates are going to be the second weekend in
May, which should be the 11th and 12th. But I'm pretty sure that's the confirmed date
now that the planned... In case people are wondering, planned events should be a Beat
Menias score competition, both freestyle and PA for DDR, and a Dance Maniacs tournament
too.
Wow, Dance Maniacs, interesting.
I might actually compete in a Dance Maniacs tournament.
Dance Maniacs, actually, I can kind of dance to.
It's kind of, it's a shock, but anyway, I'm sorry.
So you'll be doing the B3 tournament too as well, huh?
Indeed.
Shaking your ass don't count.
Whatever, whatever.
Any friends listening, you might want to say hello to, anything you want to say, you're
waiting for it.
Well, the shout-outs to the visionaries.
I'm sorry I couldn't make it to the Fremont tournament, but I heard about the Fremont
tournament and I struck winds.
Good shit.
But again, I wasn't able to.
It's the first tourney that I've actually, well, I did one, I judged one small tourney
at Sac State last year, but this is the first major tourney that I've gotten to judge.
It was interesting.
I like judging because they get a front row seat.
Indeed.
I got a front row seat too.
You were sitting on the ground in front of me.
Well, yeah, I had a front row seat that was closer than Rob except my ass got sore and
I...
Whoa!
Not that way!
My feet fell asleep and I was in a really bad spot when I had to go get up and take
a piss four times because I drank too much soda during the day.
I had a second row spot and what was awesome is when I couldn't see anything behind certain
people, I was sitting right next to the camera, so just watch the viewfinder, perfect shot
of the whole thing.
I had a backstage pass, all of the stuff Scott was hanging out outside, so we were just sort
of watching from the back of the machine going, whoa.
And there was of course the running commentary by a few people back there, you know that
person has a good technique, but you know, they're random.
What do you think about that?
We were kind of talking a little bit about this during breaks, kind of a con...oh yes,
Okay. All I gotta say is, Kakumei! Kakumei! Kakumei! Oh my gosh. Let the joke die, step
away from the joke. Hey, I just heard cock and I was like, oh, where? How large? One
thing I want to ask you, as a freestyler, because nobody else in this room can dance,
but as a freestyler, just kidding, all in good fun, as a freestyler, what do you think
about, this is kind of controversial, what do you think about the typical way to judge
attorney where you have the points, you grade everybody on a scale of 100 as opposed to
this new, semi-new tower system they've got going, what do you think about that?
Well, they're both good in certain ways, but sometimes some people get too offended with
the scores, like if they get lower than 70 they think they've done very bad, but if they
get like over 80 they think okay, and if they get 90 they do pretty good.
Which as far as I know, you know, the way, if I remember the way grades work, you have
You have to get 50 or below to get an F. If you get 70 and 80, that's the C. That's average.
Maybe I'm just a tough judge.
That's how I'd grade them.
Between 70 and 80 would be average.
But with the tower, somebody's got to be on the bottom.
Somebody's going to be on the bottom, right?
That kind of sucks, too.
Yeah, but the only thing about the tower system is it prevents people from getting biased
because some people might complain if they don't get into qualifying the actual brackets.
Well, I also got to think too that with the tower system there's usually in most cases there are people that deserve the bottom spot
Well, I mean there are a few cases where like there are tournaments where there's all good freestyles like CVGL 1
But there are some a lot of tournaments where some people just don't deserve anything higher than the bottom spot
Well as far as the tower system goes when I went to MGL the way the grid was kind of unique
But it kind of took a long time because there's like a lot of people participating
participating. When I saw the scores, the top 8 will only be in the list. So far 15
people placed, especially me when I was an NGO. Like Bruce LeRoy, he got perfect eights
on his section. Of course his routine was very good.
You know the way they did it, they changed a little bit for this one yesterday. They
did do complete towers. We had to do the whole damn thing, everybody. And the person who
I put at the bottom, the person I put at the very bottom, I wouldn't say that it was necessarily
bad. It was fun and it's the kind of thing where I think if I'd seen it Friday night
at the arcade it would have been cool, but at the tournament level it wasn't well prepared
and polished. I think things when they're in a tournament need to be polished and it's
all about show and presentation. This was just kind of looked more like, I'm just having
fun. It would have been cool for a Friday night at the arcade routine, but as a tournament
it didn't strike me as anything special.
As far as the tournament goes, if a routine looks like something that people could do
it on Friday night, it wouldn't be okay.
But if it looks like a routine that people have to put their heart on, like practice,
practice, practice.
Huh?
Did you say hard on?
No!
Heart!
Not hard on!
Who could look it down my pants?
Ow!
Well, you're doing well with this group.
Okay, I've got the jump to conclusions mat.
Well, my whole thing about the tower, I think that it still opens up the door for bias even
though you've got multiple people, which is why I don't know if anyone remembers the one
that I did at Shaft by having you judge on parts of the percentage.
And that way the final result is based on each individual piece rather
than just giving them a flat score.
I think that that sort of closes the door on bias too.
And it still actually allows room for bias because one of the sections was,
what is your opinion of this, of this match?
What is you as someone just watching it, what do you think?
Because that also has something to do with it because you've got to think that the crowd that's watching,
they're also thinking the same thing.
They're not necessarily watching, oh, how well their feet move or how polished are they.
They're saying, oh, I like this or I don't like this.
True. I think that to some point bias should play a part in it.
But because you have multiple judges, you have more room to work with.
If people don't get biased, then people will not improve on their routines.
I've seen people who say, oh, they've got low scores.
They actually look at their stats to see what they need to work on.
Hell, I even do that, like what mistakes I've made.
Like what mistakes I've made and everything.
Or what other people make mistakes.
At the end of the day, try to think of the negatives and not do it.
Look at the positives and work on that even more and make it a better routine.
That's what I try to do as well as the judges, write something negative and something positive
about everybody.
I put something negative about the people I put in first place or person, then I put
something positive about the person I put in last place.
Just because, you know, everybody wants to hear something good and bad.
Yeah, true.
But sometimes some people get very offended with it, so they want advice.
Like, try to do something original, you could say that, if the routine is not original.
Or try to be more smooth, you could say, or something like that.
It's like, guys, the ketchup dance is not that original.
Stick to P.A.
I advise them, try to make your moves smooth, try not to fumble on a few moves, try to make
your routine a little bit creative, lose enough, have some fun, don't take it too seriously.
I've seen people make mistakes, like trying to memorize the steps and everything, and
it ends up making them so nervous that they're getting everything.
That's always when I judge, the biggest thing that I look for is I look for their expression.
I don't care if they miss one of their moves.
I don't know what they had planned.
I haven't been sitting there looking at their choreographed piece of paperwork or at the
screen.
I'll look, I'll glance at the screen occasionally to see if maybe they're hitting the steps
okay because that shows preparation, but the first thing I look for is to see how they're
smoothing over their mistakes, how they are portraying themselves, and if they're playing
to the crowd.
If they're sitting there with this high energy routine and they're just there going ooh on
on their face, I'm not gonna enjoy it.
True, they must have like a smile on their face
to show that they're actually having fun.
Exactly.
Like that face.
As much as I hate to use her as an example,
one person who I think actually does display this,
what I'm talking about is actually Fiona, Dr. Hikaru.
When she freestyles, she smiles.
She plays to the crowd.
Maybe, you know, I'm talking about actually as a performer,
She actually does have good performance skills because you never, at least any time I've
ever seen her do anything, she never looks like she's concentrating too hard.
She looks like she's performing, putting forth the best show, putting forth the best face
for the audience.
And that's what freestyle should be, I think.
Yeah, yeah.
Almost like most of the people who are raking the tops, that's where they belong.
Think of people like Hypnotics, Bruce Leroy, or AJ.
Those are people I've never seen sit and frown while they're doing a high energy performance.
They're awesome.
It's just your expression.
I think that 50% of a performance is your expression.
The rest of it is the work.
True, true.
So you're saying if I smile the whole time and just play, then I'll get like 50?
No, I'm not saying that.
No no no no!
Yeah, you get 50 and the rest of it will suck.
Then I'll throw in a knee drop and you get a 95!
Well, 50 would be better than what I got last time!
Reserve the Knee Drops, Hand Plugs, Matrix Walks, and Bar Raping!
But you had everybody going, ooh, right when you started, you know.
Anyway, uhh.
Hey, what's the deal?
Hey, what's the deal? I mean, I know these songs are played out, but maybe somebody can do something original with it.
I mean, hey, they don't know you. They don't know how you would have just busted out some crazy shit or something.
Come on, comment, somebody! Please, help me! I'm drowning!
I don't know, I kind of want to see someone like Kid Zero do a routine to Dynamite Ray or something,
because he could actually make one look really, really good if he wanted to. I mean, he's crazy.
Well, the only problem with the steps, the only thing I don't like about the song is the steps, the actual basic steps. There's so many jumps.
Well, the thing about this is that even steps, you know, that could even though open up the door for trying to innovate on how to do a jump, you know.
There's different ways to do things, you know. I wanted to do, I wanted actually, I had one worked out a long time ago and all I had was second mix.
I had a routine worked out to W W involving pom poms, doing a cheerleading dance.
Cool.
I'm not sure if that's seen by SVGL or not.
And you know what, though? It would work because of the jumps.
Because I was a lot more flexible in those days.
And you know what, CaptainJackBasic? You can riverdance on that.
Yeah, I've heard about that.
Who knows? People could start freestyling to Max 300 and Max Unlimited.
It could happen.
I did that before.
How does that work?
Well...
Lotta poppin' lockin' and um...
Um...
A lot of vid to get.
So what do you actually...
Yes, exactly.
What do you notice is the current trends in freestyle? What type of styles are people aiming more toward?
Well...
Not including new-buy styles. Sorry if I'm offending anybody who does those hand-plants, knee-drops, etc. etc. etc.
Well, true.
It's all I can do, man!
Hahahaha!
But people like aiming some stuff they see from music videos or whatever, sometimes they're trying to make up their own.
Some people have their own signature moves. Almost everybody has their own signature moves.
I actually don't see a problem with an occasional hand plant or an occasional knee drop as long as it doesn't make their whole routine and actually maybe a transition to another move.
Yeah, like, if you want to do something like, if you see After the Game of Love by Tranpower
and Shaft, he did like a knee-drop, but he did like a very special version of it, like a slap-drop.
Like a, what would I say, romantic or exotic somewhat.
He laid a smackdown onto the pad.
He showed some love to that down arrow.
Oh no, impregnation right there.
Let it down.
Or people do hand slaps on the ground just to play around.
Yeah, as long as you're just not like, oh, I'm standing.
Oh, my knee's on the right arrow.
Oh, I'm standing again.
That, you know, no.
But I think that I don't think that people should just
automatically discount a type of move because it's old
or lots of people have done it.
You just have to innovate on it.
Yeah, true.
You don't want to repeat the same hand, plant, knee drop
move over and over and over unless you're
something like 18. Yeah. DZP, no preliciting to this. He is, he says hi. DZP, I remember
I was supposed to promise you that I was going to bring some balls, like 20 packs, but. We
saw plenty of balls yesterday. Including bouncing ones that were multicolored. But again I hope
to come to the one in Sacramento for P3. I'm going to see you there.
I'm just wondering, because I was out of the room for a little bit, did we do FUs already?
No, we need to do our FUs of the Week. Want to do a break and then do them, or want to
do them now? Let's do them now, and then we'll take a break.
Alright, we'll do them now. Here we go. Starting off, boys and girls.
Bad Bulls out the list. Oh my God. Alright, we got a big, big FUs
of the Week segment, so here it goes, ladies and gentlemen. We have a lot of new listeners
to the show tonight, Jamie, I know I have you do this a lot, but I think it's important.
Let's remind the listeners what the FUs of the Week are all about.
Our FUs of the Week is where we take everything that we think sucks and go, fuck you!
Fuck you right in your ass!
And do they have to be about DDR or any of that stuff?
No.
They can be whatever the hell you want.
Exactly.
This is when you give them a fuck, you shove so far up their ass, they're tasting the chalk.
That being said, Jamie.
I want to terror mix today.
My F.U. goes out to Jamie for being a picky bitch.
I wanted to start off with the best line from video game music ever.
This is fucked up? Hold on, let me see if I can find it.
There it is. Slag work terror.
Here we go.
My Fuck You of the Week, first and foremost, goes toward MapQuest. Except I was asleep for most of the trip, but I had to pee. MapQuest got us lost, but I'll let Rob be the one that's gonna go that way.
My other fuck you goes to the bump in the parking lot at Funtime Pizza, because I had to pee then too.
And the bump was big, and it made me have to pee more.
My other fuck you goes towards...
There's one I've been debating about mentioning, because I really just think it's more hilarious than anything.
To the little fucker who's been spamming my LiveJournal, I know who you are, and I think it's damn funny that you're still bringing this up.
My god, people just can't let stuff drop.
Anyway, that was pretty...
It was pretty hilarious, I had a laugh.
Shine lose.
Um, my other fuck you goes toward my cold, um, which actually had me comatose on Wednesday thanks to my quill, capital N, small i, big fucking Q.
Green death, orange death.
Green death.
You know, my teeth are green. Merry Christmas.
But it's settled in my lungs, and I've had nasty ass cough.
And I was going to do PA yesterday, but because of my cough, I haven't really been able to play much DDR.
It's been hard to walk up the stairs without my asthma acting up.
Because of my breathing.
Oh my god, you've got a dog between your legs!
You are not supposed to have a dog there, you are supposed to have a pussy there.
Angels giving you Propel to make it better.
Thank you. Oh, I like Peach Propel though.
Oh yeah, fuck you to the Walgreens in town for not having Peach Propel yet.
oh yeah I buried my old shoes finally the shoes that I fucked off last week
and I have new shoes and my shoes are black and gray and yellow my shoes are
fresh and fuck my shoelaces that I couldn't find because they're purple and
I found my rainbowy ones, they were too bright.
Um, and um, um, yeah.
Oh, and um, um, fuck not being able to think of anything else.
Oh yes, more fucks!
Fuck the situation that I heard about today.
My fianc, Suzanne, who I love lately, ran into somebody's door.
It wasn't his fault, it wasn't their person's fault.
He was just turning into a parking space, um, in a private property and everything,
and showing you the parking place, and this person with their brand new car that only had 96 miles on it,
a Chrysler, ran into their open door.
So the door's fucked up, our front bumper is fucked up.
This is fucked up.
And this is indeed fucked up.
And so now it's going to be on our insurance and their insurance, but I don't think anyone's going to really have a fault for that car thing.
But I think we're going to be getting a new car, which is cool.
I want a car.
And fuck every single 86 Corolla hatchback in town for not being mine.
And that's it.
Actually, I'm going to go next, because Loki's list is too big.
So...
Fuck Loki's list!
My list isn't that big.
My FU of the week, we'll do FU, we'll go around the room to everybody, yeah.
Okay, yeah, we go first because it's our show.
Possessive us? No.
The first FU I'd like to give us to MapQuest, you suck. Die.
Funtime Happy Pizza Place, or whatever the fuck it was called, is not off of mission.
It's completely on the other side of the galaxy.
Why the hell were you telling me it was there?
Die, die along with your firstborn and your ex-wife.
I hate you.
My next F.U. goes out to MTV and music videos in general.
They were so much cooler in the 80's.
VH1 classic forever.
I thought yes, that one animated head.
With the drugs flying out of the neck.
Uh, Thomas Tobey?
Uh, yeah, Thomas Tobey.
F.U. to Nikkari for wearing my shirt yesterday?
I'm just kidding.
Nikkari's my hero, what can I say?
Every day I polish my revolver, and I shoot myself in the head, like a rockstar.
Um, let's see, what other F.U.s do I have?
F you to Brad, he's a dick, and uh, alright, that's all I have to say for now, I guess.
Brad's a dick, like a rockstar.
And F being single, it still sucks.
Alright, locate!
Well, I have a list only because every, um, I found a new use for my camera yesterday since it does record audio.
I was doing FUs recorded into my camera as I was, you know, recording them.
So I just typed them up to make it easier.
Okay, let's start at the top of the list here.
FU Raley's that's, uh, freakin' near, um, in Fremont, FU to them,
because they don't have a Chinese food section.
I really wanted Chinese food.
They did not have Chinese food to go there, and that pissed me off.
And on top of that?
You know why that is, Loki?
Because right around that Raley's, there's like 50 bazillion Chinese restaurants.
that doesn't matter that doesn't matter at all to me but they did have cracker
nuts okay i wanted i wanted freaking chinese from there and they didn't have
maxim no maxim magazine or psm so they suck ass and they can burn in hell um on
the map quest you already mentioned that um f you to the convenience stores right
there buy funtime pizza listen you dumb bitch
are actually stupid bastard i don't want your fucking two dollar bill in 50 cent
piece no change machines take two dollar
bills in 50 cent piece doesn't work in there either you can take that $2 bill
and 50 cent piece and shove it up your ass I want to learn to speak fucking
English retard okay and let's see here now for the restaurant we went to
Jurassic ice cream and restaurant first of all why you call it drastic ice cream
a restaurant there's no fucking dinosaurs it's not dinosaur theme it
makes absolutely no sense whatsoever you have Asian people running a freaking
restaurant that serves like hamburgers and ice cream makes no sense
Jurassic where the fuck did you pull that out of oh I thought the pork that
freaking movie is good the dinosaurs and now we were in a super restaurant listen
I don't like ice in my fucking drink and when you give me more ice and there's
actual soda I'm gonna take that ice and freakin first I'm gonna murder you I
will put you that part of it
no no no
however you in this night
and yet okay so
if you then for uh... putting too much ice in my dream
it's correct that i like for safe but still
too much time
uh... let's see here
today
as a computer
some bitch okay with her ass the size of a Buick. Fucking decides, I don't need to say where I want to sit now!
So she stands in front of me with her ass like in my lap. Listen you dumb bitch, I don't want a
lap dance from you nasty from from this nasty bitch let alone you know while seeing this movie
okay and then you have to sit next to me munching on your fucking Doritos okay listen
you can go to hell your ass is too big for the theater sorry don't come back you hear and um
Let's see, let's see, let's see.
Um, F.U. to the minivan with license plate 4YKZ148.
Haha!
Um, you're a dumbass and you can't drive.
Um, listen, if you're gonna cut in front of us, stop trying to put on your brakes and shit, and guess what?
Uh, minivans suck, uh, so you can burn in hell.
Uh, and finally, finally, oh, oh, uh, one more.
um another one is for derby club owners taking different to taking different tokens these tokens
are so tiny i mean there's why are why don't you just use a standard token size i mean instead of
having these machines that dispense you smaller tiny ass tokens for this machine it's expensive
enough and i don't want to have to spend twenty dollars on some tokens and then find out oh look
they don't fit in the damn machine there's financial reasons for that they say mgl has
some deal with Sega for like the first 90 days or something they have a machine they have to use
seven tokens so they can get an exact count of how much money they're making off of this plan.
You mean they could just like oh no go into the freaking operator settings and see the freaking
stats for that? Like any other machine on the face of the fucking planet? Well actually well
there's a problem with that because if with all the double token deals they can't get they can't
make it exactly
why why why why why
it doesn't really fucking matter okay
you don't understand how arcades work
you never worked it before
this is why sega has no systems anymore
finally
may i finish
okay
finally
and this is the biggest one of them all
but people fucking cutting me off in the coiling
i don't give a fuck if you're running the tournament
announcing the freaking results for freestyle
And that's all.
God damn, your face got hella red.
That deserves applause there. There are veins popping out of his head in places you never knew there were veins.
Any children listening to this, please do not tell your mother and not be intimidated like this.
I'm just kidding about that vert, too. That's funny.
By the way, you're being worshipped in the shower room right now.
you're being worshiped in the shower right now
the Loki show ladies and gentlemen the views and opinions expressed on Orange
Lounge radio are all Loki's
they're all him yes send him all the emails
alright moving on to the rest of the room let's go around and talk to our
guests starting off with
wackwab it's me okay first of all
a big fucking hell to my bike because the tire went flat
again, during class, so I ended up having to walk my bike around everywhere. I thought
my F2 song was the cat song. I changed my mind. Well, fuck you then! Okay, um, yeah,
fuck all my new, er, fuck my new math teacher from calculus because he does not speak English
at all. You wanna fuck your teacher? No, I don't! He's hot for teacher! It's some, it's
some old scrawny Russian dude that has such a horrible accent, it sounds like he's speaking
Spanish instead of English. It's bad. I'm looking at, I'm trying to listen to what he's
saying in the lecture and I'm like, what? What, did you say derivative or something
else? I don't know what you're saying. I just want to stand up and yell at his face. He's
like
everybody in this room needs anger management courses right now
i can manage my anger just fine by kicking someone's ass
that's what orange lounge is, it's our venting thing, you know, we don't wear anger out here
No, it's not. I'm still going. I'm still going. I'm still going. I'm still going. I'm still...
Yeah, it was just meditation.
I have to also add to the fuck you on MapQuest, because next to them I had to sit in the backseat of Rob's car with having to piss.
I sat there for probably about 45 minutes holding it while we were trying to find this damn pizza place driving around the wrong side of Fremont.
We're going around Mission Boulevard up 680 up up 880 in a frick big frickin circle
Well, it'll be one for a minute. It's a big car. I can roll over
I'll just blame it on that guy. Of course the other guy in backseat was mad. Yeah
And let's see what else
Fucked my car for having a bad timing belt in it because now I can't bring it up with me to Davis this quarter until it gets fixed and it's going to cost extra dollars to fix.
And why are you messing with my dog? Don't abuse my dog!
Well, you were trying to turn its tail into a cock, so it's...
Well, let's see, I had one more. I think I had one more. I'm trying to remember what it is.
Fuck my hard drive for being too small because I couldn't burn CDs because it didn't have enough room to copy the information.
What's wrong, HardDriveEnvy?
I only have a 20 gig hard drive. I feel so weak.
I feel so weak and primitive.
It's not size that matters, man.
Wait, actually, this is hard drive talk, I forgot.
Yes, size does matter.
I still feel smart.
Done? Are you done? Good.
Okay, the following...
The following one, what to say, will be very affinity buildable until then under 17.
Dave get out
But it's under 17, it's very offensive, but if you but if you want to listen anyways go ahead
Don't blame me for everything. I'm gonna say
Fuck shit cock piss cunt whore. Oh that's
Okay, the first fuck you have to do it
it's not this game is one direction one time I got lost for 30 minutes it only
took me like 15 minutes to get there regularly that's my first house
what gang fuck being cursed I'm always never gonna just do whatever I could do
Let me see. Oh yeah, here's the one big F you right here. A big F you right here.
December 13th. Okay, Friday the 13th. The day of MGL.
This is the reason why explicit was destroyed.
The alpha part. And why I switched to beta.
Let me see. The first part that happened in the morning. I lost my damn disc that had almost all my final stuff I needed to turn in.
Which cost me like 20% of my grades.
great yes I had an A to a C or C B to a D which killed me so badly well I
include computer science 15 yes computer programming and that the teacher said
plagiarism for that he can kiss my ass I said my 12 minutes cock thank you for
that visual
that was you like throwing your cock across the room
catch jamie, catch
what do you mean to the word detachable penis
okay that's it, let me see, back to the day of
MGL, Friday the 13th
I tried driving there, almost got into an accident, not my fault
My car almost burned out because the car fan broke on my car.
It could have been stuck in the road out of nowhere.
And B.A. Hella sucks on M.G.O.
Because what the hell does a Qualifier song have to be so fucking hard compared to M.G.O. 2 Evil?
Work in my heart, reverse, dark, hidden.
Why does the rest of it have to be...
My idea.
You know, yesterday for Perfect Attack, the Qualifier song was Sugaru, Boost, Rever- No, it wasn't Rever- Boost, uh, Flat. Boost, Flat, Mirror.
Oh my god, I seeded 13th out of 16 people and I somehow came in 4th in the end. Don't ask me how that happened, anyway.
Well, Sugaru, that was the easy- That was easy shit. But then my book- How could you do it hidden, dark, reverse? That's like fucked up.
What the song says.
This is fucked up.
Let me see.
As far as the PA part, that made me less interested in PA.
Thanks for helping, bitch.
I'm in jail.
Since it wasn't put in replay, I screwed up.
Yes, and I had to do an improv, a straight up improv.
Playing around, I actually knew the steps.
But it ended up being too obvious that everybody knew it was just an improv.
Well, he's a nice place to live, but still, I wanted to do it for my real routine, which I work pretty hard on.
And I wasted hell on money. That means, like, how much money did I waste?
Fuck, I wasted 60 bucks total, because not many people pay me back for the balls.
Not everybody. Half the people pay me back for the balls.
They say, can I have a free try? Fuck, I have to waste money.
I almost didn't have enough money to pay for the gas money to come back to Sacramento.
In other words, I have to borrow money and end up being, I have to pay them back like 5 bucks more, because you get 5 bucks if you can borrow 10 bucks from me.
Just remember you gotta tell people you give favors like you give head.
Okay, that's too much to say right there.
It's, yeah, not at all. It's from Go.
I won't, yeah.
Yeah, but just to let you know, that day just killed my reputation.
But now I'm a new person, so, hahaha, you can't kill me now!
And I have some problems, fuck the incompatibility between StepMania and like, for some reason my Windows XP does not work with StepMania for some reason.
okay we'll keep up and put the server that kind of crashed on second money
forms that is a very fuck fuck fuck that server
okay because I wanted to the big etiquette port concept yeah that one
dollar hosting dot com with the commercial with the bouncing babes
bikinis wearing the pirate shirts that saying you know our
go host with one dollar hosting dot com I never knew that commercial existed we
had already signed up for fuck you
for restoring us back to September without our permission.
Yeah, I missed the make Eddie get porn contest. I couldn't sign in.
I missed all the things I was going to get.
Since I'm like nineteen and a half, I would have been able to get the stuff.
I still got plenty left, man.
Don't worry about it. There ended up not being a contest because
two people entered.
I was born.
And so I'm giving just porn out to everyone who entered. So I'll give you that.
yep i want their refuse
okay i miss you
at the chair
if i get screwed by anybody or anybody in the future
that's all you know
there was a night
nice and loud
by nice and proud
what
okay my car all dates are with
as special music today
yeah it better be
what what
what is it
it's my little pony
all that my favorite why do you have my little please
here
okay now is our visit to the dot one day
couple of whatever that that's not a big issue if you find
i have
okay
that one
yet in the guacamole
okay anyway
while doing that out
guacamole del taco anyway all that i'll just start my a few because they don't
have that many anyway
so anyway i'll get back to his area i said you sound like a k o g remix of
their black eyes
okay
my first at you goes to my teachers at school for giving me so much the fucking
study
high school is hard
freshman year was easy
sophomore year everyone is a bitch
and it's hard at the study
thank you rob
My second F.U. goes towards my computer for being the biggest fucking piece of shit ever.
And my mom won't buy me a fucking new one, because it's such a piece of shit, and she's like,
oh, we just need to get it completely re-cleaned and everything.
Oh, wham.
No, I can't load any programs. I can't load a Word document.
I can't, like, I can go online or go on IM. You gotta load Microsoft.
Yeah, I can do one thing at a time. Okay, are you done?
No, I'm not. I have one more. Okay, hurry up.
fuck you to girls for not liking me
i don't ask for much
many girls like you
safety to tolerate you
uh...
the
there's one thing to get the girls
freestyle
i thought i got so funny
uh... here's a lady get girls
free money
uh...
that's like
i don't have the official girl here
please
well and record many of the current i don't think
good old sex you know get them but it keeps them
okay
now let me finish i'm very you can't buy a good oral sex
let me finish now you know i should actually right now
well
It's not like I'm asking for much. I want two things.
One, that they like me. Two, that they're under 2,000 pounds.
That's all I ask.
Dave, when you're 18, we'll buy you a whore.
Weeee!
I'll take you to the strip club, Dave.
Dara, 1-800. We are 18.
We'll make you a man, Dave. We'll take you to the strip club.
Yeah.
Take some Viagra. We need it.
Smoke good.
There's a ball.
Does Brad have- are you done with your episode?
Yes, I am done.
rapidly because you have a quick one
weeks and you said it was it's way too fucking long if you guys do is again i'm
going to run over all your guys ass
uh... i know what you guys take way too long
i'm done
line with the shorty
I have the power! No, wait, that was He-Man. I don't know.
Alright, let's get to the chatroom menus.
You're going to have to cut these ones down, Rob, I think.
I'm going to read these fast. I'm doing speed reader, okay? Here we go.
First, Cory the Sultan says,
F you, fuck you Fremont, fuck you RedShirkai.
You won't get a DDREX press release original soundtrack.
Fuck you DDRXtreme for not giving me a AAA on Dom Dariam.
Fuck you DDRXtreme for hurting my leg.
Fuck you, Fremont, for having shitty pads.
Fuck you, Tigger, for getting two grades on Waka Laka.
Fuck you, Tigger, for getting seven grades on Fantasy Max 1 version.
I was supposed to play Max 300 when I did his FUs, and I didn't, so fuck me.
DCV says fuck you to Mr. Cool at Fremont Tournament for bitching and moaning the whole time.
Fuck you to MGL for the extreme line as long as...
FU to MGL for the Xtreme Line as long as China's population.
OrangeBeaniePatty says, Fuck you to myself for deciding not to go to Fremont.
Muhimer says, I need to read his emails.
BRBcodingStyle says, Fuck you to people who pick on heavier people for trying to DDR.
to Cleveland, Aladdin's castle for moving all the fans to the Max 2 machine and leaving
the 5th and the 6th players hanging.
USFBB says fuck you to all those people who wouldn't help me earlier in my quest for knowledge
about the menstrual cycle.
I will know everything about the vagina by next week, um, rave sluts, sorry that was
last week.
Chaos, a big fat fuck you to Milpitas Golf Lands pads because I got 14 greats on We Will
Rock You Heavy but two misses because the stupid pads stickied and I couldn't play the
Legend of Max oh my god sorry about that guys I got the patch sorry I jizzed all
over it dark Tetsuya says fuck you did no hold on dark Tetsuya says fuck you to
Dell the new computer I was supposed to get for my birthday didn't come I make
it come evil Naoki to DX how much would you pay me if I cosplayed as a school
girl and did a routine to love love sugar 39 cents
DDR Angel, my fuck you this week, is at my journal, livejournal.com slash tilde k-a-y-l-e-a.
Go to last night's entry and read at random. The whole story is there. Only reason I said
check my current journal post for the FU is because I don't know how to word it right.
I thought our journals protected everybody anyway, so how are we going to read it? Well,
I have access, but anyway. Brad, shut the fuck up. 23rd Magus says, let Explicit know
Not explicit, no, I'm working on my Maxell limited routine.
I have an F.U. to scroll once again.
Fuck it, fuck it, fuck it in its fucking ear.
I also have an F.U. to stoic.
Before Jamie kills me, I'm talking about the steps by Chacrilla, not the song.
The song is leet, the steps are masochistic to play.
Fuck 56k, I need to fucking download some MP3s for my DJ bit, and I get one song every
half hour.
What the fuck?
Okay, out.
I thought Jamie didn't like stoic.
Okay.
Wait, so the play-through magazine actually related to talking to me?
Jamie doesn't like stoics.
Oh, yes, that's what I thought, Magus.
Good luck.
It's not as easy as you think, though, unless if you're doing beginner mode.
Yeah, there's a beginner mode, actually.
But, anyway, just good luck.
I want to see the routine sometime.
I want to see the Legend of Max on maniac routine.
Good luck.
You'll need it.
Oh, God.
SoCalKick says,
Fuck Saturday school for being four hours and very, very, very fucking retarded and run by the most ignorant teachers.
Fuck you to whoever was in the car that drove by me and Owen last night after watching Catch Me If You Can yelling,
eat shit and die, faggot, at me.
Why were you at Saturday school, huh?
What's up?
Bad boy.
Bad.
Bad, bad, bad, bad, bad.
Hey, get on with it, guys.
Bombay, fuck you to Roseville Golf Land for getting extreme before Scandia and sucking.
Bombay, fuck you and sucking. Good power.
Hey.
Hey, you apologize right now, sir.
No, he knows I won't.
Oh, okay.
But not like that.
VidPalace says, fuck you to restaurant customers who have 30 people in their party and only tip $1.
Oh, ho, ho, that's rude.
Because they supposedly only have enough money to pay the bill, but not enough to tip.
That's why you're supposed to add the money on the bill.
Actually, I thought that large parties over 15 and gratuity is supposed to be added.
Yeah, I always thought that if you bring in a party to a restaurant with more than 8 people, gratuity is automatically added.
That's what always happens to me.
Yeah, what the fuck.
Must be a Vegas thing.
Fuck you to the WB for not re-showing Everward on their Easyview today, because that show is awesome.
Actually, I saw the Easyview today. It was a small bill, I saw.
Fuck you to not getting any free stuff at CES, fuck you to semester exams for being worth 20% of your semester grade, and yes, let's like to rave.
Chubbs! Fuck you to being sick because it made my PA suck. Fuck you to Mr. Cool for being a douche.
And last but not least, bug you to Orange Lounge for not interviewing me at Fremont.
All I have to say to you is, cry a little more. I'm just kidding.
Strasa says, private message to me. Angel says, fuck you to my co-worker for bitching over me getting her one dollar bill.
getting her one dollar bill. It's just a dollar, bitch. Fuck you, fuck you in your ear, Jamie.
You for that quote. Oh, thank you, Jamie, for that quote. Moving on. Vidpowah says they
don't add to the tip because they're nice. Jamie, that's lovely. Now I've got to go to
the email bag just for Muhimer's F.U. because he's the only one that sends me F.U.s over
email. Muhimer says fuck me for always sending my fuck yous by email. Yes, you're in the
chat room why do you use email oh well it's okay it's all good gives us an excuse to go
check the mail but fuck exams for being so early cramming sucks fuck yesterday's swim
meet for being so horribly unorganized i was forced to sit in the hallway just to gather
my thoughts while being stomped on by people and then being told that i can't eat food
in the hallway go die aquatics director anywho fuck my best friend sister's boyfriend for
making her distressed over something that was fake as an add-on to my emails fuck pink
and purple candy hearts for valentine's day because they're overpowering my bags yummy-ness
and they suck.
Alright, with that ladies and gentlemen, we're done with the FUs of the week.
Oh my god, that went for an hour.
That was cool.
This has been Anxed Hour on the Anxed Out Radio.
And I'm spent.
Back to sanity.
Wow.
Anxed?
Same?
Are we even going to do like a listless or anything like that?
I don't know if we're going to have time because we got to do the cage match.
We're going to come back and we're going to do the cage match.
After the cage match, if we have time for a listless, we'll do one.
If not, we dig that bit in the ground anyway, right?
Do we have any ideas for a listless?
We'll think about them over commercial.
You shut up, look.
In the meantime, more extreme shit.
Enjoy.
Play me after it's closed
Over and over and over you
I'd never get over you
Over you, over you, over you
Never over you
For the sun will shine
If you stay mine
There could never be a cloudy day
Shining, shining, shining through
All the love that I feel for you
I wish you would stay mine
Until the end
Oh, my love is flowing deeper, oh, my love is flowing deeper
Father, son, for time, a new day will come
Our love will keep on flowing, flowing and flowing, flowing through
The love I'll always feel for you
You will stay mine until the end of time
Until the end of time
Only for you until the end
I want to take you home
Freakin' heartache
From the two of me
I know you feel me
I know
Maybe, maybe, maybe you hide
Maybe, maybe, maybe
What's that party? What's that party? Go on get down.
Oh, go with me, oh, go with me
And I know
The music makes you hot
The music and the power
We are what we're supposed to be
Illusions on your fantasy
All of the lies you seek or fake
What you do is what you wish to do
We are the God of Symphony
We do the things you want to see
Bring my friends to the extreme
Our friends are so unreasonable
Say to the unpredictable
I doubt a lie if you speak and say
What we do is what you wish to do
That's all I know, best for our friends
Showing off the little things
Bring my friends to the extreme
One by one, we make it in fun
We are the central heroes of the world
We are the ones who've got our hands on our back
To stay by your back, raise your mind
Hi, this is Mel B of RTF, and for an extra $1.99 a minute my girl from Mel B can join
and join us on all the fun together.
Hey, if you're a broke-ass like I am, why don't you come to the one place that costs absolutely nothing to go to
and still the fun is just as great. It's Orange Lounge Radio, Sunday nights.
Kick it with me and you just might realize the best things in life aren't free.
Yes, Irene has an important announcement.
We're coming back from break.
I paid off my debt.
I hate you!
I hate you.
And so I'm going to get a two-story house before you...
A cunt. A real fucking cunt, you know that? Why are you letting her be better than me
at Animal Crossing? This sucks. Ow, ow, ow, ow, my tummy. I was just thinking of something.
I paid off my house all the way. So did Dan. We have statues of ourselves.
Well, you know what you and Dan are? Cool. Yeah, you're kind of cool. I was just thinking,
I had a revelation. You know why Mel said that he was a broke-ass?
Oh, in that commercial, yes.
Because of DOC.
Yeah, because of Derby Owners Club.
And I'm addicted to it now.
No, I actually...
I've played one game, I have a horse, I want to play more!
Labrador Lover.
I can make a better name than that for anyone.
The reason why Mel B. I had to play that promo is because they might be back at the end of
the month, I know at least one of them is hopefully going to be coming up, Sharks Girl,
the other half, might be bringing Mel B with her, might not, but either way we like Mel,
so hopefully he'll be back at the show at some point.
Also in the future, I've been promised a visit from Chubbs and Maple at some point, so I'm
going to make them do that, and don't know what other guests we'll have on the show in
the future.
Let's get No Styling on Cory at the same time.
No Stylin' on Cory Action?
Oh!
Alright.
We need to get, we seriously need to get, um, Darkstone back up here.
Yes.
Oh!
That reminds me!
Thank you!
Next week, I have a three-day weekend, which means I don't have to work on Monday, which
means I can have a hangover if I want.
Which means...
Which means that since Shami never gets hangovers, she can drink all she wants to anyway.
Next week, on Orange Lounge Radio...
and that's driving me home the drunk show boys and girls sky and dark
sakura get drunk live on air for your listening pleasure
oh boy rob do you realize that it's going to be quite
expensive to get me drunk it's all right we'll make it work somehow
it's all about winners cup vodka man that stuff's like so cheap
i've downed a bottle of wine in three minutes but wine's not hard you need that some gold
I don't know, wine doesn't do anything to me.
But you can make really good butterscotch milkshakes with Goldschlager.
Really?
Oh yeah.
It's cinnamon-y.
You use butterscotch.
That sounds good.
Alright, so next week on Orange Lounge Radio, the Drunk Show.
Catching up on some comments in the chat room, Vidpawa says, I should delete Irene's house
crossing haha
uh... okay with the lead every tell someone i have to move it you read
everything i think it was like i did with your house rob
no that i have to make an estimate uh...
uh... we've been getting sorts of my updates uh...
in our chat room uh... mozzarella that my friend michelle
is working on our radio drama
that we're gonna play on the show i'm sure gonna trouble called uh...
adaptation of i feel sick
which was the spin-off of uh... johnny the homicidal maniac
and uh... she's been working very hard on it and i've heard part of it and it
sounds really fabulous
and i'm in it so you will listen to me
and uh...
the yeah anyway
so we're gonna have that on the plea
simply sooner than later
you know michelle take your time work on it makes a cool
which are you doing
uh... okay he we've got we made an offer you i'm sorry finished with
i guess so i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry
bite my big toe
robin by shoe that was called rose go brush your teeth
there over the head of the brick
no problem i was puffy
uh...
chub says he will come up if we get him drunk next week
let's see uh...
you have this personal sexual experience
uh...
stress uh... called irene by the way the chick with the biggest dick on the
air
at school
uh...
i'm gonna wash your face with these if you don't have a fuck-up
all of the way for european is good the first time know what the two are
let's talk to look
out uh... the sim update and then we have to get right
these you are
that says revolution
uh...
i wanted to uh...
low-key sim update please
all right
Well, actually, I should say the end of last week was a big week.
It was the Trinity Mix 3 results.
And, well, you know, I hate you all for not playing my freaking file.
You can burn in hell.
Well, I'll say that for another day.
So, anyways, we've got the results, the official and the public results for the voting.
First place, there was a tie between spin and simple and clean.
1. Invoke 2. Boom Boom Dollar
First place for Heavy was Invoke.
Second place was Stoic, done by Moogle Hunter.
It's really crazy.
Yay, Moogle, yay!
Third place was Su-4, which is a remix of Volume 4 and Sagaru.
It's kind of like Volume 4 with the Sagaru twanging in it.
It was interesting.
Standard, first place was Eat Em Up.
It was a Pac-Man song from Ridge Racer Type 4, which you might be hearing later.
Second place is Blue Fever, which is a speed mix of Blue by Eiffel65, and third place was
Arian also.
Oh my god, it's the Hidden Sevens Style song.
You still have it unlocked.
Guess what?
Anyways, so, what do I have to say about this?
Well, you know what?
I'm checking to see what place Loki got.
I got like 18th or something.
You got, uh, let's see, 40, yeah, where are they?
Uh, keep going down.
Wait, wait, wait, there it is.
Oh, I got 50.
50 out of 68.
You were 50th out of 68 people.
That's because...
What the hell?
Okay.
All right, let's see.
You got beat by the theme of Strider Hyrule.
Hyrule.
First of all, Strider Hyrule is cool.
Do you know what that, Strider, the best Capcom game ever are?
Anyways, um, I basically, I have a song that basically sums up my feelings along with someone else's feelings about Tourney Mix 3, so um,
Uh, if Rob, if you will do me the pleasure of, uh, playing an MP3 for me, Earth to Rob.
I'm sorry, Jamie's yelling at me, because I made her cry.
Well, sorry, um, could you play an MP3 for me?
I suppose, what?
I had an idea of that, like, way along with whatever song you wrote.
and
gave fire
plays one
this is my thoughts of turning mix
uh...
So teach your name and sparkle to the deck, so give it one more try
The cocksuckers will remember me from Ptolemy's school
The guy who made that duke of your ideals, I will never do
Just because you're an enemy is all the generic trans shit
You show a rocker's book, that was a crazy fucking gift
Well now I'm back to rock your world, my honest fucking life
Why you pussies don't realize you needed to survive
Trapped inside a tool and saved the secrets of the world
A wonderful place to science, music are the magic meld
All you motherfuckers want a job so rip the bar
Bro fuck you or fuck your mum, go back to Ulala
But if you got an ounce of sense then stay and fucking lose it
Life doesn't happen all at once so why'd you fucking use it?
Mr. Carlos' arrows fill the screen, you're probably all just thinking
On the way to this my lead is working, set my spirits sinking
Well come on these fuckers here's bad news, I don't give a shit
So take this fucking freeze arrow and ram it up your clip
All these shames would want to do is show you the meaning of life
Maybe you'll just throw it back at me, you had a sharp knife
Well, I'm not wasting any time on shit like you and I'll fucking tell you why
I don't want you to find happiness in your life, I want you to rather die
Fucking stitch my heart, go word, it's on the yokey stick
It's taught a mix, you go to hell, that service is a brick
So all you arses can go back to your faggot little dunce
DJ Damien signing out, you motherfucking nuts
That made Captain Jack fart
And for those who didn't know, that was DJ Damien with Art 2. He did a really shitty entry the first Turning Mix 2, and he did a really shitty entry for Turning Mix 3, but you know what? That song is funny.
Basically, the fault I have to say in this, and a lot of people have problems, is there are so many files entered. Obviously, I'm not surprised that I didn't get picked as far as voting goes, because people have to play like freaking a hundred files.
files and that's just unreasonable. I mean, to even expect people to play all the files.
So, it's kind of unfair there because everyone that wasn't known didn't get their files played.
So, you know, that kind of sucks but whatever, you know, I could do it better so I probably
will. As far as sim stuff goes, my new site is actually sort of online right now. I'm
uploading pages and content later on this week. I've sent out emails, a mass email to
a bunch of different people at Simfile Creators out there. And so far I've only gotten one
response back. So I'm sending out another email to you guys and it's going to basically
be if you don't send me back an email, I'm getting an okay to put your files on my site.
So if you don't want that happening, you better send me a fucking email. So my site's coming
up. The URL for it is going to be www.willddrforfood.net slash leachfromloki. And there's already a
main page up there right now but of course none of the links work because I haven't uploaded
anything else yet. So, you can check that out right now and there should be more stuff
coming up later this week. I'm shooting for the early part of this week, but I don't know.
We'll see. And I'll be offering, there'll be places, an actual script where you can
upload your own files and even at your own page with your own files on it if you want
or else I'll make you a page. Basically, we're just going to have the largest collection
of stuff on there. So, basically, you know, you'll see that there's going to be...
Do you have crap like that one in your collection too?
Why not? Some people want to play that. So, maybe we'll put that in a section of files
that suck or something like that. I don't know. It really doesn't matter to me. So,
other than that, let's see. I think I'm going to have, there's going to be some interviews
with Simfile Creators and we're going to do like some themes or releases and that kind
thing so it'll be fun to watch and you'll see there's already a group of
people baumannysims.com that's sort of doing the same similar thing that I think
they've beat me to it because you know they put their site up first but site
looks like shit and they don't really have that much right now but we're gonna
be strong battle lines yeah we're gonna see way do you see like a thousand files
come online just all of a sudden so you know take that and whatever and uh take
up your clit. Alright, we need to get to the cage match because we got to get that done
definitely. That's one segment we have to do each week. Last week in the Orange Launch
cage match we had Yumi Hamasaki won for the second week in a row with Connected and I'll
play a clip of that in the second. First, I'm going to explain the cage match for you guys.
This is when we take three songs, we battle them against each other, you guys vote on your favorite
And the winner goes into rotation during the Bomani Music Amore program, which plays 24
hours a day on this station when we're not here.
So let's hear a clip of last week's winner.
We're not going to play the full song, although you can still vote for it.
And if it does win this week, it gets retired next week, because we'll have won for a month
straight.
This is Ayumi Hamasaki with Connected, last week's winner.
Alright, that's Yumi Yamasaki with Connected, that's your first candidate in the Orange
Orange Lounge Radio Cage Match
Eggman
We've been up yum yum
Yum yum
Ad mayo't
Aaaaaaa
the
world's it was going to the next one there so I'm gonna get the first time
I was too busy telling not not jokes this car room
I'll feedback on that a
pac-man what is not you my I affects with
I like it
it was like a really bad I nightmare warm water
there
where your music
uh... no i didn't like it very much right
i mean if it's one of the really cool but
it's always just really repetitive
so i'll give it
here
i would
fact
yes i think what you're going to think it's playing in my direction
and i don't care
uh...
who's like
yeah i would
I just had a ferret hit me in the face.
Let's see, the song, I'll probably give it an 8.5 out of 10. It's a pretty good song.
It's a pretty good song, but for some reason, I feel like Ayumi better for some reason.
But this song's pretty classic, though.
They could've done a little better, but it's pretty good.
I give it a 7, because I think that's about the highest stage I ever got to on Pac-Man.
All right, next up, Blokey, tell us about the other songs in the cage match.
The next one, you might remember her stuff from DR Max 2.
She did the song today, this is Tesla Confusion.
I don't know what I'm gonna do to make you see that I'm free
I'm free to say, I'm free to leave, I'm free to do what I feel
But I'm not sure if what I want, I need to take it over
When you're away, I feel confused
I want to be beside you, I want to say you're on my knees I want to know what you feel
You need to know when you're around that there's a cure but later when you're away I feel from you
p0k3smot42o muhaha
Oh, uh, woah, hello, that's the wrong one, my bad.
Uh, that was Test with Confusion.
and
on a scale of 110
i like it
and no i don't think my songs pretty mixed three at
the full version
not a cut-down version
But yes, I do pick my music files from my Sim collection.
See, we're close. I give you half a point.
But, uh, I'll give it a nine.
Uh, let's see, um...
It was better than the Pac-Man song.
I... I...
And Jamie, stay over here kicking me on the floor.
Yeah, she's doing it as a dick. Ow!
Don't...
You're beating me up. Um...
Yeah, uh... I give it an eight and a half.
You need to do that more often.
I think that sounds very great.
What, you like me kicking you?
The scores are probably good, there's a...
9.8 out of 10.
You need to kick people more often, not me.
It's gonna be a very good battle, but some person...
And why did you...
Jimmy just took my hat off and put it on Rob.
I also prefer Ayumi for a while.
Ooh, a chick fight.
TNA.
What the hell are you talking about?
Yes, versus Ayumi.
I thought it was pretty groovy. I also, I also give that song a seven. Okay. So anyway,
you can vote for, you can send in your votes now. Send them as a private message to me
in the chat room right now. You can vote for Connected by Ayumi Masamasaki. You can vote
So now, instead of going back to break, since we just played some music, you have to send me PMs so they don't count. Don't type them in the main channel because I don't count them there.
So, uh, explicit's given a kick out of just reading you people in the chatroom.
Um, black-eyed, did you have something you wanted to say?
I have the microphone right now, I figured you had something you wanted to say.
Why? My hat does not look dumb.
Oh, I'm cool, because I wear my hat backwards.
Yeah.
Anyway, did we figure out if we can do our segment that we wanted to do?
I mean, I've got, I can talk about something, man.
Okay, great.
Then we're going to talk about, we're going to introduce a new segment on this big show.
It's time everybody, sit around, bring in the family, sit around the radio, get the
kids in, tuck them into bed, because it's time for a new segment on Orange Lawns.
Now we kind of did this a while ago, except it wasn't an official segment.
You might remember a few weeks ago, I don't remember what episode number it is, but maybe
somebody like Angel, who knows, she knows this show in and out, she's very smart when
it comes to this show, she might remember what episode number this was, when Loki talked
about his experience with the Hooker.
I don't remember what episode that was, but, was it 20?
Oh, Black Lab, that was when he was here, it was 20.
Okay, in episode twenty you talked about the black lab, er,
I didn't talk about the hooker who was named Black Lab, no. She was black though, wait.
Anyway, so we thought we'd make a whole segment out of this in the future. Ladies and gentlemen,
give it up for Storytime with Loki.
Alright, so, uh...
Hold on, I'm sorry, I have to bring in your music, Loki.
So what are you going to be telling us the story about tonight? Well, I'm going to talk about the time
that I went to goth night at the rage in sacramento's club that we've got down here and you know
me kind of you know really I don't get out that much but when I do it's just weird shit
that happens so that's why we have you know story time so this is about like I went to
goth night well let me let me introduce this okay all right so before I was dating my girlfriend
right now. Um, I was dating this other girl who, um, her name was Forest. Um, she was
a cr- No, she was not dark black. Well, well, I'm not going to comp- Well, yeah, okay. The
forest was very thick, but that's not what I'm going to talk about here. Okay, so basically
we were going out and she was turning into Jesus Freak that she is now. Um, so before
that I was talking with this one girl who used to, you know, she was really had like
a crush thing on me all throughout high school and I just kind of ignored it. I didn't really
I don't care, but we were talking and stuff, and she wanted to go out to this club, but it was late at night, and she had no one to drive her, so I was like, oh, I'll take you down there, because I've never been there, and it sounded like fun, it sounded different, so we went to Goth Night down at the Rage.
So I get there, and there's like these really freaky people, okay? I mean, never have I seen so many drag queens and like people doing goth shit and stuff like that in my entire life, but it was fun because I like the music, I like industrial, and that kind of thing. They had K.M.F.D.M. and, you know, Rammstein, that kind of shit, so that was pretty cool.
This girl was really hot. She was nice. So we go there and I'm meeting all these weird people. There's this guy wearing a corset and she was commenting on his corset and asking her where he got it and that kind of thing.
But the really weird thing that happened to me that night is we were talking with her friend, one of her gay friends, I can't remember, I think his name was Thomas, yeah, gay friend Thomas, and now she was kind of, you know, hanging on me and stuff and all that kind of thing, and we were talking with him and stuff, and then her, his friend, also gay, was, you know, kind of eyeing me up and shit.
And so I was like, kind of, okay, what's going on here? And so there, you know, you're talking, and then I guess Thomas goes and talks to his friend, and comes back, he's like, my friend has made an interesting proposition, and I think he'd like to hear it. I'm like, okay.
Um, he wants to know if you'd be willing to go home with him tonight.
I'm like, hell no! No, wait! Sorry, don't swing that way.
And he's all, no, really, it's, uh, then, you know, Thomas is like, no, really, it's good.
You know, I've done it before. I'm like, no. And no, no.
So basically, she was, like, acting like my pimp that night.
I don't know. It was kind of weird.
It was kind of cool, though, because she was hanging out with me and she's, you know,
She was an exotic dancer once, and it was really sweet because she had piercings in
all the right places, except she wouldn't pierce the boys.
She didn't want to pierce her nipples, but she had piercings in other places.
I kept trying to get her to show me her piercings, but she wouldn't.
She was kind of shy.
She also had pictures, too.
Is she shy?
I know.
She's also taking pictures with her just wearing caution tape, and then the caution tape being heated up a little bit so that it's form-fitting.
I wanted to see that. That was kind of cool, but no.
Let's see, other than that...
Oh, this story kind of sucks. I had something really last night that was funny, and this is why we were going through the whole segment.
But unfortunately, I didn't record what I wanted to actually talk about today.
Let's see here. I can do the strip club story.
Okay.
Alright, well, real quick strip club story. Now there's some strippers that really kind of scare me.
There's this one chick, you know, she comes up, I'm at the bar there,
you've got my dollar bills down shit, she comes to rub her tits in my face, and that's kind of cool.
capital
but when she does it though it's like
that's good shit i mean i was like i wasn't prepared for that she had a
well what the fuck you see with
is with most annoying high-pitched voice that you can ever imagine
it was
the
sound of the world
Anyways, so yeah, that was scary.
We're going to be doing another strip-flip trip, though, pretty soon, though, because my friend's getting married, and I know he's going to be throwing a bachelor party, plus next week we're talking about going...
My girlfriend's going to strip-flip!
She's going to strip-flip at the end of the month with her friends, and supposedly
at Centerfolds,
I guess they do
full-nude strip-flips, or
guy-stripping, full-nude.
I never knew that.
I'm there. You gotta get tickets in advance, though, so it's eight dollars to go in.
But she's going with her friend and a couple of her friends, and they're going to do that, and they're going to buy each other lap dances. So that's kind of cool.
But I want to definitely hit up the strip club again, because it's fun.
Yeah, centerfolds, they have actually, Gold Club centerfolds, they've got their own actual forums. It's kind of funny watching people post in there.
I went to the Gold Club centerfold forums the other day. I don't remember why. I was talking to a friend online about them.
And um, yeah, they were interesting stuff. That's all.
you know, it'll cost you half as much in each, you know, to go in there. So, okay, yeah,
we'll do that. So, we go in there and basically the shower room is like this kind of large
communal shower thing. They've got these two chicks, you know, totally naked in there.
And they've got their sprayed whipped cream or not, yeah, like shaving cream all over
their bodies. Well, the shower room, what you can do is you can put dollar bills in
your hand and you can basically touch them all over their body wherever you want. Well,
And so as long as you have a dollar bill in your hand, you can keep putting dollars on them and stuff.
And then they started getting a little bit more freakier, and then they started going down on each other and shit in there.
I mean, I didn't know this kind of stuff happened in strip clubs, but I guess it does.
And then they had, um, if you paid $20, they would sit on your face.
But you just had to-
But you just have to keep your mouth shut.
So I guess it looks for the people with really big noses.
Look, I'm going there!
So, yeah, it was very interesting. The only thing I regret is because it was such a large group, I couldn't really get to the front of the line to, like, you know, be able to put dollar bills on, you know, Naked Chick's breast, but it was fun while it lasted. I mean, I don't know, it was interesting.
You know, I'm getting in so much trouble for this because the last time that I talked about weird shit like this, my girlfriend was bored and decided to listen to this show.
I love you, you're listening. Yeah, she does all this weird shit that we've done. I mean,
Lisa, I'm not like my friends who go and get, you know, the VIP room dances and get head
in there. I mean, so, and this, okay, if for all the people that are visiting Rancho Cordova,
this is Gold Club Centerfolds off of Folsom Boulevard. Do check it out. Yeah, that's all.
That's my story.
I like cheese.
Irene's playing Animal Crossing.
I'm going to have to do some more interesting weird shit in order to come up with stories, or start digging back into my past, because I've done a lot of awkward, weird shit before, and I'm sure, you know, they'll come up.
Well, you know what? For next week, that's your homework. You know, go find a funny story in your life and write it down.
I'm going to start a Paypal account. It's Loki's go to strip club fun account.
You never know, it might work.
Jamie, you want to announce the winner of this week's cage match?
Um, here's a quarter, Matt.
Woohoo! First donation to your strip club needs.
Oh, here we go!
Okay.
And, guess what?
Fuck everybody because I win.
That's because everyone's whipped to Jamie.
Just cause you all love me.
Yeah, it's probably all the people that listen to her F.U. shows all the time.
You're all nerds like me.
And the winner is me!
Oh, I'm sorry, Aphex Twin, and Eat'em Up.
Yeah, cause I'm cool.
Bless all of you people who are old school like me.
Not much to say, Jamie.
I'm gonna kick you again.
No, she's got my dog! Give it back! Give it back! No!
I just ate a little dog with the microphone don't do that again
Wipe it off on Rob
Okay, we're gonna take really quick break like one or two song break
We're gonna come back to wrap up this big train wreck of a show so stay with us. Won't you won't you be my neighbor?
And we'll be back
Let's do I want to play something we play one of mine, yes
I'll start with this song and then we'll do one of yours, okay?
Okay.
back
I can't wait to see you in the next video!
Loki's going to introduce this next song for us because it's special.
Okay.
Special ed.
for every for all those people out there that are thinking
it would be a really great idea to mix max three hundred with
name of baumanni song or any song that's in the whole baumanni series
um... here's why you shouldn't do that
Is this going to sound like a... never mind, I'm not going to say it on air.
Enos,
Blackfeet, Pogo.
Let's listen in on an
Orange Lounge Radio Staff Meeting
Extreme Bamani Radio
That's us. Orange Lounge Radio.
Dot, dot, dot.
Jamie's twitching. She went into a coma. That song killed her.
Let's just say that song fucking sucks.
We're gonna remix this because they have some lessons a little bit.
I'm having a...
I could just remix better than that.
I have had a cry.
How much of this life is worse than Max Dinosaur?
Oh god, I heard that.
It sounded. It sounded.
You know what it sounded like?
Burning?
A twin mix.
Well, actually, later on, uh...
Sing for that one!
I've got something else that you guys might like.
Well, anyways, that was a light entry in Turning Mix 3.
This is all the shit that was cluttering up, you know, the song list
that the reason my entry didn't get played.
I should have put my entry as the name of the game, Max300,
and it'd be like, oh, Max300, I'm gonna play that.
You know, so...
Frickin' A.
Okay.
Oh.
Okay, let me call numbers.
But yeah, there's a bunch of horrible shit out there.
Helium Era is a good example.
I've got another one that's Max 300, the Positive Reversal, some remix.
It's Max 300 backwards.
It's really shitty.
And then there's another one that's, we might be playing later, Max Doctor?
No.
Oh, what the hell?
Hell no.
I'm gonna read it into the lounge soon.
But, um, yeah, well, hmm. I've got some more stuff, though.
Plenty of horrible sound files.
That was very homoerotic, though, that song.
I would like to state, uh, Politary, I believe, has been banned from Orange Islands for a little while.
Although, we, her good songs, we accept, we let them through, like, you know, uh, memories, memories and, uh, you know, me.
That's pretty good.
We let those, we let those through. I don't know, there was another one that we let through, I thought it was that one.
Anyway, but that song? That song's banned for ten years, from Orange Islands Radio.
Let's just ban all Max 300, anything with Max 300 in it.
Okay, anything that is not Konami produced with Max in the title is now banned from this station.
Word.
No, any Max that sucks, because there's some pretty good Max files, but Max dinosaur, Max, whatever that title is.
Actually, there's been, okay, I've seen one really good, actually two very good mixes with Max in it.
in it. There was Max Resurrection, that was really good. It's on Simply Retarded, it's
on their site. But then there's also one that was Dropout 300, that was really good.
I thought of another one that's actually okay, Piano Max Unlimited, that was cool.
Oh yeah, that right there was STM, he was the guy that actually, a long time ago. Now
Now if you remember, now they have that musician's trial thing right now for 2DX9 style or whatever.
They did a similar thing back in the day for 4th style, and they also did it for 5th mix.
5th mix, the winner of it was Paranoid Eternal, and that was done by E.M.
STM did another, he has a bunch of music files he's done.
In fact, Virtu Corey released, what was it, there was a Trip Machine strange mix that
It was floating around in the net and people thought it was Trip Machine Survivor.
That was hilarious.
So that was going around, but that was actually a remix done by that guy, STM.
And he actually, you know, he was one of the lucky ones that actually got an actual song in DDR.
Yeah, it's in Xtreme now, so go play his remix and it's actually pretty good.
What's your favorite part of the song?
Next week worst like the cage worst or something. I don't know
We should do one. We should do one. We're like only one song. You know survives and the rest get dumped off the playlist
All right
What we could do is like we'll have like a turn it like a cage match tournament of all the worst songs
And all the ones that get that and all the songs except for the winner will get put under a CD
I know it would win the losing. Let them move.
No, no, no. Oh, what do you mean, win the losing?
Max for you. Max for you.
There's a bunch of Omani remixes out there that are official on DanceMania. There's one I've got on my CD here, it's Candy the Planet Remix.
The one that's out right now for people who are playing in DDR Extreme, there's Burning The Floor and MomoMix.
I've got a Let Them Move remix on that CD that's really, really bad.
Imagine Let Them Move and Max 300 mixed together.
It's been done.
There's this guy, Twin, who used to be in our chat room.
He used to do Let Them Move remixes all the time.
Final thought, Dave?
Final thought?
Final thought.
I need to play DDR Extreme.
And I will pass V.
or not at Roosevelt-Goughland.
They'd be going to the bathroom so badly.
Well, that's like one of the worst songs ever, how can I think of?
Or just get some damn lessons, or something.
And end up with a waksa wakla, or...
Max for you, or whatever the damn thing people are talking about on the internet.
Unless if it's very good, you can give it to me and I'll see, I'll rate it.
And Scania should get New York Streams soon.
It's on its way, and I can't wait till it comes.
Alright, Black Lab, final thought.
Derby Owners Club is my new crack.
I have to go play it next time I go back to the Bay Area, which hopefully will be soon.
But now I gotta get a job so I can blow money on DOC. I'm sad.
You could blow so you can blow.
No!
I... Don't bring that up again!
Again?
Brad, final thought?
All your fried chicken are blowing to me.
Does Irene have a final thought?
Are you allergic to corn?
It's fine, I only had a little.
I want another one.
Wait a minute! If you're allergic to corn, why eat anymore?
I won't die.
Um, let's see...
Loki, your final thought of the day?
My furrow hurts from all this yelling and screaming.
I can't be enthusiastic and stuff.
Especially with this stupid science thing.
I'm not being so hateful.
Why? I hate the world!
Let go of your hate.
You know, if people would stop being stupid and start dying, the world would be a better place.
I feel the conflict within you. Let go of your hate.
You know, that's one of the reasons I don't get drunk is because I'm not afraid I'm going to get violent.
I mean, what if the actual inhibitions I have is from killing people and then that goes away?
Then I would wake up out of a drunken stupor and see a bunch of bodies and blood everywhere.
Wouldn't that be frightening?
I just hug people.
I turn into the absolute opposite when I'm drunk.
Instead of being all angsty and violent and everything, I can start loving everybody and
wanting to hug everybody I see.
Have you noticed that?
And DDR-Llama, or if anyone has contacts with DDR-Llama right now, please set up my uploading
script because I'm waiting on you to finish it and you said you'd do it like three days
ago and you haven't and it's really frustrating because I need to upload my site and get it
done!
Were you whining?
NO!
Anyways, I'm dead.
Go!
I get to be last.
My final thought of the day is, um, uh, yeah, we're running long and I'm not helping because
I can't think of a final thought, um, oh, my final thought, um, as the old cheerleaders,
the old cheerleaders from Saturday Night Live said, sex can wait, masturbate.
My final thought of the day is I'm going to have Boba and you have to stay tuned for the
after birth. Alright, bye guys. Bye.
You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio. Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
Orange Lounge Radio is hosted by Dark Sakura, Sky, and Loki.
If you'd like to leave us a comment, send us an email at
orangeloungeradioatyahoo.com.
and now here's your fortune cookie message of the day
Don't cut him no slack!
Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles!
Splinter taught them to be ninja teens!
He's a radical rat!
Leonardo leads Donatello's dust machine!
That's a rat, Jack!
Raphael is cool, but rude!
Give me a break!
Michelangelo is a party dude!
Pardon!
Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles!
Thank you very much for listening, and we'll see you next week.