Do you want to hear the most annoying sound in the world?
You're listening to Orange Lounge Radio, The Mani Talk, and then some.
Orange Lounge may contain adult content. Orange Lounge may contain many four-letter words.
Orange Lounge may contain a scene of nudity.
Orange Lounge may contain hot monkey sex.
Just kidding, Orange Lounge will not contain hot monkey sex. In this episode...
Hey, are there any balls down there?
That's the biggest berry you've ever seen, Jingle Berry.
What's your favorite scary movie?
Showgirls. Absolute frightful. What's yours?
There are no stupid questions, just stupid people.
Don't torture yourself. That's my job.
Now's the time on sprockets and we dance!
I don't get you, my pretty. And your little dog, too.
I don't come through.
I'm sorry, but all questions must be submitted in writing.
Why did they have to take the word gay?
No! What he expects us to punish him with a shot is Hindu.
Hey!
Shut up! Where's my gun? This is my boomstick.
Sky. Come on girls, it's time to drop the bomb. Loki. I can't, for the life of me, get the hooker to have sex with me.
What kind of war human being would find that funny? Orange Lounge Radio.
You are tuned in to the Bamani Scene's most stylish radio station of all things Ben Money.
It's cute and lovely. We are live and this is episode number 27 for January the 5th of 2003.
My name is Rob Roberts. You might know me as Sky. Joining me as always are my awesome, wonderful, stupendous, and bouncy co-hosts.
In this corner, the happiest bunny on the farm, Miss Jamie Summers, also known as Star Trek.
And that's from hell.
In that corner, say hello to our tech master, Loki.
I'm not bouncing. I don't know what the hell you're talking about there.
I saw your chi-chis, they were bouncing.
Also with us tonight. Holy shit. We have got seriously probably the biggest show yet
We have so many people in studio. It is crazy is the first show of the year and there's everybody's here to celebrate
Let's go around the room. Say hello to everybody first up. Say hello to the one the only chat room
I think the most active person in the chat room quite possibly right recently. Say hello DDR angel
and
with DDR Angel to bro say hello to stress ah hello in the back there is
jabberwocky just came into the room for a ruler next jabberwocky is 23rd magus
is here in the house yo to 3m up in his house okay Brad's back there and also
say hello to Irene oh my god Jamie's so amazing she gave us the Harry Potter sex
Harry Potter sex oh my god what the hell did you just say we do not have enough
microphones to cover all this shit going on in here tonight hell Rob doesn't have
enough flows to cover what's going on tonight come see me when you're not busy
tonight ladies and gentlemen we may have monkey sex yes Rob is not wearing any
My pants, thus my need for a ruler!
Alright, we're gonna come back, it's a huge show.
We've got interviews from the, or interview I should say, from the SoCal trip
Loki and I took over the weekend.
We might do Match Game live in studio tonight.
And my nuts.
And we've got Jamie's Nuts, all after this.
It's the MP3 you've all been coming over from Xtreme.
Or you haven't.
It's the Legend of Max here on Orange Lounge Radio, enjoy!
Oh
1, 2, 3, 2, 1
Ugh.
Hi!
Oh my God!
You've got mail!
During my service in the United States at the time, I took the initiative in creating
an internet.
You bastards!
in the United States of Congress, and I put the initiative in creating the Internet.
But you can't expect to wield supreme executive power just because some watery tart threw a sword at you?
I don't want to talk to you no more, you empty-headed animal food truck whopper!
Please, good people, I am in hate.
You are in the dark black forest of Orange Lawn's radio. Here we are.
big fat house tonight filled with people this is crazy
I'm fuzzy and full of nuts
some new promos this week thanks to the lovely DDR Angel and Stressa
you guys made some new promos for us
what was going through your mind when you were making those, why did you decide to make promos
what was up with those, it was just random and hey look
it sounds good, alright sounds good, hi Angel how you doing
no comment
Wait, what was I supposed to say?
Alright, first off, as I promised in the chat room, tonight we are bringing back the word of the day.
You remember when we did rave and we had the sandstorm? Jamie, tell us all about tonight's word of the day.
I think we decided on this one. The word of the day is slut.
The word of the day is slut.
And whenever we say the word slut, you get this
The biggest slut in the world, Politary
I don't want to hear Politary over and over and over again
No
So just don't say slut
Oh, you said slut
uh...
baby will kill you
okay shit so now you all know if it is the secret to grow the word of the day
and we're allowed to do that now because the band the years over so the bands
over so we can play a political as much as we want to see what's next new band
you want to be a m
they have all figured out here yay okay voluntary is bad for orange lounge for
another year but i think that they do a thing that will consider
all right
that you've got to say things to do a mike or else they don't hear it on the
radio
by the sharp all right sharp object
word okay so i think when you stick
we need to go back to a time warp here we need to go back to two weeks with
jamie by the way is what you're acting
lovely
lovely job last week i i didn't get any of the whole so i heard that that was
the whole time. I didn't hear that because of all the propelling. You know what? I get
the same problem. When I drink Propel and play DDR, that's like instant pee. I went
through three bottles of Propel that show. Were they all berrylicious? Uh-huh. Alright,
cool. I have nuts stuck in my teeth, sorry. Whoa! Whoa! Me too! How come we haven't heard
from Loki? Where's Loki? Oh, you're right there, okay. That's because I don't have a
chair and I'm sitting on the floor without a mic. I thought you liked getting to pet
the rug here. That's a wrong rug, I think. Don't you like petting rug? Uh, yes. Okay.
Are you a rug munchkin? We need to time warp back to two weeks ago. We did the last show.
Only on the weekends. Oh, then up came the weekend. Loki and I, we took a little road
trip. We went down to SoCal. Bit or a table of one? Bitches. We went down to SoCal and
we were there and we have a little summary of it. Right? We're going to play this bit?
Yeah. Alright, let's see. Let's see if this works here. Our live piece. Well, not our
live piece, but our somewhat live piece. A week delayed.
I don't want to know about your piece. I'm going to go back to eating my nuts.
Anyway, enjoy this bit from SoCal. I can never reach.
First here on Orange Lawns Radio. So here it is, the taped garbage part of the
show. As you may or may not know, last week, Loki and I decided to take a little trip,
and we decided to visit Southern California. And with me here, of course, is Loki. Say
hello.
Hey, everybody.
Now, describe for us, Matt, since I'm not a very good speaker, what kind of place are
we at right now?
We're in the giant mall that I wish we had. Yes, we are so very unprivileged up in NorCal.
This mall is just huge, and there's giant lights in the sky, neon lights everywhere, it is paradise, definitely.
And they got lots of shops, and they have a frickin' anime shop! Why don't we have a frickin' anime shop up in Norical? That sucks.
And they have a Dave & Buster's. That's pretty cool.
Yes, overpriced games. Woo-hoo, but they had a...
What was that derby game?
Derby Owner's Club.
The hot new Milpitas game.
It was fun. I jacked someone's horse, so that was kinda cool.
horse breeders don't my horse
come back here with my horse wilbur
so that kind of fun
and then we just saw a guy another day which was uh...
a giant penis
but before they had even worse i can uh...
previous of like movies they're just gonna really suck ass
movie started at two the actual film started at two thirty
let's put it that way
awful awful
sort of the kind of crap we've done this weekend we've we've been we've seen all
the sites. We went to Cyberzone yesterday. We went to Arcade Infinity last night. What
other kind of junk have we done here? I went to Japan Arcade. Got to play Beam the
A-3, so that was kind of fun. Played lots of Pump It Up. Played a game that's a Korean
knockoff of Dance Station 3DDX, which was pretty fun. Got to try that out. You played
8th style and 7th style, and sucked. I played Mambo-Go-Go, and sucked. And I played Cracking
DJ. Crack. Never mind. I did not suck at Cracking DJ, that was fun. We got to play also, what
else, oh, Poppin' Music, that was alright, didn't really like that, but whatever. Poppin'
music owns you it's giant seizure lights for your pushing pleasure I'll stick
with a cracking DJ crack so anyway one other thing that we've gotten to do this
week is we got to visit an old friend of the show an old an old buddy of the show
that's been listening I think ever since the very first episode if I'm not
mistaken no since the third episode I don't know nobody listened the first
episode hi forgot yeah anyway say hello everybody it is the one the only so
cupcake everybody
nothing what is up what is that my brother how was your day
uh... a blast especially seeing everything i just got
uh... yes the recipient of some lovely party gifts from a part of sounds radio
actually it's from loki but you know it's it's part of our country right yeah
yeah
yes yes the uh... price pack and what
what lovely things do we have been uh... price back
uh... the only few things i know they give out
uh... movies enemy dvds in
so he didn't even have to make it out to get that point that's amazing how do you
feel
uh...
was issued tell me if you were facing that you're you've got your walk away
you're like twenty dvds are so well made up twenty like ten at least
and uh... what this about you don't even
on the dvd player in a very on the dvd player what what's this going on
i don't know any dvd movies i really read some but
Now I have something to use my DVD players for.
You can watch such fine films as Blue Crush
and Undercover Brother.
Amazing films there.
Yes, I'm sorry. Remember, you only need one hand to use a DVD remote.
Terp, terp, blink, blink.
If you got porn.
Ha! Jokes on you, it was VHS porn.
You still only need one hand to use a VHS remote!
Back to the tape.
Can't wait!
Alright, so, you know, here it is, your chance, you finally get to be on the show.
What kinds of things do you have to say for the listeners?
Um, nothing much, actually.
Well, you sure talk a lot in the chat room, and now that you have your chance, you don't have anything to say now?
Or should I say, and you don't have anything to say now?
No, I don't.
You don't talk that way in real life, by the way. You promised me you would and you don't.
you don't I don't talk much in real life amazing most people you meet from the
DDR community don't talk much all I hardly ever talk much and let me I don't
talk much I don't know when we got the plate max to in the middle of a theater
and watch people go what are you doing what they step in on the Aerosport how
do you do that I have that brings me back to the stupid people that seen up
Mr. Spanky took it and shoved it up his a**.
However, if I can't find it, I can give you a PS1 keychain clip pen.
Okay, we'll just get back to the tape.
Okay.
And in case she didn't say what I think she said, she's gonna say,
Um, you haven't emailed me the proof yet.
That's right, now where is this proof that she speaketh of?
Um, I lost my Dextra, I'm sorry.
Oh, well, I think she lost her GameCube pen. What do you have to say about that?
Hey, I was right!
So, let's see, what else can we
talk about here in the little SoCal segment? What are we going to do with the rest of the time
here in SoCal? Well, one thing we're going to do tomorrow is check out AI
because it's rumored that they're going to get DDR Extreme there, so hopefully they will.
We got to see the crazy whore. It was rumored that what was in Cyberzone
going to get it yesterday and obviously it wasn't. Omaha, Nebraska. Freaking Omaha, dude.
If I ever have a band, I'm naming it Freaking Omaha. Instead of Max II and the Aussie Landers,
this time we got Xtreme and the Rednecks. Yeehaw. I'm just not very happy with that.
Hey, we got our 2DX machine when we come back, so that's kind of cool.
And there was a fellow from Omaha that came out to Shaft, so you know, he wasn't right
neck at all, he was a very cool guy, so I'm happy for the, I'm happy yet insane with jealousy
for those folks in Omaha, what can you say?
Not anymore.
And I got to see definitely a bunch of cool stuff, you know, that one mall we went to
was pretty sweet in Little Tokyo, and I got to spend money, and I bought models and cool
stuff.
Cool. Any words of advice for things we should do while we're in SoCal or the places we should go?
You are the resident expert right now, at least out of the three of us.
This isn't the biggest mall. You still haven't been to some of the biggest malls we have around here.
You should go to The Block. You should honestly go to The Block. That place is huge.
Okay, but what other mall has a giant glowing phallic symbol?
I don't know.
there's this giant glowing green thing and oh my god now it's red and it glows
and it looks like and look at the little tip it's even got a little tip and I
took some pictures though while we were down here oh I gotta mention this really
cool game I played yesterday okay this game involves a monkey running around on
a grid undressing a woman I know how weird that sounds that was a bucket
But it was so addicting, it was better in DDR.
Anyway, it was really cool, it was a lot of fun.
And afterwards, you get 15 seconds to zoom in and Google
the woman.
Yeah, fun.
All right, we better wrap up this segment
and get back to the real show.
But we have to ask SoCalKicks, because we always
ask the hosts of the show whenever it's over.
We always go around the three of us,
and we always say our final thoughts of the day,
and any guests that happen to be in the studio.
So I'm just going to ask SoCalKicks, what are your final thoughts of the day?
Loki gives the best hookups.
He also gives the best... Never mind, we're going to go back to the show now. Good night!
No, wait! Hey, hey!
Alright, one, two, three, four!
Alright.
I think I said something like, uh, no, I do not! I don't know what you're talking about!
That is wrong and very disgusting.
And you enjoy it.
Uh, big thank you to our buddy SoCalKicks for spending some time with us.
Let me proof you get a pen.
If you really want a pen now, I can send you a Bic.
A Bic?
Yeah, buy a box of Bic. You're gonna flick your Bic?
I'm gonna flick my Bic. Dude, Brad's pen glows.
It's a Rayvar pen.
Ooh, I wanna take E and make out with everybody.
Brad!
Don't you be turning into a slut on me!
I said slugs.
You said it on purpose.
Nobody heard it.
Alright.
So, then also, what happened when Loki and I were gone, that Friday is when, here in
Orange Lounge World Headquarters in Sacramento, finally, 2DX8 style lands here in Sacramento.
I know you guys talked about this on the show last week, so I won't go too far into it,
but 8 styles here, it rules, the end.
This week, Xtreme started spreading like a bad case of VD all around California.
And it made its way to Stockton last night, so we took a trip down to Stockton Golf Land,
as I call it for short, GAG, Ghetto Ass Golf Land.
And we went down to GAG to play DDRXtreme.
So five of us went, the three of us hosts, and Angel's Trace all went.
What do you want to say about, specifically what do you want to say about DDRXtreme?
Because I know there's lots of people listening going,
It's extreme!
I don't know, I felt that Frozen Ray was me.
Shame on Goughland for getting a bootleg! Bad bad!
They had the most ghetto marking.
They took the DDR, um, the 7th mix sign that was up there,
and they put a big sign over that said,
Extreme DDR 8th!
8th mix, because they're stupid.
Stupid people.
I wish it had said a turd mix. I would have paid so much money for it.
I'll make one for him.
So what do you guys think? What did you guys think of Max 2?
Ah, fuck DDR. What did you think of
Extreme in comparison to Max 2?
It's Max 2 Plus. That's exactly what I thought. It's just
DDR Max 2 Plus. Uh, no?
Um, let's see. There's a few things, uh, a few things I was disappointed on is the Oni remixes that they had in Max 2 that were supposed to be playable now.
They only had one set of steps, and that was the Oni steps. So, ooh, thanks for going all the way and, uh, giving us, you know, new steps for those.
Um, some of the new songs I just didn't really care for. There was a really cool pop music one that was like-
in a bag. You know what? I didn't see, except for you, Rob. No one else played that fucking
song. I wanted to do something fucked up my last stage, so I'm like, I'll do the big hot
air song. No one played that song. Actually, I was looking at the top three songs for 321
Stars, Vanity Angel, surprise, and Tears. Those are the only. Now that was the thing
I liked about extreme is that the videos they keep getting better the video for stoic was pretty funny because it's just like the 2d
X1 except as the afro guy doing it and
They said the video. What were some other songs? I actually played
I did the I do I do I do and it had this whole little like retro thing going on with all these little pictures
of hot little Asian girls and
Speed over Beethoven at Beethoven running all around all this other best video one of the best videos has to be for legend of
Max with the guys running in the background shit like that. I was off. Oh my god
No, I liked the one for Jet World.
That was cool.
I wish they had the singing ladies with the humongous heads.
That was beautiful, Jamie.
Talk about non-core.
Personally, in my opinion, Extreme was just, yeah.
Extreme was little.
Yeah, that too.
It just, it's with more shit.
I I just it's hard for me to get excited about extreme. There's nothing that
Exciting in it who somebody's making this room a disco over here with lights
How about eight style? Yeah, whoo
Yeah, eight styles much cooler. Yeah, I wish though
I remember way back when they showed that there was like a joke picture
That someone had made like a giant 2d x-pad to play with their feet
They should do like one of those
To hell with all you and your stupid 2DX. 2DX sucks ass. All of you suck ass.
Thank you, shut up.
Super strong, no less.
All I know about Xtreme is it's just a green Max 2.
Yeah, it's a green Max 2 with twice as many songs, with more modes, and more options, and more difficulty.
It's just the same damn game. Hey, it's actually it's the first base with 230 songs in it. Yeah
They'll all get played out. Wait call it beat mania because that's what it really is. It's just beat mania, right?
No, it's beat mania. It's beat mania. I don't know. It looks like Street Fighter. You know, it's got pixels
It's on a monitor you push buttons. It's all the same, you know now granted
I haven't played extreme yet, but how can everyone got all excited?
you know to go from third style to our third mix to fourth mix and all it was
was just you know added songs and stuff you know they changed a few things here
and there you know but when it goes from max to extreme everyone's just like
we're jaded you know yeah maybe that's it I don't know but we didn't like the
CD banners okay no one liked the discard no one really cared here's a here's a
You know what I like?
Puke it up.
What I did like is that they had the song list, you could divide it by game, that it
came from.
Yeah, see, I know, I mean, like, see, I hear that Extreme has a few new options too and
stuff, but I don't know, like, it seems like everyone got all excited from, you know, transition
from third to fourth, but not from, you know, seventh to eighth, or, you know, I don't know.
Anyway, yeah.
I mean, it's okay just to have, like, new stuff to kind of break the monotony of Max 2 because I can only stand to hear the whistle song so many times, you know?
It's gone. It's gone.
And it's gone.
Well, thank you.
It might be an unlock, but it's good.
Whatever. Whatever.
It's kind of nice just to have some new songs kind of mixed up a little. Like I said, the videos are nice, so it's pretty to watch, but...
I didn't see ghosts come back.
No, ghosts did not come back. I didn't see either.
That pisses me the fuck off. Because I liked playing ghosts.
telephone operator did come back that was pretty cool so anyway and I saw
somebody there playing freckles just so they could get extra stage I'm like
Jesus okay you're playing it to get an extra stage yet you're wasting a stage
to get that extra stage what's up with that well then fuck that it's kind of
weird though because it's now the extra stage you can pick any song you watch
this on reverse 1-5 with butterfly extra stage. That is pretty cool. And heavy. I'd have to
say that, Para Nera Survivor, that was hard. That was fun. I only got about halfway through
on doubles. I owned A on the Oni. I double A'd A. Yeah, you double A'd A on heavy on
On Singles the first time, I passed A on the ONI steps, which are our cata on doubles,
and that was fun.
And Trip Machine Survivor's Easy as Hell, it's a weird fucking song, weird, weird song.
What was that one song, Guacamole?
Gum Land, A Couple.
That song pissed me off, but I was more pissed off because of the situation, everything was
against me.
It had a really crazy-ass cactus in the background.
Yeah, it was pretty cool. The cactus playing Samba was pretty cool.
Like I said, the videos are great. The videos keep getting better and better.
The best fucking background in a DDR game ever has to be A. A has the most kick-ass background image for it.
Yeah, that's pretty cool.
Chat room's asking, what about V? V's video.
I really dug the splash screen for V.
There's Tron walking down the stairs with her all shadowed out with the blue light from
behind.
I don't remember the video itself though.
I think it's just one of those generic rave videos.
Generic random shit.
That's pretty much it.
So there wasn't any special video for that.
I think A didn't have a special video either.
I remember it just had the dude, the Renaissance guy.
Yeah.
Alright, so that's all of our thoughts on Xtreme, anything else?
Yeah!
Angel, you're so quiet over there.
You have anything you want to say about Xtreme?
No, just no.
We're eating death cookies.
Okay!
Murder never tasted better.
They had this really cool Japanese heavy metal song that was in there.
It had this character from Poppy Music in the background dressed up like a samurai.
He looked really evil looking.
So that was kind of cool.
They had that in there.
It was a really awesome heavy metal song.
though. The guy that was playing it was really cool at freestyling, too, so that was kind
of cool to watch.
All right, so I think at this point in the show we're going to take a quick break. Sound
good to you? Anything else you want to say on Extreme, Jamie?
Why is that pizza? Yeah, we've got to go get that.
It was extremely, um, yeah.
No, I wouldn't say it's a waste. I wouldn't by any means say it's a waste. It's a badly
needed upgrade to Max 2, but it doesn't bring anything new into DDR.
That's so completely average.
They didn't put any of the cooler songs from 2DX in. That kind of pisses me off.
Some of them.
A is kind of fun to dance to, but I mean, it's just, it's steps were a little easy.
Although I hear the only ones are harder.
I only played two games. But now I have a decent selection of Tac songs.
They should have put it in Cracker.
Yes!
Tears?
Sucked ass.
Hyper-Eurobeat? I wasn't touching that with a ten foot pole.
and bring the age of those that suck ass
thank you much it speed over beethoven was as fun as people so lots of tax
the tax cool
stoker
uh... one of the songs was name the end
what feature
what's your idea
i hate that's what
and i say someone economically every minute until they bring back the whistle
song
when was the show and i hope they never bring that back that's my least favorite
tdr song
has been the school quality
okay we're gonna take a quick break and still is funny when we mentioned miss
Is Muffet getting AIDS?
We're going to come back...
No, I thought that your hooker story was pretty funny.
We're going to come back and do the FUs of the week, so send those to me over in the
chat room, and dear God, we've got a lot of people to get through tonight, so make them
short!
Alright, we'll be back after a quick break featuring those two little letters you all
love.
so
Hello? Hello, is this thing on testing? Testing 1-2?
I'm looking in the index, but I don't see anything for how to run a radio show.
Hello? I don't understand this. Does this thing work?
This thing reads like stereo instructions! Is this on?
What the hell? Orange Lounge Radio. Broke-down ghetto Bimani
radio. What the ****? Yes, you are listening to Orange Lounge Radio. By the way, the beep
was really ****. Thank you, thank you for sharing that. Alright, we are back and we're
going to get right into it, the FUs of the week. Now we have a lot of new, it's a new
year, new people listening to the show. Hello everybody, thanks for listening to Orange
Lounge. Join in the chat room, go to our website at orangelounges.skie.cx and join our chat
room. Pizza's been here. That's getting added to the list, man! Didn't you see everybody
eating pizza in front of you? Blind much? Jamie's sitting here going, nah, nah, I love
pizza. Strisa's got pizza sitting in his freaking hand. Is the pizza here yet? Oh my god. I
thought they were supposed to deliver the pizza five minutes ago. Poor Loki. They did.
What are we paying this guy for?
We're not.
He gives good handjumps. No, I'm just kidding. I'm kidding. God, I'm kidding.
Oh, somebody said the S word.
All right, all right. Talk about the FUs of the week, please.
Pretty please, Jamie. Tell us all about it.
Fuck a duck screw a kangaroo.
It's going to be one of those shows. It is one of those shows.
I don't know.
The five cases a week are when we get pissy and say, fuck you.
See, Rob likes to censor and go, F, not me. I don't care about watching my fucking language.
So, fuck.
Okay, if the two minutes off my life thing were true for everything, I would be burning in hell right now.
But remember, I have to take over hell.
Ah, yes.
Alright, so we're ready to do these FUs of the Week.
My kunitori of hell.
Did you say your kuditori of hell?
People who watched Udoni Kenshin would get it.
Oh, okay.
Alright, here we go, the FUs of the Week, starting off with the FU goddess that we always start off with.
Fuck, say it, Rob. Say it.
It's the FUCK SHIT COCK HORSE PISS CUNT USED OF THE WEEK.
My first fuck you of the week goes to my shoes.
People who have seen me know about my burning feet.
I have the coolest pair of shoes in the universe. You might want to see a doctor about that.
Bite my ass.
I bought these shoes two and a half months ago from the Vans Outlet.
And the last pair of shoes I got from the Vans Outlet lasted me a year and a half.
These are starting to really kill my feet. Before I got my pair of shoes before these,
I was having really bad problems with the arches and the old shoes.
I couldn't play DDR without having my arches hurt and having my feet just be really painful.
Well, these shoes
are starting to do it to me, and I've only had two and a half months that I've been wearing them.
So, fuck my burning feet.
They might like it.
Shut up, Rob.
Next thing.
but starting off went back to my career
because they have this and now on top of the on top of the machine
and cancer nice and good anything
if it's not going to your eyes when you're trying to play a song for the
first time
absolutely
welcome all of the couple
family and a couple family
i think the mob on songs that the god damn mobile song
luckily
anyway
this is the way it was going like doesn't matter if those like tearing up
the whole time so i think you play
but i think we're hurting questions
and then i think it was an issue
appealing up so they like
runs into the ball of my feet and the ball
and then
but i think that's because i have to be lucky for all of my clothes
because all of them acting
i think my room
he got about twenty hours
I have done two loads of wash.
I have about maybe ten more to go.
I didn't realize my wardrobe was so huge.
The other thing, fuck my new pair of jeans.
Because they were falsely made and now I can't return them because I've already worn them.
In the rain. Fuck the rain.
Because it's not.
And fuck your Yankee blue jeans.
Bravo. Thank you.
that it
moving on to look is if i have to ask i don't know as if i have to ask what is
that the other week is a terrible okie
well start off with the most recent thank you for not telling me there's
pizza here
how much is the observant when there's so much shit going on
i'm hungry
i'm seeing i'll
i mean strippers
anyway
I thought you said that your list of priorities put food above strippers.
It did.
Well, my food's almost gone, see?
There's a really huge F.U., and that goes to drivers, again.
Akine.
I'm gonna kill you.
You freaking get near me!
Seriously!
Stop trying to cut me off! If you're skipping to the old Asian bitch, stop changing lanes!
For no apparent reason!
I don't give a shit if you don't know where you're going!
Don't get in my way!
F you to stupid driver's ed people! You're driving 40 miles under the speed limit
and you piss me off! I don't care if you know how to drive because you're never going to learn how to drive
C point A!
Okay?
Also!
F you to freaking golf lands!
They suck ass!
Okay, stocking golf lands alright but their carpet sucks shit.
roseville golf land
well you kind of have to have drumsticks play drum mania
that's kind of the point of the game
bang the sticks against the drums that's how it works
uh... although they'll go down in here
they have created
if you hear extreme
for one reason
michael but they've been
NO ONE SHOULD PUT A RICKY MARTIN COVER IN ANY FUCKING DDR MIX!
That's it, for now.
It works for somebody, amigo.
Oh fuck that!
Matt has a mouth full of anyway, going back to...
Jamie, Jamie's had a relapse. Yes.
Back to the Golf Land thing.
Fuck those idiots last night, I had your asses kicked out and that was cool.
Alright, uh, my turn.
Are you sure?
Yes.
My FU of the Week. I would additionally like to give an FU of the Week to drivers.
Yeah, fuck you.
If you were driving on I-5 North about last Sunday night, about, oh, I don't know, anytime between noon and nine, because that's how long we were on the goddamn road.
If you were driving on that road, fuck you. I hate you. Burn in hell for all eternity because you don't know how to fucking drive.
Loki had enough road rage for the both of us, at least.
I was driving it. He was yelling at everything. It helped pass the time. What can you say?
My other F.U. goes to work. I don't want to go back tomorrow. Fuck work.
What other F.U.s do I have? I guess that's it.
That's it. That's all the F.U.s I can think of for right now. So fuck, fuck Stockton Golf Line for being ghetto.
Oh, fuck people that don't know how to follow a token line. Fuck the token line. Just fuck the token line all together.
I can't fucking stand the token line because nobody ever knows how to follow the token line because
Nobody is smart that plays DDR, apparently.
Listen crazy bitch, you don't fucking put 12 tokens on the goddamn line!
One at a time, you dumbass!
I'm gonna be playing a lot!
Fuck that bitch who puts 12 tokens on the machine and says,
you say, you're only supposed to put one up.
Oh, I'm gonna be playing a lot.
Fuck you!
You're gonna be playing none at all when I have my foot so far up your fucking ass
you won't be able to walk straight for a week.
No, you showed the pit so far up her ass that she tastes rubber.
Anyway, um, yeah, so fuck the token line.
Good thing I didn't see her.
Because nobody knows how to follow it. Try a sign-up sheet. It takes a pen and a piece of paper.
And, um, and again, if you steal a pen, you're fucking sad.
If you have to steal a goddamn fifty cent thick pen, your life is really fucking sad.
I hope you die. I hope you die of syphilis.
And F you to that stupid flamboyant retard who is playing Para Para.
I understand that Para Para is a game for women,
but fucking, seriously, you're way too-
Oh, yes! And F you to people who play Bimani games that look gayer than me.
Nobody is gayer than me! Nobody!
That was just- it was just so weird.
It- it- it's just- but this guy was more flamboyant than...
Oh my god.
Liberace! This guy was more flamboyant than fucking Elton John!
He must have been the most flamboyant person on the known...
He scares me! Scares me!
I have video of it, though. It will be going up on my website.
Yeah, we're going to be making flamingpara.com
I'm done.
I got really ranty this week. That was amazing.
Jamie, I see why Jamie likes this.
so i fear
with the p h three p r
and uh... fp and david bussert were overcharging on their games
that sucked
f miss thang my horse in derby owners club my horse named miss thang
we're coming in last place in every single race you suck i hate you
and fp the owner of cloud the fucking horse that beat both of ours because you're a stupid little girl
and you think you know better
so ha i jacked your fucking horse how do you think about that huh don't have your horse in the water because i have it
Alright.
My music again, please.
Okay.
Fuck my Trueno in Initial D. I love the car to death, but it has no acceleration, so I
made a new car.
I have an Integra Type R now and it's named as Magic.
That's all.
Okay, I have another ramp.
Oh, God.
With the exception of Jamie, fuck Initial D players.
You all drive the same goddamn car.
I saw seven of you coming out of the Golf Lamb parking lot, all with cheap-ass plastic
spoilers on your little rice rockets.
No, no, no, no.
The erector set spoilers.
Yes, the erector set spoilers.
God, you people are sad.
Initial D is not real life.
Remember folks, you're driving a Civic, not a race car.
God.
Stickers, do not make it go faster.
Ooh, I put the Type R sticker on my, my, uh, Toyota, um, excuse me, there's no, any, no
Toyota car.
Your car is sad, and so are you.
You can't drift on Highway 80.
Get over it.
Oh, that doesn't stop me from getting my actual Corolla, 86 Corolla hatchback to modify into
the Torino Sprinter with me on the paint, because, uh...
No, I'm just kidding.
But Jamie's cool like that.
She's okay.
She's the exception to the roll.
I think the whole reason I would have a Ricey car is because I think they're funny.
Jamie can appreciate the comic value of a funny car.
I think they're funny.
I want to get, like, an 85 Mustang GT and, and, and, like, Rice's...
an FU to the stupid bitch at Rayleigh's the Chinese food takeout place listen
bitch I don't want a sample I didn't want a sample before stop trying to give
me a fucking sample after I get my food obviously I want what I'm getting and
not what you're offering stop trying to offer me the fucking sample stupid
Chinese bitch. I'm done. Wow. Okay. Oh, back to the FUs. Let's go around the room. Are
we done with your FUs, Jamie? I guess so. Give me money. Fuck everyone who doesn't give
me a dollar. Alright. Here we go. Going around the room. This is the song I chose for all
First of all, F.U. is a butterfly upswing mix. I pick it by accident, then I accidentally
put it on maniac. What the hell? I wasn't in the mood for a cata. I got four cata's
on my belt. I accidentally put on a cata. Auto fail within, I don't know, 30 seconds.
thirty seconds
waste my entire
fifty seconds
eight
still
butterfly upswing mix okay
all righty
a page from the book of rob
p0k3smot42o0
Oh, you made me forget what I was going to say!
Angel, you got any FUs of the Week?
I had one, but he took it.
You want me to go with somebody else and come back?
Yeah, sure.
Alright, Stressa, give me your FUs of the Week.
Wow, interesting list for me today.
Which kind of goes against the usual.
First and foremost, the parents still need a serious...
Well, I'll let you fill it in however you like, okay?
My mom is still pissing me off to no end. My dad, well, he still needs a lesson in pulling his head out of his ass, but that's a side issue.
I want to send out an F.U. to my ex. She's been totally pissing me off lately. She sent me this Dear John-like email and hasn't said a word to me since.
well what the hell next on the list what life and the general ideals that some
people they've got all their I see shit they don't like giving people well you
You know what? Big steel dildo for you. Right up the ass.
Got that. That's the impression he and I didn't want to think of.
Anyways, I think I'm about done.
All right. Allergies must die.
We ready for Angel? Did you remember?
Alright, go to Loki, because he thought of another one.
Um, this is just a really short one, unlike the other ones.
F you to the Ralphs that we went to last night, because they were out of three important things.
One, large boxes of Bagel Bites.
Two, Maxim Magazine.
And three, PSM.
All the things I wanted from the Ralphs that they didn't have, so F you to the Ralphs.
That's it.
In favor of the Ralph's they have some money they have some money and chocolate whipped cream. Yes, ready with chocolate ready with chocolate with it
All right, I'm gonna run through the chat room FUs. We'll come back to angels. She thinks they're hers. Okay
On with the chat room FUs
It's really a F you to having to come home on my birthday and missing orange lounge that day
well, that's okay because we do rebroadcast every Monday night and
Supposedly that I heard a rumor we do them on Thursday afternoons to when it actually works
But it hasn't for like the past month, so it's always been like 15 minutes late or some shit
So Thursdays at 2 we try to do them, but Mondays at 7 it always happens, so you can always catch up on orange limes that way
Black web fuck power outages one messed up on my clocks last night fuck my video card
I can play online games at the best pings
But the shittiest frame rates Loki you better keep your mouth shut on that fuck the timing about my car
It needs to be replaced and will cost near $800 that kept me from rearing my car up to Davis this quarter
Oh yeah, and fuck the city of Davis, too. Fuck the owner of TapX that refuses, and it got cut off.
Silly Mac. I'm guessing he refuses to turn up Macs or something like that.
And, uh, yeah, he's reminding me I need to make an announcement, which I will do.
And, um...
Okay...
no styling says I want to say my fuck you of the week is or to script it sucks
and doesn't work like it's supposed to dot dot typical no style in English
there now it's beautiful a stapler X keeps it simple a big F you to garbage
day amen garbage they suck you need a pushpin oh yes I need a pushpin I don't
think I have any pushpins or do you have any after use of the wheat jumper yeah
The people who don't have push pins.
Sorry? Is there, there might be some over there.
See if there's a push pin over on Brian's desk.
Underneath the cookies of doom or in the little jar.
See if there's, see if there's some push pins over there.
Matchboard.
I'm sorry?
Wait, he said garbage.
I don't count people saying it in chat room. I don't count people saying it.
I don't count it when people say slut in the chat room.
I just spent an awesome 27 hours with my best friend Owen, and also fuck school tomorrow
even though I'd rather be at school than being lazy doing nothing at home.
Fuck people who are happy!
He didn't say that, I did.
Slinky!
Fuck school and trends!
school really badly for having to go back tomorrow
u s f e b says but you too
shit nothing just
to say fuck you i just wanted to say slides let's let's let's let's let's
the power of the school cuz after a break i don't want to go back if you
to Fox for delaying 24 for three weeks. Hey, man, fuck Fox. F you to people who don't like
the song Bag, because I love that song. And, uh, Sluts. I hate our chat room. I hate them
so much. No, I'm just kidding. I love you guys. Muhimer. I'm not saying that first word.
And I have to check the mailbag, because his FUs are there. JB says F you to doing two
projects at the last minute. Whose fault is that, Mr. Man? All right. Those are all the
lovely FUs of the week. Oh, Jamie got another one. I hope it's not about my bathroom.
I say fuck you to cheese, thank you.
Okay. Angel, did she get yours? Oh, yes she did. Okay, here we go.
I thought so. Fuck co-workers who forget to come in at the time that they are scheduled because she thought she was supposed to come in at 4 and she was scheduled for 1.30 and I was supposed to leave at 2.
too. FUCK YOU!
Yes, and fuck my boss for trying to kill me with Pepper!
Tried to kill you with Pepper? How is that possible?
She was making sandwiches, and I was bending down to get the tomatoes out of the cooler, and
yeah, um, Pepper got in my nose. You bastard.
Does Brad have any FUs in the week?
the
what is it
we're all sweet thank you
okay not really it's kinda kind of you have to keep for making us run away from
golf and though we love him for it because india kick ass
that's not a few has a group like you don't want to go off and
I don't want to fuck them, they have AIDS.
Alright.
Those are the lovely FUs of the week. They suck because they broke Speed Demon and wouldn't fix it, those bastards.
Everything else is broken there, why not? Slinky says FU to people who jam seven quarters
and break the coin slot for Max 2. That does suck.
That's like the girl putting in her twelve tokens all at once.
They go stupid.
nephew to school. We don't want to go back. We will never want to go back. It's Christmas
vacation time.
I don't have to go to school.
I don't have to go to school either. Ha! Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
I have to go to work though.
At least I'm not one of those corporate whore types.
Hey, I can surf the internet at work.
Me too. He he.
Hey, I download 500 megs worth of sim files every day, so ha. Oh, I got a late one. I
I got a late one. It's from a new person in our chat room, so say hello to the new person.
It better come late than never.
This new person was asking about DDR in Auburn, by the way. Where the hell is there a machine up there, Brad?
Second mix.
Okay, they used to have a third mix at the, uh, some Pizza Express. It's not there, I hear.
But there is a second mix. Probably the only one in all of California.
I wanna play!
It's in the, um, signature theaters, and the volume is all the way down. So try playing BeatMania with no sound. It's pretty fun.
fun.
Anyway, Tadpole says, I want to say, fuck you, to my grandma, for making me turn the
volume down solo. I can't hardly hear anything. Fuck you to Pizza Express for not having DDR
anymore. And a great big fuck you to gas stations for gas being so damn expensive. Ooh, even
that?
Yeah.
Fuck gas.
So I don't try.
Oh.
Treadrag. Treadrag.
i guess that that one about uh... the seven points in the max two is actually
from when they somehow missed it because uh...
he doesn't count
i don't know
no i had it on the
c i thought this thing was for both of those of us
whatever anyway who cares
moving on
that's all of our if he's the way those beautiful wasn't
are we going to another
we want to talk
talk more about
titty our orders let's talk to our our guests that we don't have here on the
show very much. Like, ever. Let's talk to Stress on DDR Angel.
Ugh, Loki. I just want to make a comment. I like that fort. That fort was cool.
Yes, yes. I live up in the boondocks, up in northern...well, I'm out there. If you know
where Santa Rosa is, you're likely to find me there. The fort is cool. I wish I could
take a trip out there. The fort is damn sexy.
We don't know if people live there, because we do see smoke every occasionally, but nobody
ever really checks it out.
Go figure.
Could it be those big graffiti signs that say, keep out of the fort?
Very well possible.
Of course, you know, we should still make that image for Jamie, the Jamie New World
Order, beginning in the fort.
Let's start my own cult, we'll move into a compound.
Woot.
Well, it actually might be considered a dark black forest, but of course Jamie will have
the interesting opportunity to meet said forest.
Be the army of Stoics, and I will have a dark black forest because I don't particularly
care for that song.
overplayed but I want I want my own compound where I can make people I want
to recruit stupid people in this compound and then make them die face
first in the pool of jello I say we all quit our jobs and move into the fort yes
we must move into the fort orange lounge live from the fort next week all right
so there's the fort how are you doing angel we haven't heard much from you
Why did you start playing DDR? What got you into DDR? Was it the flashing seizure lights or the music?
The truth or other?
Other. We never tell the truth in the show.
I don't know.
Alright, so most of us don't know why we play DDR.
I got conned into it.
You got conned into it. Good answer.
And then I couldn't stop. And I still haven't stopped.
It's an STD all of its own.
Is DDR a disease? Maybe it is.
It's an addiction.
It's an addiction and I need help.
Unfortunately, they don't have a 12-step program for this yet.
And they're not going to, because whoever tries to start one, I'll kill.
It's an addiction like crack, cocaine, and alcohol, and then Longerburger baskets and things like that.
It's an addiction that's good for you.
Vanilla crack. Vanilla crack!
Propel.
Hi, my name is the 23rd Magus and I'm a Romani addict.
Get me a gun.
Isn't this the point where we're supposed to clap or do something?
Isn't the point where someone's supposed to go,
Hi, Magus!
There we go!
Gee, I'm feeling better now.
You know what? I think that it's really...
The Space Aliens came and invented the Bimani series, no, it was Tran's race.
This is the great space Kog'Al Tran came on her flying saucer with her cat and her snowmobile
and decided to make us all Bimani addicts.
Ooh, the snowblower of doom.
You haven't seen the video, watch the video for some reason.
This is DDR, not the last Starfighter.
It is like that, see, they're going to make us into an incredible race of rhythm-dancing
And at the last war, at the end of the world, we're all going to have to dance off against the aliens.
That would work, except for one thing. We're not Asian.
Oh, exactly.
But I am.
Yeah, exactly. See, we kill any deaths to the kneecaps.
Hey, I may be honky with no reason, but there are some Asians here who can help.
I don't know. If you count maybe about 150 years back, I could qualify.
Late fuck you to pizza for being so damn yummy and good that I eat it all and I get fat in my arteries and I die.
Ugh!
Yay, Dad!
Propelico! Ugh!
Yeah, anyways, as far as the beginning of my Bomani DDR-type addiction, it was because of Angel!
It was she who conned me into it, and ever since, I don't quite know what's become of me.
Yes, but you have gone from one step to five, all in one day!
Have a murder cookie!
They're death-orific!
Yes, cookie! Death cookie!
I'm really scared.
For the people who aren't seeing these, we have holiday Oreos.
They can't call them Christmas Oreos because it's not politically correct.
So they're holiday Oreos, with red filling.
And they're red, like they're stained with blood.
Like a tampon.
Now they're menstrual cookies!
We'll call it mensios.
That's disgusting.
It tastes like a cycle.
I feel bad because I forgot to check the mailbag for the FUs of the week.
There was one sitting in there so I've got to do it.
You can't always send an email though if you want.
You want to hear more? How about the tax on you wouldn't let me play for anyone else, okay? All right? Oh?
Wait he requested a song for ZF you should I give it to him?
No, I never let people have their requested songs so deal
All right, I'll be nice because only because we forgot okay
Muhaimer
Muhaimer says yay for drunk parents and their friends making drunk eat the snowman outside my house on New Year's Eve by
Decorating him with beer noisemakers in the hat
That is the winner!
That is the best FU I think I've ever read on this show.
Look at the eventually drunk squirrels running around.
That was worth going back to the FU segment for right there.
Drunky the snowman.
I want to make one.
Now featured on DTRPC.
Stressa is a dirty cowgirl!
I'm a little girl
You dare cheated some girls
Haha
the
i think square is top of
will shape the world
you know you have to show you the shirts
i'm gonna show you the shirts that uh... jamie and i were to put the
provides our own
well you want to get a surprise
yes the pressure of the pressure of the state is
uh... working ok we are more
And fuck websites for not having PS2s, DDR Max, MP3s.
Damn it, I want them badly, so I can jam to them in my own unique and embarrassing
style. Fuck me, I can't spell.
Um, actually...
Actually, it's DDRUK.com, but they're not there anymore, so...
Soon to be my new site, Leech from Loki 2.0. It's coming up in a week or two.
You can look forward to Leech from Loki. LFL 2.0.
no it's going to be will be here for food dot net slash lease from loki
uh... if you want to send us an email if you want to send his nephew if you want
to send us a comment a question
hey we always are accepting i'd like to money visit especially tonight we've got
so god damn many people in studio
if you ask us all a question
send us an email listed on the orange lounge radio at yahoo dot com i'm not
taking over the chat room just email
and many send us an email to our country dot com with something you want to ask
everybody please serious agrees only i'm negative
13.62 my bank account so if you do want to send money
i have a paypal account set up it's nightmare underscore hunter at yahoo dot
com
uh... feel free to add to it if you want
because i need cash
uh... thank you
i'll give you a dollar
so comments suggestions questions and marriage proposals all accepted at
orange country and i sent money
i accept bribes
i think we're finally going to get to a break
an hour into the show we need to break the difference was like we were a break
stuff
breakdown
we're in a great deal of late
let me tell them that we'll play it
the right is that we're going to break like that
too much to use may be asian
eighty and
email one more time it's orange lounge radio that's all one word at yahoo dot
com
let orange lounge radio dot orange lounge
speaking English
here is
Let's speak English fun. Oh, what's Loki's email? It's nightmare underscore hunter at yahoo.com
That's Loki's email. Give him money and then give him money. I think somebody's gonna send you money
All right, I need what do you what do you do if you get cash what are you gonna do for us?
That's what the chat room wants to know
For you
Fucking sim say 2,000 sim files on it. What more do you want? Will you show us your boobs?
Oops.
Don't you have to have something to show in order to show it?
No, then we take money away.
Alright, we're going to go to a break.
We'll be back after some happy fun joy songs.
Happy, happy JoJo!
State of mind, and I'm here to talk to you
Space man, state of mind, break me away
Instead of flying to the Milky Way
Space man, state of mind, waiting for you
Instead of flying, waiting to the blue
Take me out tonight, another star so bright
I wanna see your rocket
Flying to the space, to a far galactic place
Know how to rock it
Flying out to the part that's old
Fighting all alone
Boy have I got a dream for you
When you're coming back home
Bait man, bait man, take me away
And then fly into the milky way
Bait man, bait man, waiting for you
And fly away to the moon
Nandandira tari...
You are my favorite!
What you gonna say if I ask you to get outplay with your ammunition?
Flying by the wall like you've never seen before
It's time for addition
Time for addition
Flying out to the combat zone
Fighting all along
What have I got to see for you
When you're coming back home?
Bait man, bait man, take me away
Let's fly into the Milky Way
Bait man, bait man, waiting for you
three... Normal
Bait man, bait man, take me away and let's fly into a milky way
Bait man, bait man, waiting for you, and let's fly away into the blue
Bateman, Bateman, waiting for you, and then fly away to the moon.
Bateman, Bateman, Bateman, Bateman.
The following bit of randomness has been brought to you by Orange Lounge Radio.
Dateline, the Muppet Show.
It has been reported just moments ago that a large, heavy object was dropped from the ceiling.
Further developments will...
Hey, any balls down there?
About the biggest bird you've ever seen, Diggleberry!
talk about. I don't have anything to do with it.
Uh, do I have to do everything? Oh yeah, let's hear a sim update before we get to list list.
And we'll do a list list. Let's do a sim update.
Uh, sim update. Finally, we can stop playing DDRPC if you haven't done it yet because they
released the last stupid character set. Not that anyone even fucking cares anymore because
I don't. The game sucks ass. But if you care, it's some stupid princess and some prince
guy, and I don't care, it's crap. Whatever. Enjoy. So, they're there for your enjoyment.
Um, aside from that, Turning Mix 3 is wrapping up. Tomorrow should have the results, um, they're...
I'd have to say this has been the worst run tournament I've ever seen, and they should all burn in hell for it, and I'm gonna do better for it.
I'm gonna do a better tournament than they will, because I own them!
Speaking of which, how did Make Edit Get Porn go?
Well, you know what? Some people just don't understand this concept of deadlines.
So you know what? The people sent me edits to get porn. The people didn't. Go fuck themselves!
You should give me porn anyway.
I know, I have plenty of porn to give away. I mean, people don't like porn in my work for some reason. I don't know why.
They just put it in the coffee room and I take it.
I think that porn is funny.
But, yeah. Porn blows. Get it?
How's that?
But yeah, so that's what's going on.
As I mentioned slightly earlier, there's going to be a
Leech from Loki 2.0s coming up, because I got web hosting
thanks to DDR Alama from DDR Mania X and Chris Stanford
from the Step Mania site.
They're giving me web hosting with unlimited space and
limited bandwidth, so I get to put whatever the fuck I want
on there.
I guess they're trying to challenge me to crash the
boards or something, but whatever.
So I'm going to put all my SIM files on there slowly in
theme packs.
We're going to do interviews with step file makers and that
kind of thing.
So, that's pretty much what's coming up. Right now I'm just redoing the design of the site because I have to try to figure out how the fuck to sort 2100 step files. So, that'll be fun.
Aside from that, do check out bmonistyle. They're putting up all week long the new DDR Extreme DWIs. In fact, they're the thing for the Legend of Max and Paranoid Survivor samples.
So, definitely check them out if you haven't yet for Sim Files and that kind of thing.
Really aside from that, not too much going on other than, you know, DDR Extreme coming
out and, you know, us finding out more about it, but looks like we pretty much, you know,
we know what songs are going to be hidden in there.
And I have a continued little rant, sort of.
Basically this is a fuck you to everyone that said I was wrong about Sakura being in fucking
DDR Extreme because I knew I called it a long ass time ago and all of you naysayers can
burn in hell
so that's all
okay i i went back to over the mailbag to uh... look at some
back to see if we've got
you do
i would see if we got an email and guess what we do we have a question
from uh... so cal kicks of course
It's a question specifically for Loki.
Can I have the Robotech Macross Saga DVDs?
Well, if I had them to give, then yeah.
But I don't, so no.
Can I have some more porn?
I have titles I like.
All I get is the stupid Playboy shit, and so, you know, I pretty much gave you all the,
well, some of the new stuff.
I guess, yeah.
You know, whatever I have.
He says at the end, PayPal may come if two or more of the requests are met.
I don't know how two or more is possible, because you only made two requests!
You're being edumacated, apparently.
You know what, if he actually came up here to visit us instead, he could come to my house
and not only watch all the Robotech stuff, but watch all the Macross stuff, because I
happen to have the whole box set.
And Final Fuck X, which I got a copy of last night.
Your HP tastes good!
Did it turn out alright?
Yeah, it was cool. It's just VCD quality, whatever, you know.
It's the same as the other VCDs I have from Japan. They're porn, they're censored.
Censored porn sucks. It's like made-for-TV porn.
Alright, I'm opening up another email here.
Dark Tetsuya wants to know, when will you put more of an SMA into rotation?
I do have a request for one song. I want to hear Red Hot. It's really cool.
Yeah, all of mine's on MP3s are porn.
All of, oh wow.
Whoa!
Was that like that letter bit?
All of my MP3s, by the way, because I've had all the Vanessa May stuff, they're gone, because
guess what?
My hard drive broke, so you send me red hot, it'll make it into rotation.
All right, we'll get red hot into rotation.
I need a noose!
Damn you, you Vanessa May damn whore, all right.
Jamie made a noose.
She has a noose on her neck, and I have a noose on my neck.
This is weird.
Okay.
Moving on.
Hey, dual mic penetration.
i want my news back
okay
uh...
let's talk about some show news things that have happened in the past uh...
coming in the future the show
uh... voters
you said coming
you slide
i'm sorry to know what did you say that you're a slight
I love you all night long if you let me sing for you
From the outside coming in...
Your eyes still work. Your eyes still work.
This is...
You made me watch Showgirls.
I did make her watch Showgirls.
That's a good movie.
For me to poop on!
I never actually thought it would be something like this.
But, when you enter this...
Whoa! Hello!
I just got a little show there.
When did the studio turn into a gay nightclub? Stop that!
He almost gave me a lap dance.
The weird part about it is, I was still standing.
News!
Why don't you sit on this?
And now he's been tied.
I'm sorry, you had a thought?
No, no, it was coming into this from the outside.
Yeah, I said it again.
Look who's the dirty slut now!
Maybe coming to be our worst nightmare.
Hi, I have news. I wanted to get to Orange Lounge News because this is actually really
big news. We've made our first bestest friends on the interweb and those buddies of ours
I saw your tummy. I'm blind. Our new bestest friends on the interweb are located at east
eastofosaka.net
and jamie had to do a lot of that to get this to happen, no I'm kidding, I'm kidding
37? In a what?
Trying not to suck any dick out of the parking lot
Hey, you get back here
all right uh... yes eastofosaka.net, they're our friends, our bestest friends on the net
and uh... they've led us onto their forums so if you thought the orange lounge forums
sucked on uh... the little
free thing we had then fine
We've got cool forums now because they're a part of the East of Osaka.net forums, so
my avatar owns all of you.
I still think mine's cooler because I actually spent a long time working on it.
Of course, it's the same one I use on DDR Freak and on Step Squad board, and I would
use it on Sack of Imani, but we can't have them.
We have one thing to say.
You don't love us!
What the hell was that for?
We love you!
Yay!
You guys all ran away.
Cause you said you loved them and then you didn't say us and we visited you.
I love everybody.
Listen you guys, I'm a huge slut, okay?
I love you!
I'm getting a lap dance, three of them, all at once.
I'm gonna go hide in the corner.
Anyway, the link to the new boards are being posted in the chatroom now, or if you are
too lazy to follow the links in the chatroom, just go to our site, orangelounge.skie.cx,
click on forums, and it takes you to the new forums.
And if you don't, we'll kick your ass.
You'll lose our love.
And the forum crew.
I don't want to lose your love tonight.
Okay.
So definitely check out the new forums.
And next week, next Saturday, is a pretty nifty tournament going on in Fremont.
And I think this is the first time, besides Shaft, that all three hosts will be attending
a tournament together.
All three of us.
Am I correct?
One of them might be competing.
Yeah.
Oh, you're going to compete?
I'm at GPA.
Oh, very cool.
You're not going to compete, Logie.
Okay, we'll go cheer Jamie on.
I may or may not do PA.
We're all going to be going to Fremont to check out the tournament there.
It's at some pizza place.
I don't remember the details because I'm lazy, but DCV's in the chat room.
How does it matter? They have pizza there.
That's all that matters.
DCB can post a link for all of you to go visit if you want to come to the tournament.
We'll be there doing interviews and stuff.
And DCB wants you to pre-reg.
If I have the money to a man, I'm getting keyboard mania tomorrow, so my money's kind of tight.
Alright.
I'll bring the bat though.
Oh, we need to get new bats to have everyone sign.
Okay, that's a good idea. We'll go get new bats.
I've got to go buy a new orange bat because everyone signed them at the Mountain Mike's tourney, so I have to buy a new bat.
Yeah.
Alright, there's the link to the page right there.
Rabbeats.com slash tilde killer pals slash Fremont2.html.
You'll never remember that so just click the link in the chatroom.
Internet.
The interweb!
You're showing us pictures of, oh it's the ghetto DDR extreme 8th mix sign from Stockton
Golf Land.
Nice.
Very nice.
Speaking of which, we got to check out the nice ghetto max 2 that they're giving away
in the cyber returning.
Oh my lord.
I hope they clean it up. I hope they clean it up a little.
I'm looking forward to that tourney a lot.
It's a machine, but there's not much of a machine.
We've got another question in our inbox.
I want to answer it.
Do you like big cock?
It's a rude question. I don't think you'll want to answer that one.
I do, because no one else loves the cock.
We'll have a real guest.
Wait! That's the question!
They want to send that they want no one orange light no style and wants to know when the orange line was gonna have a real
guest
Fuck you no style. I will show my at my hey
Board starts coming over here. I'm all for it. Okay
Hey, you know, I think somebody just want to have their name right on the radio. Well
You had something you wanna say Jimmy are you gonna you're not gonna go jump off a bridge with that thing around the neck
Are you big cock?
Is that going to be our special guest, or big black cock?
Alright, tonight's special guest, my cock. Say hello.
Is your cock black?
I can get a sharpie.
Rob's going to have like little arrows tattooed.
Just dip it in hot fudge or something.
That is a big brown cock. A very hot cock.
I don't know if I like this show reverting to discussions about my cock, but in a way it's kind of cool
You brought it up my friend
And I'm bringing it up right now
It got all over me
And Rob was delivered a sharpie
Put it away! Put it on! Put it on!
What do you do to keep that thing in your pants?
I pander my dick.
Is there a difference?
I'd like to see a freestyle routine where somebody just whips their cock out at the end.
What song would that be good to?
Blow My Whistle.
No, we need to do a freestyle routine where we throw dildos into the crowd.
Or those penis-shaped chocolates.
That'll be on paranoia or something. You can just flip your cock out and...
When is somebody going to do a routine where they whip their cock out at the end? Come on.
I'm surprised all you comedians out there like to play DDR. Nobody's done it yet. Come on.
Some women play DDR2, let's see some tits. Let's see a topless DDR routine, come on.
Wait, they have to be good looking. We must make sure there's no food around either.
It's bad enough, those female freestylers who think that they have a good routine just by grabbing their boobs.
You know, that sucks. That's not good freestyle.
What are you talking about, that's not good freestyle?
It's not good freestyle. It's called stripping, not freestyle.
It's good Maxim magazine, bad freestyle.
It's called maybe slut style.
Hey, I had a check mark on all of my judging little forms there. Grab boobs then, okay?
I had to make a provision when doing the rules for shaft, no boob grabbing.
Because that doesn't make a good routine.
Okay, that's getting into one of my pet peeves of DDR freestyling.
Ooh, let's hear it.
Don't grab your boobs!
What if I...
I'm sorry.
What if I grab my boobs?
Is that okay?
Okay, wait, wait.
What if Alan Rickman got on stage and started whipping out his cock?
Okay, first of all, he wouldn't.
Okay.
But you know what?
I don't see the male freestylers grabbing their dick or anything while they're freestyling.
I will enter a routine and I will grab my dick during the routine.
I'll make you happy if I do my suggestion.
I wonder why you suggest it?
I'm using it as an example, okay?
Oh, okay.
You know I'm a crazy bastard, I'll do it.
I can't freestyle, so at least I'll get a laugh when I grab my dick, you know?
Hey, it's a whole new meaning to PA.
Penis attack.
Awesome.
Hey, Evan.
Every day with Rob is a penis attack.
I figured out how to make one.
Oh great, we have a double-ended noose. How kinky.
That's for the goth sex pervert, right?
And it's black. Does it glow in the dark?
You tell me it's yours.
You gotta make it all flopsy.
Get your own goddamn mic. Hold on a second, hold on a second. Here we go.
Here's the stupidest thing to do on radio. Watch this.
Okay, I'm going to use the mic and I'm going to make it funny.
Are you ready? Okay, here's a gay man's...
Here's a lesbian's nightmare.
Here's a gay man's nightmare.
There you go.
Nobody in the audience.
That was very intentional.
Now, Rob, try to describe that.
I had a question for you, Evan.
Evan, why do you think nobody's whipped their cock out at the end of a DDR routine yet?
Because we haven't seen the private DDR routines that Brad and Irene have.
Late at night.
And you know what, hold on a second, before Brad says anything, I do want to make this parting comment.
Although I haven't seen it, I have heard that Irene's cock is quite nice.
Oh boy.
Yeah.
We're going to take a quick break at this point because we've reached our cot quotient
of the show and we're going to come back and we're going to play the match game live in
studio.
We're going to do listless first?
Yeah.
Let's list the match game.
We always do match game.
We got to do the cage match some way too.
Yeah, we have to do cage match.
Let's do the cage match now.
Okay.
All right.
Fuck the break.
We'll do the cage match.
All right.
Here we go.
Let them break.
going to talk about last or two weeks ago we didn't do a cage match last week
correct no no I didn't so last week two weeks ago in the orange lounge cage
match where we pit songs against each other because we like to we had a Yumi
Hamasaki win with connected in a very very very close vote I believe it came
down to a game of rock-paper-scissors fuck all of you for not voting for
Knight Rider bitches yeah Knight Rider was the shit but unfortunately it lost
fuck me for being bad at rock, paper, scissors
alright so uh...
the first
the first time you're able to vote for one of three songs
in the cage match, you can vote for last week's winner
i'm engrish today
here's last week's winner, two weeks ago's winner, this is how Yumi Hamasaki
with connected. Here's a little clip. Alright, that's the Yumi Hamasaki with connected. That's
the first one you can vote for us last week's winner
this first pick in the cage matches the group called bond
with the song called way go to play out of this they have this for us
it's short cool and way go
all right here it is this first song in the cage matching before this week
seconds i'm sorry you go for you and start hearing about this is bond with
Fuego.
I love that song. Anything with the name Fuego.
Because I like fire.
That was a pretty neat song. What did you all think of that?
Let's go around the room. What did you think of it and judge it on a scale of 1 to 10?
It's awesome 10.
I think Fuego tastes pretty good, that soda.
Oh, Fuego. That is a really cool song. Somebody should make steps for that for DDR.
Loki?
Don't look at me. I'm not going to friggin' make that.
I give it an eight because it just sounds like Vanessa Mae.
I'll do it. Seven. Good.
Uh, personally I think that deserves an eight.
I don't know. I'm also very partial to Fire.
It does wonderful things for me.
Angel says 9.5.
She says I instead.
Uh, I agree. It's Vanessa Mae the sequel, but it's still pretty cool, so I give it a nine.
Alright, moving on, the next song. Loki, tell us about this one. Now we're only going to play part of this song, correct?
Yeah, because it's like an eight minute long song.
So we're going to play a few minutes of it, so tell us about this song.
This song was entered in Turning Mix 3, the cut-down version of it was.
This is an mp3.com artist, which should be going mainstream, I hope, soon.
It's AirBass with their song Spin.
And after this is over you can vote for this one if you want. This is airbase with spin
Oh
Alright, that was Air Bass for the song called Spin, that wasn't even the whole thing.
So, that's the end of the Cade Smash.
I meant for Hollick.
Three songs.
You have Yumi Hamasaki, last week's winner was Connected, Bond with Fuego, and Airbase
with Spin.
Uh, you guys can vote now, send your votes over a private message to Skye, and while
you send your votes, let's hear the verdicts on Airbase.
Drop.
What?
Yes.
Hi.
It was repetitive.
He thought it was repetitive.
Scale of one to ten.
I would probably play that in the background while I'm working on banners and stuff and
in my artwork, so I give it a seven and a half.
Seven and a half, alright.
It was just more dancey stuff.
There's nothing wrong with dancey stuff, it's supposed to be long because it's a twelve
inch mix, so you can mix it into other shit, but anyway.
Twelve inches.
Shut up!
I can't even talk.
Anyways, um, I like it, it was one of my favorite entries in Fraternity Mix 3, I wish I could
have had a chance to cut it down so that it'd be less repetitive. But anyways, I'd give
it a 10.
Alright. Brad, what did you think of Airbase's spin?
Cool, but they should have DDR sized, it would have been great. So, I'd give it a 7 as it
is.
Alright. Dave, what you heard of it? By the way, hi.
Yeah, hi! I just kinda came in and took pictures, but I guess I was kind of listening, so I give it a seven and a half.
You're full of shit.
Magus!
Blade ten, fear out.
Stressa.
Well, that was easily said. Um, I actually am quite fond of this track, I think.
Wow, such spirit. Um, I'm gonna give that an eight.
Uh oh, I'm tied.
Angel, what do you think?
you think? I said, um, time. Um, it's kind of a bullet thing. Uh, I'll give it an 8,
sorry. Alright, an 8. Uh, I liked it, it was cool, except I didn't like that re-re-re
part, and uh, Bond was better, so, uh, Fuego was better, so I can't rank it higher than
that, so I'll give it an 8. Alright, so, the votes are coming in right now, we'll
I need to send you all He-Man likes big butts.
I'll find that file and send it to you later.
So you can vote for Ayumi, you can vote for Bond with Fuego, or you can vote for Airbase.
Rob's good at typing with one hand.
I'm typing with one hand.
I wonder how you got so good, Rob.
Okay, so we'll tally those votes during the next segment.
Ladies and gentlemen, it's time once again for...
The Orange Lounge Match Game.
Now tonight is special, usually we let the chat room play along, and we do encourage them to play along, however we have so many people in the studio tonight, we're going to have live contestants, so we can get live reactions and everything like that.
So, if you guys want to play along in the chat room, you can send us your suggestions, that would be great.
But in the meantime, our contestants for tonight will be our out of town visitors, say hello to Stressa, and DDR Angel will be your contestants tonight.
Hello again.
Great!
Alrighty, look.
all right so they will be competing against each other for what what's the
prize tonight a ride home black cock a big a big black cock is what you're
playing for tonight and petting rights
fair enough the prize is a handful of Jamie's nuts they can't have my nuts I
need those
and in the crack
let's go out and quickly introduced to celebrities celebrity number one start
in the back
three and once again was a
celebrity number two
day
delivery delivery
something that was pretty cool
the delivery number four stop eating my night
celebrity over five
i've got lost
celebrity number six
all right there we go
defeat
first of all but i'm unfortunate what we're gonna have to do while we uh...
com player answers may have to ask her are just leave the room
get all your answers and will send somebody to come get you
no yes yes please isolation boost
because we're basically
i think to speed this up a little
isolation boost
group there
was uh...
to remove something
The boot, the boot equals Animal Crossing, goodbye!
Alright, alright, here we go.
Alright, here's the first question, here's the first question.
Shut the door a little bit. Okay, here we go, here's the first question.
First question.
Sammy the snacker loves to eat and play DDR at the same time.
When the arcade manager came over, he took one look at the pad and said,
Damn it, Sammy! You got blank all over the dance pad!
Sammy the snacker loves to eat and play DDR at the same time.
When the arcade manager came by, he took one look at the pad and said,
Damn it, Sammy! You got blank all over the dance pad!
I can't read my writing because you gave me a fucking highlighter.
Here, can we find him another pen?
Here, we can share a few pens.
Chat room suggesting things like salty slut nuts.
Oh, I'm sorry, that was the...
They tricked me, god damn them.
They got me to say slut.
back to the match game. Damn it Sammy, you got blank all over the dance pad.
Rob, the word of the day is slut.
Alright, everybody locked in? We all ready? Everybody's in?
Dave, you in? Alright, alright, bring him in, bring him in.
We could use this opportunity to talk shit about him.
When the arcade manager came over, he took one look at the pad and said,
Damn it, Sammy, you got blank all over the dance pad.
Stressa, you're first, because you're pointing at the other person.
I love that, volunteering.
I would like to think that the manager said, Damn it, Sammy, you got animal cookie heads all over the dance pad.
Cool!
Animal cookie heads, all right.
Stressa's answer is animal cookie heads.
Let's hear from Angel.
angel
dammit sammy you got
vanilla crack
vanilla crack all over the dance pad all right let's go around and see what the answers are
jamie dammit sammy you got pussy pussy all over the dance pad i'm sorry that is not a
match pussy is not a match
i like this one
lowkey
snack on that and play ddr
dammit sammy you got
your salty nuts
all over the dance pad. Oh, very good. You matched with someone in the chat room, but
not close enough. Dave, dammit. Dammit, Dave, you got cheesy poops. Cheesy poops all over
the dance pad. I'm sorry, not a match. Not a match. Brad, dammit, Sammy, you got haggis.
Haggis. Hard-hardened harbinger of haggis. Haggis all over the dance pad. Bummer, not
Not a match.
Overstuffed Scottish haggis.
No, it was Spanish haggis.
I'm sorry.
I said the line around my back.
Alright.
Magus.
Damn it, Sammy.
You got...
Propel.
Propel!
All over the dance pad.
Ah, very close.
Okay.
And I said, you know, because thinking that Sammy the snacker is going to be really excited
to be playing DDR and eating at the same time, I said, Damn it, Sammy, you got jizz all over
to the dance mat.
Damn it, I was going to say that!
We do not have a match.
Which is half a match with Salty Nuts.
Alright.
Ice Slice Boost.
It's called...
You know, Rob.
Rob.
It sort of went with pussy because I was thinking Sami might be a girl.
Oh, very good.
Or unless you know Sami just happened to be, you know, snacking away Rob.
Yes.
Irene would like to say Maddie's in the igloo.
Oh, Maddie's in the igloo.
Thank you. Go whacker with a bug man. Tell her to try to get the dummy.
All right, isolation boost, isolation boost.
Next question, here we go.
Scores all tied up, zero apiece.
Ralphie the Raver... are they gone?
Okay, yes, they're gone.
Ralphie the Raver...
I'm sorry, Ralphie the Raver
loves to play Para Para Paradise more than anything in the whole world.
his favorite thing to do on the machine is to blank
ralphie the reyvar loves to play
para para paradise more than anything in the whole world
his favorite thing to do on the machine is to blank
I have mine. Wait, wait, wait, wait. We only have three questions tonight, by the way.
I'm afraid I'm kind of going with a logical answer here. I don't know.
Ralphie the Rayvar loves to play Para Para Paradise more than anything in the whole world.
His favorite thing to do on the machine is to blink.
in? Everybody in? In or out? Alright, get the contestants. Condom Attestants. Hi. You're
not our contestant. Hi, what's up? Oh, Neil's here. What's up, Neil? Can you get the contestants?
Angel, Ralphie the Revar loves to play Para Para Paradise more than anything in the whole
world. His favorite thing to do on the machine is play. Jizz! Jizz! Alright. Jizz. Ralphie
the Ray Barstracer loves to play Para Para Paradise more than anything in the whole world.
His favorite thing to do on the machine is to...
Suggestions, maybe?
I'm not sure.
All right, you've watched people play Para Para Escape.
Yeah?
I think it's something on the sidebar.
Think dirty.
Yeah, think dirty.
Right, they're stroking themselves.
Masturbating? You want to say masturbating?
Your answer is masturbating, all right.
favorite thing to do on the machine is to masturbate okay
we have to use the masturbate i don't know if that's all that
record i would hope that masturbating leads to another
okay
all right so excited he comes all over the screen i don't know
all right while we go around
while we go around and read the answers i think uh... it would be best to uh...
the most appropriate for this question
all right ralphie the ray of our loves to play part of our days more than
His favorite thing to do on the machine is to...
Drop E and hump the coin return.
Bravo, but not a match.
Lowkey, his favorite thing to do on the machine is to...
Swing around his big black cock, close but not a match.
If it was stroke, that would have been a match.
Almost, but not a match.
My answer...
Get a Korean Booty.
Ralphie the Rayvar loves to play Para Para Vardice more than anything in the world.
His favorite thing to do on the machine is to rip out his cock.
I don't know, judges.
Why is cock in such a big font?
Because I like cock.
I think because there was so much mention of cock that was matched up with each of them
to get a half point.
Each of them gets a half point?
Yeah.
Alright, fair enough.
Fair enough.
Half a point each.
Ow!
we're doing it okay okay guests leave
her we're doing a condensed version so just one more question
all right one more
one more question here we go
out you go
already out anyway
last question area half a point each
But here's the next question. Carrie the Camera Whore
I don't have my music. Carrie the Camera Whore loves to take pictures at DDR tournaments
but her collection of turdie pics is never complete
without a picture of blank.
It would be a female. She's a short little Asian girl with paragoons.
Hey, what's up, Evan? How you doing?
Carrie the Camera Whore loves to take pictures at DDR tournaments, but her collection of turny pics is never complete without a picture of blank.
Yes?
What? I didn't finish what I can do.
He just handed me the mic. My God! The pressure! The pressure!
Okay, this is Carrie the Camera Whore?
Yes.
Carrie the Camera Whore! Yes, we all know Carrie, don't we?
That person who either likes to chat with everybody and take all the pictures and keep them for herself,
or says that she's going to upload them to the website any day now?
Oh, I'll upload them tomorrow. I just got them scanned.
Everybody's writing?
Yeah, everybody knows what you're putting. However, you have to actually write it down.
Did you write it down?
In's the rules.
Who's actually matching?
Oh.
Yeah, sure.
Rob's cock.
Without a picture of Rob's cock!
Yes, ladies and gentlemen?
All right.
You need one of those little tiny microscopic lenses.
Ha.
Get the victims.
All right, here come the victims.
It's Ra- I am Ravery.
Carry the camera, whore.
Oh, sorry, I don't want to read it before they get here.
Hello, wait.
Okay, here they come. Here they come. Here I come.
Alright, here's your question. Stressa, you're first up.
Stressa, Carrie the Camera Whore loves to take pictures at DER tournaments,
but her collection of turning picks is never complete without a picture of...
Upskirt shots.
Upskirt shots! Very nice.
Carrie's a lesbian, apparently. Alright.
Carry the camera, horror angel.
Loves...
If you like panty shots, you must go out and get the anime.
Uh, what is it? It's, uh, VR, uh, the, the...
Night Saver? No, it's, uh...
Night Saver?
Go Kaiser?
No, no, no, no, no. VR 40 fresh! VR 40 fresh!
You must get VR 40 fresh, because every other shot is a panty shot.
Upskirt.
You know, it's amazing how many times I have to crawl through tunnels in that.
How dare you? You made me forget the question.
Well, I'll read it to you again.
Carrie the camera whore loves to take pictures at DDR tournaments,
but her collection of tourney pics is never complete without a picture of...
I have to say upskirt shots. I'm sorry.
Upskirt shots. They're both saying upskirt shots.
Does genitalia count as an upskirt shot? Because, like, I'm close.
Why? Because you made me think that way, and that's the first thing I thought of.
Sure it was. Okay, here we go.
And Rob, I'm sure you've worn a skirt before.
Hi, what's up?
Get out!
Alright, here we go.
Starting with Jamie.
Jamie, that camera...
Actually, she's always on the cover of National Geographic.
She's the one washing her clothes in the river.
You know, topless.
I'd like to give my answer.
I'm going to have to modify what, it's pretty much what my answer was going to be.
Instead of her big black cock, it's going to be her big black cock.
Her big black cock. Sorry, not a match.
Dave, her collection of tourney pics is never complete without a picture of...
Two girls humping the secret rendezvous.
Two girls humping the secret rendezvous. Beautiful.
But not a match.
Thank God that didn't go out on air. Unless you want a mic to say that again.
Thank God I wasn't given mental imagery of...
Okay, it happens.
Brad, her collection of tourney pics was
never complete without a picture of Fiona showing off her ass.
Thank you, Brad, for saying everything
we were saying. Her collection of tourney pics was never complete
without a picture of Fiona showing off her ass. Good answer, however, it's not a match.
My answer, did I get everybody else? No. Oh, I'm sorry, Magus. Oh, he's hiding behind me.
I had to kind of go... Well, how's that match? Because the first time I saw Fiona, she was
showing her ass off through her skirt. Oh, okay. Then that's a point. Yay, they get a
point each. All right. All right. I had to go... I have a point and a half each. I had
to go with the longest one. Magus, her collection of turning picks is never complete without
picture of a big black cock a big black cock not a match sorry is there penis
envy going on today or what what where this is all a tribute show the Reuben
no it's just it's all a tribute show the Reuben it's just big black cock dating
get the memo
i'd like to see a big black cock
is she a sweet transvestite moving along
her collection of turning picks is never complete without a picture of
asian penis
i put asian penis
well it's not a big black cock
in fact nevermind
i'm not a you can make that joke yourself about palace too much
talk about the racing we talk about dick too much of the show yes i have your
right to be able to talk about
beautiful
all right
we're gonna come back and i think we're gonna try a list list next
and then we're right into a list
you know remind you we are
and don't forget how do you know what what would you like to have a ground
okay i think it's a good thing we're gonna do a tiebreaker around out
jimmy's connect jimmy's taking over as host because
unfortunately you
my hosting skills
document i such a big black hot
uh...
all right jimmy's coming up with a question right now
okay here we go
the staff of orange
most likes to talk
Okay, the staff of Orange Lounge most likes to talk about blank. That's the tiebreaker?
Yes. All right, here we go.
The staff of Orange Lounge most likes to talk about blank.
All right.
Bring him in, bring him in. All right, everybody in? All right, here we go.
staff of orange lounge most likes to talk about
okay i will take a break this week
with some
orange
talk about
well here it is
uh... angel your first assignment the staff of orange lounge most likes to talk
about
and fifty dollars does
Big black cock! Big black cock, says Angel. Good answer.
Stressa, the staff of Orange Lounge most likes to talk about.
Well, considering the current flow of conversation...
Don't say the same thing. That's not how you break a tie.
That's true. Yeah, it might be true.
Well, I'm going to be out there in left field, and since I don't have much else on my head
at this minute. Propel.
most like to talk about my big black cock. What? That's a half point. So Angel gets another
half point. No, it's a full point, baby. Alright, a full point. It's a full eight point. Angel
leads by two. It's a full foot long of points. Alright. Brad, most likes to talk about dead
babies. Skinny white cunt! That didn't get picked up on the mic in that sound. Skinny
Yeah!
Skinny white cunt!
Skinny white cunt.
What did you call me?
Skinny white cunt!
I thought so.
Oh!
Wait, Fiona's not white.
Oh, was that my outer monologue? I thought that was my inner voice.
Is this white, or pink?
This whole weekend?
Wait, wait, excuse me! Nobody saw this, but I just got hit by the door three times! My ass got hit by the door three times, thank you!
Okay, quick question.
After you go through the door.
Quick, quick question.
Female Asians with big breasts, man-made or myth?
Next time, Jerry, bring it.
I think we should go on to our next answer.
Oh yeah, mine was dead babies, because nobody probably heard that.
Or we forgot, I don't know.
I had to go for the obligatory. Propel!
Yes!
No, you are up by one point, so if I said Propel, we go to another tiebreaker round.
If I said Big Black Cock, Angel's going to win by a lead.
Angel gets a Big Black Cock.
My answer was, on Orange Lounge, we talk about Ted DDR.
Angel wins!
Angel, go get a handful of Jamie's Big Nuts.
That's your prize.
Just get your hand in there.
justice all yes to them all up now with them put it in your mouth
it
you know you want to suck it all come on
michael gogo
all she's getting
you hot for her to handle
he's got a mouthful enough
All right, that's it.
And once again, my nuts are safe for consumption.
We're going to go.
And with that, I think that we have a very appropriate song
here to be playing.
It's going to be called Cramming for College.
So do enjoy.
All right, enjoy.
This is our next break music, because Loki wants to hear it.
This is called Cramming for College.
Yes?
Public announcement.
I think I just pissed myself.
Okay.
You smell funny.
I'm so scared I sold my armor.
All right. I hope you enjoyed the match game. We'll be right back. If you want to send us an email,
OrangeLawnTradioYahoo.com, if you have more questions for us. In the meantime, we have to tabulate the votes.
In the meantime, we've got to tabulate the votes. We'll do that during this break for the cage
match, and we will be right back.
Okay, class. Our final exam will be coming up at the end of this week. Our final exam will be in
big black cocks. The test will be comprised of
twenty percent written,
thirty percent oral,
and fifty percent anal. Any questions?
Professor?
Yes, dear?
Will there be any extra credit?
I am so glad you asked.
Ooh ooh ooh, ooh ooh ooh
I
I'm the king of the game world We said that I can't do
Do you believe in love? Yes, I'm the king of the game world
I'm the king of the game world Do you believe in love?
If you believe in love
Yes, I'm so big in love
I'm not your man anymore
Oh, yes, I'm your power
Da da da
Ooh-ooh-ooh
Don't you think you can't go on?
If you believe in love
You're standing there with your arms unfolded like a eucalyptus care
Even before you glanced at me, I already felt the chemistry
Don't know what it is about you that's got me feelin' right
I each, I once, let you get away, boy, you're a lucky one
I don't need you, cause the truth is, got my hands full of fatties
But I want you, gonna put you at the very, very top of my head
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
You are all I care
I want that, that
I don't need you
Cause the truth is
Got my hands full of love that it is
But I want you, gonna put you at the very, very top of my lip
Yeah, I want you, gonna have you, and that's the way it is
Okay, we'll do this. We'll do Paranoid Survivor from the new DDR Extreme, and then we'll come back and we've got a list list for you guys.
Orange Lounge Radio, will you put your thing down, flip it and reverse it?
back, Orange Lounge Radio, and everybody is furiously working on their list, because we
are going to do a list list. But first, I want to announce the winner of the cage match,
very close by the way, this song won, the other two were tied, and this song had one
vote more than the other two, so it was very close, the winner of this week's cage match
once again, Ayumi Hamasaki with Connected.
How you doing over there, Jamie?
I'm ready to do the listless.
You're having that sad, sad spinster look on your face.
It's because my number three song, I'm trying to imagine, my number three choice, I'm trying
to imagine what it would be like, because we haven't even announced our listless yet,
what it's going to be.
Why don't you tell them?
Well, we're doing one for top song in any other Bimani game that you would like to see in 2DX.
Usually we do it, you know, what we want in DDR, well screw DDR, we want 2DX.
Right, and with Extreme you had a bunch of other Bimani songs crossing into DDR, so Jamie thinks we ought to do it the other way around, put them in 2DX.
In fact, I'm actually erasing my number 3 because I'm going to put in something from another game.
Alright, so if that's the case, then I think we usually, I'll start, I don't use the start, we'll go around, we'll do Jamie last, we'll go around this way.
Oh fine, thank you.
I'm saving the best for last year.
Okay, so I'll start.
My number three on this list of songs from another Bomani game that ought to be in 2DX
that aren't...
Fireball!
I think that song would be funny in 2DX.
I could kind of imagine how it would go.
You know, you can only get so much of the trance and Eurobeat stuff.
I'd like to see something a little funky in 2DX.
So Fireball's my number three pick for what ought to be in 2DX from another Bomani game.
Let's go over to Angel. Your number three choice is... Oh, you only have two so far?
Actually, yes, that song is on it. Angel's got to think of another one? Okay.
You had one? All right. Number three choice.
Uh, Tokyo Already.
Tokyo Already. That's a pretty good one.
It's Eurobeat, and Eurobeat's getting big in 2DX.
Tokyo Already, pretty cool song from Dance Maniacs, right?
All right, Monkey Dance is already in 2DX, dummy.
Stressa, your number three pick.
OK, I know it might sound a little hokey,
but the idea of having Like A Virgin
might be kind of interesting.
Like A Virgin from Parapara.
Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, I'd want it just for that part.
That'd be pretty cool.
Mm-hmm.
Did you already go, Jamie?
We're going around this way.
My number three, badly, is Superstar.
Superstar!
I knew you were going to think about that one.
Superstar. Loki.
This is one of my favorite Dance Maniacs tracks. It's Mind Parasite.
Mind Parasite, interesting choice.
From Dance Maniacs. Jamie, you're number three.
You said you were going... I was going to ask.
Yeah, you are.
I pick On the Jazz.
On the Jazz?
Interesting one.
Why On the Jazz?
Just because it would be fun to play all the sax line in it.
I mean, you think about how San Malete went with all the horn parts.
Yeah?
Interesting choice.
I wouldn't have guessed.
I didn't even think you liked that song.
I do.
I'm kind of surprised you put it.
Okay, cool.
Well, that's cool.
Good for you, Jamie.
All right.
Number two picks.
I'm going to get Hell from Jamie, but I chose Dark Black Forest as my second choice.
Black Forest.
I don't hate the song, it's just overplayed.
I would have to agree with that.
Dark Black Forest should be in 2DX.
Stress out.
My second choice, why?
Because I love the beats.
Boom Boom Dollar.
Oh my god, Boom Boom Dollar in 2DX.
I'm completely sad and pathetic.
Would be fucking hilarious.
Have mercy.
Gee, I thought it was going to be Bumblebee.
That would be fucking funny.
I'm sorry. I give it a point for comic value. Brad!
What? What?
Nothing. Dave was just making a joke.
He said that he was going to burn his PS2 to the ground if that was on.
Then I'd be like, yes, and then I'd take the ashes and let it rise like a phoenix back into a PS2 and then I'd play it.
Brad, you're number two big.
Well, thanks for the comedy killer.
My number two big is Ecstasy, because that song kicks ass and owns you all.
It'd be like having insertion.
Ecstasy.
Loki.
Well, it's only fitting since, you know, if we're talking about a new mix of 2DX, it would
obviously be with the new mix of DDR, so why not the Legend of Max?
Legend of Max.
My fingers would fall off.
My turn, my turn, my turn.
It feels like burning.
Jamie, you're number two.
It feels like burning heat.
My baby mama.
Yes.
I'm thinking about playing the bass line with that.
That's fine. We can have a dupe. That's fine.
Angel.
Okay, this is my personal favorite at the moment.
I chose Eurobeat.
Eurobeat, go!
Well, 6 style had a lot of pair of songs in it, so Eurobeat would definitely fit in.
So Eurobeat.
Angel's number one choice.
Well, since we talked about... Oh, I'm being told that
Gamlande Couples in Beatmania the final.
Can somebody give me...
oh yeah that's our talk about two d x not be made not five t two d x haha
that's right thank you
i didn't know that that's still pretty cool if it's in uh...
even in the final but that's not to the x
my first
since we talked about
let's talk about some pretty
beginning it is into the exercise
what's all that
yes sucks to be me
Let me think some more.
All right, we'll come back to Starza.
Oops.
He's not doing it.
I forgot.
I'll stick to my game face.
OK, my number one and the best song in the world,
the Miracle Moon remix by LED.
Which was in BeatMania as well, but it needs to be in 2DX.
It needs to be in 2DX with harder notes and stuff.
That would be awesome.
I would jizz in my panties.
Oh, crap.
I think I'm going to take my noose off now.
Since Rob was a bastard and stole my number one, I'm going to just pick this really wig
off one here.
Kachaka.
I almost picked that.
I think I spelled Kachaka wrong, but whatever.
My number one? Clunk Clunk. Clunk Clunk. Oh, good one. Good one from Keyboard Mania. That's
a good pick. Did Stressa come up with one? How about Captain Jack? Captain Jack! Because
no Bomani game is complete without Captain Jack. Beautiful. And if he wasn't there, he'd
i
okay so dang jamie read this list so far as it stands
fireball Tokyo already like a virgin superstar my parasite
on the jazz ghost dark black forest boom boom dollar
as to see legend of max was it saying
is misspelled
because i did its twice it's the grammer check okay
Legend of Max, My Baby Mama, Guacamole de Couple, Eurobeat, Miracle Moon LED Mix, Cachaca, Clone Clone 1655, and Captain Jack.
elimination round where one song, sorry kids, it's gotta come off this list. This is a hard
one. I guess I'll start. One song that's gotta come off this list for 2DX that I don't wanna
see in 2DX. Boom Boom Dollar. That's forever and always a DDR song. I don't see it in 2DX,
sorry. So I'm taking Boom Boom Dollar off the list. Angel, take one of these songs off
The Guacamole List song.
Oh, damn you, damn you!
Why? Because I don't know it. My bad.
We should play that during the break, man.
You're a bad woman.
Rob, I just heard the news.
I heard that you have a bad case of balloon fight.
I've heard that Pim can cure this, along with Sega.
Sega!
What are you doing here?
Molesting you, apparently.
Sonic!
Okay, let's see here. Fireball took you already, like a virgin.
Superstar mind parasite, I'm the jazz.
Ghost, dark black forest, ecstasy, legend of Max.
My baby mama, Eurobeat.
Eurobeat?
Miracle moon.
What the hell is that?
T'Chaka!
Clung Clung 1655 and Captain Jack. Captain Jack.
I'll tell you what, here we go. Just delete everything except Captain Jack.
And it's all set.
Yes, Captain Jack is loved.
Alright.
Moving along. Stressa, what comes off the list?
I'm sorry, Angel, but Dark Black Forest must go.
It's all good. I don't hate you.
much. You'll get a beating later. I do. Jerk. Alright. Badly. I want to go last. Tough. I want a pony. Anyway. I don't want to piss anybody off because I'll take mine away. I'm going to have to go with Captain Jack. You bastard taking Captain Jack off the list. I hope you die. That's alright. Stressa. I'm just kidding. As payback for you taking
For you taking off my song from the list, I still say you're a DIRTY KILLGIRL!
Just because I'm not a huge fan of this song in both DDR and Beatmania, buh-bye Miracle
Moon.
You will rot in hell for this!
Miracle Moon comes off the list.
I think I'm going to have to go with taking off Eurobeat, just because as far as having
Eurobeat song goes in 2DX, that wouldn't be much of a challenge.
Alright, so... It doesn't have a lot of neat, synth-y stuff going on.
So, we have the final list that our chat room now gets to vote on.
Send me your votes over private messages in the chat room right now.
Jamie, tell them what their picks are.
Fireball, Tokyo Already, Like a Virgin, Superstar, Mind Parasite, On the Jazz,
Ghost, Estacy, Legend of Max, My Baby Mama, Kachaka, and CloneKling6035.
Sky's voice the game is not an option if you vote for that
it doesn't count don't waste your vote. By the way this is yet another week that
all of my choices have stayed up.
You're special. I am.
My movie pic got voted off last week.
And just for
Angel and anyone else that may not know here it is Gamlaan day couple while we
tally the votes. Send them in right now.
I think I wanna get to know him
It turns out that we're so
Rising
Summer level up
Tell me what we are
Feeling
Summer level up
I'm the one in love with you, boy
Do do do do do do do do do
So now when the air jumps
Jumper jumpers grab my knees and stop now
Feel like I'm your girl
Enjoying the place you got
But something's not for treat, it's just a bit summer now
Summer la-la-la
Can you hear my heartbeat?
A rhythm that I repeat
Summer la-la-la
Can you hear my heartbeat?
I know I'm in love with you
But I like it, but I like it forever
Bye bye baby balloon Bye bye baby balloon
Bitch, get a new song, an open letter from Orange Lounge Radio.
We are back and I'm having my picture taken.
Oh, there, that was fun.
All right.
Whee!
Hey, I got flashed by Angel, that was pretty cool.
We have the results, ladies and gentlemen of The Listless.
from any other Bamani game that ought to be in 2DX that isn't yet. And here it is, the
number three choice, you voted Superstar!
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
No, Brad, can't you do the rap? Can you do the rap for us?
Don't make me bust out my white honky rap skills on yellow ass.
Come on, Emma Brad.
I don't even remember how it goes.
My name is Kaos, and I'm-
No, wait.
That's all I remember.
I am here, and my name is Kaos.
Whatever.
This happens to me like VD is to Amadeus.
Anyway, number two pick.
You picked it.
The number two winner is clunkclunk1655.
I'm winner.
Winner.
Keyboard mania in the house.
Ought to be on VDR, or ought to be on 2DX.
And the winner.
This kind of makes me sad a little bit,
because I know it'll be in 2DX anyway.
But you did vote it, your number one choice,
by quite a landslide, ladies and gentlemen.
legend of max
has responded ought to be a today that why did anyone take it off the list
you're all growing why did anyone take on the list if you don't like it
now i see i think what you say
i said
that's a little wet shit
well
all right that was the uh...
when he signed a
don't give me dots
you voted it alright
yeah it's your fault
it's your fault
rob's voice the game
why
what would a game to my voice be it'd be awesome
i could make a song using your voice
as the
you know kinda like fine it'll be called legend of let them move
the honorary number one winner is sky's voice the game are you happy
are you happy
how about uh...
pass was raised again
parents rage wins
i think the man from drink out that that's going to be rated
is he going to grow from a mushroom
as you take the mushrooms you'll see it grow
you know it's that he knows what he is you're going to that guy c man and he
He ends up being a boss in a Konami game.
What is up with that, you know?
Doesn't that guy from Seaman look just like the boss that's in Contra, the new Contra game?
Yeah, the shriveled space game.
Ooh, I'm coming undone. Ah, ah, ah, ah.
Talking about that fish.
I got it all over the ground.
They're suggesting in the chatroom that Rob's voice the game, Slut Edition.
I don't know what y'all got against politics, shit ass!
Gumby says pantsless sky voice game, no, hell no!
Hell no.
I thought you wanted to show off your cock.
Only in a freestyle routine, I'm not gonna show off my cock, what are you talking about?
That's just radio, that's radio funny, oh you weren't here for that.
I said why doesn't anybody in a GDR freestyle routine whip out their cock at the end of
it?
Everyone knows you're just a big ol' slut.
Haha.
What? I'm sorry, all I heard was nails.
Why does everybody think I'm a slut? I haven't gotten laid in forever.
Do you all think I'm a slut?
Slut? Slut? What?
Ugh.
Aw, here you go again.
Okay, capin' on Paul Terre.
One of the most...
She is the most...
The most...
Slutty?
Wait, no, no, no, no!
She's the most talented musician in the world.
Ever.
Yeah, too bad she's Naoki.
Is this before or after she gave you a blowjob?
She may be the most talented musician in the world, but she's not talented at music. She's talented in other ways, she's just also a musician.
That may be so.
They're having a group orgy! It's Hybro Uroby, the group orgy, okay?
You've got, you know, the DDR All-Stars, which is basically, you know, B4U, you know, all them buck naked, freakin' just gettin' freaky.
And then you've got, then you've got Politary in the mix there, and some other chick that we don't remember her name because she doesn't really matter, because they all suck.
And then, ew, the Naoki's in there. Oh, screw Naoki, he can be out of the, he can be filming.
I'm sorry, I think Jenny Rom's a bigger slut than Politary.
We already know that half of B4U is really Naoki, too.
Have you heard the new Polteri song where she plays the didgeridoo?
Come on, guys! She's Australian! Fucking kill my joke!
There's been a sniper shooting!
Okay, she stopped doing the didgeridoo sound after I...
Ah! I like Black Lab's term
for Polteri. Ostrasion.
She's Ostrasion.
oh god they're criticizing me because we've said slut like 20 times and
haven't played the
I thought she needed to be pressed, Rob.
We banned her from the remainder of the year.
Alright, that's enough.
We hate politics, and we want politics.
We banned her from the remainders of the year.
Alright, that's enough.
Because we hate Paula Terry and we want all of her balls to die.
I don't know what, this chat room is obsessed with my cock and me giving lap dances and me being a slut and like all this other stuff.
This is scary.
I need the chat room's help.
Why would you call Matt a slut? He's a bigger slut than I am.
I am.
Say it again.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
What?
Well, he is correct, but that's not the point, okay?
I am the biggest slut of them all.
Oh, sorry, Rob.
All your sluts are blunt to us.
I'm just going to do the hotkey here.
Hey, hey, they have loose slop in Reno.
Tricked you, almost got you, I thought I was going to say slut, but.
They need to change it, still you're in my part.
Let's see, in the chat room, they're saying Matt is not a slut, he's a one-woman man whore.
That's cute.
I still...
Ah.
The song should be called...
SoCalKicks suggest Dave is a slut to his hand.
Yes, Jamie.
Here's a slut to the Crisco can.
Crisco doesn't work!
What the hell are you talking about? What would you suggest, being the expert on the show?
I don't know, saliva.
Here's my opinion on the whole thing. God, I can't believe we finally brought this on the show.
It's over. Welcome to the last episode of Orange Wilder, buddy.
Bomani what? DDR what?
Okay, well let's see here.
See, the thing that really sucks about all those freaking loops is they get sticky after a while, okay?
That just sucks, okay?
Okay, no more masturbation chat.
We need Mr. Spanky for this.
Okay, you just get two Ziploc bags, you fill them with hot water, and you tape them together so they're kind of like a little, you know, and then you just...
What was that, Jamie? That was a C-bomb! Oh! Did the delay get that?
I don't know if the mics got it or what. We don't have a delay. We're a shitty radio,
remember? That was beautiful, Jamie. That was so awesome.
Remember, folks, the FCC does not approve of Orange Lounge Radio.
fucking fcc with chrisco's sticky lube
it's all about the ziploc bags in the water
two ziploc bags, this sounds like
we have a slut call
and for the record i said like a big ol' cut
Okay, we have a suggestion from the chat room that we need to change the topic, and we should
talk about cake.
Frankly, I think cake makes a crappy lube.
Frosting, maybe.
You can do so many fun things with frosting.
There's the butter spray.
Of course, I think that we should actually get the tips from the people who actually
We have cocks.
What they really need is to coat your cock in teflon, okay?
Cuz nothing will stick to it, is that why they need it?
Exactly!
But how do they get teflon to stick to your dick if nothing sticks to teflon?
Well how do they do it with pots?
Shit man, how do they do it there?
You know what?
Okay, okay, okay.
Just cock stroking chat. You're all a bunch of cock masters.
I resent that.
You're not the master of your cock?
I want to talk about that Joan soda you had the other day, Rob.
Hi.
Nice cock.
You're a little...
Right.
Oh, speaking of which...
Oh, we went to get the...
Oh, Irene, you have the biggest cock here in the room right now.
Really?
What do you like to do with your cock?
Well, I mostly like to masturbate. Sometimes I like to pee.
With buck futter?
Yes, sure.
Buck futter. The day is mine.
This show went to the toilet about three hours ago.
Show back.
I think it went about like 40 episodes ago.
I have to ask you about the penis, mightier.
Anal bum covers.
Oh, maybe they should have like DD or UpCock cam.
It sounds like something you have to get like a surgery, like you know how when you get
tested for STDs, they sit there, right in the penal.
Some of us haven't had to.
I haven't either, I've heard stories.
No, it's so funny, once I was at In-N-Out, and my mom thought, yeah, that was funny.
In-N-Out, cock, get it?
The person next to us was reading a magazine called Therapist, and the person reading it
was obviously some therapist who subscribed to the monthly magazine or whatever.
My mom pointed out, she's like, you know that if you put a space between the first three
letters, it says The Rapist, and she's just like, oh my God.
My mom's like, yeah, you'll never look at that word the same again.
Still you're in those parts.
No Stylin is doing his typical interesting random comments here in the chatroom and he
says, who wants to go to DDR camp?
What the hell would DDR camp be?
Is that like a...
I don't know.
Is this one time at DDR camp?
Is that like a camp where they're going to kill us all?
This one time at DDR camp, I played Beat It Mania.
This one time at DDR camp, they made all the girls wear skirts and then they put cameras
was in the floor and made them dance.
Weeee.
Um.
I just like, weeee.
Who would be the first counselor at DDR camp to try and molest somebody?
Loki.
Loki has his hand up.
Uh, I didn't have anything to say.
Oh, he was volunteering.
Okay, how many DDR players are hard up for dates?
All of them.
Not me.
Oh, and not you.
Almost all of them.
Wait, no, no.
No, I take that back because now...
All of them that aren't involved with Orange Lounge. Ha ha ha.
Okay, I would say that would go towards any females. Obviously I would not want to molest any guys because that's just weird.
Wait, what? You have a girlfriend?
Yeah, but this is hypothetical. Hypothetical can't hurt me.
Not hypothetical, just pathetic.
I'm hyperpathetical. I'm hyperpathetical, okay?
Hyperglycemic?
Telepathetical.
All right.
I was telepathetic.
EOSFVB expresses great disappointment that we went through that whole segment about masturbating
and didn't bring up lotion, and then says, and then more than Jake says, it puts the
lotion in its skin and puts it in the basket.
Well, they didn't really finish.
They stole the mic from me before I could finish, but yeah, lotion would definitely
work.
Actually, that's pretty good.
It puts the lotion on its skin or it gets the hose again.
How about a dead baby joke?
More than the Jake wants us to tell a dead baby joke.
Alright, here it is.
How many dead babies does it take to screw in a lightbulb?
How many?
None, they're dead!
Alright, well there's one, I'm just going to read this one from the chatroom.
What is a dead baby?
What?
A baby that is dead.
That's not funny.
Why is people laughing?
More than Jake says, what's the difference between a pile of dead babies and a Corvette?
What?
I don't have a Corvette in the garage.
That's pretty funny.
Alright, we're getting about to that time where we're going to end the damn show, so
we're going to go around and get everybody's final thoughts, so let's start with all the
guests tonight, starting in the back with Dave.
Dave, what's your final thought of the day?
Homework sucks. I have school tomorrow. That is bullshit. It's school. Finals are coming.
Nooooooooooooooo.
Give me that.
Okay, I don't quite understand the school system over here. Why would you have finals after a break?
See, back where I come from, we have finals before we go and vegetate.
Thank you very much.
Sorry, sorry. So you can forget everything.
Apparently he's almost gone.
Somebody pass the mic to somebody else.
Brad, what's your final thought of the day?
My final thought is, what do you get when you cross an owl on a bungee cord?
My ass!
I thought you were going to say cunt, fuck, shit, dick, ass, pussy.
Moving on.
We haven't gotten to the last part of it.
Stress up.
Your final thought of the day.
First of all, I would like to thank everybody for making this such a wonderful weekend.
The experience was very fun.
And final thought is, huh?
All right, Angel.
We need to light Loki's hair on fire.
Yes.
light lowkey's hair on fire
dress him up as rage
uh... jamie
contribute to the dark soccer needs new shoes fund
contribute to the jamie needs new shoes fund actually people
a popin music controller
because that's i have one more controller to get before i have one
everyone that's been out at least you know except for the arcade ones
get me one
no women and kids
i was very rude as a company don't force was done
best show
this is fun
we have to talk about it more often lucky
if i don't have the day
i don't know that
dick that you're talking about but he gets too much attention
anyways uh...
well my girlfriend's not here, obviously
jackass
so yeah
I should start a fund, see
how many people give me money
that'd be cool
I need to get money
Dave needs to get laid fund
all money goes towards me to get laid
For your 18th birthday, we'll take you to the Buddy Ranch.
Fuck that, man. We can take you to the strip club, okay?
And most of the chicks there give head when you go into the private dances.
So I've heard. I've never actually had it happen, but...
Brad's doing the dancer dance.
Happy Buddy!
No, you have to have a Barbie doll.
Anybody?
Here, use the ferret.
Alright.
Are you done with your final thought?
My final thought is Work Sucks, Dancer is the best video ever, and yeah, I need a date.
Well, shit cock couldn't flick, it's like, oh, I hit the, I hit the slut.
Haha.
Give me that.
I can imitate Popolatary.
Okay. You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
Orange Lounge Radio is hosted by Dark Sakura, Sky, and Loki.
If you'd like to leave us a comment, send us an email at orangeloungeradioatyahoo.com.
And now, here's your fortune cookie message of the day.
They come over here and they seek out our land They chop up our heads and they boil them in oil
Children are lean, we have no heads We drink and we sing and we drink and we die
We have no heads No, we have no heads
They come over here and they chop off our legs They cut off our hands and put nails in our eyes
For Grady is dead and Oh Hanrahan's gone We drink and we die and continue to drink
Oh Hanrahan! No, Oh Hanrahan!
They'd bury or deal down in condition, hey, The poor children crying in bed, in bed,
In bed, in bed, in bed, in bed, In bed, in bed, in bed,
Thank you very much for listening, and we'll see you next week.
Thank you.