[SPEAKER_00]: Tonight, November 30th, 2008, Grand Theft Auto 4 PC gets controversial DRM, a 10-year-old game gets a new patch, and could Sackboy soon become a Street Fighter?
[SPEAKER_04]: And we're back, and welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: We are that show on the internet dedicated to video games, video gaming, gaming culture, and the gamer lifestyle.
[SPEAKER_04]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not joining us tonight, sadly, is DarkSakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_04]: She is out tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hopefully, we'll be back next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also joining us, say, well, why am I saying hopefully?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, she better be back next week or we're going to be in trouble.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also joining us, say hello to Tech Master Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_04]: How are you doing, Loki?
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: You should tell them how you got injured
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: I probably pushed the envelope a little bit too much because, you know, when we were doing this race, we were running.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, everybody that was racing was really into it, and it was a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: My roommate did an awesome job with the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I gotta say, it was very... You should have done it, Loki, except you probably wouldn't have been able to do it because you would have been...
[SPEAKER_04]: Like me.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I don't get out of breath.
[SPEAKER_05]: My legs get sore before I get out of breath.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what ultimately happened to me is that actually I started getting sore in the area where I had my surgery and I had to come home and take painkillers.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was so bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I ended up passing out pretty much during the time we had the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: So a little embarrassing, yeah, but we've all done dumb shit that sometimes takes us out of our other commitments.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, last week I went and played Airsoft and I...
[SPEAKER_05]: I think Poison Oak, but I don't know if it's Poison Oak.
[SPEAKER_05]: It doesn't itch.
[SPEAKER_05]: God, I hope you didn't bring that in this house.
[SPEAKER_05]: Luckily, I think I'm immune.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've never had it, but I don't want it now.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've never had it either, so I don't know if it's Poison Oak.
[SPEAKER_05]: It just looks like a rash on my arm where I was crawling through brush and grass and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who knows what it is, but it just made a rash and doesn't really itch.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought Poison Oak is really itchy and spreads like crazy, but...
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was fun, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: We shot each other with guns.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, shooting each other is always fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what's interesting is what I ended up doing last week instead of the show is I was kind of like waking up in the night.
[SPEAKER_04]: I actually was using the Xbox 360 to kind of check out Netflix and all the streaming movies.
[SPEAKER_04]: And one thing I am loving, obscure-ass documentaries that you can only find on Netflix.
[SPEAKER_04]: Seriously, I watched a couple of them.
[SPEAKER_04]: I watched, get this, there was a documentary I watched on Netflix
[SPEAKER_04]: strippers that they were these girls that turned to stripping to make ends meet after Hurricane Katrina.
[SPEAKER_04]: and the movie was called... Well, that's weird and specific.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: The movie was called Hurricane Strip was the name of the movie and I'm like, I have to watch this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, how obscure is that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Seriously, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: But here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: The movie itself kind of was dumb because on one hand, you had a documentary about Hurricane Katrina and then, you know, which was very powerful to see that imagery and impactful, you know, it was obviously a terrible tragedy that happened, you know, you know,
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: Why do women want to strip?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, for money and attention.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, we could have told you that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It really never, for me, it never tied it into why did they feel the need to do it because of Hurricane Katrina or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It felt like I was watching two completely different movies.
[SPEAKER_05]: They probably started off making a documentary about strippers and it was just too whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then all of a sudden Hurricane Katrina happened.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're like, hey, there we go.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's how we can tie this into it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And people are interested in Hurricane Katrina so they will watch our crappy movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: or it will end up free on Netflix someday.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_04]: It was not good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Seriously, don't waste your time with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know it's like, hey, strippers, or hey, interesting documentary on Hurricane Katrina, but I'm sure there are plenty of more informative documentaries on Hurricane Katrina that are much more powerful than this, which was kind of garbage.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was just garbage.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: I really only played Saints Row 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've been playing a lot of Saints Row 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm done with it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm almost 100% complete with the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, I don't like the new friends list on there.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's too hard to find, you know, what people are playing at.
[SPEAKER_05]: It takes me forever to scroll through that list.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whereas, you know, I can just hit the button, you know, guide button again and just pull up my friends list and it just has a drop down of what people are playing.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I can look at it at a glance real quick.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, I do like the community games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Those are pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um,
[SPEAKER_05]: I kind of like the new shop, how they have it set up with where you can see screenshots and box art and stuff like that for the games.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_05]: It does seem to be a little harder just to browse stuff sometimes, but I'm just getting used to it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that's kind of my thoughts on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I really love the new features.
[SPEAKER_04]: The avatars are cute.
[SPEAKER_04]: Netflix is awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Community games are awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I appreciate that Microsoft tried to modernize everything, which sounds weird because not only is the Xbox an old system, but they're basically trying to put some of these new stuff in an all-new package.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't like the... So there's a lot of problems.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't say it's a negative thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, NXT overall is a positive thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just think some things are a little more difficult when they don't need to be.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't like all the advertisements on there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, for example, when you first bring it up, it's like what's going on in Xbox and stuff like that, and they have all this crap that I gotta scroll through.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just... You know, that's kind of annoying.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wish I could take that away.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love the little intro video when you first install it.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um...
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't you think gold users shouldn't have to see as many of those ads?
[SPEAKER_04]: I understand.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some of them are for their little inside Xbox videos and things.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't mind it because it's free stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: At least it's not...
[SPEAKER_04]: Flash here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is your IQ smarter than Sarah Palin and all the stuff you see on the internet?
[SPEAKER_04]: At least it's not that bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just small gripes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, going to the community games, I did play... I tried to play everything on there, or at least a lot of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jeez.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's taking you a while.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I haven't gotten to play everything.
[SPEAKER_05]: A lot of it I downloaded and I looked at it again.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm like...
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh, I don't want that, you know, I'm just deleting that.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, um, I ended up buying a couple of them.
[SPEAKER_05]: I bought a Weapon of Choice, which is awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's kind of like a Contra-type game, which is really weird weapons and weird characters and enemies and stuff that you fight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, so that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's kind of quirky.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, and then the other one, I don't know why I bought it, but it was kind of fun, was, um, I think it was like, um...
[SPEAKER_05]: SignSurfing, and that was kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just really simple, just a little fun mess around game, which is kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_05]: The word puzzle one, I kind of thought about buying that, but I haven't gotten a chance to yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then I just go on there every time I'm on there usually.
[SPEAKER_05]: If I'm on there for an extended period of time, I'll look to see the new ones that have come up and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: But as I was complaining before when we were talking to Bobby...
[SPEAKER_05]: Some of the graphics, it looks really unpolished.
[SPEAKER_05]: A lot of it looks like the games aren't done and they're just putting them up to see if they can make any money off of them.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just really bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Even some of these independent developers and stuff, like some of the Japanese ones, like we've talked about in Warning Forever and
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, other than that, like I said, Saints Row 2, playing through that, it's getting to the point now where I'm just doing the 100% stuff so I can finish the entire game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Playing Grand Theft Auto 4 now because everyone got hooked on that because they thought for some reason that...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: That game is very sad.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's very sad because they didn't do anything to it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they, in fact, actually took things out of... If you played the original GameCube one, you'll know that they had a fountain and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, now you have to buy those things.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I think that was the way it was in Wild World.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't remember.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's still sad that they took stuff out and they made stuff simpler.
[SPEAKER_05]: And there's no reason for it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_05]: The Wii for Wii Sports
[SPEAKER_05]: I laugh every time I see the commercial.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I hear there's a new boutique in town.
[SPEAKER_05]: God, you're stupid!
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, are you excited about a store in a fictional city in a game?
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, come on!
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I can appreciate what Nintendo's trying to do.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, even though they have gotten pigeonholed as the casual game company and the one that's catering to women, and rightfully so, let's face it, they're selling like crazy.
[SPEAKER_05]: and if it helps enable more people that usually wouldn't play games to play games I'm okay with it I'm okay with Nintendo reaching out to a different audience as gay as it might make you feel okay well here's the thing though is their games like as of after Mario Kart basically that's come out all the games have been released by Nintendo haven't sold very well and
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's been going downhill fast.
[SPEAKER_05]: Especially the fourth quarter stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wario Land Shake It, surprisingly, didn't sell very well.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wii Music, well, we don't even need to go there.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Animal Crossing, surprisingly, not that big of a seller.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just people realize that they haven't changed anything.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the people that don't realize it are the people that probably aren't going to buy it anyways.
[SPEAKER_04]: What about the overall picture?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because the pool's getting pretty diluted out there when you look at all the third-party titles.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, is it just because...
[SPEAKER_04]: People that would have bought Animal Crossing are instead tempted by these cheaper budget games that are shovelware?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think so, because there's nothing really competing with those genres of games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, Wario Land Shaky doesn't really have any good side-scrolling platformers that are competing with it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wii Music, maybe Guitar Hero would have competed with it, but I think Wii Music was bad to begin with.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Animal Crossing, really the only thing that kind of compares to it that came out around the same time is My Sims Kingdom, which sold even worse than, you know, Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, I don't think...
[SPEAKER_05]: I think you'll do pretty well, but right now they haven't given us any hope to...
[SPEAKER_05]: There's nothing really different.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the problem.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like, oh my god.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've got to read some comments from chat here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Chat.OrangeLawnTrader.com, of course, always our other guest here on the program.
[SPEAKER_04]: The fourth guest, or tonight, they've been promoted to third guest because DarkSakura's not here tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: GameGuru says, how do we know City Folk isn't selling well?
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't have an MPD.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you have a little kind of an insider perspective on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, just from what I've seen.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it could be selling very well.
[SPEAKER_04]: On a grander scale, but from what you are seeing, it is not.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, we're selling out, but it's just not...
[SPEAKER_05]: There wasn't that many to begin with.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think Nintendo's made a lot of very disappointing decisions in the past two years.
[SPEAKER_04]: And a lot of that has affected the hardcore gamers like you and me.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it just kind of goes right into what Acidic Vampire says in chat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nintendo is reaching out to other people but neglecting the hardcore gamers frown.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's kind of my issue.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the whole thing... Right there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, and my thing was, too, is before with the GameCube, when they were done with the GameCube and they're developing the Wii and they're promoting the Wii, it's like, listen, the Wii is for everybody.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Wii system is not... We're not going to be pigeonholed in being known as a company that puts out games only for children.
[SPEAKER_05]: We are trying to appeal to everybody.
[SPEAKER_04]: but they're not they're just doing the same thing that they've been doing before they're just complaining that everyone sees them as a company that puts out you know games for like you know too many family games and too many uh just casual games and well complain all you want but that's what you're doing and here's here's the other thing too i can respect what nintendo does from a business perspective which is what i'm kind of saying with these commercials and things it's like you know as a business move it's it's a smart idea and it's something new but at the same time on a personal level i can still kind of go but it sucks
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: and hardcore gamers kind of push the Wii to be so in demand in the first place.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Nintendo's going to need them if they launch another system or an upgraded version of the Wii, which is kind of my fear is what's going to happen is that we're going to see the next system that comes out of Nintendo is going to be, and it could be as soon as next year, maybe 2010.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would say no later than 2010, you're going to see it Wii HD or something where Nintendo
[SPEAKER_04]: Now they're going to start catering into all those features, you know, but their big selling point is going to be, but it's also a Wii, just like the Wii was also a GameCube, you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_04]: So, you know, I think to get that support, they're going to need to win us hardcore gamers back, and the more you push us away, and the more that Xbox and even now Sony starts to woo us over, which who would have thought that would have happened a few years ago, that we'd be talking...
[SPEAKER_04]: So great about Sony, but whereas Nintendo's been making a lot of disappointing decisions this year, Sony's been making a lot of I can't say great decisions, but satisfying decisions.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's put it that way.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're content with Sony right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let me just put it this way.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know what's coming up for the first two months of 2009 from Nintendo, and it's sad.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, it's sad if you own a Wii.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let me put it that way.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you own a DS, you might not be so disappointed, but
[SPEAKER_05]: Seriously, this is the trend that they're doing now is let's start remaking GameCube games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can you put any less effort into that?
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, seriously.
[SPEAKER_05]: What, we got Play for Wii Mario Tennis and Play for Wii Pikmin is the first two games of next year for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_05]: Woohoo!
[SPEAKER_04]: With Pikmin!
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, awesome!
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Pikmin all over again!
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, we're gonna get to a story later tonight about that there's a surprise cooking over at Nintendo, one of their developers.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it possible that Nintendo is setting the stage to really knock our socks off next E3?
[SPEAKER_04]: They better.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's all I'm saying.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have a feeling next E3 it's gonna be about the DSi.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I...
[SPEAKER_05]: I hope that they do something good because, man, my bar for them is set so low right now, it's like, there's very little, maybe a new Zelda game, or F-Zero or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or that Kid Icarus game that's been rumored for a long, long time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, that'll never happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I'm just saying, you want to win me back, here's some ways.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they gotta be good, they can't be shovelware.
[SPEAKER_04]: You shovelware Kid Icarus, I'm gonna be pissed.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm gonna be twice as pissed as I was before.
[SPEAKER_04]: You gotta make it good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just stop being so stingy is what they need to do.
[SPEAKER_04]: GameGuru says the thing is that the core gamer and the third party has abandoned Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, we're going to get to one of the stories later tonight about how some of these companies are now starting to say, look, we're just not capable of doing what we wanted to do, so bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but the core gamer's finicky, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: If they come out with a really kick-ass game, they're going to come right back, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: So it...
[SPEAKER_05]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_04]: interview in look into as to why do game blogs and even podcasters like us and so on find the need to nitpick the negative in every single game out there and I think it's centered around Mirror's Edge and how Mirror's Edge is really getting these reviews that are just all over the map you know some people are giving it oh my god best game ever etc etc and some people are saying and just really nitpicking the shit out of the game you know are people doing it just to
[SPEAKER_04]: Be negative on something.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, fucking Power Trip is what they are.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're getting treated like royalty, getting promo shit sent to them.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're getting basically blown by these game companies.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then they're just like, oh, well, this game isn't as good as blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, and this is why I'm going to... You know, just like complain about little shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's probably because they're... You know, this is so ironic coming from you.
[SPEAKER_05]: but you know what though I find fun in different things I mean like Earth Defense Force perfect example that game is absolute shit if you were to look at it like by you know graphics AI everything is god damn retarded in that game but it's fun and that's the whole point is that's really all that counts is if the game is fun who gives a crap if it's ugly it's fun that's the whole point but you just were sitting here dogging on the community games for having crappy graphics but they aren't fun either
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, alright then, alright, fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: And seriously though, I mean, there are lines that, you know, can be crossed, you know, where it's like, okay, yeah, it might be fun, but seriously, man, that looks awful.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, any other games you've been playing this week?
[SPEAKER_04]: We've kind of gotten on all these tangents, but it's been fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Any other games you've been playing this week?
[SPEAKER_05]: Um...
[SPEAKER_05]: No, but I've been using my PS3 as a Blu-ray player quite a bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kung Fu Panda is pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sweet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mamma Mia is coming out pretty soon, and Dark Knight, and SingStar ABBA.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: PlayStation 3 is this week, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I believe it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm excited.
[SPEAKER_05]: well I was it I um someone had mentioned like I have pre-ordered right now one of the limited editions of Dark Knight with the stupid bat pod things I want a piece of crap for my desk you know like right now cool things to put on it so I will see if I actually buy that but
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, games I've been playing this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pretty much, you know, same old stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was talking about Netflix.
[SPEAKER_04]: I did dive into community games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I picked up Snake360.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, we had Aaron on last week who was really the dude behind Snake360.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, you know, I had a good time with Snake360.
[SPEAKER_04]: I really like that Aaron has pushed the limits of everything that you can kind of possibly do within the confines of what community games lets you do.
[SPEAKER_04]: All these different modes, all these different maps
[SPEAKER_04]: He's really kind of done a lot that you can do with this game when it comes to having the multiplayer, having the timed mode, having the pick up a certain number of pods in a level mode, having the different mazes.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think the soundtrack, it was really smart of him to pair up with Kyle Ward and his company and have the music because it
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: That's something that Microsoft just plain won't let him do.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I worry for community games as a whole because I think there's going to be a lot of people that don't know so much about, you know, well, community games have all these restrictions to them.
[SPEAKER_04]: And like he can't do online leaderboards because Microsoft won't let him.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, you know, he's found a lot of very creative workarounds.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll give him that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Instead of achievements, he has goals and the goals will unlock things.
[SPEAKER_04]: Instead of the leaderboards, he has the online leaderboards where you go and put in the codes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: you probably won't enjoy the game but I think as a local multiplayer especially is a lot of fun I crave it to be on Xbox Live and I'm kind of disappointed Microsoft won't let some of these games go to the next level I hope they will I hope some of these really good you know impressing community games such as you know Weapon to Choice I think is doing very well you mentioned it earlier and Bobby had the dude on his show tonight from Weapon to Choice maybe some of these guys will get to upgrade if they want to a full-on game I don't know
[SPEAKER_04]: SuperStreetFighter2 Turbo HD Remix
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the same game you've had already!
[SPEAKER_04]: And I know you already know this about Street Fighter 2, but to me it's a little bit insulting that they would charge $10 for that first game and then come around a year later and charge $10 for essentially the same game.
$15.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, yeah, an additional $5 or whatever you want to say for this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: And yes, I realize Street Fighter 2 is a classic, but at the same time...
[SPEAKER_04]: There's only so much you can do with it, and I think Street Fighter 4 is more of what, in my opinion, a redone Street Fighter 2 ought to be.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Street Fighter 4.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you get in Super Street Fighter 2 Turbo HD Remix that you didn't have before?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the same game with four new characters, of which, give or take, in my opinion, I guess I like Fei Long, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're kind of give or take.
[SPEAKER_04]: It isn't worth the five bucks to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or...
[SPEAKER_04]: So there's that and then there's the new graphics and the new sound.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the rebalancing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to say something here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, the rebalancing for a casual fighter person like me is irrelevant.
[SPEAKER_04]: The graphics aren't bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll give it that.
[SPEAKER_04]: The HD is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: The sprites are done fairly well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although it's not a smooth game because you still have...
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: I appreciate what they tried to do with Street Fighter 2 I appreciate that they tried to go to the indie community and this OC remix thing and they actually got people to remix the songs but for me they don't work they don't match the mood of the original songs at all and I could tell this from the minute the character select screen came up I was like what did they do to the character select music this is awful
[SPEAKER_04]: So, sorry, I know that statement's probably not going to make me popular amongst fans of the OC Remix circuit, and it's not to say that website hasn't done a lot of great things in the past, but I think it's left best these tracks that made it into this game as Remix, and I realize it's a whole play on that word, Remix, and da-da-da-da-da.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it didn't work in the game at all for me.
[SPEAKER_04]: And sound to me is very, very important in the game and the music.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if you're going to try and rate me for $15 more based on nostalgia, I want my tunes to have some sense of nostalgia.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I realize I can revert to classic mode, but again, what are you trying to sell me?
[SPEAKER_04]: If you just wanted to sell me the classic songs, you already sold that to me a year ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I expect that these remixes are going to have some type of... Maybe I'm just bothered because I've heard remixes of these songs before that were more true to the originals and that were better for me.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I did not like the soundtrack at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: Call me names, tell me I'm hatin' if you want, but in this particular circumstance, I did not like the music.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not a real big fan of Street Fighter 2 anyway, so I didn't even look at it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was just like, eh, 15 bucks, screw that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not going to buy it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not going to buy the original either.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now if they came out with yet another Bionic Commando game, then yes, I would probably...
[SPEAKER_04]: I think they are afraid if people check out this game, they're going to realize it's a waste of their money.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's not enough here besides the continued whoring of your nostalgia.
[SPEAKER_04]: God, I feel like I've been through that enough in the past two years thanks to Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_05]: I gotta give them credit.
[SPEAKER_05]: At least the sprites look good.
[SPEAKER_05]: They put the effort into the graphics of the game and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not just blurry.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, um...
[SPEAKER_05]: But yeah, I mean, really, if you're not really... If you bought the first one on Xbox Live, you probably don't need to buy this either.
[SPEAKER_04]: Honestly, don't bother with it on Xbox at all if you don't have the right controller.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't try to play this game with a regular Xbox 360 controller unless you have somehow been able to overcome that whole... I'm telling you, every bad thing you hear about the Xbox 360 controller is true for this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't.
[SPEAKER_04]: if you have to get it get it on PlayStation Network for the controller alone unless you have an arcade stick on 360 or something
[SPEAKER_04]: And of course, folks in chat are completely disagreeing, which is fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: I kind of expected that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hitstun says, but really, STHD is the definitive Street Fighter now, even more so than Street Fighter 4.
[SPEAKER_04]: All fighting game players need to buy it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Acidic Vampire says, that's what some movie studios do.
[SPEAKER_04]: When they know a movie's going to suck, they don't release it to the press for advanced reviews.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's the weird thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think the game overall is getting good reviews.
[SPEAKER_04]: I realize I'm... And I'm not doing it for the sake of going against it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just personally... I did not like it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I'm not sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't like it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Deal with it.
[SPEAKER_05]: But that's another thing, too, is this whole game review stuff, because they remember this all just like Chrono Trigger and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: No offense.
[SPEAKER_05]: Chrono Trigger is an awesome game and stuff, but they didn't really do too much to the DS game, and it's getting almost perfect scores and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it is Chrono Trigger, so it's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: But...
[SPEAKER_04]: See, then HitStun goes on to say, if you don't have a 360, and I might be taking this out of context, I apologize, says, if you don't have a 360 or PS3, it's a good reason to buy the console just to get the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, God, do I disagree with that comment.
[SPEAKER_04]: If the game in question is Street Fighter, because it's really not.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: I haven't really priced them lately or at all, but I would be willing to bet you could probably get a full-size arcade cabinet with Street Fighter 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Probably wouldn't be that expensive.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, that would be my guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just the original Street Fighter 2 or whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: You might even be able to get it for just slightly more than $400.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you're really that insane that you'd buy a console for a freaking downloadable game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, that's weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a comment that will piss off the Street Fighter fans even further.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now this I will say just for the sake of pissing people off.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll admit this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Playing Street Fighter 2 HD Remix almost made me want to go buy Mortal Kombat vs. DC Universe.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's how much I did not enjoy the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, that's not right.
[SPEAKER_04]: You think that's taking it too far?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's taking it too far.
[SPEAKER_05]: Taking it too far?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm getting yelled at by chat for that comment.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was pretty bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, look.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's get into some of tonight's game news.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, see, here's what I'm saying right here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Street Fighter 2, you can get a Street Fighter Alpha 2 arcade cabinet, $600.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you better believe that you can get an original Street Fighter 2 machine, yeah, literally about $600.
[SPEAKER_05]: So just, if you're really that insane that you would buy a console for this, seriously, just go buy the real arcade game.
[SPEAKER_05]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, before we get to some gaming news tonight, let's talk about some housekeeping tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to do a contest soon to give away the code for Banjo-Kazooie.
[SPEAKER_04]: We were supposed to do it last week, but we're going to retool it to be something that both our live and our podcast listeners can do.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we're not going to be doing it tonight, but there will be something probably next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we'll kind of give you more details on that when everybody's back and when it's not the holidays.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also...
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think we have a lot else to talk about in housekeeping tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just the stuff with our Facebook, of course.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have OL Army on Facebook, MySpace at username Orange Lounge Radio, and LiveJournal at Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, unless you can think of anything for housekeeping tonight as far as news goes, but not a lot going on with the show otherwise.
[SPEAKER_04]: Same old, same old.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, the...
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I can't think of anything other than Burger King Tender Crisp sandwiches aren't that great.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, we're going to get into the news tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, before we get into the news tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: We usually do our little thing on Bobby's show before we go live.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bobby Blackwolf, the man who we follow on All Games Radio Live Sunday nights.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if you guys heard it, but there was some weird little cryptic message.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I tried to ask Bobby about it, but he's totally ignoring my text.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I'm trying to figure out what that website was.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, did you guys hear it?
[SPEAKER_04]: It was something like FLive.net or something?
[SPEAKER_04]: FNG Live?
[SPEAKER_04]: I couldn't hear it all, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll have to go back and download it and check it out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Something weird going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's get into the news.
[SPEAKER_04]: And tell Bobby to stop ignoring me.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is very rude, Bobby.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, I'm calling you out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's get into tonight's gaming news.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, why don't you start off?
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, well, a couple weeks ago, the brand new download content for Grand Theft Auto 4 was announced.
[SPEAKER_05]: Grand Theft Auto's Lost and the Damned, or Lost and Damned, I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which is going to revolve around the biker gang that was in Grand Theft Auto 4, The Lost.
[SPEAKER_05]: And would be a brand new thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess a brand new story mode.
[SPEAKER_05]: Doesn't really add anything like I wanted to it, like tanks and crap, but...
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, new story, sweet.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was going to be released in February.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right now, though, what's interesting is GameStop has the download content available to purchase on their website, which is supposed to be released in February on the 17th.
[SPEAKER_05]: And so apparently you'll be able to buy this redemption card at GameStop.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, talk about a way to whore that out, but...
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's a hint folks, if you go to GameStop you're going to pay sales tax.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you buy it online you're not going to have to pay sales tax.
[SPEAKER_05]: At least you shouldn't have to pay a sales tax.
[SPEAKER_05]: So don't buy it from GameStop.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's pretty easy right there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't some states charge you sales tax even on the download stuff?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, in that case, it doesn't matter then.
[SPEAKER_05]: But then again, it costs you gas to drive down the GameStop.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gas is cheap right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have you noticed?
[SPEAKER_04]: In the two weeks we've been off, gas dropped a dollar.
[SPEAKER_04]: What are you talking about?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's still a cost.
[SPEAKER_05]: And even after all that, it's just to buy a code that you would enter in to download it anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: So just save yourself the time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Save them the...
[SPEAKER_05]: Ego of being able to pre-order cards.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, that's sad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just go buy it online.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why do you even need to buy the game sub?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, maybe it's just the convenience.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait, when is this coming out?
[SPEAKER_04]: February.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, never mind.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was going to say so people could buy it as a Christmas present.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, so they can pre-order more stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: So they can get you to turn in some games as a pre-order download content so they can get another five bucks from you.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry, but the fact that you would pay for download content at a store and then go home and download it is just stupid.
[SPEAKER_05]: According to me, I mean, what do I know, though?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, maybe somebody doesn't have internet capability or what have you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then you wouldn't buy the download content!
[SPEAKER_04]: This isn't a disc!
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a card with a code that you enter it in online and download it!
[SPEAKER_04]: It's stupid!
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, yes, fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's absolutely retarded.
[SPEAKER_04]: Zushi says free poster at GameStop.
[SPEAKER_05]: Woohoo!
[SPEAKER_05]: Free poster!
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, well, if they've got a free poster, then I better go down there right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, I can't do the rest of the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've got to get my free poster.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, look, look, look.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, I like free things.
[SPEAKER_04]: In fact, I would be probably one of the three people who doesn't own Grand Theft Auto Vice City.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if you actually want to order Grand Theft Auto 4, a pre-order, if you want to do it for your PC, order Grand Theft Auto 4 on the PC, you can actually get a free copy of Grand Theft Auto Vice City just for placing the pre-order.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is all via Steam, so Valve and Rockstar Games teamed up, and if you pre-order Grand Theft Auto 4 PC via Steam, then Vice City will be free.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which, by the way, you've got to do it right now, because Grand Theft Auto 4 releases, like, what, Tuesday on PC?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's awesome, except Anna Dreyas was way better anyways, and Vice City this time is really old.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just buy Grand Theft Auto 4.
[SPEAKER_05]: You don't even need extra stuff for it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So anyways, speaking of other things, Grand Theft Auto 4 on PC has the ever infamous secure ROM in it now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thankfully though, there's not going to be as much limitation as some of these other games.
[SPEAKER_05]: There is no limit on concurrent installations, but you will have to authenticate it once you've installed it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you'll have to, I guess, authenticate it again if you reinstall it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it's basically just to make sure that the CD-ROM, I guess, is... I don't know, in your drive when you're playing the game or something like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Something stupid.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I can't help but think this is probably going to be cracked next week already.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, Secure ROM has really been no obstacle for a lot of people...
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways, it's quite a controversial thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it's not just the limited installations is pissing people off, but the whole, you know, that whole thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I don't know whether you would call it a rumor if it's a proven fact or what, but the whole like, you know, that it might screw up your drive.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I already have it installed in my system and nothing's messed up so far.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, yeah, it doesn't really matter for me.
[SPEAKER_05]: But then again, I'm not buying the PC version of Grand Theft Auto 4.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkTetsuya relays an interesting comment.
[SPEAKER_04]: He said, it's like I told the people at GamePolitics.
[SPEAKER_04]: Considering how hard Securom is to get rid of, I'd rather take my chances with Trojans and Keyloggers.
[SPEAKER_05]: You just, you know, have a trusted place to download your wares, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess so, although you shouldn't be advocating piracy.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think we should necessarily be advocating secure ROM either.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not advocating piracy.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just saying I'm not buying Grand Theft Auto 4 on PC.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because you already have it on 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: What do you need it on PC for, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not buying Grand Theft Auto 4 on PC.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, yeah, because I do have it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've already finished it.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's no reason for me to actually play this on PC other than it looks prettier and, well, you know, I do have a game PC now.
[SPEAKER_05]: I might as well put games on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, I got you.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you're just looking forward to all the hacking.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all I'm looking forward to.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can Securum prevent that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Or do you think that they wouldn't bother because that's kind of the reason why people get it on PC is to screw with it?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, it's not going to affect it at all because Securum only really protects the main executable for it.
[SPEAKER_05]: All the data files are what's going to be modified to whatever you want to do with it.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh yeah, PETA did a little spoof on Cookie Mama.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently they don't really care about people's trademarks or anything like that because it's parody, but I mean, seriously, it's just... It was really just an overall excuse to get people to watch the video that's embedded there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Majesco had a really cute response to it where they actually quoted Mama, and I thought that was very cute what they did.
[SPEAKER_04]: But as far as PETA goes, love them or hate them, there ain't...
[SPEAKER_04]: It's working.
[SPEAKER_04]: People are talking about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'll tell you what, probably hundreds and thousands of people saw that video that wouldn't have before simply because it did tie into video games.
[SPEAKER_04]: So love them or hate them, they did what they had to do.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it worked for all intents and purposes, I suppose.
[SPEAKER_04]: As much as I don't necessarily agree... It's not that I don't agree with PETA 100%, but...
[SPEAKER_04]: I just wanted to say Majesco had a very cute response to it and props to them
[SPEAKER_05]: I was going to say that there was another story that I think is kind of big.
[SPEAKER_05]: The story kind of got blown over a little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Eidos, once again back in the spotlight, for trying to fix their Metacritic scores for Tomb Raider Underworld.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently, they sort of blew...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: That's not the first time I've heard of something like that, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, that's the first time I've heard of the Metacritic spin on it, but I've definitely heard of companies saying, like, you know, well, what review are you going to give it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, well, if you're going to give it a high review, then you can post it early.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can break the embargo.
[SPEAKER_04]: But if you're not going to give it a high review, then you have to wait until, you know, the street date.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's kind of messed up, and there's probably a good reason why that a low review might be, you know, warrant this game.
[SPEAKER_05]: But apparently the Tomb Raider Underworld version for the Wii,
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: How do they give you a save?
[SPEAKER_05]: You have to go download it off the internet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, because I'm sure everybody can just do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's really annoying.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just kind of trying to check out the Metacritic scores.
[SPEAKER_04]: 78 is the current score on the PlayStation 3 version.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's not bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's not a bad score, all things considered.
[SPEAKER_05]: Look at the Wii version.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wii version has a 68.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's not too bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's actually not a horrible score.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's in the yellow, but it's...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_05]: A 28.
[SPEAKER_04]: Game Party 2 Midway Lawn Darts Beanbags Horseshoes Shit Game
[SPEAKER_05]: It's unoriginal, it's also dirt cheap.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's $20, and that sold actually pretty well, from what I remember.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that's $20 that, honestly, you know, despite all the crap I gave it earlier, it's $20 that's better spent on Super Street Fighter 2 HD Remix.
[SPEAKER_04]: And honestly, you know, despite the hard time I gave Street Fighter 2, I mean, it still is Street Fighter 2, which is better than, like, 80% of the Wii games out there right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: If not more.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some of the other stuff from last week.
[SPEAKER_05]: There was a new update to the Wii that broke the Twilight hack and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: And also targeted modded save files and some other stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: And apparently, yeah, it was, you know, bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: And what it did enhance, though, is it added, I guess, the ability to use USB keyboards in the Mi Channel or something like that for when you're typing stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's funny, though, is it got...
[SPEAKER_05]: Rebroken again a few days later by hackers and they released a new version of the Twilight update or the Twilight hack that allowed you to install the Homebrew channel but still though thanks for trying and then finally one last thing a couple things that were kind of interesting new arcade games and Guitar Hero apparently is coming to the arcade and the weirdest part about it is Konami's helping them
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know, they've got a little bit of experience there.
[SPEAKER_05]: There is going to be some online functionality with it.
[SPEAKER_05]: No word if they're going to actually have any additional songs or if it's just going to be stuff from Guitar Hero 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the hardware itself looks like kind of the World Tour guitars but with arcade parts.
[SPEAKER_04]: So look, for those essentially that were hoping that Konami would one day bring Guitar Freaks out to the US, forget it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Forget it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's done.
[SPEAKER_04]: These folks at Activision and Neversoft, well I guess you can't say Neversoft, but Activision and so forth and Red Octane have their mouths firmly planted on Konami's cock where it ought to be.
[SPEAKER_04]: because it's kind of where the idea came from in the first place, one could argue.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Konami likes it and they're getting theirs from it, so it's a win-win deal all around.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is what it's going to be.
[SPEAKER_04]: Take it or leave it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And of course they say that that doesn't necessarily mean that there won't be a Guitar Freaks game, but that basically means that there's not going to be a Guitar Freaks game, I mean, more or less.
[SPEAKER_05]: Then all the other games that were being shown off as well, American Idol, they're going to have a
[SPEAKER_05]: Beatmania 2DX 16 Empress
[SPEAKER_05]: EA apparently is teaming up with GameStop and it's an idea that they're throwing around right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're offering people a season pass.
[SPEAKER_05]: According to a...
[SPEAKER_05]: survey that's been sent out, they were throwing out the idea of having an EA Sports season pass where someone would buy this for, say, a $20 enrollment fee.
[SPEAKER_05]: And what would it do is it would cut 33% of the cost from all EA Sports games that were purchased in that year.
[SPEAKER_05]: So if you bought the pass and you say you're a person that buys the Maddens, the NCAA football, and all that stuff, you would save 33% off each game.
[SPEAKER_05]: which I mean it's not a bad deal if you think about it because you're actually saving you know 20 bucks a game about so if you buy a lot of games or if you even buy one game with this deal I mean it's worth it to do it because you actually break even with the first game and then you start saving money with the second game but once again they get you to buy more than one game so
[SPEAKER_04]: This is the solution for a weakening economy, I suppose.
[SPEAKER_04]: Get you hooked in early.
[SPEAKER_04]: Season pass.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess that's how it's going to go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because, see, here's the other thing about the season pass.
[SPEAKER_05]: You say, for example, you may have bought NBA 2K10 or whatever next year.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, now, say if you buy the season pass for Madden or something like that, and you're thinking about buying an NBA game...
[SPEAKER_05]: True, true.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess we'll see how this plays out, but I'm not much of a sports game fan, so it's not like it's a deal I'm going to take.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I know there are people out there that might just want to jump on the deal, because a deal is a deal, and if you are a person that buys these games, this isn't necessarily bad news.
[SPEAKER_05]: And if you are a person that buys sports games, think about it this way.
[SPEAKER_05]: Get with your friends.
[SPEAKER_05]: One person buys that, or chip in for the season pass, and you just have one person buy all your games.
[SPEAKER_05]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: And there you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Save a lot of money.
[SPEAKER_05]: Work the system.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if this is actually going to happen, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: We will see what happens.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it sounds like it was a pretty busy week last week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: And here I was spending my gaming time watching Netflix on the 360, and I watched a documentary about gay bars in Mississippi.
[SPEAKER_04]: No kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm telling you, they have everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have documentaries on everything on Netflix.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: I started a documentary about Walmart.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's my biggest problem.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe it's just the one here.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yeah, so I thought I'd check out the documentary.
[SPEAKER_04]: The documentary is on everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: On Netflix.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everything.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, we were talking a little bit about Street Fighter 2 during our gaming week.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: It kind of coincided with the Street Fighter 2 Turbo HD Remix.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're actually doing a lot of different promotional stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: You may remember with Pinball FX.
[SPEAKER_05]: They had a special table for it.
[SPEAKER_05]: They have special themes out for Xbox.
[SPEAKER_05]: and your Xbox Dashboard.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I think there's some on the PlayStation Network as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, also coming to your favorite sack puppet game, LittleBigPlanet is getting four Street Fighter 2 skins.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're going to have a Chun-Li, a Guile, looks like Zangief, and Ryu.
[SPEAKER_05]: and those are all going to be available soon apparently it's actually been leaked out but they have the pictures online and I'd say that's pretty conclusive if you ask me but you know matter of time before these are released I could see maybe even next week so
[SPEAKER_05]: Got any?
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm sure they're going to be probably about like five bucks or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because they're usually about two bucks a skin.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I don't know how I feel about paying for the LittleBigPlanet skins.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just a little silly.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just download all the free ones.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I download the free ones too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you get the turkey stuck on your head?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I forgot to get that one.
[SPEAKER_04]: I got the Venus Flytrap one.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was the last one I remember getting.
[SPEAKER_05]: They also have one that's a TV stuck on their head.
[SPEAKER_04]: To be honest, I haven't played a lot of LittleBigPlanet lately thanks to World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't go out on Black Friday I went out to breakfast on Black Friday and we had a hard time trying to find a place to park in the damn parking lot and you know what it was a parking lot for?
[SPEAKER_04]: Mervins!
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what's big about Mervins?
[SPEAKER_04]: They all went out of business.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're not even doing anything for Black Friday except further liquidations.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I went to a theme park for Black Friday and I actually had a lot of freaking fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was fairly empty and I got to ride some pretty awesome coasters.
[SPEAKER_04]: Those of you from SoCal, X2 is awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just wanted to get that out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's talk about more gaming news.
[SPEAKER_04]: I did dog on the soundtrack for Super Street Fighter II Turbo HD Remix, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: The people at OC Remix do a lot of great remixes, and although I didn't enjoy these remixes in the particular game, I think these might be kind of fun to listen to outside of the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you want to, you can download the remix soundtrack for free!
[SPEAKER_04]: It's available right there at Overclocked Remix.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you go over to ocremix.org you can download the soundtrack for free.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Despite the hard time I gave this game earlier, it is very hard to complain about something that's free.
[SPEAKER_04]: So props to all these folks who spent their time putting it together.
[SPEAKER_04]: And don't get too mad at me because I dogged it in the game earlier.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do think it's a good thing they're putting it out there for free.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, speaking of Street Fighter 2 HD Remix, if you live in Europe, you have a little more time to think about whether you want to purchase it or not, especially if you're a PlayStation owner.
[SPEAKER_04]: No worries for you Xbox 360 folks, but the game was delayed on PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was released in North America as scheduled the day before it came out on Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: European 360 owners hopefully got the game a little late.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if it actually ended up coming out at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hopefully somebody in chat can clarify it, but it was delayed there in Europe.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's funny now that I think of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think they've got it by now, just so you know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I was just saying, I was wondering why they were releasing the PlayStation 3 version a day before the Xbox 360, but now that we think about it, that they don't have a demo for the PS3 version, people don't know that it sucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: And so, you know, that kind of goes back to your theory that that's why they kind of rushed the demo for it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And maybe, you know, one extra day without the demo, people can't try it and...
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think it's necessarily that Capcom thinks the game sucks because it's getting good reviews.
[SPEAKER_04]: Obviously, I'm just missing something.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess for the fighting fan diehard, all the little tweaks they've done with the game and so on to balance and so on make it worth it for them, which is fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Keep in mind, I am not a hardcore fighting game fan, nor have I ever confessed to be, but I do enjoy the occasional fighter.
[SPEAKER_04]: I actually do enjoy the Mortal Kombat games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know that makes me weird, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Soul Calibur, especially.
[SPEAKER_04]: Love Soul Calibur games.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, I'm getting off track.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Something else coming to the PlayStation Network, which has been teased before, I think, by us.
[SPEAKER_05]: Soldner X, which was a PC game, originally available, I think, mainly on PlayAsia.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: I remember tons of advertisements for it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Pretty awesome looking HD classic shooter game.
[SPEAKER_05]: They do have it available.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to be coming, apparently...
[SPEAKER_05]: Next week for $10, and it should be, of course, full HD, 1080p, two-player co-op support, leaderboards, and trophy support, and it looks fantastic.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that should be coming out.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think actually that's this Thursday is when we'll be making it out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yep, on the 4th for $10.
[SPEAKER_05]: So definitely worth checking it out, especially if you're a fan of Gradius or something like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really cool-looking game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would love to check this game out, but SingStar ABBA.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not going to have time.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've got Dancing Queen to sing to my heart's content.
[SPEAKER_05]: Personally, I just haven't really been downloading anything on the PlayStation Network because they don't have those prepaid cards.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't like buying my points.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like trading in crap that I don't want for points.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought they did now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought they did have the cards now.
[SPEAKER_05]: In certain stores, I don't think GameStop has them yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: GameStop GameStop GameStop
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, let's talk about some releases around the world that are going to be coming out in this next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we'll start off with Japan and what's coming out there on December the 4th on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fallout 3 gets its Japanese version this week, so check that out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Saints Row 2 also gets a Japanese release on December 4th.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you live in Japan and want to check out one of Loki's favorite games, Saints Row 2 is where it's at.
[SPEAKER_04]: On the PS3
[SPEAKER_04]: Assassin's Creed is getting a price reduction, but if you want some new games, you can check out ProYaku Spirits 5 Kanzaban is coming out as well as Saints Row 2 on the PlayStation 3, both on December 4th.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you want to look at some other consoles like the Nintendo Wii, you can get Wii Speak comes out on December 4th.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the standalone thing there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cooking Mama 2, Taihan Mama wa Oshiyogashi comes out from Taito.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cooking Mama 2 in Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: on the Nintendo Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if you want to check this game out, 428 is the name of the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: 428, Fusa Sarita Shibuya Day comes out.
[SPEAKER_04]: An interactive graphic novel.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that looks kind of neat, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: It looks like real actors.
[SPEAKER_05]: It got a perfect score from Famitsu.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, perfect.
[SPEAKER_04]: 40 out of 40.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yet you don't hear much about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now here's a game that looks like it could work for a hardcore game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, it's got live cutscenes mixed in it and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: So this isn't a game that they can really release here at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not without some major overhaul.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have to reshoot everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's too bad because there's a game that might be something that us American, we hardcore gamers are looking for.
[SPEAKER_04]: Unfortunately, I'll have to understand Japanese, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, PlayStation 2, Dragon Ball Z, Infinite World comes out on December 4th on PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yet another Pachinko game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Volume 11 of Pachisla Koryuku series.
[SPEAKER_04]: And yes, it's another Evangelion PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pachinko Game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Real Road also comes out.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's R-O-D-E Road.
[SPEAKER_04]: Real Road comes out in regular and limited edition flavors on the PlayStation 2 this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it looks to be an adventure game but kind of with some role playing elements.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: and it's kind of a busy week on the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: Another Pachinko game there as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hajime no Ippo, The Fighting comes out as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Busy, busy.
[SPEAKER_04]: And as far as the PSP goes, I don't think there's a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh no, they got a big, big game coming out this week in Japan on PSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: One big release, one big, big game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loco Roco 2 comes out this week in Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a big, big title there in Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: SingStar Classics Animal Crossing Let's Go to the City Prince of Persia PlayStation 3
[SPEAKER_04]: and Nintendo DS all this next week in Europe.
[SPEAKER_04]: And also, if you're a Fire Emblem fan, that's a big title coming out on the DS as well as some Dragon Ball Z titles, Dragon Ball Z Origins.
[SPEAKER_04]: And lastly, one PC title I want to get out there, Gothic 3 Forsaken Gods.
[SPEAKER_04]: Those are your Europe release dates this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Filling in for Dark Sakura tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: U.S., not a whole lot coming out this week, but this is the biggest week of December.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's pretty sad.
[SPEAKER_05]: But this week we have Destroy Humans, Path of the Theron on Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Neopets Puzzle Adventure on PC, DS, and Wii, I believe.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mushroom Men, Rise of the Fungi for DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nancy Drew, The White Wolf on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_05]: SlingoQuest on the DS Mushroom and the Spore Wars on the Wii Prince of Persia on PS3 and Xbox 360 Grand Theft Auto 4 on PC MyFitnessCoach on the Wii
[SPEAKER_05]: Tales of Despereaux on the PS2, Wii, and DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: The last game from Brash because they went under.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fun, fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: My Fun Facts Coach from Ubisoft.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wordfish from Ubisoft, both on the DS there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kingdom Hearts Chains of Memories on PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: SingStar Abba Vampire Story Ski and Shoot Prince of Persia The Fallen King DS
[SPEAKER_05]: and Animal Boxing on the DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: I remember that Destiny game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kind of a weird looking thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Family Party 30.
[SPEAKER_05]: Great games.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's from Game Factory and I think it's actually a port of a simple series game from the...
[SPEAKER_05]: Dreamer Puppy Trainer King of Fighters Orochi Saga on the Wii
[SPEAKER_05]: Happy Cooking on the DS from Ubisoft Spray
[SPEAKER_05]: Some crappy French games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Emma at the Farm and Emma in the Mountains.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love your description.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just some crappy French games.
[SPEAKER_05]: They are really bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's for little girls.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's really bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then Bigfoot Collision Course on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that is it for the first week of December.
[SPEAKER_05]: And sadly, that is the most populated week of the month.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well, hey, if you're not looking to get new games, you can still continue to supplement the ones you have from download content.
[SPEAKER_04]: And in January, Fallout 3 is going to be getting some new download content.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fallout 3 is one of those games I probably won't have the time to check out until January, so this will be just in time for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Operation Anchorage, which is where you go into a military simulation and you actually get to save Anchorage, Alaska from Chinese communist invaders.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, not Sarah Palin.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess it's in the Fallout story.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Pit.
[SPEAKER_04]: You get to go to a raider town called The Pit, which is outside of Pittsburgh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Get it?
[SPEAKER_04]: The Pit?
[SPEAKER_04]: Ha!
[SPEAKER_04]: That's coming out in February, and then Broken Steel is coming out in March.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's where you get to join the Brotherhood of Steel.
[SPEAKER_04]: and forget it.
[SPEAKER_04]: How can I follow a 90210 joke?
[SPEAKER_05]: Fable 2 is getting some download content as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: They just announced the brand new island that they're adding called Knothole Island.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's going to feature a bunch of cool stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're going to have three unique quests and three unique dungeons.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can unravel the mystical secrets of the Resurrection Shrine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Plus they're going to have some new outfits.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like an armored knight outfit, an assassin, a barbarian, leather clad biker.
[SPEAKER_05]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_05]: And six new weapons, a dozen of unique potions that I guess will drastically alter your appearance, new weapon customization, I guess they're going to have new augments, and 50 additional leaderboards.
[SPEAKER_05]: and along with that they're going to have actually some free download content as well in case you don't want to buy it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And of course that Knothole pack is going to be 800 Microsoft points.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can I just say though that Knothole is a terrible name because it makes me think of a very naughty place because Knothole sounds too much like Balloon Knot.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a really bad, bad name for an expansion pack.
[SPEAKER_05]: Knothole Island with the biker outfit.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just saying, yo.
[SPEAKER_04]: You thought Animal Crossing was gay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just saying.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, and apparently, I guess the free download pack they're going to have is some stuff, I guess, teasing from the main download thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're going to have Knight's Boots, Assassin's Gloves, a special weight loss potion, and a collectible silver book.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you'll also want to download that in case you don't want to buy this content so you can play co-op with people that do.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that might be good too.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a rumor now that Fable 2 will be hitting PCs sometime soon.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently, an inside source claims that they've heard some information, I guess from someone at Lionhead, that Fable 2 would be coming to PCs on February 15th.
[SPEAKER_05]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: Teehee!
[SPEAKER_04]: Heeheehee!
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a game called Gabo, and it's actually a reworked version of Seaman 2, apparently.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is all coming from Yut Saito's blog, and he's the guy who invented Seaman, if you can believe it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And apparently, I guess it's still like a year away?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a ways off for this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: But they have actually a little demo on the blog that you can look at, which is kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, if you're a big fan of this series, which, you know, the series did have its fans, despite our whole little five-year-old joking.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's just interesting to see the iPhone kind of get more and more and more games.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, there was some rumor out there that the iPhone has crossed like 10,000 different apps.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that's a little high, but there's definitely a lot of stuff available on the iPhone now.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's always room for C-Men on an iPhone.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyways, there was a rumor...
[SPEAKER_05]: That I may have talked about a few weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or do I?
[SPEAKER_05]: About the new 360s that will be coming out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually shipping now, apparently.
[SPEAKER_05]: With onboard memory.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: The new arcade systems are supposedly shipping with the new Jasper chipset.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which promises a cooler 65 nanometer GPU on the motherboard.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they have...
[SPEAKER_05]: expanded the onboard flash to 256 megabytes, which would be enough for storing the new Xbox experience.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I guess going forward, it's of course going to be preloaded on all the different systems.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can also use that space for game saves or whatever else you want to use it for.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just like an extra...
[SPEAKER_05]: 200 megs of space, which is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: And apparently, I think the arcade system still will be coming with an external 256 megabyte memory card, so they're kind of doubling the onboard space with that, which is kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_05]: And new is always good.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you've known this for a while now, haven't you?
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: You tell me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, anyhow...
[SPEAKER_04]: Professor Layton, the first movie is going to be coming out in January of 2010.
[SPEAKER_04]: in Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if you don't know this series, Studio Ghibli definitely kind of influenced these games.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's probably not much of a surprise.
[SPEAKER_04]: They didn't make the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: They just influenced the games.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not a big surprise that this is going to be made into a movie eventually.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you'll have to get a sub or something if you want to watch it here in the US or just pray that it'll come out here eventually.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, because they've had at least three or four different releases in that series in Japan.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just we haven't seen them all over here yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it makes sense, and they're insanely popular over there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Heck, I mean, they made an Animal Crossing movie over there too, remember?
[SPEAKER_04]: Just to answer GameGuru's thing in chat, is Studio Ghibli making it?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, they are not.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was just saying that the games are Studio Ghibli-esque.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just a comparison.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't want to alarm anybody.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't be alarmed.
[SPEAKER_04]: So now it's my turn tonight to pick a classic game of the week that I think you all ought to be playing.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm going to really dig deep tonight because I've been promising for quite some time that if I ever get to do another classic video game of the week, I would pick something from the Commodore 64.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is exactly what I've picked tonight as a game from my childhood that I remember from a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a game called Lazy Jones is tonight's classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, the interesting thing about Lazy Jones is that it was a game that was kind of made up of all these other smaller games that kind of came together in this big entity.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was like WarioWare back before there was WarioWare, if this makes any sense at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: And yeah, we're looking at a video of this game in progress here in the studio, and you can see this minigame, you are stabbing turkeys coming off a conveyor belt with a giant fork, and you have to avoid stabbing the telephone that's randomly bouncing around the screen.
[SPEAKER_04]: and DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: The Spectrum Version
[SPEAKER_04]: The video games are somewhat inspired by other games.
[SPEAKER_04]: There are definitely games that are like Frogger, like Space Invader in here.
[SPEAKER_04]: But there's also some games that have funny names.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like there's a game in here called 99 Red Balloons.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is a game where you just have red balloons that continually go up towards the top of the screen.
[SPEAKER_04]: You try to get a hold of a couple of the balloons, and if you're able to do that, then you can get up to the top and give a woman a big kiss.
[SPEAKER_04]: and then you get a balloon to go back down where you go up and down by grabbing these different balloons and none of these games go on a particularly long time you just play the game for about a minute until the clock runs out and your score basically transfers to the larger score that you have so this game is really wacky and just kind of takes us back to a time when you know really really was only one person that made games but the other thing that kind of made Lazy Jones special at least to me was the fact that it had a really unique soundtrack and I know you can kind of hear it in the background
[SPEAKER_04]: is definitely kind of its own little thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, I want to play for you one clip in particular from the game Lazy Jones by David Whitaker.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to see if it sounds familiar to you at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's a clip from the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now that's a clip from the Lazy Jones game that came out years ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did that sound familiar to anybody at all?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it actually was sampled years later in 1999 by a band.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was actually sampled by the group Zombie Nation.
[SPEAKER_04]: Current craft 400.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah, it's the same song.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, kind of funny, because the game was, you know, originally made with the C64 sound chip in it, and it's that kind of unique noise that is still used today.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, back to the clip here a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I think one reason I just really remember this game was, you know, like I said, it was really awesome to have one video game that had, like, all these mini-games in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you just kept trying to really increase your score in the mini-games, because some of them were really hard.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because some of them would end, like...
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah, here's the random... There's two random doors, because there's only 15 minigames, so like 18 doors.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's random things you'll walk into as well, like there's a broom closet that you'll randomly walk into, and then a potty.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you watch your guy go to the bathroom.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not explicitly or gross, but he just walks in there and then walks out.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's so random.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, there it is!
[SPEAKER_04]: Lazy Jones for the Commodore 64 my classic game of the week and stowing away on a DarkSakura's classic game of the week segment she'll be back next week with her own pick
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, that's going to do it for Part A of Orange Lounge Radio tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: And when we come back, we'll have plenty more in Part B. We're going to talk about the Nintendo Wii a little bit and some of the top secret things going on with the Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: Talk a little Chrono Trigger and talk some PC games, which we don't talk about enough.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we'll also open up the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_04]: All when we come back with more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we're back here on Orange Lounge Radio on this lovely Sunday evening, November the 30th of 2008.
[SPEAKER_04]: One more month left in the year, if you can believe it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tomorrow will be on the 1st of December.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura has the night off.
[SPEAKER_05]: However though,
[SPEAKER_05]: I believe, because Nintendo would not be so kind as to release an Excite Truck 2 so soon, it's probably going to be F-Zero.
[SPEAKER_05]: Would be my guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which is not necessarily bad, because Excite Truck was awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't even think about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you keep that kind of awesome control...
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't mind if they release an Excite Truck 2 because I would be there lined up at midnight ready to buy that game.
[SPEAKER_05]: That game was awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Excite Truck, absolutely most favorite game of the Wii ever.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do think F-Zero's gotta come out sooner rather than later.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even though the AXGX thing, I guess, must have disappointed some folks.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love F-Zero GX.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's an amazing game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I really hope... Yeah, as GameGuru says in chat, F-Zero WX would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um...
[SPEAKER_04]: or as Actdeft says in chat, chat.orangeentree.com Excite Truck 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Excite yourself.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think Excite Truck 2 would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: You don't even need to... This is one of those games that I would hope that they don't go back and try to tweak too much of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just add a lot more tracks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Add the ability to download new tracks later on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe four-player split-screen multiplayer or four-player multiplayer over the Wi-Fi service.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just really simple stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: They don't really need to go too crazy with it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe improve the graphics a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, on F-Zero, you could have up to 30 people in a race on the GX.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if they could do that online.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: As long as you can't cheat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, you know, Mario Kart, everybody cheats.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I would have a feeling they probably would be able to cheat somehow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, GS68 says it perfectly in chat.
[SPEAKER_04]: F-Zero Wii needs to not have exploits, damn it.
[SPEAKER_04]: F-Zero X has wall raping.
[SPEAKER_04]: F-Zero GX has space flying and snaking and so on.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, um, hopefully, yeah, hopefully it's, whatever it is, it's probably going to be awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because, like I said, Excite Truck was awesome, F-Zero would be really cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm hoping for another Excite Truck or F-Zero game.
[SPEAKER_05]: If it's something new, great, you know, news always, you know, optimistically good, I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe this will be something they announce at E3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe that's why it's such a big secret.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they have been working on it for two years now.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's true, because what have you seen since Excite Truck?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's why you haven't seen Excite Truck 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: And do you think it would take them two years to make Excite Truck 2?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm hoping it is F-Zero.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_04]: If they're going to make it super awesome, maybe.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you think it might be randomly a non-racing game?
[SPEAKER_04]: Or do you think no?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_05]: This company only makes racing games.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that's good, because you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: They know how to make a good racing game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm optimistic.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, Capcom has actually kind of put out a statement about why these games are not coming out on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: Street Fighter 2 couldn't ever be WiiWare even at 480p.
[SPEAKER_04]: The file size is just too large given the storage restrictions for WiiWare.
[SPEAKER_04]: Theoretically, it could be discs-based, but there are no plans at the moment.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: And to be honest, I mean, how good-looking would it really be if you took, like, an HD title and downscaled it to 480p?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just not even worth...
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: God, I even forgot what it's called, Virtual Console.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, and also in Japan, you remember next week we get Street Fighter versus, was it Tatsunoko or whatever?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or Capcom versus, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: See, that's what you need to be playing on there.
[SPEAKER_05]: They port that over and do something with it, that'd be pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, well, there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on to stuff going on on the DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, Chrono Trigger is coming out on the DS here.
[SPEAKER_04]: It just came out this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know anybody personally that picked it up.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm curious.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't played it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I did enjoy Chrono Trigger, but I still have to finish Final Fantasy IV on the DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: I got a lot of DS playing to do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, in Europe, of course, they got screwed and they don't have the game yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently, though, it is coming out in February.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what some sources have told Eurogamer, is that the game is supposed to be making its way out there in February.
[SPEAKER_04]: This, of course, the new Chrono Trigger DS version with the new dungeon, the new ending, two-screen display, touchscreen controls, Wi-Fi multiplayer, and so on and so on.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't get why it takes so long.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't get it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's already localized, so what's the delay for?
[SPEAKER_05]: The only thing I can think of is this time of year, as far as duplication goes, a lot of the plants that duplicate games are at full capacity right now, and if they're thinking that they're not going to be able to duplicate this game enough to have adequate supplies...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: But I want to get this comment from chat because I think it's good.
[SPEAKER_04]: VXJasonXV says, The only people clamoring for Street Fighter HD Remix on the Wii are the 13, 14, 15 year olds who don't have the money for their own systems and only have the family Wii and won't be getting the 360 or PS3 as a gift or anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good point.
[SPEAKER_04]: Get a job!
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go out and get a job.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just wait.
[SPEAKER_05]: Seriously, I mean...
[SPEAKER_05]: if there's anything you can learn from this whole Street Fighter Turbo HD remix thing is it pays to wait because if you bought the original Super Street Fighter 2 Turbo or whatever on Xbox Live Arcade now there's a new one that's coming out that's better it's like crap, I just wasted money on that remember if you wait for things to get ironed out there will be a version that will be coming to the Wii I'm sure
[SPEAKER_05]: Just have to be patient.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or get a job.
[SPEAKER_05]: Something else that might be coming to the Wii, and once again, this kind of goes back to the Chrono Trigger thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't understand why they couldn't just bring it over.
[SPEAKER_05]: The localization's done already.
[SPEAKER_05]: Disaster Day of Crisis may be coming to North America.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently, one person was emailing Nintendo customer support, I guess, regarding
[SPEAKER_05]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't see why they wouldn't because it's a Nintendo game.
[SPEAKER_05]: It takes no effort on their part to bring it over here.
[SPEAKER_04]: All the work's done already.
[SPEAKER_04]: At the same time, though, what if the dude was wrong?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think a lot of people are putting a lot of stock in what this rep says.
[SPEAKER_04]: What if they made a mistake?
[SPEAKER_05]: well if they made a mistake then yeah i could see but my point is it's done it's already been released in europe so it's translated already they've got it done it's just it bring it over if it's in english already you can bring it over here i'll see what the big while you're at it how about mother three right am i right translation hasn't been done over there
[SPEAKER_05]: It's better than Wii Music
[SPEAKER_04]: Didn't Mother 3 come out in the UK?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought it did.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, if it did, everyone wouldn't be bitching because they would be importing it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, I'm just crazy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, because there wouldn't be an issue with why would they even have to do a fan translation then because it's already done for them.
[SPEAKER_05]: There would be no more bitching.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well, apparently, We and WeFit have been a big cause of part of the Black Friday chaos.
[SPEAKER_04]: The most popular products out there on Black Friday this year, and of course, if you've never heard of this, you probably don't live in the U.S., Black Friday is the day after Thanksgiving where people go fucking nuts over sales just in time for Christmas.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's basically Canada's Boxing Day without any...
[SPEAKER_04]: It's all a consumer holiday, specifically, whereas I think there's actually some reason for it in Canada.
[SPEAKER_04]: But here, no, it was all made up by the stores.
[SPEAKER_04]: Number one most popular product on Black Friday was the Nintendo Wii console.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not a big surprise.
[SPEAKER_04]: Number five Wii Fit was the number five biggest product on Black Friday.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not surprised, eh?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not surprised.
[SPEAKER_05]: People will play it for a while and they'll be all excited about it and then they'll put it away.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I bet it's a bunch of parents also buying it for their fat kids, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fat Kids won't play that exercise game.
[SPEAKER_04]: VXJSNXV says, I thought Boxing Day was December 26th.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Instead of the day of Thanksgiving, they have the day after Christmas.
[SPEAKER_04]: But same idea.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's chaos at the stores.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I don't hear about Canadian Massacre at Walmart on Boxing Day either.
[SPEAKER_04]: Canadians are smart not to shop at Walmart.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, not just that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm assuming a little more civil because they didn't trample each other.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently there's some news that Rare may do a new Killer Instincts game.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know... How fucking often does this rumor come up?
[SPEAKER_04]: What now?
[SPEAKER_04]: What now has provoked the new Killer Instinct of the Week rumor?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, basically this is coming from...
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, their studio manager, Matt Betteridge, and he says, Killer Instinct is an IP that is fondly remembered and we may do something with it, but it's a tricky market to be like the old Killer Instinct.
[SPEAKER_05]: So basically, we would have to...
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't remember it being that awesome, so I don't really care if it comes out.
[SPEAKER_05]: And to be honest, I don't really care about most things that Rare puts out.
[SPEAKER_04]: So... No, I gotta say, it is pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love me some Killer Instinct.
[SPEAKER_04]: I really do.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's why it pisses me off.
[SPEAKER_05]: God, it just doesn't... I don't care.
[SPEAKER_04]: Orchid vs. Spinal.
[SPEAKER_04]: Come on, this game was awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, they would have to put a lot of work into it, and...
[SPEAKER_05]: As long as they throw in Cameo as an unlockable character because that would be weird.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you could brutally murder her and that would be funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_04]: YYR in chat says, I'm from Rare.
[SPEAKER_04]: Our official announcement is that there will be an official announcement made at an undisclosed time in our own heads.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, I am so angsty every time I hear this rumor about a freaking new Killer Instinct game because it seems like every other week there's some cryptic goddamn quote coming out of somebody's mouth from Rare that cock-teases a new Killer Instinct game.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm getting the more angsty, the more and more time that goes by and they won't announce something already.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, you know what this means.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, you can start us off tonight, because DarkSakura's not here.
[SPEAKER_05]: FQ to PopCap Games.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was busy transferring all my saves and all my information from my old 20GB hard drive to my new 120GB hard drive for my Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I bought the hard drive used, I do not have a transfer cable that can facilitate just transferring everything in all one foul swoop, so I had to actually use memory cards.
[SPEAKER_05]: And can you guess what two saves would not fucking transfer on there?
[SPEAKER_05]: Zuma and Bejeweled 2 both PopCap games and why the fuck will they not transfer over all the other games for all the other systems including some of the PopCap games transfer just fine but for some reason Bejeweled 2 and Zuma have to be a little bit which happen to be the two the wife has to have exactly and so and they will not transfer I put something on their Twitter you know saying hey what the fuck you know why is this not working they're like
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, we're looking into it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which means, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, complain, complain, complain.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hold on, hold on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, I know, despite this whole thing, me yelling at Rare, I know there are actually people from PopGapGames that do listen to this fair program here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Patch the bitch.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what we need to do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Patch this so that it will move.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, maybe this is the first time they're finding out about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's an odd error.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, that's not something that I think you could have foresight into either.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's just an error out of the blue.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that sounds like Microsoft's involved somehow, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is strange that it is...
[SPEAKER_04]: Just those two games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Normally the limitation is that you can only transfer files to a memory card with the same profile.
[SPEAKER_05]: So for example, I had to have a profile signed in on one console with the old hard drive and logged in as me and then had another console logged in as me as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just copied the profile.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I had to transfer from one profile to the memory card back to my profile on the other system.
[SPEAKER_05]: and it will allow you to do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: It won't allow you to transfer from a different profile or something like that because you can't do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: But those were the only two games that would not let me transfer them at all.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what else would not let me transfer it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hexic HD would not let me transfer that game to the other hard drive.
[SPEAKER_04]: And see, that's one of Microsoft's own games.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you think there's something on a deeper level going on here.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think you have misdirected anger.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, that they won't even let me re-download.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's stupid.
[SPEAKER_05]: So not that I really play that game, but it's still, come on, man.
[SPEAKER_05]: So like if I deleted that game somehow by accident, then I would never be able to get it back.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, my FUs of the week, I don't really have a lot.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to say FU to alcohol for being so nummy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I had my first little sip of alcohol in like seven months the other day.
[SPEAKER_04]: I said I would have a glass of wine on Thanksgiving and I had a Pinot Noir.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, it's kind of interesting that we're coming off of the FUs of the week to this, but there's a brand new website called Bad Hacks.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's badhacks.net, and it features a collection of ROM hacks that are, well, basically sexist, racist, homophobic, misogynistic, pro, and occasionally slightly amusing.
[SPEAKER_05]: and apparently you can download all sorts of really bad hacks on there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some of the interesting stuff on the list here and I'm just going to kind of go down the list real quick.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_05]: BabyMaker, BastardMaster, DeadBubbleBubble, DickAndMilk, DickKids, DickTales, FuckersQuest, GauntletXXX, GayGhostFuckers2, Homocop, InnerCityRansom, KillerMan, LittleRemo, TheChildAbuser, MarioNude, MegaCrap, MegaFag, MetalQueer,
[SPEAKER_05]: Naked Little Mermaid, Naked Samus, Nazi Dr. Mario, Nude Punch-Out, Orgy Time, Pot Man 3, and then some of these really elaborate ones.
[SPEAKER_05]: Happy Scrappy!
[SPEAKER_05]: Super Nazi Penis Cartel Freedom Fighters Leet, and, uh, South Park Zelda.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, that's not bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, what else here?
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh,
[SPEAKER_05]: Super Mario World Chaos Complex, Sex Pot Racing, fun fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, is it just me or is it a really fucking slow news week or something?
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, what the fuck?
[SPEAKER_05]: Why is this news?
[SPEAKER_05]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a really fucking slow news week.
[SPEAKER_04]: People have too much fucking time on their hands.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can also play Super Goatsy Brothers.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yippee, hooray, hi, yay, yip.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm so excited.
[SPEAKER_05]: But yeah, there's lots of interesting stuff on there.
[SPEAKER_04]: As if you couldn't find enough of these on your normal websites.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow, there's a whole website.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's an entire website about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's this God Hates You?
[SPEAKER_04]: What's that a hack of?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, it's like a... Is it a Bible game that they hacked or something?
[SPEAKER_04]: Spiritual Warfare is... Okay, interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Babymaker, what's that a hack of?
[SPEAKER_04]: Dig Dug!
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's gonna be classy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fun times.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Look, let's talk about PC.
[SPEAKER_04]: Look, if it's going to be a slow news week, then why don't we talk about some things we don't normally talk about here on the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's PC gaming news.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, you know the game Fear?
[SPEAKER_04]: This was a pretty popular game that came out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, it was console as well as PC, but I think it was pretty well known for the PC.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fear 2 Project Origin is the sequel to this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's apparently being banned in Australia.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was just recently refused classification by the Australian Classifications Board.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't they ban now?
[SPEAKER_04]: Due to high violence, apparently Warner's trying to assess the situation, and they are right now appealing with the ACB and trying to figure out their options, trying to get Fear 2 released in Australia.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was supposed to be coming out February 11th in Australia.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're hoping they can turn that around, but you might have to import an underground copy of this game if you want to play this over in Australia.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just buy the PS3 version.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's region-free.
[SPEAKER_04]: PC is region free too, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's get to the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the part of the show every week where we like to take some time to interact with you guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: You guys send us emails at mailbag at orangelaunchradio.com and we take some time to read our favorites here on the air.
... ...
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm opening up the mailbag right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hate it when we get freaking spam email.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did somebody sign us up for spam email?
[SPEAKER_04]: This is like a ha-ha-ha thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jerks.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I think Spider signed us up for spam email.
[SPEAKER_04]: It sucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't we disguise our emails on the side?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, but they still find a way.
[SPEAKER_04]: YYR sent us an email and wants to know, please tell us what the meaning of life is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, what is the meaning of life?
[SPEAKER_04]: To live.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can make the easy 42 joke here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or I could give you like a serious deep answer, but this is a show about dick and fart jokes.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if it would fit in here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me put it this way, the meaning of life is to have impact on others.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what I believe the meaning of life is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow, that's way too deep for this program.
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on, we have another email from Katakos.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, sometimes it goes by Reese.
[SPEAKER_04]: Lord Katakos wants to say congratulations on episode 300, even though it's not over 9,000.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yeah, you guys and girls just keep on going so you can get to 9,001 to be a prodigy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right now we're at 50%, but that's halfway there.
[SPEAKER_04]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rob, you need to get 100% healed.
[SPEAKER_04]: Come to the server Illidan and I'll use Healing Wave on you and you'll be good to go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just a general note to WoW players out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not changing servers.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I don't mean to be rude.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I have a guild of real life friends where I'm at on Ravencrest.
[SPEAKER_04]: As much as the community calls that server Raven Fail because we have no progression whatsoever on our server.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's pretty sad when our social guild is like one of the top 10 horde rating guilds on the entire server and we kind of sleep our way through.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't mean like literally, but we're very casual in our approach.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not to say we don't work hard.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're very casual in our approach and we've managed to clear quite a bit of stuff as a guild.
[SPEAKER_04]: These are most of the Death Cake people you remember from Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, I remember.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was going to say that we have over 9,000 minutes worth of programming, so there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a good way to look at it.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you count up all the to-go podcasts and all that stuff, when we were doing almost five hours a night for a little while, remember that?
[SPEAKER_04]: We'd do a three-and-a-half-hour show, then an hour-long podcast.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_04]: Those were the days, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, how was an email there from...
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not sure what the point was, but hey, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have an email from Fabrice in Belgium.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wants to say hello and I hope there's a show tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: And this was written last week when there was no show.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I want to apologize to Fabrice from Belgium.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: He says, anyways... He puts that in quotes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways...
[SPEAKER_04]: Like Loki style.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm planning on buying a pinball machine in the future as I understand the best pinball machines are arguably the Addams Family and Terminator 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I'm a big fan of Sega.
[SPEAKER_04]: This will probably be a question for DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which is the best Sega pinball machine?
[SPEAKER_04]: She's not here tonight, but if she were, I bet you anything she would say World Cup 98 because I'm almost positive that was the Sega table.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's like her favorite machine of all time.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm 99% certain that would be her answer.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know they're not the best machines by far, but I'm too big of a Sega fan to let this pass by.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is Independence Day any good?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll probably have a chance to buy that one.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do not know much about that table.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're right, DarkSakura would be the expert.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think I played that one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you?
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you remember that being good?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did Sega do the Jurassic Park one?
[SPEAKER_05]: I like that one.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't remember if they did that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was going to say they should have a Sonic spinball table.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wouldn't that be awesome?
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be kind of awesome with a blue pinball.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wouldn't that be cute?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: And thanks to Fabrice.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry the real pinball expert isn't here tonight to answer the question.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll have to ask her for next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Boy, you just struck out.
[SPEAKER_04]: First, we didn't do a show.
[SPEAKER_04]: The night you were going to stay up and listen, and I really apologize for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then the night you have your question read on air, DarkSakura's not even here to answer it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did Sega do Jurassic Park?
[SPEAKER_04]: That was a fun promotion.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll have to ask her next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hopefully I remember.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's go to another email.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's from Dan Shadow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey guys, survived the gaming season?
[SPEAKER_04]: What surprised you the most?
[SPEAKER_04]: Personally, Left 4 Dead blew me away.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to be up in the area next weekend, which I believe is this weekend.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whoops.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe we can meet up.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'd like to meet you all.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oops.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, hopefully he comes back because apparently he didn't make it out tonight because we were off last week and didn't even ever get to our emails.
[SPEAKER_04]: are bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's our last email tonight from Cheeseburger.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, OLR, I want to buy my dad a PlayStation 3 for Christmas.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's pretty ambitious.
[SPEAKER_04]: We just got a 52-inch plasma LCD TV and all we have is crappy cable.
[SPEAKER_04]: Where do you guys and girls think is the best place to buy it?
[SPEAKER_04]: All I want is the Blu-ray player and don't intend on playing any games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Websites are okay options too as long as I can use my unverified PayPal account.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ooh, in that case, you might just want to go for a used PlayStation 3 from eBay.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: Cyber Monday, Tomorrow
[SPEAKER_04]: so tomorrow would be a good day to kind of check your big retailer websites to look for big deals and the reason why they wait until Monday is because a lot of people do their online shopping at work and Monday's the first day back to work for most people including myself so you're going to see a lot of good deals on Cyber Monday online if that's where you're looking to buy things so keep an eye out
[SPEAKER_04]: Keep an eye out.
[SPEAKER_04]: And don't be afraid to use sites like Frugal, Google's shopping site, to look for good deals.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, a PS3 is a PS3 is a PS3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cheap-ass gamer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that's a good site, too, especially with games.
[SPEAKER_04]: So keep an eye out.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: it's funny, I was looking in chat they were talking about Commander Keen they actually have ported a clone of Commander Keen for the Wii, it's in their homebrew community now, you can download Commander Keen for the Wii that's kind of neat
[SPEAKER_04]: I got one more email from Rob with two B's about the Wii and says, this one's for Matt.
[SPEAKER_04]: I recently upgraded my Wii firmware.
[SPEAKER_04]: Guess what?
[SPEAKER_04]: My SD card was completely wiped clean.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is a shame because I don't have a homebrew channel or anything on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you hear of anything similar?
[SPEAKER_04]: I had painstakingly backed up my game channel so that I wouldn't need to download them again.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some I deleted from my Wii memory because of the incredible daunting size of WiiWare.
[SPEAKER_04]: Grr, argh.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, well, here's the thing, um, I didn't update my system at all because I don't connect to their, you know, internet for, I don't connect to the store.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because to be honest, I don't buy anything on there and there's nothing I need to download and if I wanted to download...
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: Unless I get a WeSpeak microphone, I'll need to update it for the WeSpeak channel, which I probably still wouldn't do because I wouldn't use that.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, no, I haven't updated it yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Although, if you have updated it, I believe there's a new Twilight hack out now for the 3.4 firmware, and you can download that and redo all your stuff if you need to.
[SPEAKER_04]: It sounds to me, though, that Rob is not into this whole hacking homebrew thing at all, like me.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just not into it because I don't have time.
[SPEAKER_04]: So why did his SD card get picked on?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I don't know why it wiped your SD card unless you had modified saves on there or something, but unless they're trying to get you to update it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't understand why they would want you to re-download everything.
[SPEAKER_05]: That doesn't make any sense.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, um...
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, Nintendo sucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's Team Twizers or Tweezers or whatever they're called.
[SPEAKER_05]: So there's other games that they've already figured out exploits to that can be used instead of Twilight Princess.
[SPEAKER_05]: So this by all means is not an end.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well that's going to do it for tonight's Mailbag.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you want to send us an email, DarkSakura will hopefully be back next week to read your emails.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, other fun stuff that's going to be going on here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, this isn't really fun, but FunCom, the company behind such wonderful games like The Age of Conan.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, they've had to cut staff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently, hard times have been had, and last Tuesday they actually had to...
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, plus just Age of Conan I don't think lived up to expectations.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think there were a lot of people that bought that, played the one month trial, and didn't stay with it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I could see that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was going to check out the game, but just kind of never got around to it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now it seems to be going the way of Tabula Rasa, which is kind of sad.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a lot of MMOs out there and Warcraft is kind of owning a lot of them in the face.
[SPEAKER_04]: Only very few are able to hold their own against it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll tell you what though, if you like God of War and you own a 360 and will have never an opportunity to play God of War on the 360, you should check out Conan, the actual Conan game that they released because it is such a blatant ripoff of God of War, it's not even funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: But there's boobies and lots of blood and that's all you really need.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, that's all you need.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, PC games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really old PC games, but really classic PC games.
[SPEAKER_04]: StarCraft is over 10 years old and just got patched this past week to patch 1.16.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: So it'll only use as much as it needs.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's some other tiny little exploits, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: It does some little exploits with the Zerg race, especially, that were fixed.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that's great that Blizzard is still patching this game 10 years later.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we have somebody in chat, VXXXV, is like, I've been waiting for that.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Korea rejoices.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what's neat about that?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to make a lot of people go back and re-look at StarCraft.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just like the Burnout Paradise thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a great way to keep your game alive even after maybe it's kind of been cut out.
[SPEAKER_05]: While there's some interesting stuff coming out, of course, some more download content for Rock Band, the weekly stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: This week they actually have a new free track that you can download, which is the track Headphones On by Miranda Cosgrove.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's going to be released alongside a bunch of other songs, including Are You Dead Yet?
[SPEAKER_05]: by the Children of Bottom.
[SPEAKER_05]: Looks like Finley with Tato E. Possible.
[SPEAKER_05]: and these are all European bands, by the way.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then this is kind of weird, Naked Brothers Band.
[SPEAKER_05]: They've got Body I Occupy and I Don't Want to Go to School.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess crossing over to the Nickelodeon crowd there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Pilatero Y2 with Hey Poco Rock and Roll.
[SPEAKER_05]: Squeeze with Tempted, Tokyo Hotel with Ready, Set, Go.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: And All American Rejects with Real World.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it should be noted that all these are for 80 Microsoft points instead of the usual 160, and they're only on sale, I believe, for the month of December.
[SPEAKER_05]: So after that, they will go back up to their normal price.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sales everywhere for the holiday season.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, yeah, they had a lot of sales actually on the PlayStation Network, and so there's a bunch of titles that were half off.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I didn't even talk about it during my gaming week, but I got to play Echo Chrome.
[SPEAKER_04]: My friend has a game, Echo Chrome.
[SPEAKER_04]: What a strange little puzzle game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of fun, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's now the right price, $5.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I noticed they have all these user-created levels and things.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a pretty chill game.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a good way to put it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a chill, chill-out game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was playing Flow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember that game?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I went back and played a little bit of that because Nellie's like, what's that?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a lot of relaxing music there.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm like, yeah, it's this game Flow.
[SPEAKER_05]: You move the controller around.
[SPEAKER_05]: She's like, I don't want to have to move the controller around like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm like, too bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um...
[SPEAKER_05]: Then in other news, apparently obsessive gamers are not necessarily addicted to games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently 90% of hardcore gamers do not have a legitimate addiction problem.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is coming from a brand new survey mainly focused on I think some of the WoW players and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course there's all sorts of disorders out there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some people just take their hobbies a little bit more seriously than others, but that doesn't necessarily mean that they can't stop.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sometimes I think I can't stop, so maybe I have a problem.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or not.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not playing well, so that's already saying something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, wait a minute, what are you trying to say?
[SPEAKER_04]: Every time I power on the Xbox, there you are in Saints Row 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm only going to play that until I'm done with it, and then once I'm done with it, then...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you know what's interesting about these expansions is that there's no new classes.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's not a lot of big things that are expanded here.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're story expansions.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're only going to be downloadable through the PlayOnline viewer, and they are all supposed to come out in spring 2009.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry, I take that back.
[SPEAKER_04]: The first one is supposed to come out in spring 2009 with the other two following.
[SPEAKER_04]: The first one is called A Crystalline Prophecy, Ode of Life Bestowing.
[SPEAKER_04]: A Shantoto Ascension, The Legend Torn, Her Empire Born
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: I wish they'd overhaul the engine to make it newer, gen graphics and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think I could take it if they released a new Final Fantasy Online game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Would you go back, you think?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: If they fixed it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the first effort.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you know, I hear this whole level sync thing really helped.
[SPEAKER_04]: That whole thing where basically if you're a level 75, you can downgrade yourself in level and all your gear will scale so that you can level up with your level 40 friend who can't find a party because he's level 40 and level with them.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you both gain experience.
[SPEAKER_05]: See, that'd be nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm like, oh my god, that's what that game needed three fucking years ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would just level down to level 1 and just grind down there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hell yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: It'd be awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: So...
[SPEAKER_04]: I throw gamers and WoW players in two different categories.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm already starting to get a little offended here.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a friend whose behavior completely transforms when he plays WoW.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye-bye social interaction.
[SPEAKER_04]: Otherwise, he's just fine when playing other games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow is kind of a social game though, you know, in a way.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's an old saying though, amongst people who know better, real life greater than wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I don't put wow first before real life commitments.
[SPEAKER_05]: Final Fantasy Online just felt really different.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was like kind of...
[SPEAKER_05]: It was cool because when I first started, it was like, oh my god, you know, you think when you first get to the first force and stuff, it's so big, and then you're like, oh, there's planes beyond that.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like, holy crap, it's actually discovering the world and stuff, and then you go through all of it, and then it's like, eh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like the first time you board an airship, you're like, this is so fucking epic, and you know, just all this.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will never forget the first time getting on a ship.
[SPEAKER_04]: in Final Fantasy XI and then pirates fucking attacked the ship and I was like, oh my god, this is so scary and I was like having to run into the basement of the ship and lock yourself in there while the higher level characters were taking out the things but I thought that was so amazing how you would basically be forced to work together with the other players to take out the threat or you all die, basically it was neat or you have to lock yourself in the basement like a scared little kid like I did
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course, and they do some of those area effect spells and it might still hit you anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Swipe back into the corner and cry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Curl into it slash fetal.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, gosh, that's going to do it, believe it or not, for tonight's gaming news.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was a little bit of a slow news week this week, but hey, that just leaves us some time to get to your calls at 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio while we wait for some calls.
[SPEAKER_04]: Any last minute things you want to talk about, Loki?
[SPEAKER_05]: Um...
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you can think about it, because we've got a call coming in.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, it's Spazinator.
[SPEAKER_04]: Spazinator.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's on your mind, dude?
[SPEAKER_08]: This may be kind of a downer for the show, but I'm kind of a wit's end right here, and I could use a little help from the All Games Radio audience at large, specifically any listeners that may be in the Buffalo area.
[SPEAKER_08]: As I had mentioned to Loki in a private message earlier in the week on Xbox Live, I just recently had my PlayStation 3 stolen, and I'm hoping that any listeners out there that may be in the Buffalo area may have heard
[SPEAKER_08]: or seeing something through Grapevine, maybe Rumor, seeing someone that normally doesn't have a PlayStation 3 on them and could relay any information to the Buffalo Police Department, specifically District E. Basically, any kind of lead would be great because, well, it's kind of like too full for me.
[SPEAKER_08]: A, it's not exactly something I can easily replace.
[SPEAKER_08]: and B, while it should be fairly evident that I'm disabled and the PlayStation 3 X is like a coping skill for me in dealing with my disability and subsequently after my disability has been acted up and I've been getting
[SPEAKER_08]: and some things like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that way I could kind of like... As long as you only have one user, it will do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Otherwise, it will sit in the select user screen type thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, technically my profile did.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the key thing was it had my credit card information on there.
[SPEAKER_08]: And because of that, I really did two things.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, I canceled my credit card and no idea if I was able to remote access my account using my PSP to change the password on my PlayStation Network account.
[SPEAKER_08]: That way no one could get onto the profile and buy anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: Any chance that you called Sony and see, I don't know if they would do this, but maybe if you've told them what happened, see what the last IP was to access it?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm reaching here.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know what you can do in these scenarios, but that would be my first thought, is to call Sony and see when the last time that thing signed in was.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I did bring this up, and in fact, I thought up the same thing, and the only thing they can do is,
[SPEAKER_08]: If I were to have left my password as was, the only thing they could do is see if anyone would try to input their own credit card information onto my profile.
[SPEAKER_08]: And if they did, I would have their name and address and whatnot, but at the same time as
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not totally sure, but I think it's kind of iffy because if they input their credit card information, chances are they could also change my password too, and even I won't be able to access my own account, you know?
[SPEAKER_04]: That seems a little weak from Sony.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think there'd be a little more they could do to help in this situation.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe they need a police report or something to be able to do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have no idea.
[SPEAKER_04]: Unfortunately, I've never been in this situation, but...
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, buddy, I hope it helps for whatever reason.
[SPEAKER_04]: Again, if anybody has heard of anything about this, let us know and we'll forward it over to Spazinator or just contact the police for heaven's sake.
[SPEAKER_04]: And this goes in general.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I guess we could kind of turn this into more of a community thing for everybody in all parts of the U.S.
[SPEAKER_04]: because unfortunately it leaves gamers like Spazinator in the cold if we support...
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, purchasing these stolen systems and things like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you know of these things going on, do the right thing and let police people know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, really.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, thanks for your support.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's definitely appreciated.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hopefully I'll get some good news soon, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well we're hoping for you, Spazinator.
[SPEAKER_04]: Keep us posted.
[SPEAKER_08]: I will do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, good luck, buddy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ah, what a bummer.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not going to ask how it was stolen.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope the house didn't get broken into or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yikes, not a fun situation.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Time of day, Orange Lounge Radio land.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Jason.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, Jason.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope you have some better news.
[SPEAKER_04]: The last call was a little bit of a downer.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I was hearing bits and pieces because I was helping Ryan with something and trying to make sure all the volumes are set nicely in here and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_02]: How is Ryan?
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_02]: How is she doing?
[SPEAKER_02]: She's busy.
[SPEAKER_02]: She's in school now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know she used to listen to the show back in the day but hasn't had enough time lately, but let her know we said hello.
[SPEAKER_02]: They said hello.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, she's right there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, she's listening over my shoulder.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ah, wonderful, wonderful.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's on your mind, Jason?
[SPEAKER_02]: That StarCraft news was really good to hear.
[SPEAKER_02]: I saw you get all excited in chat.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, this is something that dates back to when I lived in New Mexico in like, I don't know, maybe 2001 or 2002?
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe 10 years ago, Jason?
[SPEAKER_02]: With how old this game is?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, not that early, but...
[SPEAKER_02]: When I remember, the thing that sticks out most in my mind, this is going to be the weirdest thing I've ever really said, but the thing that sticks out most in my mind is just how far back reaching this goes in the sense that the fact that online replays were able to be saved at, I don't know, 1.03 or something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: When that feature came out, that was amazing, especially because the file size for any average game was less than 10k.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then when I first did it, I played a couple games with some people, and then I went back and watched the replays.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was like, well, wait a second.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was discussing with them strategy and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to see that too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Never could.
[SPEAKER_02]: They just now put this in.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's my high school life coming back to say, hey, I'm cool again.
[SPEAKER_04]: Isn't that weird?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, why would they add that now, of all things?
[SPEAKER_04]: Isn't that so strange?
[SPEAKER_02]: I started playing through the campaigns again, and it was fun, it still is.
[SPEAKER_04]: One of the other little features in the patch we didn't mention is that now you can use slash R to reply directly to the person you last talked to, that's another new feature in the patch.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a Warcraft thing, which I thought was kind of funny, because that's exactly what you do in WoW, to reply to people.
[SPEAKER_02]: How much of a surprise, woo!
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Synergy amongst the thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: And speaking of WoW, I know you didn't call the talk WoW, but I've got to mention this.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Armory got a huge upgrade this week, and those achievements that you've been getting on your character, now you can look at them in the Armory online.
[SPEAKER_04]: But not only that, like, if I were to look, like, I've got to show Loki this, because he's a big achievement whore, so he'd kind of think this is funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I'm explaining what I'm doing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to the Armory right now, and I'm looking up the achievements for my character, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: And, like, look at this.
[SPEAKER_04]: It breaks down exactly which achievements I have and what categories and all that, but not just that.
[SPEAKER_04]: If I want to look at a particular achievement, let's say general.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's one achievement I've been going for lately is...
[SPEAKER_04]: to all the squirrels I've loved before.
[SPEAKER_04]: Show the critters of Azeroth how much you slash love them.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you get a 10-point achievement if you're able to find every little creature in Azeroth and type slash love, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, not only is the armory tracking that I have that achievement enough, but if I click on it, it shows exactly which six I've slash loved and which ones I have yet to do.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's fairly comprehensive.
[SPEAKER_04]: integration like this is a great thing it's always 10 years delayed in StarCraft's case but anything like this to integrate that much you don't have to start up the entire game just to see this information it's almost always a good thing to have and I also want to show Loki this I can put in my ex-boyfriend's account and compare and I can see right there no no but I can see just I can notice that I have 360 more achievement points than he does and that makes me feel better about myself awesome there you go
[SPEAKER_02]: No, Rob's not an achievement whore.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, not at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I'm just sad and pathetic.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, so back to StarCraft.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything else you want to share about what's going on?
[SPEAKER_02]: I just want to see what the StarCraft 2 requirements are going to be.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's not like it's coming out holiday season or anything, so I shouldn't be jumping the gun or anything, but it's going to be... Wasn't it either that or Diablo 3 that isn't actually likely before 2010?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I think I remember hearing something about that, but yeah, that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_04]: I bet you we see, I bet you we'll finally get StarCraft 2 next year.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it was playable at PAX, for heaven's sake.
[SPEAKER_04]: It will probably be out next year, just in time for the holidays, and then you'll probably get Diablo 3 in 2010.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just in time to buy three games.
[SPEAKER_02]: But we've already beat that topic to death.
[SPEAKER_04]: Consider we're one month away from 2009 and 2010 doesn't seem that far off because that's probably when we're going to see Final Fantasy XIII as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: This year went by so fast.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it was a crazy year.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, buddy.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to let you go to get to more calls, all right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Such is life.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have a good one, buddy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye, folks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wanted to call in last week because of where I was.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, failed, I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I saw the pictures in your live journal.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tell us about the trip you went on.
[SPEAKER_06]: And where exactly did you go in San Francisco?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, a few different places.
[SPEAKER_06]: There was a
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh man, well we saw the Blacks Museum, so what I wanted to call about was this incredible arcade that I got to go to.
[SPEAKER_06]: There was a whole bunch of old games, like this link I'm posting is an old arcade, it's an old pinball game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which arcade was this at?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I go to San Francisco quite often, and I, for some reason, have decided to never seek, I somehow have never seeked this place out.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I know the Pier 39 arcade and some of those other things, but where exactly was this, and how did you find it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, man, I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'd have to ask about it, but... Well, what made you think to go there?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, it was my mom's suggestion.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who would have thunk it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, on my photo bucket.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything else you want to share about your week?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go for it.
[SPEAKER_06]: One of the games I was playing, one of the games I was playing in San Francisco was the old 1976 game Death Race.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah, this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, man, that's an old, old game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think I remember that coming up on the show not that long ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, okay, what did you think?
[SPEAKER_04]: You got to play that, and what did you think?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I thought it was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: I even made a remake for the PC.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll have to dig that up and link it in chat, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dark Tattoo, you have a good one, buddy.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to take some more calls.
[SPEAKER_04]: Take care, bud.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, he's cutting out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, can you hear me?
[SPEAKER_04]: You're cutting out a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you have any other things running, like torrents, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whoa.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_04]: No!
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, I'm hanging up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's do this.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't usually do this, but we'll try this.
[SPEAKER_04]: This will sometimes help.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey there, GS68?
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, let's try this shit again.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, it sounds a little better this time.
[SPEAKER_04]: What is on your mind, GS68?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well... Okay... Besides that, I'll get around to playing... Well, Echo.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think there might be an audio thing going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go ahead.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck this shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fuck this shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi, you're on Works Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh wow, what happened at year 68?
[SPEAKER_03]: He got a little frustrated.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_03]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, this is Osfer.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey Osfer, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_01]: Sorry I tuned in a little bit late.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know if you covered this story or not.
[SPEAKER_01]: But did you see that part where it was talking... This was on Joystick.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was an article about the Zelda director saying he wouldn't quit until he surpasses Ocarina of Time.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like he wouldn't quit working with the Zelda series.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was wondering, what do you guys think needs to happen in the Zelda series to make it surpass Ocarina of Time?
[SPEAKER_01]: Or do you think there's already been a game in the Zelda series that's better than Ocarina of Time?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think the way they can make it better is to fuck the shit no um it's just not gonna get old I don't know why I'm so immature yes I think there is a game that has surpassed Ocarina of Time and it's called The Legend of Zelda A Link to the Past so in my opinion he can quit already because he already made the better game really I have a friend that likes A Link to the Past the best too but I don't know just for me Ocarina of Time is still the best
[SPEAKER_01]: He was also talking in terms of sales, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I think it's going to be tricky to do.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think Twilight Princess was pretty darn good.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I think it really showed what the Wii games could be pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although, you know, that game was kind of originally designed for the GameCube.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I think what it really might take to really knock people's socks off is to kind of take that same approach, but with a Zelda game that is designed for the system it's going to be out for.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it'll probably be this Wii HD thing that'll be out in 2010 or 2011.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which will be a port of a Wii game, because they'll do a Wii version and a Wii HD version.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wouldn't be surprised if we see a play on Wii Wind Waker game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would like to see a Wind Waker game that wasn't in a world that was flooded with water.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was just...
[SPEAKER_05]: Spoiler, but in Wind Waker you actually go under the ocean and you find out, oh my god, it's Hyrule but flooded and it looks pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm like, why the fuck couldn't they have just done this and made it really cool?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's kind of like Wind Waker to me is kind of like Mega Man Legends was.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's another game that needs more.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I'm thinking if Zelda wants to really, really expand its audience and really cater to many people out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Zelda Crossing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Different types.
[SPEAKER_04]: The game that's just persistent.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: What you do, you just need to add a few things into the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: You need to add kidditch matches.
[SPEAKER_04]: You need to add vampires that sparkle.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you need to add...
[SPEAKER_04]: So basically, instead of a wolf, Link turns into a sexy vampire guy, and then Zelda just starts singing See You Again.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think we're on to something here.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then he sparkles, and we just talk about how beautiful he is.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've been waiting at midnight.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, honestly, the thing that's going to make Zelda better is something we haven't thought of yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's my cryptic answer.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it really is.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's something we haven't thought of yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Steering wheel controls.
[SPEAKER_01]: That is something like what Loki said about Wind Waker.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think it would be cool if they made a Wii version of it.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know how you conducted with the Wind Waker?
[SPEAKER_01]: You could actually...
[SPEAKER_01]: Probably do that with the Wii Remote, and that would be just something interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dude, whatever happened to Link's crossbow training?
[SPEAKER_04]: Easy.
[SPEAKER_04]: I put it in a CD case to where it would be forgotten.
[SPEAKER_05]: Forever.
[SPEAKER_03]: What the hell was that thing called?
[SPEAKER_03]: The Wii Zapper.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whatever happened to the Wii Zapper?
[SPEAKER_04]: There's games that actually use it, like Call of Duty.
[SPEAKER_04]: In the next Zelda game, we need more Link's crossbow training with sniper rifles and cannons and things that are more explosive than a stupid crossbow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Call of Zelda?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's wrong.
[SPEAKER_05]: But no, seriously, they could just do, you know, the first thing they're probably going to do is just do that play on Wii thing for Wind Waker.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then you'll probably see a new Zelda game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Unfortunately, I don't think it's going to be on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: I agree with YYR in chat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Coming soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Super Links Crossbow Training Turbo HD Remix.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you know what they're going to do when they do come out with a Wii HD?
[SPEAKER_05]: They're just going to remake all the stupid games that were on the Wii, and they're going to make them all HD now.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you'll buy them anyway, because you're a consumer horror.
[SPEAKER_04]: And people will buy them.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, Osfer, we're going to let you go, but thanks so much for the call, and I know you really didn't get an answer out of us, but I think it's because probably, sure, there could be a game that one day surpasses Zelda if they just want to put the effort into it, and hopefully they will, and appease us hardcore gamers.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think you were right, though, when you said that it would have to be something that we haven't seen in a game yet.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like, the thing with Ocarina of Time for me was just how expansive it was.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like, that feeling I got when I first stepped out into Hyrule Field, I was just like, holy crap, there's so much to do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe there's something to be said for the potential of a Zelda MMO.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It may be a little weird, but, you know, when in doubt, sparkles.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have a good one, buddy.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right, see ya.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, that's going to do it for the Skype line tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks so much for your guys' calls.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you didn't get through, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you can always send us an email, mailbag at orangeonstrater.com and we'll take more calls next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Last minute stories to get out of the way before we take off tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: There was a bunch of rumors coming out about stuff coming from Sony.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently this was leaked from some sort of Sony staff meeting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some of the stuff we've been hearing about...
[SPEAKER_05]: over and over now.
[SPEAKER_05]: LittleBigPlanet on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_05]: MotorStorm on the PSP apparently are in the works maybe as early as next year.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not surprised.
[SPEAKER_05]: They need something because there's nothing really coming out on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_05]: They said that MotorStorm was shown off on the PSP, but it was target footage and not the actual game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, there was supposedly...
[SPEAKER_05]: God of War 3 stuff shown.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently it's really awesome looking.
[SPEAKER_05]: Uncharted 2 also shown.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not a big surprise that they're going to make a second Uncharted game and Kills in 2 stuff was shown off as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Another interesting thing would be the PSP 3000 system.
[SPEAKER_05]: The new system that came out.
[SPEAKER_05]: One of the things about that was it was pretty impossible to hack the
[SPEAKER_05]: Custom Firmwares on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, now it's even easier to do that because a mod group has actually released a new tool now called the PSP Light Blue Tool.
[SPEAKER_05]: And what it is, is it's a memory card that will act like the Pandora's battery and will allow you to add the custom firmwares to your system.
[SPEAKER_05]: And what's funny is it will sell for $30 and apparently it came out last weekend.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Then finally, we know about Gardening Mama that's going to be coming to the DS soon.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, there's a new trademark being made.
[SPEAKER_05]: The title is Trademark Pet Shop Mama, and it is actually a port of a DS game that's apparently available now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think Mama might have to be euthanized.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think Mama's getting spread too thin.
[SPEAKER_05]: Pet Shop Monogatari is the game that's being ported and has everything from penguin washing to apparently a bear that's jumping in the air.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Another game though that is being ported and thankfully coming to the United States finally, Trackmania DS will be coming thanks to Atlus March 17th to the US.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's pretty cool because Trackmania is all sorts of awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would like to see a Mama game where Mama is trapped in Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fix this, Mama!
[SPEAKER_04]: Mama's brothel.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stripping Mama?
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what's funny?
[SPEAKER_05]: Milfing Mama?
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's something I would just like to bring up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Where the fuck's PlayStation Home?
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought it should have been released by now.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just kind of curious, you know, that they promised it's supposed to be here for 2008.
[SPEAKER_05]: So what?
[SPEAKER_04]: So what?
[SPEAKER_04]: You didn't get into Home.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck that shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: I really don't care.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like I said, you know, yeah, fuck that shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I just think it's funny, though, that they still haven't come out with something, you know, even though they've been teasing this for over two years.
[SPEAKER_05]: And hell, it's still in the commercials.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, they're teasing for the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Look at all these cool games you can play on it, including PlayStation Home.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, you can't.
[SPEAKER_05]: You cannot play that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love what Joshi16 in chat says, Brittany Mama, where you get to neglect your kids for points.
[SPEAKER_05]: They were teasing home back in January and December of last year with the new PlayStation 3 commercials with, what was it, Ladies and Gentlemen.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's sad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well, if that's it for Last Minute Stories, then that's it for the show here tonight on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know it was a little bit shorter, but that's what happens when you take a co-host out for a night.
[SPEAKER_04]: But thank you guys so much for tuning in to us and supporting us as you do every week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, remember, if you like your Orange Launch Radio, please help us spread the word.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tell two friends about the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's really how we...
[SPEAKER_04]: Spread the word about the show because we are an independent podcast.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't have any big name magazines or big websites backing us.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just us as it always has been for the past seven years.
[SPEAKER_04]: And without fans, we're nothing.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're just crap.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we appreciate you guys and your support.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even if you disagree with me on your particular views on a video game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right, HitStun?
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to go around and get everybody's final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_05]: and the accounts I'm going to take over until, I don't know, tomorrow when he leaves on Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, way to be proactive!
[SPEAKER_04]: My final thought is thank you, Aaron, for putting us in the credits of Snake360.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought that was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I forgot to tell you about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: In the credit screen, it says special thanks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Launch Radio, woo!
[SPEAKER_04]: Not only do we have a gamer pick on Xbox Live, but now we are actually mentioned in a downloadable game.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we're all...
[SPEAKER_04]: Now we just need to take that big step and actually get the Orange Lounge Radio game released on Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know who we have to blow to make that happen, but we might have to get working on that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That might be a New Year's resolution for 09.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know what you think.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just, you know, I've thought about it a few times now.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's just when you actually get down to figuring it out, game development's really hard.
[SPEAKER_04]: Game development is hard.
[SPEAKER_05]: And to make something really good takes a lot of time.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's just like, holy crap, that's a lot of time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Art is hard, right, Loki?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, thankfully, what you cannot make yourself, you steal.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, my gosh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to say goodnight and get on out of here.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see you next week on Orange Lounge Radio for another great show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Until next time, until next week, fuck this shit.
[SPEAKER_00]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_00]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_00]: To join us for a live show, visit www.allgames.com Sunday nights at 6pm Pacific Time.
[SPEAKER_00]: The views and opinions expressed on Orange Lounge Radio do not necessarily reflect those of the entire staff of Orange Lounge Radio or AllGames.com, but we're probably right anyway.
[SPEAKER_00]: See you next week!