[SPEAKER_01]: Tonight, November 16, 2008, Wii music sales are initially disappointing, an old video game movie is getting upgraded for Blu-ray, and as little
[SPEAKER_09]: Hello Internets and welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: We are that podcast and live program dedicated to video games, video gaming, gaming culture, and the gamer lifestyle.
[SPEAKER_09]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_09]: Joining me as always, say hello to Jamie Summers, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rawr.
[SPEAKER_09]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_09]: Rawr.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rawr.
[SPEAKER_09]: Tonight is the episode where we will be speaking to ourselves in animal speak all night long.
[SPEAKER_10]: Meow.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, and also say hello to Miep Miep Miep, uh-huh, uh-huh, Miep Miep, Loki.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm not participating in this.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, we have to speak Simlish.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're speaking Simlish tonight?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Since that is a little more video game related.
[SPEAKER_04]: Run through a translation filter back into English.
[SPEAKER_09]: How are you doing, Loki?
[SPEAKER_09]: Seriously, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: Pretty good.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, good, good.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, well, you know how it works here at Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: We do a little program here for about three hours talking about the latest and greatest in gaming.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, the show kind of started as us sitting around the table at dinner after a long night of playing DDR and fighting games in the local arcade and some pinball and all that good stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: Once in a while, golf, maybe.
[SPEAKER_09]: And just talking trash about games and other things going on in our lives.
[SPEAKER_09]: And kind of carried over onto this little program.
[SPEAKER_09]: We invite you all to our dinner table through our chat room.
[SPEAKER_09]: Chat.OrangeLoungeRadio.com
[SPEAKER_09]: and when we tape live on Sunday nights at allgames.com at about 6 o'clock Pacific Standard Time right after the Bobby Blackwolf Show.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's start off tonight's show as we always do with a little bit of How Was Your Gaming Week and we'll start with DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_09]: How was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_04]: I played something other than Ragnarok, although I did play a lot of Ragnarok.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh my gosh, what?
[SPEAKER_04]: I played, and you saw me play it, the Doctor Who Top Chumps game that thanks to one of our lovely listeners sent to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not this Rob, but that Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: And something will be on its way to you as soon as I am no longer broke.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, but it's, it's cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'd never played any Top Trumps game before.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of, it's really simple, and it, the, I played one of the, um, I guess ones in Adventure Mode, and I went, I did just a single game, and I had to play against a Slothine, which was, you know, I was like, eh, I don't like them.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I lost my first game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It wasn't very great losing my first game.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's sort of like playing war, but you choose your stats on your card to play against someone else's stats on their card.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you play for cards too, and it's bizarre.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm going to try to practice a bit more at it and see if I can get any good at it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I also have, even though I haven't played it yet,
[SPEAKER_04]: I have Castlevania Order of Ecclesia so I'm going to be hopefully giving that a try during the week if I actually have time because I've got two art projects due and my Animal Crossing is coming tomorrow so I'm glad for that and I've also been playing a little bit of Fable Fable 2 so that's it sweet have you been playing anything fun?
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, I played this week more Saints Row 2 because I've already finished the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going for 100% completions, so I've been playing through the mini-games, which are actually pretty easy so far.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think some of them are difficult, like some of the insurance fraud can be difficult because it's kind of random of what cars come and how many times you get hit and that kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um...
[SPEAKER_07]: but like I finished the septic adventure part where you spray sewage onto people and property and that's funny because you fling poo at them and also played through some of the helicopter assault stuff which is also fun because you're just firing rockets at things then also went and played through some of the online of that trying to get some more ranks and badges and stuff and
[SPEAKER_07]: I wish it wasn't so cumbersome, because getting to the ranked games, it takes forever.
[SPEAKER_07]: And once you're done with that, there's no going back to a lobby or going into another game.
[SPEAKER_07]: It just kicks you back out to the main menu and you have to go through the whole thing again and again.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's kind of lame.
[SPEAKER_07]: But eventually I'll get enough trophies, I guess, if I stick with it long enough.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I am 80% done with the game, so that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Then the other thing I've played this week, of course, we switched to Grand Theft Auto 4 for multiplayer because people got tired of me beating them all the time in Saints Row 2, so now they want me to beat them all the time in Grand Theft Auto 4.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's what's been going on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: Whatever, it looks fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I'm looking forward to checking that out.
[SPEAKER_07]: I went back and played some Rock Band 2 because I finally got my cymbals for my new drum set.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because I vowed that I wouldn't play the drum set until I got the cymbals.
[SPEAKER_07]: And now that I've got the cymbals, it's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Unfortunately, I got only a 2-pack because they weren't selling 3-packs yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: It sucks.
[SPEAKER_07]: Then I went ahead, I didn't really get to play Animal Crossing this week, but we did get it a little early.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've been watching my wife hog the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I played it at PAX, and just from what I've seen, it really is almost exactly the same as the other two games.
[SPEAKER_07]: Very minor changes.
[SPEAKER_07]: In fact, there's a few things that are kind of neat in it, but they don't even mention them at all.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, apparently, there's like an Easter egg if you take a certain path each time.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, say you start the game and immediately run across this one bridge or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, eventually it will carve out a path for you in the leaves or in the grass or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's kind of a neat little Easter egg.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: I blame the economy and the stock market and gas prices.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm getting to the point now where I have too many things to play at once.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ubisoft sent me a copy of Snowboarding for the 360 and then I got a copy of Rain Man's Raving Rabbids TV Party that I got to try out.
[SPEAKER_07]: And DS games, I'm going to try to play Trackmania DS this week because I like the PC version.
[SPEAKER_07]: also Line Raider 2 at some point and I got a download code for Banjo-Kazooie so I'm probably able to try that because I never really actually played the original and god, Fallout 3 at some point because I still haven't finished that and I gotta finish Fable 2 so it's busy but Animal Crossing does mark the last game I'm buying this year so that's nice oh and Resistance too, I still gotta play that
[SPEAKER_09]: SingStar Abba
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_09]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, what am I going to say?
[SPEAKER_09]: Obviously, I'm already addicted to WoW.
[SPEAKER_09]: What am I going to add to this?
[SPEAKER_09]: I will say this.
[SPEAKER_09]: They've really kind of kicked up a notch this expansion compared to the last one, the Burning Crusade.
[SPEAKER_09]: The new dungeons are pretty awesome, the three I've played so far.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: is actually really awesome because it's nothing but epic boss fights for a five man, which is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: And some of the quests are neat.
[SPEAKER_09]: They've added this whole new vehicle thing into the game, which is kind of fun, kind of controls a little bit differently.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I think for lore fans, I'm not huge on the lore in WoW, but I know lore fans are really getting a kick out of this one with some of the twists that are on it.
[SPEAKER_09]: And if you're into WoW, you probably already bought this game.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you're somebody who used to play WoW that's debating coming back, you might want to take advantage of that offer that Blizzard's doing where you can get the 10-day free pass to Burning Crusade and all that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because I'm going to tell you what, for new people, there's really not a lot in Wrath of the Lich King for you.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's actually probably the game's shortcoming.
[SPEAKER_09]: Whereas in Burning Crusade, at least you have Blood Elves, Draenei,
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: But otherwise, there's not a lot for new people.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's not a lot you're going to see at level 1.
[SPEAKER_09]: Granted, you have a new profession, a haircut thing, but that's not worth $40 for the expansion.
[SPEAKER_09]: But if you do have a level 70 character, if you've quit WoW during the Burning Crusade and you're kind of curious what's changed with this, I definitely think Lich King is worth checking out.
[SPEAKER_09]: So definitely check out Wrath of the Lich King if you're a Warcraft fan.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you're not, there's nothing here that's going to win you over.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't think.
[SPEAKER_09]: Although I do think the quest lines so far in the dungeons from 70 to 80 have been awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I love the music too.
[SPEAKER_09]: The music has been very ambient and pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it has a zone called the Fjord.
[SPEAKER_09]: And who doesn't love the word Fjord?
[SPEAKER_09]: And yes, it has Vikings and all that stuff, which is pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: And you get to kill them in the face.
[SPEAKER_09]: And that's pretty much been my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_09]: I also have gotten to get my grubby little hands on Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_09]: I haven't really gotten to play it very much at all.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I would agree.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's not a lot here we haven't seen.
[SPEAKER_09]: And kind of as I was saying on Bobby's show as we were doing the toss over to our program tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: The GameCube, in a way, was almost a better deal.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, granted, you have the online stuff now, and there's a few new things here and there, but you don't get to unlock the old-school NES games anymore.
[SPEAKER_09]: And Loki, when we were talking about it on Bobby's show, you had a great idea for how Animal Crossing kind of put that magic back, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I mean, like they've been doing with some of their other Nintendo games that come out, add some minigames in there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Make some minigames.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can even make them like retro NES games or something like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_07]: or even like, was it with, you know, just have, and he has demos or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hell, they did it with Smash Brothers.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know why that's such a big deal now or just something.
[SPEAKER_09]: Game and watch games for heaven's sakes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just something, you know?
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, I don't know what it is about mini games, but hey, it is Nintendo after all, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just, it seems like that they're not trying, that they're just basically putting in the most basic content ever, and they're making it so that you don't have to play this, you know, multiple times a week or something like that, even though you probably should if this is, you know, a game that you're going to be playing, because that's how you play this, is you have to constantly go back and maintain stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, like, the city is literally all the, you know, special event stuff that would happen, you know, all the people coming and visiting your town, they're all in the city now, which...
[SPEAKER_07]: The city is kind of lame.
[SPEAKER_07]: I wish it was like other villages.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe expand your village.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe, I don't know, make it look different.
[SPEAKER_07]: Put some effort.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, here's what it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think, you know, whereas we loved Animal Crossing and the minigames thing I think is important because
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: I remember we had a lot of that going on.
[SPEAKER_09]: There was incentive to go back and forth.
[SPEAKER_09]: Whereas at least you still have the items and things.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, come visit my Shrine of Fire and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: Honestly, I think Animal Crossing has become a game for 10-year-olds.
[SPEAKER_09]: Exclusively for the tween area.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like the 10, 11, 12, 13-year-olds.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't think there's anything left for us old folks anymore.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was really...
[SPEAKER_07]: What's the fear of actually putting virtual console games in this game?
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, so it may cut down on the sales of your virtual console games that you have featured in this.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_07]: They're digital.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not like you have to manufacture discs.
[SPEAKER_07]: It costs you nothing.
[SPEAKER_07]: If anything, you sell more copies of Animal Crossing and you get more people to do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hell, you could maybe even...
[SPEAKER_07]: Charge them as download content.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or here's an idea.
[SPEAKER_07]: The virtual console games that you have on your system you can put in your house or something like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or select ones.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like say if I own Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can put Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_07]: game in my game or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or I can purchase Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_07]: and put it in my house or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: I...
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just, it's lazy.
[SPEAKER_09]: All it is is lazy.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, here's the thing about Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_09]: The disappointing thing for me as a hardcore gamer is that Nintendo is still going to sell like hotcakes this Christmas.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wii's are still going to be a must-have.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wii Fit is still going to sell like crazy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Soccer moms are going to buy this for their kids.
[SPEAKER_09]: and honestly, things like, you know, look, this has been like a recurring trend on this show.
[SPEAKER_09]: We bashed Wii Music previously and said, but it's probably really good for 10 year olds.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here we are bashing Animal Crossing, but your 10 year old will probably have a lot of fun with it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why would I get Wii Fit?
[SPEAKER_09]: I won't probably exercise much with it, but my 10 year old probably will.
[SPEAKER_09]: The Wii is not being taken seriously by a lot of us hardcore gamers anymore.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's the kid system.
[SPEAKER_09]: Will it still sell?
[SPEAKER_09]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_09]: But they're going to lose a lot of credibility with us if they don't start turning around some games fast in 2009.
[SPEAKER_09]: And to lose that brand loyalty is going to be painful.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Remember before, the GameCube, it was looked at as a kid system.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Wii hasn't changed that at all.
[SPEAKER_07]: In fact, now they're really pushing it that it's more of a kid system or
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: Change it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Make it different than the last two that you put out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Can you imagine if Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_07]: 3 came out?
[SPEAKER_07]: It was exactly the same as Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_07]: 1 except it was at night or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's seriously what they're doing.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just the same.
[SPEAKER_09]: With Wii Speak.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it's seriously that bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just they're not trying at all.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the sad thing is it's because it's Animal Crossing and people will buy it.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're not going to learn!
[SPEAKER_07]: That's fine if 10-year-olds are happy with Animal Crossing because maybe they didn't play the other versions of the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_07]: But they'll be equally disappointed when Animal Crossing 2 or whenever the next one comes out for the next Nintendo system, they're like, holy crap, this is exactly the same as the last one I played.
[SPEAKER_07]: And we'll be going, holy crap, it's exactly the same as the last three I've played.
[SPEAKER_09]: Queltipo in chat says, yeah, but at least GameCube had the debut of Resident Evil 4 to combat the supposed kiddiness and eternal darkness, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: It still looks like a Nintendo 64 game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, that's really... I have the Nintendo 64 version, so that's all it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: It doesn't even have to be the look.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just they didn't change... The towns are basically the same as the other ones.
[SPEAKER_04]: But maybe they're just saying the formula works, why mess with it?
[SPEAKER_09]: I really don't have a lot of incentive to buy this game, although I guess I already have it, but to recommend it to others.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here's a very interesting counterpoint to your whole Mario at Night thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: GameGuru says someone hasn't played Lost Levels, which was Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_09]: 2 in Japan.
[SPEAKER_09]: In a way, Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_09]: 2 in Japan was Mario at Night, but the levels were different.
[SPEAKER_09]: They did have poison mushrooms, a difference between Mario and Luigi, but the look was the same.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: Yet another great comment from Janai in chat.
[SPEAKER_09]: Chatroom's got great comments tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: Janai in chat says, Nintendo is really pissing on its fans for not bringing Mother 3 out.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's a great comment.
[SPEAKER_09]: So meanwhile, while they're cranking out these games, they've got a game that might appeal to us that they refuse to release here in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_09]: Amazing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, well anyhow, that's pretty much going to do it for my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's get into some housekeeping news tonight, of which we don't have an awful lot, but I do want to make sure I announce here, towards the top of the show, we have a special guest joining us tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's going to be awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know you guys have heard about the Xbox 360 New Xbox Experience is coming out pretty soon, this next coming week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, one thing that's going to be rolling out on this is the community games on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_09]: You might remember when these things were first previewed a few months ago at the Game Developers Conference, I said, this is it.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is going to be a huge thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is going to be like the YouTube...
[SPEAKER_09]: Snake!
[SPEAKER_09]: Snake360.com Snake360.com
[SPEAKER_09]: This Game, and Music Games that we've talked about in the past.
[SPEAKER_09]: And we'll talk about that a little later.
[SPEAKER_09]: Meanwhile...
[SPEAKER_09]: That's really it for housekeeping.
[SPEAKER_09]: Otherwise, I'm just going to say, hey, join us on Facebook at OL Army.
[SPEAKER_09]: Join us on MySpace, Orange Lounge Radio, and join us on LiveJournal at Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_09]: And Twitter at OLR.
[SPEAKER_09]: And this week, I will not ignore the pre-OLR twit like I did last week, and I apologize for that.
[SPEAKER_09]: I will read your twits tonight when we get to that story on Samba de Amigo.
[SPEAKER_09]: But we're not ready for that yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're going to get some other stories first, and Loki is going to start us off tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_07]: It should be called Show Us Your Twits.
[SPEAKER_09]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think that should be the official name of the saying.
[SPEAKER_09]: You like that, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_09]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_09]: Show us your twits.
[SPEAKER_09]: Very good, Loki.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Quite clever tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, so kind of going into what we were just talking about, disappointment in Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wii Music has definitely been disappointing for Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's actually only sold so far not even 100,000 units.
[SPEAKER_07]: Only 81,000 units according to the NPD or according to Nintendo, 65,000 to 66,000 units.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can see why, because the game itself, really there's no point to it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a toy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Something that could have been literally downloaded on their WiiWare service, which it probably should have been.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jamie, you were the lone holdout for Wii Music on this program.
[SPEAKER_09]: Did you get a chance to check it out yet?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I've had school.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was just curious.
[SPEAKER_04]: Honestly, better games to play.
[SPEAKER_09]: So finally you're admitting it.
[SPEAKER_09]: There are better things out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I admitted it from the beginning that there were better things to play.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just said that I liked it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought it was cute.
[SPEAKER_04]: My inner musician sang out and went, cool, I did this crap in music theory.
[SPEAKER_07]: I say it's great too for 10 year olds but anyway I don't think a 10 year old would even want to play this I'm sorry this is like for like 5 year olds it's for kids that like shake around shit that don't know what they're doing you know in a game they're like oh my god it's like I'm making music
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: That's cool because sometimes the parents want to go talk and have adult conversations whereas the little kids are screaming and being annoying and put them in front of this and they'll shut up.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now, is the numbers here skewed a little bit because this game came out late in the month?
[SPEAKER_09]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_09]: To be honest, 81,000 doesn't sound like a bad number to me.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, maybe it's under expectations, but you consider there's been other music games out there, like probably Beatmania didn't sell that much.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, this was released, this is basically one week worth of sales, because this was released in the second to last week of the month.
[SPEAKER_07]: But to be honest, from what I've seen, it's not selling very well at all.
[SPEAKER_07]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think people... Once again, they're trying to find games that the people that buy the Wii system for Wii Sports would possibly buy.
[SPEAKER_07]: That is really their challenge right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: What can we do to get people to buy games that really don't want to buy other games other than Wii Sports?
[SPEAKER_04]: Wii Lacrosse!
[SPEAKER_07]: WeSports2
[SPEAKER_07]: and then the parents are like, well, Wii Sports is fun for the whole family and I'm not really bored of that yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: Funny point from YYR in chat, Wii Music has sold more copies than Rock Revolution, fact.
[SPEAKER_09]: We won't go there with Rock Revolution.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's a whole other can of worms.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's move on, shall we?
[SPEAKER_09]: Folks are kicking Nintendo while they're down, apparently.
[SPEAKER_09]: Motiva is an Ohio-based company, and they've, of course, filed a lawsuit, yet another one against Nintendo, saying that the Wiimote is violating their patent.
[SPEAKER_09]: They filed it in 2004, technology used to create a human movement measurement system.
[SPEAKER_09]: that will use a handheld tracking device in communication with a base station that is then used to create an interactive gaming experience among other capabilities.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now here's what I want to know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nintendo's getting sued by all these people that claim they have the patent for the Wii Remote and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: How can everybody have the patent for the Wii Remote?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because there's all these people that are suing them saying that they have patents for this stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Shouldn't they be suing each other because now they have patents that also kind of overlap?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's weird.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, that's the part I don't really get either.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, right.
[SPEAKER_09]: All these people are claiming we invented the Wii years ago.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, we invented the Wii Remote.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, no, we just paid a settlement to this other company and said they invented the Wii Remote.
[SPEAKER_07]: You need to dish it out with them then because they're the ones that actually claimed the... I am Spartacus.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I am Spartacus.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it's really ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_07]: I...
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's also, it's like, oh my god, we didn't realize they were so similar two years after it came out.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'd be really curious to see what happens with one of these lawsuits, because we keep hearing about, oh, somebody's suing them, somebody's suing them, yet we haven't heard about really anybody winning or losing yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it's basically, it's like, yeah, we created the Wii Remote, we want you to pay up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I think we created the Wii Remote and all these hundreds of thousands of dollars say we did.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, yes, you created the Wii Remote.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_09]: and more.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have to reset that joke now, excuse me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, in Soviet Russia, joke tell you.
[SPEAKER_09]: So we called TiVo this week to get a comment on this story, and you know what they told us?
[SPEAKER_07]: I am Spartacus.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, well, I don't feel bad now for interrupting that joke.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I was going to say, what's going to be an interesting turn of event is when TiVo sues Nintendo over the technology for a pointer and, you know, that kind of an airface.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just lawsuit after lawsuit in the world.
[SPEAKER_09]: Can't we all just get along?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, but it's not allowed to.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't you know that war is the true way of things?
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, it's not, but still.
[SPEAKER_04]: War is population control.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, Nintendo is being sneaky.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very, very sneaky.
[SPEAKER_04]: And their sneakiness will definitely fool a few people, but they haven't said anything about it efficiently, nor have they actually...
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, put any kind of thing on their site from what I understand.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it was actually seen at Target.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's official.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is a multiplayer control set is what it's called.
[SPEAKER_04]: There is a Mario Kart wheel, a Wii remote and nunchuck, and it's $74.99, which is actually more expensive than getting them all individually.
[SPEAKER_04]: So...
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's sweet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Two cents more, according to Kotaku.
[SPEAKER_04]: But at the same time, it's like, okay, why?
[SPEAKER_04]: Why do you even need the damn wheel?
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, no.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think that's more than that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because I think the wheel itself is only $10.
[SPEAKER_07]: Although some people charge $15 for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Depends on where you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think they're going over official retail price.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, officially it's supposed to be $10.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it's actually $5 more expensive than buying them separately.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think.
[SPEAKER_07]: In fact, I will... Well, I don't know why I'm looking at GameStop's website.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I think they have theirs for $15.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know we sell them for $10.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's just funny.
[SPEAKER_07]: But yeah, another kind of holiday gift thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, you really don't need the Wii wheel, but I guess people have trouble.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh no, we have to have the Wii wheel or we don't have the proper grip on the thingy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, the Wii wheel sells for $14.99.
[SPEAKER_07]: I thought it was supposed to be $10.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know that I've seen two different SRPs from them and one was $14.99 and one was $10.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I think they're supposed to be $10.
[SPEAKER_07]: But people still charge $15 because guess what?
[SPEAKER_07]: People don't know better and they will buy it for $15.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's because people are dumbasses.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, I have to admit something.
[SPEAKER_09]: Through the magic of radio, you may not have even known I was gone, but I had to run in the house because I've had a migraine and I don't remember if I said that at the top of the show, so I was making myself some coffee so I could have some caffeine because that's good for headaches.
[SPEAKER_09]: What the hell is so damn funny?
[SPEAKER_09]: I heard you literally laughing all the way in the house.
[SPEAKER_07]: That their combo, that their bundle here with one remote nunchuck and a Wii wheel is actually more expensive than buying them all separately.
[SPEAKER_07]: That is pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a bagel.
[SPEAKER_07]: so uh yes i also ran in to get jamie a bagel and really i mean why should you buy this in a big old bundle like this when i'm sure right next to all of them are the individual components separate of each other and it's just stupid but whatever you know can't hurt them for trying i'm sure that's probably like one of those target exclusive sets or something like that
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't say anything on the box.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's official Nintendo stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, yeah, but sometimes I know with like Activision, they make special bundles for like Guitar Hero and stuff like that for different retailers.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, you know, it won't say Atari exclusive or whatever, but it's made exclusively for those retailers.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my god, the room smells like caffeine.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it's good.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I gotta be up at work at 6 in the morning.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know, now I'm never going to be able to go to sleep tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's okay, I can stay up and play WoW.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, speaking of innovation, Nintendo has revealed their 2009 lineup, or early 2009, basically for...
[SPEAKER_07]: Mario & Luigi RPG 3
[SPEAKER_07]: is scheduled to come out February 11th to the DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, now there's a good game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, that's a cool game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Castlevania Judgment, they're getting it a little bit late.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Play for Wii Mario Tennis coming January 15th.
[SPEAKER_07]: Play for Wii Mario Tennis is the port of the GameCube game with Wii controls now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Final Fantasy Crystal Chronicles Echoes of Time will be coming to both DS and Wii on January 29th.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also not listed on there would be Sin and Punishment 2 and Punch-Out.
[SPEAKER_07]: But maybe soon after that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Queltipo gives a nice, mature summary of the 2009 lineup for Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yay, Mario & Luigi.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fart to everything else.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know, Punch-Out might be kind of cool even if they're just capitalizing on Wii Sports, the boxing game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, it's Punch-Out!
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, I didn't realize Punch-Out had been re-released so many times.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, they've had different versions for like the Super Nintendo and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: The Super Nintendo one was awesome!
[SPEAKER_07]: It was kind of underrated.
[SPEAKER_07]: It might be pretty neat, but, you know, I...
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't have much faith in Nintendo just because of the example of their products that have come out recently.
[SPEAKER_07]: It doesn't seem like they're trying.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sin and Punishment might be pretty cool because the first one was fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sin and Punishment looks awesome, but it just doesn't look like they're trying.
[SPEAKER_07]: The stuff that's developed in-house just doesn't seem to be that good.
[SPEAKER_09]: Shonen Jump is a manga compilation.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: So how much did I talk about video games in there?
[SPEAKER_04]: There's ads for stuff and little articles in there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, for whatever reason, this game got the jump on Blood of Bahamut, which is the game that Squeenix is teasing.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a DS game, and apparently what you do, you can play this game with four people locally, and you defend your city from attacks.
[SPEAKER_09]: So it's like a city defense game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Apparently, though, you build them on a creature or something.
[SPEAKER_09]: At least that's what the teaser image kind of makes it look like.
[SPEAKER_09]: So there'll be more information.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's where Bahamut comes into things.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm assuming.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll be hearing more on this game soon, but who knows if it's coming to the US or not.
[SPEAKER_09]: I would assume it is, because Squeenix has gotten a little better about their whole universal game, you know, worldwide game thing, especially if Last Remnant's any indication, which, god damn, there's another game I gotta play this holiday season.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like SimCity of the Colossus.
[SPEAKER_09]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sure there's a lot of Squeenix fans who are going to be curious to check this one out.
[SPEAKER_09]: But yet again, another kind of interesting game for the DS.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why is the DS getting all the love?
[SPEAKER_09]: I guess it's because more people own DSs than anything else, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, it's just like I was saying last week when I was talking about Order of Ecclesia.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why can't we have these games on consoles?
[SPEAKER_09]: I want to play them on my television, not when I'm lying in my bed playing my DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: They should make a DS TV tuner.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes and no.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think the idea is cool in theory, but at the same time, I want them to have a platformer, like the type of thing you'd see on the DS, but with that LittleBigPlanet-style graphics, really sharp, good-looking, use the high-end graphics.
[SPEAKER_09]: They already have a TV tuner for the DS in Japan.
[SPEAKER_09]: And they also have it if you review games and you're putting together professional stuff, but the rest of us...
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, if we have a DS dev kit.
[SPEAKER_07]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like we'd ever get one of those.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: It could happen.
[SPEAKER_09]: You never know.
[SPEAKER_09]: It would never happen.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, let's move on and talk about some release dates and some of the games we will be getting our hands on a little bit sooner.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll start with our friends over in Europe, right, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: For our UK releases, and this is stuff that we may or may not get our hands on, but yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: On the 18th is Evercrack 2, The Shadow Odyssey Spore, Creepy and Cute, Parts Pack Try saying that three times fast, shit Lord of the Rings Online, Minds of Moria 19th, New Xbox Experience 20th, Last Remnant 21st is a whole shitload of stuff, you ready?
[SPEAKER_09]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_09]: Which is not a surprise, by the way.
[SPEAKER_09]: Even though they don't have Thanksgiving over in Europe, it's still the same busy period it is here.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's Cubello, Orbeant, Roto-Hex, Cradle of Rome, Gothic 3, Forsaken Gods, Grand Theft Auto 4, Hasbro Family Game Night, whatever, Left 4 Dead, that's on PC and Xbox 360, Legendary, LocoRoco 2, Mortal Kombat vs. DC Universe, My Dog Coach, Understand Your Dog with Cesar Millan,
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait, that's the Dog Whisperer game, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_04]: Need for Speed Undercover on Damn Near Everything, Neverwinter Nights 2, Storm of Zaheer, Pokemon Ranger, Shadows of Amia, Rise of the Argonauts, also on Xbox 360, PlayStation 3, and PC, Skate It on Wii, Tomb Raider Underworld on Damn Near Everything Else.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, busy week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Busy, busy week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, and it's very similar to that in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_07]: as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: So starting things off here, we've got, well, for today, Shaun White's Snowboarding came out on pretty much everything.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, Animal Crossing on the Wii finally made its way out this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then later in the week, we've got some pretty cool stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Need for Speed Undercover coming out on practically everything.
[SPEAKER_07]: Left 4 Dead coming out on 360.
[SPEAKER_07]: and I think also the PC on that.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then Tecmo Bowl Kickoff coming to DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: Galloping Ride on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're in the Movies coming on Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually kind of interested in this.
[SPEAKER_07]: It might be a fun party game.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that's included with the Xbox Vision camera which hopefully will be used for more than just this game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hello Kitty Big City Dreams coming out on DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: Lord of the Rings
[SPEAKER_07]: Online, Minds of Moria, the expansion pack there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Can I interrupt with a funny chat that's funnier than my Spartacus joke from earlier?
[SPEAKER_09]: Blackwolf says, Loki, you just misspoke.
[SPEAKER_09]: You stated that Animal Crossing was a new game that came out on the Wii this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: My mistake.
[SPEAKER_07]: Please correct yourself.
[SPEAKER_07]: Animal Crossing Wild World, I mean City Folk, the game that you may have seen in other systems now is being printed for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: The first game in the Let's Make GameCube games for the Wii game has come out this week and it's called Animal Crossing City.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh no, that's not the first game either.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, must I remind you of Resident Evil 4?
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, alright, you're right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Countless other games.
[SPEAKER_07]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Merv Griffin's Crosswords for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, that's going to be awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Whoopty shit!
[SPEAKER_07]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_07]: Tomb Raider Underworld coming out on the DS, PS3, Wii, and Xbox 360 Skate City Heroes coming out on the Wii Ultimate Band on Wii and DS Cooking Mama, World Kitchen on the Wii hopefully less broken than the last one Spore, comic book creator for PC man, let's horror spore some more that's kind of rhymed that was cool, you should say it again man, let's horror spore some more woohoo
[SPEAKER_07]: Disney's Bolt coming out on practically everything Castlevania Judgment don't buy that game ever coming out on the Wii
[SPEAKER_09]: Just like with Rock Revolution, I don't know what it is that draws me to these games that really get shit on by the public, but I'm fucking curious about it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I want to buy it just to kind of check it out.
[SPEAKER_07]: They want you to make your judgment on it and judge with your wallet and do not buy it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or if you are planning on buying it, wait a few weeks for it to really suck and then to drop the price on it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Find it used?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe I can find Rock Revolution used now.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's probably getting cheaper.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can only imagine.
[SPEAKER_07]: Pet's Monkey House.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now you have monkeys infesting your DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, that sounds kind of awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hopefully you won't catch the deadly Mutaba virus.
[SPEAKER_07]: AMF bullying World Lanes for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dynasty Warrior 6 coming out on the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, it's only like nine months late.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rune Factory 2, Fantasy Harvest Moon on DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: Neverwinter Nights 2, Storm of Zier I think that's another expansion there NPPL, it sounds like nipple Championship Paintball 2009 There's a game called nipple?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's NPPL, National Paintball Players League Nipple's the game Show us your twits on nipple Nipple
[SPEAKER_10]: Agatha Christie's Evil Under the... It would probably sell more than Rock Revolution based on name alone.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, to be honest, the game looks like... What are you doing, the game of Nipple?
[SPEAKER_10]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's Nipples!
[SPEAKER_07]: Agatha, Christy, Evil Under the Sun on Wii, Cradle of Rome on DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: Supposedly this week is that 160 gigabyte PlayStation 3 bundle now with Uncharted, Drake's Fortune.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, the game that everyone forgot about and is over a year old now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sonic Unleashed on PS2 and Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: The 360 and PS3 both got delayed.
[SPEAKER_07]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Pets Rescue, Endangered Paradise.
[SPEAKER_07]: Karaoke Revolution, American Idol 2 on PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, and Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, guess what?
[SPEAKER_07]: Rock Revolution with the drum kits finally coming out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Only a month late.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that'll be on PS3 and Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_07]: But really, why even bother?
[SPEAKER_07]: And Tony Hawk's Motion on DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_07]: Tony Hawk.
[SPEAKER_07]: Those don't suck anymore.
[SPEAKER_07]: Imagine Movie Star on DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't even bother with that one.
[SPEAKER_07]: God, there's too much shit coming out.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's the busiest week of the year.
[SPEAKER_07]: Gothic 3, Forsaking Gods on PC.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rayman's Raving Rabbids TV Party coming out on Wii and DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: Pet's Crazy Monkeys on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_09]: Which, by the way, Loki played it at PAX on stage in front of everyone.
[SPEAKER_09]: Comedy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, I wanted to play the actual part where you can slide around on the moose using the Wii balance board, and you sit on it and lean back and forth.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, yeah, sure, you can play that after you play this dancing game with some chicks, the frag dolls.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, and we're going to videotape you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, and then when you're done, we're going to say, fuck off, and you're not going to get to play the actual thing you wanted to play.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what was great about that whole thing is that...
[SPEAKER_09]: You were there to play something else that was being horribly ignored by everybody.
[SPEAKER_09]: And you were really excited to check out a different game at the booth, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't remember what it was.
[SPEAKER_09]: I wanted to play Rayman's Raven Rabbids.
[SPEAKER_09]: But there was something else in the booth that you went over there first to go play.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hawks?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I think that's what it was.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then the cute girl came up and was like,
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, you want to play Rayman's Raving Rabbids?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I didn't even do that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was like, you know, I wanted to play Rayman's Raving Rabbids because that's kind of one of the things I wanted to do when I got there.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I didn't want to play the dance game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm like, I want to play that one.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've done the dance game in the other one and it was, guess what?
[SPEAKER_07]: Not much different than this one.
[SPEAKER_07]: And everyone's like, oh, getting real into it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm like, yay.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't want to dance, I want to ride the moose.
[SPEAKER_07]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_07]: Pets, Crazy Monkeys, coming to the Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also another monkey infestation game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Metal Slug 7, coming to the DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: Legendary on PC this week, Pets Cats Clan.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like cats, but with more cats.
[SPEAKER_07]: CSI New York.
[SPEAKER_07]: I do not want the kook Cats Clan on my DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, that's bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: No Cat's Clan.
[SPEAKER_07]: No CCC.
[SPEAKER_07]: Imagine Ballet Star coming to the DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh my god, this is so awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, really it's not.
[SPEAKER_07]: Championship Foosball coming to the Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, these are the games that demand your attention on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do not fucking knock Foosball.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's foosball!
[SPEAKER_07]: On the Wii!
[SPEAKER_07]: Exactly!
[SPEAKER_07]: Lips coming to 360.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey now, that game looks pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Iron Chef America Supreme Cuisine on DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: Luminous Arc 2 for the DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also comes with a soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_07]: Kind of a little fancy deal that they've got going there.
[SPEAKER_07]: God damn.
[SPEAKER_07]: Still not done.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alone in the Dark Inferno.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is the version that's supposed to be not broken.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um...
[SPEAKER_07]: Popstar Guitar with two guitar grips on the Wii and Popstar Guitar on the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, this is another guitar hero rip-off game or guitar freaks rip-off or whoever you want to rip off.
[SPEAKER_07]: It sucks with pop music, so don't buy it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Burnout Anthology, coming out with the last three Burnout games.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Last Remnant on Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_07]: That looks pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Age of Empire Mythologies on the DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: Cake Mania in the Mix on Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: All Star Cheer Squad on the DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: and I think I'm getting into next week.
[SPEAKER_07]: So we're done.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sweet.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank God.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's get into some of the Japanese releases and talk about what's coming out in Japan.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's a game on the Xbox 360 called Otomedius Gorgeous which looks pretty hot and I'd like to know where the hell this game is in America.
[SPEAKER_07]: That is an arcade game from Konami.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know it's a Konami game.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like Proteus but it's bigger.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a shooter with hot chicks and the shooter actually looks kind of graphically pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: It kind of looks like UN Squadron to me a little bit.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is it on Wii, you said?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, it's on Xbox 360, of all things.
[SPEAKER_09]: So this game looks pretty hot.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's coming out this week in Japan.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also coming out, The Last Remnant is coming out in Japan this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's also coming out in a bundle-style thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: So keep an eye out for that because they're hoping to sell some...
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm dying to play...
[SPEAKER_09]: Why don't they just port, like, Guitar Freaks or something?
[SPEAKER_09]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_09]: Animal Crossing, City Folk hits the Japanese shores as well, as well as the version that has We Speak.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sengoku Basara 2 Heroes gets a price reduction this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's not a new game, but it gets a price reduction.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you want a new game, check out this new game from Compile.
[SPEAKER_09]: We love Compile, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: Sugoro Chronicle.
[SPEAKER_09]: Migite ni ken o hidarait ni saikoro o comes out this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I have no idea what the hell this game's about.
[SPEAKER_09]: It looks like it's some type of board game translation that's coming out in Japan.
[SPEAKER_09]: Kind of like, I guess you could say, a Mario Party-ish game, but it looks like there's some RPG elements in that game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Doesn't look half bad, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: Coming out on the handheld systems, or actually, let's take a look quick at PlayStation 2, because some folks still have that.
[SPEAKER_09]: You also get another version of Mercenaries 2, World in Flames, as well as a game called Koi Haime Musou comes out as well, from Yeti.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's Hime.
[SPEAKER_09]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_09]: Remember, that's part of the reason why I do this, because I butcher all the Japanese names.
[SPEAKER_09]: It means princess.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's wonderful.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, goody, another Princess game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, this is probably the game that most folks are waiting for, not just in Japan, but in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_09]: On the Nintendo DS this week, Chrono Trigger finally hits on November 20th, so keep an eye out for that.
[SPEAKER_09]: And with that comes a whole lot of accessories from Hori.
[SPEAKER_09]: New pouches in different colors, a new little cleaning cloth thing, as well as a couple other games.
[SPEAKER_09]: Tomica Hero Rescue Force, Touch and Direct from Sega, and a game called DS Recording Diet comes out as well on the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_09]: And lastly, over on the PSP, checking out what releases we have there this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's not quite as busy of a week in Japan as it is in other parts of the world.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ratchet & Clank, or as they call it, Clank & Ratchet.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maruhi Mission Ignition comes out on the PSP this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: As well as, again, Hori is also putting out some cases and things for the Sony PSP.
[SPEAKER_09]: Otherwise, you have All-Star Yaken 2 Portable.
[SPEAKER_09]: And, wait for it, Mobile Suit Gundam!
[SPEAKER_09]: That's right, another Mobile Suit Gundam game Gundam vs. Gundam, and it even comes with its own PSP pack if you want to check that out Is that like a Gundam remake of Spy vs. Spy?
[SPEAKER_04]: No My friend calls it Gundam
[SPEAKER_09]: Also, I think this is kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think it's like a Disgaea spinoff because a game has come out all about Prinnies this week on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_09]: Prinnie, Ore ga Shujinku de Inisuka comes out this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think you can be a hero too or something like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's coming out in the US too in February.
[SPEAKER_09]: You get 1,000 lives in this game.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a side-scroller action game and your character has literally 1,000 lives.
[SPEAKER_09]: I hope it's really hard, because that'd be funny.
[SPEAKER_09]: It must be.
[SPEAKER_09]: But, you know, printies were kind of disposable in Disgaea, so that is kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_09]: That actually sounds like kind of a funny game, so you might have to check that one out.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's move on with some other gaming news.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, this is particularly exciting stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Speaking of other release dates, Street Fighter 4 has a date for PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, you're saying that it's going to be February 20th, 2009.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there's also some reports saying that there's going to be 25 characters in the console release and maybe some other fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: So who knows?
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_09]: Sunnyvale Golfland
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure we're going to see it.
[SPEAKER_09]: It is popping up around the U.S.
[SPEAKER_09]: Folks are importing it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think some of our New York listeners called in several weeks ago to talk about it.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just kind of sad it's not getting an official quote-unquote release in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_09]: It doesn't really stop a lot of people nowadays.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe because it's coming out on the consoles.
[SPEAKER_09]: When games come out on consoles, it kind of kills the arcade release.
[SPEAKER_09]: Unless it's Derby Owner's Club or DDR.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can do it, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, if developers are smart enough to incorporate things that you can tie into consoles, like, for example, DDR with edit data or, you know, F-Zero GX with, you know, data that you can port to the arcade and that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think if they do it smart, both can benefit from it.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, well, hey, Street Fighter fans.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you are a hardcore Street Fighter fan, you've got to be a really hardcore Street Fighter fan to appreciate this.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or if you just like bad movies like me, you're going to be excited that Street Fighter the movie is coming out on Blu-ray.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, that's right.
[SPEAKER_09]: The Jean-Claude Van Damme, Raul Julia, and most importantly, Kylie Minow as Cammy Street Fighter movie is coming out on Blu-ray.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's an extreme edition of the Street Fighter movie.
[SPEAKER_09]: And...
[SPEAKER_09]: It's so sad but true that this is Raul Julia's last movie.
[SPEAKER_09]: But you can experience it one more time.
[SPEAKER_09]: He actually was the best thing about the movie.
[SPEAKER_09]: I even remember this 20 years later.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, not quite that much, but like 15, 20 years later.
[SPEAKER_09]: But he was the best thing about that movie and the rest of it was complete cheeseball.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cammy was great.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_09]: Kylie Minogue was pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was pretty great to see her in the movie.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think the reason that this movie's coming out now or soon, I guess Well, to tie in with all the other Street Fighter crap Well, yes, and also to make it seem like that the new movie isn't as bad as it really is, because you watch this movie and you see the new movie and you're like, holy crap, that's awesome you know, whereas the average person who's seen it can go yeah not great Very good point It's like, thank god it's not thank god it didn't kill any good actors in this one
[SPEAKER_09]: I will say this though, and not to spoil anything about the movie, but the very last thing in the entire movie, the little pose they all do at the very end, is by far the best part.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because it's so fucking cheesy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Good question from Frisbee in chat, chat.orange.radio.com Can we expect Street Fighter, the movie, the game?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_09]: Considering some of the people who were in development of that game have come out and now spoken about why the game was such crap, I don't think you're ever going to see that game again.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think that's the type of thing they've kind of swept under the rug and would like to leave there.
[SPEAKER_09]: So thanks for reminding them of such painful memories.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you want to play Street Fighter, the movie, the game, you just need to go find MAME.
[SPEAKER_09]: SSJ100Matt says, they are making that Street Fighter the later years into a TV show.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I would do it if my email would pull up, so just give me a second.
[SPEAKER_04]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_09]: Woohoo.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have a stunning total of one email.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it comes.
[SPEAKER_09]: By the way, as a reminder, that email address is mailbag at orangelaunchradio.com if you want to give DarkSakura some work to do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: So this comes from Geekboy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey guys, for episode 300 I sent an email and you asked how old I am.
[SPEAKER_04]: My 13th birthday is going to be on the 23rd.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, my parents know I listen.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't freak out.
[SPEAKER_04]: So SakuraMax beat that fatality.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is Jamie.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm on Twitter, so please give me the JSRF soundtrack info on there.
[SPEAKER_04]: And yes, I know I have typed this horribly, but I am too lazy to type slowly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is Orange Lounge!
[SPEAKER_04]: Exclamation points a lot.
[SPEAKER_04]: Done.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would just be happier if you actually... Dude, you spelled just, like, everything right.
[SPEAKER_04]: So why not try just using your shift key to capitalize stuff, okay?
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Pyramid Head is inferior Pyramid Head is inferior
[SPEAKER_09]: That's a pretty controversial statement right there on this program.
[SPEAKER_09]: Pyramid Head is inferior.
[SPEAKER_09]: Pyramid Head may be near and dear to many of your hearts, but I mean no ill will.
[SPEAKER_09]: If anything, I want to expose everyone to something more creepy and superior.
[SPEAKER_09]: Games with a horror theme may have their most memorable monsters and moments, but I believe that there is one out there to best them all, and it comes from Earthbound.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, the old Super Nintendo game with Ness in it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Before I continue, I'd like to put up the old spoiler warning here since what I'm referring to is the final boss of Earthbound.
[SPEAKER_09]: At the end of Earthbound, Ness faces Giygas, an enemy that has been inhabited by the very manifestation of evil and has become a formless, swirling mass of red and black.
[SPEAKER_09]: As the fight progresses, Giygas becomes more erratic and unsettling.
[SPEAKER_09]: The fight itself is disturbing even by today's standards, and it's a Super Nintendo game to boot.
[SPEAKER_09]: The parallax sprite of Giygas has a fetus in it, the audio in the fight is the actual boss itself, and Giygas' speech is just plain creepy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Truly an experience in itself.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here's a little clip of actually what that might look like.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's actually a little creepy sound that Giygas makes.
[SPEAKER_09]: That is a little bit creepy.
[SPEAKER_09]: And if that wasn't bad enough, consider the fact that there is complete leftover data for a potentially creepier rematch against Giygas in Mother 3.
[SPEAKER_09]: What was found was a sequence of imagery that gets progressively disturbing as the fight would have progressed if one were to play it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wouldn't you get freaked out?
[SPEAKER_09]: If you were fighting the hollow red outline image of a dead relative's face with pupil-less eyes and mouth gaping wide open, right.
[SPEAKER_09]: And there's audible speech for this iteration of Giygas.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is kind of creepy, all things considered.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyhow, even if you never play Earthbound, I implore the listeners to set aside a few minutes to watch these amazingly How's that spelled?
[SPEAKER_09]: frightening experiences.
[SPEAKER_09]: G-I-Y-G-A-S Search for Earthbound's Giygas Final Battle and Lucas Nightmare on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_09]: Greeny.
[SPEAKER_09]: So there you have it.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can put Giygas in the next Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_07]: game.
[SPEAKER_09]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's what I'm talking about.
[SPEAKER_09]: I want a horror all-stars game.
[SPEAKER_07]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll put him in Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_07]: and then it'll piss fans off even more because you had another character from Earthbound and they're not bringing it over here.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like what they did with Kid Icarus.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyhow, that's going to do it for tonight's Mailbag.
[SPEAKER_09]: Mailbag at OrangeLaunchRadio.com if you want to send us more emails.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like, oh, you won a Kid Icarus game, did you?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, one's coming.
[SPEAKER_07]: and someday, maybe, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: So Activision, you know, since they are going to be planning on making a lot of Guitar Hero games, needs some more developers to help them with that.
[SPEAKER_07]: So they have acquired Budcat to do that.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Budcat Creations, the studio that has been responsible for all Guitar Hero titles on PlayStation 2 since Guitar Hero 3 is...
[SPEAKER_07]: is currently in development of a new game in the Guitar Hero franchise.
[SPEAKER_07]: And one guess would be that it's Guitar Hero Metallica.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it says with Neversoft at the helm, Budkaz working on PS2, and Vicarious Visions will be responsible for the Wii and DS versions of whatever the next game will be.
[SPEAKER_08]: and Budcat also just worked on, I guess, a Wii game that just came out on the WiiWare service, Our House, which was published by Majesco.
[SPEAKER_09]: In the middle of the street?
[SPEAKER_09]: Our House?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Never mind.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is there really a lot of development that needs to go into Guitar Hero Metallica?
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently.
[SPEAKER_07]: Other than putting note charts together and
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, they have to make it so uniquely different.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, just like how Guitar Hero Aerosmith was so different from Guitar Hero 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, you know, we do need to create the exaggerated models of the Metallica band members.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, hey, it's interesting that Budcat is kind of being assimilated into the Acty Blizzard empire, but what can you do?
[SPEAKER_09]: More interesting stuff coming out for Guitar Hero, an official Gene Simmons brand Axe guitar coming out for not just Guitar Hero, but Rock Band as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sweet.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a wireless guitar.
[SPEAKER_09]: It looks like a freaking axe, not the deodorant.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm talking about like I'm going to chop you in half type axe, which actually looks pretty fucking sweet.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's coming out November 15th for $80.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll waste my money on that.
[SPEAKER_09]: That date just passed, so it's already out now.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's coming out for $80.
[SPEAKER_09]: It is compatible with PlayStation 3 and PlayStation 2 versions of Guitar Hero and Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_09]: The little controller actually will work with both.
[SPEAKER_09]: It uses a little dongle to get the signal there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Apparently, the actual guitar is like a three-quarter size official replica of the official Gene Simmons Axe guitar.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now, unfortunately, this guitar will only work for PlayStation 3 and PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you are an Xbox 360 owner, you have to wait until April of 2009.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you're a Wii owner, January 31st is when you get your version of the guitar.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I don't know why Xbox 360 owners have to wait so much longer, but there you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: They got, like, what, the Mad Catz bass guitar.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, as if there wasn't a million different guitars out there already, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: But I have to admit, this one does look pretty freaking sweet.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I do need a new guitar, but I play the games on the Xbox 360, so... Well, I'll tell you what, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: Speaking of guitars, this has nothing to do with it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to throw that ferret in a fireplace.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, you say that all the time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have you?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: The ferret is undefeatable.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what's funny is that in Wii Music you have all these obscure things, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: You have cheerleaders, triangles, cowbell, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: All that stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why don't we have ferret in Wii Music?
[SPEAKER_09]: That might have made the game sell more copies.
[SPEAKER_09]: Think about it, Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be the OLR edition of Wii Music.
[SPEAKER_09]: Think about it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Samba de Amigo is going to be on mobile phones.
[SPEAKER_04]: It will actually be with T-Mobile and AT&T phones, which pretty much spells out iPhone for me since I think T-Mobile has the iPhone now too, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Or was it?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I think in other countries they do, but not here.
[SPEAKER_04]: But also, T-Mobile has their sidekick too.
[SPEAKER_04]: So basically those nice big screens.
[SPEAKER_04]: But Samba de Amigo is going to be coming out for T-Mobile and AT&T phones.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's going to be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's, I mean, basically just Samba de Amigo.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you're not going to really have it being all fun and Morocco-y.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think you just shake the phone.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was going to say, I mean, how much can you really replicate the experience of Samba de Amigo on a friggin' cell phone?
[SPEAKER_09]: That's what I don't get, you know?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a little silly to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I might have to try it, but that's just to see exactly how it works.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, who knows?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't see any kind of a date on it or anything yet, but just keep looking if you care.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe I don't care.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, you can show right over there.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was how little I cared.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, we asked our listeners tonight in a little segment we're now going to call Show Us Your Twits on Twitter what they thought about the Samba de Amigo game.
[SPEAKER_09]: I need music for the Show Us Your Twits segment.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't have any music.
[SPEAKER_09]: I need to get some music.
[SPEAKER_04]: Find something porny.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's see what I can find.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_09]: Digging out some music.
[SPEAKER_09]: What do you guys think the listeners said while I tried to dig out some music here?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think they said burrito.
[SPEAKER_09]: Bean Burrito, Chimichanga.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's see if I can find live radio folks.
[SPEAKER_09]: How about now you're a man?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's not appropriate.
[SPEAKER_07]: Inappropriate.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, here we go.
[SPEAKER_07]: It has a line about big titties in it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here we go, here we go.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's try this again.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're going to go to a segment now we call Show Us Your Twits.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's see, 13xforever says, Nope, played just fine with my iPhone.
[SPEAKER_09]: DJ Tyron says, could be fun for a few minutes on the iPhone.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't see it being really worth it though.
[SPEAKER_09]: Music games generally suck on mobile.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dark Tetsuya says, even if I were into mobile gaming, probably not.
[SPEAKER_09]: Half the gameplay is shaking the maracas and you don't get that on a mobile.
[SPEAKER_09]: Deekman says, after the Wii version's crappy controls and no support on the console release, I'm not expecting anything Sega does to be good anymore.
[SPEAKER_09]: MistyOLR says, hell, I'll probably check it out if Verizon decides to make it work on my phone.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actdeft says, Samba de Amigo without maracas ain't Samba de Amigo.
[SPEAKER_09]: GS68 says, I don't play mobile games.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have a DS and a PSP.
[SPEAKER_09]: Marin Marvel says, probably not.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think it would be hard to emulate a game like that and make it as fun as the original in a mobile phone version.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, unless it was on the iPhone, maybe.
[SPEAKER_09]: Still, probably not.
[SPEAKER_09]: Crows says, ew, mobile games?
[SPEAKER_09]: Dem fancy cell phones were made for phone calls, nothing else.
[SPEAKER_09]: For gaming, they're probably even weaker than Game Boy Advance.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, Tipo says, sure, why not take a game beloved for its peripherals and put it out on mobile phones?
[SPEAKER_09]: What's next, Steel Battalion?
[SPEAKER_09]: and lastly, Geekboy says, I never had the chance to play the original because I was too young, but I wouldn't buy this in case I ever do get the chance to.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't want to ruin the experience.
[SPEAKER_09]: My cell phone is really crappy.
[SPEAKER_09]: I want an iPhone.
[SPEAKER_09]: If anybody wants to give me one, contact me.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll sell you mine for $400.
[SPEAKER_09]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: Show us your twits.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you want to follow us on Twitter,
[SPEAKER_09]: OLR is our username on Twitter.
[SPEAKER_09]: And you can answer questions and show us your twits every Sunday night here.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll sell mine autographed for $400.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, we autographed it, but it wore off.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_09]: Gaming news.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do we gotta?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, because we're almost to the classic game of the week, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_09]: And we have an interview tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: Aaron from Snake360.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know it's a busy show tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: We gotta keep it moving.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Guitar Hero World Tour and Rock Band are both getting brand new songs from the new Killers album, Day and Age.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's originally thought to only be debuting on Guitar Hero World Tour, but of course the MTV came out to say, hey, that's not true.
[SPEAKER_07]: So there's going to be a three-song track pack available day and date with the new album.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it will be available for...
[SPEAKER_07]: Guitar Hero World Tour for 440 Microsoft Points or 549 on the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, each song will be available individually for 160 Microsoft Points, $1.99 on PS3, and actually on the Nintendo Wii for 200 points a pop.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then for Rock Band...
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll be releasing, I guess, alongside with the thing as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: And no word on price or if they're going to just be doing like a three-song pack that says it looks like they're going to feature...
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it looks like it also might be the same.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, three different songs from there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Whereas Guitar Hero World Tour had Human and Losing Touch, Rock Band 2's got Mr. Right Side alongside with Smile Like You Mean It.
[SPEAKER_07]: and I guess both of them get day and age.
[SPEAKER_09]: The Killers are pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: I approve.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's one of the songs I really like to sing in SingStar.
[SPEAKER_09]: Which, by the way, SingStar is kind of an underrated karaoke game.
[SPEAKER_09]: It really does add to the party atmosphere to have the original videos playing in the background.
[SPEAKER_09]: I gotta say, all things considered, the SingStore, I know I'm totally getting off track, but I don't care.
[SPEAKER_09]: The SingStore works pretty well.
[SPEAKER_09]: I actually did play that game a little bit this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: We actually downloaded some of the stuff from SingStore.
[SPEAKER_09]: Paula Abdul Opposites Attract with the video and it's actually a duet and you can choose to sing Paula's part or MC Scat Cat.
[SPEAKER_09]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just wanted to say that even though it has nothing to do with the killers but it made me think of that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyhow, back to Rock Band and Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_09]: Some other download stuff coming out very soon.
[SPEAKER_09]: Rock Band is going to be getting the Dead Kennedys, a three-pack of Dead Kennedys songs.
[SPEAKER_09]: California Uber Al's, not Allies, but Al's.
[SPEAKER_09]: Holiday in Cambodia, you know that song.
[SPEAKER_09]: Police Truck coming out in a three-pack.
[SPEAKER_09]: Mission of Burma also getting a three-pack.
[SPEAKER_09]: Micah, That's How I Escaped My Certain Fate and That's When I Reached for My Revolver.
[SPEAKER_09]: I like that song.
[SPEAKER_09]: Century Media Girls of Metal three-pack.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's two songs from Lacuna Coil and one song from In This Moment.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then one more individual song coming out this week from Crooked X, a song called Gone.
[SPEAKER_09]: Guitar Hero, not to be outdone, is also releasing some songs this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Not quite as much, but they did land a pretty big-name artist, Jimi Hendrix.
[SPEAKER_09]: A Hendrix track pack is out this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: If Six Was Nine, Little Wing, and Fire live from Woodstock.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's pretty hot.
[SPEAKER_09]: So check those out.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can either get something modern there in Rock Band or something.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I guess it's not all modern, though, because some of those other songs were kind of like 80s punk, but pretty good diverse selection between the two games this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also to diversify your gaming week, DarkSakura is here to pick a game from the archives and dub it as her classic video game of the week because you kids need to respect your elder games and check out an old school game once in a while.
[SPEAKER_09]: And even though DarkSakura has kind of had some newer choices as of late, like last week was Symphony of the Night and you can kind of play that on the newer consoles, tonight's pick, going back to the very, very old school, right DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_04]: That it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: The game of the week is Wizards and Warriors, which is the game that I played a shit ton of.
[SPEAKER_09]: Me too.
[SPEAKER_09]: I love Wizards and Warriors.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's take a listen.
The map.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like the music that it plays when you go inside one of the little rooms in the trees.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, tell us a little more about Wizards and Warriors.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wizards and Warriors, you play as this dude named Kuros, who is wearing full plate armor, unlike the box.
[SPEAKER_04]: where he's dressed up as Conan the Barbarian, go fig.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, 80's Nintendo artwork was awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bite my big toe.
[SPEAKER_04]: Damn inaccurate bastards.
[SPEAKER_04]: Making men look like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, so you start off in the forest.
[SPEAKER_04]: The forest is wonderful and beautiful and scary and deadly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Full of spiders and creatures and thingies.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you can go inside trees.
[SPEAKER_04]: and the trees have doors and they make special noise every time you open the door and you get this cool music and suddenly the trees have like special things that you can jump on and spiders to kill so um um you basically are going through the game and you can get treasure chests that like if you find the ones with gems in it it says thou hast discovered gems
[SPEAKER_09]: There it was right there.
[SPEAKER_09]: That has discovered Dagger of Throwing.
[SPEAKER_09]: The Dagger of Throwing is so freaking useful.
[SPEAKER_09]: I remember that game.
[SPEAKER_09]: This game was awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you can also get potions and food as your healing items, weapons, and tools.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um...
[SPEAKER_04]: You have unlimited continues, and basically the only problem of dying is that your score gets reset to zero.
[SPEAKER_04]: So the main guy has a sword or an axe and a shield.
[SPEAKER_04]: However, in the sequel, you can actually choose to pick an element and then...
[SPEAKER_04]: Go through the game like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not really going to talk too much about the other versions because they were inferior in comparison to the first one.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's like, why couldn't they get him to look right on the cover?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry for going back to that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's still bothering me.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkTetsuya wants to point out, don't forget the sequel, Iron Sword, that that box art actually had Fabio on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I remember that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that also made the game slightly inferior.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, um, but I mean really the game is very simple.
[SPEAKER_04]: You just go through all the different stages and you have to, um, basically you have to keep unlocking, um, rescuing these women throughout the level until you rescue the princess.
[SPEAKER_09]: I always like to think of them as wenches.
[SPEAKER_04]: They were being held up by ropes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, now the thing, there is a trick with this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the big trick with this game is that if you go through the different levels and keep picking up however many, what was it?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it was the different keys you needed, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_04]: You can actually, if you go back into the second forest level, which is basically after you do the underground and come back up, there's actually a way to do a series of jumps to where you will jump over pretty much the screen divider back into the first level of forest.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you can play through the game again.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you'll actually beat the game halfway through the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because you'll just have all the number of items you need.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the princess will just be left there going, uh, dude, where are you?
[SPEAKER_04]: So you actually don't have to fight the final boss to beat the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can just glitch the game out hardcore.
[SPEAKER_04]: The bad guy, Malkill, was also in an episode of Captain N, the Game Master.
[SPEAKER_04]: Freaking stupid show.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was in the Nightmare on Mother Brain Street.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: and the world, in the game it was called the Kingdom of Elrond, in the show it was called Excalibur for some reason.
[SPEAKER_09]: Can I just say something completely random?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm watching the video of this guy playing Wizards and Warriors, and the little beehives that the bees come out of look like poop.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, they do.
[SPEAKER_04]: I call them shit bees.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, Kurose, the main guy, he was in a show called The Power Team, and they made him look like He-Man.
[SPEAKER_04]: But now this is one cool thing, and I wasn't quite aware of this, but the Wizards and Warriors story was turned into a book called Worlds of Power, a different series of novels for young children, and it was about a boy named Matthew who was trying to use his imagination creatively and instead brings his father's night figure to life and has to go help fight the battle.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that's just the story.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, I love this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hate every other version after it.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, the end.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wizards and Warriors is your classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Check it out if you happen to own a Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like this music too.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well done.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thou hast rescued... What was her name?
[SPEAKER_09]: Lucinda, the distressed damsel.
[SPEAKER_09]: 500 points.
[SPEAKER_09]: And conveniently, she's wearing a bikini.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who knew?
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe she's a harem girl.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wizards and Warriors is your classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're going to use this opportunity to take a quick break here on Orange Lounge Radio, but we'll be right back.
[SPEAKER_09]: Don't go anywhere.
[SPEAKER_09]: We still have Aaron to bring on from the game Snake 360, which is coming out with the new Xbox experience this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: And we have your phone calls and the FUs of the week and some news about LittleBigPlanet and some other things coming up in Part B. So don't go anywhere, darn it.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll be right back with more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: And welcome back to more of Orange Lounge Radio here on this lovely Sunday evening, November the 16th of 2008.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sorry I'm laughing, which isn't going to make much sense to the podcast listeners.
[SPEAKER_09]: But during the breaks when we were taping this live on Sunday nights at allgames.com, we like to just play some music for about 10 minutes just to give ourselves a chance to rest, use the restroom, take a break, and our live listeners to do the same.
[SPEAKER_09]: So we play some music from assorted video games.
[SPEAKER_09]: And one of the music we was playing there during the break was Super Mario... Did I just say we was playing?
[SPEAKER_09]: Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_04]: We was out there playing.
[SPEAKER_09]: We was playing something old school.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, we were playing the theme music from Super Mario Bros.
2.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I can play a clip of it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Playing clips of songs is okay on podcasts.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just can't play the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know the old school song?
[SPEAKER_09]: And DarkSakura comes in here and starts singing Dookie over all the lyrics.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dookie, Dookie, Dookie, Dookie, Dookie, Dookie.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I started singing along too and then it went Dookie, Dookie, Dookie, Dook, Poop.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then we just started busting up because we're like five years old.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, anyway.
[SPEAKER_09]: Look, let's get back to... And Frisbee says, dookie dookie panic.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's a Mario Brothers 2 joke, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_09]: I thought that was a funny joke.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're going to get back into some gaming news here during this Part B. You guys are going to call us a little later on with your phone calls and interview.
[SPEAKER_09]: Aaron Teplitsky is going to be joining us.
[SPEAKER_09]: Snake360.
[SPEAKER_09]: And you can see the teasers at snake360.com.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like the old school Snake from the cell phones, but like camera angles and color and multiplayer and goals and modes galore.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's nuts.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll talk all about it with Aaron here very soon.
[SPEAKER_09]: But first, some more gaming news.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, the recently released Banjo-Kazooie game, Nuts and Bolts, has...
[SPEAKER_07]: A little bit of a problem if you have an older TV, or an older TV that also happens to be very small.
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently the in-game text is too small to see on some standard definition television sets.
[SPEAKER_07]: And originally Rare had said that they weren't going to fix the problem, that it would be too expensive in terms of time, resources, and money to alter.
[SPEAKER_07]: The company has now gone back on that word and said that they will have a fix within the next 30 days.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which just goes to show you if the internet bitches enough, it will get its way.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, it can't be that hard.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, after all, Dead Rising had the same problem and the same fix.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, come on guys.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just like, what, editing a font?
[SPEAKER_07]: Seriously?
[SPEAKER_09]: I imagine though, from the developer's perspective, getting these patches out there has got to be a pain in the ass.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, to be fair though, all games that are published on the 360 are supposed to go through a process where they actually test them on a standard definition 14-inch TV.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the text has to be readable on that, and it has to play well, look right, and all that sort of stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: So the...
[SPEAKER_07]: I have no idea.
[SPEAKER_09]: How this gets missed or approved, you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, seeing that, in my memory, it's only been two games really so far that have had this issue, I think that the precautions and the steps are in place to make sure this doesn't happen.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think that maybe they were trying to rush the game out to the market and didn't quite have time to go back and fix said problem with game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Until after the fact.
[SPEAKER_07]: And at first they said, oh, let's see if no one notices.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, you know, sure enough, people noticed.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they're like, ah, let's see if they're fine with us not fixing it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And sure enough, people weren't.
[SPEAKER_07]: So now they have to do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, speaking of Banjo-Kazooie, Loki has been able to hook us up with...
[SPEAKER_09]: This right here, I'm holding in my hot little hand on Justin TV.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you guys can see that there, if you're on the radio, you unfortunately cannot see it.
[SPEAKER_09]: But what this is, this is a code for you to download the original Banjo-Kazooie game on Xbox Live absolutely free.
[SPEAKER_09]: Free!
[SPEAKER_09]: And we're going to be giving that away next week on the show.
[SPEAKER_09]: A popular game is coming back that we haven't played here on the show in a long time.
[SPEAKER_09]: One vs. the Chat Room is going to be played next week, and this code is going to be given away to a lucky winner.
[SPEAKER_09]: So even if you didn't pre-order the brand new Banjo-Kazooie game, you can still get your hot little hands on the old school one on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're going to be giving that away.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just because we love ya!
[SPEAKER_09]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_09]: So next week, be here for one versus the chat room.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sadly, I'm sorry podcast listeners.
[SPEAKER_09]: It won't work out that we can give one away to you guys this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I promise the next contest we do will be open to all.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was satisfying, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hunting the chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: Getting up and getting to wave that.
[SPEAKER_09]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, so stay tuned for that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Meantime, we're going to move on to the PlayStation 3 and talking about LittleBigPlanet.
[SPEAKER_09]: Man, what a mess LittleBigPlanet has suddenly become.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: I talked about this game last week.
[SPEAKER_09]: This game is awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: I still love this game, but it sounds like moderation is really starting to get a little crazy there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sony apparently has laid out some rules this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ensure the content you share with other users is suitable for all ages and everybody has access to your level if you publish it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Please respect other people's intellectual property rights.
[SPEAKER_09]: For example, don't use images, brands, or logos that you're not entitled to use.
[SPEAKER_09]: And if you come across any content that you feel the need to report, then please do it responsibly.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hoax reports will be considered inappropriate behavior.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I don't know if this has made anything better for them to come out and clarify because apparently some really popular levels on LittleBigPlanet have been hit, including one called Azure Palace, which I haven't played myself, but apparently
[SPEAKER_09]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: Apparently it's a very, very popular level.
[SPEAKER_09]: One of the favorite.
[SPEAKER_09]: It got hit for moderation this week, if you can believe it.
[SPEAKER_09]: And they can't figure out why this game got hit for moderation.
[SPEAKER_09]: Was it the blood splatters they had in the level that apparently were?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: It gets worse than that, actually.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not just that one.
[SPEAKER_07]: Many of the top levels have been hit with moderation, including the World of Color, which is another one.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which, there is nothing copyright in World of Color.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't get that.
[SPEAKER_09]: That is weird.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, the level creator of Azure Palace is pissed.
[SPEAKER_09]: He made a comment, So, needless to say, uh...
[SPEAKER_09]: Whoever is pulling these levels, Sony, Medium Molecule, whoever, I imagine it's Sony, whoever is pulling these levels is starting to bite the hand that feeds them a little bit because if you piss off all the people that are creating the great content for your game, there's not going to be much left but those, you know, win nine trophies in 30 second levels which get old fast.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's really sad, though, because lots of levels are getting moderated.
[SPEAKER_07]: Some, you know, maybe they're kind of borderline.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's like that Tetris level that was sort of like Tetris, but not quite.
[SPEAKER_07]: That got moderated.
[SPEAKER_07]: That level was a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's a bunch of other ones, but there's seriously a ton of threads on LittleBigWorkshop, the official website for LittleBigPlanet and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: And...
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, tons of stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's a 22 page post on there that's just going.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, and some of the things, like some of the comments.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's a minigame actually in LittleBigPlanet in the Frozen Tundra world called Spline Rider where you get on a thin sled and slide around on a track.
[SPEAKER_07]: Seems kind of familiar to a popular online game called Line Rider.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it's okay for Media Monocle to go ahead and rip off other games but it's not okay for other people to do that.
[SPEAKER_09]: and they actually have... And it's okay for them to have a strip club in the game, but heaven forbid you see a blood splatter.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know those blood splatters?
[SPEAKER_07]: Those are actually taken from the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're in one of the Asian levels in there where there's blood splatters underneath these blades that are there.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it's stuff that's in the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just...
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: What's going to be left?
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: then you can still make a copy of the original level again and re-upload it if you need to.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, if you want, one good thing if you think someone's going to kick your level offline, make it so that they can download a copy of your level as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: You have that option on there so someone can actually save it, even put it in your comments to make sure you save the level when you're done.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can actually save it to your moon and then it doesn't matter if it gets moderated.
[SPEAKER_09]: and if anyone from Sony or Media Molecule happens to listen to this show because we do have some industry people that listen to this show but kind of keep quiet and they don't really let us know they're listening if anybody from either of those companies happens to listen to this show it is imperative you guys comment on the situation like this week I mean you can't let this keep going on much longer it is starting to snowball out of control it is imperative you get your legal department on the ball and say something quick
[SPEAKER_07]: And the other thing too is because people aren't saying anything, people are thinking the worst.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, are they going to steal my levels and use them in a download pack or something they're going to charge money for?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, why are they doing this?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the thing that's really ridiculous about it is, say you work 20 hours on a level and upload it and stuff like that, and they moderate it for some retarded reason, you can't re-upload it again.
[SPEAKER_07]: So you can't really make a copy of it or do whatever with it.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I seem to remember this comparison being made in the past, but GS68 makes it again tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: See, Blastworks has levels with copyrighted imagery, yet their staff doesn't mind that shit.
[SPEAKER_09]: And nobody sued Blastworks yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, very interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: TigerClaw says, this could probably spark a global boycott of the game if they don't fix it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know so much about that because I think a lot of people that were going to... The games have already all been sold a lot of times.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_09]: Most people that were really eager about the game have already bought it.
[SPEAKER_09]: YYR kind of follows up with that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Global boycott will never happen.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's as likely to happen as an internet petition meaning something.
[SPEAKER_07]: The FUs of the Week
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura wants to start us off tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: F you to apathetic voters, as in people who don't vote.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, really, there's people, well, actually, specifically, the people who complain about an issue and don't vote on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because if you, if it doesn't mean enough to you to go out and make your voice heard, you know, at least by giving your vote to the issue, then you have no right to complain.
[SPEAKER_09]: But like if somebody just abstains from voting for a school board member because they don't know anything about them.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm talking about big issues.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I'm just saying though.
[SPEAKER_04]: If it's something that's really not going to affect everything from day to day, that's one thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: But if it's something like, oh, example, a civil rights issue.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hmm, Alameda County.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I'm sorry, only 22% of them voted.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Lazy asses.
[SPEAKER_04]: But just make sure if it means something to you that instead of just bitching about it, you do something about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki!
[SPEAKER_07]: F you to my place of employment for still not giving me a raise and for potentially making my job even harder.
[SPEAKER_07]: My coworker is quitting here within the next couple weeks and
[SPEAKER_07]: Unfortunately they're going to probably hire someone else to fill his spot and I'm going to get probably some of his bigger accounts and they're planning on giving me yet another really big account and it's just more work for me to do with no sort of compensation for it and it kind of sucks but their mentality is you don't like it, leave and unfortunately I've been there for almost 10 years and I would rather
[SPEAKER_09]: I really just want to give an F you tonight to Noah's Bagels and their bagel dogs because they're so delicious and I can't stop eating them, especially now that, you know, after the gallbladders come out and my health is starting to get back to normal, thank God.
[SPEAKER_09]: F you to those things for being so damn yummy and I know they're not good for you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry that my FU is a little more silly compared to some of the others tonight, but sometimes it's the little things.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, anyhow, let's get back into some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: The magic number is five.
[SPEAKER_09]: What magic number?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_09]: I thought three was a magic number.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's what they told me on Schoolhouse Rock.
42.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, I see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, who's been looking forward to LocoRoco 2?
[SPEAKER_09]: I never really got into LocoRoco1, but I'd check it out.
[SPEAKER_09]: I would check it out.
[SPEAKER_04]: LocoRoco is crack!
[SPEAKER_09]: At any rate... Yes, ma'am.
[SPEAKER_04]: On the online portal for the LocoRoco 2 site, there is actually a Flash minigame that you can play.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's over on Spill Games' website, and it will be there until the 21st of November, so try it while you can, and download it while you can.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry, did I say that out loud?
[SPEAKER_04]: But I will be linking the...
[SPEAKER_04]: the site in the chat room however to go ahead and say this on the podcast it is at games.co.uk slash game slash loco roco 2.html so give it a try it's cute alrighty it's the cuteness there's some people are calling it in chat Loki Roco it's not Loki Roco
[SPEAKER_09]: That's a cute name.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki Roko.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's what we'll start calling him on this program.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki Roko.
[SPEAKER_07]: This rumor's been around before, but now it's coming into yet another venue, I guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: Electronic Gaming Monthly, their usual quarterman segment of different rumors and speculations.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, he now has a rumor saying that LittleBigPlanet will be coming to the PSP in 2009.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, it makes sense that they'll do that, and I think with actually the controls, it could work.
[SPEAKER_07]: You could easily do that on there.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know how it'd look, because the PSP obviously is not as powerful as, I don't know, the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it's not being developed by Media Molecule, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: It seems that they are actually at the...
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh yeah, that's right.
[SPEAKER_07]: It won't have them.
[SPEAKER_07]: Instead it's Sony Studio Liverpool.
[SPEAKER_09]: We asked Media Molecule for comment and what they said is that they were going to moderate this game for being too similar to their own.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's kind of a bummer.
[SPEAKER_09]: They said, I am Spartacus.
[SPEAKER_09]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, it's no surprise, though, that they're going to hoard this franchise out into the ground, that there's a PSP version coming out.
[SPEAKER_09]: It might actually be pretty cool, especially if, wait for this, especially if the levels you get, assuming this whole moderation thing gets figured out, if you could get the levels on your PS3 and transfer them to your PSP, that might be pretty awesome, actually.
[SPEAKER_09]: Don't you think?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know if it'd look right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because of the proportions and everything?
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't imagine that they'd be able to do the same kind of quality on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's got to be scaled down quite a bit.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know about you guys.
[SPEAKER_09]: It sounds pretty interesting to me.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, damn, the news will not just stop coming in about Burnout Paradise.
[SPEAKER_09]: What was it?
[SPEAKER_09]: Just last week we were talking about the awesome old school cars that were going to be in the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: And now, apparently, toy cars are coming to Burnout Paradise.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know...
[SPEAKER_09]: Criterion, they're really awesome about this.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're showing you how to keep the game alive.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, now apparently they are going to be introducing tiny little collectible cars.
[SPEAKER_09]: No idea if the cars themselves will be tiny in the game, but they all look like little Hot Wheels and they're pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: Apparently there's nine cars in all.
[SPEAKER_09]: Carson GT Concept P12, Krieger Racing WTR, Hunter Takedown 4x4 and Hunter Manhattan, so on and so on.
[SPEAKER_09]: Apparently they're all going to come out next year and...
[SPEAKER_09]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: Criterion just keeps supporting this game.
[SPEAKER_09]: I love the monster truck.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's going to be awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: This little purple one with flames on it.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're putting hot wheels in the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Good for them.
[SPEAKER_07]: That would be funny if you could actually drive the little cars around and they act like big cars.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can smash through things and just pow, pow, pow.
[SPEAKER_09]: Power wheels, pow, pow.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, forget it.
[SPEAKER_09]: That would be a preschooler driving a car around would be pretty awesome, don't you think?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a 21 year old and leads a raiding guild and the character is called Nim.
[SPEAKER_04]: N-Y-M-H.
[SPEAKER_04]: 27 hours worth of leveling and being kept alive by a healer.
[SPEAKER_04]: So Nim got all the experience and made it to 80.
[SPEAKER_04]: And apparently...
[SPEAKER_04]: The one right after was someone called Darius who was suspended by Blizzard at level 79 and bumped back to level 70 after using an exploit.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, snap.
[SPEAKER_09]: I want to know what the exploit was.
[SPEAKER_04]: Grinding.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Grinding in a crypt in the Grizzly Hills area.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wait a second.
[SPEAKER_07]: Grinding is not an exploit.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, he didn't get banned either.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, Darius got banned.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or rolled back or whatever you want to call it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I wonder what that exploit was.
[SPEAKER_04]: He got wall-marted.
[SPEAKER_09]: He got moderated.
[SPEAKER_09]: He got Walmarted.
[SPEAKER_09]: Moderate!
[SPEAKER_09]: Now, what makes this so notable is that, you know, it's supposed to take you, like, a month to get to 80.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, the game came out, what, Wednesday night?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm level 73, and I've been playing pretty hardcore.
[SPEAKER_09]: Most people in my guild are only, like, 71, maybe 72.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, apparently this place that he was grinding at has a really high respawn rate, and monsters are neutral monsters.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a crypt in the Grizzly Hills area.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go spam it, everybody, and crash the server!
[SPEAKER_07]: There's a lot of level one boars there, and he just kept killing them.
[SPEAKER_07]: Solid Goomba comments and says, Mom!
[SPEAKER_09]: Bathroom!
[SPEAKER_09]: which must have been exactly what happened here with this guy.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, you know, despite all the fun being made of this guy, the thing that he did that the rest of the people aren't doing, they obviously found this area in the beta, figured it would be a good area to go to.
[SPEAKER_09]: When the game hit, they went straight to this area.
[SPEAKER_09]: This was their sole intention, to gain XP as fast as possible, and with a Warlock of a certain spec, it's pretty easy to do if you have a dedicated healer, and did nothing but level.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyhow, you know I've been playing Wrath of the Lich King quite a lot this week, but something that might actually be able to divert my attention away from Warcraft this next week is the release of the new Xbox Experience.
[SPEAKER_09]: One thing we've been talking about a lot on this show is the addition of community games to the Xbox dashboard.
[SPEAKER_09]: One of the games that is going to be coming...
[SPEAKER_09]: Out is called Snake360, and it has an interesting tie-in to music-based video games, which we've been talking about a lot on this show, you know, previously in our history and anything.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway, to join us on the show tonight to talk about Snake360 is its creator, Aaron Teplitsky.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're going to get on the phones and get a hold of Aaron and talk to him a little bit about his new game, Snake360.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, hey, Aaron, are you there?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I'm right here.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, well welcome to the show.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks so much for taking the time to be on Orange Lounge Radio this evening.
[SPEAKER_09]: How you doing this Sunday night?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm doing great.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you very much for having me on here.
[SPEAKER_03]: I really appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Awesome, not a problem.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, we're all about, you know, the independent games as well as the big boys.
[SPEAKER_09]: So tell us, your game is Snake 360, coming to the new Xbox 360 experience.
[SPEAKER_09]: Tell us a little bit about Snake 360.
[SPEAKER_09]: What is this game all about?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, basically what it is, it's similar to, you know, Snake games that you've probably seen before on cell phones, old computers, and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_03]: But what it is is a complete reimagining.
[SPEAKER_03]: Graphically, you know, it's got 3D graphics, it runs nice and smooth, and, you know, it has a very clean look.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a little boxy, but, you know, that's the way Snake is.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, basically, you know, it's not...
[SPEAKER_03]: You're not going to get a huge graphical masterpiece.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you're looking for that, then you'll play Gears 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: But what it lacks in graphics, it definitely makes up for in the gameplay department.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's got classic gameplay and a whole wide range of levels.
[SPEAKER_03]: They start ridiculously easy.
[SPEAKER_03]: You've got your four walls, and that's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: and then it goes up to insanely difficult.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you like retro games, arcade games, just challenging games in general, you're going to get a lot of mileage out of Snake360, especially seeing as how it's got internet-based leaderboards.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, I think you're selling yourself a little bit short on the graphical ability of the game because, you know, sure, we all know the game Snake on cell phones.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's, you know, a blocky game where you kind of go, but I noticed in watching the trailer on your website, Snake360.com, you kind of do all these little
[SPEAKER_09]: Well you know, what I try and do is I throw in the instant replays and the
[SPEAKER_03]: Camera effects from the different angles and part of it is functionality related because sometimes you want to view the whole level.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sometimes you want a view of just you so you can line up better, get a view of your surroundings.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe you want to zoom in, maybe you want to zoom out.
[SPEAKER_03]: So part of it is just functionality related.
[SPEAKER_03]: But also we've come to expect a lot of these things in games.
[SPEAKER_03]: if you're in battle mode and you just cut the other guy off and surprise the heck out of him and everybody in the room is screaming and yelling you're going to want to watch that over and over and over again to rub it in his face so you've got the instant replay for that reason
[SPEAKER_09]: Sounds great.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, now, I don't want to talk just about graphics.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's talk about music for a minute, because even though this game has nothing to do with arrow stomping or beat matching, I hear there's a connection in here for fans of dance music games, which we have a lot of at Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's the connection?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, well, actually, it turns out I was looking for music, and I'm no musician, so I went to Kyle Ward and John Mendenhall and their record label, SCI Recordings.
[SPEAKER_03]: Their website right now is SCIREcordings.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: and we struck a little bit of a deal and as it turns out players of the In The Groove series of games and also the more recent Pump Pro are going to find that they're familiar with a lot of the music in the game and we fleshed it out with some music that they won't be familiar with and in total there are nine of their songs in the game and I think that the players are going to really enjoy the soundtrack it's you know pumping you know get your blood moving and
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe cause you not to crash into a wall, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, well, I'm really fond of the soundtrack, and I've been listening to it for months straight, working on the game, and I'm not sick of it yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I guess that probably says that it might actually be working for the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: So you mentioned you've been working on the game for months.
[SPEAKER_09]: How long did things take from idea to where we are, the game's launching November 19th?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I'll be quite honest with you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Throughout 2007, I was thinking about this game constantly.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm working this little IT job for a non-profit, which is completely not the field that I want to be working in.
[SPEAKER_03]: And just driving from place to place, I'd be thinking about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'd be thinking, well, this is how I want this to work, and this is how I imagine this.
[SPEAKER_03]: And towards the end of the year, with X and A out, I just said, well, why don't I take a stab at this?
[SPEAKER_03]: and my original intent was to target Xbox Live Arcade and I actually submitted to them and it took them a long time to get back to me I don't know what happened with that but in the time between the time I submitted to them and the time they gave me the final answer they announced community games so I'm thinking yeah hey that's not a bad idea and then finally they came back and they said well we have limited space for casual action games on Xbox Live Arcade so we feel it's not a good fit at this time
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'm like, well, you know, community games.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that was back in March.
[SPEAKER_03]: So starting in March, I started working on it, you know, more frequently.
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually started, completely started last December.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's when I just, you know, started from scratch with XNA and, you know, got a snake moving on the screen and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then I really took it into high gear in August.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I really started about a year ago, but I'd say, you know, solid work is probably about seven months of work
[SPEAKER_03]: All my spare time went into this game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know that was a long, convoluted answer, but yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, that's all right.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's very interesting to kind of hear that you actually had submitted it originally as an Xbox Live arcade game, but yet they turned it down.
[SPEAKER_09]: And when you look at some of the stuff that's on Xbox Live Marketplace that they let through... Well, you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's interesting you say that, because I'm not the only one who's been turned down.
[SPEAKER_03]: Have you heard of the Japanese shoot-'em-up developer, Cave?
[SPEAKER_09]: I think I have, yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was absolutely floored when I found out that they submitted two of their games to Live Arcade and they were turned down because I absolutely adore their games.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have a Japanese PS2 that I basically play shoot-em-ups on.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm planning on getting a Japanese 360 so I can play the upcoming Cave Shooters if they're not localized here.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was absolutely floored.
[SPEAKER_03]: But on the other hand, I felt, well, you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: If they're being rejected, then maybe I don't feel so bad.
[SPEAKER_09]: At least you're in good company.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, well, talking about the development cycle of the game, you know, a lot of folks kind of, you know, are critical of the Xbox 360 control scheme.
[SPEAKER_09]: But you kind of found an interesting way around it for a game that requires kind of precision in turning like Snake does, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, well, everybody knows that the 360's D-pad leaves a lot to be desired.
[SPEAKER_03]: One of the first things I did when I started playing XBLA games was I went and I bought an arcade stick because even for Pac-Man, you know, it just gums up the works.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't play Pac-Man with that D-pad.
[SPEAKER_03]: So at first, you know, I was thinking, well, you know, we can use the analog sticks and you've got those options, but really the best solution, and I say so in the trailer, not in the trailer, I say so in the other video I put up, I say so in the documentation, and I say so within the game itself.
[SPEAKER_03]: The best solution is to use the A, B, X, and Y face buttons.
[SPEAKER_03]: A is down, Y is up, and then you've got X and B for the sides.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that is absolutely the best way to control this game.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: That sounds like a very creative workaround.
[SPEAKER_09]: So that's probably what I'll use.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, we weren't using those buttons for anything else.
[SPEAKER_03]: Basically, I was thinking, well, you know, we could do turbo boosts, we could do this and that.
[SPEAKER_03]: But in the end, I decided for this version, because I might expand it later, especially considering that
[SPEAKER_03]: The version I'm releasing is not the version I originally anticipated.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't quite get everything that I wanted in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: But for this version, I decided, let's keep the accessibility high.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's keep the gameplay simple so that you look at it, you know exactly how it works, you can jump right in.
[SPEAKER_03]: The challenge of this game is not in new gameplay elements, but it's in the challenging level designs and all the other things you can do with it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, it works extremely similarly to the way that, uh,
[SPEAKER_03]: any internet ranking board work before we had online leaderboards that were integrated into the game itself.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anybody who played Ikaruga on GameCube and participated in the rankings there, there are also rankings in a lot of arcade games where they basically just put codes on the screen.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you go to their website, you put in the code, yeah, you put in the code and boom, there you are on the internet rankings.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we'll have it keep track of your email address so that if you submit the same score twice,
[SPEAKER_03]: or if you submit two scores for one course, it'll automatically overwrite your lower score with your higher one.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the reason there are over 50 leaderboards is because there's going to be a leaderboard for every course, every difficulty, every round you can play in survival mode.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can go crazy competing for high scores in this game.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're still finishing up the internet ranking.
[SPEAKER_03]: It should hopefully be ready by the end of next week.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now, you mentioned there's all these different types of internet ranking boards.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's because you have all these different types of modes and handicaps in the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it sounds like you've made this very accessible for children as well as, you know, hardcore people that really get into these types of arcade games.
[SPEAKER_09]: Tell us about some of your favorite modes that you have in the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I mean, the main game mode basically throws you into a course consisting of eight levels.
[SPEAKER_03]: and actually it may or may not consist of eight levels depending on whether you lose any lives along the way and I'll leave it at that but if you can complete all the levels on the course you'll get a code for internet ranking and the courses are played on several different difficulty levels what you'll get is you know basically this kind of the same concept
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, for example, on easy, maybe you'll get something that kind of looks like a tree.
[SPEAKER_03]: On normal, you'll get a tree.
[SPEAKER_03]: On difficult, you'll get a tree with more branches, that kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: So they'll take the same concept, and we'll just keep making it more and more difficult as you go up in level.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, you know, a lot of the level themes are very interesting, and part of the fun of the game is to see, oh, well, now I'm playing on a new level.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wonder what this level's going to look like.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the survival mode, well, that's just, you know, classic.
[SPEAKER_03]: A lot of the old Snake games just played like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: you get one life and you just last as long as you can and you grow to ridiculous lengths and this version throws in a time limit that you can't just go in a circle and survive forever and you get a time bonus when you pick up a target but you're just going to have to be really careful not to block yourself off from more targets or trap yourself it's very interesting and one of the fake achievements I'm going to call them goals in the game is to last in there for four minutes and it's harder than it sounds
[SPEAKER_09]: What about some of the things you've put?
[SPEAKER_09]: Now, this is something for a player who's really, really good at the game, but what about somebody who's not so great at Snake 360?
[SPEAKER_09]: There's kind of modes you've put in for them, too, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, well, you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: My mother's even played this game using a couple of handicaps that I've put in.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's slower speeds.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can turn the Snake speed down to slow or even slowest, which is half the normal speed.
[SPEAKER_03]: It plays pretty slowly.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you've got good reflexes, you'll want to stick with the normal or the faster speeds, but there's a slow speed for them, and there's also visual guides that you can turn on in the form of lines that extend from the targets in all four directions, so you can line up more easily with those.
[SPEAKER_03]: And if you play with those on, then you won't be eligible for the Internet ranking, but it's something that'll get a lot more people into the game, making it easier to
[SPEAKER_03]: That sort of thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: And there's also something exciting I threw in called Kid Mode.
[SPEAKER_03]: And with this, you know, anybody can play.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like bumper bowling for Snake.
[SPEAKER_03]: Basically, you know, you're rushing into a wall.
[SPEAKER_03]: Boom.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nothing happens.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, you're stuck on the wall.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, well, now you have three seconds to turn and go somewhere else.
[SPEAKER_03]: and basically the effect of this is you won't die unless you trap yourself somehow, spiral, you know, that sort of deal.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you could just, you know, go there all day and then the easy difficulty has no time limit.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you could spend three hours, you know, on one level and take as much time as you need so long as you don't trap yourself.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, sounds like there's something for the young and the old alike in this game, so awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, and if you're not sure whether you're young or old, if you start playing and then the game sees you're having trouble, it'll offer to turn one of these handicaps on for you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_09]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's talk about kind of the bigger picture for a minute, just community games in general.
[SPEAKER_09]: Kind of not just your game, but all the other games kind of going in when the new Xbox Experience launches.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, we've heard kind of leading up to this launch, we've heard a lot about Netflix, we've heard a lot about avatars.
[SPEAKER_09]: It seems to me...
[SPEAKER_09]: for as big of a deal as at least I perceive this community games thing to be where we have a lot of great indie developers showing up.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're not hearing as much about it as you would think, you know, with all these, what, 20 games on the service right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: Are you kind of surprised that there's been a little less focus on community games leading up towards the launch?
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, on one hand I am, but on the other hand I'm really not because, you know, let's say I'm EA or Activision or some other big name publisher and I've got $60 games on the shelf from launching a new IP like Mirror's Edge and, um,
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, all of a sudden, Microsoft is promoting the heck out of all these little five and ten and two and a half dollar games.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'm going to be a little bit, you know, pissed off.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to be like, hey, hi, we want to keep selling our $60 games, so you guys better lay off and delay this to next year or we're going to stop publishing on your console.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would be my point of view if I was a big name publisher.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'd be, if I were them, I'd be happy that they're not plugging the heck out of this stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Excuse me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Obviously, these relationships are very important to Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, yeah, I'm kind of not surprised that we're a little under the radar.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I think once people get a hold of the new NXE, they're definitely going to notice community games.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's right there with Live Arcade and the Game Store.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you go to the Game Marketplace, it's right there as a category.
[SPEAKER_03]: And if you've been accepted into the NXE preview and you already have it, you can see plain as day there are already 20 games on the service.
[SPEAKER_03]: So,
[SPEAKER_03]: The visibility is not going to be an issue.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's going to kind of sneak up on people and really surprise them.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, very cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, one thing, before we let you go, Aaron, one thing we always like to ask our guests here on Orange Lounge Radio, it's a segment we always do every week, we want to ask you, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_09]: What other kinds of video games have you been playing besides Snake360?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you know what, this last week has been kind of crazy.
[SPEAKER_03]: I took the whole week off from work, you know, presumably to focus on Snake, but then I basically came down with a really bad cold, and my fiance had a really bad cold as well, you know, starting last week and going into this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I was very distracted all week, partially with, you know, with Snake, partially with having a cold, and then, of course, for a lot of times I couldn't stay focused, so...
[SPEAKER_03]: I diverted my attention with a little bit of Half-Life 2, which I hadn't really gotten to play very much of yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm enjoying it a lot.
[SPEAKER_03]: I completed a few more of the advanced portal maps.
[SPEAKER_03]: I still have one left that I'm completely stuck on.
[SPEAKER_03]: I picked up the new Namco compilation, Namco Museum Virtual Arcade, which is a complete cash-in because it's so shoddily thrown together.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it features every XBLA release Namco has had up to this point, and it was only $30, so I'm a sucker for those.
[SPEAKER_03]: and so I played that a little bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: I haven't been able to get out to an arcade but I usually try to play a step game at least once a week.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's the only kind of exercise I can do.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well Aaron, rest up and feel better.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know we've been hearing you coughing a little bit tonight but I hope by the time this game launches you're well enough to celebrate when NXT comes out on November 19th.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm really excited you were able to have me on here talking about it and I hope for all the arcade game fans, retro game fans or
[SPEAKER_03]: Just, you know, fans of fun games.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hope you guys could take a few minutes of your day to check out Snake360.
[SPEAKER_03]: The trial game will run for four minutes, and you'll be able to try out one of the courses on three different levels and battle mode with two players.
[SPEAKER_03]: And just give it a shot, and I appreciate, you know, giving it a try.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, well, the game is Snake 360, and it's launching with the new Xbox 360 experience on November 19th.
[SPEAKER_09]: It has got a free time trial for you to check out the game, and if you want the full game, it's only going to set you back 400 points.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you want more information in the meantime, check out the website at snake360.com.
[SPEAKER_09]: Aaron, thanks so much for joining us tonight, and best of luck with the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: I hope it does really well for you.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'd love to quit my IT job, but thank you very much, Rob, for having me on the program.
[SPEAKER_09]: I hope you guys will check out the demo.
[SPEAKER_09]: At least look at the YouTube on the website.
[SPEAKER_09]: It looks pretty rad.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyhow, let's go ahead and move on with some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: Speaking of retro games, you may remember the Atari 2600 flashback systems that were released a while back.
[SPEAKER_07]: They even had one that was in the
[SPEAKER_07]: True2Life, Woodgrain.
[SPEAKER_07]: But now, the same company that brought those out are actually now bringing out USB Atari 2600 controllers.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can actually use those to play whatever the heck you'd like, but mostly they're ideal for main usage, and they are compatible, of course, with Windows, Mac OS, and Linux, and will run you $14.99.
[SPEAKER_09]: Boy, they just love to whore out the old school Atari 2600 stuff, don't they?
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, going from old school controller that's $14.99 to something rather new school, who doesn't love to play pinball?
[SPEAKER_09]: Right, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_09]: You love pinball.
[SPEAKER_09]: Pinball is fantastic.
[SPEAKER_09]: You spend a lot of money on pinball, but you buy the authentic pinball machines.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know how big of a fan you are of video pinball games, you know, the types of things.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Would you be willing to spend $300 on your obsession?
[SPEAKER_04]: Depends.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it like an ultracade?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, here it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nanotech Entertainment is putting out what's called a Pinball Wizard Controller.
[SPEAKER_09]: Real flipper buttons, an actual plunger, motion sensing thing for the tilting on it, $300 for the controller.
[SPEAKER_09]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'd do it.
[SPEAKER_09]: You'd have to be pretty sick into this in order to justify this, but Nanotech is putting this out.
[SPEAKER_09]: It is the Pinball Wizard Controller.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's got what's called a Mosh Ion or whatever, Mode Ion, Motion, IO Adapter.
[SPEAKER_09]: No special drivers required for this.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's apparently fully configurable.
[SPEAKER_09]: It will work with a lot of existing pinball games that are out there right now, something they call a fancy-smancy future pinball engine.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_09]: Apparently it ships with a combination of a variety of different 3D pinball games already out there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Some recreations of famous pinball tables from Gottlieb.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know what tables those are yet, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: That hasn't been said.
[SPEAKER_09]: But you can keep an eye out for more information on this.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nanotech Entertainment.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's nanotechent.com.
[SPEAKER_07]: All I got to say is the who will sue.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why is that?
[SPEAKER_07]: Pinball Wizard.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know, because of the name, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that by now, you know, it should be fair use.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a little much for me.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'd rather just take the plunge and get a real machine.
[SPEAKER_09]: I need one already, but they're so expensive.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't have the money.
[SPEAKER_09]: And yeah, I got that collection on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: I guess I can just keep that for now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, there is something that actually is a little interesting, I should say, as far as some stuff for Rock Revolution, if anyone is actually interested in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's interested in that game?
[SPEAKER_09]: Rock Revolution.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, as I said, I'm still curious to check it out.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm just waiting for the price to drop, which should happen soon.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I also love the movie Showgirls.
[SPEAKER_09]: So take my opinion with a grain of salt.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, at any rate, there's some downloadable content for Xbox Live Marketplace.
[SPEAKER_04]: There is Desro, Death Reel.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a cool song.
[SPEAKER_04]: Naoki, remixed by Kuro, which is my only shining star.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, got tongue-tied.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mutsuhiko Izumi with Model DD8.
[SPEAKER_04]: Daisuke Kurosawa with Progressive Baby and Chimera.
[SPEAKER_04]: So...
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, so despite all the crap we've given Rock Revolution in saying why don't they just bring out Guitar Freaks over here, interesting yet non-surprising that some of these tracks are crossover, at least the artists are certainly from those series, coming over to Rock Revolution.
[SPEAKER_09]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: There actually is a press release also out by Konami stating that it actually is shipping, will be $129.99 and is available for Xbox 360 and PS3.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, well, check it out if you really want.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now what's kind of interesting is we talk about game piracy a lot.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well there was one game actually that was out there, World of Goo, that was actually pretty good.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was more of a puzzle game that came out on PC and WiiWare.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's interesting though is the developer actually has come out, designer Ron Carmel, who mentioned that his game has received a 90% piracy rate.
[SPEAKER_07]: and um yeah apparently he's been doing some research in the different torrent sites with you know some torrents with 500 seeders and 300 leechers and received emails from people who initially stole the game but ended up buying the full product and um it's kind of interesting to see that like you know smaller developers like this are really affected by piracy you know quite a bit um
[SPEAKER_07]: It's kind of neat though.
[SPEAKER_07]: Remember they had a t-shirt for this at one time.
[SPEAKER_07]: Remember they were doing that Target thing with independent games tied in?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Too bad that never happened.
[SPEAKER_07]: It happened for like a week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, exactly.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was kind of sad.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, I get to go see it for free the night before it comes out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you?
[SPEAKER_07]: Are you going to review it for us here on the show?
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm trying to get out of it because I, as it is, I was managed to get a couple extra tickets for, um, Irene and, um, Nelly's mom, but my sister might want to go see it.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I'm going to try to see if she can go my place, but I don't think that's going to happen.
[SPEAKER_07]: So.
[SPEAKER_07]: I probably will have to see it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Kuroishi in chat says, oh yeah, and those Candy Mountain shirts.
[SPEAKER_09]: I own one of those.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_09]: I bought the Candy Mountain shirt at Hot Topic.
[SPEAKER_07]: Candy Mountain, Charlie.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh yeah, I forgot about that.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, are you going to be buying tickets to see Twilight?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm dying to know what you feel about Twilight.
[SPEAKER_04]: If somebody buys them for me.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was just curious if you were a fan or not a fan.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to read the books first.
[SPEAKER_09]: Understandable.
[SPEAKER_09]: By the way, there's a new trailer apparently for Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince that's showing before Twilight that looks pretty hot.
[SPEAKER_09]: I wouldn't be surprised.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you're a Harry Potter fan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, maybe that'll be worth going to see it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Harry Potter!
[SPEAKER_09]: And a new trailer for Star Trek is apparently in front of the new James Bond movie, which I need to go see.
[SPEAKER_09]: I love James Bond.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_07]: Have you seen the new trailer?
[SPEAKER_07]: Speaking of trailers, and since we're totally off topic right now, the new trailer for Watchmen?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I haven't seen the new trailer.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just the last one with the Smashing Pumpkins song.
[SPEAKER_07]: See, because I'm actually reading the actual graphic novel there.
[SPEAKER_07]: So a lot of the stuff that I've seen in the graphic novel, obviously I can see in the trailer.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's interesting, though, is it uses one of the songs that's in the trailer is a song that's on one of the radio stations in Grand Theft Auto 4.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's actually the trailer, the song that they used when they first teased Grand Theft Auto 4.
[SPEAKER_07]: They had their teaser trailer.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was that same song.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_09]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: Lots of good movies on the lineup for next year.
[SPEAKER_09]: A lot of anticipated movies.
[SPEAKER_09]: Of course, we had a few of them this year between The Dark Knight and everything else.
[SPEAKER_09]: Which, by the way, doesn't Dark Knight come out on Blu-ray pretty soon?
[SPEAKER_09]: And just in time for your SingStar ABBA
[SPEAKER_09]: here at the home of Roberts.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyhow, Left 4 Dead.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here's another game I've got to check out, and I've just got no freaking time left between all the Wrath of the Lich King I've been playing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Left 4 Dead apparently brings some clues to other Valve games, Team Fortress 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: Apparently, according to Kotaku, one of their readers actually was looking through the Left 4 Dead demo and found something very interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's a little cereal called Choco Bites.
[SPEAKER_09]: Team Fortress 2
[SPEAKER_09]: Apparently, though, there's only nine Team Fortress 2 classes out there right now, so a tenth one is coming soon, apparently, if this little Easter egg is to be believed.
[SPEAKER_09]: Very good catch, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: I gotta say, that's pretty impressive somebody caught that.
[SPEAKER_09]: But, uh, Valve?
[SPEAKER_09]: Valve has some pretty rabid fans, and I understand why.
[SPEAKER_09]: They are definitely masters of the first-person genre, I would say.
[SPEAKER_09]: Between Half-Life and Portal and now Left 4 Dead is generating tons of buzz.
[SPEAKER_09]: People love their Valve, don't they?
[SPEAKER_04]: They sure do, but guess what else people like?
[SPEAKER_09]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Rare.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's actually an Easter egg in Banjo-Kazooie Nuts and Bolts that says they're all in the pipeline, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: New Killer Instinct, Battletoads, and Force Gemini games, even Ghoulies 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, you'll never believe that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I ruined my own humorous tape.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: So...
[SPEAKER_09]: Xenogias
[SPEAKER_04]: as in Z-E-N-O-G-I-A-S.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: That'd be funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: That'd be funny if the people translating it weren't told about Xenogears.
[SPEAKER_07]: Kind of going back to the whole Left 4 Dead thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: They should make some other games in the whole Half-Life Valve universe including I think that they should make one based off the parody Half-Life Full Life Consequences.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you've ever seen that video it's hilarious.
[SPEAKER_07]: No I have not.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry to say.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's hilarious retarded.
[SPEAKER_09]: Good comment from chat, kind of going back a story, talking about the whole Team Fortress 2 thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Seg has an interesting thought on what that could be all about.
[SPEAKER_09]: He says, I think that the 10th is actually the announcer for an action figure.
[SPEAKER_09]: The announcer is the 10th character, and the announcer could be an action figure.
[SPEAKER_09]: So no new class, just the acknowledgement that the announcer is the 10th character.
[SPEAKER_09]: Interesting theory.
[SPEAKER_09]: An action figure?
[SPEAKER_09]: were you listening to the story?
[SPEAKER_09]: the back of the box teases collect all 10 action figures there you go I thought they were actually making action figures no but that would be kind of rad too don't you think?
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's it for the stories tonight until we get to some last minute stories, but now's the part of the show where we like to open up the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_09]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Our 800 number is toll free in the US and Canada, but if you're in Europe or somewhere far away, you might want to consider using Skype because it's going to cost you money otherwise.
[SPEAKER_09]: Meanwhile, while we wait for a call to come in, oh, never mind, we got calls coming in right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll just, we'll hold off on last minute stories for just a little bit.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_09]: This is Ake Ripper in Sweden.
[SPEAKER_09]: How are you doing Ake Ripper?
[SPEAKER_09]: What's on your mind tonight?
[SPEAKER_05]: Just ranting about Left 4 Dead.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's just completely awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: Tell us something about Left 4 Dead, because I don't think any of us in studio have actually gotten a chance to really play it yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know it's kind of on the list of things we want to do, but I know for me, I still have the Mirror's Edge demo to play too, but there's been another game taking up a lot of my time.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you haven't heard.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, plus you are, as we all know, a WoW addict.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, we know.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm like a... What can I say?
[SPEAKER_05]: Um...
[SPEAKER_05]: Old WoW addict, sort of.
[SPEAKER_09]: Recovering.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, tell us about Left 4 Dead.
[SPEAKER_09]: What makes this game so flippin' awesome?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, it is... Well, you have... You are playing like four... You have a maximum of four people.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you are to survive... Survive... Like this stomping zombie assault...
[SPEAKER_05]: That's just blow you away, really.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's so utterly good.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now, correct me if I'm wrong, even if you're playing this game by yourself, you actually have like three other people with you that are all run by artificial intelligence, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: How does that work?
[SPEAKER_09]: Is it good?
[SPEAKER_09]: I would imagine that they would be stupid.
[SPEAKER_05]: I haven't got much experience playing with bots, really, since
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, it's all about the multiplayer multiplayer experience and playing to online play.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the only thing that's interesting in my way, in my view.
[SPEAKER_09]: Toshin in our chatroom seems to think the bot AI is probably better than humans.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actdeft agrees, though, that Left 4 Dead is really all about the multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, but...
[SPEAKER_05]: I would disagree.
[SPEAKER_05]: The bots are, from my point of view, quite stupid.
[SPEAKER_05]: But then again, I'm not in one way super at shooters in a way.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's sort of weird in one way, since my take on most shooters
[SPEAKER_05]: on single-play shooters, that is, is that give me god mode, and that's it, really.
[SPEAKER_05]: But multiplayer shooters, you can't do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good for me in one way, so I get to learn to play in one way.
[SPEAKER_09]: So you can't cheat in this game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I know a lot of people are looking forward to this game, and Elise can check out the demo right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's out there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I have actually been playing the demo for a week now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: The demo was released actually last Friday to us that pre-
[SPEAKER_05]: bought it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, pre-ordered?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: I remember that this game, if I remember right, this had some of the longest lines it packs, too, the previews of this game.
[SPEAKER_09]: So a lot of people are definitely anticipating this one.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's Valve.
[SPEAKER_09]: People love their Valve.
[SPEAKER_09]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, but if you think of it, it has a, well, what is it?
[SPEAKER_05]: It was originally shown at E3 in 2007, actually.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then at some point it got
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, if you want to give us a call, 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio and we'll take a couple more calls tonight and then we've got to get to some last minute stories and get on out of here for the night if you can believe it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, let's go ahead and go to the phones.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_09]: Hello, this is Seg.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, Seg, what's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, earlier this week, Gamasutra put up an article about IP property in academia, specifically with game schools.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the thing that really got me were the comments that the president of Digipend
[SPEAKER_06]: really caught me off guard, especially coming from a president of an educational institution.
[SPEAKER_06]: Specifically, apparently the policy at DigiPen is that any intellectual property presented in the classroom is solely owned by DigiPen.
[SPEAKER_06]: At least that's the policy as I understand it.
[SPEAKER_06]: and as a graduate of a game design program but at a different institution, Emerson College, I found that really offensive to the student because it says that, I know I'm skipping over some of the details on it, but
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently, the reason that they chose to own, you know, just to decide that, oh, the school owns all the property and has all the control.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wait, wait, so just to clarify, you're saying if a student creates something for a class project, the school owns it?
[SPEAKER_09]: At DigiPen, yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the reason that he cites...
[SPEAKER_06]: is that, oh, the IP laws are so complicated, and it just makes things easier, and all this.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I felt that that's missing a very large, significant teaching moment, an opportunity.
[SPEAKER_06]: to the students by just pushing off to the side.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, at least with Emerson College, which is my personal experience, the policy is basically a quasi-shared where Emerson... I made a thesis video game called Antidote for my BFA thesis.
[SPEAKER_06]: and I own it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's mine with, I mean I can put an asterisk on the software that I used and all that but as far as Emerson College's role, I use their equipment and they have a distribution license pretty much.
[SPEAKER_06]: They can showcase it as here's what one of our students did but they don't own it.
[SPEAKER_06]: They don't own everything which allowed me the capability to do whatever I want with it.
[SPEAKER_06]: whereas students of DigiPen apparently don't have that ownership in their own thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, for example, you may know a game called Portal.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I've heard of it.
[SPEAKER_06]: You may have heard of it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was actually a few students from DigiPen who created a game called Nebacular Drop, which... I remember that.
[SPEAKER_06]: So... Oh.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, weird.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry, there was a feedback loop.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um...
[SPEAKER_06]: They made Nebacular Drop, and that was the game that got them the job at Valve.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it was sort of just like this gentleman's agreement that DigiPen wouldn't care that it's slightly similar because they got the jobs at DigiPen.
[SPEAKER_06]: But there's no guarantee that any student at DigiPen would get that affordedness.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is it possible that DigiPen does this, I mean, just theorizing here, maybe in a way to protect the students so that students aren't ripping off from each other?
[SPEAKER_09]: Like if you see something really cool that another student presents and you're like, wow, maybe I want to kind of make that game someday.
[SPEAKER_09]: Could it be a protection thing?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's sort of afforded already.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, somebody else outside of the classroom can also do that.
[SPEAKER_06]: regardless.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's my sort of test and for anyone, not just for video games but for anyone wanting to do a higher education in creative arts and even not just creative arts is just ask the question can I put my work in a creative commons license?
[SPEAKER_06]: Can I choose specifically choose to do a creative license or not?
[SPEAKER_06]: because then you have the choice of where you want to put your work and incorporating whether it be commercial or free or Creative Commons work into your work because the sort of weird thing that hasn't been addressed is because DigiPen owns this work you can't do copy left apparently I mean that's a murky area and I'm not Mr. Lawyer here but
[SPEAKER_06]: It kind of means that you can't do the Coffee Left attributions that you're supposed to do if you use a Creative Commons license thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because it's a restrictive copyright onto one particular entity that doesn't allow you to do Copy Left.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, I didn't see the story on Gamma Studio, but now I'm very curious about it, especially if there's any kind of follow-up to it, because you would think at some point this is going to be challenged.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, what if the students create something they want to make?
[SPEAKER_06]: The comments on there have been rather debated extensively.
[SPEAKER_06]: And there are other schools... I mean, the thing that gets me is that this isn't unique to the video game industry.
[SPEAKER_06]: People like to make that oppression, but it's not.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's...
[SPEAKER_06]: General creative endeavors.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, you know, I studied television and radio when I was in college.
[SPEAKER_09]: And one of the classes I was in, we had to write a script for a TV show, basically.
[SPEAKER_09]: But we essentially owned it.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_09]: It wasn't something that we would write a script and the college would own it.
[SPEAKER_09]: But at the same time, we were encouraged, if we wanted to, to write a script based on a show that was already out there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Exactly, yeah, and let's say you wrote that, I mean, if you wrote that script that was heavily lifted off of something, it would be all null and void, but then you got the plagiarism, which is already policies in any college, and that counts as a plagiarism and all that.
[SPEAKER_09]: But for some reason, you know, at our school, it kind of didn't matter, because, you know, we weren't, obviously, you weren't going to say, it was just for a school project, you know, whatever, but, you know, there were some people that were writing scripts that they planned to use someday in the real world.
[SPEAKER_09]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: and I just find it very troubling that this certain academic institution wants to not only not teach IP policy I mean those were classes that I was required I basically went to a film school and created my own little curriculum for interactive media within the new media program but
[SPEAKER_06]: There are a lot of kids who made their foundation and were able to travel off from that independently of the college because they had the capability of doing so.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it strikes me that DigiPen doesn't do that or want people to do that.
[SPEAKER_06]: It just seems that they're more centered on making people that will fit into a role in a larger company and denying the choice of having students
[SPEAKER_06]: not only form a grander knowledge of the industry and being an actual participant and professional that is aware of the industry, but just making people that fit into smaller slots.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I think that's a missed opportunity.
[SPEAKER_06]: for students, to box them in that way.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've got to read, I can't talk about this for too much longer, but I've got to read some comments from chat, because Charam has some very interesting things to say.
[SPEAKER_09]: YYR, who happens to be Aaron, who we talked to earlier in the show about Snake360, says, just to clarify, Microsoft doesn't touch your IP if you publish a game on X and A. But the flip side of the coin, they're not responsible if you get sued over IP infringement and so on.
[SPEAKER_09]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_09]: Bobby from the show before us, Bobby Blackwolf, says something else interesting here.
[SPEAKER_09]: He's done some stuff with game design.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know he's played around with X and A. You know, I really thought this was standard with game design colleges.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is the first time I've heard of a game design curriculum that didn't own your homework.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hell, the last company I worked for owned anything I created as a program even on my off hours because I was dumb and didn't contest that portion of the employment contract.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's different.
[SPEAKER_06]: First of all, that's very different.
[SPEAKER_06]: in an employment context that is extremely different.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the reason is that in an employment context, you are being paid
[SPEAKER_06]: to do this work.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that is completely different from being in an educational facility where you are paying or funding on your own, you know, scholarships or whatever, to get an education to formulate a base for you to get to an employment situation or make your own company.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's vastly different than employment.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, I mean, in the employment context, yes, you were doing work for hire.
[SPEAKER_06]: But in the educational aspect, you're not doing this work for hire.
[SPEAKER_09]: Blackwell just wants to clarify real quick.
[SPEAKER_09]: The company that he did, it was actually a defense contractor company, but they would still own the games he created on the weekend.
[SPEAKER_06]: but I guess the difference here is in a school you pay them, in a company they pay you so that's why you kind of have the different now like in California there's laws that prevent a company from having that overreach where as long as you do not use company equipment, you are not on company time and you don't use company specific knowledge the company you're employed to cannot
[SPEAKER_06]: take claim of anything you do as long as there's that separation.
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course, not every state's California.
[SPEAKER_06]: But that's also in the legal framework of you're being paid to do creative work.
[SPEAKER_06]: But in an educational environment, you're not being paid to do work.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're paying them, if anything, for a rental fee.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hate to reduce it so simply, but you're paying the institution...
[SPEAKER_06]: for that, and there's no precedence for that besides certain very few colleges making that ownership policy, which a lot of colleges don't really go that far.
[SPEAKER_06]: They may have some influence, some collusion there, but to have complete and utter ownership like that is not very common.
[SPEAKER_09]: I gotta wrap up, but thank you for bringing up a topic, especially on a night when we've been talking about moderation and kind of talking about these usage rights.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think sometimes these are things that a lot of people don't think about that goes on behind the scenes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Can I just close with one thought?
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_06]: Regardless, for anyone out there who is
[SPEAKER_06]: and others.
[SPEAKER_06]: Be aware.
[SPEAKER_06]: Be aware, this is something you should ask the admission counselor regardless of whatever field, even if it's creative or not.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is something you should be aware about before you make your decision for your higher education.
[SPEAKER_09]: Very good advice, especially considering we have a lot of people around that age that listen to this program.
[SPEAKER_09]: Seg, thanks so much for the insight.
[SPEAKER_09]: Always appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks for having me.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's always great to be on the show.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, you are most welcome.
[SPEAKER_09]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_09]: And hey, I hear there's another episode of Homestar Runner coming out very soon?
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, now.
[SPEAKER_06]: First of all, I'm only representing myself and being only myself.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_06]: But there's also that coming around the bed.
Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: Take care, everybody.
[SPEAKER_09]: You too, buddy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_09]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, if you want to give us a call, 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_09]: Probably going to do one more quick, quick call, and then we're going to call it a night.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's me, Legend of Zaku.
[SPEAKER_00]: What's up, guys?
[SPEAKER_00]: Not much.
[SPEAKER_00]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_00]: Nah, just hanging in there, just trying to, like, you know,
[SPEAKER_00]: Since I'm currently unemployed right now, because that job market is busting my balls right now, I'm just holding myself back from gaming in general.
[SPEAKER_00]: Except for the stuff that I managed to get for free.
[SPEAKER_00]: But yeah, let me see, I just found out over the weekend that Capcom, in their most infinite wisdom, quote-unquote, you know, I'm being sarcastic here, has decided to hold back, you know, the arcade releases, Street Fighter IV, effectively, you know, just saying, fuck you, we're not gonna do it, go fuck off, the arcade industry's dead.
[SPEAKER_00]: Which is pretty, I mean, I don't blame them, though.
[SPEAKER_00]: I guess I don't blame them because, you know, fighting games, especially in the arcade level, are kind of, have been relegated to a niche recently.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's not like DDR where it has that casual appeal where people can just easily jump into it without any risk.
[SPEAKER_00]: Whereas you've got fighting games that are much more difficult.
[SPEAKER_00]: They have a much higher learning curve in terms of moves and all that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Zaku, I hate to kind of throw you a curveball here, but you made a very interesting comment on the last call, the kind of ties in, because you're talking about job market, economy, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_09]: You were mentioning on kind of to say phone call here, when I worked full time as a mobile software engineer, I had to sign a typical confidentiality agreement basically stating that anything I wrote or ran on their machines became essentially theirs.
[SPEAKER_09]: In light of what's happened, what do you think about kind of everything we've been talking about?
[SPEAKER_00]: From what I actually read that story earlier this week, you know, about DigiPen basically, you know, and their policy on owning everything you pretty much submit to them, which is kind of typical.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's kind of typical for how a company operates, you know, where if you're working in software engineering, for example, or any work-for-hire stuff that you do at freelance levels, you pretty much don't own the content, the content.
[SPEAKER_00]: The creator, you know, the actual, the person who commissioned it actually does.
[SPEAKER_00]: In this case, you know, the person commissioning in a software engineering company is the company itself.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, it needs employees to actually, you know, like me as a software engineer to actually type in the code on the screen and make it work.
[SPEAKER_00]: But, you know, it does, you know, it does worry me somewhat.
[SPEAKER_00]: But then again, I don't, you know, I don't really, I can really understand why they do it just to cover their own asses.
[SPEAKER_00]: in case they want to avoid as much litigation as possible in terms of who owns the IP, the school, or the student.
[SPEAKER_00]: It basically solves a lot of problems before they even creep up.
[SPEAKER_00]: I know it's a sad reality that many people actually submit work and then realize that, oh, oh,
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh crap, I might have used a good idea and then now they're screwed because it's going to take a while to create something much better than what you already submitted because you can't use it anymore because it's someone else who owns it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Zach, I've got another kind of interesting question for you because you talking about having gotten laid off from the mobile company kind of makes me think about this.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't think I mentioned this earlier in the program, but earlier this week I was actually interviewed by the local news.
[SPEAKER_09]: They were doing a story about the Warcraft launch
[SPEAKER_09]: and they wanted to talk about how video games are like economy they're kind of economy in spite of our falling economy people were still lining up to buy this game you know and I'm using Warcraft as an example but they were kind of talking about how video games were economy they were rescission proof
[SPEAKER_09]: Recession Proof Of course, you have basically game devs that are failing left and right, shutting down, laying off people
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, it's probably because they're not taking in enough money for the games that they're selling.
[SPEAKER_00]: But on the other hand, on the consumer level, you realize that people, you know, games right now are much cheaper than any big-ticket luxury items like iPods or flat-screen TVs.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, even the used game market is still thriving right now because of the recession, because people want to play for cheap.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's why, you know, GameStop's making a killing right now with the used games that they have on the, you know,
[SPEAKER_00]: Right there in the bins.
[SPEAKER_00]: Because people want, you know, they want instant satisfaction in that sense.
[SPEAKER_00]: And some of them are willing to save up for something, you know, something like $50 or $60 for like one game, must-have game of this year.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, personally, I would pick Fallout 3 over Left 4 Dead, but that's just me.
[SPEAKER_00]: But people have their, you know...
[SPEAKER_00]: they're going to be saving up for something for that one thing they want to get this year since the economy is really going under and they're not in a position to actually spend as much as they did last year alright well Zaku we got to wrap up and let you go but any other quick last thoughts for our listeners let me see the arcade scene is not dead it's just going through it just basically got hit in the stomach it's just trying to get up right now let's hope DDR saves it again
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, Zaku, take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks for the call.
[SPEAKER_09]: And good luck on the job hunt.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks.
[SPEAKER_09]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, Loki, anybody?
[SPEAKER_09]: Last minute stories for us tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like pie.
[SPEAKER_09]: I do too.
[SPEAKER_09]: I want some pumpkin pie.
[SPEAKER_09]: Real bad.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki, any pie-licious stories for us?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I don't have pie-licious stories, but this is kind of cheesy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mmm, cheesecake?
[SPEAKER_04]: You can put cheese on apple pie.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, Uwe Boll has been... No, hold on, hold on.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's not making another movie.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, at least this is not an announcement of another movie.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's being charged with libel.
[SPEAKER_07]: and is being forced to pay a $2.1 million fine.
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently, he had badmouthed the Fantastic Films International Company, the very film distributor handling his movies, and now he lost his court case, and so he has to pay money.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oops.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hilarious.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what he gets for being a dick!
[SPEAKER_07]: and then what else was I looking up here?
[SPEAKER_07]: Not too much.
[SPEAKER_07]: Probably pornography.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, not pornography.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was looking up some old videos of the Half-Life 2 stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, Half-Life Full Life something or other.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, the same guy did some other videos called the Idiots of Gary's Mod and they're hilarious.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I also found a cam
[SPEAKER_07]: I watched it with no sound.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, well, sounds like that's going to do it for another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: We've got to wrap up.
[SPEAKER_09]: Get on out of here.
[SPEAKER_04]: In ribbons and bows?
[SPEAKER_09]: That's right, in ribbons and bows.
[SPEAKER_09]: Next week is the week before Thanksgiving, if you can believe it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Time is flying.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not allowed.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, Rob, you have to be politically correct.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the holiday.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sorry, the Harvest Festival, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: We had a discussion about this in my team meeting at work.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're like, okay, who is offended if we say Christmas?
[SPEAKER_04]: No one raised their hand.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay!
[SPEAKER_04]: We're calling it whatever we want to in this room, and then we'll call it the holiday.
[SPEAKER_04]: The appreciation.
[SPEAKER_09]: Most Jewish people I've talked to, Jewish being the biggest religion and most obvious one that doesn't do Christmas, they do Hanukkah instead, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: Most Jewish people I know are kind of used to it and don't take personal offense to it and kind of get into the whole celebration thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can't celebrate the secular holiday.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, to be perfectly honest.
[SPEAKER_09]: They get into the Hallmark side of it, but not the meaning behind it necessarily.
[SPEAKER_04]: To be perfectly honest, my own celebration is Yule.
[SPEAKER_04]: If our fireplace wasn't shit, I'd be burning a log every year.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Christmas itself, as most people know it in the Western world, is a secular holiday given a name by the Catholic Church to convert pagans because Jesus was not born in December.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was October.
[SPEAKER_09]: So Halloween is closer to Jesus' birthday?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, just curious.
[SPEAKER_04]: It'll be whenever they do the census.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, look, I don't want to get into religio chat too deep on a video game show.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I think it's funny, but that's okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: But we'll do our politically incorrect Christmas and deal with it special or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, and Actdeft refers to zombie Jesus.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe we'll do a Christmas gaming marathon or politically incorrect.
[SPEAKER_09]: Gaming marathons are the big thing right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: People playing games for hours and hours on end to raise money for charity.
[SPEAKER_09]: We need to do something like that here at Orange Lingerie.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know how or when.
[SPEAKER_04]: A play-a-thon?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, a play-a-thon.
[SPEAKER_04]: As long as it's not TDR.
[SPEAKER_09]: We need to play obscure games.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll let the users vote on what we're going to play.
[SPEAKER_04]: How about, you know what, I should catalog my collection.
[SPEAKER_04]: As long as they don't pick some of the shit that's in my collection.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I do have some shit in the collection.
[SPEAKER_04]: We should pool like 40 games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actdeft says Guardian Legend.
[SPEAKER_09]: That can be one of the games.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like every hour, play a new game and let the chatroom vote on what game we play each hour.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm totally, totally down for that.
[SPEAKER_09]: We should do something like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: It'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: And we'll call it our Christmas marathon.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who called it Jesus Ween?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyhow, we'll try to figure out that idea and bring you more on that a little later.
[SPEAKER_09]: And we can open up the studio.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've talked to my roommate about it.
[SPEAKER_09]: We can open up the studio and have people in and out of here throughout the hour and something like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyhow, we gotta wrap up.
[SPEAKER_09]: Get out of here for the night.
[SPEAKER_09]: So everybody's final thought.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki, your final thought for us tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have a headache now, too.
[SPEAKER_09]: My final thought tonight is Child's Play.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because Seg is screaming in chat room, mention Child's Play.
[SPEAKER_09]: Child's Play is on now.
[SPEAKER_09]: Mention.
[SPEAKER_09]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: Child's Play.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think DarkSakura is zombie Jesus.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just found out one of my zip drives has escaped my keychain somehow.
[SPEAKER_07]: That sucks.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hope there's not pornography in there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, that's gonna do it for tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks you guys so much for downloading our show and checking it out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, if you like what you hear, all we ask, tell a couple friends about the show.
[SPEAKER_09]: Spread the word.
[SPEAKER_09]: We really appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know...
[SPEAKER_09]: that's how Aaron from Snake360 got on this show in the first place because a friend of his told him about the show and worked out the whole interview thing with us so it just goes to show no matter where you are in the game playing spectrum whether you just play them or you write them spread the word about Orange Launch Radio because we are a community based program and if you have no friends or you're just feeling up to it because you want to really help leave us a nice review on iTunes a nice five star review on there or any of those other podcasting sites throughout the internet because it also helps us spread the word because that's all we got
[SPEAKER_09]: No fancy magazines or TV stations backing us up.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just us.
[SPEAKER_09]: And we've got to take on those big boys all ourselves.
[SPEAKER_09]: So that's going to do it for another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Next time we will see you is one week from tonight on next Sunday at allgames.com, 6 o'clock Pacific.
[SPEAKER_09]: Tune in, won't you?
[SPEAKER_09]: Or stay tuned to our podcast for more.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll see you next week.
[SPEAKER_01]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_01]: To join us for a live show, visit www.allgames.com Sunday nights at 6pm Pacific Time.
[SPEAKER_01]: The views and opinions expressed on Orange Lounge Radio do not necessarily reflect those of the entire staff of Orange Lounge Radio or allgames.com, but we're probably right anyway.
[SPEAKER_01]: See you next week!