Orange Lounge Radio
Who's your hosts? DarkSakura, Skie, and Loki
One year and one week later after Jackbox Games kickstart and release they're back to talk about doing it all over again with the Jackbox Party Pack 2
Join us to ask questions along with your comments, calls, and more which all starts right now on the show where every gamer has a voice
Orange Lounge Radio
Hello my friends out there on the internet and welcome back to another week of the show where every gamer has a voice
It is Orange Lounge Radio tonight with episode number 616 for October the 4th of 2015
My name is Rob Roberts or on Twitter I'm at Skie and I am here with you every week in Studio N7 in lovely Sacramento, CA with my co-hosts
Say hello over there to the one and only DarkSakura or Jamie Summers
Hello, how are we fighting about? Is there a cookie that we're fighting over?
No, I wish I had a cookie
I wish I had a cookie too, sorry there are no cookies to be found here
There are pumpkin chocolate chip cookies at the grocery store
Yum
I told Becky she needs to make us some
Sorry DarkSakura, our cookie is in another castle
Well fuck that cookie, I'll make a cookie
Alright, also say hello to TechMasterLoki
Hi, I'm here
Hi, you're here, how you doing?
Doing alright
Two weeks in a row of perfect attendance everybody
Let's put it on the board
Number of weeks without an absence too, there we go
I feel like I should have one of those little white tote board thingies
You know, with the changing numbers
Anyway, myself, DarkSakura, and Loki here with you all of course to talk about
Video games, gaming culture, and the gamer lifestyle
You know what, no extra guests here in studio tonight
But that's okay because we always are joined by you guys in our chat room
Over at live.vognetwork.com
Where we do tape live every Sunday night at 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern
Right after the Bobby Black Wolf show
Again that's live.vognetwork.com
And SSG100Matt in our chat room saying everyone gets a star today
And I'm assuming that is a gold star there in the chat room
Appreciate it
I don't recognize any other type of star
That's right, you don't ever see people handing out silver stars
It's like
Here's your bronze star
You know what, what if I like the color green?
Do I get a green star? Like how does that work?
We're orange lounge radio, should we have orange stars?
Come on people, think outside the gold box
Alright, no I'm kidding
We appreciate all the gold stars
Raginator in chat, I love this one
Says, two, two weeks without absence
Ah, ah, ah
That's a good quote
Raginator made a funny joke
Oh my god, this is going to be an amazing show tonight you guys
I'm so excited
Seattle chat says warp star
I like that
Although Starboard Power Coupling is on Thursday nights on the network
Anyway
We're here to talk about video games
And we actually do have a guest that's going to be joining us via the Skype line
In about 15 minutes here live with us
And we're really excited to welcome back to the show this week
Jackbox Games
And Steve-o is going to be joining us this week from Jackbox Games
To talk all about the Jackbox Party Pack Part 2
And we are very excited to talk about this upcoming release
Because I don't know if y'all played Part 1
But that was a lot of fun
And you know
In the interest of transparency
We here at OLR
We've made it no secret that we kind of
Alright sometimes we're a little partial to Jackbox Games
And it's not just because they'll come on the show
But I grew up loving those things like You Don't Know Jack
And you know the things that Berkley Systems used to do back in the day
Which you know if you trace their history
You know basically went from one company to another
Acrophobia and all this stuff
So I'm really happy to have them on the show
Talk about what they're doing these days
Because I really feel like they've kind of had a renaissance of sorts
In the past couple years
With the relaunch of You Don't Know Jack
And all these other things that they're doing online
So we'll be talking to them live
And if you want to join us in our chat room
Over at live.vognetwork.com
You can actually ask questions along with the interview
It's interactive like that
Very excited about that
Meanwhile though we are going to get to a kickoff topic here in studio
Because we do of course talk about
What's going on in gaming and gaming culture every week
Here at Orange Launch Radio
And tonight's kickoff topic
I want to talk about
A little bit of a real life experience
That I had today
And I want to get Dark Soccer and Loki's opinion on this
As well as you guys in our chat room
And today I went shopping
Which you know
Everybody goes shopping once in a while right
But today I went shopping to a lot of different places
Because my buddy Shane
Who calls into the show quite often
Who you know was a guest on Horde House
I'm sure a lot of you know him by now
Shane has this fascination
Shall we say with Power Rangers dolls
Which you know I get it
Everybody's got their thing right
You know what if you collect amiibo
You have no right to talk
To talk down to Shane about what he's collecting
So he loves his Power Rangers things
And he actually like
He does that thing where he kind of tracks
Like the different stores and what they're getting
And I think there's like a forum that he's posting to
So long story short
We had to go to like Target
Over on this side of town
And the Walmart over here
And Best Buy
All to look for basically Power Rangers dolls
And amiibo
Which was something that I was looking for
Because you know they've had the recent reprinting
Of some of the hard to get amiibo
So I was looking for some of that
At these different stores
Well the reason why I bring up going shopping
To all these different stores is
I'm really noticing
And I feel like we've talked about this on the show
A couple years ago
When this was first starting to take place
But now that we've had new games come out
Like Lego Dimensions last week
Shelf space being made for Guitar Hero
Skylanders
Amiibo
I am really feeling the toy-splosion
That's happening in the video game world
And I mean
When I was at Toys R Us
I'm telling you
Like one whole wall
Dedicated to the Lego Dimensions
And because you know what the Lego Dimensions is
It's the starter pack
But it's not just the starter
It's starter pack for Wii U
Starter pack for Xbox 360
For the one
For the PlayStation 4
And then it's level packs
Like you know
Portal 2
Back to the Future
Simpsons
Fun packs
Which is like more vehicles
Fun packs which are like characters
And then they have like
Team packs
Or something like that
Which are a few characters
Yeah
And then
Okay so
That's just Lego Dimensions
Now add to that
The fact that Skylanders has a new game this year
Everybody's going fucking nuts over Amiibo
Guitar Hero and Rock Band are now making a space
Which I
I know that isn't really toys
But it's still that odd peripheral space
That everybody said was dead
Cause remember this show goes back to
Dance Dance Revolution right
So when we started this show
Cause if you didn't know
Myself, Loki, Dark Sakura
We all met playing Dance Dance Revolution
And look at me now
You would never have noticed that
You would know that Loki has a strange affinity
For Eurodance music but
It is true
But anyway
Some of it I mean
Some of it
But anyway
You know at that point
I remember we would have conversations about
DDR saved peripherals
Peripherals were a joke
In gaming for the longest time in the 90s right
Because
What do we love to quote from the wizard
The power glove
It's so bad right
Cause it really was bad
Did you guys play with the power glove?
It was bad
And smelled funny
Yeah it did kind of smell funny
And then the U-Force
It didn't
Remember the magazine ads for the U-Force
Making it look like you would actually be playing pun
It didn't fucking work like that
It did not
Work like that whatsoever
The power pad
They made what like two games for the power pad
And that was okay
So it's like
Peripherals were kind of in this weird dead place
Where they didn't really make them
During the Super Nintendo era
Yes
I love the Super Scope
I know the Super Scope
But like what there was like one Super Scope game
Maybe I think there was a second more obscure one
I mean like there were not a lot of games
Well Super Scope 6 and then of course
The robot game
Cause really those are the only two games that you needed
Still what a weird ass
I mean think about it
Battle Clash
What a weird ass concept
That the Super Scope was to begin with
Who had the idea to put a fucking bazooka
Like
Hey we need a zapper gun
But that's too small
Let's have a bazooka
I'm not knocking
That peripheral
Because it was awesome
But I'm just saying
It was really weird
When you kind of go back and think about it
Why couldn't we just do the zapper again?
No?
Bazooka?
I don't know
But anyway
So all these peripherals come and go
But now it seems like
I don't even know if it's a renaissance
Or if it's just the fact that
Disney and Lego
Which are huge entertainment companies
And toy makers are now seeing these big dollar signs
Thanks to what Activision did with Skylanders
So now they're flooding with all this
But what is up with the toy splosion?
And how does this make you feel
When you go to the video game section
At let's say Toys R Us or Target
And over half
Excuse me
Over half of it
I mean
And that's not
Look at the square footage
Video games themselves
Don't take up much space
And a lot of that is shifting digital
And that might be part of this as well
But over half that shelf space
Are the toys
And the peripherals
And things that we
Like ten years ago
You could not have guessed that this was going to happen
You could not have guessed
And that's pretty nice for
Companies like GameStop
That are fearing that it's going to go all digital
Because it's not
There's no way they can
If they have all this crap that they have to sell
So
I don't know
So far
Prior to this year
It was pretty easy for me to avoid all that stuff
Because I'm like
Fuck that
I'm not really going to invest in Disney Infinity
Or
Skylars
Because just Skylars
I don't really give a shit about that
Disney Infinity
It was expensive
I tried it a little bit
And then just kind of like
It's not my age demographic
But then again
There's the Lego game
And I
That might be my Achilles heel right there
The thing about that Lego game for me
And I finally took the plunge
And I bought that Lego Dimensions
It is the tie-ins that they're tying in with
Are so random
But awesome
Like Portal 2
Simpsons
That Midway arcade thing
Ghostbusters
Back to the Future
That's the thing
Doctor Who
That's what finally sold me on it
Is that it wasn't just Disney movies
Or this made up universe
Which Skylanders is
But it was like
Really awesome things
Like all in kind of a giant blender
What do you think of all this
Dark Soccer?
I mean
You kind of used to collect this stuff
The Dreamcast game with a dish
Hello?
Well
But I was also
I was super into Cardcaptor Sakura
When I got that
And I came really close to getting the Sakura Taisen one as well
But you know
I had this big thing for collector's editions
Like back when we had a bunch more disposable income
Now we've got the income for it
But it's not so disposable
If that makes sense
Sure
And Dan and I were looking at it
And we're like
Well you know what
We could get this
And spend
$150
Or I could get Animal Crossing Happy Home Designer
For $50
And you ended up with Animal Crossing
Well there was that
We were actually going to get the Wii U Pro Controller
And then we looked at Lego Dimensions
And then did the math on it
And I ended up getting a game
With the Amiibo reader
The Amiibo card reader
Because I need all of the Animal Crossing cards
And that's more important
Which is funny
For me personally
And I'm not slamming your decision
But for me personally
I have zero interest in that Happy Home Designer thing
Yeah
I have no interest in it
But that's cool
How much of the last Animal Crossing game did I play?
Yeah I know
You played a lot of it
You played a lot more than I did
That's for sure
And now I get to design everyone's freaking homes
And they better love me for it
Let me go to the chat room
Which is lighten up over at live.vognetwork.com
Kaijuto in chat says suckers
And they mash all that stuff in
To sucker you to buy a cheap mediocre game
And Bobby Blackwolf defending his actions
Saying I'm a sucker
But I am having too much fun being a sucker
You know I gotta say though
And I really truly feel this way
Like I enjoy Legos anyway
So the fact that they kind of made a game around it
Their games are pretty good though
Like I wasn't like Lego Marvel
I was like yeah Lego games are pretty good
You know and they're pretty good
But I
It's just they're good I don't know
I really truly love the Amiibo figures themselves
Like and I know I've gone on rants about Amiibo
And that's all about the distribution
And now that that's finally calming its tits a little bit
And it's getting a little easier to find
You know some of the things you want
Especially if you're willing to pay just like
Four or five more bucks to get it from a Japanese import
Which is totally easy
You know I'm getting those figures a lot easier
And I gotta say I really just as a nerd
Who was raised on the Legend of Zelda and Mario Brothers
I just love those little figures
And if they didn't do anything with the game
I would be kind of okay with that
Because let's be real they don't do that much
Like Amiibos aren't
I mean it's cool that they have a little extra
And it's usually just something
Just a little extra something like a Mario Maker
And one extra little costume
Mario Kart and an extra costume
I'm not buying those figures for the costume
I thought that for Splatoon I'm like
Oh maybe I've got this you know Bowser
I'm gonna try using this
Oh sorry that only works with the Splatoon Amiibos
I'm like well then why would I buy those?
That's stupid
Wat meme in our chat room
Wat says
I'm holding out for the Montgomery Ward exclusive
One could only hope
That a store like Montgomery Ward
Where I believe
What was it we bought at Montgomery Ward
I think my Super Nintendo came from Montgomery Ward
I bought Killer Instinct there
Did you?
I believe that is where my mom bought my Super Nintendo
For Christmas was at a Montgomery Ward
Which has been leveled many years ago
And became a target
I believe the sales person said
Oh yeah our biggest selling game
On Super Nintendo right now is Drakken
And then my mom bought Drakken
Which I was like
What the hell is this game
When I played it
Well I mean luckily that was the packing game
And I played that like ten times more
But then
Wasn't it nice to have packing games all the time
Yeah remember those days
Then I went back to Drakken like a year after I had the Super Nintendo
And I was like what the fuck was I missing
This game was awesome
Then they did a sequel, Dragon's View
That game was tight
That game was awesome
So thank you Montgomery Ward salesman
For introducing me to a game I probably would have
Never figured out otherwise
Cialan Chat says
I want the Samus amiibos
Just to let Nintendo know
That the series still needs love
Raginator in chat over at
Live.vognetwork.com says
Seeing as I am a diehard
Magic player, the actual collectible card game
Back in the day, I can't say
Shit about Skylanders, amiibo
And so forth, you know that's a good comparison
Is that there's always
Been a space for collectibles
Even in the gaming world
Right, I mean board game
People right, aren't there usually like
Several editions of a game
Or even a game like
What Dominion has all these
Like it seems like there's like fifty different
Probably I'm exaggerating but like
All these different booster packs and things like that
For that game, or hell Cards Against Humanity
Right, how many people
Are like oh, if you go to PAX East
You gotta get me the exclusive cards
For my Cards Against Humanity game
Because they add something to the game
Whereas amiibos just add like a
Costume to the game and it doesn't really matter
It's just kind of an excuse
To sell DLC
But more expensive and it's
Less valuable
So like if someone tried to say hey
I'll tell you what
You know Mario Kart, do you want a really cool
Koopa hat, that's gonna be
Twelve dollars
You'd probably say fuck you, I am not buying that
But since they're selling it with a statue
Sure
We'll do that
And maybe I'll get to use it
In another game someday
Maybe, maybe
Alright, well we're
Going to get to our interview here shortly but
Before we get into our gaming weeks real quick
We'll at least probably get Dark Soccer's out here
And then we'll move into
Our interview tonight, so
Dark Soccer, how was your gaming week?
We always like to start off the show after our kickoff topic
Talking about our gaming weeks
Kinda busy, yeah
I of course played Dragon Age Inquisition
I
What else, I got
Animal Crossing Happy Home Designer
Although I haven't had a chance to start it yet
What else
Oh yeah, we got our Wii U
Which you know we
Like a whole lot and we borrowed
Super Mario 3D World
And Dan and I started that together
Cause you know we can play co-op and
You know we fussed each other for you know
Knocking each other
Into enemies and what not, it was still pretty fun
And
Something else but I don't remember so
I'll just say that's it
Alright, Loki
How was your gaming week?
I did play a lot of stuff
I started off trying out Ingress
So I've been playing that
I'm so proud
I'm so happy
So I'm level 3 now in Ingress cause I captured
Two portals today and
It's basically just kind of
It's kind of gaming in that
Space between other things
I guess if that makes sense
Just taking my kids to the park
Instead of just sitting there
Bored while I'm pushing them on the swing
I can hack a portal and push them
On the swing, it's multitasking
It's like foursquare really
That's why I always kind of like you know we always
Just check in, we go places, it's kind of like that
Except now you can kind of, you can literally like
Piss on something for your team
And be like it's mine
I claim this in the name of Spain
I don't know if like I'd be going down like to
Oh I gotta go to some event or something in San Francisco
Or something, I don't know if I'd do that but you know
I don't know, it's something to do
While I'm waiting for things
I guess if that makes sense
So I don't know
And then let's see what other
Brief thing can I get into
Played a little bit of Lego Marvel Super Heroes
Because my son is still playing that
I think he's like 220 hours now
In that game
It's like you were with Minecraft at one point
I think he spent
More time in that game
So I'm looking forward to getting whatever the next
Lego Avengers
I love this comment from Bobby Blackwolf in chat
Loki gets a Wii U and then starts playing Ingress
That's great
I can't play Ingress at home
So it's just when I'm out
Ingress is an outdoor game
It is
And it got me to go walking one lunch
See that's what the game does to you
It's crazy
But anyway, I don't want to turn this into an Ingress show
Somebody suggested that I do one
I'm still thinking about it
Super Mario Maker
I made a level called
Jigsaw's Castle of Carnage
And no one has passed it
Except for me
It's incredibly hard
I know Bobby was talking about this on his show
Earlier tonight
All the levels are just torture porn
And I don't mean that
In a Jigsaw movie kind of way
It's all just
Everybody wanting to be asshole Mario
It's not asshole Mario
I have hidden blocks
It's not trolling you
It's just genuinely difficult
I guess
It's not incredible
I passed it after about 50 tries
It's just torture
There's a mistake in it too
I accidentally missed one of the pits
It has a block covering
I'm like ah shit
I gotta fix this and pass the game again
If I want to edit it
That's staying there
I played Splatoon
And I actually figured out how to play that finally
And enjoying it now that I have the paint roller
At this point though I can't use my other Amiibo stuff
For unlocking costumes
Still trying to figure out what I'm using that for
I think that's about it
That's about it for your gaming week huh?
We are actually going to go to
Our interview because it's about 6.30
So we are going to actually give
Steve-O a call
With Jackbox Games
And he is actually the editorial director
Over at Jackbox and tonight
We are going to be talking about the Jackbox Party Pack
Part 2 and I'm really excited
To welcome to the show Steve-O
Are you there Steve?
I am can you hear me?
We can hear you just fine welcome to Orange Launch Radio
Thank you for having me on
Thank you so much for being here
I don't know if you heard earlier in the show
We admit that we are a little partial
To Jackbox Games
Just because you guys come on the show
Just because I love
Game Show Games
I was talking about this with Mike last time we were here
When he was here
I don't want to necessarily repeat the conversation
I was so bummed when 1 vs 100
Went off of Xbox Live
I feel like you guys are making games
That help fill that gap if that makes sense
Oh yeah definitely
In fact as we
We are constantly trying to come up with
New ideas for games
The 1 vs 100 idea
Something that really keeps coming up with us
Something like that
That we might try to do someday
That is very similar to that but not that obviously
We wouldn't steal the idea
No you would never steal it
No no
Because you can play our games
On streams and there are hundreds of people watching
Since your phone is your controller
You can have a lot of people playing
I wouldn't be surprised
If we make something like the 1 vs 100
Kind of style of game sometimes
Inspired by
We'll say inspired
How has that streaming
Thing been going
Because I noticed
You guys noticed early on
With some of your earlier fibage
And some of the games you put out
During this renaissance period
Ever since the newer You Don't Know Jack games
You guys are putting out more things
On the networks
I noticed that the streaming
Has really been a big part
For you guys
So much so that I noticed in Quiplash
It seemed like you made some decisions
In the game such as enabling streaming mode
And doing these things that
Kind of catered towards live streamers
Have you been surprised that that has been
Such a huge part of the games?
Absolutely, in fact
We knew it was the thing
But we didn't realize with our games
How popular it would become
When we first did the first fibage
That's when we noticed
We saw people playing
They were giving comments
It would be great if the host had
A little bit more control over certain things
Such as
Well
There were things like time issues
People are playing on a stream
And they're not really live
15 seconds delayed because of the stream
How does that work?
Are they still seeing all the information they need
On their phone or on their controller
In case they can't see
They're not synced up with what's on the screen
We had an issue
At the beginning where
Any of the people
Who had logged in to play the game
Could actually hit the start button and start the game
So people
Out in the world were pressing
Start and not everybody had gotten in yet
So we sort of tailored that to be
Only the first person to log in
That would be the host or whoever is running the stream
Only the person who is running the stream
Can push the start button now
Stuff like that that we heard feedback on
And now we're really starting to integrate
Damn those trolls
It made the game even better
Even trolls can teach you a thing or two sometimes
Even though we shouldn't admit that
I noticed some of your games
Are tailored now to more and more people
For example
A lice water went up to 100 people
And I'm noticing in one of these games
That's in the Jackbox Party Pack
Bomb Corps
How many people can participate
Not necessarily play but participate
In Bomb Corps, tell us about that
Because that seems like it has to be done
With a streaming audience in mind
Because I know I can't hold 10,000 people in my living room
Well actually
There's a couple of games
In the Party Pack
The Party Pack 2
That we've integrated this
Audience feature
And so what the audience feature is
Is sort of like
You're not actually a player in the game
But you are participating in some way
So for instance in Quiplash
The audience
There's 8 core players
Up to 8 core players
But as many as 10,000 people can join
Because they can vote on their favorite answers
And actually affect the outcome of the game
So
We have games
Like lice water
Goes up to actually 100 players
That could actually play it
As a player
But now we're starting to find
This other little area which is called the audience
Where it's sort of like a
It's like partial participation in the game
While you're viewing it
And when you're
When you're not like a full time player in the game
You know our servers
The way our architecture is sort of set up
We can sort of support more of a
Semi player if you will
So the people who are watching on streams
Aren't just passively watching our games now
We can get 10,000 people in
And actually have some sort of effect on the game
It is this really fascinating
Trend I'm seeing with games
Not just from you guys
But I was at TwitchCon for a little bit
And I was talking about that on the show last week
And I know you guys were there too
I noticed there were actually games being made
With Twitch in mind
And there was this one game being shown
Where they could add obstacles and things
And I remember in the Tomb Raider collection
That was one of the earliest ones I remember
That would really affect things
It sounds like you guys are kind of taking that as well
Where you're playing with the world
And they can impact the game
I mean how is
How was TwitchCon for you guys
And all that?
I wasn't out there
We were out there
My coworkers were out there
And yeah it's definitely
And the Twitch folks
Are very interested in what we're doing too
So they're being very
Open to sort of
Helping us get our stuff
Optimized for
Twitch
So I think we have a good working relationship
With them that's kind of building right now
But I was out at PAX Prime
Not too long ago
And we actually did a
Talk with the folks
Who do iDAR
I don't know if you're familiar with that
It's a game where audience participation is there
People are
Sending hashtags through Twitter
And they're sort of
Adding bombs and all sorts of things
To the game
The way we do it is a little bit different
You're either voting on a winner
Or you're playing along with the questions
The trivia questions
There's a lot of different ways
Integrating this sort of concept
Of like hey people are
Enjoying just watching games
Wouldn't it be cool if we could actually give them
A little bit of participation too
Let's talk a little more about some of the games
That are going to be in the Jackbox Party Pack
In case you guys have missed it
Or out there listening
I know on your blog and through your various
Social media streams which also includes
A live stream, you guys do your own live streams
On Fridays right?
2 o'clock central on Fridays, tune in
There you go, you can play along with people
Who make the games
You have 5 games that you've announced on your blog
That are going to be included in this game
Fibbage 2, Earwax,
Idiots, which I love that name
Quiplash XL and
Bomb Core
Now I got to ask a tough question
That I think a lot of folks are going to be thinking
And I got to ask it
Why did you pass on a You Don't Know Jack game
For this collection? I was a little surprised to see that
Well, you know
We're not killing
You Don't Know Jack
Oh yeah
I just noticed
It was passed on for this
So I was just kind of surprised
Because I was expecting that to be a game
Not that I'm disappointed
One of the things
What we learned when we were watching
People play the Jackbox
Party Pack 1, the original
Was that the games like
Fibbage and Drawfold
Were super streamable
And that's what we were
Kind of, a lot of the games that we were trying
To make for this version were
Sort of tailored a little bit more toward that
And while You Don't Know Jack is streamable
For sure
It's limited to four players
And it's really hard
With the timing of the questions
The way the game is kind of set up now
To really get an audience that's on a 15 second
Delay kind of involved in it
So the games that we saw
That were really big hits from the
Jackbox Party Pack 1
Like Fibbage, like Drawfold
We saw that those were games that people were
You know, they were able to
Create their own sort of content
On their phone slash controller device
And Fibbage, it's your entering
Lies, in Drawfold
You're drawing things that are funny
So we kind of tried to go
A little bit more in that direction with this
Party Pack 2
And so, you know, like I said
You Don't Know Jack is not dead
The five games in this pack
I think people are going to enjoy
From the perspective of
They're great party games
They're great for your controller
They're great for streams, or your phone is a controller
They're great for streams
And I think when we do You Don't Know Jack again
We'll definitely try to
Make some changes that make it a little bit more
Fitting with the kind of way we're doing things now
Okay, you know what, now I'm glad I asked
That question because what you're saying is making a lot of sense
See, I thought you might be being that
Band coming out on stage not wanting to play
Their hit single, I thought maybe that was what was
Going on, but no, I'm glad I asked that because what you say
There makes a lot of sense, you're right
The streams are more of that party
Streaming thing, whereas You Don't Know Jack, the timing is so important
That makes a lot of sense
Although if you throw your bras and panties
Up on stage, we might
Go ahead and make one
Well, if you insist
Alright, anyway
Loki, get on that
I hope you take like, you know
X-Men Underoos or something
Take? That would
That would complete my collection
Awesome
See why we like having them on the show
Alright, let's talk about some of these games that are in the Party Pack
I want to start with Bomb Corps
Because to me, when I looked at Bomb Corps
I was like, alright, this looks really different
For Jackbox, but I'm like
I'm here for this, this is the kind of retro
Looking thing, tell us a little more about
Bomb Corps and where this idea came from
And how it fits into the pack
Yeah, so, you know, what we wanted to do
Was like, since you use
Your phones as controllers
Or your tablet or your laptop
We have this ability to send secret information
So that's something that doesn't
You know, you don't get on a
When you're using just a standard game controller
So everybody, the fact that everybody could get
You know, sort of secret information that not everybody else had
We tried to
We were coming up with ideas that would
You know, really play to that
So with Bomb Corps
It's funny that you say Bomb Corps
Because we went back and forth on this
Is it, like, when it's
C-O-R-P period, is it corp?
Or corp, Bomb Corp?
We don't even know, we're going with corp
But you can call it corp if you want
I don't know, but then I also think
An actual, like, core of the bomb
I don't know, I thought maybe it was a double entendre
Because I notice you guys like puns
No, I thought that might
I thought that might have been the thing, but alright
Yeah, no, but anyway
I got, yes, so
The idea kind of came from this idea of
You know, how can we
Leverage this idea of, like, everybody
Has different information, so in Bomb Corp
You get, each
Player gets a little bit of information as to how
To diffuse a bomb
If the timer's ticking down
And you kind of have to do a co-op
Work together to diffuse the bomb
So, you know, I might say
You might say, oh, I've got rule number one
You know, don't cut any red wires
Unless they're next to white wires
And then the second person has a different rule and says
Don't cut anything about red wire, you know
So, or, only player three
Can cut wires, so it's
It starts off a little simple
And then it gets really, really complicated
Or really not complicated, it gets more challenging
There you go
Now, I'm just thinking, though, if I were the
I mean, you're gonna have those Lokis
Or the assholes of the party who lie about the direction
I don't do that
Well, you know what
Fine, we all know it's Jamie that does that
Who would say, oh, I made a mistake
It's Irene that would do that
That's true, Irene
Oh, come on, I'm the person in Maniac Mansion
Who just gets sick of the game, goes and blows up everything
Yeah, maybe
I pushed the red button in the pool
It's always Irene that's drawing the penis
In those games, it's all
It's like, okay, hmm, yeah, I wonder who did that
It's always Irene
Well, some of our games actually call for drawing up penises
So that's good
I think I actually saw on your Twitter account
Somebody lucked out and got the room code
D-N-I-S or something like that
It cracked me up
Yeah, you know, we actually go through
We actually go through an exhaustive process
Every time, it's like, what do we need to add
To this list that's not gonna get us in trouble
You know, and so
There's like an hour every time
We put out a game, it's like, alright, here's the
Existing list, is there anything else we've missed
You know, there's always something
You know, V-U-V-A
Bulba or something, I don't know
There's always something that we're like, well
That's okay, we'll leave it or we take it out
Are you telling me that Jackbox Games
Has a list of four letter words that goes around
The office, hey, if anybody can think of
Another four letter word that's not on the list
It's an hour long brainstorm
Every product, yeah
Let Steve and HR know by five o'clock Friday
Yeah
I mean, you know, mostly you're trying to get
The sort of, the really bad, like racist stuff
Anything that could be a derogatory term
Out of there, but then there's always one
That comes up and you're like, how did we
Miss that, like the penis one you just said
So
Alright, anyway
But the point, I was gonna say about BombCorp
If you, you know
The thing is, if you decide to blow everything up
And you decide not to play along, we think that
The moment where everyone blows up is pretty
Funny anyway and never gets old, so there you go
It's the Magroober experience
It is the Magroober kind of thing, yeah
And I'm gonna say that from now on
When I say the BombCorp
I'm gonna just say it that way when I'm plugging it
Right here on this show
Let's talk about some of the other newer games
I'm familiar with Fibbage and Quiplash
Although I'm sure there's lots of new features
We'll go back to those if we have time
By the way, if you guys have questions for Steve
Please, by all means, ask away in our chatroom over at
Live.vognetwork.com
I wanna talk about some of these other newer games that are in it
Earwax, we were joking around
On the show last week because we thought this was a pretty
Funny concept, so this is a game all around
Sound effects
And you just string sound effects
It's like charades but with sound effects
Tell us more about Earwax
Okay, yeah, so that was one of the things
When we started with Party Pack 2
We really wanted to get a game with sound effects
Because we had
Fibbage where you're typing in answers
And Quiplash 2 and we had Drawful where you were drawing
Things and we were like, what else can we do?
Well, we could submit sounds
And so we
Tried a whole bunch of different ways of
Doing it and what ended up being really the funniest
To us was this idea of
You get a prompt and it's
The prompt could be like
Retirement home
Love affair or something like that
Please God no
And then you have a car
A handful of sound effects
When I say a handful of sound effects on your phone
Or your tablet, you'll have a list
Of sound effects that are kind of like the cards in your hand
And you don't hear them
Necessarily, you just see the description of them
And you kind of are trying to put
Together a one-two punch
Two sound effects back to back
That best fit
That prompt that you got
So everyone submits their two sounds
And then you go through
A reveal to hear everyone's sounds
Back to back and it's usually pretty funny
And then there's a judge for each round
The judge is actually the person
Who picks the card in the first place
Old folks, retirement home, love affair, whatever
And then the person who's the judge
Gets to pick which one they like the best
That sounds
What's most interesting
About that to me is
Who's the person at the office that had to compile
All those sound effects
They've got a dream job, I'm telling you
Right, well Andy Poland is our
You know, our audio music guru
And I will say
That many, many of those sound effects
Obviously, we already had in our big giant
Database of sound effects that we use for all our games
But with the help of
Some interns
By the way, in BombCorp
You are an intern
Working at BombCorp
So we got to have a lot of fun with our interns
Our actual interns
During the summer
But anyway, I'm going off on a tangent
We had interns help us organize
The sound effects, but it's all Andy
When you hear a nice long fart sound effect
Andy Poland made that at some point
In his bathroom or near his bathroom
Oh my god
That's amazing, I love that
You passed it on to the interns too
Fantastic
Let's talk a little bit about Bidiots
Which is my favorite name of any game there
And I'm sure you guys must all have to
Brainstorm these names for the games as well
And somehow
Some genius comes up with this
But let's talk about Bidiots
So actually what you're drawing on your phone
And then the other players bid
On the art, like what is valuable
Or funniest, or how does that work?
Yeah, so
You're given
Kind of like our game Drawful
You're given a prompt
And you draw
This thing as best you can
And it's probably not going to be that
Your drawing's not going to be that great
But you get two drawings
And you draw two drawings within a minute and a half or so
And then you submit them
And they become pieces of art in this art auction
And then once you've submitted all your art
And everyone's submitted all their drawings
Everyone becomes a bidder at this auction
So it becomes much more
Of a fast paced
You know, just like you're at a real auction
And you get some secret information
On your phone
Or on your device, whatever controller you're using
That tells you
Certain things are worth a certain amount of money
There's a little bit of vagary there
So you kind of
Have an idea of what some things might be worth
And what they might not
And the other thing is
It might say, well, the drawing of
Bananas
Bananas playing volleyball
Or whatever
Might be worth a lot
Or might be worth
$3,200
And then you see an image up on screen
And it looks like it might be bananas
And it looks like there might be a ball
And the thing is
Obviously, for the purposes of the game
We've given everybody very similar drawings
So, you know
You may be thinking that this is a very valuable
Bananas playing volleyball
When in fact it's bananas
Doing the limbo or something like that
And it was only worth $900
So the idea is that you're bidding
You're trying to guess what each thing's worth
And then at the end of the game
However much money you have left
Plus the profit you've made on
Basically what the art pieces
Were valued at
Minus what you paid for them
That's the profit you make off of
And so at the end of the game you're trying to have the most profit
Awesome. Well, these games sound like a lot of fun
I love that, you know, it could have been tempting
To probably just make
Sequels to everything
In Party Pack 1
And I'm sure that would have been a lot of fun too
And you do have sequels, essentially, to fun games
But you have a little bit of that but mixed with these new ideas
And I think that sounds like it's going to be
A lot of fun. I'm looking forward to playing it myself
I want to get to some of the questions
In our chatroom over at
live.vognetwork.com
You know, we're a little bit delayed here
So we're just now getting a question on the sound effect thing
And we have a question from Matt in our chatroom
So when someone actually farts in the office
Do you all just blame it on Andy?
Like the dog, since Andy's the sound guy
We actually
Well, no, I'll tell you why
Because Andy, we're in Chicago
And Andy is actually in Michigan
So we have him
On an iPad
On a robotic
You might have seen
These things, but it's like
A stand with a wheel
And it's got his face on it
So he comes to meetings
And he moves around the office
It's like a robot
So to answer that specific question
No, we would not expect
It would have been Andy that farted
Because he's a state away
He's on his segue
But we do have
A lot of us have sound effects
At the ready at our desks
To play at any moment during the day
That's amazing
Of course, I know actually a lot of companies
The working remotely
And all that is being more and more a thing
So I'm not surprised to hear that at all
Let's see, Tigerclaw in our chatroom
Over at live.vognetwork.com saying
It must be a challenge to come up with all
The trivia in the game
Considering those questions get outdated
Faster after people play through it
Multiple times
Sure, that's a risk
That just means people are enjoying your game too much
That they wore out all the questions
So let's come up with new questions
For these games
Quiplash, the first version
Was out just a few months ago
And now here we are coming up on
Quiplash XL
Where do all these prompts come from?
How do you do it?
Well, thank you
We have a great staff
Of writers that we have on staff
It's a little bit different for each game
Quiplash
The prompts are
The challenge with those is not
Having too many that are similar
To each other
Because in Quiplash XL we have a thousand
Prompts
You're going to be hard pressed
To get through all of them
And some of those are from the original
Quiplash
We've added on to the original
So the challenge there is
Man, we've already
Asked about
What
Pat Sajak's
Breath smells like
Before
So we can't do what
Alex Trebek's breath smells like
So you get a lot of that kind of thing
So that's the challenge there
Those are a little bit easier to come up with
Because they're not based on facts
Now if you talk about something like Fibbage
Those are all sort of wacky
News of the weird
Kind of things
So you're kind of beholden to
Criminals and people out there
Just continuing to do stupid things
And getting in the news
Which luckily they do
So that's kind of
With Fibbage it's sort of like you're constantly
Scouring the daily news
Updates to see what
Stupid person has done another stupid thing
Or has created some
Completely useless
House made out of whatever
Florida Man
Yeah, Florida Man
Was everywhere on Facebook this week
Of the guy who lit his gas tank on fire
Trying to kill a spider
Oh yes, exactly
And in fact those things go around the office
And they're sent out and they're like
Fibbage 3, here's stuff
For Fibbage 3
You guys must have so much fun
At the office passing all this stuff around
I mean, it must be just kind of like
Being a part of the game all day
That's amazing
Yeah it's interesting and the thing is
When you're doing something like a party pack
You've got
Five mini teams
Out of a small group of people
So some people aren't
Even working on certain games
So you might be working on
Two or three and somebody else might be working on
Two or three, you might overlap on one
But we keep a constant
Slack thread going at work
So everybody kind of
Gets a little bit of insight into what's going on
In all the other games, even if they're not on the team
You kind of still feel a part of it
So I think that's a really cool thing about where we work
Alright, let me get one more question here and then we'll
Wrap up because I know we've had you on for
Way longer than we usually say
It's going to be 15, 20
Watmeme is in our chat
And I have a feeling he might know this is a loaded question
So this might be a good one to ask here
Watmeme in chat says, ask Steve-O
What would be his dream version of
You Don't Know Jack?
I think I know who that is, but I'm not going to out him
I have a feeling I know who it is too
But that's okay, I know this is a loaded question
So please answer
Well the fact that he called me Steve-O
The only people who call me Steve-O
Are the people who work at Jackbox
Because when I first started
At the company back when it was Jellyvision
There were like five Steves
So they had to give every Steve a little slightly different thing
And I got lucky, I got Steve-O
There were some really weird ones
So everywhere else I'm just Steve
At Jackbox, I'm Steve-O
So I know this is somebody who either
Been watching our streams or works anyway
I'm also going to say
Without telling people your full name
Your last name is not O
So it's not like they just used the last initial
Right, there's not even an O in it
Yeah, exactly
Yeah, no
My dream version of You Don't Know Jack
You know, it's kind of hard to
Put my, you know, we did the TV show
Did you know we did a TV show of You Don't Know Jack?
Yeah, I did, I was probably, I think I was the one guy
That watched it
Oh, you were him?
Oh, thank you
I was it with Paul Reubens, how could you not?
Because that was, was that before or after
The infamous, I think that was after
It was after, he was like resurrecting
His career, he was doing that movie
Blow with Johnny Depp at the time
That's right, that's right
I remember getting a Christmas card from him
And it had him and Johnny Depp and a bunch of
Women from the show
It was strange
And there's supposed to be a new Peewee movie, but anyway
Yeah, so my point is
We tried it as a TV show, we thought it'd be great
Because it's kind of like a TV show that you play
But it, you know, it didn't work out that well
It was, it had its, it didn't have its
It had its qualities, but
But like, as far as like the ideal
Version of You Don't Know Jack
I think if we could get it so that
You could play with more than four people
That you could stream it and that
The great thing is
That we still have Cookie, you know, our
Tom Gottlieb who plays Cookie Masterson
You know, it just would not be
The same without him, so thankfully
We still have him, he's been around
Ever since, you know, You Don't Know Jack volume 3
Even before that, but he was
The host of that, so it would have to have
Cookie Masterson, it would have to have
Support for more than four players
And I already have ideas
For the next version, but I don't want to
Give them all away here, plus I'll probably
Bring it all to work and people will be like, no
So, hahaha
Act Deft in chat is suggesting a one versus
100 You Don't Know Jack hybrid would be
The best thing ever
That's a direct quote, best thing ever
Oh, ever? Ever
In that case we'll get right on it
Apparently better than this program
Or pornography even, who knew
But there you go, Steve-o
I want to thank you so much for being on the show
Let's talk one more time everything
People need to know about Jackbox Party Back
Jackbox Party Back 2 is out
What, it's out this, like next week
Right, it's like ten days away, nine, right?
Yes, October 13th, so that's Tuesday
Tuesday, October 13th
Xbox One, PlayStation 3
4, Steam
Amazon Fire TV, Google Play
There you go, but
No Wii U, Steve-o?
No Wii U?
You're speaking the language of Ben Jacobs
Our beloved programmer
Who is in love
With all things Nintendo
We all love Nintendo, but
Right now it's not the right platform for us
I understand, I understand, I'm just being
Twitter, because I know you guys have got to get those tweets
Once in a while, what about Wii U?
But anyway, I understand, no, you guys are
Obviously supporting an awful lot there between all these different systems
And uh,
$24.99 local currency, right?
$24.99 American
And yeah, it's
I mean, I don't
I try not to sound like too sales pitchy
When I say this, but like, the work that we put
Into each of these games, we feel like we could
Sell each one of these five games for like
You know, $15 a piece
So the fact that you get five of them for $24.99
I mean, you can't afford not to buy
Okay, there, I did it, I went
I went all file, I went all sales pitch
It's $5 a game, $5 a game
Yeah, $5 a game, there you go
Alright, well Steve-o, best of luck to all you guys at Jackbox Games
And you guys are welcome back anytime
To announce whatever it is you might be working
On next, I assume inevitably
Someday this will be so successful
We might be here in a few months
Talking about Jackbox Party Pack 3
We will call you from our yacht
Sounds good, I look forward to it
Alright, thanks for having me on guys
Alright, take care, thanks so much for being here
Alright, bye
Alright, that was Steve from Jackbox Games
Of course, as they call him around the office
Steve-o, and if you want to read more about what Jackbox is up to
Jackboxgames.com
They're on Twitter as well
Over at Jackbox Games
And they're on Facebook
Hey, you know where? Jackbox Games, there it is
And I know I'll be picking up Jackbox Party Pack 2
On next day, I can't promise that I'm going to live stream
Because I don't need you all messing with my game
But no, maybe I will
Maybe I will do something
I think that bomb game with everybody involved
Will be a lot of fun
Bomb Corp, will be a lot of fun to play with everybody
To register participation
For this week's episode of Orange On Radio
At vognetwork.com
Use the passphrase, bacon
Alright, we're going to move right back
Into the show
And start to get into some news
I'm going to talk about my own gaming week though
I didn't really get a chance to get to my gaming week
But I don't have a whole lot to add
Because I bought stuff, I bought Lego dimensions
But I haven't played it yet
So this week, what I've actually been playing
I've been playing an awful lot of Diablo 3
I finally passed Paragon level 200
For the season
That'll tell you how much I've been playing Diablo 3
But once I finish the set bonus
For my Demon Hunter, oh my gosh
I just mow things down
I've been having a lot of fun with that
I finally got around to playing
And if Cody is out there listening, or even Extover
They're going to be both so proud of me that I finally got around to this game
On the Xbox One
I finally played Ori and the Blind Forest
I picked that up in a sale
A couple months ago
Finally decided to sit down and play this game
And I've got to say
It's got a really moving intro
Just in the beginning
Just in the first 10 minutes of the game
I was like, oh god, it's going to be one of those types of games
That really kind of moves you with the story
Even though the narrator kept reminding me
Of one of the dragons in Final Fantasy 14
If you've played Heaven's Word
You'll know what I'm talking about
If you haven't, don't worry about it
It sounds like the narrator in Ori and the Blind Forest
Ori and the Blind Forest is a Metroidvania
To use that term
It's one of those types of games
It's obviously a different type of setting
And the character is very different
And the fact that you have this ability
Where you can kind of consistently jump up a wall
In the very beginning of the game
It's like one of the first abilities you get
Causes the level design to be very different
Because you have a lot of curvatures
And branches and nature
And other ways that kind of prevent you from just jumping
Up all the walls
So in that way it kind of makes the design of the game
A lot different from games I've seen before
And the art direction of the game
Is great
It's a beautiful game
And so yeah, I've got to say
I am really enjoying Ori and the Blind Forest
The one little drawback
Where I'm at so far
Is that the difficulty of the game goes up really fast
And you start getting into
If you think
Loki makes asshole Mario Maker levels
Wait until you play some of these things
In Ori and the Blind Forest
There's some really tough parts of the game
Granted, you can save your game
Essentially at any time
And I thought that was also an interesting mechanic
If you have enough energy
Which you collect from exploding plants
And inanimate objects
And monsters as you kill them as well
You get a little bit of energy
You can create a save point anywhere
So that makes getting through some of these excruciatingly difficult parts
A little bit easier
Unless of course you create your save portal
At a horrible place
But I really enjoyed
Ori and the Blind Forest
And I want to play more of it in this coming week
So that was pretty much my gaming week
Diablo 3 and Ori and the Blind Forest
Housekeeping tonight
We do not have any shows off planned
But remember
DarkSakura and I
Will be, we should start promoting this
DarkSakura and I will be at
GamerX or GX3 is what they're calling it
Because they want to make sure the message is out there
That everybody games
You don't have to be gay to enjoy GamerX
But it helps, no I'm just kidding
Everybody will enjoy it
No matter what
If you're a part of the quilt bag or you're not
You're going to have a good time there
We will be there
We have a panel that DarkSakura and I will be on
I'm actually moderating it
Podcast Cross Zone 3
Really excited about that
And I totally forget the time and the moment
I can't remember if it's Friday or Saturday night
But we are actually going to be there
And DarkSakura and I still have to figure out how this is even going to work
VOG Network, if you haven't heard
Is a sponsor of GX3
We helped pitch in for the Kickstarter
I've always been a fan
Of this concept
So we pitched in
For people somewhere at the convention
So this is, I believe
The first time
Maybe because Bobby has done some of those Atlanta meetups
But this is going to be the first time
We've actually had a table at a show
And you can come by and say hi
And we're going to figure out
I don't know if we're going to have a classic game available
Or if we're actually going to be recording bits
For use on air
Which I think is going to be a big part of what we're doing
We're working on a top secret project behind the scenes
So we're going to be doing a lot of interviews
And nerds alike
Getting their viewpoints
So we'll be there at GX3
That's in San Jose December 11th and 12th
That weekend
I also take bribery in the form of fan art of my characters
In Dragon Age
There you go
Bobby Blackwell says
We've never had a table
And using that in quotes
We've actually had to turn down tables out there
Because I'm only one person and don't want to be tied to a table
The good news is
We're going to have more people
I know myself and DarkSoccer are going to be there for sure
And we might enlist the help of some of our friends
To help us man the table
Or we'll man the table
Or whatever the table when we're not there
So we'll work on it
Anyhow, that's all I have to announce
We are ready to get into some news
So let's start it off
With what's going on in the gaming world this week
Loki
So Microsoft has purchased Havoc Physics
The middleware
For calculating physics and animation
From Intel and they've used it on a bunch of their games
So what's this mean?
Don't know yet
But I know that one of the big games that uses that
That's coming up soon will be Crackdown 3
And of course they've used it recently
In Destiny, Dragon Age
Inquisition, Call of Duty, Advanced Warfare
A lot of the major games end up using that
And
Basically they've
Asserted that they're going to continue to innovate
For the benefit of the
Development partners and part of this innovation
Will include building more complex
More complete
Cloud service
Which they're kind of demonstrating
With Crackdown 3
Having everything fully destructible
So
Is this going to create interesting scenarios
Where the Havoc Engine might be used
On a Playstation game and I know I've seen that happen
Before
I don't know if they're going to lock it down to just one
Platform and stuff, I think it's just another revenue
Source for them
Maybe more of a thing to kind of
Sell their servers
And stuff like that
I don't know
I hope not
That would be kind of dickish
Tigerclaw in chat says
Havoc has been in a lot of games
That we played
Havoc is out there a lot
I think if they did lock it down that there would probably
Be an alternative that would come about
Gotcha
That's true
Somebody will inevitably
Copy it I suppose
Just like all those Minecraft clones
Except Minecraft still exists on so many platforms
And they're still supporting it
Just because Microsoft owns it
Doesn't mean they'll cut off support completely
They know where the money is
As many platforms as possible
What meme in our chat is saying
Gotta say Xbox is killing it
Since Phil Spencer took over
You know I agree
I totally do
I don't know if I would go so far as to say killing it
But definitely like
Turn that shit around
Would be maybe the phrase I would use
Because I'm sorry
But it was not going well under
Don Mattrick and I'm sure he's a fine person
And I hope I don't miss out on a potential
Coffee date someday because of my big mouth
But I'm just saying
All that razz on the
Xbox one
Was under his leadership
But yeah when Phil Spencer took over
Focusing on the positive
You know you really sense that turn around
And one thing I really enjoy about Phil Spencer
Is that he kind of admits
About the competition, you get the sense
From Phil Spencer that he plays games
Like he is a gamer
He plays games, okay yeah he's a business guy too
But like he'll acknowledge like yeah
Sony, Nintendo, doing good stuff
You know we're trying to offer our own stuff
Over here that we think is really good
Each generation has their kind of fails
I mean there's PlayStation 3 kind of
Botched the launch
You know Xbox One
Sort of botched the launch at first
But so did PlayStation 3
PlayStation 3 as I mentioned
And then Wii U
That's true
Everybody gets their turn at the fuck up table
But everybody
Does awesome things too
As much as we razz the companies
When they do things not so well
Things should get called out when they're done well too
Even with Wii U
I know a lot of Nintendo fanboys would fight me
And with good reasons because there are
A lot of great
Exclusive experiences on Wii U
And in fact I was just asked the other day
About what console should I get
And I said did you consider Wii U
Did you give it some serious consideration
Because you know there's some great games on it
And maybe you'll decide well it doesn't have Call of Duty
So I don't really want it
But you know you gotta at least consider it at this point
So anyway sorry we went on a tangent
Here over at live.vognetwork.com
Anyhow let's move on to another story
Speaking of Wii U I swear this was not all set up
For a transition but
Splatoon of course being one of those games
That are really swinging the people over to the Wii U
And apparently Splatoon has been hacked
Because you know what they say
Because the hacker's gonna hack
Hack hack hack
Well apparently a Splatoon hacker
Was online and can like
Screw up your save file
If your character won't load up when you're going
In the main plaza
And I guess it's like an
Octoling that will carry
The Hydra Splatling
So obviously it's a hacker because the thing hasn't released
Yet and what happens to get
Around this don't leave the room until
They're gone because returning
Back to the base is what screws up the save
File and there's a character in the game
Whose name is K and it has numbers in it
But nobody's gotten the full name
But you worry that something like this is
Probably spread around
Pretty quickly so
Be careful
Some folks actually found out that it's kinda
Easy to play as an Octoling in
Online matches
There's a whole YouTube video that walks you through
It that you do a text modification to the player
ID in the save file
I'm obviously not gonna get into the details here
I'm just gonna say it's out there
But I guess this is all gonna be
Patched by the time the next Splatfest
Comes out because that's when they'll do an update to the game
And certainly this is gonna get
This is gonna get sewed right up
So that doesn't happen anymore
By the way the theme has been announced for the next Splatfest
Friday October 9th
At 9pm for 24 hours
It will be
Planes versus
Cars
Do you prefer to travel by plane
Or do you prefer to travel by car
I think it should be three teams
Planes, trains and automobiles
There you go there's no team train
Japan always does things differently
Maybe they'll have team train
Or Europe will get something else
But anyway I'm gonna be team plane
Just because
I like car trips too but you know
Planes take me to places like Hawaii
That the car doesn't get me to so
I'm gonna be team plane for that one
Just in case you wanna be playing with me
But keep in mind Rob you have to take the car to get to the plane
That is true
Well you could take transit you could take a train to get to the plane
But you could also take a bus
You could
Or a van
You could take the train to the plane that will take you to the rain in Spain
The automobile is more versatile
I would go with the automobile
Yes but they don't serve you alcoholic
Beverages in the automobile
In fact it's against the law
They don't know what I'm doing in the backseat
That's not true though
In limos they do serve you
Hell yeah
Yeah but it's not team limo
Limo is a type of car so
Whatever whatever alright
Let's move on Dark Soccer what do you have for us
I have some crap
Anyway
We all like our humble bundles don't we
And now we have the
Humble Monthly Bundle
Woo
So they are doing a
And I'm quoting a highly curated bundle
Of favorite games once a month
It's gonna be
The Humble Monthly Bundle costs 12 bucks a month
And it will show games
That have been in the various weekly ones
And some that haven't been featured
And of course 5% of the subscription
Goes to charity
So like right now
We have Legend of Grimrock 2
In there right now
You can just go to
HumbleBundle.com
monthly and have a look at it
I guess it shouldn't be too surprising
That you know with the Loot Crate
What the Dollar Shave
Club There's a Pusheen one now
Oh for Loot Crate
No not well Loot Crate
But it's a Pusheen
Oh like a Pusheen of the Month Club
I remember when the Blank of the Month Club
Was something that you would read about
Speaking of planes like in SkyMall Magazine
Or like just something they would
Advertise on TV or the
Columbia House get 12 CDs
For a dollar and then they're gonna send
You the CDs of the month and if you don't like them
Send it back like it seems like that whole thing is
Back like big time like it
If I could send the games back
You'd get different games because a lot of them I probably already have
Yeah that's the one problem with Humble Bundle
But when you consider your charity
There's always a good element of it too
To throw in there
Feel like you're doing a little bit of good with the games
I don't know I'll have to look into it
I might actually jump on this
Might be a good way to force myself to play some games
That I wouldn't usually play
Let's travel around the world and check out some
Release dates some things that we'll be playing
A little sooner than
Perhaps what is coming up in the Humble Bundle next month
Starting in the US
Loki
Alright so starting off we've got
Dragon Age Inquisition Game of the Year edition
Yes the one on the DLC
I'll get another one
That's on Playstation 4 and Xbox One
Here's your chance to get it on another platform
That could be that's what I do
No because I can't mod other platforms
Disgaea 5
Alliance of Vengeance on Playstation 4
Dengeki
Bunko Fighting Climax
On Playstation 3 and Vita
Did you say Bunko Fighting Climax
Yeah Dengeki Bunko
Bunk that's the game my mom would play
That's with a C not a K
I'm like how do you do Bunko Fighting?
Do the dice get up and attack each other?
That's what I saw in my mind
Bunko Fighters
Grandma's gonna throw down
Cause she didn't get the roll she wanted
Sorry Loki
There's a little known game called Rock Band 4
That's coming out this week as well
On Playstation 4 and Xbox One
And if you want to get it with some instruments
They have all those available for you as well
Transformers Devastation
The Platinum Games
Transformers
That's coming out on Playstation 4
And Xbox One as well
Ride on Playstation 4
I guess Devastation is also on Playstation 3 and Xbox 360
Farming Simulator 16 on Vita
I thought I've seen that before but I guess
It's been delayed again
Gotta wait for that
Man
As if we're not in the fourth quarter already
Alright
And then the next thing I've got
Let's see
Brace yourself winter is coming
And then finally on
I guess this is Sunday or Friday
Chibi Robo Ziplash on 3DS
I think it's the one with the amiibo
Oh yes they have one with an amiibo
And then Uncharted the Nathan Drake collection on Playstation 4 is coming
And Sid Meier's Civilization Beyond Earth Rising Tide
So that's an expansion for an expansion
Oh no it's an expansion for the new game
That's right
And that's it
Alright
By the way in chat over at live.vognetware.com
Dark Tetsuya says Bunko Fighters
Is that another dream game?
Nah I don't think we could
Officially put it on the dream game list
But if like YYR hears this
And like that's my next game
I'm not gonna complain
So I'm just saying
Alright anyway
Let's travel to Japan and look at the Playstation 4
Where this week FIFA 16
Gets its release in regular and deluxe edition
On October the 8th
Also Grand Theft Auto 5 gets a price reduction
It moves into the best hit series
And the Uncharted collection is out this week
In Japan as well
Moving over to the Wii U
Nada
In fact their next release
I don't think they have anything until November actually
In Japan
For the Wii U so you might not be reading those dates
For a while
But on the Playstation Vita
Actually this is the first week in a while we don't have anything on the Vita
We have a
Neptune vs. Zombie Gundam
Gekkei Jigen Tag Blank
comes out next week
But that's on the 15th
So this is finally a quiet week on the Vita in Japan
Could that be because
They're expecting a big reception to
Guru Guru Chibi Robo
In regular and amiibo set over in Japan
That is releasing on October the 8th as well
I hear this is gonna be the last Chibi Robo game they do
Well if it sells well
Then of course they'll do another one
I think they kind of made that
I don't wanna say a threat but it was a threat
Like on Twitter like you know
Well if it doesn't sell well
I'm kind of fine with that
Anyway also on the 3DS
A price reduction for Simogami Tensei 4
As it moves into the Atlas Best collection
So that is what you have to look forward to
In Japan this week
Let's go over to the UK
With Dark Sakura
On October 6th we have Prison Architect
For Mac and for PC
Blackband 4 comes out on
Xbox One and Playstation 4
Skyhill comes out on Mac and PC
And then on October 8th
We have Bridge Constructor Stunts
For Android
That's it
Alright just a few more stories for you guys
And then the classic game of the week
Loki?
Alright I'm surprised well
Bridge Constructor that's kind of what people do in that
Anyways it just makes stunts so I'm surprised it took them this long
To actually release something like that
Criterion
They're working on
Possibly a successor to Burnout
And that makes me happy
Because I want more Burnout
And this is coming from a Twitter conversation
They're saying you know
What they're working on
Two things first the game is a multiplayer sports game
Coming spring of 2016
Which I remember that's that like
I think there's like an off-road
Racing sports thing
That they've got coming
And then the other one
It says then we make a driving game
What sort of driving game you ask?
A spiritual successor
Speed traffic and crashing lots and lots
Of crashing
Yes please
That's what I need in my Burnout
Game is just big fiery
Car crashes
I don't understand why no one would fund
Or like
Put money towards another Burnout game
I mean come on
How well of these Need for Speed games have done
Not very good
I bet if they went to Kickstarter they'd get it
If it was like fucking Burnout and said Need for Speed
Way better
Alright
Speaking of crowdfunding
Maybe Criterion
And those employees aren't doing this
But Cave is thinking about it
You want some shooters on the Playstation 4
Some more shooters
Cave is thinking about
Getting some crowdfunding
They're asking on Facebook
Could we get $300,000 to $500,000
To do
Actually that's the Steam port
But a million would allow them to do a Playstation 4 port
And they're saying for 3 million
They'll do a new game as well
To a console
So I don't know
That seems like an awful lot of money
But then again
If they're selling it for $20 a pop
They would have to get what
15,000 people
To get on board
That's a lot of money for
I don't know
I can't imagine an arcade game
Having that kind of budget
It would depend
On
It's also like how into
These types of games are you
Maybe we say that we dismiss it
Because we're not super into shooters
But you know some people really love their bullet hell games
I'm not even thinking necessarily the genre
I'm just thinking of how complex of a game it is
I mean yeah I understand there's bullet patterns
And all that stuff but really how much
How many art assets are you talking there
I mean the level design
I just don't see that as being a very in depth
Game that would require 3 million
Dollars to
Make another one of
I mean I just don't know
Well that's fair
Well we are going to take a trip down memory lane
With Dark Sakura
And Dark Sakura is going to step into the gaming vault
And find a game that she thinks
You kids should check out this game this week
It is the classic game
Of the week with Dark
Sakura
I think this is kind of an
Obscure pick this week but I don't know that's just me
It was one of my favorites that I had
Alright so what is the classic
Game of the week this week?
The game is SNK Gals Fighter
It was a one on one
Fighting game that
Came out on the Neo Geo Pocket Color
In 2000
I played the stew out of this game
Just because I really liked it and it was really funny
So this was for the
Queen of Fighters tournament
That was organized by a Miss X
Who is really
Yori Yagami dressed up in drag
So that they could
Win the K talisman that grants any
Wish so
It's really just like a little
Sd fighter it's really cute
And it's very similar to how
The King of Fighters
R1 and R2 played but a little bit faster
So it was
Honestly like I said one of my
Favorite games ever that came out on
The Neo Geo Pocket Color
You could play as
Mai Shiranui from
Fatal Fury 2
You had Athena from Psycho Soldier
Yuri from Art of Fighting 2
Leona from King of Fighters 96
Shirmi from King of Fighters 97
Also the namesake of my cat
Nakoru from Samurai
Shiki from
Samurai Shodown 64
And Akari from The Last Blade
You also had hidden characters
You had Whip and you had
Yuki Kushinata who was
Kyo's girlfriend
In King of Fighters 97 and it's the only fighting
Game she's actually been playable in
And of course your boss is Miss X
Who is Yori from
King of Fighters
So it was
I mean
There's not really so much to say about it
It is really just a
A little fighting game
But a lot of the little stuff
The you know attacks
In it were really just made comical
You uh
For a chibi pocket version
Of the game cause you know a lot of the pocket
Versions of fighting games were straight up
Bad like if you played Mortal Kombat
On the original Game Boy it's really
Bad but this
You know again I haven't played this
But this looks like okay
It's a chibi cartoony like you know
Amped up silly I guess
Version of the game but it looks
Surprisingly fluid for a pocket game
Oh yeah it was really good
I mean it was surprisingly good
And you know
Even with the limitations
Of the system at the time it was
Very solid I played
I probably played through this game for
Until I beat it with everybody
And I always forget that
Athena in this game is the same Athena
From the NES game
It's like a soldier
Crazy
There it is
And that's actually the outfit
That she's wearing in that one
Is her King of Fighters 99 outfit
So there you go
That's all I have to say
This is the only version of this game ever that's been out
And it's just
Really cute and very funny
So you get
You know little cameos
From some of the other characters of course
From the various SNK series
In endings and backgrounds
And whatnot
Well you know sometimes she picks
A mainstream game but sometimes she picks
A more obscure game that hey maybe you hadn't
Heard of this and considering it was only on the Neo Geo Pocket
Color I'm going to assume a lot of people
Probably never heard of this so there it is
SNK Gals Fighters
I didn't even know about this game
I love that she just drew a picture and now she's singing
Karaoke as one of her moves
Yeah if you want to borrow it
Did Leona just strap dynamite to her?
Wow
She has the earring bomb but they changed it for the game
For this one
So it's just really cute
It's kind of fun
If you're interested in borrowing it I would be more than happy
To lend you a Neo Geo Pocket Color in the game
Sweet
Bring your own batteries
I like dark soccer she gives me stuff
Which I still need to bring over some of my
Super Famicom, not my Super but my
Actually I do have a few Super Famicom cartridges
And my Famicom cartridges
I don't even think I talked yet on the show
About what I bought, no that's okay
Because we'll talk about that at the start of part B
Let that be our teaser
I have a few
We are going to take a break and we'll talk about that
We're going to talk about the FUGL Question of the Week
Which has to do with multiplayer games
Since we had Jackbox on tonight and they really
Excel at doing those multiplayer games
Thought we would have a question about that tonight
So we're going to talk that with you guys
Your phone calls and 1877 game OLR
And emails which I think
There's quite a few emails tonight
Dark soccer is going to be busy during the email segment
Yay! So we'll get to all that
When we come back after this break with more
Of Orange Lounge Radio right after this
Welcome back everybody
To Orange Lounge Radio
We are live tonight with our
616th episode, it's the second half
For this October the 4th
Of 2015 and I
Can't believe it's already October
Where's this year gone? And 616?
Didn't we just celebrate episode 600?
Oh my gosh where'd this year go
At least the good news is now that it's
October it is officially time
For Pumpkin All the Things
And I'm very excited about the Pumpkin All the Things
Time of year
You know I got my pumpkin spice latte
I love all of them actually
I had those pumpkin latte M&M's they were great
You know what else is also a good season for?
If you happen to like that kind of thing
Root vegetables
Oh because this is the time of year where a lot of those
Are in season and so forth
Which pumpkin kind of is
Well we have an amazing cafe at work
And I'll just leave it here
I've been having some stomach problems so I haven't been able to
Eat a lot of heavy crazy foods
They had one that was like rutabaga
And beets and parsnips and carrots
And everything and I am enjoying
Carrot ginger soup
Yeah ginger is amazing
It's a great spice
I feel weird calling it a spice but you know it's a great flavor
Well it's also really good if you
Have stomach problems
I love ginger beer and you can't get it
At every store but like
Bathmo
Oh my god I have to tell you
This is completely off topic
That's okay we do that here at OLR and you the most
They're opening a total wine by my house
Total wine gets frivolous
Oh so you're going to be a total lush
Yep and I will get you ginger beer
When I go get my frivolous
My favorite is that there is a total wine
It's over by for you SAC people which is I know
A very small percentage of our audience
There's a big mall there's a total wine
Not far from there but the hilarious
Thing on the back side of
The plaza the side that's by Chick-fil-A
For those that happen to know the area
No it says
On the sign still circuit city
How long
Has circuit city been gone
And it's still on the sign
Where total wine is
That's the building they converted
Oh my gosh drives me crazy
It's still in the shape of the big plug
Who remembers the commercials
That was always the cool part of the store
But that one is the one they use for the Halloween
Store right they rent out that building once in a while
I think so and it was also like stupid
Prices or something I don't know
It's called stupid prices
It's a recent history
We're local there it is
Once in a while I'll get those tweets
That are like it's so weird to hear about
Local things on OLR I forget they're in my neighborhood
That actually happened to me on Tumblr by the way
I was posting I was like
Yeah we got like 10 minutes of rain
You know it was a few days ago and
I was like I wish we had more and then I tagged
At Sacramento and one of
The people who follows me is like oh my god
I live in Santa Clara
Yeah and I can speak Bay Area too
That's the good news there's a lot of people there
I met my friend Brian the pagan
Jew on
Hi Free Looking Brian
But you know that's how I met my friend that way
And he and his husband
Razi
But I feel fortunate through OLR
If we can have a cheesy moment for a minute
I feel fortunate through OLR that I do feel like
I know people
And I have acquaintances if not friends
Like in almost every major
City in America because
Of you know Twitter
Podcasting and things that have happened
Because of this show and I'm so thankful for that
Anyway not to get too warm and fuzzy
But it's just a reality it's how I feel
I can't help the feels
Let's land back into reality for a minute
Here though because at the end of part A
Dark Soccer was teasing this about Loaning Me
Games so I suppose it's time we talk
About another big purchase I made today
I was really I needed retail
I didn't need retail therapy but it's one of those things that you don't
Realize you need it until you're doing it
I bought a Retron 5 today
And I've been talking about doing that
For a while
But I finally did it today
And I did it because
Well the Retron 5 will play the NES
The Super Nintendo, the GBA
Famicom and
Genesis, did I say Genesis?
But those are the five
Systems it does, sadly it will not do Neo Geo
Pocket Color
It also will not do like
Super Game Boy and add on games
So because I do recall reading a review
Where it won't do Sonic and Knuckles
Interesting
Like any of the add on type games
Well that's okay and part of the reason I did it
And I know there's mixed reviews on
Retron I know I'm going into it with that
But the HDMI support
I think is pretty cool and
Will help me a lot in streaming
Wink wink nudge nudge
So that was you know and the price is actually
Cheaper where I got it than it was on Amazon
And how often do you see that so
Yeah and Tigerclaw on chat
Even saying you need to do some games
For the Retron 5 on Twitch and that's the plan
And SSJ with that same comment
About the add on games
So yeah
There you go
And AkumaJP is reminding me
Not to mention international in regards to
Our audience, that's true
Like I actually
AkumaJP I feel fortunate that if I went to
Japan some day
He could help me out in some of the culture shock
And getting to different places I needed to go
Same thing if I were to ever
Go overseas into what we've
Affectionately called on the other show
Hoard House, Londonland or not
Londonland
With Raven and EJ
On Girls Gone Wow
And Syl from the Geek Card
And Razorbug and Robface and all the
People I know over there it's like
And Pika Uno could totally take me to Disneyland
Although I hope they didn't
Up the prices at Disney Paris
Like they did here in the US
Recently because that sucked
The prices at Disneyland went up today
Did you hear about that Dark Sakura?
There is no longer a premium pass at Disneyland
Well Dan and I actually had a
Conversation about it
Well prepare to pay a lot more money
If you're gonna get the passes
Well part of the reason though is that the passes are probably cheap
When the parks weren't getting a lot of attention
Now that you know the Disney parks
Are crazy popular
They can
I've heard that this is a move to
Weed out the crowds
That's what we were saying
You would think wouldn't Disney want the crowds
But yes of course they do
But to a certain limit
And I think Disney has kind of hit that limit
When they have to turn people away
They've kind of hit the limit
I think that could be a big part of it
But anyway
We're getting a little bit off base
But yeah
We will
I'm sure have to start a Disney podcast someday
When I can afford to go to Disneyland again
Yet I say I can't afford Disneyland
And I'm like ooh I just bought a Red Tron 5
But Disneyland gets a lot more expensive than that
That won't even buy
Like a two day park hopper anymore
When I spend on that Red Tron 5
I didn't see if they still have the SoCal discount
I didn't see anything about that
So we just need to talk to Marissa
I just want to be clear
I do love Disneyland
I love it and I miss it
I haven't been in over a year
But it's getting expensive yo
To do Disney
I really want to go before Big Thunder is gone
But still
I'm not going to be able to help it when they open Star Wars Land
I do want to see that
I'm not even that big of a Star Wars fan
But I just want to see how Disneyland does Star Wars
I want them to migrate the bucket of meat
Hopefully
I would think that would be a great fit at California Adventure
If they could do the bucket of meat
At some Wall-E themed place
So if they open Star Wars Land
Does that mean they're going to move Star Tours
I don't know
I would think logically
Yes you move Star Tours over there
Have a new Star Tour and then you close the old one
And use it for something else
But a lot of Star Wars is already injected into Tomorrowland
Because they're Star Tours
I believe I heard Space Mountain
Is going to have a Star Wars type theme
No they can't
It's a rock and roller coaster
If it's a temporary thing
It's not permanent
Remember the rock and roller coaster
It's going to be like that
Dan and I were actually talking about
Maybe sometime in the next year or so
Going to Disney World
So we can do Mission 1
Or Mission 2, whatever it's called
But then the Captain EO Theater
So how's Ingress in Disneyland?
Insane
There's like 500 portals in one park
And it's always constantly flipped
That's a great place to just AP farm
I am loving this you guys
Loki, within the scope of a week
Within the scope of a week has gone from
I hate Ingress, you're dumb for playing it
I just didn't get it
And I still don't really get it
But it's kind of something to kill time
So how many portals do you think there are at Disneyland?
I love it
If I'm going to have to
I don't normally go on the roller coaster
So I have to have something to do while I'm sitting there
Alright, I'm going to curb all the Disney chat
Although Bobby Black Wolf is screaming in chat
And I say screaming because it's all in caps
Come to Disney World instead
I've been giving that some serious thought
And if I could get the time away from work
I would love, love, love
To go to Dragon Con
I'm using my quotey fingers like really early
And go to Disney World on like Monday, Tuesday
And then go to Dragon Con
I would love to do that
What I would like to do is fly into Orlando
Or close to it
Go to Disney World and then rent a car
And drive up the Florida coast
And spend like another week in Mobile with my family
And then come home from Mobile
That would be perfect
Bobby Black Wolf is saying two days isn't enough for Disney World though
Good point, good point
Alright, anyway
We'll get into travel talk later
We got to get into some rapid fire news
So let's get to it
Traveling around quickly looking at what happened in the gaming world this week
With these quick stories, Loki
I'm not surprised but Super Mario Maker has already sold a million copies
I mean it makes sense because it looked awesome
And they said already over 2 million courses have been made
And it's been played 75 million times
And I want DLC
I'm wondering if they do like a DLC pack that's like Zelda 2 Adventures of Link
Because it is kind of side scroller
It would be kind of nice to have like non-Mario themes
I don't know
Hopefully
I just have a feeling we've only seen the beginning of what they're going to do with Mario Maker
Oh I think we have
If Splatoon and Mario Kart 8 are any example
I'm loving this Nintendo that understands DLC
I never thought I'd say that but I really am
Yeah
And then along with that
Speaking of community created things
Battlefield 4 they have a new outbreak map that's coming out
That's being designed I guess by the community
They've got
It looks kind of cool
It's like a jungle type environment
And you can drive boats on the river and stuff like that
So that's kind of cool
Maybe a free update that will be coming out soon
And then
Amiibos
Nintendo is bringing back some of the more rare Amiibos
Apparently the Captain Falcon, Fox, Greninja, Little Mac
Lucario and Shulk are going to be coming back
I may have picked up a Captain Falcon and a Little Mac
We found the Fox by the way
The Fox McCloud
Nice yeah
They are out there
So those will be coming back
Select retailers soon
And then along with that there's going to be some new
Animal Crossing Amiibos
Including they've got
Celeste
Mr. Rosetti, Kix and Blathers
And I'm assuming those are going to be for
Animal Crossing Happy Home Designer
I don't know
Rosetti is kind of fun
Yeah some of those Amiibo I would have to have
What about Tom? Do they have Tom Nook?
I know they have his kids
Timmy and Tommy
But I don't know if they have
They were annoying
Here's the thing
I'm kind of not feeling the
Animal Crossing Happy Home Designer
All the Amiibo stuff
That's cool that Jamie likes it
It seems like that would be more something like
For like
I don't know
Animal Crossing
Like
Imagine if you will
Instead of having random animals in your town
You buy the Amiibos for the animals
You want to live in your town
Alright
Anyhow we'll
Keep on moving with some more stories here
Because we can probably debate these Animal Crossing
Amiibo for some time
I say this now that I'm not going to get any
And then watch my shelf will suddenly
Where did you get the Blathers from?
I bought it because I could
They're out
No I meant for non-Animal Crossing
I don't know when that is planned
For non-Animal Crossing characters
I'd rather pick up a bunch of those
Than just buying a bunch of the figures
Alright
Moving on, speaking of Mario Maker
Japan getting another piece
Of DLC announced
We have yet to have one announced
But another character in Japan
It's Game Center CX's Arino
Who will have the suit and tie
So again this is one of those
Amiibo suits
That's used in the 8-bit version of the game
You can't really use it in the other levels
But that's still kind of cool
That's going to be some DLC
Can't wait to see what's coming out here
Do you think we'll get that here? Because I don't think we will
Well I'm kind of wondering if we will get that here
Or at least some sort of update because
Aren't we going to be playing those levels
Since we do play levels from Japanese players
I guess that's true
So wouldn't we have those suits?
That's a good thought I didn't think about
That we could essentially play a Japanese level
That would have those suits whether they're out here or not
That's a very good point
Unless they're just going to filter those out for us
Oh yeah like maybe what is
The Game Center person for us
Or for them will become a different personality for us
Well no I'm not
Oh maybe I don't know I just thought maybe
Everybody with DLC here
Maybe Jeff Keighley is going to be a suit in Mario Maker
Reggie Fils-Aime
I would love that
My buddy is ready
I'm seriously
Why didn't they put him in Smash
I mean come on that would have been so perfect
I missed out
You never know
They make the Mii
With Reggie a lot in the
I don't want the Mii I want actually
Reggie and the Mii is cool
You can make whoever you want but like I want
Actually to have officially
Supported Reggie in there
Mii Fighters aren't good enough
No it's not good enough
Moving on
What used to be the Best Buy
Theater in Times Square
Which was also once the Nokia
Theater it is now a Sony
Sponsored theater and so now
It is the PlayStation Theater
Not to be confused with a place
That will actually like have PlayStation
Experiences and so forth but being in
Times Square isn't that it's a theater
It will be live performances and
It will occasionally though have events that
Will showcase Sony PlayStation
Type events and you can bet that if
Sony has big announcements to make they may consider
Using this in New York City
So we'll see
You can also see that the official PlayStation
Twitter account actually tweeted some pictures of the
Inside of the theater looks very
Nice in there let's hope this branding sticks
They have a guy from
Doing No Man's Sky you know kind of the spokes works in there
On
Colbert's show and
He had a PewDiePie
On his show
One of the things that he was saying though
He's all
Is this game coming out soon?
Because it's got to be coming out soon if you're on my
Show so I'm wondering like
If they're going to be announcing something soon
Because it is true they've been doing
The whole
They've been doing that ever since
E3 and stuff but they've been doing talk show
Circuit where they're showing off the game
It's kind of usually
Yeah I thought it was supposed to be this holiday
That that game was out
Maybe surprise would be
I'd like a surprise please
Speaking of not to be too tangenty
But apparently Colbert
Had PewDiePie on
And very respectful
Sort of interview but in the Colbert way
Colbert still took his digs
In the way only he can do
But a lot of people comparing and contrasting
To how Jimmy Kimmel kind of came off
Like an uninformed ass
Which is also his shtick
I mean being an ass
Is kind of how he got famous from the man show
I mean right because that was his first
Big show was the one he did with Adam Carolla the man show
And they were kind of asses on that show
And that was what it was
But anyway people really
Giving kudos to Colbert and I got to say
I haven't watched a lot of episodes of his show
But I've always loved Stephen Colbert
And you know my love of Stephen Colbert
I watch a lot of the highlights thankfully
To the internet because I don't stay up to watch
Those shows but like I watch a lot of the highlights
And yeah I mean he's doing a great job
There's yeah and
I might be partial because I've loved him ever since
Strangers with Candy and even a little bit of
Exit 57 so I think it's cool that
They really do need to have Strangers with Candy come back
I don't think it can now
Why?
I don't know oh Bobby Blackwolf correcting me
Kimmel's first big show is
Win Ben Stein's Money I forgot about that
That's right
Oh yeah
That was before the Man Show I think it was
Was he the first host though?
I thought they had a woman on but maybe she was later
Because he wasn't always
The host of Win Ben Stein's Money
That came later wasn't it?
That show was awesome Yeah that show was a good show
I gotta say I need more Ben Stein
Where is Ben Stein?
He started going really political
He kind of went down that Margaret Cho route
Where she got less funny and more political
And I think that's kind of what happened with Ben Stein
So I don't know
Bobby Blackwolf says
That Ben's doing Clear Eyes ads
And Mega Man X400 says
The best game show host
Was the mean British lady
On weakest link
Anne Robinson
Yes
Which village is missing their idiot?
It's time to find out
Who is the weakest link?
Goodbye
That show is so fucking rad
Why is that gone?
Have you seen
Because we have basic cable
And occasionally I turn it on TV
Because I don't actually watch TV I just get it
Because it's $10 cheaper with cable for some stupid reason
So we have basic cable
And occasionally I'll turn it on and see what shows
Are on and there's like this game show
With a bomb and so you have to
Answer these questions and the answer is
Whatever when you cut and if they get it wrong
They get sprayed with some sort of
It's yogurt
It's dog urine
It's like really disgusting
Stuff
It was on Fox and I think it did so horribly
They moved it to one of the off brand
FX or something
It wasn't even that it was on one of the local channels
Because that's all I get
Maybe Fox kept it
I haven't watched TV in a while
What happened to TV?
Fox cancels Firefly
But keeps the bomb blowing up
Rabbit poop in people's faces
Firefly is too intelligent
For the audience that is Fox
So that's why
They have to
Put that crap on there
Hey rapid fire news
Where we talk about this news rapidly
And don't go on tansions
Hey Google and Microsoft
I'm sorry Rob have you met us?
No
Who are you people and what are you doing in my house?
Google and Microsoft
Hey they used to be going
Head to head to each other over different patents
Because you know everybody loves to fight about patents
But Google and Microsoft
Agreeing to a truce
There were 20 lawsuits
Between the two companies
They have all been
Settled essentially
Ending the five year dispute
This has to do with phones
Xbox video playback
Now they're going to actually come together
And on certain patent matters
They will actually brand together
Building a royalty free video format
That prevents these legal skirmishes
In the future
So that's always nice to see people resolve their differences
And all this patent
Crap get weeded out
That's nice
How about you Dark Soccer what do you have?
Eh nothing I give up
No I'm kidding
Stop
So Nvidia has decided to rebrand
Grid
All in capitals as Geforce now
So basically it's their version of cloud gaming
To give you 1080p
60 frames per second
60 frames per second gaming
Over the internet blah blah blah
So yeah rebranding that's all
If you see a change that's why
Also the game
That pretty much started it all when it comes to fighting games
Is
Now on Playstation Network
It's karate champ
So I mean how's that
For a slice of 1984 right?
That takes me back to Straw Hat Pizza
Straw Hat Pizza
Which is still around I guess
Which I've never been to
Really? Yeah
It's not bad but they used to be everywhere and then they just kind of fizzled
Do you think there's good pizza in Alabama?
No
I bet you'd be surprised
Didn't you say there was like a sushi place you loved in Alabama?
I thought there was
Yeah but they opened it like well after I moved
Did you know there's a place
Sorry to do tangents but that's what we do here at OLR
Since I've been informed
Did you know that there's a sushi place
Near here called Nemo Sushi
And the little logo
Is actually an orange fish
That has white stripes on it
And I'm like
I could go there and eat little Nemo
Why would you call your restaurant
Nemo Sushi
You're gonna eat Nemo
See I would've if I was gonna do one called Nemo Sushi
It would be a little boy in pajamas
And you could sit on beds and eat sushi
Fair enough, alright sorry
I still want to go to that Ninja Sushi
I apologize for the tangent
But it was important
This tangent was brought to you by fish
I'll never forget we went to a place called Taka's Sushi
Just because we were like
Because of the name BeatMania2DX LOL
I don't even know if that place is still there
They have the sakura roll which I had to eat
You had a sakura roll at Taka's Sushi
A sakura roll
So anyway
There's been leaks
Of new Street Fighter 5 characters
There's one called Lara
And I'm trying to
It was actually shared by
Famitsu
But I'm trying to see exactly what her style is
It looks like she's a Brazilian Jiu Jitsu
And then
There was also announced
Nekali and Rashid
And then they also confirmed
Zangief
Yay, Street Fighter 5
Excellent
Done
Alright well then let's go to our
FOOGLE question of the week
Each week we take Facebook
And Google Plus and we slam those
Words together and you get FOOGLE
Of course you can follow us
At Facebook.com slash OrangeLoungeRadio
Or Google.com slash
Plus OrangeLoungeRadio
And tonight we thought we would ask
About multiplayer games
Since you know Jackbox Games
Was on the show tonight
And they specialize really in multiplayer party games
We thought we'd ask about your favorite
Multiplayer game to have people
All in one place to play
And we were really looking for
In one room type of stories
Because yeah you can play everything online today
Including you know the Jackbox games
But I think it's
Kind of fun to talk about having people
Over and getting the party on that way
So let's go to Facebook
Where Master Claw starts us off tonight
Saying Super Smash Brothers Melee
Mario Kart 64 and GoldenEye 007
Saw the most couch multiplayer
In my house
I haven't had many friends IRL since then
Aww that's sad though
You always answer our questions
If you listen to this show you must be a good guy
You should have lots of friends IRL
Maybe you just don't have friends that play video games
But you'd be surprised
I'm sometimes talking to play Mario Kart with you
Bryce H. replies
And says Mario Kart 8
And Just Dance
See I don't, so people
Really do the Just Dance with lots of people around
I would think I'd be a little scared to do that
Oh come on you did the Abba Dance
With me and Tiara
That was a private moment
Tiara was here wasn't she?
I was a private dancer
You weren't dancing for money
I didn't know that was anything except a laugh
Didn't I get sushi? I don't know
I don't know
Degenerate Johnny says
Although I would have loved to say We Dare for the Wii
I couldn't find good swinger couples
To play with me, Sy
So I guess I'll have to stick with Super Smash Brothers
Oh Degenerate Johnny
Ragenator says
When I was in college
My college campus had a 4 slot Neo Geo MVS
A few of us really got into playing the crap
Out of Samurai Shodown 4
Amakusa's Revenge
Granted only 2 people could play at a time
In terms of non-video gaming
I used to love Magic the Gathering the actual card game
Sadly I can't afford to constantly get new cards
Nowadays plus card shops are a pain to get to
For my neighborhood anyway
So I have to settle for the Steam incarnations of Magic
You know I was wondering if somebody would reply with an arcade game
Because you know
Arcade games were definitely a multiplayer experience
All in the same place many years ago
Hence how Dark Sakura, Loki, and myself met
Actually was playing DDR
I wonder if anybody said DDR
So I guess maybe dance games would be included
Didn't I just say just dance?
That must be a thing with age
In my 20s I must not have been as inhibited as I am now
Alright Silent Tom
Says my favorite multiplayer game
Is the best of the Rock Band games
I get
Excuse me Rock Band games
A game my wife, her and her best friend and her hubby have
Get together and have some drinks
And have a great time
And ER also saying Rock Band
Back in college we played that game a ton
We also played a lot of fighting games
Which just aren't the same online
SSG100Matt says my friends and I
During my middle and high school years
Would always play the Mario Party games together
Primarily Mario Party 2
We played the hell out of that game
And would always get into playful arguments
About setting off Bowser parades
Star stealing and coin stealing
We also had developed calluses on the palms of our hands
And had several broken N60 games
To be fair those things are really easy to break
Hitstun says nothing beats a big game of Bomberman
It's easy to pick up and play
So it's great for parties
It's about time we get a Bomberman game on current consoles
Who owns that IP now?
Oh yeah
It's Konami
Nevermind
What you weren't a fan of Bomberman Zero
Or whatever that was on the
Oh god
Anyway
Dark Tetsuya says
I'm gonna say Para Para Paradise
Because even though it wasn't technically multiplayer
If you get a bunch of nerds in a room
That know the routine to a given song
They're all probably gonna do it
In blatant disregard to the sign
Forbidding such activity
Okay you're right I was totally wrong on what I said about dancing
Yeah it's hilarious when they
Forbid that type of thing it's like what is this
Footloose or something?
Dancing is foreboden
Here at Golfland
Lastly on Facebook
MegamanX400
Our pal from Video Game Realness
Podcast says
Hands down the game my friends and I have played the most
Even since high school has been Smash Brothers
Each iteration has provided
Hours of replayable fun
As everyone's skill levels improved
We all shifted over time and performance
So it kept things interesting and competitive
For us
Those are the answers from Facebook
But let us not forget Google Plus
Where we have ActDeft saying Super Smash Brothers
They never failed to deliver
On the local multiplayer department
Retertainment says
Seen it since all you really needed to play it
Was a DVD player
Oh god they really drilled that series
Into the ground though with all the scenes
Have you seen the Twilight seen it?
That's nothing but trivia questions
On the Twilight games oh lord
Sent it on fire
And lastly
MartinD replies and says
Maybe a weird answer here but probably
Tekken 3 is still the game I played
The most with my friends back in the day
A lot of fun
Also any FIFA game is a lot of fun to play
Against friends not really into the party games
I don't think Tekken 3 is a weird answer
Irene and I used to play the shit out of that game
And it was all about Panda
I worked in an Amco arcade when that was out
I still am proud of the day
That I went in and the guys had been there
Like almost all day practicing King
And I decided to just take
You know go back and forth with Jen and Julia
On the left
AkumaJP giving an old school answer
In our chat room saying
If it doesn't have to be multiplayer my friend and I
Played the shit out of Shinobi on the Genesis
4 person turn by turn
Yeah I mean
Sometimes a multiplayer gaming experience
Was passing that controller around
And everybody kind of doing the part of the game
That they're best at or you suck
And can't get past this part let me take care of it
Bomberman 2 with the multitap
On the SNES
That was pretty awesome
Yeah they really haven't had a new one in a while
The last one I can think of was that
They had one on the Xbox 360
And I think it was on PlayStation 3 as well
But not zero
Not zero there was like on the network
Nintendo network
The online download
Yeah there was Bomberman live
Alright
Anyhow that does it for the Fugu question of the week
But we've got some more news and your phone calls
Here in a little while
In the meantime Loki
Yeah so it kind of makes me wonder you know with
You know the decision for
Konami going into this whole
More so into the Pachinko
And you know on mobile games
Division maybe it's not the greatest thing
Sega, Sammy for example
They're cutting 200 jobs
In its Pachinko division
Based on poor sales
So
They're putting, soliciting voluntary retirement
For 200 jobs
And I guess they're saying that there was
An extraordinary loss
And that basically
The poor sales of
Pachinko machines like
Pachinko slot
Hokuto no Ken Tomo
Or Fist of the North Star
And Bayonetta's Pachinko slot
Not even hitting half the sales
They were expected to
I hope Bayonetta isn't
Like gone forever
I have this really bad feeling it is
I'm going to try not to think negative thoughts
And just hope that she shows up in Smash Brothers
And gets an amiibo
But I just feel like it's not going to happen
So I guess there isn't
Tons and tons of money
Could it be over saturation of the market?
I mean because I can't imagine
Well I don't know
There's probably a ton of Pachinko slot
Parlors or arcades or whatever
In Japan so
Do they maybe have too many?
I mean I don't know
Why it wouldn't perform as well
Alan Alchemy in chat over at
Live.FogNetwork.com says
They need to port Bayonetta to PC
God damn it
Maybe the first one
But the second one they can't
That game would not have happened if not for Nintendo
And I don't see Nintendo
I mean unless there's something in the contract
Where like after five years they can do it
Like maybe what happened was Zombie U
And I still believe we can
Yeah so anyway
Moving on
Let's get to another story here
Although a masked bishop joined our chat room
Apparently just to say Bomberman 64 was amazing
Oh yeah the old school Bomberman's were all awesome
But then Bomberman 0 happened
And we all wondered what the hell happened
Alright anyhow
Let's move on to some updates on the
Xbox One console
You know PlayStation 4 got its big update
And I know Xbox One's right around the corner
It's supposed to be the big backwards compatibility one right
But also some other features that are
Supposed to be in the Xbox One update
Cortana was originally
Going to I believe be a part of this
However will not
Be making a debut until
Early next year
According to Major Nelson
Unfortunately that is not going to be a part of this
Roll out however
Folks in the dashboard preview program later
This fall will be able to actually use
Cortana but I gotta be honest
I don't ever use this voice search
Stuff it doesn't seem to work
And I can't get the microphone to work on my laptop
So it's just like normally I do that
If I don't want to find Photoshop
Digging through the menus I just type Photoshop
Really I've never had any problem
With Siri
I wasn't going to use it anyway
Siri's a little different because you know that's in the palm of your hand
And that is I will say that's convenient
For Siri's going to be on the Apple TV
Remind me in 20 minutes I don't think
I would ever use it on Apple TV to be honest
But I do use Siri for
Remind me in 20 minutes to check the oven
I use Siri to text you from my watch
Do you really? Yeah I do
When I'm on my way to the show I'll just tell Rob
This and then I even have my punctuation
But see those are all portable
Things and just on something
That's on your like set top
Box I don't see a lot of use for it
I will say the thing that Apple
Is doing and maybe Microsoft's doing this
With Xbox One I don't realize it
Is that the Apple thing will
Tell you this movie's on Hulu
Or this movie's on Netflix and so on
That's useful because there's so many freaking services
Now I don't know what movie is where
Like where do I get to watch old
Episodes of Strangers with Candy with Stephen Colbert
Because it's not on Netflix but it is on Hulu
That type of search is really useful
That's actually going to be on Apple TV
Right that's what I'm saying that's one thing that I think will be
Good on Apple TV but I don't
Think it's planned for Microsoft's
Thing if it is then I guess that's something
I might use I like I just turned on
The microphone just for the fuck of it to see if
You know what would happen with
Cortana and he said there is
An eclipse try to open something
I'm like I don't know what you
Cortana just told you there's an eclipse
Yeah so there's an eclipse period and it's like
Trying to open something I'm like okay
Thank you for that information tell her to divide by
Zero and see if she makes funny like Siri does
Alright anyhow also
Some things that have been added to
The Xbox beta app in
Windows 10
So this is kind of related
Party text chat available for the
Xbox beta app members
Reading and replying to messages directly from
Notifications
Alert activity alert notifications
Like if somebody else is on Xbox
Add you as a friend or whatever
And then activity feed sharing you can share within
The activity feed so
Cool
Some additions there to Xbox
And I'm sure the
Big software update for everybody
I think that was supposed to go live in October right?
With the big backwards compatibility and all that
I think that was coming up very soon
Alright meanwhile Dark Soccer what do you have for us?
Actually I was talking to
Ikuma JP real quick
And I had like a total brain translation error
But
Siri would be Shiri
In Japan which means butt
So I wonder if you'd be like
Hey butt
Hey butt you're a butt
I'm just
Trying to help
You can friend my butt
Anyway
So Twisted Pixel
We know them right?
Splosion Man
Well you know that they
Were acquired by Microsoft in
2011 well they're going solo
They have
Had an amicable split
And they are going
On to expand their relationships
They're going to see other companies
They're going to
Be a poly
Poly gaming
They want to live the life of a single company for a while
They're gonna be swinging
Do those things they didn't get to experience five years ago
Exactly so they've had an
Enrollment
Of sorts I guess
They still had to work with the prenup
But you know
That means Splosion Man on Playstation 4 soon enough right?
Maybe
Could be
But
The Microsoft General Manager
John Needham said
I can't wait to see what this talented team creates next
And that's it
We'll see
Alright
Logie
Alright so in October
We're going to be getting some
New Playstation Plus games
Including Broken Age
Super Meat Boy
On Playstation 4
Playstation 3 Beginning Chariot
Kickbeat, Kung Fu Rabbit
And also Unmechanical Extended
And Vita, Broken Age
Kickbeat, Kung Fu Rabbit
And Super Meat Boy
Also in October
The Drive Club
Demo or whatever that was
Will be leaving as well
So be sure to download it
Before October 6
And then
Along with that
Wait why are they getting rid of it?
That seems so weird
There was this big hype up about the
Release of Drive Club on Playstation Plus
It was something they had launched
Took forever to get
And now they're going to pull it?
Was it that bad?
I thought
Some people really enjoyed it
But I found it hard to play that
After playing Forza Horizon 2
No thank you
And then along with that
Of course Super Meat Boy is going to have
Different music though on Playstation 4
And the Vita release
That's just because
The original
Audio designer has decided
Not to license the music for the new versions
Of the game so they're going to be getting other
Music
For the game
There sounds like some very interesting
Drama there because you know they're not
In specifics but it's very much
Like a I'm not going to work with them
Again type of thing
Very interesting drama there
They're basically replacing the soundtrack
They have different musicians
Including
Some of the artists that worked on
The Binding of Isaac, Rebirth
Hotline Miami and Plants vs. Zombies
Hotline Miami
Had a sick soundtrack though
It would be kind of cool to hear how it
It's going to be weird
I kind of thought some of the best
Stuff in Super Meat Boy was the music
The music was so good and fit the game
Not to say that the new soundtrack
Will be bad it's just
It's going to have big shoes to fill
It's going to almost feel like a different game
It's going to be a very interesting kind of
I don't know
Experiment
I guess for lack of a better word
In how important is the soundtrack
To a game
We'll see
The games will be up for download
On October 6th
I could also see
That maybe the whole social aspect
And the fact that the game will be shared everywhere
Maybe the guy
I don't know maybe it's just more of a personal thing
Between him and the other makers
I don't necessarily want to make stuff up
The fact that that music is going to be streamed everywhere
It has been streamed everywhere for a long time
I guess that's true
There's a lot of YouTube videos with all that
Alright
Well moving on it's a little bit of a slower news week
So we're having to dig deep a little bit here
So we're talking about website launches tonight
But I think this is interesting
It's about a topic I think a lot of people
Have an opinion about certainly
And that is game reviews
And you guys know Metacritic
And Metacritic is often controversial
Well there's a new site
That's been launched this week
That's picking up some exposure on some gaming blogs
Called Open Critic
And Open Critic is
Trying to focus on video games
But they're doing some different things with it
Such as they'll be just a simple score average
Not weighted differently from different websites
And apparently you can actually
Go in there as a user and whitelist
Different outlets
To only see reviews from
So that way if you think a particular
Website is shit
And you don't like their reviews
You can just basically
Blacklist them and they don't actually show up in the scores
That you see
And that's a very interesting concept
Because even with movies it's like
Well maybe you agree with Cisco but you don't agree with Ebert
Type of thing you know
Or whoever the, who do they have these days
There's nobody that compares to Cisco and Ebert now
Is it Roper and some other dude
But anyway you know there tends to be
Probably certain outlets that you agree with more than others
You know like vognetwork.com
Wink wink
Anyhow
It's going to be interesting to see how that goes
Also apparently one other big twist
Is going to be displaying non-numerical scores
Because
You know some websites have said
We're no longer giving games a score
And so open critic is still somehow
Going to rate that
I don't know if that's using words
Or how they're going to do that or if they're just
Assigning a score based on how the review reads
That could be very interesting and controversial
But anyway I thought that was just
Worth bringing up
Not that I usually will give these websites
Free plugs but
I do often times have conversations about
You know the importance of video game reviews
Is Metacritic helping or harming
The developing of games because we've heard about
The whole bonuses tied to Metacritic scores and all that
So it's interesting that somebody wants to
Come in and shake that up a little bit
So
Very interesting
Alright
Let's move on with the mailbag
Tonight Dark Soccer
Going to dive into the mailbag
Head first and pull out some emails
That she believes are worthy of reading
On the show, there's actually quite a bit
So I should shut up and let her get to it but I will say
If you want to email us for a future week
Participate at orangeloungeradio.com
You know I was just told today
That on the Facebook
The email address has been wrong for like
How long ago did we switch the email address?
I don't know
I totally forgot to change Facebook, it has now changed
Participate at orangeloungeradio.com
If you see the wrong email floating around out there
Please let me know, I'll fix it
Whatever the
I've got an email
That I think is in
Braille?
Oh yes, I saw
That one, there's like a bunch of coded
Text or whatever
We don't, do we
Do we have a cipher or something
To crack the code?
Nope, moving on
I guess unintelligible
Garball is what we got for an email this week
I'll
See if I can look at it later this week and translate it
But it better be good, I swear to god
If I translate it, it's like
Oh my god, Becky, stop sending me pictures of cookies
Is she listening?
No, I just messaged
I just put on Facebook, Becky cookies
And she's like, well I'm actually making some right now
And I'm like, I'm coming over after the show
If I translate that message and it's butt butt fart
I'm going to be very upset, I'm just saying
I will be
But if it's butt fart fart
Then we're fine
I just wanted to say hey butts
Hello LR
It's your friendly neighborhood alleged
Word murderer with an opinion and a serious
Question, god this is a long email
Stop it, YYR
I personally believe that the Vita's commercial
Failure in the US is almost entirely due to
The rise of smartphone gaming and
The resulting change in market
Conditions, heck the 3DS
Was almost a failure for the same reason
Have we forgotten that it sold
Miserably during its first year or so
It wasn't until Nintendo dropped the price
And a steady stream of high quality games
Released that it began to sell well
Without both of those things it would have flopped
Just as hard, the casual games that kept
The Game Boy Advance and Nintendo DS popular
Even when Nintendo wasn't
Releasing the gold
Gold the movie adaptations
The games featuring
Popular toys or kids characters
And so on
Have almost all moved to phones and tablets
Today's market has
Changed without both a low price tag
And a continuous stream of quality games
The market is done with you and therefore
It was done with the Vita very quickly
Speaking of continuous what's left in the
Pipeline for the 3DS
Most of my friends already seem to have abandoned theirs
If and when Nintendo releases a new portable
The market for them will be even tougher
Than it was this time
I wish them good luck, I really do and for the record
I love my Vita
Which, by the way
I picked up
My Vita again for like the first time
In ages when Happy Home Designer came out
Not my Vita, my DS
I haven't played my American one
Since Pixel Poops
You should lend it to us
I also got that Japanese one and then
Akuma sent me that game from Japan
And I have some other stuff to play on that
But I haven't played the American one since Pixel Poops
You should lend it to us
I might be talked into that
I'll lend you a Neo Geo Pocket Color
Alright, now I'd like to pose a question
To the panel, the chatters and really
Everyone listening
I thought of this when talking with Amy
This week about pop music
According to statistics
Everybody eventually ages out of pop music
They're no longer interested in new stuff
They're perfectly content to go back
And listen to the years with the music they
Already enjoyed for the rest of their lives
And never look forward again
On average this happens in their early to mid 30's
Though for women it happens a bit later
Than it does for men
Do you think this will also happen with all of us
In video games?
I asked this question because I'm starting to think
That this process has already begun for me
I managed to get a PS4 about a month ago
With The Last of Us for $275
Figured I'd need it eventually for Shenmue 3
So why not?
I hooked it up and downloaded the cross buy games
I already owned
Since that weekend it has never been turned on
Not even once
While this is likely partially due to
My current most played console
It feels odd to me
I haven't yet purchased Super Mario Maker
In fact I feel absolutely zero need to buy it
Any time soon even though 12 year old me
Would have put in 100 hours already
My Xbox 360, Xbox One, 3DS and Wii U
Backlogs have gotten so long that I feel like
I just don't need it
So what am I playing right now?
Sonic Adventure 2 on 360
I'm having more fun with it than I've had
With anything else I've played this year so far
Despite the fact that I 100% destroyed it
When it came out almost 15 years ago
Now I have access to over 35 years
Of video games on demand
At my fingertips
And sometimes I feel like I'd be perfectly content
Just playing what's come out already
Never looking forward again
What are your thoughts on this?
And do you think you'll personally reach this point?
I'd also love to know what the listeners think
And if this doesn't become a future foogle question
I hope they'll respond via email or in some other way
Looking to spare Rob
From the year old jokes
YYR
You know what? I actually think this is a great question
But I'm gonna say that
And I would pose this to our chatters
If we do have any quick responses
I'll read those out on air
But are video games gonna go the way
Where as you get older you're not gonna be able to appreciate
The new stuff like you appreciate the old stuff
But see I would actually say that I'm not sure
What you said at the very beginning
Is even accurate
That we don't understand pop music today
I mean for me personally
And everybody's different
And that's the first thing to remember
But for me personally
There is some newer music that I actually really enjoy
Some of it I don't understand
At all
Like One Direction
That's not music
But you know
Younger girls would disagree with you
There's a difference between
Cookie cutter pop
And actual pop music
I do but I also think a lot of it's relative
Music is music
But like the new Church's album
Is what I've been listening to
Like non-stop
It's so fucking good that just came out like last week
Or me and Mystery Skulls
But is Church's really pop music?
I don't know
The new Carly Rae Jepsen album
And I feel so embarrassed saying that
Because I know how tacky
That Call Me Maybe got
But her new album with new stuff is actually really cool
I really like it
But I am also
So looking forward to
The 20 year anniversary
And if you know me you know why
Of Jagged Little Pill
With demos from the 90's that have been unreleased until now
Like I cannot wait for that
And I listen to ABBA all the time
So I kind of get both sides of it
So for video games it's actually
Kind of similar
Like there's some new stuff
I don't really understand and I'm not sure
I'm ever going to and for me that would be stuff like
A lot of sports games
Madden, that's just a train
I'm never going to be able to get on
Call of Duty for me
But I understand for Loki
He's got to play them all and that's cool
And I only play them for a little bit now
I really need to go back to Advanced Warfare
Why did I buy the season pass if I'm not going to play online?
But
There's some games
That take me a while to understand
And appreciate later
I think Minecraft is the quintessential example
I didn't get Minecraft at first
What so ever
And it wasn't until the 360 version
Came out that framed the game a little differently
Where I was totally on board
And I was like okay I understand Minecraft
This game is an awful lot of fun
But Minecraft was always bigger with I think a younger
Generation before I got it
And this isn't even unique to video games
Because Snapchat
Do you know how popular Snapchat is?
And I didn't understand it
At all
Until Alan finally sat me down and was like
This is why people use it
And you can create stories
And it's just a fun way for you to look
And you can send people messages and all this stuff
I just thought it was a way to send people dick pics
I thought it was just for dick pics and nothing else
But no apparently there's this whole other
Like it's huge
People use Snapchat to communicate like a lot
But
But anyway
I kind of think that analogy
Kind of works
For a lot of different things
But I also don't necessarily
Think it's accurate to say that for
All people you're not going to be
Into necessarily newer pop music
And newer things
It can also be that like a lot of pop music nowadays is cookie cutter
I mean granted a lot of pop music back in
The 80's was cookie cutter too but for some reason
It's just I don't know
Because it's age!
Well now also you have like at least back then
It was more like
You actually had to sing it nowadays
So you can sample and just
Throw your voice through a computer
And
I know I might be weird
And you guys are going to disagree with me
I see that in some ways as another instrument
Like you know
We kind of laugh at some of the people
Who overuse it
But like with like Cher's Believe
That is a great pop song
And it just would not be the same without the
Do you believe in like
The way it sounds like a computer
The major autotune
The obvious autotune
Ok but here's the thing
You can make fun of that but then on the other hand
Ok I'm going to watch this
You can go to Kate Bush
And what she did
She did like this whole like reimagining
Of some of her pop songs and in some of it
She uses that whole like
Autotune stuff as art
I need to get that
And you can't fucking tell me that Kate Bush
It's not
Kate Bush is like progressive rock
Imogen Heap with
Hide and Seek
Everybody knows that song from the Dear Sisters
See that was like
Autotune as an instrument in a way
So it's like
Church's does the same thing
So I'm not necessarily
I don't necessarily subscribe to the fact that autotune is always bad
Do some people abuse it? Sure
Or Lord
Well all the background singing and
Instrumentation was her
So my favorite Lord meme
Will always be the whole like where she posted
The thing on her Instagram that says
It was graffiti that says Lord help me
And it was spelled L-O-R-D-E
And she just put as the caption I'm on my way
That's cute
Anyway
Darktitsuyu in chat says
I do kind of miss the stuff we listened to
Back in the early 2000's when we did the original
Show. You know it doesn't seem
I've been trying to see if they make Eurodance
Kind of like that and I feel like it's more
Evolved into like that
The trance and the Euro vocal trance
Which isn't bad by any means
I love that stuff and I listen to a lot of stuff
On Spotify
Is there any more from what's that artist
That kind of partnered up with Paul Terry there for a little bit
Orbitribe?
Oh I have no idea I have to check
Spotify. I just know Armin Van Buren
I swear to God is putting out a compilation every week
And a podcast
He's got a great ear
I could listen to any of those mixes he does
It's great
On a tangent I guess I got away a little bit
From the original question
I don't even remember what the original question was
Okay the original question was
Pop music we tend to not
Listen to the new stuff and focus on the stuff we
Enjoyed as kids. Is that going to be the same situation
With video games?
I am just saying
To be honest although I completely see your point
Your analogy is not always true
So therefore no
I think I'm pretty interested in
Games coming out now
Just there's only certain games I want
I think now it's like
I don't have Blockbuster and stuff where I could rent
Games for five bucks and just play everything
Now it's just kind of more selective
About it
I kind of have a better idea what my tastes are
And also you know it used to be that
The only exposure on
What a game is was from looking at the box
Hmm does this look interesting?
I guess we'll rent it
I don't have like now where the internet
You see trailers, you watch the impressions of it
You hear people talk about it, read the reviews
I mean there's a lot to it
You know what's interesting though?
And to give YYR the benefit of the doubt
I just saw this comment in chat
And I'm sorry
You're going to think I'm yelling at you and I swear I'm not
I respect your opinion. Kasan in our chat room
Says I can't think of
Three good music videos from the 90s
And I'm sitting here about to flip a table
I'm like what? What are you talking about?
There wasn't three good videos from the 1990s
Oh my god like some of the greatest music
Videos were from the 1990s
Like you know
I for one think Alanis
Ironic was a fantastic
Video at the time. Madonna did
So many great videos in the 90s like Ray of Light
That Jamiroquai
Virtual Insanity was so cool
All Gorillaz videos?
That was...
I mean my god there's a ton of good stuff
How many other Michael Jackson videos?
So I kind of look at that comment and go
What the fuck are you?
Again you're welcome to your opinion
And that goes to show that YYR to your point
I think the opposite might be true
Most of the time
Not all the time
But I think the opposite
And what I mean by that is I think people today
Who grew up on PlayStation 2
Like don't know a world
With anything older than a PlayStation 2 or 3
I think those people
Have a much harder time
Going back to NES
Atari 2600
And appreciating the value of those games
The way that we can
Most of the time
Not saying all the time because certainly there's gonna be
Like that 18 year old that listens to OLR
That says whoa you're wrong
My son refers to anything that
Is 8-bit as Minecraft
So he's just like
So that game looks like Minecraft
So that comment kind of made me think
Because I'm sitting here going what are you talking about
And I'm thinking well maybe
He doesn't have that same perspective
That I do because I lived it
You know and if you're younger
You didn't have the emotional attachment to those videos
The way maybe that I do
And so I think with video games
To YYR's point that's very true
So YYR I actually think
The complete opposite of what you said is what's true
If that makes sense
Anyway
There you go and now everybody in chat is like
Naming off great 90s music videos
Smashing pumpkins oh my god
So many amazing 90s music videos
Sabotage by Beastie Boys
Smack My Bitch Up by Prodigy
Remember the big twist in that video
And that was a controversial one I got banned from MTV
Anyway I just want to say
I'm not yelling at you
Your point just kind of made me go
What? For a minute
So anyway
Let's move on next email
There are still a few
So next email comes
From Robert M
Do any of you yet know whether
The bases of Lego Dimensions
Figures slash builds are able
To store data such as studs collected
Alternate builds, experience levels
And so on nope
I do not know the answer I will in a week
But I'm sure we have some people in our chat
Who have played the game who know that
Do the Lego Dimensions characters save
Information
Cause Amiibos can do that right
Amiibos do it Skylanders do it
I'll give some information cause you can take them to different
Does it? Okay
Maybe somebody in chat can
Fill us in with a little more information on how that works
Cause even though I bought it today I haven't played it yet
So Brad from Pop Culture
Jumping in to say the vehicles do
There you go
Alright
There's the best answer I can get for now
Alright next email
Eating's Grey and Way Allutation
Says sorry Jamie it's been a while since I've
Messed with Grandpa by using Pig Ladin
Oh I already know who this is
I couldn't help myself by the way I just
Caught up on all OLR episodes and I'm
Happy to hear Rob is thinking about bringing back
That Wednesday show out from
Hiatus
Quickly it's not just my decision
To make that clear
It's something that Extra for myself
And Grandpa are all talking about
And even inviting
If Shane wants to be a part of it he certainly can
Although if he doesn't then we respect that too
Not to get too
Tangeny sorry I'm interrupting
Darkseiders email but I think people want to know
Right now really for us
We're all kind of burned out on online games
Like you know I don't even
Really play Final Fantasy 14 these days
Just because there's a real lull
Between content patches
I don't think Grandpa's playing anything but maybe
Heroes of the Storm I'm playing Diablo 3 granted
But we need to find a new focus
And once that's
What the three of us have to sit down and figure out
So it's almost like starting a new podcast
And we realize
There's a lot of people out there
Who really don't care what we talk about
Because they're tuning in to hear Grandpa and Extra for
Gang up on me which is fine
But once we figure out what that
Supposed topic of the show is going to be
And how that format is going to work
It'll be back in some form
Which reminds me I need to talk to you about something
Okay
Anyway
I know you guys
Have been wiping on that difficult boss
Known as real life but I'm confident
That you guys will pull through as you always do
As long as Rob keeps up with his heels
And Grandpa keeps his drink on
Because he's better at DPS when he's drunk
Extra is perfect the way he is tanking
And spanking
I will pass that message along
And Grandpa is back from
His big NBA trip
He went over
He gallivanted across Europe and had beer from all over
And supposedly under the guise of education
Yeah
So anyway
A little bit of news came out
Last week on Digital Card Gaming front
As some of you might have heard
In Spring 2014
Wizards of the Coast slash Hasbro filed a lawsuit
Against Cryptozoic Entertainment
The lawsuit stated that
Cryptozoic's digital card game released
Hex Shards of Fate
Infringed on Wizards of the Coast
Hasbro's card game Magic the Gathering
In regards to copyright, trade dress, and patent claims
I remember this
Well I'm happy to say that the lawsuit has been settled
As of Thursday of last week
Link below
HexTCG.com slash press dash release dash settlement
However
Those who have read the press release
May have noticed the word license
Has shown up twice
Although details of the settlements are unknown
The appearance of the word license
Make the story a little interesting
For me at least
Regardless I'm glad to know that the matter has been settled
And I hope that this
Bit news will ease
The concerns of would be hex players
Who might have been put off by the lawsuit
My question to you guys
In chat is this
We all know that copyright laws are extremely out of date
I understand that we're all not lawyers and senators
As far as I know
But imagine if you could change those laws
How would you change them in accordance
To the technological age we live in today
I'm not a lawyer
It'd have to be revamped
With all due respect
That is such a deep question
I'm not sure I can think of an answer on the spot
About how to fix it
I want a politician to tell me how they're going to do it
And I'm going to nod and say that sounds good
How would you do it?
I would think it would be a lot harder
To trademark
Very vague, broad
Things
That seems to be a lot of the problem
Is just the broadness
That people can actually patent
And the fact that
I don't want to say you can't patent ideas
Because I realize that defeats the purpose
But I gotta say
Since you're listening to old episodes of OLR
I really truly think
We have what? 616 episodes of the show we've done
If there's like 10 OLR episodes
You must listen to before you die
That episode that Kyle Ward was on
A couple months ago
And sorry I don't remember the number off the top of my head
I need to crowd source that one for a minute
Dark Tetsuya what number was that?
That is one of the 10 episodes you need to hear of OLR
Because
Kyle talking about
What he went through with his game
And what he realized about these various
Patents that Konami actually owned
We were sitting here going
Thank you 596
I knew it was right before 600
That is one of the 10 I truly feel
I can't believe you can actually Google our episodes
Would you guys agree with me?
I think that's really one of the 10 best episodes we ever did
And just that insight
That he really gave us into that
And kind of how the sausage is made
Sort of thing
I really think kind of plays into exactly why you're seeing the word license
I think Wizards of the Coast
Or whatever had some type of patent
In this thing that had
Hex by the balls that they couldn't get out of
And so they had to license it
And I don't think the fans
Should lash out at Hex for this
I think the fans should take their case to
Wanting this patent law reformed
And how was a patent granted
For this in the first place
Question mark
I think the rules about what we do
And what we don't patent
Need to be more clearly defined
I can see them with patenting the rules of the game
Or something like that
And if they're copying the exact rules of the game
Then there could be issues
But I think general
Patents for just like
Arrows scrolling up a screen
Or method to blah blah blah
I think they should be granted
For a couple years and then that's it
Make your money off of it
And then it goes public domain
Kind of like how medicine is
When you find a drug that's patented for what
7 years and you get to make it
And then that's it
Then it can go generic after that
Because that 7 years is long enough
Especially with an idea like arrows
Scrolling up the screen
Look how long DDR lasted
It's really not around anymore
It is not the cultural thing it was
When we first started doing OLR
You know so I think these ideas
Kind of have their cycle
And then they kind of come and go
And look what happened with the plastic instruments and all that
Well you know who's pushing for all that
Copyright stuff to be extended out
Disney
Absolutely
Well because they're scared as hell what's going to happen
When Mickey Mouse goes in the public domain
I mean I could
I could put a picture
I mean I guess I could do this today under parody law
Technically but I could sell a shirt
Of me pooping on Mickey Mouse
I could sell a shirt
And there's nothing they could do to stop me
Once Mickey Mouse is in the public domain
That's what they're afraid of
You want to charge like $200
For me to go to Disneyland
I'm going to make my own Disneyland
I could have a picture of a shirt
I could have a picture of a shirt with Mickey Mouse
On it that says I love dick
And there's nothing they could do about it
Now they can because I can't sell that shirt
I mean I could do it under parody
If I put it onto my Twitter account they can't do anything
But if I sell a shirt with Mickey Mouse
That says I love dick they could sue me
But they won't once
Mickey goes in the public domain so you're right
Disney is scared as hell of that stuff
Banksy just did it with Dismaland
Oh that's right
But he didn't use the characters exactly
And you could kind of say that's parody
It was parody it was also a political statement
But yeah
Boy did we get on a tangent with that email
We do that here at OLR don't we
Alright
P.S. Rob I'm happy to
Know that you're starting to fulfill the first
Part of your new years resolution
In regards to streaming yes I did watch the
Broadcasting of your stream from yesterday
However I've yet to see
That platinum that you were hoping
To get on Diablo 3 PS4
Which was the second part of your new years
Resolution lol
It's all good Rob not all of us are meant to achieve
Platinum status in games
Snuggles and huggles to you all
Not so sincerely degenerate Johnny
I've got three months left
Here's what's going to do me in I'm not going to have
The vacation time over the holidays like I had
Last year because of the job switch so
I don't know we'll see we'll see
I'm also actually considering
Doing like a weekly twitch again
Because you know how I was
Playing hot to full boyfriend
I'm actually just thinking about doing just
Jamie fucks around in Dragon Age
And cheats
As long as you kind of like give commentary and talk
Through it it could be very interesting
I just like playing the game
And like answering people
We talked about this last week though where it's just different
Depending on the stream you know I did a Diablo 3
You guys have to tell me what you think of this I don't think
Anybody saw it but it's on my archive
Twitch TV slash Rob Roberts
Maybe I'll do it again tonight if I have time
I was playing some Diablo 3 yesterday because for me
PC streaming is the easiest but
Using that new game show software I actually
Set up different camera things
So that like when I was in between stages
It was my little cam you could see my cam
And the Diablo screen I would kind of talk to the camera
And then I could even click a button
And it would make the screen even smaller and you would
See the chat room and I would respond to chat comments
Although there weren't a lot yesterday because it was Saturday afternoon
But then when I actually went into the Rift
And I was doing heavy game playing
I clicked another button and made the game full screen
And I just talked over it and I thought that was
Like I like being able to switch between
Them I think is even better
Than just a static image that's what I would like
To do more of in the future but that game show right now
Is kind of limiting on
Some features but
Anyway I'll get into that at a later time
I gotta let Jamie finish the email
Hey OLR Delvin here
From Video Game Realness, long time listener
First time emailer Delvin is
Awesome and he's my podcasting buddy
On a seasonal show, reading is fundamental
Did you know I did a show on RuPaul's Drag Race?
We do a podcast
The listeners might not
And knowing is half the battle
This past weekend
Was the start of a League of Legends
World Championship and I have been watching
A fair amount of it
Despite being terrible at the game
I have been playing League of Legends for a few years now
Also have friends who have played it
Since the game first came out
To see where the game started
And what it has become over the past few years
Is incredibly mind boggling in a good way
As far as the esports scene
For the game goes, it started out as friends
Who were good at the game, made teams
And competed at local or national events
And now has grown into a full fledged sport
Having managers, sponsors, drafts
And large amounts of viewers and teams
That have become full on brands
And household names among the gaming community
I'm curious to know
What is OLR's thoughts on esports
Mainly League of Legends has become
And do you see it as good or bad for gaming?
Your pal, Delvin, Video Game Realness
P.S. For those who don't know
Rob has a long lost brother who plays League of Legends
Professionally for Cloud9 Gaming
Under the name LemonNation, look it up
I'm not really good at them, therefore I don't really have much of an interest in them
But it's not that I want to see these games tank
Because I don't
I don't carry that negativity
And I think the money that gets poured into this stuff
I mean, A. It's exposure for gaming
It's more of a positive image for gaming
That it's not all necessarily
Just like guns blazing
And Doom and Mortal Kombat
Ripping heads off of bodies and stuff
It kind of gets a little more into that
Strategical side of games
So I like that that's kind of what's out there
More and more in the populace
And with TBS taking on some Counter-Strike
Next year and so forth
A little more of the
Strategical and the actual game side of things
But I personally
It's hard
I try to watch it and I'm just kind of like
I don't understand what the fuck's going on
But I did
Shane and I watched on Twitch a little bit of the
Heroes of the Storm stuff
A lot of my co-workers play that
Which is basically
League of Legends dumbed down
For people like me
Blizzard is A plus
Pro at dumbing games down
And making them accessible and that's not a bad thing at all
That's just what they do
And they're going to do it with the Team Fortress thing
And the first person shooter with this game they're making now
Overwatch
Anyway
Shane and I did watch some of that
I was kind of into it
Because at least I understand this game
But do I get caught up in the celebrity
Of it all and that end of it?
Not really
That I'm not really so into
And I'm not sure I understand
That yet
And that's what I struggled with a little bit at TwitchCon
As well is that
I guess I'm surrounded by a lot of famous people
But they're just
Other con-goers to me
I'm not really caught up in that celebrity
But at the same time
They have no idea what the fuck I'm doing
With a podcaster that I'm part of
The longest running video game podcast on the internet
They don't know that
It's this interesting kind of like other side
I don't know how to phrase it
But yeah
I guess that's my very long winded thoughts on that
Overall I think it's a good thing
It presents a good image
For video gaming and gaming culture
But I have a really hard time
Getting wrapped up in the celebrity
And especially over that particular game
It's just not one I'm thrilled about
But I don't want you to take that as like a negative
That I hate it because I don't
Okay cool
It's just like football
I don't hate football, it's just not for me
I like hockey though
And I bet SSJ100Matt's happy to hear that
I like hockey, that I understand
So there you go
That's my thoughts on the email
I don't know if you guys have something to add
Or if anybody in chat is saying anything on that
Seattle in chat says
The only Blizzard game I really really want to play
And maybe Starcraft 2
I love Diablo 3
But like I'm terrible at Starcraft 2
I am terrible at it
I will say when I've watched the professional Starcraft 2 stuff
I'm just like how do they fucking know what to do so fast
But then I think back to
When you and I
All of us here
Used to play
DDR back at Roseville Golfland
And we were doing songs like Orion 7-8
With the note chart that's just all the arrows
Smashed together
Like that's how fast your feet are moving right?
And like when people would watch us
Play that they were probably like
How the hell do they move their feet that fast
How do they read that
I can't do that anymore
But it was practice
And a real love of the game
And just playing it over and over and over again
And so I get it
That's what they're doing in Starcraft 2
Is that they know all the keyboard shortcuts
And that crazy shit because they really love the game
And they learned it
So anyway
That's my thoughts
My long winded thoughts as usual
I don't know if you guys want to add anything
And that was it for email
That's it for email that was a long email segment tonight
But very good you guys did a very good job tonight
Participate at OrangeLoungeRadio.com
And now
That that is over it is time
To get a little bit angsty
Here at OLR with a segment we call
The FUs of the Week
And why do we get so angry here at OLR?
Well we have issues
A major FU to my digestive system
I'm sure people remember a couple weeks ago
I was out sick
Like sick sick
Like quarantine sick
And it turns out that I still have a problem
They actually don't know that because I blamed it
On the Jewish holiday that was going on at the time
Well I mean that's originally why I was going to be out
But it turned out that I ended up being told
Don't go out among people
Gotcha
So I still have the problem
For the last week or so
I haven't been able to eat more than about
600 calories worth of stuff a day
Oh my gosh
And I've had to go a few days without any coffee
Which is difficult
So I
Yeah, screw it
I hate it
I like pie and I'm going to eat pie tonight and if it makes me sick
Oh well
Pie is awesome
Loki, how about you?
I guess my FU of the Week is going to be going
To
Just
I don't know
Not being able to find the right font for my stupid
Games logo
Because I know what it is
Try Papyrus
Or Comic Sans
Don't you fucking dare
Or the best thing I've ever seen called
Comic Papyrus
Actually I'll show you a funny one
Is Comic Slab
It's basically Comic Sans
But done with a slab serif
So it's kind of funny
We'll see
I will
Check those out I guess
So that's what I've been working on this week
And wasting so much time doing so
By the way I have like a million fonts now and none of them
Seems to be good enough
My FU of the Week
Goes to Shane for being an enabler
And just watching me spend all that money today
And not trying to do anything
To stop it
That's fair, right?
Alright, there it is
The FU of the Week segment
By the way, Hitstun in chat over at
Live.vognetwork.com saying
That Hitstun has finished
Loki's castle level and saying
My FU of the Week goes to Jigsaw's Castle of Carnage
So there you go Loki, somebody beat him
There you go
How many tries did it take you Hitstun?
I just want to know
Alright, anyhow
Let's get to a couple more news stories and then we'll get to the Skype line
Which I'm only going to leave open for a little bit tonight
So if you want to get through you better be fast
And I'll let you know when that's open here in just a moment
Now Hitstun says 20 tries
That's still really good
Yeah, it's better than I did
So Jeremy's level is from Koopa Club
He did some, I swear to god
I died like 70 times on one of them
I will have to try this
And I was cursing his name in 7 different languages
More news stories, Loki
Alright, so beat Takashi
Is going to be in the new Yakuza game
That's pretty cool
Let's see
Apparently
I'm not really sure who
Is supposed to be in the actual game here
Did you watch the little trailer thing?
Nope, I did not
Okay, so someone posted on Twitter
Just the back of his head
And said, guess who's going to be in the next Yakuza game
And I was like, oh it's Kitano Takashi
And I only knew it from the back of his head
But I knew that he also did a bunch of Yakuza movies
Like that was his thing
And then I saw the little trailer and it's totally his voice
So
Neat
Cool
That's all I got
I just thought you'd enjoy that because I know you were a big fan of Takashi's castle
I was
I really wish they'd bring
I just
That's what I want
I want like a channel of just
Subtitled
Japanese game shows
Is that like a thing that can happen?
Because I know
It's got to be out there
Because they used to record that stuff for our Japanese class
So I think they have like a local channel
In San Francisco or something
They've got to have
Because we used to watch
Furuhata
Oh god I love Furuhata
There is a channel in the bay area
That does all Japanese TV
Mostly like dramas and game shows
That's what I want
Japanese game show channel
And I need to watch
More Silent Library because that was also funny
That was the closest thing I had to a Japanese game
Was that the MTV?
It was
It was so stupid
It was like a Japanese game show
It was really stupid
That show kind of got it
When they try to bring that stuff over here
Like with the hole in the wall
They lose it's charm
They're like
Oh that's what they did
And they just make a really terrible knock off
It doesn't have the same
I don't know
Like seriousness
Perfect example
Like some of the cooking competition shows
In Iron Chef Japan
It was very serious
And very artful
Iron Chef America is like
The pompousness
And grandstanding of it all is what made that show
Great and when they brought it to the US
It was kind of like I'm his cousin
I do things differently
Woo
It's sort of
It's still good but it lost
That charm to it
Agree
She links us to
Actually a pretty awesome movie called Outrage
That has
Takeshi in it
Very cool
Alright well one more story for you guys
About and some of you might have heard about this
But did you know there was an unreleased
And unfinished South Park game
It was apparently cancelled
It was on the Xbox
The first Xbox
I almost said the Xbox one
But I made the first Xbox
And yeah if you actually watch some of the video
I mean this is a very early build
I mean half the town is not even finished
But it moves around in a 3D
Environment which is very interesting to see
And it's not at all like
South Park 64
Yeah it kind of looks a little more like South Park 64
But with better polygons
And so forth
But it looks like they even had some cut scenes
That were in there and some of the voice acting was done
There was a workable combat system in place
Cartman can actually fight dogs
In one part of it
So that's kind of neat
Buzz Monkey was the studio that made
The game and it was eventually snapped up
By Zynga and became a part of that collective
But the game never happened
And I don't know if that's because I think it was a little late
In the Xbox's life that this was being put
Together and maybe they decided not to do it
But we still have the fractured
Butthole which I
I will never get over that title
That is still coming
I think I'm going to make that my goal this week
To go back and play signature
Because I never finished it on Xbox
And I need to go play it
And finish it before I get to the fractured
Butthole
Now when they release that are they going to include the first game
With that too because I think that's coming out on PlayStation 4
Because that would be pretty cool if they did
I don't think that's part of the plan
Because it's a different studio doing it too
That's too bad
I think the game itself will be different
But as long as, I mean if Trey and Matt are still involved
They'll have that same humor
Which is usually on point
It depends what season it is
Sometimes it's on point, sometimes it's
I miss a lot of South Park
It's one of those shows I forget is on
Because it's so infrequent that there's new episodes
And then when you happen to see it on TV
It's like oh god this episode is ages old
But then when you remember
Oh yeah there's a new South Park on you watch it
Most of the time it's really
Really funny and on point
I just don't like the multi story arcs
They do the four episode long
God, one of them they did was awful
It was Imaginationland
I didn't like that one at all
I liked that, that was fine
Some of the other ones are coming
Exactly, anyway
Phone lines are open
1-877-GAMELR or our username on Skype
OrangeLoungeRadio
If you want to give us a call
We'll be happy to have you on the show
We're only going to keep this open for a little bit
So if you want to call
Try to get in now
It's almost 9 o'clock here on the west coast
Which means midnight on the east coast
And lucky us we have a call coming in already
So let's get to it
Hi you're on OrangeLoungeRadio, who's this?
Hey guys it's Jason
Hey Jason, oh my gosh are you driving right now?
I am hands free
I have my headset in my phone
I am in the high country of California
Just about to hit Truckee here
Probably about the time this call is going to be over
No I know you're a good boy
And you wouldn't drive
And have the hands and all that
But I can hear that rushing wind sound
Of the car
So sad you came right through Sacramento
But couldn't stop by tonight because you're on a schedule
I understand
I'm already a little bit behind because I am
A wonderful procrastinator
And we'll just leave it at that
As long as you waved when you went by Sacramento
I absolutely did
I saw all the buildings and I was like I think it's that way
You
You felt my presence
As long as that's the case I'm happy
What's on your mind tonight? You must be listening in the car
What's up?
I am here with your weekly
Twitch report
I think I mentioned
Last week that I am
Predominantly a variety
I follow variety streams
The
Extent of esports and streaming for me
Is I watched a couple of the internationals
And then I follow a couple of
Speedrunners which are definitely
Kind of in the middle ground but they still have their personality
That they put into it
But I am predominantly a variety caster
But I still kind of pay attention to
Trends
Twitch really likes putting the top games
In your face especially on the mobile app
That being the default view so you see this kind of stuff
And the obvious
Trends like variety casters still have
Their
Trope caliber expectations
Everybody's breaking out the scary
Games for October
Have we covered
Until dawn?
Whoa what do you mean by covered
Because sorry I just dropped my phone
Literally while you were talking
Was there anything
I'm not actually sure how old the game is
It's less than a year and a half
Because it's modern consoles
Was there
With Five Nights at Freddy's
Kind of
Spearheading the fear
Of the games and that kind of stuff
And everybody trying to be into this space
That series
Until Dawn
Stoma
What are some of the newer ones I can't even think of
Me personally I follow some stuff with Fatal Frame 5
I'll tell you where we're at
With Until Dawn is that
That game actually only came out probably about six weeks ago
It's not an incredibly old game
It's been out for about a month
And actually I think that was the last livestream
I did for my Playstation 4
It made me play it
And yeah
It is another one of those scary games
And it's like I just knew
Do you want to walk left or walk right
And I'm like great
Which direction is going to get my head chopped off
And which one is going to get me to safety
I kind of can't deal with that type of pressure
It's scary
But yeah
You know what's interesting
Is I really think Sony wrote that game off
I really do
They originally wrote that game off
And I think it has to do with the performance
Of The Order
And I don't know what those games have in common
Besides the fact that they were both early showcased games
For Playstation
But I don't think Sony has thrown a lot of oomph behind that game
But I think
Because of livestreaming
In large part
I think that game is doing a whole lot better
And unfortunately we lost Jason
And knowing where he is in California right now
If he's coming through Truckee
I'm in the mountain ranges of California right now
And so I'm actually trying to call him back
I don't usually do this
But for Jason who does a lot of favors for OLR
I will make phone
I think we have him back
Hi Jason are you back with us
Maybe
Jason I know you're in the high country in California right now
So your signal probably sucks
But I'm hoping you understand me
So I was just saying that Until Dawn
I actually think it's kind of gained that cult status
In a way
In a big way
But I bet that game is doing better than they expected
And I actually think livestreaming
Absolutely plays into that
Because that game does lend itself pretty well
Because you know there's people out there going
And it's like participating with a bad movie
Don't go back there
People in the live feed or whatever can scream
Don't go left, don't go left
And either the person is an idiot and goes left
And gets their head chopped off or whatever
So anyway
Did you have some thoughts on that you wanted to try and get out
I was mostly curious about how old it is
Because of the variety rounds that it's making right now
Like I said I didn't think it was too particularly old
And it's strange to think that with the prime season
That applies to the theme of the game
That they would already kind of like set it aside
But I really hope that they've seen successes with it
Because the sheer amount of play time
I think I saw it at number 25 on the top games on Twitch
And you know that kind of stuff
It only takes one influential streamer to crack the top 20
But certainly with the rotation
People saving it closer to Halloween
And all that kind of stuff
That's a big deal to have that
I'm not hearing anything about scary game lineups this year
You're cutting out a little bit again
But I think especially this really is that time of year for scary game streaming
And yeah I think Until Dawn is going to be a part of that
I don't know if you heard, not to shift things radically
But I don't know if you heard the Jackbox interview earlier in the show
But they were talking a little bit about how streaming is really kind of
And almost I kind of feel like in that interview
Is a part of the reason why You Don't Know Jack isn't a part of this second box
Is that well we wanted to focus on games that were better for streaming
And multiplayer and so forth
And that was kind of a, like it made a lot of sense when he said it
And I was like wow that's kind of neat
So, anyway
I think unfortunately Jason is cutting out again
So I'm going to have to go ahead and end the call
And just hope that he has a safe drive
On his way back there
And hopefully he'll be able to hear this on the podcast feed or something else later
But I am going to go ahead and open up the Skype line again
At 1877 Game OLR
Or username on Skype Orange Lounge Radio
You know we don't often get called from moving vehicles
So that one was a little bit special
But anyway it is lighting up again
So let's get to the next call
Hi you're on Orange Lounge Radio, who's this?
Hello Rob
Hey it's Marissa, how are you?
I'm good, how are you?
Good, great to hear from you, what's on your mind my friend?
I feel very rude
Because I only had the opportunity to tune in just now
But I'm always happy to hear the show
That's okay, it's a long show
It's a long commitment to listen to the whole show, I understand
That's true
Yeah I was out and about also
But you were talking about scary games
And actually Chris and I have been playing
The Walking Dead game together
And slowly and surely we've been learning
That I'm the more depraved one
Based on our decisions
So you let that person live
You're an asshole
We learn new things about each other
So in other words
With the difficult choices you make in that game
For instance, there's some scenes
In that game where it's like, do you want to save
This person or this person
And so you probably, you know, save a person
And so Chris will probably
You know, be like, why would you want to save that person?
Right, you guys kind of get into those type of arguments
I've learned that I am a cold ass
Motherfucker
And my boyfriend
Is a sweet, thoughtful man
That's what I have learned
Like why would you let that person
Live, he was an asshole anyway
You know
He was dead weight, you gotta keep moving honey
Now I'm sure you are sweet and thoughtful
Aplenty in real life
But it's just the video games bring out
The worst in you, which is fine
It happens to me too
Yeah, don't defend the media's position, right?
Exactly
Actually
I did have some
Some news too, it's not directly
Game related, but for anybody that likes
Sci-fi or on the video
Game side, for anyone that
Really enjoyed The Scarecrow
Scarecrow
I've had a long day
Not the most recent
But the previous Batman games
Is played by Dino Andrade
I'm part of an audio
Podcast or radio drama
With our friend Ben, who has called in a few times
He also hosts the show Port Center
On YouTube
And we're releasing one a month
It's called Jump Leads, it was based on a popular webcomic
So I'm excited to announce
That for anybody that likes Red Dwarf
And Doctor Who
And everything British and fun
I feel like I've known Dino
Online forever
We've followed each other on Twitter
Since the beginning
I missed him at Dragon Con
Because you never know what the schedule
Is actually going to be
I've got to message him offline
Now that things have calmed down a bit
Hopefully with convention season
And try to get him on the show
He's one of the best voice actors here
At Orange Launch Radio
Have you guys talked about the strike?
We brought it up last week
I wasn't sure if I wanted to go there with you
But since you said it
I'm going to go there
I actually did repost
The thing with the terms of the strike
And the link to vote on it
On my public Facebook
My understanding is that
They've gone radio silent on that
We know it's a possibility
We don't know if it's actually happening
Or not yet, right?
Yeah, it's been pretty quiet
And you know
It's funny because out of all the nuances
Of the whole argument
The only thing that I find the most interesting
Were people talking about other sides of the industry
Not perhaps being fairly compensated
And why should you worry about the actors
First, and I kind of thought
So you're saying that everyone should just be equally
Screwed?
You know what?
I think a lot of the concerns
And I'm not going to be one to get into the money
Because I don't know how that all works
But as far as the whole
Having certain rules
Like going into the studio and screaming
For four hours on end
What's funny is that when you helped us out
And we got Greg
And those guys on the show
The fact that they were talking about
Oh, does your agent make sure that you only get the two
It kind of dawned on me
Oh yeah, not everybody gets that
So kind of setting those sort of
What are essentially safety
Safe working conditions
I think is more than fair
So for that side of things
And again, I'm not going to get into the money things
I just don't know
But as far as those safety conditions
That seems awfully reasonable
It is, you know I did
I've done things where I've blown out my voice
I didn't have certainly any protections like that
People think that
This is a problem that just doesn't affect just acting
But any career where there's some sort of artistic end to it
They think because you get some sort of satisfaction out of it
That it's okay
Or it's not a big deal
Well yeah, it's not okay if you scream once
But if you scream for four hours
You can ruin your instrument
And video games
For actors it can be
One of the most rewarding
Because of the amount of dialogue
And story can also be one of the most grueling
But you know
On the money thing
Regardless of the specifics
People deserve to be compensated
Fairly for their time
No matter what their job is
Of course
This also goes out to all my friends
That are graphic designers
People that work in fields
That involve computers
Or musicians or photographers
Where people go
My nephew is good with computers
So I'll just have them do it
You want things done right
You need skilled, hardworking people
And I've heard most often
The argument about how
Certain sides of the video game industry
Aren't fairly compensated
Well everybody should be then
I know what to tell you
There's a lot of people
There's a lot of people out there that say
Well if the voice actors just go on strike
And do it for free
But you are right in that regard
That well you'll get what you pay for
And we'll be back in the era of 90's CD-ROM games
When the acting wasn't quite what it is today
If that makes sense
Well you know that's
That's kind of affected
The industry as a whole
I mean again it's not just voice acting
That's been affected by this proliferation of
Competition for jobs on the internet
And driving down of prices
But you know that aside
It is interesting when I see people that say that
Well I'll just do it for really cheap
And then I'm going to get this great exposure
And this great gig
Well that's wonderful but
That sustaining career that you want
Isn't going to be there for you then
At the end of the day
So you're like
Oh I'll do this thing really cheap right now
And that's going to give me all the exposure I need
And that's going to skyrocket me to the top
When I'm going to do what I love for a living
But if you do that then that career isn't going to exist
Well I hope they can
I hope they can all work it out
I hope they can hug it out
And figure this stuff out
And you have some support in chat
In our chatroom over at live.fognetwork.com
I'm definitely with Marissa on this one
And Dungeon Buster says that could be the future
Without skilled voice actors
Not even the 90's look up
Chaos Wars voice acting on Google or YouTube
Classic 90's bad acting
Resident Evil nuff said says Raginator
Anyway
You know what? This is easy
So you deserve to be played less
Yeah but I
I mentioned this last week on the show
When I've done Rocky Horror and emceed that show
And I'm on stage for maybe 20-30 minutes
And I'm kind of yelling
Then I come in
By the way I have a show I should plug this
Because I didn't earlier
But for those that do happen to be local here in Sacramento
I am going to be hosting Rocky Horror at the Colonial
On Saturday at I think 10.30 pm
As part of the 9th annual Sacramento Horror Film Festival
I've been fortunate enough to be asked back to do that
But when I come in here next week
You guys should fully expect
Hi everybody this is Rob Roberts
Welcome to Orange Lounge Radio
I just smoked four packs and came on air
That's what it's going to be
Yeah and sometimes you know
This can be complete BS
But to me it always seems that
When I run my voice ragged
It makes me more vulnerable to sickness
Yeah and I'm worried about that
Because there's something going around
Anytime you wear your body down
You're making it more vulnerable to sickness
Anyway Marissa I hate to do this
But I got to wrap up so we can wrap up the show
Because we're running a little long
Thank you so much for the call
It's always good to hear from you
Alright take care
Alright I think that is actually going to do it for the skype line tonight
Because I know Jamie wants to go get pie
And I have some other things I want to take care of around here
We are after midnight on the east coast
So I want to go ahead and move to wrap things up
But I do want to check in and make sure
Are there any last minute stories or things we want to bring up here?
Crowdfunding started for them's fighting herds
So if you want to back that
You can check that out on Indiegogo
That's right I remember hearing about that a couple weeks ago
They're already at about
Just over halfway
About 200,000 from goal
With 17 days left
Nice
Alright
If that's it for last minute stories
There was one other thing I saw
They have more
They have more footage
Of an unreleased Nintendo 64 game
It was a sequel to the Neo Geo
Shooter Viewpoint
Called Viewpoint 2064
Yeah
It's kind of random
I guess it was from a prototype
Cartridge that someone bought on eBay
I'm liking all these
Unreleased games
Unearthed prototypes
It's always kind of fun to see what we might have missed out on
Alright
Well we're going to wind down here for another week here at Orange Lounge Radio
But hey I want to really thank you guys
For tuning in and listening to our show
Whether it be live or in the podcast forum
We really appreciate it
And thank you guys so much for participating
If you liked what you heard here at Orange Lounge Radio
Please consider telling a friend or two
About the show because word of mouth is really all we have
We'd appreciate a tweet
You want to tweet? Hey guys listen to OLR
We would love that so much, thank you so much
And a five star review
On iTunes or Stitcher Radio
I know all your favorite podcasts ask you
But we're all asking you for a reason
Because it goes a long way
So we really appreciate that
And that is going to bring us to a close
Here at another week of Orange Lounge Radio
Great show tonight everybody
Thank you Steve-O from Jackbox Games
For coming on the show tonight
And I want to thank Evan over at Jackbox Games
For helping to arrange that
So thank you very much
Big thanks to Jackbox Games
For supporting the show
Best of luck with Jackbox Party Pack 2
I know I will be there checking that out
As will I'm sure most of us here in studio
And our listenership out there
So it's time to go around
And get everybody's final thought
Tonight here on the show
Darce Agro we haven't heard from you in a little bit
We'll start with you, what's your final thought here tonight?
I'm Mrs. Marissa
Me too, I haven't been to Southern California
In a long time
Let's just go, except I feel depressed going down
And also not going to Disneyland
It's that whole new job time off thing
I can't get time off until December
Let's all just meet up at the Bravo Cheese Farm
There you go, meet halfway
Alright
Let's see, my final thought tonight
I want to wish a happy early
500th episode of Bobby Black Wolf
Because next week is his 500th episode
So tonight was $4.99
And I just want to make sure I did not forget
To give him his kudos where it's due
Bobby Black Wolf is
A big reason why O.L.R. is still going
After all these years because there was a period of time
Where we were going to
Not be a live show anymore
And Bobby helped save that
So we were able to do live
We were going to be a dead show
I don't know if we were going to be dead
But it would just be a very different show
So thank you Bobby for keeping it live
Congrats to the discipline it's taken you
To get all the way to 500 episodes
Last but not least, Loki
Your final thought tonight
I don't know
I'm thinking
I'm at that awkward point where you decide whether or not
You're going to make a costume for Halloween
And you know instead
Much like my game project
Instead of doing something simple
It's either extremely complicated or nothing
In the wise words of one
Shia LaBeouf
Do it!
Just do it!
So I guess we're being
Listened to by Becky and Julian
Oh are we?
If Mother approves
Because sometimes we get a little R-rated
But I guess we can watch our F and Mals
While Julian's here
We can try
There you go, so we'll try
Well I have to know, what game is Julian going to talk about?
Probably Pirates 101 and Lego something
That's fine, oh is he playing that new Lego game too?
No I don't think Dimensions
We should do a show
Where we can bring the kids on
My son would love to talk about Minecraft
Or whatever it is, the Lego game
Bring your kid to OLR
It's just like, alright let's do it
You know what, I just say
Maybe for April Fools next year we'll just let them host
He gets kind of shy so
I don't know, we'll see
That would be funny
I think the listeners would love that
I think they would love that, so we'll have to make that happen
In a few weeks, so there you go
S2100Matt says if we've done a drunk show
We could do a kids show
And ActDef says, OLR
Kid tested, mother approved
I think I just got another text
Just open that up with the themes from Wonder Shows
So we get
LOL Minecraft
You know what, you can never talk enough Minecraft
So now I have to go over to Becky's and have a cookie
Alright sounds good, have two cookies
One for me
That's going to do it, thank you guys so much
For listening to Orange Lounge Radio
And supporting independent broadcasting
We'll be back to do it again in seven days
We'll see you then, have a great week everybody
Good night
See you next week
Thanks for watching!