By the way, this is part of the show. It's too hot to podcast blah blah blah low-key has brought another edition of
Secret club tonight
For those of you who don't know what secret club is secret club is where we're going to tell you some secrets
About things that will be happening in the game industry very soon however
There is a rule that goes with secret club and that is that you don't talk about secret club in other words
You're going to hear some things on here
You don't say you heard him here because we've gotten in trouble over stuff before and we just don't care to have the limelight
Anymore, it's really not that important to us so that being said secret club rules one
It's just it's you know really juicy stuff that you got to tell somebody so I know a lot of people were disappointed with
Capcom not porting over resident evil zero over here only Japan's getting it and you know everyone liked resident evil
For we and stuff well they are porting a game over. It's not resident evil though. It's
Another game also happens to have dead things running around
in
January
Dead rising coming through the wii yay, so that would be pretty cool. That could be interesting
Also, they have a pretty strong lineup for the winner so far one that's been delayed bionic commando as actually now set in
February
Hopefully that sticks resident evil 5 in March and Street Fighter 4 in January
Of course the latter ones being all on PlayStation 3 and the Xbox 360
That's a weird month for Street Fighter 4 January. Yeah, well. There's another I read another story though
From juice France those in the same thing. They said a winner release for it, so it fits so all right
It's a good spot to put it. I mean cuz there's nothing comes out in January. That's it
All right, we're gonna do something very special now, and I'm gonna leave I'm leaving
I'm running to the store because we're gonna do cake and I need to get some plates and some forks and all that good stuff
And I need some other stuff myself so this store happens to be just down the street and around the corner
So I should be back in no more than 10 minutes, so you guys gonna. Time me how long I'm gone
We have exactly 10 minutes to run
Showing time you guys are gonna run the show talk about whatever you want fill time
interact with chatters take off your top for Justin TV who cares
Have fun. I'll flash my cleavage all right, so you
Is this the race in my mind? Okay, so somebody's got to say on your mark get set go okay ready?
He's gonna get in a car accident die
That's games timer is running. Maybe we'll be able to do a show next week cuz he'll be dead
I don't want to sit in Rob's chair, but I want to fuck up his computer
Can't hear you the windows closed
Uh-huh, that's Rob's alarm that doesn't do any good. He's running
Don't understand why why does he not have plates that's what I said, that's not what I said like I
offered to wash
the plates
I'm gonna go buy some so that my cosplayer has some pretty awesome cleavage
You've gotta have those did Rob say part B. I don't know
Let's close the computer down yes
Whoa shit my mic was off. I was
I can't be a host rather than Mike. Oh no. Oscar told me to say boob ten times, so I'm gonna say it ready boob ten times on air XD
Har-har-har, this was said
You know I need to add a thread for a thread with auto in
The ole army thing I've been playing a few people
It's been fun, but most of the time I get invited to games and no one knows who I am
So just a reminder for all our army people I believe there is a group for steam
I believe there's also is a clan on X fire might want to join it true because it's getting kind of lonely
Pass the mic over
You may like it, but women have precedents because we have boobs
Awesome, you know what I'm gonna. Do I'm gonna go to the bathroom a game. Thanks. We are hijacking the afterbirth officially
Oh my god always does this
Okay, okay, wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait hold on
And this is what happens when women run show
We've come to hijack the afterbirth and talk about comics we hate the scrolls
they suck so bad and
um and they suck
They do suck and they turn green well. They are green, but they turn into other people
And that sucks, and we don't know who's actually a scroll for all we know half the chat room could be scrolled
Andrew could be a scroll, but we wouldn't know the difference even if he did turn green. I love Marvel, but Marvel hates me
The show makes me turn green. Scroll!
Okay, act death protests and toshin protests and a bunch of people said that they're not scroll so that means they are
You just want us to
If you say you aren't a scroll, you are a scroll
Do they weigh less than a duck?
I mean we can find out
And don't eat us cuz you can't become us
Wait different universe. Sorry
And cheeseburger if you have to ask it means you are one
Yes, the Hulk does turn green actually the Hulk turns gray and red and
He in one universe he eats people's brains damn the Patriots and poops them out I
Just thought it was intensely hilarious that they had to save his poo
Because it had alien matter. No no it had alien rubber bands in it
You know not what you just what you're talking about unless you read the comics in my bathroom I
I keep comics in my bathroom everybody just die monster. You don't belong in this world
I do okay the comics in my bathroom right now is that three volumes of the ultimates I?
Have I'm sorry one
And I know it's why exiles cuz it's awesome, and you suck. Why God why?
Can I kill him ultimate volume one and two
You're actually not supposed to like it supposedly if you like Marvel
But it's actually better written than the actual Avengers ha ha ha I said it see how easily provoked Jamie is I?
Actually have nothing against the ultimate series I
Have everything against you though, so it's okay. I
Know I know
So if you're into comics if you were into the Iron Man movie there is a new invincible Iron Man series that came out
Not this last week, but the week before you'll probably be able to find it in
Your local comic book store. It's a good starting point for people who have
Seen the movie and want to learn more about Iron Man, but have never read any of the comics
the main villain so far is
Jebediah stain who is the son of Obadiah stain the main villain from the Iron Man movie you'll see
And you'll see roadie, and it's it's a very good comic a good writer good artist well
Yeah, okay artist. I'm not too happy with art, but overall a good recommendation for a comic
Rob has now been gone for five minutes and 45 seconds
Five minutes have elapsed
Another good comic this week was x-men divided we stand number two
Which is one of the Messiah complex comics dealing with the x-men featuring?
That's what you were reading earlier
I have downloaded it and have yet to read it because I was reading Mighty Avengers and reading this Silent Hill
Series that I'm waiting on to be finished
My Silent Hill comic was very disturbing and it was about a
A contract killer who ran off with his boss's wife to Silent Hill
Happens I want to go to the best place ever you want to run off to Silent Hill. You'll have a killer good time
Herman Herman head goes fast for tonight
No
He has to drag around that great knife
So how was Mighty Avengers
Mighty Avengers is very interesting because it's fantastic wasn't it it was more scroll tastic
But it was more or less Bob is nuts the comic. Yeah
basically
another good comic that is coming to trade paperback soon, I believe is the
Captain Marvel short series
Anybody who is into classic Marvel knows that Captain Marvel died of cancer many many years ago, but they brought him back
And I know that sounds sucky and it actually has to do with this whole secret invasion thing
But the storyline was fairly decent and the art is very good
And it's definitely worth checking out once it comes out in a trade paperback
I've been told to say something. I can't normally say around Rob. Okay, I
Don't say whatever the fuck I want around Rob so maybe um
What's something that really grosses Rob out
kind of ritual sex
There I said it he likes boobies
All men like boobies. It doesn't matter if they're gay. Yeah, I remember one time at Disneyland
What
He only sucks if you pay him
Only if you're female, sorry lalalala lalala lalalala lalalalala
Lali lu they know I suggested that I say vagina I can say that around Rob though. We saw Margaret Cho. Hi
This is a woman who's part of her stand-up comedy was about her period so no that doesn't work I
I like what she said though. She said that if Richard Pryor had a period he would talk about it. How do you guy?
now
Well, you're not housing a hottie. How do you guy why not?
Because I'm sitting down you should put the webcam thingy on that and do some stuff that we can
stop
Oh, yes, I know what Rob doesn't like Rob doesn't like looking at girls butts
He likes that song right yes nine minutes have elapsed
You know what Rob lied to us he lied to me he's never coming back
Probably right and he probably got into a car accident. The cake is a lie
Given that it takes five minutes to get to the aforementioned store
And then you have to go in and get plates, and then you have to pay for plates
You know what we should do we should go to grab the plates out of the cupboard and go ahead and serve out some cake
And go I guess guess what Rob you know that bet he's doing what he's buying a present
He's getting you a Walmart gift card
I should've told him to buy candles, and then you could all sing me happy birthday, and I could I'm doing it right now nine eight
seven six five four three
two one
time
My mommy just texted it at me. What'd your mom have to say happy Memorial Day tomorrow?
I'm saying thanks mommy. Happy my birthday weekend
and
Happy DJ Ranma s birthday weekend
time
And happy Lenny Kravitz birthday weekend even though. I'm not really into any of his music Rob you're late
Train wreck-a-rama we has Rex Metal Gear
So I told Rob to get candles I
Told Rob to get bent
There is a poem on my LJ from one of my friends, and it is called love
It's the wonderful love of a beautiful maid the love of a staunch true man the love of a baby unafraid have
Existed since time began, but the greatest of loves the quintessence of loves even greater than that of a mother
It's the tender passionate infinite love of one drunken marine for another
That's fantastic Rob is late late late late. Rob is late late late late
25 seconds
You're a butt fire you Rob I could we could have used the dishes
And I would have loaded the dishwasher
But then you would have had to been here to like clean the dishes. I got some pretzels and chips for me and look
Triscuits redesigned their package isn't that something?
So what did I miss?
Rob you missed the hurricane it came in it rocked us like a hurricane and then left
Yes
Thank you for the scorpions reference any
Time
I want to know what the hell my mom is doing up at 1130. She doesn't have to work tomorrow Rob. It's a holiday my mother
Yes right now
I don't have a mic so I'm just you want your mic back. Okay, I'll pretend to be Rob
Better than a drunk show
Jamie's mom on Skype no Rob
Oh, no, no, no, it's a reminder here ladies and gentlemen
Yeah, you've caught my mom before
I'm like
I can't hear
Hey, I since you texted me I thought it was okay to call you
Yeah
Guess what?
But you're live on orange sounds radio again. Oh
Boy, and a lot of people are listening now. Hi, Jamie's mom
Hello, that's Drew and and Tara's here. Hi mom
Hey, Tara
And that were y'all doing out there in sunny, California. It is nighttime. But the night is young
I thought it was sunny all the time in California. No, that's only on movie sets
If you're on acid
And you remember you remember Rob, right? Yeah, I do. Hey Rob. Hi. How are you?
Oh, how are you? We've got lots of good. We've got lots of comments from chat. We have siren says hi
Jamie's mom misty says hi. Jamie's mom go banjo says hi
Tyrel says tell her Tyrel's loves her
We keep our chat room patched in during the show so everyone is saying hi
Well, that's cool. I was feeling kind of lonely
Everybody loves my mom
Happy birthday, mommy. She named her
Yeah, okay
I have to tell you cuz
Everyone on the everyone who listens to the show knows me as Jamie Summers and that's in tribute to you naming me after the bionic woman
Yeah, yeah
Do they know that a little six-year-old girl picked out that name because she thought it'd be very cool to name you
Woman, I've said I told this story online before I'm just glad you didn't name me Erica
Oh
But after Erica strata, you said you were gonna name me Erica
And papa got pissed off that you named me
Jamie and not call me Maury just so you know, yeah
Akuma JP says hello from Japan to Jamie's mom. Oh, really?
Tell an embarrassing story, but I'm vetoing that request
Cuz you've already told the condensation story and you've already told the projectile pooping story
Aside from Argentina
From Argentina, yeah
Wow and
Hi from Mexico
I'm sorry, you kind of echoed a little bit. Um
Well, we um, one of our listeners acts death says hi from Mexico. Oh
And no gold banjo summers is not my real last name. You know, he's mysterious last names on air. So you can't stalk us. Yeah
But um, you can you can tell a story as long as has nothing to do with me being naked
Hmm
Hey
Can I say what you used to call the beach area, please do
The light the beach area what?
golf golf shore
It's it's Gulf Shores, I guess
I was gonna tell you the new kids on the block are getting back together
Everything
Okay, really I just I must have forgot somehow that's amazing
And if you laugh I kill you slowly and then as soon as she got it all she said I don't like it anymore
And one time she had Michael Jackson
I had the one of him in the yellow sweater vest the yellow sweater
That's a master bedroom because her bedroom was yellow and white. That's hardcore
I think I have a picture of that one
You also put the um the Care Bears on my wall
No, my Care Bears
Yes, it was right, right? It was those. Yeah rainbow bright. Yes rainbow, but you also had
What's that big head of dolls?
Um catch patch. Yeah, I had cabbage patch dolls
That I stood in line for several hours with every other dumb mother in the world
Getting the cabbage patch doll that you didn't like
You got me the one with brown hair, right?
Yeah
You know would be perfect for you
And you had kept except bedroom shoes
You remember them? Yes, I had they were pink and they had the heads on them
I'm such a you know picture of Jamie walking around with cabbage patch bedroom shoes on
Yeah, but I get to tell an embarrassing story about Matthew how we should dress him up in my doll dress with the bonnet
I know you you used to dress him up like he was a big baby doll
I know it was great
I've got pictures and we used to put Philip in blue shorts and the red shirt and put my five-wheel hat on him
Yeah, yeah, I was gonna tell you mom you're gonna laugh and I had to do it
Just because I downloaded the new kids on the block single
You what now I downloaded the new kids on the block single on iTunes you?
jumbled it downloaded a
Download I'm sorry kind of echoey. This is because we got microphones as Skype is weird
It's that we use it in a program through the computer to to call you
Hey, don't forget to email or text your brother and happy Memorial Day Memorial Day
I don't think I served five years in our military mama email me his phone number
Okay, cuz he changed his phone since last I had it last. I
Thought you know
No, I got Matt. I think oh
Yeah things change you know Phillips and Huntsville yes
We're telling everybody our family history so you can go to Huntsville and look for Philip
I won't give his last name to protect everything you say yeah
My brother my brother is a waiter at Ruby Tuesdays, so they were tender parts. Oh, he's a bartender now
And a waiter he does both mama. Can I say bad language around you?
Well, I hadn't used before
You're right, which I'm not gonna say
I find my brother his name is Philip at a Ruby Tuesdays in Huntsville and order an audios motherfucker and say his sister said so
And by the way, they're really nasty
Does everybody know that your brother was in the Marines?
I have said so my brother was in the Marines
And I told the story about how he chased everybody out of his tent with a stinky feet. Oh, yeah
Yes, he did
That was his defense if the bad guys ever came in there. He would just take his boots off
It probably worked in my work
Was little okay, he stank all the time his feet did it was a stink bomb well well mommy
mother dear
We have to let you go
Okay, cuz we have to we have to go we have to eat cake
Okay, well we can't can have fun be happy. Okay, and email me Philip stuff. I'm glad we could talk to you
Take care for you
And the listeners love you tomorrow do what the listeners love you everybody
Love you love you, too
There you have it that's mommy that was fun, this is my mom is now has her second appearance on the show
That's fun. Yeah, my mom is probably in bed if I call her we're getting smacked
She's a cage match to
Anyway, we have hijacked the afterbirth and talked about comics so fun, okay, all right song number one won
Two weeks ago. It was a ditty from a band called lady Tron
I love lady Tron and apparently you do too because you voted at the winner here
It is song number one last week's cage match winner was ghosts remember you only get to hear a clip of it
Again, you got to be in chat to vote for your favorite
You know what just ask someone in chat how it works
If you really don't know cuz I feel like explaining it cuz I'm gonna go help with cake
You
Oh
That was song number one lady Tron with ghosts the winner from the holdover from the May 11th show last time we were here
All right, let's get into some new songs tonight dark soccer. What'd you pick for us tonight?
Yeah, what'd you pick for us tonight?
All right, why not a little bit of classic rock the Beatles
Hey, that's true we did have home with ready for all right here. We got some classic rock the bagels with birthday enjoy
Oh
So on number two in tonight's cage match a little bit of classic
Is Jamie just screw up the camp a little bit of classic stuff. I'll fix it
Let it point is feeling a little bit. Okay a little bit of classic rock with the Beatles and birthday
You say it's your birthday. What do you say? What would you write that song though? We'll start with Yara
Let's work our way around the circle
Oh, it's the Beatles. It's White Album. It's classic rock. It gets a 10.
A 10 from T-ara, Dark Soccer. It gets a 10 because T-ara said so.
That song still holds up very well today. I give it a eight and a half
Drew it gets a 10 because T-ara already said so
Loki I'm not buying into this whole T-ara says thing so it gets an average six from me
All right, because it's an average song. All right, Loki. Then what pray tell did you bring to the listening public today at song number three?
I picked a song by a group called methods of mayhem may not recognize this group, but it's actually Tommy Lee
Producing music that unlike Tommy Lee, but it's a rock rap group, but trust me the song is pretty good
So the song's called crash
All right, you're just song number three in the cage match your last song tonight methods of mayhem with crash
Enjoy
Enjoy, or don't you decide?
Oh
Dark Sakura
Like the bass drum was awesome eight five
All right, well that's far from what you were saying, you know Loki nine nine
All right
Nine is in the number nine. All right, let's recap the song so you can vote for tonight
Oh, well, and I'll take some effuse until I say stop. All right, here we go. There we here it is
Song number one you can vote for tonight is ladytron with ghosts
Song number two you can vote for tonight is the Beatles with birthday
Song
Number three you can vote for tonight is methods of mayhem with crash
Ladies vote now send a private message to sky in the chat room with your vote
and in the meantime, we will get to the effuse of the week, which I hope have already started to come in because
We've had to fill enough time tonight
Yes. All right. We're ready to go and arrive already. All right, then let's go with the chat effuse
I've got one
More will probably come in as you start to read the one Oscar says at you to sky for missing his time limit
But then again, it doesn't matter because it was fun while he was gone
Well, we try to say this shows more fun without me here. I
Freaking adore Oscar. Okay, Oscar is like
rad
Oscar is great
But it better be in a nice way that you love my mom
I love my mommy too
Rana a few people who missed up on the debauchery of my 30th last night before bastards
That would be us. I missed out
Maybe maybe that should be amended to those who are in a position to attend yet. Yes
I hereby Boyd Rama's that you don't look good. Actually, I am amended but with another proposal to do everyone for I know I'm in
I was fine. I don't care. I think you're on snake by power of estrogen
Say more effuse
And he said
More effuse not more breaking of my computer
My f you goes to these forks cheeseburger
Okay, you know what I'm not if you keep okay
He says everything you've not reading an email these since six weeks ago
And I'm telling you this it's gone like I told you last time like I told you earlier today
The email you sent six weeks ago is gone
If you want an email read send another email and we'll see and we'll see I
Skipped a lot of emails. Okay, just because I pass yours up
once or twice
Does not mean that I hate you
I
Had to read it
Jamie is the goddamn Batman
And she hates chocolate. I am the goddamn Batman. I am the goddamn chocolate Batman. I
I
Don't think anyone's running a recording right now, you're screwed
Death says eff you to not having money by the way your mom
A lot more now than for us when I was growing up
My mind went straight to the gutter to my mind is the gutter
Mommy, you can't take my TV away cuz daddy got that for me and you taking it would be best. I was a brat
So to have my mom be as cool as she is now with me being such an ungrateful little brat
My mom is super awesome
Rob I don't think you can really let your mind go to the gutter about Timmy's mom being a screamer
Oh fuck someone's recording
By the way, according to Oscar, this is seriously the best afterbirth ever long it's going on forever
This is so busted. Tyrol says eff you to decay bongos that waste space on my shelf and attract spiders
Sauce is the best guest ever. Rebo boy for three sisters eff you to Voldemort
The males are having a huddle
Believe it or not. It's not about you
What exactly is the chocolate Batman I don't know you said that's you so why don't you tell us all right
All right
Kill the music these FUs are over. Stop. No more FUs. All right, how about a cage match wiener?
Somebody weaned the cage match tonight. It's like a baby
What?
And the cage match winner is actually close vote time to make all three songs
Bass drum one
Maybe doing Grover impressions on Justin TV for some weird reason. All right
We are finally ready to put the nail in the coffin of this damn show. Yeah
All right, it's now 1 a.m. On the East Coast
All right, I know the YouTube has been so slow on my computer lately
But of course everybody has been like leeching bandwidth. So that's what happens. That's right
It'll it'll finish before we're done. So that's gonna do it for tonight's orange launch radio
Anybody have to say anything before we turn it back over to all games?
cake I
have a very important announcement what I
Really really like cake. All right
We're going to the fortune cookie message of the day now as chosen by drew because he felt it was appropriate tonight
So if you hate this fortune cookie message, what's your email?
Classified whatever I'll find it for you and give it to you here it is fortune cookie message of the day
You
Oh
My fantasy
Alright that was very cute. Sorry wrong. I actually like that. That wasn't bad
That was those cute to watch it when I'm at an angle that I can see it
This by the way was the leech Street boys
That was cute. I approve good times. All right
We are officially pulling the plug on orange launch radio tonight and we're gonna be turning it over to all games radio
Of course the lovely radio station that hosts our show on Sunday night
We appreciate it the next live program on all games radio will be all games interactive
I'm actually not sure if they're live tomorrow though, but I'll just assume they are their show is on at noon now
They've moved to noon. So that's three o'clock Eastern
So stay tuned for all games interactive and in the meantime, you're 24. Oh, yeah, we do anything on just TV
Let's have cake on Justin TV. We'll have cake on Justin TV and we'll do gay. Yeah, cuz now it is
right
Yeah, it shouldn't I should be able to play it, all right, we'll do something on Justin TV real quick
So if you want to head over to Justin TV, we'll be there in a few minutes and we'll do some cake, too
So, but that's it. We're turning the all games feedback to all games. So I have a good one
Oh
You