[SPEAKER_02]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and released to our podcast stream twice weekly.
[SPEAKER_02]: To listen to the first half of this episode visit www.orangeloungeradio.com for links to websites with listings of past episodes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now the conclusion of this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio, live on All Games Radio every Sunday night at 6 o'clock Pacific Standard Time, 9 o'clock Eastern Time, but you're probably thinking to yourself, but hey, Rob, it's about 7.30 in the evening Pacific, or 10.30 Eastern.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's because it's time for Part B of our podcast, which goes out to the podcast feed, usually on Wednesdays, Thursdays if I'm having an especially
[SPEAKER_06]: XBOX 360 Elite
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to be awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I played for you guys entry from an ineligible listener in Part A, so if you haven't heard Part A yet, go back and listen.
[SPEAKER_06]: For those of you listening live tonight on All Games Radio, you have about four hours left to get an entry in.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll tell you what, there's not a lot of competition, so if you think you can come up with something creative pretty quick...
[SPEAKER_06]: Do it!
[SPEAKER_06]: You might win an Xbox 360 Elite.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to be pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll let you know who is the finalist for Orange Lounge Radio next week.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I think we'll know in like two, two and a half weeks who the ultimate winner is from AllGames.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who's walking away with the 1-8 Xbox 360 Elite.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't forget, just for being the Orange Lounge Radio finalist, you do get some prizes.
[SPEAKER_06]: You get like a t-shirt and $25 gift certificate to the new All Games store that's up and running.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, just for being silly and recording it for our mutual enjoyment.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, let's get back into some gaming news here on Part B of Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, take it away.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, let's see here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, this is kind of interesting because I know they haven't been doing too well for the longest time, but Atari is actually being bought up by Infogrames for $11 million.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the announced, I guess, merger, they're going to buy the remaining stock of Atari, of course, for $11 million, and that will immediately lend...
[SPEAKER_04]: 20 million dollars to the company before the deal closes and although it's hard to really say what's going to happen although Infogrames only had 51.4 controlling interest in Atari 51.4% looks like doesn't really sound like what kind of changes are going to happen after this but I guess it's nice for Atari to have a little bit more financial backing
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, here's the thing, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: Essentially, Atari's been sold for $11 million.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that what I'm to understand?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, $11 million is not that much money.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, don't get me wrong.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'd gladly take it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me put it this way.
[SPEAKER_04]: A bar company that I work for could have bought Atari.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm like, dude, this is the company that is like my childhood.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, like little childhood, like when I was like three, was when the Atari 2600 was big, but still...
[SPEAKER_06]: It's kind of weird to think that... Why hasn't EA bought them?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, seriously, it's just like, poof, snapped them up like nothing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I know that they may not be interested in per se them, but a bigger portfolio is not a bad thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, granted, it sounds like there's some other stuff involved here, like they're loaning them $20 million and stuff, so maybe it's not fair to say they're only getting sold for $11 million, but still, that's kind of what it comes off as.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_09]: It'd be like if someone sold Nintendo 20 years from now for like, I don't know, $15, $20.
[SPEAKER_06]: A bag of peanuts.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, that would be like, it would be weird.
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course, it was also weird to see the Sega logo on a Nintendo game like years ago when F-Zero came out.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was all weird.
[SPEAKER_09]: It is weird.
[SPEAKER_06]: and Sephiroth1215 in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_06]: Chat.OrangeLawnTrader.com says, Too bad most Atari or Infogrames games suck.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Dragon Ball Z games are good, but I'm really sick of them now because they just do the same thing every year.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, I guess that is the sad thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Atari honestly hasn't had a lot going for it recently.
[SPEAKER_04]: See, that would have been perfect.
[SPEAKER_04]: You could have had Dragon Ball Z 2008 or 2009 for EA.
[SPEAKER_06]: Although I have to admit, I did kind of want one of those flashback consoles.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it's not like I can't still get one, but you know, flashback consoles are cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I guess there you have it.
[SPEAKER_06]: More to develop on that, or more news on that, I'm sure, in the coming weeks, including what the joint projects will be in the future.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's talk about QMotions.
[SPEAKER_06]: They are a subsidiary of Actiga.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're a gaming company.
[SPEAKER_06]: They apparently have made some sort of agreement with Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're going to be using the wireless technology that QMotions has for types of active gaming controllers for the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_06]: Q-Motions has made these large controllers for golf, baseball, and snowboarding.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to say I've seen this before.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to say one of those times They sell them at Best Buy, I think.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to say one of those times we were on All Games Interactive last year or a couple years ago.
[SPEAKER_06]: They had one of these in the house.
[SPEAKER_06]: They just acquired one there.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that was the same thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: So they know how to make these types of controllers.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, apparently Microsoft is getting in on this now for who knows what type of project.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it kind of makes sense, you know, with the Wii doing as well as it is, Microsoft wants a piece of it somehow.
[SPEAKER_06]: So they'll buy somebody else to do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Make an agreement to do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: The press release stated that the first controller that will be coming out will be a big air wireless controller.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a full-size skateboard that will work with skateboarding games.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, this is pretty high-end stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: This isn't something that, you know, a gamer that doesn't have a lot of money can pick up.
[SPEAKER_06]: But still, I mean, if you really want to get immersed in your games, I guess this is the way to do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is what they should be setting up at the Westin.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, this is the kind of thing you don't get to play every day.
[SPEAKER_06]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_06]: What do you think, Loki?
[SPEAKER_06]: Is this the type of thing you would be interested in at all?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It sounds like, as Alton Brown would put it, it's a uni-tasker.
[SPEAKER_04]: And no one likes a uni-tasker.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nerd.
[SPEAKER_06]: Only you would quote the Food Network here on our program.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_04]: XBOX LIVE XBOX LIVE
[SPEAKER_04]: for 1,600 Microsoft points, also $20.
[SPEAKER_04]: It will also make it the most expensive Xbox Live Arcade game to date.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, but if you add up all the parts in Luminous, it's a little more expensive.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is true, but still though, out of the gate though, this is the most expensive Xbox Live Arcade game.
[SPEAKER_04]: And probably going to set a disturbing trend among games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, they're going to buy it for $20.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's put out our crappy game for $20.
[SPEAKER_04]: So...
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, but you kind of sense that Penny Arcade's going to be able to get away with it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it's all about if the game is good, but at least the IP is good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I mean, if it's a full game, I mean, they'll be awesome, but I just have a bad feeling, though, that other companies are going to look at this and go, hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: We can get our game to be $20, too, and they'll sell it and it'll be shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, if some little internet comic can get $20 for their game, then we ought to be able to sell our game for $20.
[SPEAKER_09]: You do that too well, Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've been snooping in on boardrooms.
[SPEAKER_06]: How about Macintosh?
[SPEAKER_09]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_06]: The chat room's asking.
[SPEAKER_06]: No love, I guess.
[SPEAKER_09]: So do we know anything about the actual game?
[SPEAKER_06]: There's screenshots and stuff out there.
[SPEAKER_06]: I haven't done a lot of research on the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is gone gold for Windows, Mac, and Linux.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, there you have it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you can't say you don't have anything to play on the Mac.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know a lot about this game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Isn't it kind of like a
[SPEAKER_06]: Adventure type game?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like an adventure game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kind of think of a cross between one of the LucasArts adventure games and Final Fantasy.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you've got the turn-based fighting in there as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's all the Penny Arcade humor.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: It looks really cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, Rock Band has made some progress, a lot of progress.
[SPEAKER_06]: This game, of course, just on about every console out there, except the Wii right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's out on the Xbox 360, PlayStation 3, PlayStation 2, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't they have a version of this on PS2?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, it's out there everywhere.
[SPEAKER_06]: They've announced that they have sold 3 million copies of the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: 10 million rock band songs have been downloaded.
[SPEAKER_06]: 4 million of those since March 20th, just about 6 weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_08]: Damn.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, yeah, 3 million copies of the game, 10 million.
[SPEAKER_06]: That means on the average, people are buying 3 or 4 songs a pop.
[SPEAKER_09]: And how much do each song cost?
[SPEAKER_06]: About 2 bucks, depending on what platform and what song.
[SPEAKER_06]: So on average about... I'm wondering if they're counting those albums as 12 songs sold though, but I guess they can because they charge more for those.
[SPEAKER_06]: How many people really bought that album?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sure there's plenty.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't get me wrong.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not bashing the artists.
[SPEAKER_04]: I bought a lot of songs on there.
[SPEAKER_06]: I bought quite a few too, I gotta admit.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know why I buy them.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't either, but it's the ultimate party game because you're glad to have them when people are over.
[SPEAKER_09]: You guys are so funny.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know why I buy them, but I bought them.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have those Microsoft points burning a hole in my pocket.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm telling you, that's why that stuff is evil.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because Microsoft, it's so easy to just press that one little button and spend Microsoft points.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you need to reload, just add more points.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's dangerous.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like you're not spending money, you're just spending points.
[SPEAKER_06]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't notice it until I look at my bank statement.
[SPEAKER_06]: and I go, son of a bitch, I just bought like 40 bucks worth of Microsoft points this month.
[SPEAKER_06]: What do I have to speak for it?
[SPEAKER_06]: I bought Jairus.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's pretty smart, though, that they get the points.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is.
[SPEAKER_06]: Scary.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going off the tangent train, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, dear God.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, what's up?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry, you know, because you know me, I'm looking up last minute stories and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sure, sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I had to mention this because it just, poof, they had a big little thing in the corner of the screen here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently, at Maker Faire 2008 today, MacGyver creator Lee David Zlotoff announced that he is making a big budget MacGyver movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, but they're bastardizing everything we love in the 80s.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's an A-Team movie coming out, too.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why didn't they make these movies when they were popular?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't understand.
[SPEAKER_09]: When MacGyver was still on the air.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's the whole retro thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just like a few years ago, 70s retro.
[SPEAKER_06]: They remade Charlie's Angels.
[SPEAKER_06]: They remade the Brady Bunch.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now the 80s are coming.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dude, it's just a matter of time before we get the Facts of Life movie.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who would they cast as Natalie and Tootie?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Tootie.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know, I just kind of think it's a no.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rumor is the movie will be made out of a shoelace, paper clips, and a jar of peanut butter.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can you take us back to video games, please?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_04]: So yeah, there's some interesting news coming out with...
[SPEAKER_04]: Guitar Hero, Aerosmith
[SPEAKER_04]: A length of time, but I mean, God, who cares?
[SPEAKER_06]: Meaning there's an escape clause in it should Guitar Hero tank in the near future so Aerosmith can get in on the other game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's gotta be that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It says, apparently, excluding, I guess, Rock Band's train kept on rolling, Aerosmith's entire catalog of rock and roll hits will be exclusive to Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it says, Newsweek got confirmation that the Aerosmith publicist and Activision PR that the band's songs would be locked down for an unspecified period of time.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that is for a limited amount of time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Meaning there's an escape clause, just in case.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you know, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have a real problem with this kind of stuff because I see this as the beginning.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's the little pebble that starts the snowball that starts the avalanche.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because we all know, you know, we heard last week Guitar Hero 4 is supposedly following in rock bands' footsteps where they're going to be adding voice, they're going to be adding drums, possibly.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, a lot of it's speculation.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, we know there's... But the thing is, we'll both play nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: or am I going to have to have two of everything like Noah's freaking Ark in my gaming closet?
[SPEAKER_04]: If it's up to Activision, if it's up to Activision, then no, they won't.
[SPEAKER_04]: But if it's up to Microsoft, then yes, they will.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you remember, Microsoft, they have strict regulations about their accessories and peripherals that they all have to play nice with each other.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: That shit pisses me off if they don't play nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: And when I get pissed off, we do the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, why don't you start us off tonight since DarkSakura is not here?
[SPEAKER_04]: F you to Gravity for pulling the mustard out of my sandwich and staining my shirt and my shorts with delicious mustard.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rice Princess, since you're filling in tonight, would you care to give an F you for anything?
[SPEAKER_09]: F you to Hollywood After Dark for showing Rue McClanahan stripping.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do we need to describe Bad Movie Night really quick?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, do it, do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Give him a rundown of Bad Movie Night.
[SPEAKER_06]: You haven't talked at all tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, man.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, Bad Movie Night is where we pick bad movies, bad but entertaining movies to watch.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sadly, none of my movies got picked.
[SPEAKER_06]: I brought Follow That Bird, the Sesame Street adaptation from 1980s, but my choice was not Scream last night.
[SPEAKER_04]: It wasn't bad enough, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: It wasn't that bad of a movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was just a classic.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're all pushing 30.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's pretty bad in retrospect.
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, we watched Sleepaway Camp, which I've seen numerous times, but there were a few people that hadn't seen it yet, so that's funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: I swear to God I'll ban you from chat if you ruin the twist ending to Sleepaway Camp.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, do not do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Best twist ending ever in a movie, Sleepaway Camp.
[SPEAKER_09]: And if you haven't seen it, watch it.
[SPEAKER_06]: You need to watch it, and I swear to God, strap yourself to the chair and force yourself to watch it.
[SPEAKER_06]: The twist ending is worth it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, just get through it.
[SPEAKER_04]: and you gotta love the line where the guy goes, I gotta take a wicked dump.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love Sleepless Camp.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's an ultimate bad movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then we watched this other movie which, what was it?
[SPEAKER_04]: It was like something ninjas or like... We watched it fast forward.
[SPEAKER_04]: Karate Kids.
[SPEAKER_04]: Karate Kids USA I think is what it was called.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my god, it was horrible.
[SPEAKER_04]: We fast forwarded through most of that, but there was a part where the kid called this black biker a souffle.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which I don't know how that's an insult, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: And he's all, no one calls me a souffle.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll see you later.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, what?
[SPEAKER_04]: And they basically have a battle of hillbillies in the forest or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, so tell us about the Rue McClanahan movie.
[SPEAKER_06]: So the Rue McClanahan movie, that was Hollywood After Dark.
[SPEAKER_06]: By the way, she was Blanche on the Golden Girls, just in case you didn't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was Hollywood After Dark.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's actually, the film was a part of this, what do they call it, the film crew.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the guys that did Mystery Science Theater 3000, but now it's essentially the same damn thing, which is without the robots, and now they can swear and stuff during that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: But she was playing the stripper, and they made her strip, and it was...
[SPEAKER_04]: Some of the comments they made were really funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then there was these weird chicks that they had stripping.
[SPEAKER_04]: There was no nudity in this movie whatsoever.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was made in the 60s, so it was still taboo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pasties was as far as it went.
[SPEAKER_04]: But they had some really ugly people just stripping, I guess.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow, funny stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was thinking we should do a Justin TV thing where we make fun of movies or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: That'd be great.
[SPEAKER_06]: Jamie would love that, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: She loves bad movies.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can go to the Film Cruise website, and they have podcasts that are meant for different movies, and you can play them at the same time as you're watching the movie.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like newer movies?
[SPEAKER_06]: Newer movies, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: And so, I mean, I highly, after watching this, because this seriously was, it's...
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, absolutely, without a doubt, I mean, just nothing cut down whatsoever, no watered down, in fact, it was a little bit better, I think, because they were able to, you know, say stuff like, you know, make penis jokes and stuff like that, but absolutely awesome, check out the website, so.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, we got on a tangent.
[SPEAKER_06]: My FU of the week goes to the fact that, well, this is actually a good thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's been one month since I've been out of the hospital, as of today, for, you know, when I was in there for pancreatitis.
[SPEAKER_06]: But the FU goes to the fact that I'm not sure it's completely gone.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, I still get chest pains once in a while, and that's kind of irritating.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I found out on Friday.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: FU to blood tests.
[SPEAKER_06]: Especially when the nurse gives you this really horrible tape that, I swear to God, I've tried to wash this off like five times this week, and the residue from the tape is still not coming off.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, let's get back into some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_06]: Talk about Fatal Inertia.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fatal Inertia, this is the interesting thing about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was going to be coming out as a PlayStation 3 launch title.
[SPEAKER_06]: Then apparently it was going to be on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now it's back on the PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_04]: It came out for the 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it did like last September, I think.
[SPEAKER_06]: As an arcade title?
[SPEAKER_04]: And now they're supposed to be making it better, so...
[SPEAKER_06]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, the EX, Facial Inertia EX is coming out to the PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_06]: See, that's what confuses me because it was coming on PSN, whereas the other one was on 360.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I thought it was an arcade title.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, I get it now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I guess not a lot of people got it on the 360 because I didn't even know about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: But here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're going to be adding to it a brand new training mode, more tracks in the game, and apparently the game is not as difficult.
[SPEAKER_06]: They've actually lowered the difficulty a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: $29.99 late May is when this game is coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that's about the price I think the other one was too.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it was $39.99 when it came out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: So Mega Man has made it into the Guinness Book of World Records Gamer Edition.
[SPEAKER_04]: I actually had a chance to check this out at a bookstore the other day.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought it was pretty well put together.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I still laugh at the fact that there's gaming world records in there and they're kind of retarded.
[SPEAKER_04]: But
[SPEAKER_04]: But apparently there are 46 Mega Man games in existence, making it the largest franchise out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: There are 17 games in the Classic Series, 11 Mega Man X games, 4 Mega Man Zero games, 2 Mega Man ZX games, 3 Mega Man Legend games, 6 Mega Man Battle Network games, and 3 Mega Man Star Force games.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I know there's a lot more coming out as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_06]: Lots of Mega Man.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, I was tempted, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: The other day I saw the Mega Man Collection, which was a game I think I rented once.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's great because, you know, the old school Mega Man games are awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, you know, they have the new one that came out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, it's not that new now, but it came out on PlayStation 2 and GameCube.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you can play old GameCube games on your Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, you know, that Blockbuster we went to to get Sleepaway Camp the other day had the Mega Man Collection for sale for GameCube, a previously played copy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fifteen bucks.
[SPEAKER_06]: I almost bought it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm thinking, like, why not buy that and then, you know, because it's going to come out on Virtual Console eventually.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was 1999 when it first came out, so.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, but still.
[SPEAKER_06]: 15's not bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's cheap.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like six, seven Mega Man games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Eight, maybe.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't remember how many were in there, but a lot.
[SPEAKER_09]: Only three of them are really even worth playing anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was the first three that were ever created, so.
[SPEAKER_06]: HitStun says, don't get the GameCube one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought the GameCube one had the remixed music, which was cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to say that each version had, like, there was a PlayStation 2 and then there was a GameCube one, and I think each one had, like, a different unlockable game in there or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, well, whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm probably not actually going to get the game anyway, because, you know, Irene's going to call me this week, and she's going to be like, dude, Rob, Karazhan.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm going to be like, oh, fuck Mega Man.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, let's read some mail. ...
[SPEAKER_06]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: Really quickly, ShadowCharlie sent us an email about this whole article.
[SPEAKER_06]: He basically copy-pasted an article about the Mothers Against Drunk Driving attacking Grand Theft Auto 4.
[SPEAKER_06]: Retarded.
[SPEAKER_06]: And why is that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, let me give you the gist of what happened.
[SPEAKER_06]: Basically, they're pissed because you can actually drive drunk in the game, and I believe it's the objective of one of the missions in the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're claiming Grand Theft Auto should be re-rated as adults only.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not... That's the spin that they're putting on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: There is no... I mean, you can drive drunk in the game, but...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: And you can hail a cab, you know, to take you back home, but... Sensationalism around Grand Theft Auto 4?
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, it's crazy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, surely you jest.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I know, and people, like, you know, claiming things that aren't actually in the game?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that's surprising.
[SPEAKER_09]: See, that's so stupid, because you can do other shit in the games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, murder okay, drunk driving, whoa, that's taking it too far.
[SPEAKER_04]: Excuse me, sir, you gotta change your rating.
[SPEAKER_06]: Frisbee in chat is screaming, it's not real driving, it's not real drunk.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is pretty cool the way it's done, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: The whole camera shakes around and stuff, and randomly your car will swerve in different directions.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have to kind of counter-steer for that, but I like it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, you can ride animals while drunk in World of Warcraft, and no one says anything about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_04]: No one said anything about Saints Row.
[SPEAKER_04]: You could get high and stoned and stuff in that game.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can also get drunk and drive around and kill people.
[SPEAKER_04]: In fact, they kind of insist that when you are drunk, you have superpowers and can punch people really far away.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Moving on to the next email from GS68.
[SPEAKER_06]: HeyOLRCrew, specifically Loki and RobRobRob, I have a bad feeling about your appearance at Fonamay.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're not listed under the panel section of the Fonamay 2008 site at Fonamay.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you going to try and make a last-minute arrangement or something?
[SPEAKER_06]: If there's no OLR panel this year, then I suppose us Bay Area OLR fans will just have to find some other way to meet up at Fonamay.
[SPEAKER_06]: This email brought to you by Hooters, home of the never-ending girls' butts.
[SPEAKER_06]: God, that Olive Garden thing is caught on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Everybody's signing their emails with strange things now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, we're going to have to break the news to you.
[SPEAKER_06]: We are not attending Fanime this year.
[SPEAKER_06]: We do not plan on doing a live panel this year.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is nothing against Fanime.
[SPEAKER_06]: We still love the staff and everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: The thing is that Jamie has other plans this year.
[SPEAKER_06]: And quite frankly, it's a three-day weekend.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's one of the few that us working kids have during the year.
[SPEAKER_06]: And so we just want to take the weekend to kind of do other things.
[SPEAKER_06]: and also since we're going to be hopefully doing PAX and some other shows later in the year, we've just decided to sit this one out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is anybody going to Fanime just for fun?
[SPEAKER_06]: Out of curiosity?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is the first year you haven't been to Fanime in a long time, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it hasn't.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought you went like every year.
[SPEAKER_04]: I used to like when I was in the anime.
[SPEAKER_04]: What, like five years ago?
[SPEAKER_04]: And even then, it was only really like three years in a row.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, still, those of you guys that are going to Fanime, we hope you have a lot, a lot of fun, and good luck.
[SPEAKER_06]: ASEN is being yelled in chat, and ASEN is too soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: ASEN is very soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: The problem is, I was originally wanting to go to ASEN, but my medical things came up, and I had to put it aside, because that kind of stuff is more important for me right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe next year.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm really hoping.
[SPEAKER_06]: PAX is the most definite right now, and you never know what else might happen in the future.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you have a con...
[SPEAKER_06]: that's drivable, or let's say in California or like Reno or even Oregon, hell, let us know.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll try to come if you'd like to have us there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Otherwise, if it's something we've got to fly to, it just depends on the budget.
[SPEAKER_06]: And by budget, I mean how much money we have in our pockets because we don't, you notice we don't run ads on this show, meaning we have no money.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mark from Plymouth, England sends us the next email.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a bit long, so I'm just going to read some of this here.
[SPEAKER_06]: He says, I'm not a Nintendo fanboy, although the track of this message may lead you to at first think that I might be.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to start by saying that here in the UK, there's no real Nintendo history.
[SPEAKER_06]: As back as in the 80s, Commodore 64 and ZX Spectrum ruled the gaming of everyone, and Nintendo was almost unknown to me and my friends until I was too old and busy with serious dating to get back into it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here, the NES and SNES were pretty much unknown things.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now my main point, Wii isn't increasing the gamer base as mentioned by you on episode 277, and often it's a war cry by many of the too many podcasts I listen to.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know you don't hate the Wii and are open about its strengths and weaknesses.
[SPEAKER_06]: However, I believe, not as my personal experience, that as I am a gamer, definitely not hardcore, although I'm very much into all the latest news.
[SPEAKER_06]: I am presently most all about handhelds due to access issues to the big ass TV.
[SPEAKER_06]: My Wii is also freely played by my wife, who would categorize herself as a non-gamer, and her family.
[SPEAKER_06]: In fact, my next night shift has been scheduled for a Wii Fit Night, in which my wife has invited her friends and sisters for drinks and laughs on the board.
[SPEAKER_06]: This type of sociability has led all the family to buying Wiis, and they are now the prime console.
[SPEAKER_06]: The collateral fallout is that many others in the household now play, whereas before, one person, maybe two, per household, played the kids and parents are buying games for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is there any figures on players per console for old and present gen?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'd like to bet the figure has risen.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is there anything like that?
[SPEAKER_06]: I doubt it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to kind of cut some of this email out, but he was just sort of making the point that the Wii is definitely kind of caught on in that way.
[SPEAKER_06]: But what about the software?
[SPEAKER_06]: He talks about why do some shovelware games sell well?
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that the taste of light gamers are different in a lot of early games to the Wii or games ported over from PS2 games?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's because people don't know any better.
[SPEAKER_04]: The moms and pops that are going to stores that are buying their kids' games, they look at it, they're like, okay, well, they can get Mario Kart and they can get this other game that looks very similar.
[SPEAKER_04]: And all they have to go by is the pictures on the back and stuff and the price point.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they're like, well, it's $20 cheaper or $30 cheaper, so hey, let's go ahead and give it a shot.
[SPEAKER_04]: And unfortunately, it's just like movies.
[SPEAKER_04]: You may go to your rental store or whatever and
[SPEAKER_04]: You're looking at the back of the movie and all you have to go by is the cover and what it says on the back and you can bring it home and it's complete shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: I still haven't dipped my toes into the HD gaming experience.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like the PS3, but I'm not sure due to price and limited titles, although a good 6 would do for me for now.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hate Metal Gear Solid as it just doesn't float my boat.
[SPEAKER_06]: Personally, I hate cutscenes.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Xbox 360 has a catalog, but I get burned on the original Xbox when shortly after buying one, they went and retired it for the 360.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also, my brother has gone through four 360s.
[SPEAKER_06]: So is now a good time to buy a 360?
[SPEAKER_06]: Have the issues of Red Ring of Death been cured?
[SPEAKER_06]: Or should I wait a little longer as the trading games pile is getting bigger every day?
[SPEAKER_06]: Is a smaller, cooler 360 on the horizon?
[SPEAKER_06]: I know it's an old question from last year and before, but now that 360 is maturing, has it lost its legs and arthritis is setting in?
[SPEAKER_06]: Or is now the time to jump in?
[SPEAKER_06]: An arcade is cheaper than the Wii right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have no intention of going online.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is a hard drive necessary for the download content?
[SPEAKER_06]: Or do I have to accept that patches are the way of the future?
[SPEAKER_04]: I would say that it's probably fine to buy it now.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think 360's probably going to be at its peak for the next couple years.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're right, the system's matured, but that's when all the really good games start coming out over the next couple years, and then we'll start getting into a new cycle of systems.
[SPEAKER_04]: As far as hardware problems go, the new 360's that they have out now aren't really as prone to the hardware problems as
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's what you've got to watch out for, is that maybe a new 360 is going to come out.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is really inevitable with every console, but there were some strong rumors this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think I'm spoiling anything on show roll.
[SPEAKER_06]: There were some very strong rumors this week about the Blu-ray, and I guess actually a press release was put out, so it might be more than rumor.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Xbox 360 is actually going to be getting a Blu-ray in it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Somebody's been contracted to actually put...
[SPEAKER_06]: Put that technology together where the Blu-ray Xbox 360 is going to be coming out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because HD DVD is officially dead.
[SPEAKER_06]: Microsoft has left them no choice but to get on the Blu-ray board if they want their system to play movies as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're not DVD.
[SPEAKER_06]: HD movies.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you've got to be careful because you never know what's going to happen.
[SPEAKER_06]: The day after you buy your system, this might come out.
[SPEAKER_06]: But that's just a chance you take.
[SPEAKER_06]: It happens with anything.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ask anyone who owns an Apple product.
[SPEAKER_06]: You buy an iPhone and then a few months later, SUPER IPHONE!
[SPEAKER_06]: Watch, there will be a super iPhone this year, just so you know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ross Steel UT wrote us and wanted to get in a few words about this.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to get in a few words on the idea of gays in gaming.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sexuality isn't anywhere near as taboo as it was five or so years ago.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now it seems that every other game is so chock full of cock teasing that it borders on the tasteless.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dead or Alive is built entirely upon sexual exploitation and the guy game was only pulled off the shelves because it featured an underage girl going topless.
[SPEAKER_06]: The reason we don't see gay characters in games or even a very deep exploration of sexuality besides making women as slutty as possible has nothing to do with the rating systems out there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Conan and God of War had frontal nudity, as you know.
[SPEAKER_06]: The problem here is the striking lack of diversity in the gaming industry.
[SPEAKER_06]: While game players come from all faiths, colors, creeds, and orientations, game developers do not.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, if you want to get other audiences into gaming, maybe you ought to start putting that kind of stuff into games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I think they also run the problem with the ESRB.
[SPEAKER_04]: They rate that kind of crap more offensive than female nudity.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, well, Rostu goes on Of course, I can't talk about this without mentioning the audience.
[SPEAKER_06]: Go to any internet gaming forum before that matter, Xbox Live, and you'll find rampant sexism and homophobia.
[SPEAKER_06]: One need only look at what happened to Jade Raymond, leaning up to the launch of Assassin's Creed.
[SPEAKER_06]: For months last year, sites like Kotaku and Joystick were more concerned with making creepy blogs about how nice she looked and smelled than covering the goddamn game.
[SPEAKER_06]: The idiocy climaxed in a horrific comic depicting Jade, a well-educated, experienced professional game developer, as a brainless bimbo who can't even pronounce creative
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: Thus, we get more objectified women and the role of gay characters is limited to the joke character like Makoto from Enchanted Arms.
[SPEAKER_06]: With time, as gaming businesses learn the importance of demographics and stop belittling people who aren't straight, white men, this will pass.
[SPEAKER_06]: We just need to hang on.
[SPEAKER_06]: This message brought to you by Pizza Hut, makers of the pure grease pizza.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: What do you think, Irene?
[SPEAKER_06]: You're a woman, an OMG girl that plays video games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you think that games aren't coming out geared more towards women because... See, there's a stereotype that women love playing puzzle games.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't think it's so much that as it is puzzle games don't have overly sexualized women in the games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Says the woman that plays Puzzle Pirates.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, yeah, I mean, that's part of the reason, because I don't have to think about, like, okay, I'm going to see some, you know, slutty thing, some woman, like, you know, sluttified in this game or whatever, but... Although, that sounds like a good idea for a puzzle game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Puzzle Sluts How would Puzzle Sluts work?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, they have, like... But they need to have... Okay, there needs to be, like, a code that you put in, like, up, up, down, down, left, right, left, right, B, A, start, and you get male puzzle sluts.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because we need something for everybody in this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, I think I could see how this might work.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: You would have in each, like... So let's go the route of, like, say, Puzzle Fighter, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: So you would have inside each one of the gems, like, a different woman.
[SPEAKER_04]: And when you break the gem, they would follow the bottom of the screen and, you know...
[SPEAKER_04]: more gems next to each other and they just start kind of going at it in the bottom of the screen until you get this big orgy that pile up in the bottom I like it brilliant brilliant patent pending
[SPEAKER_06]: Nobody steal it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here's a good example.
[SPEAKER_09]: Heavenly Sword.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know how the main character is this hot chick that kicks ass and all that stuff?
[SPEAKER_09]: I was kind of detracted from it because it was just like, come on.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's totally not realistic.
[SPEAKER_09]: If she were just a normal girl, I probably would have been more inclined to play it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Been more focused on actual gameplay than like, oogling over her or whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: But
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think that something like putting gay characters or sensible women in games is something that's going to have to be left up to independent game producers.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, like, for example, Saints Row 2 that's coming out, you can be a male and or female character, or you can be a transsexual in the game and run around, and you can totally customize your characters and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: But you know people that are going to be playing Saints Row aren't going to be playing them like seriously.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're going to be playing them to mock them, so...
[SPEAKER_06]: I gotta show you this, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, does this pique your interest, Irene?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because this story came up earlier this week, and I don't think it's on our show world tonight, but Lost Planet Colonies is going to be, I guess they're getting a new version of it coming out.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess it's some type of expansion.
[SPEAKER_06]: One of the characters in it is the Dead Rising star, you know, Frank West, but he doesn't have clothes on.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's just wearing a skimpy little pair of blue and yellow boxer briefs.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's all he's wearing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, is that maybe the contrast to your heavenly sword?
[SPEAKER_06]: Would you maybe be interested in checking out Lost Planet Colonies?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because, hello, good-looking man running around in his skimpy undies.
[SPEAKER_09]: See, that's debatable.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't think he looks good.
[SPEAKER_04]: And he's kind of retarded to be running around on this frozen wasteland.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it's kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's like, I'm fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that won't do at all.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I guess sex does sell, but do they really need to sexualize people?
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, there are plenty of good games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actdeft, by the way, is clearing up.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like the greatest hits version of the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, they added more crap to it.
[SPEAKER_06]: See, I don't follow Lost Planet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry, guys.
[SPEAKER_09]: Remember when games, you didn't even have to care about their sexuality?
[SPEAKER_09]: Mario walking around in overalls and shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, but as I think stories become more... I mean, let's face it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Video games today are practically big-budget movies.
[SPEAKER_06]: Big, big-budget movies.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, you know...
[SPEAKER_06]: I'd kind of like to see that sort of representation in movies as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it took a while for movies to get there, but it got there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, tell me which Yuna you like better.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do you like Yuna from Final Fantasy X, or do you like her better in X-2?
[SPEAKER_09]: Final Fantasy X is today I'm listening to Depeche Mode because I'm emo.
[SPEAKER_09]: I guess it also depends on what kind of mood you're in.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you just want to play, like your motivation behind playing the game, but if it's strictly to like get off, it's just silly.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like, come on, is that what you're going to base your game on?
[SPEAKER_09]: Some kind of like sexy character or something?
[SPEAKER_09]: You can't do more with what you have?
[SPEAKER_09]: You can't be creative?
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, let's do some more emails here because I want to get through the rest of these emails tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ben from Tokyo has emailed us.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wanted to clear some things up.
[SPEAKER_06]: We were talking about Singapore.
[SPEAKER_06]: Speaking of the gays gaming thing, we talked last week about how in Singapore they're adding homosexuality to what is instantly making a game adults only overseas.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that was Mass Effect was impacted by that because there was OMG lesbians for like five seconds in the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: So Ben wrote us, says, love the show, want to keep it short as I have to rant about some stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Singapore.
[SPEAKER_06]: In Singapore, it is basically illegal to be gay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Illegal as in you go to jail.
[SPEAKER_06]: More precise would be to say that anything openly gay is banned.
[SPEAKER_06]: Gays are not employed by public offices, not allowed to live in certain areas.
[SPEAKER_06]: That part also holds for certain foreigners.
[SPEAKER_06]: And homosexual acts are illegal.
[SPEAKER_06]: So complaining about the rating system is like accusing a serial killer of fashion crimes.
[SPEAKER_06]: By the way, it is only the American rating system that is crazy about sexual topics.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's so disheartening to read.
[SPEAKER_06]: You do have to remember that we are kind of lucky sometimes to live in a nation that at least we don't get arrested for it, even though there's still a lot of progress to make.
[SPEAKER_06]: You look at countries like Canada and Spain and wherever where gays can get married and it's just whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: No one cares because it's not like, OMG, they're going to come into my house and redecorate things.
[SPEAKER_06]: Watch out.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's, you know, it just, whatever, you know?
[SPEAKER_06]: People are so much more laid back.
[SPEAKER_06]: But then sometimes you have to come to that harsh reality where like, wow, you know, America's way ahead of some other people.
[SPEAKER_06]: Kind of just sad.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just sad.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, but even California is kind of more the exception anyway.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, if you go to any other place in the U.S., you probably, they probably won't be as accepting.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: It depends.
[SPEAKER_06]: It just depends.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like I was saying last week, I think we're getting to a point, I think we're very lucky, where most 20-somethings and most younger 30-somethings and most teenagers even, I think teenagers even more so, everybody knows someone who's gay and more and more people just have the attitude of whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's no big deal.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: They realize it doesn't mean they're suddenly going to fuck me in the ass when I'm not looking.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think people are over that real kind of childish mentality about it, you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, it's like, is that what they're really afraid of?
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, oh my god, he's gonna come fuck me in the ass.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have no idea.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm left to assume.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's funny.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: It is stupid.
[SPEAKER_06]: Copyright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ben wanted to say something about copyright too.
[SPEAKER_06]: While you just mentioned it briefly, I have to say that downloading fan subs and any other copyrighted material is of course illegal, even if there is no licensing in your country.
[SPEAKER_06]: Without licensing, there is just nobody to complain about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: That doesn't make it legal.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thus, fan subs are in a somewhat gray area.
[SPEAKER_06]: Note that this only holds if your country has a copyright law, which, for example, Thailand at least didn't have for a long time.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that kind of came up on last week's show about the whole copyright thing went back and forth.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_06]: More emails.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know there's a lot tonight, but actually these are pretty good.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ranma emailed us, very happy.
[SPEAKER_06]: There was a mention of Video Power on last week's show and was kind of running down Video Power a little bit.
[SPEAKER_06]: The first season had Johnny Arcade.
[SPEAKER_06]: He would come into the room, talk about games for five minutes that he's going to review, and then there was a 20-minute cartoon.
[SPEAKER_06]: But the second season was a game show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Four people would get a chance to ask Johnny a question to compete on the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: First round was getting the highest score in a game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Second round was trivia questions.
[SPEAKER_06]: After that was the round where you ran through the game area and you could get, you know, Jansport bags, Genesis, and Neo Geo console.
[SPEAKER_06]: I pretty much think that Acclaim did a majority of the sponsorship of the show, but I could be wrong.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, that's it for now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Keep up the good work and y'all in two months for OLRCon 2008.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's an OLRCon 2008?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: What the hell have I been?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Where have you been?
[SPEAKER_06]: I heard something was going down over Fourth of July, but I didn't know we were actually having a little convention.
[SPEAKER_06]: What the crap?
[SPEAKER_06]: Am I always the last one to hear about this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hear about what?
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess there's no Alarcon happening.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's Fourth of July.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ranma, you need to email me and tell me.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've not been told about this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nor have I. Or I forgot.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm human.
[SPEAKER_06]: I might have forgot.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll go.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, obviously, if it's all our con, I guess I'll go.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I'm just kind of curious what's going on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, let's advertise it on the show if something's going on.
[SPEAKER_06]: And lastly, Ranma closes with, this email was brought to you by Joey Paisanos of Mulberry Street in the heart of Little Italy.
[SPEAKER_06]: You'll love Paisanos.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: I think RustyLUT was completely off the mark last week with his rants over reviews, so I'm curious to hear your thoughts.
[SPEAKER_06]: If a game is bad, such as Lair, then the review scores will reflect it.
[SPEAKER_06]: If the game is good, such as Grand Theft Auto 4, then the review scores will reflect that as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thoughts?
[SPEAKER_06]: Keep up the good work.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: I never said that Grand Theft Auto 4 was probably not going to get 10s out of 10s from everywhere.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's probably pretty deserving of those 10s out of 10s.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm just saying that kind of policy about, you know, sure we'll accept the exclusive.
[SPEAKER_06]: What was it?
[SPEAKER_06]: I think they came out and admitted that they had traded for advertising on the site to get the exclusive review.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, that kind of sets a bad precedent because, yes, whereas Grand Theft Auto is a good, good game, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: What about games in the future?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, because they said, oh yeah, this didn't affect our review score.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's not forget about what went down at GameSpot and Kane and Lynch.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, let's not forget what happened to GameSpot and Grand Theft Auto 4, where there was a review that leaked out that gave it a 9.5, and then that was retracted, and there was a 10.0 review put out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's to say that they weren't going to do that?
[SPEAKER_04]: And apparently there was a process where they rate it, and then they do a peer review process, and then they re-rate it or some shit like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, it's just...
[SPEAKER_04]: It's fishy, and not to say that this game wouldn't have gotten high marks anyways, but it's still fishy, and it's not a really good situation to be in, especially after the whole Kane and Lynch thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Honestly, do people really give a shit?
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, we rated it 9.5, but really it's a 10.
[SPEAKER_09]: We were off by .5.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like, okay, it's a good game.
[SPEAKER_09]: We get what you're conveying with your ranking.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just more crap that they can throw up in their advertising campaigns for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's been rated a 10 by IGN.
[SPEAKER_04]: 10 out of 10.
[SPEAKER_04]: They can throw that in their commercials and advertise that shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just more points for them, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, there's our thoughts on that, and that's going to do it for the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you want to email us, mailbag at orangelaungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to tell you guys for future weeks, honestly, the more condensed you can make your emails, the better, because our mailbag segment has been going kind of long lately, so we're going to have to start getting choosier.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we do try to condense down big emails, but if you can do that, it makes it all the better.
[SPEAKER_06]: So just so you know.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you want to go off for a longer period of time, there is always a Skype line.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you listen to us live Sunday nights on allgames.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's get back into the gaming news.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a new card game coming out, not Eye of Judgment, but it's being released by EA.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's called Battleforge, the collectible trading card game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's coming up this fall and doesn't really say what exactly it's going to be, but they're comparing it to, of course, Magic the Gathering.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a fantasy online real-time strategy game with collectible trading cards.
[SPEAKER_04]: One to one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because, you know, developers these days love these things where they can just charge extra money for the expansions and all that stuff, huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, it's a collectible card game.
[SPEAKER_04]: What they're trying to do is they're trying to make a game that captures, you know, the fans of, like, Magic the Gathering.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be at, you know, the same level as Magic the Gathering and get people, you know, buying these card decks and stuff like that as much as possible.
[SPEAKER_04]: So...
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess it's a good idea strategy wise, but will people fall for it?
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, well, R-Type Command is coming out on May 6th.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's coming out on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's R-Type the strategy game, which ought to be interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: But what's kind of cool about this is that Atlus has actually announced that they are going to be putting out, just for a limited time, and just for those that buy the game from either GameStop, Amazon, GameCrazy, EB Games Canada, and some other specific retailers, they get to get a little free plastic miniature replica of the R9 spacecraft.
[SPEAKER_06]: TechMobile Kickoff
[SPEAKER_04]: will be landing on the DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: They haven't really said too many details on it yet, but here's what we do know.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's going to be a variety of teams with 32 to choose from.
[SPEAKER_04]: There will be all new cutscenes showing off dramatic presentations of various plays, a customizable playbook, stylus control, of course it's going to have Wi-Fi and wireless multiplayer, customizable teams, and it's based on, of course, Tecmo Super Bowl.
[SPEAKER_06]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: By the way, tonight we were going to be doing the match game, but unfortunately we didn't get around to it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Our resources were a little limited this week, so just a reminder, because this is the point where we were supposed to do match game, but we're tabling it to next week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry, kids.
[SPEAKER_06]: Our contestants are already picked.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's the Toshin and Footy showdown for the ResCode.
[SPEAKER_06]: And if one of them's not here, then we'll get somebody else.
[SPEAKER_06]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, South Korea, a 5.1% price drop.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Taiwan, a 17% price drop.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, it's very interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I guess those price drops have already happened.
[SPEAKER_04]: They happened earlier last week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hooray for price drops.
[SPEAKER_06]: That makes some people very happy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, kids, we're going to be opening up the Skype line very soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you want to give us a call, 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_06]: Our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: But first, we have a couple more quick stories for you guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: One of them is the Famicom Mobile, or I'm sorry, the FC Mobile.
[SPEAKER_06]: I probably should say it the other way because, you know, that would be a complete ripoff of the name.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I guess, I mean, it seems like the...
[SPEAKER_06]: Patent on Nintendo's thing has expired or something because all these Nintendo knockoffs have been coming out lately.
[SPEAKER_06]: And now one of them is a mobile system that will actually, not mobile phones, but a mobile system that will actually play Nintendo games on the go.
[SPEAKER_06]: It can actually take the old Nintendo cartridges.
[SPEAKER_06]: It has a 2.4 inch color LCD screen.
[SPEAKER_06]: It runs on three AA batteries.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's got speakers, a place to plug in headphones.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can plug the unit into the TV and play the NES games on the TV.
[SPEAKER_06]: and it's being sold I guess overseas but it only plays American NES games.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can find them on eBay for $40 to $50.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's because the patent expired for the original NES which makes me think in a couple of years the patent's going to expire on the Super Nintendo, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to start seeing more and more of these as years go on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Pretty soon every CD player will have a PlayStation 1 in it when that patent expires.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's going to be interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Unless they renew the patent, in which case, then, uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, this is interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is almost like seeing a unicorn, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: But apparently, Shack News website has actually seen Duke Nukem Forever, the game, in reality.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: They've actually seen the real game being played.
[SPEAKER_04]: And apparently, I guess, Shack News is very close to 3D Realms offices.
[SPEAKER_04]: And...
[SPEAKER_04]: They were shown about half an hour of footage from the game, I guess gameplay, including some environmental puzzles, interactivity, a host of finished weapons, an existence of an in-game forklift, and plenty of heads and arms.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my god, a forklift?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: What the fork?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see, it says, apparently 3D Realms, George Broussard, the developer, said, out of the blue, I just decided to show them Duke Nukem Forever for about an hour.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I would like to see Duke Nukem Forever for about an hour, and I'm sure a lot of other people would too, to at least, I don't know, how about an idea?
[SPEAKER_04]: How about you show the world Duke Nukem Forever for about an hour?
[SPEAKER_06]: How about you show them for like two minutes?
[SPEAKER_06]: Two minutes?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that so much to ask?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, seriously.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you think it's really, really going to come out?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it will, but I think it will underwhelm everybody.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess it's kind of like Prey.
[SPEAKER_06]: Even though I enjoyed Prey, it was kind of underwhelming to a lot of people because there was so much that went into it.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_06]: Like so much hype and everything that went into it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then I guess it kind of disappointed.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the thing about Prey, it like ended like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like the ending was just like kind of out of the middle of nowhere.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hear there's a sequel being planned though, so we'll see what happens with that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, we're going to open up the Skype line finally.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you want to give us a call, 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio, all one word.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can always find out more about the Skype line and how it works if you go to www.orangeloungeradio.com and click on Interact With Us.
[SPEAKER_06]: That gives you the whole spiel about how the Skype line works.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's go to the phones.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_06]: I got balls of steel Oh, I'm sorry, you're a little quiet What's that, sir?
[SPEAKER_06]: I got balls of steel You have balls of steel
[SPEAKER_01]: This is DJ Dark Knight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, what's up, DJ Dark Knight?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I see.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're getting a little happy about the news about Duke Nukem Forever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nah, just basically doing the running gag of jokes everybody else is posting about the balls of steel thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Whoa, the audio quality on this call is no bueno.
[SPEAKER_06]: Something's going on there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dark Knight, your call quality is like really staticky and it's probably going to drive our podcast listeners nuts.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hurry up and get, I'm going to give you like 10 seconds to get your question out and then we're going to have to let you go.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, um, just basically about the, um, I'm a little bit late to the show because I've basically been testing something else out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Um, mostly about the, um, GTA 4 situation and whatnot and, I mean, how much longer do you think the man is going to be before he finally dies off?
[SPEAKER_06]: How long what is going to be before it dies off?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, the demand is going to be before it dies off.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, we'll answer your question, Dark Knight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_06]: How long do you think it is going to be before the demand dies off?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, look at all the other games that have come out.
[SPEAKER_04]: They've been selling well for years.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hell, Grand Theft Auto San Andreas still sells really well.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to keep selling through Christmas.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's why.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because not everybody's up to the HD age.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's this whole domino effect going on.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is why Grand Theft Auto 4 is going to stay out there.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's because of the domino effect.
[SPEAKER_06]: By February 2009, lots of people are going to have to buy new TVs.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, they only have to buy digital converters for their TVs.
[SPEAKER_06]: And keep in mind, this is, I believe, America only.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not sure if Canada is affected by this or other countries.
[SPEAKER_06]: But at least in America, they have passed this thing where...
[SPEAKER_06]: all television will be digital signals by February of 2009.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you have to get this digital converter for your television.
[SPEAKER_06]: But what's happening is most people are getting scared, like they don't understand it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So most people are just using it to buy a new TV that has digital in it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And a lot of people, especially when you start talking about tax rebates, the stimulus coming up and everything,
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_06]: I believe the Xbox 360 and Blu-ray thing may be true they're going to want to get that out there by Christmas because they want to get a part of this domino effect because they get the high def TVs then they're going to buy the Blu-ray players and then of course you want to buy games you play on these systems Grand Theft Auto has a lot of name recognition this thing will continue to sell through Christmas for that reason agree?
[SPEAKER_04]: yes
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, good.
[SPEAKER_06]: You should always agree with me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, if you want to give us a call, 1-877-GAME-OLR, username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: While we wait for some calls, Loki, do you have any last minute stories?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, Resistance Fall of Man 2 is going to be playable at the PlayStation Day, which is coming out on Tuesday, May 6th.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm sure we're going to see a lot of press releases coming out of that probably pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Something else also kind of tying in with PlayStation Day, Motorstorm 2 has had a name change.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now it's being renamed Motorstorm Pacific Rift.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, meaning it's Motor Store 1 re-skimmed.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, caller, are you there?
[SPEAKER_06]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_06]: This is Spazinator.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sorry?
[SPEAKER_00]: Spazinator.
[SPEAKER_00]: Spell that for me.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, the screen name I usually go by is Spazinator.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, what's your question?
[SPEAKER_06]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, I was wondering, now that GTA 4 is out, do you think we're going to be...
[SPEAKER_00]: Hearing from the lawyer that we shall not name, we're going to see where those are.
[SPEAKER_00]: Lawsuits coming out of the woodwork?
[SPEAKER_06]: Pin it on Grand Theft Auto and try to sue the makers and try to get the game pulled from shelves.
[SPEAKER_06]: And heaven forbid if there's any hidden things this time around, although I'm sure Take-Two took extra, extra precaution.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Rockstar, they all took extra, extra precaution to make sure there's nothing hidden on that disc.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, now, correct me if I'm wrong, but wasn't there something mentioned maybe a few months ago?
[SPEAKER_00]: Someone here, correct me if I'm wrong, but some kind of
[SPEAKER_00]: Injunction or something on this guy, you know, saying that, you know, he can't sue anyone or...
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to say Take-Two complained about him in the court.
[SPEAKER_04]: Basically, he has to get someone else to sign off on any lawsuit that he does.
[SPEAKER_04]: But no, there is still right now... But only in Florida, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, anywhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because he can only practice law in Florida.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because we have to be registered there.
[SPEAKER_04]: But no, he's actually only able... Right now, they're still doing a hearing on whether he's going to be disbarred anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's still pending.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, I was going to say one more thing before I let you guys get going to the next caller.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, this may be just me, but I think we should probably promote this game as much as possible and get people to buy this game as much as possible.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's just annoying that, you know what, I have this lawyer along with Hillary Clinton.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, the more PO these guys get, at least in my book, the better, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: What we really have to do, here's the strategy, is that, I mean, yeah, there's one way to doing it, but what we really have to try and do is not give this guy any credit.
[SPEAKER_06]: We need to stop covering every little move he makes.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, and I've used this comparison on the show before a while ago, but I haven't said it in a while.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's the village idiot in our minds.
[SPEAKER_06]: Every time this guy does something, we publish it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Look what the village idiot did today, you know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Look at the lawsuit he filed today.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, we need to stop giving him attention.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just like, you know,
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know about you or any of our listeners or you guys, but when I was getting bullied in school, it's happened to all of us, don't laugh, Rice Princess, but when I was getting bullied in school, my mom always said, don't pay attention to them, and they'll stop.
[SPEAKER_06]: And to a certain extent, she was kind of right.
[SPEAKER_06]: The more you pay attention to these types of things, they go away because they're there to ruffle feathers.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what they do.
[SPEAKER_00]: You definitely get a point there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, hey, we appreciate the call.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you have any last quick thoughts before we jump to another call?
[SPEAKER_00]: No, I think that pretty much covers it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Thanks for taking my call.
[SPEAKER_06]: No problemo.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have a good night.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bye, you too.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like hearing from people we don't hear from too often.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, thanks for calling.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, we appreciate that.
[SPEAKER_06]: More calls.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now the phone's ringing off the hook.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, hey, it's Ranma.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ranma, I noticed a comment you just made in chat.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bullshit.
[SPEAKER_06]: Even if you do ignore bullies, they will keep at it.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what my problem was.
[SPEAKER_03]: I got bullied in school.
[SPEAKER_03]: I ignored them.
[SPEAKER_03]: It kept going to the point where I actually had to throw my fists up and get into a few fistfights.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I realize that times have also changed from when I was a kid.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I always kind of think a lot of people do things for attention.
[SPEAKER_06]: And obviously there's extremes in every circumstance where people are just fucked in the head.
[SPEAKER_06]: But a lot of times people do things for attention.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you don't give them attention, it'll go away.
[SPEAKER_06]: But there are people that...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_03]: Super Mario Kart
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you think this is the best Mario Kart yet?
[SPEAKER_06]: Or do you think it's somewhere in the middle?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's somewhere in the middle because I really dig Mario Kart DS more.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's that, you know how they said they removed snaking and so forth?
[SPEAKER_03]: If you do it right, you can still do it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just find it easier to do quote-unquote snaking and power boosting with the control stick than I could with the control pad.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what's interesting though is I find online people, like, it doesn't seem like people are cheating as much because you have a lot of people on there, you know, that don't,
[SPEAKER_06]: You have a lot of people on there that are playing with the wheel, for one.
[SPEAKER_06]: I noticed that.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's tons of people online playing with the wheel.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, a lot of people on the wheel.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, you know, it just seems like there's less cheating going on.
[SPEAKER_06]: The only cheating in the game, and something I really should have mentioned in Part A when I reviewed the game, here's the irritation I have with the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: The items, I realize it's a part of Mario Kart.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's got to be there.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a little much.
[SPEAKER_06]: They really needed to scale back.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I think part of that might have to do with them expanding it from like 8 to 12 cars at once.
[SPEAKER_06]: There is just too many freaking blue shells that show up.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, yes, yes, yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: A little much.
[SPEAKER_06]: You ought to be able to turn some of that shit off when playing online.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not yet, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: Can you turn item off?
[SPEAKER_06]: You can turn items off.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, all together, but you can't single one out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it would be nice if they gave you a little more customization where you can just turn off blue shells.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have it where you can do, like, you know, that the powerful items will appear less, will appear more, will appear normal, but to be honest, playing through each different mode, I have not noticed a difference.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I have noticed that when you're in first place with prior Mario Kart games, all you had at your disposal were banana peels and green turtle shells.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've noticed now you're getting more powerful items like red turtle shells and other items, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Once in a blue moon, you get a red turtle shell, but you never get a bullet, and you never get a blue shell, obviously.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've gotten a lot of red shells being in first place, but I've also noticed that when I'm in first place...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: I just love how they brought back the original power boosters and not a remix theme, the original themes.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was really enjoying that.
[SPEAKER_06]: It seems like they've still been slightly retouched, but it's still, it's quality.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not, you know, they didn't ruin them.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, Sky, before I go, let me ask you to see if you agree with me.
[SPEAKER_03]: With the Wiimote and Nunchuck controller, do you think it should have been more natural to use the Wiimote when you shake it to throw an item instead of doing tricks?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, because I think it might be too sensitive.
[SPEAKER_06]: And sometimes, you know, you get a little excited, you kind of move around, you hop around, especially if you're getting in the heat of it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just have a bad feeling that it would, and I sit kind of far away from the TV.
[SPEAKER_06]: So when I'm playing, the sensitivity is kind of, or, you know, if I'm trying to like point at the screen, it's really hard.
[SPEAKER_06]: I got to lean forward to get at the screen.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just have a bad feeling it would screw things up.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll meet you halfway.
[SPEAKER_03]: They ought to add custom controls where you can assign whatever you want.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's pretty much my return to the West Coast like you wanted me to.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's my return to the West Coast like everybody wanted me to.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I do know I am crashing on DarkSakura's couch for three days, which will be pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will be bringing some stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'll probably bring some New York City trinkets as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's Fourth of July weekend?
[SPEAKER_03]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, if it wasn't summer, I'd say let's have a late birthday party for me at Roseville Golf Land, but it's summer and that's going to suck.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, we could kind of make an agreement on my birthday's past, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe we could do something like that together.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll figure something out.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, we'll talk more about it offline.
[SPEAKER_06]: The listeners don't want to hear about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_03]: You too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_06]: But if you're in Northern California, specifically the Sacramento area...
[SPEAKER_06]: You might want to stay tuned the next few episodes because we're going to do something.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know we have some listeners in the stack area.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, quickly, any other last-minute stories?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_04]: The ESRB has added some more Xbox Live Arcade games to their list of stuff coming out, including Samurai Shodown 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, Red Baron for the arcade.
[SPEAKER_04]: Red Baron Arcade.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Revenge of the Plague Lord
[SPEAKER_04]: including Indestructible which is the cover track for that and Inside the Fire.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then let's see here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Guitar Hero 3 this week will be getting three songs from Muse, including Exo-Politics, Supermassive, Black Hole, and Stockholm Syndrome.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they're going to cost 500 Microsoft points.
[SPEAKER_04]: and one other thing we talked a little bit about earlier with the virtual console and people hacking it now they've already hacked and pirated WiiWare games and they have actually brought over some of the Japanese WiiWare games to the North American virtual console you can actually find those online if you're into that kind of thing but I just think it's funny how quickly they've hacked those apart already and
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, and a rumor of a Blu-ray console coming to the market for, or a Blu-ray included 360 coming to the market in third quarter, although I don't believe that, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, I was listening to Bobby's show a little bit and he made a pretty good argument for why it is happening.
[SPEAKER_06]: And plus, I think what I said earlier about the whole domino effect, I think it's damn well possible something like that's going to happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just a matter of time.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's just going to be hard with, you know, alienating their customers, but if they only use it for video playback, then that's fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, as long as they don't start coming out with Blu-ray games, I absolutely agree with you there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Absolutely agree with you there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's go to the phones.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, hey, DarkDeadSuya, what is on your mind, my friend?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, well, we were letting Loki do some last-minute stories for a little bit before we opened it back up.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, sure.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ranma, huh?
[SPEAKER_06]: We're here.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_06]: You might have to lower the speakers in your house because you're probably hearing feedback.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, well, sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: I got it.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, yeah, Ranma has a little Archon, but I had...
[SPEAKER_07]: OLR Central in October
[SPEAKER_06]: We have the Misty Dark Tetsuya OLR Central or whatever they're calling it happening in October.
[SPEAKER_06]: None of which I've heard of, so it's awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I think they've talked about the October thing before.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's the deal, buddy.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll make time.
[SPEAKER_06]: The year is a long time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Definitely we want to meet Misty.
[SPEAKER_06]: Definitely we want to entertain Ranma while he's here.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: If other strangers from the internet want to fly out here, why not?
[SPEAKER_06]: Come on over.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll have a party.
[SPEAKER_06]: My roommate's probably going to kill me for saying that.
[SPEAKER_06]: He loves that idea.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, you know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll make time for it all.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not worried about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then somebody's going to say, let's do OLR Expo in August.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know, I was thinking about that portable Famicom thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: That sounded pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not too bad, $40 or $50 considering it's portable and everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: What an awesome piece of retro.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to have to ask Jamie if she's going to pick up one of those.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hear it just plays Nintendo games.
[SPEAKER_06]: It does.
[SPEAKER_06]: It doesn't play any of the other stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, you know, when I was thinking, well, where would you actually be able to get Nintendo games?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because, you know, everybody stopped carrying them a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_06]: Flea markets and garage sales.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can pick shit up for like 50 cents a month.
[SPEAKER_04]: Game craze, or not game crazies, but playing trades, I think, still carry Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, like there's one of those stores in the Sacramento region.
[SPEAKER_04]: You got to think bigger, big stores.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're a chain.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's like 300 stores in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought there was only one of them here.
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, my bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then there's also, well, locally we've got our record store, Dimple.
[SPEAKER_04]: They carry NES games.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, when I was in New York City for a new NYOLR con, when I was there last year, we actually all went to a video game store and they had old Nintendo games.
[SPEAKER_06]: I remember because I found a copy of The Guardian Legend, which I bought for my friend.
[SPEAKER_06]: who let me stay at her place in New York City.
[SPEAKER_06]: She lives in Brooklyn and she has an old school Nintendo and I bought it for her and I said, Amanda, that's her name, Amanda.
[SPEAKER_06]: I said, Amanda, this is the best video game of all time.
[SPEAKER_06]: You need to treasure this game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think the bitch has played it yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: She's too busy with WoW.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because Irene, I know Irene called her and was like, Amanda, Kara's there.
[SPEAKER_09]: She's like, yep.
[SPEAKER_06]: Even though I don't think Irene's ever talked to her.
[SPEAKER_06]: But anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: Video Games New York was the name of the store, according to Ranma.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, DT, any other thoughts for our listeners before we let you go?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, well, I just hope Grady 2 comes out in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: 2 comes out in the U.S.?
[SPEAKER_07]: Grady 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ooh, I hope so, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: I think the odds of seeing that are much more than Cho and Iki here in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, God, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, DT, take care.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have a good week, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: And we'll see you in October.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, you too.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: See you later.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: RicePrincess
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, oh, you should hang it, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're getting it.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to hang the question mark block from the ceiling.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to put Tack and hang the question mark block, and then we'll put the mushrooms around, and we can put, like, Cartman and some of these other things they see on Justin.TV on the mushrooms.
[SPEAKER_06]: But first, we have to fix Justin.TV by actually wiring the Mac in, because the feed on Justin.TV sucks right now, so we've got to fix that.
[SPEAKER_06]: By the way, speaking of Justin.TV, real quick, did you hear about some of our friends over on Justin.TV got their stream shut down?
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: Take two, put the smack down, just for a day.
[SPEAKER_06]: They only got a 24-hour ban.
[SPEAKER_06]: They got some archives deleted, but apparently...
[SPEAKER_06]: Outro Music
[SPEAKER_06]: We had to hide our footage.
[SPEAKER_06]: Our footage is still there.
[SPEAKER_06]: We had to hide it.
[SPEAKER_06]: But we only did like 10 minutes.
[SPEAKER_06]: And if they had shut us down for 10, I would have thrown a fit because IGN and these other sites probably have way more than 10 minutes worth of video.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's all on YouTube now too.
[SPEAKER_04]: For real.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's retarded.
[SPEAKER_06]: Although Shadow Next Gen in chat says a bunch of YouTube videos were deleted too.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's just stupid.
[SPEAKER_06]: Free publicity for your game.
[SPEAKER_06]: But see, they're just bullies.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, I would say we should boycott them.
[SPEAKER_06]: We should ignore them, Rob.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's stop talking about it right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll boycott their other smaller games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good idea.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, they've got the 2K series.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I don't like sports, so that's fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: They've got their stupid, what, tennis game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Their Rockstar's Table Tennis.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck your table tennis in the ass.
[SPEAKER_04]: I ain't playing that shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then they've got...
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, they've got Dora the Explorer, which is shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: They've also got Mafia, which is coming out, and Noir, but when the fuck are those going to come out forever from now?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: All I buy is Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_06]: Any final thoughts from you, Rice Princess?
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you for being here tonight and giving us a female perspective when DarkSakura was unable to.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Any final thoughts?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to get myself a banana.
[SPEAKER_09]: No one gets that.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_06]: My final thought is actually a fruit salad sounds pretty yummy right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yummy, yummy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't get that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, that's going to do it for another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, if you like what you hear here on Orange Lounge Radio, please tell two friends about our show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tell two enemies about our show.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just tell two people about our show because that's how word of mouth spreads and more people everywhere find out about Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: And without you and your support, independent radio would be dead.
[SPEAKER_06]: But thanks to you, it's still alive.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I heard that because I was giving out our cards during the Zappos.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was like just about to play the outgoing music, but what, what, Loki?
[SPEAKER_04]: I was handing out our cards at the Zappos thing, and they're going to put it on their little blog site.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_09]: Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: How nice of them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're getting out there a little more.
[SPEAKER_06]: Woo-hoo!
[SPEAKER_06]: That's going to do it for another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Until then, I'm Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_06]: She's not DarkSakura, but she will be next week.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's Loki, and RicePrincess helped.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have a good week.
[SPEAKER_02]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_02]: To join us for a live show, visit www.allgames.com Sunday nights at 6pm Pacific Time.
[SPEAKER_02]: The views and opinions expressed on Orange Lounge Radio do not necessarily reflect those of the entire staff of Orange Lounge Radio or AllGames.com, but we're probably right anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: See you next week!