[SPEAKER_01]: The New Nintendo Channel is up and running, Burnout Paradise is soon headed to the PC, and the classic first-person shooter is about to get another sequel.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello everybody out there on the internet and welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: We are that podcast on the internet dedicated to video games, video gaming, gaming culture, and the gamer lifestyle.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_04]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_04]: Joining me as always, say hello to the one and only Jamie Summers, also known as DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_04]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm tired.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're tired?
[SPEAKER_04]: Been a long weekend?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's been a long everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's been a hot weekend too, and I'm worried about next weekend because it's supposed to be like 20 degrees hotter.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm like, we're going to die during the show, so I've got to figure out air conditioning plans.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a solution for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_06]: That window, does it have a screen?
[SPEAKER_04]: It does have a screen on it, so you can't do a little thingy, I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can kick that screen off there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Take the screen off.
[SPEAKER_06]: Put it in the air conditioner, put a block over it.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's not that hard.
[SPEAKER_14]: See those little black things on there?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's for pushing the screen off.
[SPEAKER_14]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: This is now Home Improvement, the podcast.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, and on top of that, it's Studio Improvement.
[SPEAKER_04]: The other voice you hear over there, Tech Master Loki, since he's talking out of turn.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm talking in turn.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it's easy and cheap.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're not expensive.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll figure something out.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's why we have a budget!
[SPEAKER_04]: I got a week to figure it out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which means I'll do something about it on Saturday.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll worry about it tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_04]: And how are you doing, Loki?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm doing fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_04]: Had a good week?
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh, yeah, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, all things considered.
[SPEAKER_04]: You went out of town today, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I went to Oakland and then I came back from Oakland.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you're back alive!
[SPEAKER_04]: Amazing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oakland sucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: and I helped by taking pictures of stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a pinball table and I helped.
[SPEAKER_06]: I haven't been video game shopping in a while I have enough games to hold me over I'm just gonna pretend that it's not dude, you know, playing him
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not, what, Robert Downey Jr.?
[SPEAKER_04]: You're not a big... I thought you loved the movie.
[SPEAKER_06]: I do.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you just don't like him.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I'm going to take you to see it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can do it tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, because... Oh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, somebody's back in town tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've got to go hang with them.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, we'll go this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: We will.
[SPEAKER_04]: I still kind of want to see Speed Racer even though everything I've heard about it is terrible.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've been hearing a lot of people like it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you see it, Loki?
[SPEAKER_04]: It was awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Was it?
[SPEAKER_04]: See, now I heard you wouldn't like Speed Racer unless you're a seven-year-old boy.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hate Speed Racer.
[SPEAKER_14]: I absolutely hate the cartoon and I like the movie.
[SPEAKER_06]: See, I like Speed Racer because it's done by Tatsunoko Studios and that's the place that gave us Gatchaman.
[SPEAKER_14]: Speed Racer X
[SPEAKER_14]: Uh, not really, but it's cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's cool in its own right.
[SPEAKER_06]: As long as the Mach 5 has all of its crap, I'm happy.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, that's the game they need to make.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to see a game like F-Zero, but on the Xbox 360 or PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, there was Fatal Inertia, but that was kind of eh.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to see something that'll just blow my mind with how great the graphics are and all that.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was supposed to be blow-my-mind awesome, but it was blow-my-mind average, so...
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_14]: and you can actually um you know rank up i think all the way to level 10 so i have a long ways to go there i like how they do it it's basically just experience or i guess money that you earn throughout the game so you can play you know for quite a while there's a few lag issues i ran into overall it's pretty good um i just absolutely love that game what can i say um
[SPEAKER_14]: Other than Grand Theft Auto, I did get to play a few other games today.
[SPEAKER_14]: I played God of War Chains of Olympus, and that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: I played mainly the demo before, so it was nice to actually get to play the full game.
[SPEAKER_14]: If you like God of War, you're going to love this game.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's absolutely amazing to see that they were able to put a God of War game onto the PSP and not really sacrifice anything, so that was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: And then, of course, more Space Invaders Extreme, and that game is just all sorts of awesome.
[SPEAKER_14]: So...
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, that's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_14]: I've been trying this week to get around playing Speed Racer for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_14]: And especially after last night, it was funny because Nellie went and saw the movie with me.
[SPEAKER_14]: And she's like, do they have a game for this?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm like... Wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Your wife, who hates games that aren't called Bejeweled or Zuma, wanted to go buy a video game.
[SPEAKER_06]: She likes Excite Truck.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah, I forgot she liked Excite Truck too.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, she said that this would be perfect if they had Excite Truck, but with those tracks.
[SPEAKER_14]: She's like, that would be perfect.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm like, well, they have a game for it.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm not sure if it's like Excite Truck.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm pretty sure it's not, but you can try it anyways.
[SPEAKER_04]: But does she like Mario Kart?
[SPEAKER_14]: She hasn't played Mario Kart yet.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't think she would.
[SPEAKER_14]: She loves Excite Truck.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is your wife a fan of Monster Trucks or something?
[SPEAKER_14]: No, she just likes the gameplay of that.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I hope to God they announce a sequel because...
[SPEAKER_14]: That game needs a sequel.
[SPEAKER_04]: Frisbee says Excite Truck should come down in price.
[SPEAKER_04]: It should.
[SPEAKER_04]: Has it not come down in price after all this time?
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's Excite Truck Chanel.
[SPEAKER_04]: Amazing.
[SPEAKER_14]: As far as I remember, it's not being sold anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, so anything else for your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: And it was a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had a lot of fun playing Mario Kart Online with them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, I won.
[SPEAKER_04]: I made it even more fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I lost battle mode, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: They whooped me in battle, but I won the race mode.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't like battle mode.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's not as cool as it used to be.
[SPEAKER_04]: The battle mode is not nearly as cool as it used to be, but the game... I'd consider versus mode like the game itself, and that's great.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love the courses.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love the new courses.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're all so good.
[SPEAKER_14]: I still stand by not really caring for their selection of retro courses that they brought back.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I really think that there was a few tracks in there that they should have brought in.
[SPEAKER_14]: Maybe he had taken a vote or something?
[SPEAKER_04]: See, now, but here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: If Nintendo was smart about their online strategy, they would have downloadable tracks, and they could do more retro stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, and that's the key phrase, if they were smart.
[SPEAKER_14]: But the thing is, they're not, and they're playing it way too damn safe, and there's not going to be downloadable content available for these games.
[SPEAKER_14]: for quite a while.
[SPEAKER_14]: And there is one game, and that's coming up in the show roll, about download content that... I know that there's a service that they're... Well, they already unveiled it or announced it, but it's not being implemented until the summer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, here's the other weird thing is that, you know, they've got another problem on that Wii to figure out, and that's the fact that I ran out of space on my Wii this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, granted, I've downloaded, like, crap loads of virtual console games because I'm a whore for retro games.
[SPEAKER_04]: and you know every channel they released and when I finally copied the Mario Kart channel or I wanted to or no no I copied the Mario Kart channel and then when that new channel came out this week that we're going to talk about later I ran out of space I couldn't install it I had to go back and delete so I've already filled up my Wii and WiiWare's not even up yet
[SPEAKER_04]: They've got a storage problem on top of everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know how the hell I'm going to fit download content on that thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Luckily, the WiiWare games aren't that large.
[SPEAKER_14]: Like, under 48 megs.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I'm going to have to copy the virtual console games to my card and copy them over to one of my players.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just such a hassle.
[SPEAKER_04]: One little patch is all it would take to use that SD card as a normal memory.
[SPEAKER_04]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yep, and that's Nintendo, though, for you.
[SPEAKER_14]: If it works and it's a hassle, that's okay for us.
[SPEAKER_14]: Just like the Friends codes.
[SPEAKER_14]: It works, but it's a hassle.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mr. Bobby Blackwolf, the man that precedes us on All Games Radio on Sunday nights when we tape live, he goes live at 5 o'clock Pacific.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's calling me out.
[SPEAKER_04]: He says, I would beat you, Sky.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well...
[SPEAKER_04]: I see that challenge, Mr. Blackwolf.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll set up a challenge this week at some point.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm actually not that great at Mario Kart.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to play.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I'll play.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, this can be the Chromehounds event that never was.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, I'm not that great at Mario Kart, but I'll play.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll play.
[SPEAKER_04]: It'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, Bobby.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's set up a time.
[SPEAKER_14]: Especially, you know, and that's another thing that I don't really care about this Mario Kart.
[SPEAKER_14]: The fact that the AI is retarded and the item selection is also retarded, because when you're up in the first place, you get nothing, and when you're in the last place, it's like, Blue Shell, Blue Shell, Blue Shell, Blue Shell.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Blue Shells need to die to fire.
[SPEAKER_04]: Other Nintendo games I've been playing this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: I picked up a game for $15 at Costco.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the Williams pinball table collection.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think that's the actual name of the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I apologize.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you can't miss it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the pinball collection featuring all the Williams tables.
[SPEAKER_04]: So not only did DarkSakura have a pinball week, I did too.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I played the shit out of pinball.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was awesome to get to play that again.
[SPEAKER_04]: And for the value, considering I only paid $15 for it, and I imagine it's $19.99 normally because Costco marks everything down, it's not a bad deal at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: with all the tables you get in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have a lot of retro tables in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: When you consider that Pinball FX on Xbox Live is $10, and they're very similar, but in the case of the Wii One, you get to play games you remember and love.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've got to tell you, the control scheme is kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: Funny in a good way.
[SPEAKER_04]: What you do, you use the Wii and the Nunchuck, I mean the Wiimote and the Nunchuck, and the trigger on the Wiimote is the right flipper, and then the little trigger on the Nunchuck is the left flipper.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: Which I think is interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you get 100,000 points on this table, then you get a credit to play the tournament games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which I thought was kind of cute.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's good that they have that on the analog.
[SPEAKER_06]: For example, Pinbot, like you were saying, has the spiral on it to where it's not the very top one.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like the second to last one gives you more points.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right, skill shots.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tons of pinball games have skill shots.
[SPEAKER_04]: The older ones, not so much.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was just kind of about which chute would it go down to.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yeah, Pinbot and some of the other later ones.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's got some great tables in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: A Whirlwind.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember that one?
[SPEAKER_04]: That one was fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: We almost bought a Whirlwind.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_06]: But the good thing about Whirlwind, though, is that you actually want to have the real table for that so that when you go inside after being outside all day and the wind blows on you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, it actually blows the wind at you.
[SPEAKER_04]: And unfortunately, the Wii doesn't do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sad.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's good times.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: So what else was all on that collection?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, gosh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Black Knight, I know, was there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Taxi, AJ Mix is pointing out in chat.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess they looked it up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, Actdeft is linking me to a page that has more information about the game because I'm too lazy to go grab my copy of the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It has some really old tables in it, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, what is the one?
[SPEAKER_04]: There's one with, like, a giant Satan on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a very early, early table on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: As long as it doesn't have Hyperball, then I'm okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gorgar.
[SPEAKER_04]: The first ever talking pinball machine.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the one with Satan on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Space Shuttle is on there too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I'm looking at the list.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see which of these I own.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: But seriously, for the value, it's a great value.
[SPEAKER_04]: Especially when you consider there's a very comparable game where the tables aren't quite as memorable.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, don't get me wrong.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like Pinball FX, but it's not quite as memorable as some of these tables.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, they're classic tables for a reason.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sadly, the Tommy table is not in the game, DJ Dark Knight.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Tommy table is freaking awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you like pinball at all, it's worth the money to get this for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's my thoughts on that.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was the big thing about Black Knight, the Magna save.
[SPEAKER_04]: mm-hmm mm-hmm they sent us the wrong magnet safe stickers all right so that's gonna do it for my gaming week because otherwise I was just playing World of Warcraft and usual by the way World of Warcraft accomplishment are you ready I got my epic flight form on my druid this week 5,000 gold down the crapper here's your applause ready all right thank you I got one clap
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's get to some housekeeping and then we'll get to the gaming news tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, guess what?
[SPEAKER_04]: The All Games...
[SPEAKER_04]: BlackWolf says, I thought that was a slap, not a clap
[SPEAKER_04]: GS68 says some jackass columnist for Time compared WoW to Scrabulist.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: So we're doing a brand new game tonight, and I haven't seen... We're doing Bumper Stumpers.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: We need to get that res code away.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I was going to have FootyMonster battle Toshin tonight, and I see FootyMonster's in chat, so I know he's good to go.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't see Toshin, so I'm a little worried.
[SPEAKER_04]: But we're giving away that damn code tonight, even if it kills me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ew!
[SPEAKER_04]: What are you ewing?
[SPEAKER_06]: Funhaus is in that collection, and I hate that game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Funhaus is cool, shut up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because his stupid head.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll give you more details on the game in Part B when we play the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: And let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Otherwise, we always have our MySpace at Orange Lounge Radio on MySpace.
[SPEAKER_04]: Our live journal community is Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_04]: No radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're also on Facebook.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just search for O-L-R-M-E.
[SPEAKER_04]: O-L-R-M-Y.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gaming news.
[SPEAKER_04]: We had a lot this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Take it away, Loki.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_14]: Of course, as Rob was mentioning,
[SPEAKER_14]: When he tried to install the Nintendo Channel, his Wii said, no, you're out of space.
[SPEAKER_14]: But the Nintendo Channel, or as it's known in Japan, everybody's Nintendo Channel.
[SPEAKER_14]: Fuck that, it's my Nintendo Channel now.
[SPEAKER_14]: Is available on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_14]: It will allow you to rate different games.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think Wii...
[SPEAKER_14]: WeWare games, Virtual Console, and full Wii games after you've played them for an hour, as well as there's going to be some, I think, video that you can watch of different games.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think the coolest thing, though, that you'll probably see available for it is DS demo downloads, which is pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_14]: You can stream those to your DS just like a download station.
[SPEAKER_14]: So go check it out.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's absolutely free, and who doesn't like demos?
[SPEAKER_04]: Free if you sell your soul to Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, because you have to agree that the thing will, I don't know, monitor.
[SPEAKER_04]: What the hell is it doing?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's sending anonymous usage data about the games you've been playing.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you know how the Wii's been secretly compiling the amount of time?
[SPEAKER_04]: You can go to that note in your board, and you can see how long you've been playing the games?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that information gets sent to Nintendo, and in turn, you get the list of DS games.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're like, you don't do it?
[SPEAKER_04]: No games.
[SPEAKER_04]: No DS demos for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, I'm not too worried about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I gladly clicked yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I don't care.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, seriously, what is Nintendo going to do knowing that some, you know, schmo in Sacramento, California was playing way too much, you know, And they'll know that I like Excite Truck and then they'll go, hey, people like Excite Truck, let's make another one.
[SPEAKER_14]: And that's not a bad thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's fairly smart of them to have something like that enacted.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a good way to... I think it's a good non-intrusive way, I think, for market research.
[SPEAKER_14]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_14]: This isn't like EA where it's like, hey, we've got your credit card number.
[SPEAKER_14]: We want to know what you're buying.
[SPEAKER_04]: True, I don't think Nintendo saves your credit card information because you have to input it every freaking time.
[SPEAKER_14]: Once again, it works, but it's an inconvenience.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you actually check out the channel?
[SPEAKER_14]: Nope, did not download it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Didn't even plug it in.
[SPEAKER_14]: Too busy playing Grand Theft Auto 4.
[SPEAKER_04]: I did download it, and it wasn't quite as cool as I had hoped.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have some videos on there, which is kind of interesting to see on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_14]: Isn't that just a recurring theme with the Wii?
[SPEAKER_14]: It wasn't quite as cool as I had hoped.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay, seriously.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was interesting.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, I'm glad.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's an interesting thing.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's also something they talked about E3 prior to the Wii launching that this was already supposed to have happened at launch.
[SPEAKER_14]: What's taking them so long?
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, seriously, what is taking them so long to implement this crap?
[SPEAKER_14]: It's like, oh, well, eventually we'll get a unified online service and stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, great.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm glad that you're catching up to Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_14]: It'll only be a few years now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, maybe they just had some fine-tuning to do or something, or maybe they just kind of rushed the Wii out there, and now there's only so many people that work there.
[SPEAKER_14]: People aren't interested in online.
[SPEAKER_14]: What are they talking about?
[SPEAKER_14]: Xbox Live statistics are bullshit.
[SPEAKER_14]: They're pulling it out of their ass.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm looking at chat here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actdeft says, I like the channel.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like the demos.
[SPEAKER_04]: AJ Mix says, demos is pretty much the high point, and it has the commercial that has the kid that says, I am Mudkip.
[SPEAKER_04]: I missed that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have to go back and look.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I was thinking like, wow, it'd be kind of cool if there was like a YouTube-ish channel where cute little viral things could be on there, but then I'm thinking, oh, but there's the internet channel, so I could just go to YouTube on the internet channel.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why bother?
[SPEAKER_14]: And then four hours later, you'll be able to watch the latest viral videos.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Other stuff going on in the Wii world.
[SPEAKER_04]: And a lot of fanboys, including myself, have been eagerly anticipating the release someday of Kid Icarus on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: And here's the thing is that it may have actually been spoiled this week by IGN.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know that guy over at IGN who's, you know, he's like the quintessential Nintendo fanboy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not that that's an issue, but he just is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Matt Casamassana?
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that how you say his name?
[SPEAKER_04]: Casamassana.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, he probably heard that like a million times in the third grade, Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, so this guy, he was in the IGN Nintendo voice chat podcast.
[SPEAKER_04]: First off, Nintendo has voice chat?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's amazing.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, they name all their podcasts after stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: Like they have, was it the...
[SPEAKER_14]: I want to say Red Ring of Death is their Xbox 360 podcast.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I see.
[SPEAKER_04]: So they make fun of the system in their name.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then the PlayStation 3 crayon-eating cast.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, fine, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: The IGN Nintendo voice chat podcast.
[SPEAKER_04]: He says in this, of course, Nintendo's going to have some E3 surprises.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, Kid Icarus for crying out loud.
[SPEAKER_04]: How many times do we have to say it?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's coming out for crying out loud.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, you know, and you kind of think this guy might kind of know something going on on the inside because usually, you know, these really big gaming sites are kind of in on what's to know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It really wouldn't surprise... There's been little breadcrumb clues to that this is going to happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: A, he showed up in Brawl.
[SPEAKER_04]: That should be a big clue right there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I honestly think that's a clue.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we heard that, what was it, Factor 5, I think, was developing an unknown game that was suspected to be this.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then, I guess on the next show, the same guy, he actually said, Kid Icarus, that's another one I'm really anticipating, just because I love the franchise, and I'm sure the developer will make a really pretty game.
[SPEAKER_04]: So he said it twice, that it's coming.
[SPEAKER_14]: Maybe if I keep seeing stuff, it'll come too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some things say they're coming and never do, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, well, I can't wait for, I cannot wait for Compile to reform and have a booth at E3 this year and announce Guardian Legend 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't wait for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's going to be the show winner right there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Technically, there was a Guardian Legend 2, so we went Guardian Legend 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: What was Guardian Legend 2?
[SPEAKER_06]: The Guardian Legend that we got over here in the US.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: The first one was Guardic.
[SPEAKER_04]: Guardic, or whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, just letting you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just
[SPEAKER_04]: Get together and make a new game that is like Zelda plus shooter.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: And let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, something that didn't make our little list, but I know I saw it on the internet.
[SPEAKER_04]: There was like some concept artwork that supposedly leaked.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some of it kind of screamed fanboy to me.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, it was actually, it was stuff that they were, it was a company pitching the idea of a Kid Icarus game, and they sent off a bunch of different shots.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_14]: But, like, it was weird, because if you've seen the shots, Pit looks all, like, buff.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, they have a bunch of different styles of shots and stuff, so it's not just that super buff one that you're seeing.
[SPEAKER_14]: And it was from a website, Combo, with a K. Okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: and I guess not to be confused with Zombo.
[SPEAKER_14]: There was another website that had some stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: They said that, I guess it was supposedly from Factor 5, where those pieces of artwork came.
[SPEAKER_14]: And they have, like I said, a bunch of different shots.
[SPEAKER_14]: There's some that look really realistic, there's one that looks like a really shitty cartoon, there's some emo shots, something that looks like it might have been out of Kingdom Hearts, you know, just like a whole bunch of stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: But yeah, some of it looks a little bit fanboyish, but...
[SPEAKER_04]: It's slowly... A fact that a Kid Icarus game would be coming to Wii in the first place is a little fanboyish, don't you think?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, I will be first in line to pre-order and then thusly buy this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I love the original 8-bit that much.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, you know, since they have the characters from Mother in there, maybe Mother 3's coming here.
[SPEAKER_14]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why you gotta be a dick?
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm not the one that's saying, hey, let's localize a game for Europe and I'll bring it to the U.S.
[SPEAKER_06]: Import time FTW.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anywho, for those who have been waiting for WiiWare, we have a bit of a release from Nintendo giving us some ideas of what's definitely going to be out for the launch of WiiWare.
[SPEAKER_06]: And if you are ready, has them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Defender Castle, 500 Wii Points, Pop for 700 Wii Points, VIP Casino Blackjack for 700, TV Show King for 1,000, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: TV Show King.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that's a trivia game.
[SPEAKER_04]: For 1,000 points.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, I like Defender Castle, and that's 500 points, and then TV Show King.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that going to be like Seen It?
[SPEAKER_06]: Lost Winds for $1,000.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like it pretty good.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Final Fantasy Crystal Chronicles My Life as a King for $15.
[SPEAKER_14]: That I'm not too sure if it looked good or not.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not buying that at a protest.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's no Dr. Mario.
[SPEAKER_06]: What is wrong with this picture?
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought Dr. Mario was like a late add to the list or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, but still.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's coming.
[SPEAKER_06]: I need to throw pills at Viri.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you can do it on the internet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: It'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you for watching.
[SPEAKER_14]: See you next time.
[SPEAKER_14]: Talking a little bit about Castlevania for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_14]: A second link, also coming from another Brazilian site, apparently has some quotes from Shinji Hirano, an executive VP for Konami USA, stating that Castlevania titles were headed to the Wii and DS.
[SPEAKER_14]: He says that we'll learn more information about these titles come next week, when Konami is holding a press event in the US.
[SPEAKER_14]: Goddammit, where's my invite for this shit?
[SPEAKER_14]: Seriously?
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, they promised us that when a Castlevania game was going to be coming that you would not actually have to use the Wiimote as a whip, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because that would be the most hokey thing ever.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, I doesn't really say anything about that though, but... God.
[SPEAKER_14]: If I were to guess, I would say you probably use the Wiimote as a whip.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, moving on to other Nintendo news.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wii Fit.
[SPEAKER_04]: We still don't have this game in the US, but it's come out in Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's come out in the UK.
[SPEAKER_04]: See, now this is Nintendo playing a little game with us called Here's What the UK Feels Like all the time with this game.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, darn.
[SPEAKER_14]: I can't get Wii Fit.
[SPEAKER_14]: So sad.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, well, at least I had Brawl early and Mario Kart.
[SPEAKER_14]: Are you sure you don't need Wii Fit?
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm pretty sure.
[SPEAKER_14]: Are you sure you should?
[SPEAKER_14]: I already bought Wii Fit, okay?
[SPEAKER_14]: So shut up.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm messing with you.
[SPEAKER_14]: I have Wii Fit.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's on order.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's paid for.
[SPEAKER_14]: I just wait.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, we're here.
[SPEAKER_04]: WeFit basically crushed one girl's dreams.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Quote,
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: I know it's just a game, but seriously, we already have to worry about young girls starving themselves to look like magazine models, and now we have a game that tells them they're fat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is this going to be a problem when this game comes out over here?
[SPEAKER_14]: Question.
[SPEAKER_14]: Who actually uses the weight measurement of stone?
[SPEAKER_06]: They do in Europe.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's retarded.
[SPEAKER_06]: She weighs 84 pounds.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: And she was so upset about being called fat, she ate the board.
[SPEAKER_06]: 49 and being 84 pounds, that's not really...
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it is unfortunate.
[SPEAKER_06]: And for being 10 years old?
[SPEAKER_04]: You have to remember, though, it is just a game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I kind of compare this to the fact that in brain training, like when you try to say blue, it doesn't pick it up.
[SPEAKER_04]: You go, blue, blue, and it doesn't listen to you.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you go, brew, and it listens to you.
[SPEAKER_14]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_14]: She's going to have to do a lot of starving herself in order to become a model nowadays.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's a competitive market out there, and just refit is telling the truth.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, they've actually been sort of showing a trend lately now where the super skinny, you know, rail thin model is no longer being considered attractive by a lot of companies.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_14]: I know when I get Wii Fit, it's not going to say I'm overweight.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's going to say, get off!
[SPEAKER_14]: Get off me!
[SPEAKER_04]: Being thin causes cancer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Haven't you heard?
[SPEAKER_04]: Fat is the new thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: The whole thing now is that there are actually studies out there saying that it's better to be, quote, overweight and active than be real thin and inactive.
[SPEAKER_04]: GS68 says, love handles greater than exposed ribs.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, hell yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, you gotta have something to grab onto, you know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't want to, you know, I wouldn't want to date some guy that I had to, you know, if I grabbed a hold of him, I'd, like, poke a hole through my hand by his hip bone or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or ow.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that... Sorry, skeletons aren't sexy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Skeletons belong in a grave.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I always mispronounce his name in chat.
[SPEAKER_04]: I apologize.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hippolytus says, Brain Training 2 has no blue.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that's good.
[SPEAKER_04]: That might make the sequel worth it alone, because I'll tell you, that blue thing was very frustrating.
[SPEAKER_04]: But...
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, fat!
[SPEAKER_14]: Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it took the game to tell you that.
[SPEAKER_04]: So listeners and everybody that's going to be buying this game here in America, this is your chance to practice your attitude, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because, you know, you've got to have attitude.
[SPEAKER_04]: So here's the thing, is that when the game tells you that you're fat, you go, I am, and that's more of me to love.
[SPEAKER_04]: You just have to yell back at the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, the whole point is just, you know...
[SPEAKER_06]: To just get out and do something.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the whole reason why I think that Wii Fit exists.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just so that you're not sitting around playing a game, you're up and doing something, I think.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that it doesn't matter what a game that, first of all, does not see what you look like, does not know who you are, has no concept of what your life is like,
[SPEAKER_06]: We need a sequel called We Fat that's specifically for fat and fabulous people.
[SPEAKER_04]: That should be the sequel.
[SPEAKER_06]: The point of the game is just to get up and do something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Seriously, that's why the Wii has sold gazillions of consoles as it is, and Wii Sports is because Wii has that persona of, oh, it's a video game, but you get up and you do things.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: You do?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't when I'm playing it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've really actually, I've kind of been enjoying this trend from Nintendo lately where their games aren't just about fun, they're about fun plus improvement.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's kind of like brain training.
[SPEAKER_06]: or we've got our Wii games that get us up and moving.
[SPEAKER_06]: Konami has had their similar games too.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's more or less that there's been all this complaining about, oh, video games rot your mind and you sit on the couch and don't do anything and blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_06]: But now they're doing something, exercising your intelligence, working your brain, working your body.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're making it fun.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think this is the whole...
[SPEAKER_14]: It's basically, they're following the money.
[SPEAKER_14]: They're trying to figure out what gimmicky things they can do to get people that don't normally play games to play these things and buy them.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, that's why they're focusing on the brain training stuff because people think, oh, it'll make me smarter.
[SPEAKER_14]: I need to be smarter because smarter is good.
[SPEAKER_14]: And then, you know, the whole Mario Kart and that stupid wheel attachment.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, that's pretty neat.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let me get that game.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's like I'm driving a real car.
[SPEAKER_14]: I thought that Wii Fit looked kind of fun
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm going to buy it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I got to say.
[SPEAKER_06]: The whole reason that I would want to play it is just because it looks fun and I like doing active things.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have to admit, that's kind of the reason why I'm going to get it, too, is that, yeah, it will kind of get me off the couch.
[SPEAKER_04]: How long it will last, though, that's the question.
[SPEAKER_06]: I still want to reenact DDR Night.
[SPEAKER_04]: Comments in chat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hippolytus says, Brain Age tells you you're dumb.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wii Fit tells you you're fat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gerardimo says, both of them together tell you you're fat and dumb.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nintendo is about demoralization, apparently.
[SPEAKER_04]: Queltipo says, can we have soul training, please?
[SPEAKER_04]: They should have Wii morals or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wheel of morality, turn, turn, turn.
[SPEAKER_04]: Show us the lesson that we should learn.
[SPEAKER_06]: Today's lesson is...
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the game they need on Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: They need some type of moral lesson game.
[SPEAKER_04]: And every kid in America should play it.
[SPEAKER_06]: We already get other people's moral shoves down our throat every day.
[SPEAKER_06]: We don't need our games doing it.
[SPEAKER_14]: I forgot to mention, I think this week too, I know it wasn't on that launch list, but I'm pretty positive that it's one of the WiiWare launch titles.
[SPEAKER_14]: Remember, there's also the Major League Eating game that comes out as well.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, you know.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: that's great more of a cultural and that's all it needs to be here too I don't think they should shove morals down throat but they should you know have you know common sense type things you know like you know sense training don't call people ugly names good idea bad idea the game good idea bad idea the game good idea or we driver training trick or treating on Halloween bad idea trick or treating on St.
[SPEAKER_04]: Patrick's Day yes that type of I don't know how you make a game out of that
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe like when you lose, Chainsaw Man comes and cuts your head off.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like Resident Evil 4 mixed with Wii morals.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wii ethics.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, forget it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_06]: GS68 demands pee training.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, now this topic has gone down the toilet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Next story, please.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't want the game with the toilet that sings like on those training videos.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, going back to... I'm sorry.
What?
[SPEAKER_04]: Gerardimo, good idea, feeding stray kittens in the park, bad idea, feeding stray kittens in the park to a bear.
[SPEAKER_04]: Great, great concept, great concept.
[SPEAKER_06]: Can I read the next one?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, you can.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry, I had to read that.
[SPEAKER_06]: We has games for, we has games for virtual console in the UK.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you want to know what they are?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh my god, in one of these, I so, so wish we would get it over here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, stop complaining, and what is it?
[SPEAKER_06]: They get Puyo Puyo 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_06]: They also get Metal Slug for Neo Geo.
[SPEAKER_06]: And... Now, I'm trying to...
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, these are actually released on here.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is one of the ones that's making me go, huh?
[SPEAKER_06]: Break-In is on there.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Cho Aineke.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: And for anyone who doesn't know what Cho Aineke is, it's the games with the mostly naked muscle men and speedos.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's a side-scrolling shooter.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Jamie wants Cho Aineke very much.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's the TurboGrafx version on top of that.
[SPEAKER_04]: You never know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Cho Aineke is, like, crack-tacular.
[SPEAKER_04]: You should petition Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know we won't get over here because people have corn cobs shoved up their butts.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not now.
[SPEAKER_04]: You need to play some Wii Ethics.
[SPEAKER_06]: And not even the good vibrating kind.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because it'd be a little bit less uptight if it vibrated.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, quick next story.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a couple... Quiltipo's readying his man beam.
[SPEAKER_04]: He says, ready your man beam.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, there's this company that's Matrix Software.
[SPEAKER_14]: You may not know them by their company name, but you know them from their games.
[SPEAKER_14]: They have done the Final Fantasy 3 remake for the DS and are working on the Final Fantasy 4 remake for the DS.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, now they're working on their own game as well called Alundra.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alundra!
[SPEAKER_06]: I like Alundra.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was a pretty fun RPG.
[SPEAKER_14]: The art was done by Toriyama.
[SPEAKER_14]: Uh, it says, uh, the latest project, I guess, is another original piece.
[SPEAKER_14]: Uh, this time, uh, from, uh, Marvelous.
[SPEAKER_14]: And it's called Avalon, uh, Code is the new game, I guess, because they did the launcher for the PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_14]: And, um...
[SPEAKER_14]: Avalon Code, it doesn't really say what it is, but of course it's going to be done in a similar style as the Final Fantasy remakes, kind of a 3D type of game.
[SPEAKER_14]: They said with the art style similar to Crystal Chronicles.
[SPEAKER_14]: Not a Lendera, they're not doing a new Lendera game, but Avalon Code is a new game.
[SPEAKER_14]: It looks spiffy.
[SPEAKER_04]: GameStop Insiders GameStop Insiders GameStop Insiders
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: The color is metallic rose is supposed to be coming over here.
[SPEAKER_14]: That is absolutely the first time I've ever heard of that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_14]: Absolutely the first time.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm pretty sure that this has never been mentioned on the show before.
[SPEAKER_14]: Right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Never.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, over in Germany...
[SPEAKER_04]: Some German retailers have also listed some other DS-like colors that are supposed to be coming out in Europe, and that is light blue, red, and green, and they all come with matching stylus colors.
[SPEAKER_14]: And you know, with metallic rose being such a pink girly color, I wouldn't be surprised if they maybe, I don't know, got rid of pink or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, like, they might be getting rid of pink altogether?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, maybe.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because, you know, I mean, what's the point?
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, there's not that many girls out there that need a new system.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, and Metallic Rose, that's just, that'll do just fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_04]: Will there be a comparable boy color coming out, too, even?
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know about that.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, because you've got black and white and all the other colors.
[SPEAKER_14]: It takes a real man to enjoy pink.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want Metallic Rose.
[SPEAKER_14]: But it's Metallic Rose now.
[SPEAKER_14]: Sans, you know, what was it?
[SPEAKER_14]: Nintendogs, Paw, Silk Screening.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what color I want?
[SPEAKER_06]: I want Death Metal Black.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gerardimo wants Sparkle in our chatroom.
[SPEAKER_04]: That'd be great.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sparkles!
[SPEAKER_06]: I want Death Metal Black.
[SPEAKER_04]: They just need, like, Chrome.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I want, like, Red Black.
[SPEAKER_04]: How about See-Through?
[SPEAKER_04]: We have Red Black.
[SPEAKER_04]: They do have Red Black.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, the dark, dark, dark, dark, dark red that looks like you're looking to Obsidian?
[SPEAKER_04]: Get a Red Black DS and set it far away.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, I could get a dark, a black DS and then use like transparent red paint on it and customize it myself.
[SPEAKER_04]: You could.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to customize my DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, if you go to the Nintendo store, they sell those custom DSs you can get in all those different colors.
[SPEAKER_04]: For like $4 billion.
[SPEAKER_04]: I came so close to buying one because I am a consumer whore.
[SPEAKER_05]: And how?
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe that's what I'll spend my stimulus check on.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll fly to New York and buy one of those DSs.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm just going to customize my own.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll make my own skins.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not really going to do that, by the way.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think you would.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dream Pinball for PC and Wii, Iron Man on PC, Perry Rodon on PC, Silent Hill Origins on PS2, Supreme Ruler 2020, which is a game about me.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_14]: It looked cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: In the U.S., there's not a whole lot coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_14]: I guess it would be an exciting week if you liked, I don't know, Chronicle of Narnia, Prince Caspian.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because there's a few games coming out for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that wouldn't have to do with the movie coming out this weekend, right?
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, maybe, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: 360 DS, PlayStation 2, PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_14]: I believe the Wii version is coming out next week for some reason.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: Castel of Shikigami 3, Ikaruga, DECA Sports,
[SPEAKER_14]: Wii Ski, also another $30 game.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's supposed to be a pretty fun little skiing game, also supporting the Wii balance boards, so you can lean on that.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: Drone Tactics for the DS, kind of a weird mechanical insect tactical game from Atlus.
[SPEAKER_14]: And then we've got Myst for the DS, which, you know, it's just Myst.
[SPEAKER_14]: You know, it's just Myst.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's just missed, yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I believe that's pretty much it, I think, for this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember that hilarious theme song the DECA Sports game had?
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_14]: We need to get that.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's in our Justin.TV archive, by the way.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you go to Justin.TV and you dip back in the archive, you can find that.
[SPEAKER_14]: That was the best part about that game was the really weird theme song that they had.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought the game was kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was like Wii Sports...
[SPEAKER_04]: It's almost like a Wii Sports 2 in a way.
[SPEAKER_14]: Almost.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's like a fun little party game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It doesn't have that Nintendo touch.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't explain it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Nintendo just doesn't have the really cool cheesy theme songs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's move over to Japan and look at what kind of releases are coming out over in Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not a ton of stuff this week but better than last week where nothing came out.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Darkness makes its way to the Xbox 360 this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's really the only big release on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: PlayStation 3
[SPEAKER_04]: Not a lot for you this week, although there's a couple things next week, but I'll tell you about those next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Coming out on the Nintendo Wii, Totsugeki Famicom Wars Versus.
[SPEAKER_04]: You might know that as Battalion Wars 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is coming out on the Nintendo Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's not a price reduction, because I thought they had that way before us.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um...
[SPEAKER_04]: No, if you want to import it, it's going to cost you $65, so I don't think that's a price reduction.
[SPEAKER_14]: I thought they had that a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, it's weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: Japan has been getting some releases kind of delayed.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe they're re-releasing them or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Perhaps.
[SPEAKER_04]: On the PlayStation 2, Aoshiro is coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that also is getting a limited edition version coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see what this game looks like.
[SPEAKER_04]: It looks like some type of RPG.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm thinking, I don't know, it has little cut scenes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it based on anime?
[SPEAKER_04]: There's no actual game screens I can find, just cutscenes.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm going to guess that it's a dating sim.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe it's a dating sim.
[SPEAKER_04]: When in doubt, dating sim.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it's some type of adventure game.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the category it falls into.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also coming out, Slaughter Up Core 10 Mach Go Go Go 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's Slaughter, S-L-O-T-T-E-R, not like murder with a pickaxe.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is Speed Racer.
[SPEAKER_04]: It looks like.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because it has the guy from Speed Racer on the cover.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, the classic Speed Racer.
[SPEAKER_04]: So some type of game...
[SPEAKER_04]: Rocketman, It Came From Uranus
[SPEAKER_14]: That's on 360 or Xbox Live Arcade and the PlayStation Network this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: So mature we are here at Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you have rockets coming out your anus, you might have a problem.
[SPEAKER_14]: Rocketman, it came from your anus.
[SPEAKER_04]: coming out on the Nintendo DS, Dungeon of Windaria, Luminous Ark 2, and Mahjong Navi DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yet another Mahjong title because you just can't have enough Mahjong.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see if there's anything on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, Bleach, Heat the Soul 5 comes out for the Sony PSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: So check that out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Those are your Japanese release dates for this week, May 15th.
[SPEAKER_07]: And good for them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good for them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, here's some very interesting yet fun news for us.
[SPEAKER_06]: Burnout Paradise is going to have a PC release.
[SPEAKER_06]: and Criterion said, okay, here.
[SPEAKER_06]: So they're going to be actually rebuilding it so that it works pretty well on PC.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're enhancing multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're doing community content, online features and resolution is at 1920 by 2400 and is pretty much straight from the original.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm kind of curious what community features is going to entail.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sex.
[SPEAKER_04]: I somehow doubt that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Group sex.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did somebody break DarkSakura this week?
[SPEAKER_04]: What is up?
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that should be interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: See, the sick thing is now I'm actually picturing that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, how would that work in Burnout Paradise?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Brings a whole new meaning to take me down to Paradise City.
[SPEAKER_04]: So...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, just remember that all the games for Windows stuff nowadays supports the Xbox 360 controller and, of course, the racing wheels.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you have an Xbox 360 controller, why don't you have a 360?
[SPEAKER_14]: Because you're like pro PC gaming, but you're like, I'm not that into PC gaming where I need to use a controller.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is the audience for that that big?
[SPEAKER_14]: I played Crysis with a 360 controller.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's just me.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm not that into PC gaming.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, hooray for PC gamers because Burnout Paradise is a solid game and I'm sure they'll be enjoying that.
[SPEAKER_14]: Another game coming to PCs everywhere.
[SPEAKER_14]: Everyday Shooter is coming to Steam and that was a pretty awesome game on the PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_14]: I would know though because I hate having to put my credit card information on the PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think it's available now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Lounge Radio giving you definitive gaming news every week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ah, we think it's out there.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, it's out there now.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm like, I could log on just... If I didn't think it would disrupt the all-game stream, I would log into Steam right now just to check.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I have to get that audio surf game too on Steam.
[SPEAKER_04]: I keep hearing good things about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: The only thing I bought on Steam is Portal.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not that anybody cares.
[SPEAKER_04]: Movie news.
[SPEAKER_04]: More video games becoming movies.
[SPEAKER_04]: One game that has been opted apparently for a movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess what's going on is that Naughty Dog has made the game Uncharted Drake's Fortune and it's been optioned by Atlas Entertainment.
[SPEAKER_04]: so that means that it is possible that in the next few years Uncharted Drake's Fortune could actually become a movie now when I think about video games that I want to become movies this isn't really one that pops right into my head but okay I think it could work though because it's not that much of a stretch it's just you know action adventure thing so Uncharted the movie may be coming to a theater near you in about two years we'll see we'll see
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, there's other movies in talk.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, it says that it's already in development.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a Bioshock movie to be put out by Universal with Gore Verbinski as the director, it seems.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, hey, that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: He did Pirates of the Caribbean.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it also looks like they've got John Logan as the screenplay writer.
[SPEAKER_04]: well they've made a lot a lot more with a lot less so you know the thing about Bioshock though is that when I play Bioshock it's kind of like watching a movie you know what I mean like I don't know like we're getting to this point where games are so realistic they don't have to be made into movies because they already kind of feel like movies does that make sense nope sorry not hearing you but uh doesn't mean that they won't make a movie out of it all right fine
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, it's just, you know, if there's money to be made, then they're going to make the money.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hear you.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's just, there's other games that I would want to see made into movies first.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like some of the other Final Fantasy games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: But maybe that's just the fanboy.
[SPEAKER_07]: We only had, you know, one good Final Fantasy movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that was Advent Children.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, well.
[SPEAKER_14]: Grand Theft Auto 4 Grand Theft Auto 4
[SPEAKER_14]: and 3.6 million of those the first day.
[SPEAKER_14]: So that's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I'm sure, well, they're expecting, I think, to do another, you know, a total of a billion dollars by the end of this year.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which is even bigger than a movie.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, the only movie that made that much money in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that an international figure or just a U.S.
[SPEAKER_04]: figure?
[SPEAKER_14]: I think it's international.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, still, I mean, Titanic is like one of a few, only very, very few movies has made a billion internationally.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_14]: Most of that is in, I want to say in the US, because the UK, I read, only sold like about 900, just under a million units.
[SPEAKER_04]: Only?
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a lot of games that would love to sell that.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, I mean, just under a million when, you know, about...
[SPEAKER_14]: 5 million is coming from the US, I'd say that's the majority of the sales there.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, fine.
[SPEAKER_14]: But still, yeah, it's going to do very well.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, it's been, what, parodied on a bunch of different things now.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's on Saturday Night Live and Conan, so... Although it was kind of lame on Saturday Night Live.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, it was a little stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yeah, I mean, it's definitely hitting the mainstream.
[SPEAKER_04]: So...
[SPEAKER_04]: I gotta back up in stories and talk about the Bioshock movie because there's some comments from chat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Chat.OrangeLaunchRadio.com Actdeft wants to know, will the main character save the Little Sisters or not?
[SPEAKER_04]: Quiltipo wants to know, will Johnny Depp star as a spinny splicer?
[SPEAKER_04]: Ranma says, just because the fan base is massive, that does not mean the fans will buy it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Possibly talking about buying into a Bioshock movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'd see it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'd actually see it, too, just kind of out of curiosity.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would be kind of curious how they'd approach that, too, though, because, you know, there's the whole little sister thing, and you can do very good things or very bad things, depending on your moral compass.
[SPEAKER_04]: I need Wii Ethics to help me make the decision here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here, hold on a second.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, it says I should kill you.
[SPEAKER_14]: Wii Ethics says I should kill you, sorry.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, it's not your day, Magic 8-Ball.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wheel of Morality, Turn, Turn, Turn.
[SPEAKER_04]: Show me which person I should burn.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the best ever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Outcome not favorable.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fire.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: APB is a game that is coming out from Realtime Worlds.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Realtime Worlds, they just bought the distribution rights to the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a big MMO coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: And basically, they're making no shame about this.
[SPEAKER_04]: They are saying they want to try and get this to Rockstar as Grand Theft Auto Online.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, originally, Realtime Worlds, they actually developed the game and they had sold the rights to... I don't remember who the hell they sold it to.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, they sold it to somebody.
[SPEAKER_14]: But they bought it back.
[SPEAKER_14]: And they bought it back.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because, you know, APB... Well, Realtime Worlds did Crackdown, you know, awesome sandbox game.
[SPEAKER_14]: And this one's kind of like...
[SPEAKER_14]: It's a sandbox online game, basically, where you have half the people are cops, half of them are crooks, and all sorts of chaos is going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's like a cross between... Cops and robbers.
[SPEAKER_14]: Saints Row, Grand Theft Auto, online, so it's not bad.
[SPEAKER_14]: So yeah, it'd be pretty easy.
[SPEAKER_04]: As long as there are guns and rocket launchers, I'm sold.
[SPEAKER_14]: It looks pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's the one they had during the tech demo.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was during Game Developers Conference.
[SPEAKER_14]: They had the custom characters, and one of them was Shiggy.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was with the mushroom boxers.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_14]: Very awesome character creator.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, we should say, though, right now, this is in rumor status.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not confirmed.
[SPEAKER_14]: If it comes out as APP, I'll still play it.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fanboy much?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_14]: I like my sandbox games.
[SPEAKER_14]: What can I say?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, they like you too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, let's move on with our next story.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, what's the best part about Mortal Kombat, Rob?
[SPEAKER_04]: Katana.
[SPEAKER_06]: What does everybody else think the best thing about Mortal Kombat is, Rob?
[SPEAKER_04]: Friendships.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fatalities!
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yes, fatalities.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, of course, as we know, Midway said that Mortal Kombat vs. DC was going to be a T-rated fighting game with, you know, no fatalities.
[SPEAKER_06]: But what it is, is they're not going to be as outrageous as they were, but they are modifying the fatalities.
[SPEAKER_06]: They are going to still be finishing moves in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember the last time they modified Fatalities for the Super Nintendo release?
[SPEAKER_06]: Sweat, yo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all I gotta say.
[SPEAKER_06]: And honestly, though, I'm going to reserve judgment, but I only want that game to play as Batman, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Amen.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because it's all about that one quote where he says, I'm the goddamn Batman in the comics.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is sacrilegious, though, to perform a fatality on Batman.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what I still don't get.
[SPEAKER_07]: He can perform fatalities.
[SPEAKER_04]: He can perform fatalities all he wants, although Batman, I don't think, really kills people.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think he does now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, in the movies, usually when people die, it's their own fault.
[SPEAKER_04]: Batman didn't try to kill them.
[SPEAKER_04]: They just died.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_06]: Depends on who's actually Batman at any given time in the comics.
[SPEAKER_04]: But see, the Batman god in my world is Adam West from the 60s Batman, and he never killed no one.
[SPEAKER_04]: So really, Batman shouldn't be doing fatalities.
[SPEAKER_14]: That didn't kill him, it was gravity that killed him.
[SPEAKER_14]: Gravity and a sudden stopping.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was an accident, he fell down an elevator shaft onto some bullets.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_14]: Um...
[SPEAKER_14]: Anyways, games like Mortal Kombat have been claimed before to turn children into bloodthirsty killers.
[SPEAKER_14]: But Harvard says otherwise.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because, you know, Harvard, everybody there is super smart, right?
[SPEAKER_14]: So we've got to listen to what they say.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or rich.
[SPEAKER_14]: Or rich.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hey, well, that's even more reason to listen to them.
[SPEAKER_14]: A pair of Harvard researchers say violent video games don't turn children into killers.
[SPEAKER_04]: Their parents do.
[SPEAKER_14]: According to a newly published book, Grand Theft Childhood, The Surprising Truth, about video games and what parents do, psychologists Lawrence Kuttner and Cheryl Olson dispel, of course, common myths about video games.
[SPEAKER_14]: And apparently they found during their two-year study that there was no data to support any connection between games and real-life violence.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is not the first time I've heard of this book.
[SPEAKER_04]: It sounds pretty good.
[SPEAKER_14]: They studied 1,200 middle school children in a $1.5 million federally funded study.
[SPEAKER_14]: Instead of studying children in the laboratory like other studies, they actually sat down and talked to kids after long bouts of game playing, sometimes in excess of 15 hours a week.
[SPEAKER_14]: Lucky kids, I guess, were playing a variety of games from non-violent The Sims games.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: Depends how you play The Sims.
[SPEAKER_14]: My Sims sessions are pretty violent.
[SPEAKER_14]: Was it...
[SPEAKER_14]: Grand Theft Auto and they discovered children who played violent video games those rated mature or above were just relieving stress some children did exhibit playful fighting after playing games but this was similar to what children have done always after watching action or karate type movies 51% of the male children who played for 15 hours or more violent video games per week were involved in fights
[SPEAKER_14]: in the past year compared to 28% who played regular video games.
[SPEAKER_14]: Doesn't make much sense.
[SPEAKER_14]: I guess who did not play video games.
[SPEAKER_14]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_14]: Articles.
[SPEAKER_14]: Got the wrong text there.
[SPEAKER_14]: For girls, 40% of the violent game players were in fights compared to, I guess, 14% of the non-violent players.
[SPEAKER_14]: So despite these figures, I guess Kuttner and Olsen say that this is just a correlation and that fighting was probably due to an underlying psychological problem that children had before playing video games.
[SPEAKER_14]: I like how they just kind of just, they're all, you know, even though the data suggests that, you know, they may be prone to more violence, it's just, we'll just ignore that.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_14]: I think it's already out.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it just came out, or it was about to come out.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think I checked it out on Amazon.com about a month ago, and it was coming out at the end of the month.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm curious about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's available now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, there you have it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it being widely distributed?
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you think I can walk into any Barnes & Noble and get it?
[SPEAKER_14]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_14]: It says right now on Amazon.com you can get it for $16.50.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: We are going to have a live cage match
[SPEAKER_04]: The Cage Match
[SPEAKER_04]: Tonight, the cage match is involving the Grand Theft Auto IV contest entries that Orange Lounge Radio received this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have whittled it down to four finalists tonight, and tonight, live on the show, our chatters will be picking their favorite in the Orange Lounge Radio Grand Theft Auto IV contest entries.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be great.
[SPEAKER_04]: So the way the cage match works, if you want to vote, you have to be in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: Chat.OrangeLoungeRadio.com And then you can place your vote via private message only.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll explain more about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: You cannot vote until all four songs have been played.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if you are in chat tonight, and you are the author of one of these songs, we'll go ahead and let you vote for your own song because you're actually listening live tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you get a bonus point, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, you ready to get to the four finalists?
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: They have to make, or I mean, in Grand Theft Auto 4, they have the radio station that plays when you're driving around town.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, our entrance had to make a bumper that could possibly be heard on the radio in Grand Theft Auto 4, but it had to incorporate Orange Lounge Radio somehow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like either one of our in-jokes, or one of our, it just had to have something to do with Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, so here it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: The four you can vote for tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's finalist number one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Finalist number one is Actdeft.
[SPEAKER_04]: And his submission is a little loud, but here it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's Actdeft's entry into the Grand Theft Auto IV contest.
[SPEAKER_04]: Enjoy.
[SPEAKER_12]: Are you tired and stressed of all your day's work?
[SPEAKER_12]: Pull back your anger and listen to O.L.R.
[SPEAKER_12]: Where you listen to hits like...
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't like you, can't you see Now get the fuck away from me
[SPEAKER_12]: So reject your false American idols and listen to Armour Shrouds Radio, Sunday nights, 6 Pacific, 9 Eastern, only on AllDreams.com Show is like pissing in an ocean of piss.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, that was entry number one coming to us from Actdeft.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's go around and give our thoughts on that.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_06]: A little derivative, I think, so it gets a seven.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Look, I would have given that a very high score, but look, you made way too much fun of me, and those are clips that are like five years old, and I am so pissed off that they've resurfaced.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not really, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: They were taken out of context.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll also give it a seven.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: She's not on crack.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's totally on crack.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hello, I'm Smith Weston, and I'm here to talk about a growing threat to America.
[SPEAKER_11]: Iraqi suicide babies.
[SPEAKER_11]: They may look small and cute, but don't let a situation like this happen to America.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh my, what a cute baby.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wait a second, baby.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why do you have C4 chopped to your waist?
[SPEAKER_10]: Nooooo!
[SPEAKER_11]: My opponent won't protect you from Iraqi suicide babies.
[SPEAKER_11]: In fact, he refuses to believe they exist.
[SPEAKER_11]: So vote Smith-Weston for mayor.
[SPEAKER_11]: The right choice.
[SPEAKER_11]: For America.
[SPEAKER_04]: God, the audio levels on these are all so different.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, that was entry number two.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ian M. with the Iraqi suicide babies ad.
[SPEAKER_04]: What did you guys think?
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_06]: It would have been funny if he hadn't been spitting into the microphone.
[SPEAKER_06]: The idea was funny, but the execution of said idea... But they're not professionals.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have to go a little easy on them.
[SPEAKER_06]: But that's why you go back and listen to it, and when you realize you're going, you're speaking into the microphone, then you go back and move the microphone away from your mouth.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it gets a 7.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it was a little popping piece for me that, you know, and this is a problem we even have on the show sometimes because we don't have sufficient mic guards.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it really depends on the mic you use.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm being a little more lenient because you might just have a junky mic.
[SPEAKER_04]: The idea was good, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: I actually would have added like some music or something to make it a little more upbeat.
[SPEAKER_04]: But maybe you didn't know how.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I can't punish you for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I think I think it's going to be tough against these other finalists.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I'll also give you a seven, Loki.
[SPEAKER_14]: uh could have been better if you had a lot more like internet clips of like babies cooing or like and like explosions more explosions more baby sounds and i think that would have been like pretty awesome but i'll give you like a seven because it was you know definitely more original and plain clips
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, here comes finalist number three tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Finalist number three in the Grand Theft Auto 4 contest is Able2Think.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's his entry.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a short one, 30 seconds.
[SPEAKER_04]: Able2Think, next finalist in the Grand Theft Auto 4 contest.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey ya, y'all are listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've got four strippers giving me lap dance right now and that doesn't even come close to the sublime audio quality of the OLR crew.
[SPEAKER_09]: If y'all are listening live, it's like a three hour orgasm for your ears, you know what I'm saying?
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, OLR is the shit.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now, y'all keep listening while these girls come back to my place for a little action.
[SPEAKER_09]: Come on girls, let's go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, that was entry number three in the Grand Theft Auto IV contest tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was Able to Think, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_07]: That made me snicker, but it didn't have enough going on, so it gets a 6.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think there was actually a Grand Theft Auto 4 reference in that one, which is pretty good.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's very pimp, like Grand Theft Auto is.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I give that a 7 as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: But again, same thing I told the last guy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Could I use some music to make it a little more upbeat?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, same as the last one.
[SPEAKER_14]: Actually, I'm going to give this one a six.
[SPEAKER_14]: I like the voice.
[SPEAKER_14]: The voice was funny, but it was just needed a little bit more.
[SPEAKER_14]: We're playing for a freaking limited edition 360 here, which should be going to me, I would have you know, because I am the greatest Grand Theft Auto fan out there, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here we go, the last entry tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Entry number four in tonight's contest.
[SPEAKER_04]: The finalist is, drumroll, SSJ100Matt.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here is his entry into the Grand Theft Auto IV contest.
[SPEAKER_04]: SSJ100Matt, take it away.
[SPEAKER_08]: From the makers of Sky's Voice the Game, Cosplayers vs Furries, and Orange Lounge Revolution comes... Orange Lounge Revolution Second Mix!
[SPEAKER_08]: That's right, the highly anticipated sequel to the community-created hit using the DDR simulation program StepMedia is back with a whole new list of ass-piping, anal-pissing, ocean-pissing new songs danced in.
[SPEAKER_08]: You'll play all new theme courses and brand new songs inspired and sung by all your favorite Orange Lounge Radio hosts like Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_15]: When you call my name, it's like a little home prayer.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm down on my knees.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm staying in.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want the world to know I'm happy with the pussy.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_08]: Please note, there are no real songs sung by DarkSakura because it would lead to the entire Orange Lunge Revolution team being physically castrated, dying in a boat fire on an ocean of piss while being incinerated by an underwater volcano.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: You'll also hear songs from Travis Donovan.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't get strung out by the way I look.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't judge a book by its cover.
[SPEAKER_04]: John DMN Bresler.
[SPEAKER_04]: You ever go to Duck Island?
[SPEAKER_08]: Your mom goes to Duck Island.
[SPEAKER_08]: And a ton of licensed music inspired by the show that the RIAA and North Steel UT don't want you to hear.
[SPEAKER_00]: Gaming community is fine, but there's no need to promote this cancer, and you might as well just offer torrents on the website.
[SPEAKER_08]: So come, and reserve your copy of Orange Lounge Revolution's second mix.
[SPEAKER_08]: When you do, you'll be automatically signed up for the online beta of whattheyplay.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's hot, it's new, oh snap, it's taking pictures of two guys kissing a disembodied head while on top of a couple having sex shouting fuck.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I poop from there.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it's only from the Nintendo Wii.
[SPEAKER_08]: So come on down to your local participating Liberty City game store, split a WorldCorp breach, bring your ferret, and reserve your copy of Orange Lounge Revolution Second Mix.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you do, Loki might dress up as Tim.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not a guarantee.
[SPEAKER_04]: There is entry number four in the contest tonight, SSJ100Matt with OLR Revolution second mix.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fucking ten.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was brilliant.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what we were talking about.
[SPEAKER_06]: We had clever music, clever ideas, good clips too, not just, you know, the same old ones that we hear all the time.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it wasn't even you singing Sky's Voice the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: You were doing something else.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know where in the hell you found that clip of me singing like a prayer.
[SPEAKER_04]: I recorded that in a karaoke room at Great America.
[SPEAKER_07]: You played it on a show before.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not this show.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it was on Travis' show years ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know where the F you unearthed that clip, but I'm taking points off for you doing that and subjecting all of our listeners to that.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I give you a 9.
[SPEAKER_14]: Loki, I would have given you a 9 or 10, but I'm afraid that you are, I don't know,
[SPEAKER_14]: Confusing the listeners, because I'm afraid that Orange Lounge Revolution 2 does not count towards the I Have Judgment numbers, and that would be a flat-out lie.
[SPEAKER_14]: So you can guess that.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, let's recap the four that you can vote for tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Entry number one was Actdeft.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actdeft.
[SPEAKER_04]: Great, and it was Clips and me singing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Entry number two was Ian M with his OLR ad.
[SPEAKER_10]: Entry number three, I'm so used to when it's actually full of songs.
[SPEAKER_10]: Entry number three is Able to Think.
[SPEAKER_09]: And entry number four you can vote for tonight is SSJ100 Matt.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm down on my knees.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm staying in.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, we'll use a clip of Loki that time.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, those are just random clips and four entries.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, place vote now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Send a private message to Sky in chat with your vote.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you're listening on the podcast, so sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're not able to participate in the voting process.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll come up with something for you guys later.
[SPEAKER_04]: Place vote now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Send your private message in.
[SPEAKER_04]: We will announce the winner at the top of part B.
[SPEAKER_04]: But for now, we have one more thing we gotta get to before we can end Part A tonight, and that is getting to our classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_04]: We gotta pay respect to our elders a little bit, because without our elders in gaming, there would be no Grand Theft Auto 4.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, DarkSakura, take it away and tell us your classic video game of the week.
[SPEAKER_06]: My classic game of the week is one that I have brought up a number of times on the show, which is one of the greatest shooting games ever.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's Radiant Silvergun.
[SPEAKER_06]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_06]: Radiant Silvergun!
[SPEAKER_06]: Radiant Silvergun is developed by Treasure.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have played this in the arcade, and I'm still trying to freaking find the Saturn copy, because, I mean, it's fucking Radiant Silvergun, hello.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the good thing about this game, this is one of the things that I always, always liked, is that you had, um, your weapons were all available at the same time, um, your different power-ups, um,
[SPEAKER_06]: You could do a regular forward gun called the Vulcan.
[SPEAKER_06]: You had homing missiles and you had a spread burst effect.
[SPEAKER_06]: Then you had like a lock-on spread.
[SPEAKER_06]: You had one that would shoot one beam in the front and then a ton of beams in the back.
[SPEAKER_06]: You had a plasma weapon that sort of reminds me a little bit more
[SPEAKER_06]: of the weapon, the electricity weapon from Raiden DX, remember?
[SPEAKER_06]: Except it was very thin and it would be blocked by whatever, like different items that were in the way.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then you had something called the Radiant Sword, which was a sword that could shoot out from either side.
[SPEAKER_06]: There was also a few...
[SPEAKER_06]: See, you didn't actually have your power to level up your current weapons.
[SPEAKER_06]: One of my favorite ones in here is these two balls that come out right in front of you, but you shoot them out and they hover and then destroy whatever is in their way.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I also like this sword that comes out from behind and then comes out in a wide arc and claps together right in front.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that's a very cool thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was very bullet heavy.
[SPEAKER_06]: and like the one level that Rob's playing on the feed right now is the whole level where you're fighting just this big ship that it rotates around you and moves and you have to move with it and it was a very very challenging game
[SPEAKER_06]: The Saturn version had a few different things as in it would have you play through all of the stages to unlock everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was like you were having to play it in chronological order, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was very bizarre, because you start off at 3, then 2, then 4, 6, and then 1.
[SPEAKER_06]: So there's all kinds of weirdness with it, but it's Treasure, so we expect weirdness from them.
[SPEAKER_06]: But you've also got four different characters to choose from, and each of them has their own little quirks and everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: You've got the cute girl and everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: So...
[SPEAKER_06]: The arcade mode would be played basically without the cutscenes or the dialogue, but there was a Saturn mode that did have a bit more story involved and had dialogue and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, there's one whole stage that you play, and this has got dialogue running all through the first part of the stage, and it's that, you know, sort of old man voice saying, we did this back in the day, and somebody shot somebody, and there was a big war, and a lot of people died.
[SPEAKER_05]: So...
[SPEAKER_05]: That's Radiosilver.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's freaking awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's treasure.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like a shooter, but with uniqueness.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know how else to explain it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's treasure.
[SPEAKER_06]: The only thing you can say about a treasure game is that it's freaking treasure.
[SPEAKER_06]: All of their games, where they may seem like a straightforward genre that you've seen 50 million times, they take something in it and innovate it.
[SPEAKER_06]: They do something that turns it around and makes it completely different.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, of course, they did Ikaruga, which, contrary to popular belief, is not a true sequel to Radiant Silvergun.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's more of a spiritual sequel to Radiant Silvergun.
[SPEAKER_06]: but I still honestly I think a Radiant Silvergun is superior to Ikaruga but that's me and if Treasure knows what's good for them we will be getting we will be getting more I guess re-releases of Radiant Silvergun and they'll give them directly to me and only you
[SPEAKER_06]: and GS68 points out something that I was going to mention is that Radiant Silvergun was inspired by Image Fight which was by IRM and that's the team that gave us, well the company that gave us R-Type and also completely unrelated to Radiant Silvergun but since I mentioned R-Type I have to say this is that if you order that R-Type strategy game you get an R-Type
[SPEAKER_04]: We covered that last week, but that's alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, very cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: You like it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I do.
[SPEAKER_04]: How big is it?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's, uh... We couldn't figure that out on last week's show.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's about three inches long.
[SPEAKER_04]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's fairly decent size.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, I'll bring it next week and put it on the cam so everyone can see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, you know where I hate tactics games?
[SPEAKER_06]: I love Rortypes.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it cancels each other out and you're ambivalent about the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was like, I have an R-type thingy.
[SPEAKER_06]: But no, Radiant Silvergun is treasure.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I should do nothing but treasure games for the next couple weeks, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not the game I was actually going to originally do either.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I'm going to have to help you out one of these weeks because I need to start seeing some Commodore 64 11 in these classic games of the week.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, that's all right.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've had a lot of good games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why don't you do it next week?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll wait.
[SPEAKER_06]: What system did Jamie not have?
[SPEAKER_04]: Commodore 64.
[SPEAKER_06]: Right.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll wait for a week you're not here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because they'll come up before the end of the year at some point.
[SPEAKER_05]: But is this not the most awesome thing ever?
[SPEAKER_04]: It is a very cool looking game.
[SPEAKER_04]: You want to know a secret?
[SPEAKER_04]: I've never played this game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I played it.
[SPEAKER_06]: The only time I've actually played this game is in an arcade.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, whenever we actually get our little Justin TV idea off the ground, we need to do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I need to play it.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what I did the very next day?
[SPEAKER_04]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_06]: I had lunch with sauce.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was in Las Vegas.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have to say that on the air.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: And more gaming news.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a very full show tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: We will be back with more of Orange Lounge Radio right after this.