[SPEAKER_06]: Welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio on this part B of our podcast on May 11th, 2008.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's Mother's Day, so if you forgot, you definitely owe your mother like a big bouquet of flowers.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you should definitely call her if you haven't already.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or, you know, whatever motherly figure is in your life because, you know, some single parents and so on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not everybody necessarily has a mom, but call somebody and tell them you love them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Damn it, love is in the air.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, myself, DarkSakura, Loki, here with you on Orange Lounge Radio Part B. We're about to get back to some news, but first, we have some business to take care of.
[SPEAKER_06]: We have to announce the winner of the Orange Lounge Radio Grand Theft Auto IV contest, which we're working with AllGames.com to give away a limited edition Xbox 360 Elite Grand Theft Auto IV.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: Orange Lounge Revolution 2nd Mix
[SPEAKER_01]: That's right, the highly anticipated sequel to the community-created hit using the DDR simulation program StepMedia is back, and with a whole new list of ass-piping, anal-fisting, ocean-pissing new songs danced in.
[SPEAKER_01]: You'll play all new theme courses and brand new songs inspired and sung by all your favorite Orange Lounge Radio hosts, like Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_07]: When you call my name, it's like a little home prayer, I'm down on my knees.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm staying in.
[SPEAKER_01]: I want the world to know I'm happy with the pussy.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_01]: Please note, there are no real songs sung by DarkSakura because it would lead to the entire Orange Lunge Revolution team being physically castrated, dying in a boat fire on an ocean of piss while being incinerated by an underwater volcano.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_01]: You'll also hear songs from Travis Donovan.
[SPEAKER_01]: Don't get strung out by the way I look.
[SPEAKER_01]: Don't judge a book by its cover.
[SPEAKER_01]: John DMN Bresler.
[SPEAKER_01]: You ever go to Duck Island?
[SPEAKER_01]: Your mom goes to Duck Island.
[SPEAKER_01]: And a ton of licensed music inspired by the show that the RIAA and Laura Steele UT don't want you to hear.
[SPEAKER_00]: Gaming community is fine, but there's no need to promote this cancer, and you might as well just offer torrents on the website.
[SPEAKER_01]: So come, and reserve your copy of Orange Lounge Revolution's second mix.
[SPEAKER_01]: When you do, you'll be automatically signed up for the online beta of whattheyplay.com.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's hot, it's new, oh snap, it's taking pictures of two guys kissing a disembodied head while on top of a couple having sex shouting, FUCK.
[SPEAKER_04]: See, he says at the end there, not guaranteed, Loki, that you will in fact dress up as Tingle.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's still implying, though, that it was sales of...
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, so there it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: Congrats, SSJ100Matt.
[SPEAKER_06]: But a big round of applause, everybody, please, to our finalists.
[SPEAKER_06]: They were all very good.
[SPEAKER_06]: And everybody that participated, we couldn't play them all in the final round.
[SPEAKER_04]: I get two claps.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, good job, you guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is one more than you got for your mount.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, here's the thing, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now we have to all throw our support behind SSJ100Matt as he moves into the final round, because I'll tell you what.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because it's a bunch of OLR in-jokes, you know when they play that on All Games Interactive or however they decide to do the final.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a lot of people that are going to listen to that and go, what?
[SPEAKER_06]: The hell is that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, I don't get it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we all have to support SSJ100Matt now by making sure in the final voting phase we all go and vote for him because we want him to win.
[SPEAKER_06]: We want to say that the winner came from OLR.
[SPEAKER_06]: So be sure to throw your support behind him in the finalist round.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll give you more information on that next week when the voting should be up.
[SPEAKER_06]: So check for that on our website as well a little later this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: So congrats, SJ100, Matt.
[SPEAKER_06]: Another giveaway to come later in the show, that res code finally going to be given away to somebody, thank God, in a new game coming up a little bit later.
[SPEAKER_06]: But first, more news.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, let's go back to some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't want to watch the stock market too much, but...
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess if you were hoping that Atari was going to make a big turnaround and become this really profitable company, well, no.
[SPEAKER_07]: In fact, Nasdaq has actually delisted them from the stock exchange because they have failed to... Well, basically, they failed to submit the year-end financials.
[SPEAKER_07]: And before that, the market value was way too low.
[SPEAKER_07]: So they have been dropped...
[SPEAKER_07]: Drop like an American Idol contestant who just couldn't make it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or an American Idol contestant's father from backstage.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you read about that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_06]: Funny stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, wait.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do we have more in the saga of one of the Davids?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not letting this show turn into American Idol chat.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not, not, not.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, apparently someone's abusive daddy, you know, a la Michael Jackson.
[SPEAKER_07]: Shut up!
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently there was a certain boo-boo, if you remember, last week with kind of doing... There was a cover of a song that he did that had the lyrics, Beautiful Girls, in it.
[SPEAKER_07]: That caused him a lot of money.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hate you guys.
[SPEAKER_07]: And besides, that was cheap anyways.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was as cheap as that one chick who was saying all the American Jesus-themed songs.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, so yeah, Satari got delisted from NASDAQ.
[SPEAKER_07]: And yeah, they're just...
[SPEAKER_07]: Going down a slippery slope.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hopefully someone will buy them, and it will be a little bit more than all Dragon Ball Z Atari remake games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, we reached out to Atari for comment, and this is all they had to say.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bad joke.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nobody's going to get it.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Chirp, chirp.
[SPEAKER_06]: Take a shot.
[SPEAKER_06]: LittleBigPlanet
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's talk about new and exciting games as opposed to games that were out like 20 years ago.
[SPEAKER_06]: LittleBigPlanet will be coming out in October.
[SPEAKER_06]: This was announced at the PlayStation Day 2008 event in London.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's from Kazurai himself.
[SPEAKER_06]: He has confirmed that LittleBigPlanet is going to be making its way in October.
[SPEAKER_06]: But one thing you should be aware of is that the open beta, not happening.
[SPEAKER_06]: So if you were looking forward to the public beta that was promised several times for the game, nope, the public beta is going away.
[SPEAKER_07]: So surprised.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a promise broken by Sony.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hopefully there will be a demo or something, but don't hold your breath.
[SPEAKER_06]: You'll probably just have to wait for the game to come out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let me just add another check mark on the board there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: But LittleBigPlanet will be making its way in October, unless it gets delayed again.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who never knows?
[SPEAKER_07]: It'll be all sorts of awesome whenever it comes out.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, for things that are to be coming out, as mentioned, is Home, which has been pushed back, pushed back, turned around, upside down, set on fire, and dropped in said underwater volcano, is going to be getting a fall release, which has been told us by SCEE President David Reeves, and said...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: However, it's not quite as prestigious as, say, Home.
[SPEAKER_07]: The game is actually homeless, and you can find yourself participating in wonderful activities like sleeping on a park bench, spewing out obscenities, talking to a wall, and just not being cared for.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, I need to do a quick poll in chat right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Quick poll in chat.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, which joke was funnier?
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki's homeless joke or Rob's Atari joke?
[SPEAKER_06]: Place vote now in chat.
[SPEAKER_06]: In the main chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think, you know, it's funnier.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which joke was funnier?
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what's funnier?
[SPEAKER_04]: Tonight's show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tonight's show is hilarious.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hilarious.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, go to the next story.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hate you guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_06]: We have the quick poll results are in.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rob's Atari joke.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rob's joke.
[SPEAKER_06]: Atari.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rob's Atari joke.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rob's.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because Rob used the Atari Pac-Man dying sound.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rob's Atari joke.
[SPEAKER_06]: Look at that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I rock.
[SPEAKER_06]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Love you, Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: So this isn't a big surprise.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's rumors now that Daxter and Wipeout Pulse are going to be ported to the PS2.
[SPEAKER_07]: Really?
[SPEAKER_07]: PSP games are being ported to the PS2?
[SPEAKER_07]: That's a first.
[SPEAKER_07]: And this is coming from Jukes Video France, and they're just stating that, of course, those two games are being ported to the PS2.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would say that's a pretty safe guess, and I wouldn't be surprised to see it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not a big surprise.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, so now we gotta downgrade our games to get them to sell more.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that basically what this is?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, here's the thing too, is when they port them over, they don't enhance any of the graphics or anything.
[SPEAKER_07]: In fact, I believe Ratchet & Clank Size Matters didn't look that good on the PS2.
[SPEAKER_07]: Twisted Metal, pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Silent Hill Origins, pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: But just, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't need his stinking vote.
[SPEAKER_07]: or his friendship on the PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: The thing about Project Gotham for me is that it's a little heavy on the car shop and tuning your car and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just want to play a really easy pick-up-and-race type game like F-Zero.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that's why I like F-Zero and Mario Kart.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're really easy.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want it easy and fast.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's why I like F-Zero.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because you get to drive so fast.
[SPEAKER_06]: I seriously still say F-Zero GX is one of my favorite racing games ever.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is great.
[SPEAKER_06]: So...
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see, though, what Bizarre has in store for us.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because, you know, they might just try something completely new out of left field that's going to make me go, da-da-da-da-da, want.
[SPEAKER_06]: Might you say that, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_06]: Da-da-da-da-want.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: well speaking of stuff that came through via conference call how's that for tie-in it was actually stated by Activision Publishing CEO Mike Griffith that Guitar Hero has surpassed 15 million in individual song downloads so I guess rock bands got a little bit more to catch up with but then again Guitar Hero has been out longer so
[SPEAKER_04]: In shorter time, Harmonix hit 10 million.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I think that look at it in perspective of time and then see who's doing better.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what I say.
[SPEAKER_06]: I sense a little bit of favoritism on your part.
[SPEAKER_04]: Especially since Rock Band already had to deal with Guitar Heroes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry about that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm setting up for something later.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't pay attention to that.
[SPEAKER_04]: since um since Guitar Hero was already out and already had a loyal fan base when Rock Band came out so to hit 10 million after all that I think Rock Band's got and I'm looking at this just by terms of numbers and time that I think Rock Band's the more impressive hmm
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you know, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Guitar Hero, I still like it because I think it's more fun to play guitar on Guitar Hero than it is on Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_06]: But Rock Band's definitely the better part of the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like hitting things.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck that shit.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's all about guitar freaks.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know what you guys...
[SPEAKER_06]: No, Guitar Freaks is kind of... No, Guitar Freaks!
[SPEAKER_06]: Where's your loyalty?
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry, I defected.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, I still love Beatmania 2DX.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Keyboard Mania.
[SPEAKER_06]: I will always have a soft, squishy spot in my heart for Keyboard Mania.
[SPEAKER_04]: By the way, completely unrelated, and Loki, when you mentioned it, I had to look it up, and I think that's the most hilarious thing I've ever heard.
[SPEAKER_04]: For the American Idol thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: Stop derailing the show with your idle chat.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, it's only a few more weeks and then it's over.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh my god, I don't believe this.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm the reality TV whore of you three.
[SPEAKER_06]: I am hosting a freaking Survivor game on LiveJournal right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what a whore I am for reality TV.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's you two that derail me.
[SPEAKER_04]: I explained the other night this isn't reality TV.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a talent contest.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a difference.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not a bunch of people acting like retards.
[SPEAKER_04]: You don't see anything into their personal life on the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like people acting like retards.
[SPEAKER_07]: She doesn't have a point.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is a contest.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is a contest.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're not looking at how these people are living in their daily lives.
[SPEAKER_04]: And thank God for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: They just...
[SPEAKER_07]: interview them you're not following them as they're trying to build a hut out of coconut leaves wouldn't it be more fun if the idols did have to build no no no no because you see this is why I don't watch any of the results show and I just read the winner online because I don't like watching tons of Ford commercials being you know their little musical numbers
[SPEAKER_04]: I actually have not watched a physical episode on TV this year.
[SPEAKER_06]: All I have to say is I'm missing the Survivor Micronesia finale tonight to be here.
[SPEAKER_06]: And if you spoil it in chat, I will punch you in the face and it will hurt.
[SPEAKER_04]: You've got TiVo.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know, but still.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have TiVo.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have YouTube on my phone at work.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, there's rumors now that Activision is partnering with Nintendo to release Nintendo DS bundles that will include the DS system as well as Guitar Hero on Tour.
[SPEAKER_07]: It'll be the first third-party kind of combo pack that they've done with the DS so far.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's kind of neat, whoring the game out a bit.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, I guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know, I would say that you would need the black and red, or crimson black DS, so it would look pretty cool with this, but I don't know, it's neat, I guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think, what was I going to say, I think that they're doing, I think Guitar Hero 4 is coming out in DS too, so you're not going to have to worry about just playing on tour for a long time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are they really going to move that many DS units with this one game?
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's going to sell pretty well.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, it's innovative, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's innovative, I guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, it's an interesting peripheral, let me put it that way.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think it's an original idea at all because the WonderSwan had the Beatmania wheel.
[SPEAKER_04]: Scratch table.
[SPEAKER_04]: But this is different.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is much different.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's been games that's had add-ons of a similar nature.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not saying that add-ons... I think it's an interesting add-on because I know one, like, I'm thinking Guitar Hero for the DS before they ever showed off this, you know, guitar grip thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm thinking you tap in the screen, you know, to be the music type thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: So this is definitely a lot better than that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Be interesting to see what they do with it.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Something tells me there will be some type of instrument we haven't thought of yet that's going to be in it somehow.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, come on, Rob.
[SPEAKER_07]: Look at the Wii, okay, and the Wii Wheel when they made that announcement.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was a big step in innovation to them, despite the fact that there had been third-party games that had done that since the Wii launch.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it's retarded.
[SPEAKER_07]: They just, you know, pat themselves on the back and stuff, you know, fluff themselves, I don't know what.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it's just, it's retarded.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, Guitar Hero 4, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll get more news on it later, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm sure we'll be shocked and awed.
[SPEAKER_06]: But not really.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because we already kind of figured it out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are we shocked and awed?
[SPEAKER_06]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are we just going, aww?
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, guess what else should be getting some downloadable content?
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sort of.
[SPEAKER_04]: Samba de Amigo.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we?
[SPEAKER_06]: Wait, you mean downloadable content on the Wii?
[SPEAKER_06]: How is this possible?
[SPEAKER_04]: Explain yourself.
[SPEAKER_04]: They were taking a look at the cover for Samba de Amigo and at the top is Wii's Pay to Play logo.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it could be indicative of some downloadable content.
[SPEAKER_07]: Pay to Play.
[SPEAKER_04]: Where are my maracas?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sure some third-party company will put out cheap plastic maraca cases for your... Maraca attachment.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_04]: I want my maracas and I want to pose.
[SPEAKER_04]: Damn it, I'm just going to bust out.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sure the posing will be there.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want maracas.
[SPEAKER_06]: We could develop our own maraca attachment.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's the thing, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: I bet you anything because the...
[SPEAKER_06]: The space on the Wii is so limited.
[SPEAKER_06]: I bet you anything it is not pay to download content.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's pay to unlock content.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because why not?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's working on the 360 with games like Katamari.
[SPEAKER_06]: And we need to stop referring to these things as downloadable content and call them what they are.
[SPEAKER_06]: You are paying to unlock something already on the disc.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, though, I don't know if that might be the case.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because, I mean, this stuff could be like MP3 format or something very similar.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're not actually making the music to the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just going along with it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Perhaps.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Dreamcast ones were actually downloadable.
[SPEAKER_06]: Samba 2000
[SPEAKER_06]: Samba de Amigo Samba de Amigo
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, while we're waiting for actual download content on the Wii, whether...
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess Samba de Amigo is going to be the first one or not.
[SPEAKER_07]: In the meantime, though, in July, we are going to be getting something not quite downloadable, but expanding on with Rock Band Track Pack Volume 1.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's coming to the PlayStation 2 and the Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's kind of neat about this game, actually, it's not really adding on to the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, it's almost like its own game.
[SPEAKER_07]: It has its own songs.
[SPEAKER_07]: They've got a list of about...
[SPEAKER_07]: I want to say there's 10-15 tracks there.
[SPEAKER_07]: All stuff that's currently available on Xbox Live, Arcade, and PlayStation Network like 30 Seconds to Mars, The Kill, Blink-182, all the small things, Kiss, Calling Dr. Love, and so on.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you don't own Rock Band, you can just buy this for $29.99 if you want.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess it will contain 20 songs.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, well.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or you could just pay to download the songs.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, you could just do that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, you know, or if you own a PlayStation 2 and a Wii, or a Wii, I guess, you don't really have the option.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you, Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, there's some more rock band news.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's kind of interesting this week, and it has to do with more rock band tracks, but this time it's free tracks, and we like free, but it's kind of the way that you get them, which is very interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: The band Disturbed, apparently, is going to be having some tracks in rock band, and the only way you get this is by pre-ordering their latest CD, which I think is Indestructible.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that what it's called?
[SPEAKER_06]: You pre-order the CD, and then you actually can get the songs that apparently will not be going public until June.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: with it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, you know, it's not the first time South Park would have tied into Rock Band, because think, Timmy and the Lords of the Underworld is one of the unlocked songs in the game, which is pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hope it's actual, like, South Park songs.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hope they're South Park songs, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, DVD-A, Now You're a Man.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or, uh, Shut Your Fucking Face, Uncle Fucka.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'd love some of the stuff from the movie.
[SPEAKER_06]: That would be great.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or, uh, what was the song?
[SPEAKER_06]: Little Boy, You're Going to Hell.
[SPEAKER_06]: Remember that?
[SPEAKER_06]: That had a good guitar riff in it.
[SPEAKER_06]: That'd be great.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, in the meantime, we're going to take a little trip to our mailbag.
[SPEAKER_06]: Every week, you guys email us at mailbag at orangelaungeradio.com and DarkSakura rips open the email bag and pulls out a few of her favorite emails to read for you guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: Unfortunately, though, it's slim pickings in the mailbag this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sounds like not a lot of folks emailed us.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura's going to pick her two favorite emails tonight to read for you right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: But if you want to email us for a future week, mailbag at orangelaungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, take it away.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I did get a couple from Rob with two Bs, but I'm actually still reading over them, so I'll have to save them for next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: First one comes from Katamaris Forever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good Sunday to you, OLR.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's so pleasant.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'd like to start my letter regarding what I wrote last week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Having copied down what Actdeft said on Part B two weeks ago, I tried removing Photo Channel, but since I didn't download it in the first place, it wasn't there to delete.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would also like to state that since the show reaches 1am in Michigan, I usually go live during Part A and go to sleep during the beginning of Part B. I can't thank you enough for providing podcasts through your RSS feed so that I can listen later.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, I would like to address a popular issue that I've seen recently in games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Their ratings.
[SPEAKER_04]: It seems that every new release title gets to be a number one on aggregate sites like GamerKings, only to fall down to the top 30 a week later.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do exclusive reviews usually skew opinions, hence the 100% that PS3 version of Grand Theft Auto 4 is getting?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, sure, the first reviews usually spew out love, but it's usually the first people who influence the next, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: If so, for example, GameSpot gave a game like Okami for Wii a 9.0 when the other reviewers follow suit.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess it's just buzz.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which brings me to my other point.
[SPEAKER_04]: Where's Bioshock?
[SPEAKER_04]: In a mere amount of months, the 2007 game of the year just vanished out of thin air.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nowadays, I don't hear a peep about this legendary game anymore, but just who whooped who in brawl and testimonials about GTA 4.
[SPEAKER_04]: Seriously, I've got a friend who calls this game, quote, the truth.
[SPEAKER_04]: The truth.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really, that ADD?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes Two random things I want to address Why does Rob hate Toadette?
[SPEAKER_04]: She's just the same as Toad and Mario Kart Wii is very nice but bikes seem unusable when playing with the Wii wheel
[SPEAKER_06]: Mario and Wario
[SPEAKER_06]: Luigi, and Waluigi, Donkey Kong, and Diddy Kong.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can I continue?
[SPEAKER_06]: You may.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry about the long letter.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll be sure to talk about something else next time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Katamari's forever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Change is inevitable except at the Olive Garden where endless soup, salad, and breadsticks are $9.95 every day excluding Australia LOL.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love how all of our emails now have to end their email with some type of Home of the Neverending or Olive Garden reference.
[SPEAKER_06]: Love it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey Sky, DarkSakura, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for playing my entry for the contest on the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm glad you guys liked it and said it was great.
[SPEAKER_04]: That really means a lot to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a shame that few people are entering to win, but I guess that most people listening already own an Xbox 360 or PS3.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm curious to hear the other entries for the contest, though, so keep us informed.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah, I've got a story for you guys about how I got to know your podcast.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was actually looking for podcasts with lounge music.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I typed lounge podcast and something like that into Google and it led me to your website.
[SPEAKER_04]: I downloaded an episode and the beginning was like Sky's famous intro beginning with video games, video gaming, and gaming culture, and the gamer lifestyle.
[SPEAKER_04]: Being a gamer myself, I thought, hey, I'll check this out.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I actually laughed my ass off.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I was immediately hooked.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there you have it, a somewhat unusual way of getting to know you guys, but the name Orange Lounge Radio really paid off.
[SPEAKER_06]: which is funny because a lot of times I think we haven't been discovered because our title does not have game in it and people are like, what does Orange Lounge have to do with video games?
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's just kind of funny that the reverse worked.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's ditter.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_04]: By the way, Sky, you do sound like Lazlo from GTA a lot.
[SPEAKER_04]: Smile face.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that's not a bad thing because he's so funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, okay then.
[SPEAKER_06]: I forgive you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Keep up the great show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Lots of love from Belgium.
[SPEAKER_04]: Martin.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, now, DarkSakura, it occurred to me you weren't here last week, so you didn't hear his entry, but the problem was he was ineligible.
[SPEAKER_04]: I did hear it.
[SPEAKER_04]: You did?
[SPEAKER_04]: I played it the week before.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_04]: This was the really... Oh, you know what it was?
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't play it on air that time you heard it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, then you've heard it.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: But we played it on air last week, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what I thought, and you weren't here last week, so... Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: We have one more.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Better be short.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's really short.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's from GS68.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, OLR crew, I've got seven words for Black Wolf.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you have against the ferret?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll have to ask.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hit him last week when you weren't here.
[SPEAKER_06]: You butt.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I actually don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I seriously don't know where the ferret is.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's somewhere around here.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's hiding from Bobby.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hopefully I threw him away.
[SPEAKER_04]: No!
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's hiding from Bobby.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's... You traumatized the baby ferret.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think there's a little bit of rivalry between our mascot, the ferret, and Bobby, and I'm not sure who it belongs to, Bobby or Super Happy Funtime Show, but Clicky the Pen.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think there's some type of rivalry there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Clicky the Pen.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the ferret has cuteness.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's true, but the pen goes click.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the pens are also useful.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Parrots are useful, too, because you can throw them at your co-host.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you can find it.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, you watch.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll find another parrot.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's it for the email this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mailbag at orangelaunchradio.com if you have some emails you would like to contribute.
[SPEAKER_06]: But we've got some more gaming news, and then we are minutes away from a brand new OLR game launch.
[SPEAKER_06]: You don't even know what it is yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's going to be fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm excited.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or it will suck and we'll never play it again.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what happens to games.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're either really good or they suck and we never play them again.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's go over to Loki for another story.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: So this isn't a big surprise because they were talking that Bazaar was going to be working on a new Bond game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well,
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll have to see.
[SPEAKER_07]: But the film is being released in the UK on October 31st, November 7th in North America.
[SPEAKER_07]: Does that mean that we'll actually get the game then?
[SPEAKER_07]: Or do you think we'll have to wait for the DVD?
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it'll come out fourth.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why does it say third quarter?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's fourth quarter.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess third quarter financial quarter, I guess, for them.
[SPEAKER_07]: But yeah, fourth quarter.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that would make sense.
[SPEAKER_06]: Doom 4
[SPEAKER_06]: But Doom 4 is on its way.
[SPEAKER_06]: And CEO Todd Hollinsheet said this week in a press release, quote, Doom is part of the ID software DNA and demands the greatest talent and brightest minds in the industry to bring the next installment of our flagship franchise to Earth.
[SPEAKER_06]: There are no other details given at this time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Speculation is that ID's Tech 5 engine will be used.
[SPEAKER_06]: And who knows?
[SPEAKER_06]: And story-wise, who knows where this game could go?
[SPEAKER_06]: But then again, if the movie didn't kill the franchise, then it could go anywhere.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, Doom 4.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you excited about Doom 4?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: Doom 3 looked really awesome, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: It didn't have the charm of Doom 1 and Doom 2 for me.
[SPEAKER_06]: I never really liked Doom.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you playing Doom for the charm?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, for the charm.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like Doom 1 and 2 for the mods, but that's about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't really care for the games.
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't even really get into Quake either.
[SPEAKER_07]: Duke Nukem 3D, that was my game.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what I liked about Doom?
[SPEAKER_07]: I just, you know, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wolfenstein, that was a good game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just Doom didn't do it for me.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think mainly Doom didn't do it for me because at the time my PC couldn't run it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Only had one meg of RAM, so it was a little tough to run that game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Your friend and mine, Bobby Blackwolf in chat says, ID makes great engines, they don't make great games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I liked the first Doom because, first of all, it had a difficulty level called Hurt Me Plenty.
[SPEAKER_04]: And secondly, the Wolfenstein levels.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's all about ID and IDDQD and IDBFG.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't forget Hexen and how freaking awesome that game is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hexen was great because of the NRA code.
[SPEAKER_04]: All weapons.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: And God mode was Satan.
[SPEAKER_06]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: We are going to go to the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_06]: In fact, if you heard a little background noise, it's because we already picked it up where we have two people sitting on the Skype line right now, if I'm not mistaking.
[SPEAKER_06]: Toshin, you are there, correct?
[SPEAKER_06]: Correct.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, I am.
[SPEAKER_10]: Doing very well, actually.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, now we've got a little bit of a score to settle, and I don't even know how this came about, but it turned out that we have this Rev... Rev?
[SPEAKER_06]: Rescode we've been trying to give away for, like, I don't know, like two months, and somehow we found out that you two didn't have it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And which is so funny, because tonight, like, everybody's been PMing me, like, I wanna play, I wanna play, because I want the code.
[SPEAKER_06]: But no, no, we said a couple weeks ago it was gonna be Toshin versus Footy, but we originally said we were gonna play the match game, but I hate to break it to you guys, we thought of something new.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we're going to subject you to a new game tonight because we can do that.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's our show.
[SPEAKER_10]: I am very scared about this.
[SPEAKER_06]: You should be.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you scared, Toshin?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, let's unveil the game that Toshin and Footy will be playing tonight for the Rez HD Code.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's the OLR Family Feud will be what Toshin and Footy are playing tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, here's the deal.
[SPEAKER_06]: We have surveyed several OLR personalities in different video gaming categories.
[SPEAKER_06]: The OLR family, if you will.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you two will be competing against each other head to head to see who can earn more points.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's how you earn more points.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're going to pick a number 1 through 4 that will be the board that you play when it's your turn.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, uh, on the board are the top answers in a particular video gaming category.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, let's say, best game ever.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you can take turns at the board to see what the hosts and our friends would have said was the best game ever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, if you don't guess correctly, you guess something that's not on the board, you get a strike.
[SPEAKER_06]: Three strikes, and it will go to the other player who will get one chance to steal the board and all of your points.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you definitely, uh, don't want to have your board stolen.
[SPEAKER_06]: So...
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you familiar with the show, Toshin?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, I am.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you familiar with the show, Footy?
[SPEAKER_06]: I have no idea what you just said.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, then you're in trouble, my friend.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll have Toshin go first then.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that way, Footy, hopefully you can figure out what's going on quickly.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right?
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, basically, it comes down to what?
[SPEAKER_10]: I have to say a name of a person that would have said what is the best game to them?
[SPEAKER_06]: Not a person, not a person.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's say the category was best video game ever made.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, since you know that I answered it, you would probably guess that Super Metroid is somewhere on the board.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then you'd hear, ding.
[SPEAKER_06]: But if you guessed, you know, a game that none of us... It's kind of like a bingo thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, if you guessed Crysis, then you'd hear, eh, because none of us would have picked that.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, so, because we're not Sakura Max.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: So you're going to be telling us whose names are on the board?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then I have to guess the name?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, I'm going to.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, you don't have to guess the name.
[SPEAKER_06]: You just have to guess the answers that are on the board.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is getting complicated.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here is the OLR family that have contributed to tonight's answers.
[SPEAKER_06]: Myself, Rob Roberts, DarkSakura, Loki has contributed to the board tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bobby Blackwolf contributed to the board tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Miklatov contributed to the board tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rice Princess and DMN all have contributed answers to the board.
[SPEAKER_06]: possible answers but sometimes answers are worth more because multiple people said them like for instance if it had been best game ever Chrono Trigger probably would have been worth like three points so does that make sense yeah alright here we go oh we have to do it just like they do on the show let's play the feud I said let's play the feud where's the damn music there we go let's play the feud alright
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, stop music.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Toshin, since you know what you're doing, we're going to have you go first.
[SPEAKER_06]: So Toshin, do you want board number one, board number two, board number three, or board number four?
[SPEAKER_06]: 3 Doom Doom
[SPEAKER_06]: Where's my sound effect?
[SPEAKER_06]: Family Feud's broken.
[SPEAKER_06]: No!
[SPEAKER_06]: I said is Doom on the board?
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, ding ding ding, yes, Doom is on the board.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, so you get one point.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's worth one point.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, Toshin, you have one point so far.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Doom is definitely on the sound board.
[SPEAKER_06]: Doom is all over my sound board tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, guess again, Toshin.
[SPEAKER_06]: You have no strikes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Best first impression shooting game ever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Quake.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now we all have to applaud and say, good answer, good answer.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is Quake on the board?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Quake is not on the board.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's one strike against you.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Make another guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wolfenstein.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is Wolfenstein on the board?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's two strikes against you, Toshin.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, Footy, be prepared to steal if it comes over to you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Toshin, what's another first person shooting game?
[SPEAKER_06]: Halo.
[SPEAKER_06]: Halo!
[SPEAKER_06]: Show me Halo!
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, that's three strikes, Toshin.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, Footy, it's your chance to steal.
[SPEAKER_06]: You'll get one point and whatever other points you get for the answer if you can guess what's on the board for best first person shooting game ever.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, um, he said, sorry, Wolfenstein, Quake, and, uh, which other, do you say, Toshin?
[SPEAKER_10]: I can't say anything.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know you should have been paying attention.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, fine, that's how you are, okay?
[SPEAKER_10]: I get it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Things are getting dirty.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, Duke Nukem 3D.
[SPEAKER_06]: Duke Nukem 3D, show me Duke Nukem 3D!
[SPEAKER_06]: Ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, it's the number one answer.
[SPEAKER_06]: In fact, three people, Rob, Loki, and Irene all said Duke Nukem 3.
[SPEAKER_10]: I knew Loki would have said that.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, so Footy, you just stole Toshin's point and three of your own.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now you've got four points from that board.
[SPEAKER_06]: Toshin has zero.
[SPEAKER_06]: Toshin, stop embarrassing Canada.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, no, I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're doing a good job.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, let's look at what else was on the board.
[SPEAKER_06]: Jamie said Doom, for the record, by the way.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, the remaining answers were...
[SPEAKER_06]: Portal, said Bobby Blackwolf.
[SPEAKER_06]: Unreal Tournament 2003, said Miklatov.
[SPEAKER_06]: Perfect Dark, said DMN.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, those are the other answers that you didn't guess.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow, no Golden I Love there?
[SPEAKER_06]: No Golden I Love, I'm surprised too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, Footy, it's your turn.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which board do you want to go for?
[SPEAKER_10]: That was what, 4-3, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Now it's board three.
[SPEAKER_06]: You want board one, two, or four?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, now the ding noise loads.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like an hour later.
[SPEAKER_06]: Then give me board two.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fucking internet.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Board two.
[SPEAKER_06]: Best music in a game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just one game name.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're not looking for a song.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're looking for like a game as a whole with the best soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_06]: So best music in a game.
[SPEAKER_06]: What is your guess, Footy?
[SPEAKER_10]: Castlevania Symphony of the Night?
[SPEAKER_06]: Castlevania Symphony of the Night.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a good guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good answer.
[SPEAKER_06]: Show me Symphony of the Night.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, that's a strike, Footy.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm kind of surprised, too, that didn't come up.
[SPEAKER_06]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, there's lots of games out there.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Best music in a game from the OLR family.
[SPEAKER_06]: Footy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Question.
[SPEAKER_10]: If I were to say DDR, do I have to say the specific version?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dance Dance Revolution.
[SPEAKER_06]: Portal, ShowMePortal
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, three strikes and no points, footy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, Toshin, you can still steal the board and earn a point if you can correctly guess what anybody in the OLR family named best music in a game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Toshin.
[SPEAKER_06]: World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_06]: Show me Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_06]: You guys sucked on that one.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was pretty tough.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here are the answers on the board.
[SPEAKER_06]: Top seven answers.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rob said Final Fantasy VI.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura said Mega Man 2 Loki said Katamari Damacy Bobby said Super Smash Brothers Brawl Shane said Silent Hill Irene said Chrono Trigger and DMN said Rock Band
[SPEAKER_06]: So all of those games were on the board.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nothing is selected here.
[SPEAKER_10]: I had good guesses.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_10]: I had guesses and I'm very happy with myself.
[SPEAKER_06]: You did have good guesses.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: We have a comment in the chat.
[SPEAKER_06]: TheRobD says, Toshin and FootyMonster equals bad Family Feud players.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now give me my shout out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Shout out.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm just teasing.
[SPEAKER_06]: You guys are doing fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is a tough game.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to say Ray Combs starting now.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's all I'm saying.
[SPEAKER_06]: TheRobD, I hate, hate, hate, hate you.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Toshin, board number one and board number four are left.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's your last go at the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: What do you want?
[SPEAKER_06]: One.
[SPEAKER_06]: Board number one.
[SPEAKER_06]: The category is best female video game character ever.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Top five answers are on the board.
[SPEAKER_06]: Best female video game character ever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Toshin.
[SPEAKER_10]: They have tits.
[SPEAKER_10]: Everybody is a winner.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Toshin.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, I'm going to say Samus Aran.
[SPEAKER_06]: Samus Aran, show me Samus Aran.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, number one answer.
[SPEAKER_06]: You get two dings for that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Show me working soundboard.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, three points for Samus.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was the number one answer said by DarkSakura, Miklatov, and RicePrincess.
[SPEAKER_06]: All said Samus Aran.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, Toshin, you got another guess?
[SPEAKER_06]: Zelda.
[SPEAKER_06]: Zelda, show me Zelda.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, nobody picked Zelda.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, Toshin.
[SPEAKER_06]: Three points on the board.
[SPEAKER_09]: Best female would have to be... I'm going to go with a wing.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to say Eris.
[SPEAKER_06]: Eris from Final Fantasy 7.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a good answer.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good answer.
[SPEAKER_06]: Show me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, DarkSakura says that's a bad answer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember, I have my game saved so I can watch her die over and over again.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: There's seven people that put in answers.
[SPEAKER_06]: Somebody might have liked Eris.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did anybody like Eris?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nobody likes Eris.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because they have taste.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Two strikes, Toshin.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not over yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Toshin.
[SPEAKER_06]: Guess best female video game character ever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Lara Croft.
[SPEAKER_06]: Lara Croft from the Tomb Raider series.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is there Lara Croft?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, it's three strikes.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, that's all right, Toshin.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't be too frustrated.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, Footy, your chance to steal the board and the three points.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you can guess one of the remaining four answers on the board, best female video game character ever.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, Jesus Christ.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is hard.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's too many.
[SPEAKER_10]: I would say all of them, but... Chun-Li, why not?
[SPEAKER_06]: Chun-Li, if you get this right, you will have seven points.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you get it wrong, Toshi finally gets on the board with three points.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is Chun-Li up there?
[SPEAKER_06]: Is my soundboard going to work?
[SPEAKER_06]: No!
[SPEAKER_06]: Is Chun-Li up there?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, Chun-Li's not on the damn board.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, so DingDingDingTotion gets the three points.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's now three to four.
[SPEAKER_07]: Three points Canada, four points Argentina.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_07]: As the sound man behind the scenes here, if you're picking a different sample, you can double click on it.
[SPEAKER_07]: If it's the same sample, you have to hit play.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, thank you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Toshin, I want you to say Toshi!
[SPEAKER_06]: Get back to the game, please.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_06]: The correct answer is Rob said Princess Peach, Loki said Mai because of her assets, Bobby Blackwolf said GLaDOS, and DMN said Morrigan from the Darkstalkers.
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess it was in the 2D fighter area.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: I said Samus Aran.
[SPEAKER_06]: You were one of three that said that.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was big money there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Special Ed.
[SPEAKER_06]: Love you.
[SPEAKER_06]: One board left.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's all going to come down to this one right here in footy.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's your board.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's the category.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a toughy footy.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're going to hate this board.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ready?
[SPEAKER_06]: Best Atari 2600 game ever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Top seven answers are on the board.
[SPEAKER_06]: Everyone said something different.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Pitfall Pitfall, show me Pitfall Strike Good guess though What the hell was on the Atari 2600 anyways?
[SPEAKER_06]: Can't remember for the love of me Pac-Man Pac-Man, the abortion of a game on the Atari 2600 I'm just kidding That we made fun of earlier in the show Someone might have picked it, I don't know
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, show me Pac-Man!
[SPEAKER_06]: That was a no.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, why are you laughing?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not like he said E.T.
[SPEAKER_10]: I almost said E.T.
[SPEAKER_10]: though.
[SPEAKER_06]: Footy, you're awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know we think you're awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Toshi too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, Footy, come on, you gotta get a point.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here you go, two strikes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Best Atari 2600 game ever.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to follow my fellow Spanish-speaking person.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to go with Adventure.
[SPEAKER_06]: Adventure.
[SPEAKER_06]: Show me Adventure.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, Adventure is on the board.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bobby Blackwolf said Adventure.
[SPEAKER_06]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: You got a point.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you still have two strikes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Try to get some more points.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I have, what, six more people?
[SPEAKER_06]: Six more people, six more answers.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_10]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: I can't remember name games for the 3600.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to say Galaga.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't even know if that was in the 3600.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: At least we got an answer out of you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Jeez, we had to beat it out of you.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: Show me Galaga.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I'm sorry, footy.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think Galaga was on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hate you.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think Galaga was on it, but that's all right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, Toshin, here it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's your chance to steal.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let me tell you what the stakes are here.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you steal the board, you will win.
[SPEAKER_06]: But if you don't steal the board, footy will win.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what it comes down to right here.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, Toshin.
[SPEAKER_06]: You've thought and you've thought.
[SPEAKER_06]: What would you say is the best Atari 2600 game ever?
[SPEAKER_10]: Man, I already know the answer I should have given.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is your name Toshin?
[SPEAKER_06]: I just remember of a game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Toshin, what's it going to be?
[SPEAKER_09]: Asteroids
[SPEAKER_06]: for the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Show me asteroids!
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: What was the other one you were thinking of?
[SPEAKER_09]: Crazy climber.
[SPEAKER_06]: Crazy Climber was on the Atari 2600, I think.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just thought of Joust for some reason.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let me run down the top answers.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're going to hate me for this one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rob said Pitfall 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh man, come on.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's unfair.
[SPEAKER_06]: I said Pitfall.
[SPEAKER_06]: Play the games.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're a big difference.
[SPEAKER_06]: Jamie said Kangaroo.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki said Combat.
[SPEAKER_06]: Shane said Spider-Man.
[SPEAKER_06]: Irene said Missile Command.
[SPEAKER_06]: And DMN said Warlords were the answers that were left on the board.
[SPEAKER_06]: So there you have it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Argentina and Footy Monster wins 5-3.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actdeft has the code, so Actdeft, I'm going to have you send that code over to Footy, because he'll get his right away for actually winning.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Toshin, you'll get yours later.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're actually probably going to give you just Microsoft points so you can buy it, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: What's wrong?
[SPEAKER_06]: You're still getting something, man.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want as much as anybody else right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: You want it anyway, you just gotta wait a little while.
[SPEAKER_06]: Four to six weeks for shipping and handling.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was fun, actually.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was a fun game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Did you like the game?
[SPEAKER_10]: I didn't know what I was getting into.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I did.
[SPEAKER_10]: I actually liked it.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll have to see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Chat room.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you guys like the game?
[SPEAKER_06]: Should we do it again in the future?
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to see you in the chat.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, thank you guys very much for playing and subjecting yourself to the OLR Family Feud featuring the crappy soundboard.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright guys, we're going to hang up on you and have a good night, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, thank you guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Footy, let me know if Actdeft doesn't get you the code because I have it somewhere, but I'm sure he'll send it to you, okay?
[SPEAKER_10]: He just sent me a message asking for my email, so I'm guessing we're in the works.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wonderful.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, have a good one.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Toshin, I'll be in touch with you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you guys like the game?
[SPEAKER_06]: It went on for like 20 minutes.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: A little different.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Uh...
[SPEAKER_06]: I like the concept but it's a horrible game you can't get anyone's answers the group being surveyed is way too difficult to predict it's funny to hear their answers but you're impossible to guess them
[SPEAKER_06]: Like that's any better than the match game?
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll try a version where we survey the entire chat room before the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: But then the chatters know what's coming.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the problem.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's why we didn't do it that way this time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because then they know what questions are coming.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I just see you.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is fine the way it was.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_07]: They can quit their bitching.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, we'll see what happens with that in the future.
[SPEAKER_06]: In the meantime, we've got to go back to some more news.
[SPEAKER_06]: We've got more gaming news, just a little bit, and then we're going to open the Skype line for you guys to give us a call with your own thoughts.
[SPEAKER_04]: And set it on fire.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, and then we'll set the Skype line on fire.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuego!
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, and any excuse for me to play the Pac-Man noise again will be welcomed.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, next story, please.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ninja Gaiden 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you pre-order it, you get stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: The end.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: lets you look like the bad guys that you're facing.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's basically a nice big costume for Ryu.
[SPEAKER_04]: However, if you are of the more patient variety, you can download a costume pack of three in July, which will be 200 Microsoft points.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ninja Gaiden 2 will be out in Europe on the 6th of June, so you can test out how fun it is then.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yay, indeed.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just don't like having to pre-order games because then a better deal will come out the day the game comes out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, there's going to be hopefully some interesting news coming very soon.
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently Microsoft is having a PR event next week where they're going to supposedly debut the new Xbox 360 motion controller.
[SPEAKER_07]: and, of course, we talked about it last week, their partnership with Gyration.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, the other things that they're going to be unveiling, and I know this is probably going to happen, is Banjo-Kazooie 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: In fact, there's been some screenshots that have already come out for that.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, it's going to be interesting to see what goes on.
[SPEAKER_07]: And this is during the Game Critics Awards, I guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's supposed to happen next week, so... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, a good idea came to us.
[SPEAKER_06]: Can I read this aloud for the Family Feud?
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess so.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think this is a good idea.
[SPEAKER_06]: We could survey the chatroom for Family Feud and have people in studio play.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like when we have some of our guests here.
[SPEAKER_06]: We could get Rice Princess and Mo to battle each other.
[SPEAKER_06]: We could get Nathan and Nextifer or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: Get some guests on the show to battle each other.
[SPEAKER_06]: That might be kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: That might be a way to do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Since we're dealing with some good access to the chatroom.
[SPEAKER_06]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: Then it would be a secret.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like that idea.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have to make them face like us.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: A panel of us.
[SPEAKER_06]: Then it's chatroom feud at that point.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe that's what we'll rename it to.
[SPEAKER_06]: The chatroom feud.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow, sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't mean to derail from the topic of the games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, you did.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I did a little bit.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, I mean...
[SPEAKER_06]: How much of a wee ripoff is this going to be, if at all?
[SPEAKER_06]: Or do you think they are going a totally different direction with this?
[SPEAKER_07]: It depends what they do with it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think if it's going to be like the other Q-Motion stuff, which is essentially you buy something that looks like a bowling ball, something that looks like a golf club and something like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know how popular that's going to be.
[SPEAKER_07]: It'll be nifty, but it's not going to be something that I think you'd have to go run out right away and buy.
[SPEAKER_07]: And also, I would like to see them come up with something a little bit more universal so you're not buying this huge peripheral for one game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because I'd be kind of retarded.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll have to see what they come up with.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's going to be hard for them not to be kind of accused of ripping off Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_07]: So...
[SPEAKER_06]: Because even Sony was accused of ripping off Nintendo when that 6-axis was thrown in at the last minute, remember that?
[SPEAKER_06]: And that wasn't even really the same thing, you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_07]: But still, though, it's just like, oh, now it has motion-sensitive stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: And really, what did that pan out to?
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, hardly any games use it, so... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow, we got one more story for you guys tonight, and then we're going to be getting to the Skype line here very shortly, but this next story requires some music.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you know what that means.
[SPEAKER_06]: Somebody earned themselves a stupid award this week in some horrific...
[SPEAKER_06]: The person who wins the Stupid Award on OLR this week is Edward Stoddard!
[SPEAKER_06]: Congratulations!
[SPEAKER_06]: He was arrested in Dade City, and you know what he did?
[SPEAKER_06]: He murdered his neighbor over a missing PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's right, he murdered Douglas Abrams because they were arguing over the PlayStation 3 on April 24th.
[SPEAKER_06]: No really word on what it was that they were specifically arguing about, but it just kind of begs the question, is a PlayStation 3 really worth killing someone over?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what I want to know.
[SPEAKER_07]: You could have been playing Grand Theft Auto 4 on said PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it just goes to show, you know, regardless, you know, obviously this guy obviously has issues.
[SPEAKER_06]: He needs to play Wii Ethics.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is it appropriate to kill someone over a missing video game console?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes or no?
[SPEAKER_06]: And if you say yes, then the console spits acid at you or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, wait, that's not good.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wrong!
[SPEAKER_06]: Wrong answer.
[SPEAKER_06]: Die.
[SPEAKER_06]: You need to be erased from humanity.
[SPEAKER_04]: Get out of the gene pool.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: instead of it being highly corrosive acid, it should be minorly corrosive acid so that they're left with chemical burns and you all know that they scored wrong.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ew.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that would be great.
[SPEAKER_06]: You've got issues.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, no, because it wouldn't kill them.
[SPEAKER_04]: It'd just maim them a little and everyone would know that they're stupid.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, stupid award stories usually make me a little bit angsty.
[SPEAKER_06]: And also the fact that I forgot to put it anywhere else.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I was about to mention that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was like, come on.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_06]: I caught it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Whew, saved myself.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, CFU's of the week.
[SPEAKER_04]: My FU of the week, now I told Rob what it was on Friday, but I've decided to expand it a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: And my FU of the week is to people who buy into what they're told without researching it first.
[SPEAKER_04]: And my primary example was the practice of circumcising little boys.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ow, crossing legs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I understand that for religious purposes it's part of your culture, but for purpose of aesthetics or thinking that it's healthy, no, it's not.
[SPEAKER_04]: And actually it ends up being very traumatic and also makes getting the nookie a lot less satisfying.
[SPEAKER_04]: This has been proven wrong.
[SPEAKER_04]: So also, in the same tone then, it goes to people who think that just because Specialist A has said, oh, this is not what you want to do, that suddenly it's law.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm not going to go into specifics on that in particular, but there's...
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, actually, I'm going to sort of go into specifics on this one.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: There being some sort of widespread rumor that if you were a massage therapist, then you were suddenly in adult entertainment, and this is why I get really pissed off at the whole happy ending bullshit, because of people who think that, and those jokes that go around.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't been able to get my business license for six months.
[SPEAKER_04]: So... Don't.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm very, very, very angry about that, but they've revamped the requirements for it in my town and made it to where I can get my license again.
[SPEAKER_04]: It also goes towards people who, you know...
[SPEAKER_04]: It's really just a bunch of what we think, a bunch of what we accept as fact in our daily lives is really, in most cases, the result of sensationalism and people trying to tell us what they want us to think so that we'll spend money in said area, so that more money will go into the pockets of people who
[SPEAKER_04]: FDU Driving to and from Oakland It's long and boring
[SPEAKER_06]: and it's Oakland.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that it?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it's a long drive and you're like, oh, yay, Oakland.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a yummy Indian food place in Oakland I ate at once.
[SPEAKER_06]: Speaking of food, F you to the news I got this week that due to my pancreatitis I had back in April when I was in the hospital for a few days.
[SPEAKER_06]: F you to the fact that I will be stuck on a low-fat diet for two more months, which means no Indian food.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I guess there's some Indian food dishes I can have, but no garlic naan or the stuff I really like
[SPEAKER_06]: for two more months at least.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the fact that that means I can't have cake or ice cream on my 30th birthday, that kind of blows.
[SPEAKER_06]: But at least I'd rather be eating low fat than be dead.
[SPEAKER_06]: So F you to that.
[SPEAKER_06]: And F you to the fact that on top of dealing with all that, I think I'm getting a cold or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: So F you to being sick twice at the same time.
[SPEAKER_06]: It kind of sucks.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just want this year to go away.
[SPEAKER_06]: The show's been good, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's one good thing about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: The show's been great.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hippolytus in chat asks, dude, how much weight has Sky lost?
[SPEAKER_06]: 25 pounds.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've lost 25 pounds.
[SPEAKER_06]: I used to have quite a bit of a little bit of a beer gut.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now I have a tiny little beer gut.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm going to be starting to work out soon because I'm starting to feel a lot better, like my chest and everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's going to be  I'm going to have abs by the time all is said and done.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: At least that's the goal.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's move on to the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to be taking some calls on the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can call us at 1-877-GAME-OLR Our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: We don't have time for a lot of calls tonight, but we'll definitely try to get some calls in.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you can call us right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: While we wait for some calls, do you have a quick last minute story for us, Matt?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, Prototype's been delayed to 2009.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's Prototype?
[SPEAKER_07]: It was this game that was like Crackdown, but you're like a mutant and can do crazy shit.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jump around.
[SPEAKER_07]: Big sandbox game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's supposed to come out this fall.
[SPEAKER_07]: 2009 now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, that's too bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anything else?
[SPEAKER_07]: Killzone 2 was officially announced for February 2009, so that's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think Resistance is still coming out this fall, so I think we have that to look forward to.
[SPEAKER_07]: But Killzone 2, pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: There was some footage online for that, but apparently it got yanked because it wasn't supposed to be out yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, well.
[SPEAKER_06]: That sucks.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's go to ZPhones.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hello, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh my god, it's Clicky the pen.
[SPEAKER_06]: Clicky, who gave you access to a telephone?
[SPEAKER_05]: Clicky, what are you doing?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry, Sky.
[SPEAKER_05]: He must have butt-dialed you guys or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Bobby.
[SPEAKER_06]: Was Clicky trying to flirt with the ferret?
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that's what it was.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think he's demanding ransom.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think he knows where the ferret is.
[SPEAKER_06]: Clicky Kidnapped the Ferret
[SPEAKER_06]: I know you talked, it's always funny because you do the show that's on right before us on allgames.com at 5 o'clock Pacific, and you were talking about the whole DRM, Digital Rights Management thing, which I read about earlier this week, and I was like, I want to talk about it this week on Orange Lounge Radio, and then it didn't even make it in our show roll because I forgot.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it wasn't supposed to be worth talking about.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, Loki, sum up what happened real quick because I want to get Bobby's opinion on this and our other opinions.
[SPEAKER_07]: Originally, EA came up with this wonderful idea that both Mass Effect and Spore were going to be validated via, I guess, an online call-home thing every 10 days.
[SPEAKER_07]: And if it didn't do that, it wouldn't work anymore.
[SPEAKER_07]: So...
[SPEAKER_07]: That sucked.
[SPEAKER_07]: But then they came out and decided, hey, we're not going to do that because people don't like that kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: So now Mass Effect is going to authenticate itself when you first install it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then if you download any additional download content, it will redo that as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: Same with Spore.
[SPEAKER_07]: Spore, once you install it, and also if you connect to online.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, Bobby, what are your thoughts on this?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't want to spoil your whole show because I know you go into it on your show, but quickly, what were kind of your thoughts on this issue?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, my thing was more because they're trying to market Spore because Will Wright was on the Colbert Report.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's been doing the late-night talk show rounds.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're trying to market Spore to a larger audience than just gamers, and not every person who has a computer actually has Internet access from their home.
[SPEAKER_05]: Either they use it for work or they go to a public library or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: They may have a decent computer, but it may not necessarily be online.
[SPEAKER_05]: and so even that one-time activation may be a problem for some people because they're used to just getting this DVD or CD and sticking it in their computer and playing and now you can't do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now you have to have this other charge.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have to have internet service from your home just to play it.
[SPEAKER_05]: and the reason that they got rid of the 10 day phoning home every 10 days was actually because of the US Armed Forces they can't guarantee an internet connection when they're overseas but they still play games on their PC they do have down time to get their mind off of what they're doing and I think that's why they got rid of the 10 day restriction but there's still that first time and then any other time when you're online then it will check but it's not going to force you but I think it still leaves out a segment of the population that doesn't have internet at home
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I would think, especially in the case of the armed forces who are doing a big job that not a lot of people want to do for this country, I would hope that EA would come up with a way that they can bypass it.
[SPEAKER_06]: At least the armed forces can get a special version of the game or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, granted... If there was a special version of the game that the armed forces got, it would be on the internet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I guess that's the unfortunate side of that is it would happen.
[SPEAKER_06]: But somehow, like I don't know, there's got to be something that they could do.
[SPEAKER_07]: Even with this, I think it's going to be broken.
[SPEAKER_07]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_07]: Everybody finds a way to get past everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_06]: Didn't Bioshock do something similar?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, but people found ways around that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, people  like it would only let you install it on so many computers and it had to connect to the internet each time.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then once it hit its limit, too bad, so sad.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Frisbee points out in chatroom the portal retail version requires online to start up which is well I don't know because I bought it on Steam and Steam does all that copy protection stuff you know kind of as part of I think you have to have Steam when you buy the retail version oh that's right that's right I remember hearing about that a couple weeks ago not that I know or anything but they found a way around that you heard I heard yeah okay
[SPEAKER_05]: Is that from your independent research that you did?
[SPEAKER_07]: I own the Orange Box on Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just wanted to see what it looked like on my PC.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bobby, anything else you wanted to share with our listeners tonight?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, that was it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_05]: Clicky, don't come back.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't talk about the ferret.
[SPEAKER_05]: Clicky.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's not nice, Clicky.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I know they've got an explicit tag, Clicky, but go away.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry about that, Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, that's quite okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, I'm thinking maybe Clicky and the Ferret could get their own show that no one would listen to.
[SPEAKER_06]: No one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Except maybe Jamie.
[SPEAKER_06]: She's making pouty face at me.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, bye, Bobby.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bye, Clicky.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bye, Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: Go away, Clicky.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Blackboy in chat says, I would totally listen to that show.
[SPEAKER_06]: So there you have it.
[SPEAKER_06]: What exactly would Clicky and the Ferret talk about?
[SPEAKER_06]: What do pens and ferrets have in common?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're long.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, let's go to the phones.
[SPEAKER_06]: We got more calls.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, he did a way better job than me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Definitely.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hope that he can win.
[SPEAKER_06]: We still appreciate the effort and are feeling the love very much.
[SPEAKER_06]: To what do we owe this call tonight, Actdeft?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, basically, I was going to congratulate Matt for winning.
[SPEAKER_03]: And like I said, I hope that he gets all our, how do you say it, support for him to win the oldgames.com contest overall.
[SPEAKER_03]: Though I hope he gives the console to Loki because I was going to do that if I won.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, Actdeft was serious.
[SPEAKER_06]: He was going to give you the console if you won.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I would not have let him do that because that's a foolish thing to do.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would have made him keep it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not a foolish thing to do.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would have been watching your mailbox and when I see this big box coming from Mexico, I would have written died and sent it back.
[SPEAKER_06]: Expired.
[SPEAKER_06]: That doesn't work, by the way.
[SPEAKER_07]: Have you tried doing that to Junkmail?
[SPEAKER_07]: I've tried that with Junkmail.
[SPEAKER_07]: Deceased.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, they don't believe it.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're like, oh, hey, well, someone was there to write deceased on it, so therefore.
[SPEAKER_06]: More junk.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that all you wanted to say, Actdeft?
[SPEAKER_06]: Anything going on in your gaming world this week?
[SPEAKER_03]: Basically, it's pretty much that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I haven't been gaming that much.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have been working and other stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I'm pretty looking forward to Space Invaders Extreme.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh yes, me too.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have seen some of the videos and oh my god, that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's an awesome game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It reminds me of F.R.E.S.S.
[SPEAKER_06]: I played it for about three minutes, and it was an awesome three minutes.
[SPEAKER_06]: I definitely am going to pick this game up on my PSP.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's got a great soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is on the DS, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think I'm going to get it on PSP, just for the heck of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's going to be pretty cheap, also.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like $20 on GameStop.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I think it's $20.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's cheap, and I think it'll be good.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll review the game in full a little later on, as soon as we get our grubby little hands on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll be looking forward to it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actdeft, take a break from making radio ads this week and definitely play some more games if you can.
[SPEAKER_06]: And we're going to need your help so that we can get SSJ100Matt to win the contest at all games.
[SPEAKER_06]: So as soon as I know how he can do that, we'll fill you in.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks.
[SPEAKER_06]: Take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you want to give us a call, 1-877-GAME-OLR Our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio Meanwhile, do we have any other last minute stories?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh wait, no, just kidding, we have another call Hi, Orange Lounge Radio, who's this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, it's DJ Tyrant Hey, DJ Tyrant, how are you doing?
[SPEAKER_06]: Good That was a fun Mario Kart match last night, by the way I don't remember most of it Why not?
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you not remember me kicking your ass?
[SPEAKER_08]: I was a little drinky, drinky
[SPEAKER_08]: You were drunk playing Mario Kart online?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I had just gotten home, and I'm like, what am I going to do?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't want to go to sleep yet.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I popped in Mario Kart, and I was able to navigate the menus perfectly fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: But once I got in the game, it was all downhill from there.
[SPEAKER_06]: No wonder you kept coming in last.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, did you know that we actually were broadcasting that whole thing on Justin.TV?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: I had no idea.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I went in there, logged into Mario Kart, and it was like me, Ranma, and then DarkTetsuya.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then you joined out of nowhere.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was like, oh, Jimmy must have saw us on just the TV.
[SPEAKER_06]: That is so funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you were drinking.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, when you connect to Wi-Fi, if there's like one of your friends with an open room, it has like a smiley face next to friends.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I didn't know that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, that's helpful.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow, what a good case of timing, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: But shame on you for drinking and driving.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I guess if you're gonna do it, then you gotta do it in Mario Kart.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess that's the safest place to drink and drive.
[SPEAKER_06]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or GTA 4.
[SPEAKER_08]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_06]: Or GTA 4 So that's why you picked Rainbow Road, because I was like, oh god No, I hit random, I did not want to play Rainbow Road, I hate that level so much Oh, okay, okay, alright, because I was cursing you out when you picked it I could tell, everyone was hating me at that point, and if there was voice chat it wouldn't have been very pretty Yeah, maybe that's why Nintendo banned voice chat, so it spares us from a drunken gym Anything, did you call in to talk about something else tonight, Jimmy?
[SPEAKER_06]: I totally derailed it to Mario Kart No, that was it
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: You were calling to make excuses for your drunken performance last night.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll have to play a sober match sometime.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe you can represent the OLR crew when we do our big epic battle with Bobby Blackwolf later.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Take care, Jimmy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, thanks for getting me on the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: No problem.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, that's going to do it for the Skype line tonight because we went really long with the match game thing and we want to try to end it at an east hour tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, Loki, please finish up any other last minute stories you might have tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, let's see here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, first off, let's talk real quick.
[SPEAKER_07]: We mentioned a lot of stuff about Rock Band earlier.
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently, well, first off, they've got some new stuff coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Of course, Hanging on Telephone by Blondie, Train in Vain by The Clash, and Cool Thing by Sonic Youth.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: All going to be $2 or 160 Microsoft points.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's also some, I guess, tracks on sale.
[SPEAKER_07]: All sorts of stuff between, I guess, now and June 2nd.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess two per week are going to be half price, or 80 Microsoft points.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, I guess, this week there was Crush Crush Crush by Paramore and Boston's rock and roll band.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess...
[SPEAKER_07]: Later this week, there was Grateful Dead's Sugar Magnolia and Faith No More's We Care A Lot and Leonard Skinner's Gimme Three Steps.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then, I'm not sure what's coming up later.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let me see here real quick.
[SPEAKER_07]: Next week, there's going to be Shockwave, Black Tide, and Sugar Magnolia by Grateful Dead.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then the week after that, we care a lot, I guess, Faith No More and All the Small Things by Blink-182.
[SPEAKER_06]: All the small things.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then finally, I guess, the last week is going to be Gimme Three Steps by Leonard Skinner and Dirty Little Secret by All American Rejects.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you want more information, Major Nelson had a story on it, so you can check that out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Half price.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Activision during their...
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess we'll have to see.
[SPEAKER_07]: This week also, there's a ton of demos being released on Xbox Live and the PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_07]: Born Conspiracy is on there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Haze on the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: Grid, which you've got to check out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Awesome racing game.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's on both.
[SPEAKER_07]: And next week, or actually a few weeks from now, June 5th, there's going to be Battlefield Bad Company in case you didn't get into the beta.
[SPEAKER_07]: New Xbox Live Arcade game coming in June, Vigilante 8 Arcade, which, you know, Vigilante 8 is a fucking awesome game.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's also going to have download content.
[SPEAKER_07]: No word when in June it's coming, but at least have the month nailed down.
[SPEAKER_07]: Grand Turismo has shipped 50 million units total for the entire franchise, and that's globally.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_07]: This sounds pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: I played a little bit of Namco X Capcom, or Cross Capcom.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: All sorts of stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: And this is coming from Famitsu Magazine, which has some nifty screenshots for that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Looks like Morgan's in there, and Etna?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not sure who else.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, Donovan, and looks like... Who else?
[SPEAKER_06]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_07]: Lots of people, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: Looks pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like AJ Mix's idea for a game in chat.
[SPEAKER_06]: Everyone cross everyone.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Me too.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now this is kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_07]: And remember, I think a few weeks ago when we were trying to show off Crisis Core, it really pissed me off.
[SPEAKER_07]: But thank God for the homebrew community.
[SPEAKER_07]: On the PSP, there is a new homebrew update called the FUSA Build 032.
[SPEAKER_07]: What it does is allows people with custom firmwares to use the video out and use any sort of core they want.
[SPEAKER_07]: So whether it be
[SPEAKER_06]: Hooray!
[SPEAKER_07]: Composite, Component, S-Video, or D-Terminal.
[SPEAKER_07]: They can use it on their TV play games, and they have a whole bunch of other options for that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Something that should have been done anyways in a firmware update, I think, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: And let's see here.
[SPEAKER_07]: We've got one more thing here.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's a... This is kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's a...
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess it's a gaming device called Bob that's being released.
[SPEAKER_07]: And what it is, is it's a way for parents, they would hook it up to a console of their choice, and they can set time limits for the amount of games that kids can play.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it kind of looks like a giant calculator, and it will shut the power off after a certain amount of time.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's password protected.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then finally, I have to show this to you, Rob.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're going to release this on cell phone games from Gameloft.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're remaking The Oregon Trail.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's done all fancy.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I can totally see this coming to the DS at some point.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow, it looks like Oregon Trail does battle.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's kind of weird looking.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: All fancy like, but yeah, you can check it out.
[SPEAKER_07]: They had a preview.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, look, as long as I can make a character named Jamie and she dies of cholera.
[SPEAKER_06]: Heart.
[SPEAKER_06]: But that is it.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, at least it wasn't dysentery because dysentery is so cliche.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is why I hope I catch malaria.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I don't know, Jamie, you should check this out on Kotaku.
[SPEAKER_07]: They have the ultimate horse riding simulation.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just thought of Final Furlong when I saw it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It looks like an actual horse.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hump a horse, the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeehaw.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the person's even dressed up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like a jockey?
[SPEAKER_06]: Like a horse?
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: A horse riding a horse.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh my god, a horse riding a horse.
[SPEAKER_04]: But a horse is a horse, of course, of course.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Horse riding horse?
[SPEAKER_07]: How can that be?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's going to do it for another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: But first, we've got to go around and get everybody's final thought.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_04]: Reject false icons.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I have an addition to that now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Think with your brain, not the TV guide.
[SPEAKER_06]: My final thought is reject the common cold.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: I need to play more ranked Grand Theft Auto 4 multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, and sorry for people that see me online around 10 o'clock and 3 o'clock Pacific time.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, because we do our online...
[SPEAKER_07]: inter-employee games and accidentally invited people sometimes to that and I had to kick them.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry, Jason51.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, that's what's going on there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: So 10am and 3pm, not good GTA times for Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, noon though.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sometimes we'll leave it open during noon.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, that's going to do it for another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: My name is Rob Roberts, that's DarkSakura, that's Loki, and we're out of here for a week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you guys so much for supporting Independent Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you like what you heard, please tell two people about our show because we do it for free, we do it for the love of it, and we do it to chat with you guys every week.
[SPEAKER_06]: So send us emails, rate us a five on iTunes, leave us voicemails, call us next week, whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: We love talking to you guys every week.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we'll see you next time here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, and happy birthday, Bobby Blackwolf.
[SPEAKER_00]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_00]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_00]: To join us for a live show, visit www.allgames.com Sunday nights at 6 p.m.
[SPEAKER_00]: Pacific time.
[SPEAKER_00]: See you next week!