[SPEAKER_12]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and released to our podcast stream twice weekly.
[SPEAKER_12]: To listen to the first half of this episode, visit www.orangeloungeradio.com for links to websites with listings of past episodes.
[SPEAKER_12]: Now the conclusion of this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is Sunday, May the 6th of 2007.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, it's 5-6-7.
[SPEAKER_03]: Get it?
[SPEAKER_03]: We're here for part B of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, you know...
[SPEAKER_03]: That would only happen once every few years where you get the consecutive numbers like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, this is part B of our podcast.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you missed the first half of this episode, please go back over to OrangeLaunchRadio.com and check out the first half of tonight's show.
[SPEAKER_03]: We are taping live on Sunday night here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's get back into some video game news.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, start us off.
[SPEAKER_04]: So the bastards over at Microsoft decided that it's time to ruin more fun for you, including downloading stuff that you shouldn't be downloading, like demos and stuff from other regions.
[SPEAKER_04]: So apparently now they're going to be enforcing their Xbox Live demo download region lockouts, and they're going to make it impossible for you to download content from other regions.
[SPEAKER_04]: However, if you've already downloaded stuff, good for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: You get to keep it still.
[SPEAKER_04]: But anything else, fuck yourself.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can see it.
[SPEAKER_04]: They won't delete your accounts.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can see what content's on there, but you can't do shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you can look in the store window, but you can't buy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: and I noticed you came out swinging on this story.
[SPEAKER_03]: The second word out of your mouth was bastards.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'm curious if you feel personally affected by this because you don't have a Japanese account or anything that you were using, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, not at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: We only got demos for Armored Core 4.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had a demo for Tenchu Z last year.
[SPEAKER_03]: If I'm not mistaking, aren't they controlling this by IP address lookup, basically?
[SPEAKER_03]: That they're making sure your IP address is in the country you say you're from?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, if that's the case, that's going to be fucking easy.
[SPEAKER_03]: So what's to stop them, yeah, what's to stop them from IP spoofing?
[SPEAKER_04]: Or port forwarding, or like, yeah, basically bouncing yourself off a different DNS server.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here come the hacks pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: That'll be easy.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I'm sure you'll get right on that in hacking.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure I will.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyhow, let's talk about what's coming out to Xbox Live Arcade, in America at least.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know about all regions, but I know we're getting it here.
[SPEAKER_03]: And usually the arcade releases are pretty much universal.
[SPEAKER_03]: But what's coming out this week on Xbox Live Arcade, Double Dragon is coming out.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that was rumored earlier in the week to be coming out.
[SPEAKER_03]: But this got confirmed by a press release coming out of Empire Interactive.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, Speedball is going to be released as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Speedball 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: This was a sports game featuring robots or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Although it says, actually, I'm going to correct myself.
[SPEAKER_03]: It says Speedball 2 is coming within the coming weeks, but Double Dragon is coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we don't know if Speedball 2 is necessarily this week or not, but we do know Double Dragon is for sure.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I had not even heard of Speedball 2 before.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know they call it a classic, but somehow I missed that one.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was on the Amiga, I think, and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, well, that's why.
[SPEAKER_03]: I still was on the Commodore 64 by the time everybody was talking about Commodore Amiga.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, there is actually another game coming to Xbox Live Arcade, and that's Puzzle Quest Challenge of the Warlords, which is already on PSP and Nintendo DS, and it's supposed to come out later this year.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's also going to be coming out with Mad Trax, which is like a Penny Racer the game or something.
[SPEAKER_08]: and a Rocket Bowl that's mini-golf, but bowling.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, Penny Racers really sucked.
[SPEAKER_04]: This looks a lot better.
[SPEAKER_08]: I had Penny Racers when I was little, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: This looks like, well, they had a game called Penny Racer on the Nintendo 64 and it blew up.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, I'm actually just talking about... Oh, no, wasn't that... No, that was Uniracer I'm thinking of.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, this actually... No, this kind of reminds me of it, except without the old... Like the Micro Machines games, almost.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_08]: That could be kind of... I mean, it has potential to be fun, but...
[SPEAKER_08]: But quite honestly, I'll just keep playing Uno and Symphony of the Night.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yeah, Puzzle Quest is going to be so awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't wait.
[SPEAKER_04]: By the way, we have other things coming out, of course, in all the regions of the world.
[SPEAKER_04]: This week, lots of good stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, not a lot of good stuff, but some pretty good stuff coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Driver 76 Driver Parallel Lines
[SPEAKER_04]: Hot Wheels Ultimate Racing, and Heat Seeker on PSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then of course on, let's see, the PC, not a whole lot coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've got Locomania, which sounds like a pretty interesting train simulator, and Circus Empire, which also equally probably boring.
[SPEAKER_04]: On PlayStation 3, you've got Big Fat Nada, and of course the Wii, nothing to look at there either.
[SPEAKER_04]: And finally,
[SPEAKER_04]: The DS, nothing to see there either.
[SPEAKER_04]: So a whole lot of nothing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know actually I think on PlayStation 2 also .hack//G.U.
[SPEAKER_04]: Volume 2 is making its way up.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's it for the week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pretty light week.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's going to start picking up.
[SPEAKER_07]: What about Japan, Rob?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, over in Japan we will have Command & Conquer 3 as well, at least hitting the Asia regions, which I imagine a lot of folks who import games, if they want to pick up the Asian version, can get that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Spider-Man 3
[SPEAKER_03]: Simple 2000 Series Volume 117
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, okay, so it's just games going into this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, never mind.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, they're budget games that get released by, like, D3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, Earth Defense Force, for example.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, I get it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or Zombies vs. Ambulance.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't put two and two together.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, they have the ZeroSend, and you'll be happy to know here it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: The ZeroSend is coming out on PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, if I can only download all of them.
[SPEAKER_03]: It looks like planes blowing shit up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, it looks like 1941 all over again.
[SPEAKER_03]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Psycho 2, Lady It's... Okay
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a board game simulator.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it's Shogi.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, yeah, isn't part of the fun about this segment getting to hear me butcher Japanese pronunciation?
[SPEAKER_03]: By the way, the big, big, big release this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: That means greatest something.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think this might be why you don't see much coming out this week, because finally when I got to the bottom of the page and saw the PSP releases, Final Fantasy Tactics coming out in Japan this week, the PSP version there.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'm sure that's what you'll all be playing and importing this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: So the rest of the games just kind of don't matter anymore.
[SPEAKER_03]: How about the Europe release dates, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_08]: Why don't I tell you about them, Rob?
[SPEAKER_08]: On the 9th, we have Two Worlds for Xbox 360 and PC.
[SPEAKER_08]: The 11th brings us 32nd America's Cup of the Game on PC, Busted Move Bash on Wii, Driver 76 on PSP, Go Puzzle, PlayStation 3, Hard Rock Casino on PS2 and PSP, and for the DS, we also have Picross DS and Turn It Around.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'd like to bash the Bust a Move series after this many years.
[SPEAKER_03]: Go away.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't come back.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want, like, a new actual Bust a Move, not a Puzzle Bobble.
[SPEAKER_03]: Remember Bust a Move on the PlayStation 2 with the artwork that had the baby on it?
[SPEAKER_03]: And it was like, what in the fuck shit is this game?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, didn't they have Bust a Move on the PlayStation 1?
[SPEAKER_04]: Bust a Move was on the PlayStation 1, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: It didn't start on the PlayStation 2, if I remember correctly.
[SPEAKER_03]: Right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, they've been on every platform.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm talking about the U.S.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bust a Move, Puzzle Bobble.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what I meant.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Japanese one, you know, you could emulate that on your PSP.
[SPEAKER_03]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because, you know, there's the workarounds.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yippee!
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm hooping and hollering and screaming out of pure joy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I've never played Puzzle Bobble in my entire life out of the 50 times it's come out on the console.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've played Puzzle de Pon, which is almost the same thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: You should play Puzzle in Desert, it's fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, Warhawk.
[SPEAKER_04]: Warhawk.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, you're so funny, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm so glad we have you on this program.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or go fuck yourself.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, for anybody who likes their, you know, nifty looking skins for, you know, or versions of their DS, as I point to Andrew with his old school Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_03]: His Walmart bot cover for his DS.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just got the finger.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, I have one that's sent by Miyamoto.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have one that's signed by me and that's more awesomer.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's a Golden DS Lite that has a backlit die-cast sword and shield crest.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it has a custom charge stand and two painted styli in silver and black.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the only way that anyone's going to be able to get one is to get it on eBay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have to have custom stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: I need custom stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't get me wrong, I think it's a great cause and everything, but I'm just waiting for Nintendo to steal the ideas.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, Sony will release another PSP which will have the Zelda shield on it with the sword.
[SPEAKER_04]: It won't make any sense, but they copied it, so that's all that matters.
[SPEAKER_03]: They'll just call it Dark... What was that game?
[SPEAKER_04]: The Soul Calibur.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, what the hell was that game?
[SPEAKER_03]: Dark Cloud.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dark Cloud, thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: They'll call it the Dark Cloud cover.
[SPEAKER_04]: They need a new Dark Cloud game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways, so there was an interview with Iwata...
[SPEAKER_04]: He was talking a little bit about the state of Nintendo and a little bit about the releases.
[SPEAKER_04]: Basically saying that they're going to see a brand new Mario, Metroid, and Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_04]: game in 07.
[SPEAKER_04]: So all three of those games are probably coming out around Christmas.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're going to make their big splash.
[SPEAKER_04]: But they are coming this year.
[SPEAKER_04]: At least that's what's planned so far.
[SPEAKER_04]: So don't be surprised if they move to next year.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know, dates under consideration, or dates subject to change, or whatever that crap is they always get away with doing to us.
[SPEAKER_04]: Soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: They'll be coming out soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, to be honest, who's really surprised that, like, Metroid Prime 3 or whatever is coming out in the fall?
[SPEAKER_04]: They gotta have something for this Christmas.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it's like, woohoo!
[SPEAKER_03]: I never thought that would be coming around Christmas.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tell me I can play it on the internet and I'll get tons more excited.
[SPEAKER_03]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tell me I don't have to use friend codes anymore and I'll blow a load.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll be very excited.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, this news made me about that excited.
[SPEAKER_03]: It really did, because this is one of my favorite, all-time favorite 80s Commodore 64 games ever.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's Impossible Mission.
[SPEAKER_03]: This game is incredible, incredibly great for the Commodore 64.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sure it's one of those games that my memories of it are way fonder than the way the game actually is, so don't try to tell me any difference.
[SPEAKER_03]: But however, the important thing about Impossible Mission is that it is coming out on the Virtual Console.
[SPEAKER_03]: But here's the trick.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not... You'll notice it's a Commodore 64 game, or was a Commodore 64 game.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it is not...
[SPEAKER_03]: A, like, you know, the rumors were that Commodore 64 was coming to Virtual Console.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is not simply a rehashed Impossible Mission.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, no, it is Impossible Mission with now, like, updated, also they're going to do updated mode with, you know, new graphics and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, like, a new version of Impossible Mission with the retro one included.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, you can think, like, a lot of those Xbox Live titles are kind of like this, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: But the interesting thing about this is that would make Impossible Mission the first Wii download title
[SPEAKER_03]: Actraiser, PSP, DS
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm so excited.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, guess what's coming out to the UK Virtual Console?
[SPEAKER_08]: Virtua Fighter 2!
[SPEAKER_08]: Sadly, however, it is the Mega Drive version.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, which over here, I do believe the Mega Drive was the Genesis.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know, it's going to be the crap version.
[SPEAKER_08]: And, you know, I am not a fan of Virtua Fighter.
[SPEAKER_08]: My husband's a big Virtua Fighter fan.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm the Tekken girl of the house, but
[SPEAKER_08]: Virtua Fighter 2 made me cry, except that I did try the trick where you could hit Kage over and over and over again and knock off his mask.
Fuck them both, Soul Calibur.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also, the right now that's out on the, that's coming out this week for a virtual console in the UK.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, this makes me happy, is Wonder Boy and Monster World, which I would really love, because I actually do own that game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Very, very fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's too bad we don't have Master System games.
[SPEAKER_08]: for Virtual Console because I would love to have Alex Kidd in Shinobi World.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yet.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want a new Daytona game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that so much to ask?
[SPEAKER_04]: Just for the theme song.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want any new Sega game to not suck.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is that too much to ask?
Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: So if I may continue.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also out is Shockman, which was a PC Engine game.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was actually in the Shibing... Let me start over.
[SPEAKER_08]: SheBeanMan series is called Shockman, which is basically like, you know, we're going to be Mega Man, but not really.
[SPEAKER_08]: There were a lot of PC Engine games that were like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then we have Atlas Kid and the Enchanted Castle, also a Genesis slash Mega Drive game.
[SPEAKER_08]: And like I said, Virtua Crap 2.
[SPEAKER_08]: So.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like Virtua crap.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's why I take in my Virtua toilet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Taking a shit in Second Life.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or PlayStation Home.
[SPEAKER_03]: Chat.Horizontalradio.com comments, Actdeft is cheering you on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Daytona on VC.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkTetsuya says, oh shit, yes, Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: Completely pop-up?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, not on VC.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm talking about a fucking brand new game.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, like a redoing Sigarelli.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want Daytona 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want a newer game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Daytona 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thousand.
[SPEAKER_04]: Million.
[SPEAKER_07]: Death Race Daytona Edition
[SPEAKER_04]: Alien Hominid is awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I think they should do that for, like, completing a game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, getting, like, all 1,000, you know, achievement points or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: They should do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, how expensive can this be to put out?
[SPEAKER_03]: They are charging me $60 for a goddamn video game, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_03]: But maybe they, I guess, well, because of rentals and stuff, maybe they want to make sure people actually own the game or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe a little something special for actually owning the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because back in the 2600 days, they didn't rent video games.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I miss that.
[SPEAKER_03]: One way that you might want to train for winning those trophies is playing other video games because video games are good for you.
[SPEAKER_03]: At least that's according to Yahoo, who this week ran a story about five ways that video games can make you better, stronger, and faster.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I thought I'd share those with you again coming from Yahoo.
[SPEAKER_03]: They can improve your eyesight is one.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that was from a March 2007 study at the University of Rochester because it tested college folks.
[SPEAKER_03]: And apparently after 30 hours of gameplays,
[SPEAKER_03]: The ones who played the games outperformed the ones who didn't play the games in their ability to accurately pick out objects in a cluttered space.
[SPEAKER_03]: So they can play Where's Waldo better.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if I sit close to a TV, that's supposed to ruin my eyesight.
[SPEAKER_04]: This will actually help me as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if I play a game on the TV and sit too close, it'll kind of wash.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: You'll have to run a separate study on that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Number two, they can help you focus.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they're relating this to, you know, folks that have like ADHD, you know, they don't have the ability to focus and stuff and like playing a video game forces you to focus.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I beg to differ because I have gaming ADD.
[SPEAKER_03]: I never beat video games anymore.
[SPEAKER_03]: Seriously, I play them for five hours and then get sick of them.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's sick.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think they mean not necessarily over long term.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think they mean for periods of time.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, well, it's not for long term.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's not gaming ADD.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's just called, this game is fucking boring.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm sorry, what were you talking about?
[SPEAKER_13]: Ooh, look, a bird!
[SPEAKER_13]: If you get the reference.
[SPEAKER_04]: They focus so much that they play and forget about their families and get divorces.
[SPEAKER_03]: Step number three, they can help you lose weight.
[SPEAKER_03]: And of course, you know, DDR, iToy Kinetic, Wii Sports.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or gain a lot of weight, depending on which game it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Number four, they can help you understand classic literature.
[SPEAKER_03]: You spoony bard!
[SPEAKER_03]: For instance, Halo is being used by Roger Travis, who is an associate professor of modern and classical languages at the University of Connecticut.
[SPEAKER_03]: He uses the Halo story as some type of comparison to his stories, the Homer epics.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, there's a story to Halo?
[SPEAKER_08]: How does Halo sound like the Odyssey or the Iliad?
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, specifically, I think he's citing Aenid.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was Virgil.
[SPEAKER_08]: That wasn't Homer.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was Virgil taking inspiration.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Were there headshots in the Aenid?
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait, hold on.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm trying to read through this story here.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Aenid was by Virgil.
[SPEAKER_07]: What the hell is that?
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, the story does say that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, then why did they say, up here, they say Homer.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because it was inspired by Homer.
[SPEAKER_03]: You want literature, you play Zenisaga.
[SPEAKER_07]: You want literature, you fucking read a book.
[SPEAKER_07]: How about that?
[SPEAKER_03]: And step five, they can literally save your life.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they are saying... Trauma center!
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, well, not just trauma center, but Dr. James Rosser of New York's Beth Israel Medical Center says to his patients that he's awesome at Super Monkey Ball because his hand-eye coordination helps in surgeries.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't want him in the doctor.
[SPEAKER_03]: He co-authored a study.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know, seriously, I'm moving to New York.
[SPEAKER_03]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: Five ways that video games are good for you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see, I'm looking into the chat room there.
[SPEAKER_04]: So would that be like, you know, hey, I'm a great proctologist.
[SPEAKER_04]: I practice a lot on Oonga Boonga.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_03]: James Patrick defending Halo a little bit, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Halo has a lot of story.
[SPEAKER_03]: A lot of it is just not in the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, it's called sarcasm.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, then I won't read the rest of his comment.
[SPEAKER_03]: Vandalus is making a Shakespeare reference saying, do you bite your thumb at me, sir?
[SPEAKER_03]: And I know why he did that, because remember when we went miniature golf?
[SPEAKER_03]: We went miniature golfing with Vandalus the other night.
[SPEAKER_03]: We actually went to Golfland and golfed.
[SPEAKER_03]: Drew Nami was there, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I was out there quoting Shakespeare.
[SPEAKER_13]: I do not bite my thumb at you, sir, but I do bite my thumb, sir.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, like, I think I actually impressed... I think I actually impressed William, because he kind of looked over at me and he was kind of like, you actually know Shakespeare?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, but I pointed at Miss Oscar.
[SPEAKER_03]: I also want to point out, you might want to turn your mic on once in a while.
Fuck.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: I pointed out the best, though, Shakespeare fact of all.
[SPEAKER_08]: In the play Hamlet, the word bunghole is in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: You were the type of girl that stayed after class to look up shit in the dictionary, weren't you?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I was not.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because that's what we did.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would stay behind to look up the entomology behind it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Disgusting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Originated from the Latin word shite.
[SPEAKER_08]: No shite's the British deviation.
[SPEAKER_03]: And this is why DarkSakura is in charge of the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_03]: She's very familiar with shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Therefore, she's perfect for reading your emails.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, just kidding.
[SPEAKER_03]: We love getting emails.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's part of what makes this show so special is that we have the interaction with our listeners.
[SPEAKER_03]: Be it the Skype line, the chat room, or emails.
[SPEAKER_03]: So if you want to email us, mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com DarkSakura, open up the mailbag and pull out some shitty email to read.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, the first email of the evening is sent to us by Ion671.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dear OLR guys and girls, I was looking at the screens for Eye of Judgment and while I'm not going to buy a PS3 for some aspects, the fact that you can see your animated monsters in your hand on screen
[SPEAKER_08]: To me, seems like a cool idea.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now developers just have to use it, maybe I'll follow.
[SPEAKER_08]: Too bad Nintendo doesn't have the camera.
[SPEAKER_08]: Seeing your Pokemon next to you on screen, think about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: A good idea?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: I admit when I first saw it at E3, I was kind of like, huh, well that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is it a next-gen system seller?
[SPEAKER_03]: No effing way.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because seriously, I don't see why they couldn't have done this last gen.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's so special about the Eye of Judgment, really?
[SPEAKER_08]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pokemon Stadium Pokemon Stadium
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, next email comes from our friend overseas that wrote us last week, from Matt.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, Orange Jones Radio, I'm writing you this week to answer the question posed in Part B of your podcast last week about the European Bimani community.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can say that where I am, it is alive and well, although I wouldn't describe it as thriving like California.
[SPEAKER_08]: Finding a machine here in Italy is pretty difficult unless you go to a bigger city like Milan or Torino.
[SPEAKER_08]: The arcade culture that is so fragile and dying where we come from kind of never existed here, as culture phenomenon video games are really frowned upon.
[SPEAKER_08]: Unless you were playing Winning Eleven, then you were automatically labeled as Sfigato, the Italian equivalent of a nerd.
[SPEAKER_08]: That being said, where you do find machines, they're always in immaculate condition and have a sizable community around them.
[SPEAKER_08]: The vibe I get from the European scene is like it was for me in 2002 in Tennessee.
[SPEAKER_08]: No websites like DDR Freak or communities of that nature exist,
[SPEAKER_08]: But, you know, everyone by name who plays regularly, and that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: By the way, DDR Freak was around in 2002 because I was a moderator in 2002 when it was NorCal only on the green board.
[SPEAKER_03]: And he said that it's not like it is in California, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Where the machines are all torn up and dirty?
[SPEAKER_03]: I was going to say, I guess the perception of what the Mamani scene is like here...
[SPEAKER_03]: Must be different over there, because I'll tell you, it's, you know what, go look at the DDR freak like NorCal, SoCalForums.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a lot of retrospective posts about how the community used to be.
[SPEAKER_03]: What was the last great DDR tournament you went to, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_08]: B3.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then how many years ago was that?
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, the one I ran.
[SPEAKER_03]: And how many years ago was all this, though?
[SPEAKER_08]: A couple years.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, you know, it was within Orange Lounge Radio's history.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it was in, what, 2003?
2003?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it was 03 is when B3 happened.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura is an equal opportunity bitch, actually.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I'm just whenever the opportunity hits me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just especially to foreigners because she hates British people, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I want to move there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dear British listeners, send me a ticket, please, and I'll rub you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, she just wants to stalk David Tennant.
[SPEAKER_03]: But anyway, next email.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I don't want to stalk David Tennant.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want to go drinking.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: With Billy Piper and then hope something happens.
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: She's pretty, but not my type.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: Next email comes from Necky.
[SPEAKER_08]: Speaking of one of our listeners from the UK.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dear OLR, how's you?
[SPEAKER_08]: Last week's Don't Give a Shit episode was amazing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Be sure to get Warrior Bob back on as he is really cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also, after hearing the whole Sony God of War goat fiasco, I was left feeling a little hoarse.
[SPEAKER_08]: Giggle.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jamie, Dead and Furious.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've heard of... Let me finish with email people.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've heard of this game about two months ago, my home site, dscommunity.co.uk, and it really doesn't look like that great.
[SPEAKER_08]: Have you seen the screenshots?
[SPEAKER_08]: Personally, I don't like, but you're open to your opinion, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: On the theme of dead, touch the dead.
[SPEAKER_03]: That guy works in a fucking plug for his website every time he sends us an email and Jamie falls for it every time.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just like to point out.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't fall for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually... No, it's cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm all for promoting the indie websites.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just giving this guy a hard time because he works it into every email.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's cute.
[SPEAKER_08]: Lord of the Rings Online is a bitch.
[SPEAKER_08]: My mate has been trying to install it on his Vista since the day it was released.
[SPEAKER_08]: With Rob saying the game sucks, kind of influences my decision.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hmm, worth it or not?
[SPEAKER_08]: Nothing left to say except the new Guitar Hero 2 song packs kick ass.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, hell yeah, they do.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wah, bye, Nikki.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oblivion is so my game at the moment.
[SPEAKER_08]: Played it loads.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oblivion is incredible.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, I just wanted to say, if you want to try Lord of the Rings, it's actually really easy.
[SPEAKER_03]: All you have to do is you can go to any computer store and you can get a trial disc for like $2, except the only problem is it's labeled World of Warcraft because the game rips it off in every single way.
[SPEAKER_08]: Rob, first of all, UK.
[SPEAKER_08]: Second of all, they're trying to install it on Vista and it's not working.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you can play World of Warcraft on Vista and I'm pretty sure they have the same trial thing in the UK because you can download them now.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I mean...
[SPEAKER_08]: It's different than World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just trying to say Lord of the Rings is not fun, and I already played it when it was called World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let them judge for themselves.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why are you listening to this show?
[SPEAKER_03]: You want me to judge it for you.
[SPEAKER_03]: It sucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you beg to differ, email nasty things to us.
[SPEAKER_08]: Next email.
[SPEAKER_08]: This comes from Osfer.
[SPEAKER_08]: Looks like somebody new.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wasn't drunk, Osfer.
[SPEAKER_03]: I promise.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's Osfer, not Osfer.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yo, this is Osfer.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just wanted to say that I love the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: You guys are sort of like a radio version of Attack of the Show from G4 TV.
[SPEAKER_03]: We know you meant it as a compliment, so we'll take it that way.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: When I met Kevin Pereira, he was really cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't say anything negative about the people on that show because they are really talented and all that jazz.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, I just wanted to know, Loki, DarkSakura, and Sky, how good are all of you at DDR and Beatmania?
[SPEAKER_08]: Personally, I suck at Beatmania, but I still love the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: As for DDR, I'm fairly decent.
[SPEAKER_08]: When it comes to difficulty, I'm able to do 10 footers like Max Unlimited, getting a grade of B, and Zephyr Oni, getting an A. As for my perfect attack, it needs work, but I'm not able to AAA anything in the arcade, yet I've AAA'd lots of songs on Heavy at home.
[SPEAKER_08]: For me, I actually was pretty far up there, and then...
[SPEAKER_08]: I just get really, really, really exhausted really easily, so.
[SPEAKER_03]: I used to be pretty good at DDR, especially when we started this show.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was beating nines regularly.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't ever quite have the stamina to clear a lot of tens.
[SPEAKER_03]: I could clear bag, but I couldn't really do the max 300s because there's just too much stamina.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think I got bag once.
[SPEAKER_03]: But my perfect attack was good.
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually AAA'd quite a few seven and eight footers in the arcades, and I actually would participate in tournaments.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I came in fourth place in a couple of them.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the highest I ever got is fourth place.
[SPEAKER_03]: But to me, that's still a pretty decent showing for me.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was very proud of myself.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I suck now, but I don't have a good excuse like Jamie.
[SPEAKER_03]: My excuse is I got fat, and that makes me not so good at DDR anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I lost all my stamina.
[SPEAKER_04]: I used to be good.
[SPEAKER_04]: I used to be able to do hard kata's and even my wonderful edits on doubles all the time.
[SPEAKER_04]: And now I can do sevens and eights and stuff, but it really kicks the crap out of me.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just I don't have the stamina for it anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: If I played all the time, maybe...
[SPEAKER_04]: Just had a DDR machine in my house or something, that'd be different.
[SPEAKER_08]: I got really lazy with Beatmania, though, after not having a reliable machine to play on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because we were playing 2DX7 style for a long time when we had it at Scandia.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Beatmania, I went from crappy to really crappy.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I had actually just started beating Seven Stars, because you were there when I beat Nine O'Clocks and...
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_03]: Not at all.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'm just kind of bored of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't care about 2DX anymore.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, there is another bit more to this email.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also, when it comes to DDR Supernova 2, where the hell is the info?
[SPEAKER_08]: But this time last year, we practically knew most of Supernova 1's song list.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why do you think Konami is keeping this under wraps?
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks for reading, Ossifer.
[SPEAKER_08]: And yeah, they actually tried to keep it under wraps last year, as far as I was aware.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope they do keep it under wraps.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope it's like Max 2, where we didn't see that shit coming until it was there.
[SPEAKER_04]: That made it exciting.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want a surprise.
[SPEAKER_04]: In Extreme, or not Extreme, but Supernova, it was like, here's everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just not exciting.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would totally love, though, to have an unlock system the way that Max did.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, to have stuff come out over time, which encourages people.
[SPEAKER_08]: The more that you play, the sooner you're going to get stuff coming out.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think that that would be really fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: You remember how we would congregate around the machine?
[SPEAKER_08]: I remember.
[SPEAKER_08]: And say, okay, we have to do this many more until we get our next song.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm telling you, DDR needs a card system in the US, and it needs something more battle-y.
[SPEAKER_03]: It needs to become a more competitive game.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's how the game could evolve, but no one's listening to me.
[SPEAKER_03]: And battle mode, or whatever the hell you want to call it, is not enough, because it's not the focus of the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's a PS to this.
[SPEAKER_08]: It says, I don't consider myself to be that great at DDR yet.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why?
[SPEAKER_08]: I've met MegaManX and he lives pretty close by here in Northeast Ohio.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't really think... This is my opinion on gaming, especially in a competitive sense.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why make a competition of it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Why just not have fun?
[SPEAKER_03]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why not just have fun with it?
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, I remember reading... Actually, you know Foxtrot, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: The Sunday comic in the paper.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like how the little girl was trying to make...
[SPEAKER_08]: Like a paper airplane or something.
[SPEAKER_08]: And her dad's like, oh, let me show you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't you want to have the best?
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't you want to be this?
[SPEAKER_08]: She's like, no, I just want to have fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: And no offense to this guy or his ego, but I have no idea who that guy is, he just said.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know who that is.
[SPEAKER_08]: Neither do I. I have no idea.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sure he's nice, but I'm good at DDR apparently, but I don't, you know, he's not that famous.
[SPEAKER_13]: Of course, neither are we.
[SPEAKER_13]: Of course, I've got to open up the usual can of worms.
[SPEAKER_13]: Guess what other game had a battle system that was actually pretty decent?
[SPEAKER_13]: In the Groove.
[SPEAKER_13]: Guess who swallowed that up?
[SPEAKER_03]: I disagree.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think In the Groove was the same damn game as DDR.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just a different wrapping.
[SPEAKER_04]: Guess what game had a battle system?
[SPEAKER_04]: Step Mania.
[SPEAKER_04]: Guess which one became In the Groove?
[SPEAKER_04]: I do not want to have this debate again.
[SPEAKER_08]: Rob from Sakura Maxx.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey Jamie, just made a quick email to say pump up the volume rocks.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's your favorite class in Ragnarok Online?
[SPEAKER_08]: I liked Acolytes.
[SPEAKER_08]: I did have a super Acolyte, but I played Assassins.
[SPEAKER_08]: I actually managed to get an Assassin Cross on one of my free servers.
[SPEAKER_08]: Still youngest listener who wants to blow shit up and hopes you get eaten by a Gru.
[SPEAKER_03]: When I played Ragnarok Online, I played an Acolyte who had a bow in his hair because he was cute and pretty.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was my wallpaper on my phone for a long time.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_03]: I played a bad Acolyte.
How much they suck.
[SPEAKER_04]: and of course we'll feature a wonderful mix of music from a bunch of different games and should be performing at the Nokia Theater around October 19th.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's actually pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know why, I actually really want to go to E4ALL, even though I've heard the talk about it's nothing more than a glorified EB Games.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, I just kind of want to go to that atmosphere.
[SPEAKER_03]: And obviously the opportunist in me sees that it's a great promotion opportunity for our show.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I just kind of want to go and check it out.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it would be fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the other thing too, to be honest, it sounds a lot more exciting than the E3 this year.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even looking at E3's show four plans, stuff like that, it's like,
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you know, but E3 wasn't supposed to have the glitziness this year.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'm sure we're just a little bitter for not getting invited, which is true.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I'm kind of excited about E4ALL.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think I definitely want to go.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hope we all can go.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would be fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: But we'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some controversy going on this week with Blizzard, of course.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, it's earlier been said that they are going to be announcing a new game on May 19th.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, oh my God, is this blown up.
[SPEAKER_03]: And honestly, I don't know who to believe.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because folks are saying, oh, leaked, it's StarCraft, the MMO.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a StarCraft MMO that's coming out.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's World of StarCraft, even though that name would make no sense at all because it's more than just a world.
[SPEAKER_03]: Drew, why are you twitching?
[SPEAKER_04]: And I don't think they would do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know why?
[SPEAKER_13]: Why?
[SPEAKER_04]: Compete with World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_13]: Drew's twitching.
[SPEAKER_13]: I want to know why he's twitching.
[SPEAKER_13]: Number one, we don't need another MMO from Blizzard.
[SPEAKER_13]: Number two, I know competing with yourself is actually good for business sometimes, but I don't think it would be such a good idea here.
[SPEAKER_03]: And of course, just adding fire to this rumor, Vivendi was giving a presentation to Wall Street and said, quote, all Blizzard franchises will become MMOs, which strikes me as hilarious because to me,
[SPEAKER_03]: and I know Blizzard fans are going to get pissed but honestly to me World of Warcraft does already feel like World of Diablo to me honestly like the game plays very similar to me so I don't know what the big deal is but whatever but then Blizzard quickly responded to that quote the rumor is not true in regards to Blizzard we believe the rumors circulating about this subject is based on a misinterpretation of information provided to industry analysts bottom line you don't know shit until May 19th period
[SPEAKER_03]: You're going to hear every rumor under the sun.
[SPEAKER_03]: You won't know for sure until May 19th.
[SPEAKER_03]: Personally, I think it's StarCraft 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's not an MMO.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's just StarCraft 2 the way the StarCraft fans want their sequel to StarCraft.
[SPEAKER_13]: It damn well better be StarCraft 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would be happy with that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, so there you have it.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll see what happens when the big announcement is made.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, speaking of big announcements, and this is actually a very, very big announcement to me personally, is that one of our gaming legends, well, I should say legends in game making, Don Bluth, who brought us, you know, Dragon's Lair, is working on a Dragon's Lair movie that's a prequel to Dirk the Daring's whole ordeal outside of the Dragon's Lair.
[SPEAKER_08]: So...
[SPEAKER_08]: Hopefully it actually will legitimately have a tie-in and be a little bit better than Dragon's Lair 2 was.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dragon's Lair 2 was the acid trip game, I'm so sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: But there better be gruesome, gory skeleton deaths in it.
[SPEAKER_08]: That'd be really awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know how I feel about the Dragon's Lair franchise being milked to death 20 years past its prime.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hope it's not going to be as awful as the old cartoon was.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know how I feel about this.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, in the end, I will judge based on the product that's delivered, but, you know, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I only have so much love for Dragon's Lair in my heart, and believe me, I do have a lot of love.
[SPEAKER_03]: I completely loved the Commodore 64 version of the game, if for nothing else, but I thought the music was some of the best soundtracks, like, ever in an 80s game.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, um, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Speaking of 80s cartoons, you probably heard this week that they put up the first episode of the 1980s version of the Pac-Man cartoon on Xbox Live Marketplace.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I did not hear that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's for free download, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_03]: Already?
[SPEAKER_03]: Already.
[SPEAKER_03]: Holy shit, I missed that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to check that out.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought that was funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: TheRobD in chat says, Dragon's Lair franchise.
[SPEAKER_03]: It wasn't a franchise.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was one arcade game that was innovative.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, there was a sequel because they had the sequel.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be coming out, though, for a low, low price of $29.95.
[SPEAKER_04]: And pretty much, you know, the GameCube or PlayStation 2 version with tacked on Wii controls and going to have the bonus content that was also available on the PlayStation 2 version as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, if you think that's worth $30, then definitely worth picking up.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, like, maybe I'm the only person on the planet that didn't buy this game for the GameCube or PlayStation 2 because I played my friend's copy.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm actually kind of interested because it was a fun game.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I think with the Wii controls, it would be, you know, really fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, for $30, it's not a bad deal.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a good game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Are you going to get it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Anybody else?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not buying it.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: One more story for you guys, and we're going to open up our Skype line at 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_03]: GamePro ran a story this week called the 10 worst-selling game consoles of all time.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think this was done by actual sales figures, but it says, okay, quote, here are the 10 worst-selling consoles of all time in terms of high-profile systems that stood a viable chance.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Fairchild Channel left.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I'm actually going to name the ten systems.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to know how many of these you actually own, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_03]: First off, those of you, okay, I'm assuming none of you have read this story yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: What would you, if you haven't read the story yet, what would you guess is number one?
[SPEAKER_03]: The number one worst selling console of all time.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Fairchild Channel F. Fairchild Channel F. I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: What would you say, Drew?
[SPEAKER_07]: The Jaguar.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Jaguar.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: I would actually say the Neo Geo.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jaguar, Jaguar, Neo Geo.
[SPEAKER_03]: I already know, so I can't answer.
[SPEAKER_03]: Virtual Boy says Frisbee and Chat, Master Systems says GS68.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Number 10, the Dreamcast.
[SPEAKER_08]: I own two of them.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Dreamcast sold only 10.6 million units during its short three-year lifespan.
[SPEAKER_03]: Only?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I want to know how many of these systems Jamie owns, by the way, in her house.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, what do you want to say, Loki?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I was just going to say, hopefully Sony can beat 10.6 million units in three years.
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh, let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Number nine, the TurboGrafx-16.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have a Turbo Duo and a PC Engine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Number eight, the Saturn.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have two of those.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have three.
[SPEAKER_03]: You guys are nerds.
[SPEAKER_03]: Number seven, the Sega CD.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have three.
[SPEAKER_03]: No love for Sega on this list.
[SPEAKER_03]: How do you have three Sega CDs?
[SPEAKER_03]: Isn't one enough?
[SPEAKER_08]: I have a drawer loader and two side loaders.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, no, I think one of our side loaders was broken.
Fucking nerd.
[SPEAKER_03]: Number six, the 3DO.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hell no, I have taste.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've played a 3DO.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know, I played one once.
[SPEAKER_07]: I haven't bought a TDI.
[SPEAKER_03]: Number 5, I believe, was the Virtua Boy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Number 5 was the Virtua Boy.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have one in one of those hard cases.
[SPEAKER_13]: Drew says it never had a chance.
[SPEAKER_13]: It never had a chance, and believe me, I own one.
[SPEAKER_13]: It never had a chance.
[SPEAKER_08]: I actually do own one, and they call him the Great Red Migraine Machine.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Amazing Red Seizure Machine of Death.
[SPEAKER_03]: With a horrible controller!
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, it was a horrible controller.
[SPEAKER_03]: Number four, the CDI.
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: You don't have that?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, because it had those shitty not Zelda games on them.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it had Myst, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: I could play that on PC.
[SPEAKER_03]: 570,000 units sold to the CDI.
[SPEAKER_03]: Number three, the Atari Jaguar.
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: The only reason I would ever want one, though, is for Tempest.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's exactly what the story says.
[SPEAKER_03]: The system had Tempest 2000, but every other game was garbage.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sold 250,000 units.
[SPEAKER_03]: Number two, the 32X from Sega.
[SPEAKER_03]: You do have that?
[SPEAKER_08]: I have two 32Xs.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you agree with it being the number two worst selling console of all time?
[SPEAKER_08]: Selling has nothing to do with that.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's more of an add-on than a console.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, but by their terms, sold versus hype.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is a fair entry on the list.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm surprised the Pico's not on here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here it is, the number one.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is not the Neo Geo.
[SPEAKER_03]: Although that was a good guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't believe that wasn't on here.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's one of the ten.
[SPEAKER_03]: The number one, the Apple Pippin.
[SPEAKER_08]: I do not have a Pippin.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Pippin was made between Apple and Bandai, which is funny because there's a lot of people who've always said Apple should get into gaming, Apple should get into gaming, but Apple did get into gaming in 95 with Bandai.
[SPEAKER_03]: They launched their system for $600, and this was in 95.
[SPEAKER_04]: See, I figured that the Neo Geo for sure would be up there because it weren't their game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't remember how much the system was, but the games were like a couple hundred bucks, weren't they?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, but you get arcade-perfect games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll buy an arcade cabinet then.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, seriously.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's been worth it to me.
[SPEAKER_08]: I actually, you know, I can sit down and play my Samurai Shodown 2.
[SPEAKER_08]: And on top of that, with no region lockout, you have no problem.
[SPEAKER_08]: After a while, some of the games go down in price.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, we can pick up some of the classics, you know, Magician Lord and, you know, all kinds of games.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have GameTap.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have Magician Lord and GameTap.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, but keep in mind, I had this, you know, five years ago.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: 42,000 units sold at the Apple Pippin and always makes PC World's worst tech products of all time lists.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good job, Apple.
[SPEAKER_03]: We salute you.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, we are going to open up the Skype line if you want to feedback on the worst console you've ever played or really anything in general.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll take your calls right now, 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype if you want to call us that way because our 800 number is only toll-free.
[SPEAKER_03]: in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_03]: and Canada.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can also call us on Skype.
[SPEAKER_03]: The username is Orange Lounge Radio on Skype.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's go to the phones and take some calls.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_03]: This is DarkTetsuya.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi, DarkTetsuya.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, I just had an announcement I had to make.
[SPEAKER_03]: Announcements, announcements, announcements.
[SPEAKER_03]: A horrible way to die, a horrible way to die, a horrible way to talk to death, a horrible way to die.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who never sang that at campfire, huh?
I never sang that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I never went to camp.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, never mind.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm hoping somebody in chat knows that song.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, DT, what's the announcement?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who would you say would be your two biggest fans?
[SPEAKER_03]: Our two biggest fans?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, before you were on staff, I would have said you, but you're right for the site now, so I can't say you, DarkTetsuya.
[SPEAKER_03]: Definitely Misty.
[SPEAKER_03]: Probably... Well, apparently... Maybe Misty and... Oh, see, Ranma's an op.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, Misty's an op, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe Misty... Well... Alright, well... Ruin everything!
[SPEAKER_03]: You're doing it wrong!
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, what?
[SPEAKER_10]: Give me your goddamn announcement.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm getting to the point.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, as of about two weeks ago, during Guys on the Show, she asked me out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ooh, like asked you out on a date or what?
[SPEAKER_03]: What's going on?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sweet.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, wait, so you're saying that some of the biggest fanboys and girls in OLR history are hooking up?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is a scary day in Orange Lounge radio history.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is a very scary day, and this radio station might have that effect on people.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're going to crash Guys on a Show, and we're planning on it in November.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wait, you're not going to crash the real show?
[SPEAKER_03]: This show?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Guys on a Show is just kind of the, you know... Guys on a Show might be canceled by November.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if I would crash a show like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of like beating a dead horse.
[SPEAKER_08]: You should come back to Guys on a Show so we can play what we'll be having for dinner.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_13]: Crashing Guys on a Show is like pissing in an ocean of piss.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: That is, like, the worst and the best analogy at the same time.
[SPEAKER_03]: I really don't know what to think of that.
[SPEAKER_03]: That'd be like pissing in an ocean of bed liser.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, congratulations.
[SPEAKER_03]: And keep in mind, Artitsuya, if you should start having relationship troubles, there'll be a new advice show coming to the station soon to help you out.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, you know, put Rice Princess's number on speed dial.
[SPEAKER_03]: And congratulations, and I hope things work out for you guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hope she makes you some of her arts and crafts, because she's so funny, because she finds OLR inspiration.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, like, I've got all these random messages from her, like, I was at the 99 cent store, and I saw these orange things, and they made me think of this date.
[SPEAKER_03]: She's cute.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, get some OLR beats from her.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, DarkSakura, anything you want to comment on the news going on this week in gaming?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, man, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's
[SPEAKER_03]: Not really, I understand that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it's kind of a slow news week, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks so much for your call and good luck and everything.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, have a good night, all right?
[SPEAKER_03]: You too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like that he calls it.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's really not a lot I want to say about gaming.
[SPEAKER_03]: TheRobD says, Guys on the show, it's like pissing in an ocean of piss.
[SPEAKER_03]: Can somebody put that as an iTunes review, actually, for this show, since guys on the show isn't podcasts?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because, like...
[SPEAKER_03]: Legend of Zaku He's using his chimp voice
[SPEAKER_01]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, I think Zaku's one of our biggest fans, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: You've been listening to us a long time, haven't you?
[SPEAKER_01]: I think over three years now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Three years now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jesus, go outside.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, just drinking on Saturdays and going to my old plain drunk TDR.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: In these three years, I used to sometimes go, oh boy, here comes a Zaku call.
[SPEAKER_03]: But now I kind of look forward to the Zaku calls because, man, Zaku just tells it like it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you know why we celebrate Cinco de Mayo?
[SPEAKER_01]: Um, Mexican Independence, even though I'm not Mexican.
[SPEAKER_01]: Beer.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know.
[SPEAKER_01]: And drinking, and lots of Mexican flavor.
[SPEAKER_01]: Beer that's not called Corona, please.
[SPEAKER_03]: Weren't you like, please don't be offended if I get this wrong, weren't you like Peruvian?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I got it right, yeah, I'm awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, alright, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, just chilling that day, just trying to get a buzz off of Corona with a shot of rum inside there.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a video game story in here somewhere, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, and just trying to play DDR after two drinks, after a margarita.
[SPEAKER_01]: But yeah, and then just today, just watching Spider-Man 3.
[SPEAKER_01]: Nothing much.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, I really didn't have that much of a weekend.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you're calling into the show tonight just to tell us this or what?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, that and basically Supernova 2 location test getting cancelled.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what I wanted to ask you about because you called into the show last week to talk about this.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know.
[SPEAKER_01]: One week I say it's on and the other week it's not on.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's not bothering me.
[SPEAKER_01]: I can understand Konami just taking a look at themselves as developers and realizing that they really want to
[SPEAKER_01]: They probably, you know, for all we know, they probably might be spending the time just making it better.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or making another Frogger game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because you realize you and the rest of the internet will tear this game a new butthole if it sucks.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, they've already did.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, they're already prejudging as we speak.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're already saying that, oh, LoL is not going to get released.
[SPEAKER_00]: I can understand that as a developer.
[SPEAKER_01]: Indie Groove is better.
[SPEAKER_01]: Why the fuck did you get rid of Indie Groove?
[SPEAKER_01]: As a developer, I understand that if you...
[SPEAKER_01]: If you release a piss-poor product, you're just going to piss people off further, so you want to prevent that by spending more time trying to make something really presentable to the masses.
[SPEAKER_03]: I keep forgetting you're a developer now, and you develop for cell phone games, huh?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: You've got the toughest job in the industry, my friend.
[SPEAKER_01]: We go through a lot of features during the development process.
[SPEAKER_01]: Even though we're close to shipping, there's always one or two big features that we try to get on
[SPEAKER_01]: before they try to make the application better.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you know, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it's got to be internally tested to hell before they're going to do an open test.
[SPEAKER_01]: Right, so they're probably going to, from what we know, they could be implementing new features, adding more songs to make it a worthy location test.
[SPEAKER_03]: We don't want this game to get bubble-bubbled.
[SPEAKER_01]: Right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, all right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anything else, Saku, before we go to another call?
[SPEAKER_01]: Just make sure to tell your arcade to get 2DX Gold.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because if you don't in the next few weeks... Zaku, my local arcade is a golf land.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, the chances of actually being released in this country are getting slim at this point.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I urge all my Bimati brethren to please get out there, get your arcade to pick up gold.
[SPEAKER_03]: Zaku, I would love to, but my local arcade is Rozo Golf Land where video games go to die.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will, however, give countries a place to call.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll give the bowling alley a call.
[SPEAKER_01]: Get Dave and Buster's to do it.
[SPEAKER_01]: They have the biggest purse.
[SPEAKER_01]: So if they buy for all their locations, that would be pretty big.
[SPEAKER_01]: That should make some sort of impact.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, Zaku, thanks so much for the call.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good luck.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hope you guys get work on the 2DX.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hope the 2DX campaign works.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rob D in chat says, Okay, my iTunes review has officially been changed from OLR, your source for the gamer lifestyle, to OLR.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like pissing in an ocean of piss.
[SPEAKER_03]: Beautiful.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I want people to look at the iTunes reviews and go, What the fuck is this show?
[SPEAKER_03]: What the fuck is this show?
[SPEAKER_03]: I better download this show and check it out.
[SPEAKER_03]: See?
[SPEAKER_03]: Reverse psychology works every time.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they realize that you're just scamming them and they stop.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, hey, I...
[SPEAKER_03]: You guys said it!
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi, you're on Orange Songs Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, what's up, guys?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's Toshin.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi, Toshin.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_11]: Just having another reference to another Wednesday-related show.
[SPEAKER_11]: I went shopping this weekend for games.
[SPEAKER_03]: I bought a couple.
[SPEAKER_03]: You went shopping this weekend for games.
[SPEAKER_03]: What'd you buy?
[SPEAKER_11]: I went to Big Chain Store and they had a sale, so I picked up both Phoenix Wright games.
[SPEAKER_11]: I got Cardfighter's DS, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_11]: Shut up!
[SPEAKER_11]: It's a good game on the Neo Geo Pocket Color.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's true, but none of us knew about the bug until somebody found it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it still in the wrapping?
[SPEAKER_04]: You can take it back.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't worry, they're going to probably offer a return program where you can send it back to SNK.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then wait six weeks for a replacement copy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: You'll probably get another free copy of Metal Slug something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Speaking of which, the Game Boy Advance of Metal Slug still hasn't come out yet, and it's been in development for months, almost a year now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Metal Slug Forever?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, almost.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, sorry, Toshin.
[SPEAKER_03]: Go on.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, I picked up Metal Slug Anthology, so that's... For the Wii?
[SPEAKER_11]: No, for the PS2.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you have a Wii?
[SPEAKER_03]: You don't have a Wii, do you?
[SPEAKER_11]: No, I don't.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what I was going to say.
[SPEAKER_03]: I meant the... Drew, I meant the system.
[SPEAKER_03]: Grow up.
[SPEAKER_03]: God.
[SPEAKER_03]: This isn't Wednesday, man.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: This isn't Wednesday, but Drew's in the, you know, pee-pee-poo-poo mentality of those jokes.
[SPEAKER_11]: Save it for the afterbirth.
[SPEAKER_03]: For real.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, um...
[SPEAKER_03]: I was going to say, okay, so you don't have a Nintendo Wii, but you have a PS2.
[SPEAKER_03]: What of these games have you played so far?
[SPEAKER_03]: Have you played them all?
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm working on Phoenix Royale 1 right now.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's pretty good?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, it took me a year and a half to get a copy, for crying out loud.
[SPEAKER_11]: I couldn't find a copy anywhere.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: And have you played any of the other games?
[SPEAKER_11]: I like Metal Slug a lot.
[SPEAKER_11]: I love Metal Slug anyway.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's just a fun game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Please explain the draw of Metal Slug, because I know Jamie tries very hard, but Matt and I still tease her, so you gotta stick up for Jamie here a little bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's the draw of Metal Slug?
[SPEAKER_11]: It's just old-school, run-around... It's like... You like Contra, don't you, Rob?
[SPEAKER_11]: You like 8-bit stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I like Contra.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think it's just like Neo Geo's version of Contra, with better sprites...
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not that I don't understand the draw of Metal Slug.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just I don't understand why it's got to be on the PlayStation 2, on the Xbox, on the 360, on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why do they have to re-release it 7 billion times?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why, hello there, Bustamove, which we were talking about earlier in the program.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, God, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, now that I think about it, SNK kind of sucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, like, sometimes they really, really suck.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, like, the N in SNK stands for suck.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or UC, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's... Sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: The N stands for suck?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: So Don Phonics worked for me!
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: Orange Loud... OLR, the L stands for suck.
[SPEAKER_03]: SMRT.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, that would be it.
[SPEAKER_03]: OLR, the L stands for smarts.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, I just drooled everywhere and laughing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Send those blocks of Crayolas care of Rob.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, I had a secret meeting with Ken Kutaragi this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: What can I say?
[SPEAKER_03]: You jumped ship again?
[SPEAKER_03]: Even the entire chat room was like, what?
[SPEAKER_11]: Train wreck.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, anyway, sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Your call's derailing this show, Toshin.
[SPEAKER_03]: We need to wrap it up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Any other thoughts?
[SPEAKER_11]: If I'm derailing the show, get back on the train.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like Toshin's call is the microwave waves to Rob's pacemaker is basically what it is.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey, at least I'm doing something right, I think.
[SPEAKER_11]: What'd you say?
[SPEAKER_11]: I said at least I'm doing something right, I think.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're derailing this show.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's the right thing to do.
[SPEAKER_03]: Remember, we don't give a shit anymore.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, Tosh, thanks so much for calling, Tosh, and have fun with the games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, later.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what's funny about that phone call is he really wasn't calling to comment on any news or anything going on.
[SPEAKER_03]: He was just kind of like, hey guys, I bought some games this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: But we love those types of calls.
[SPEAKER_04]: I forgot to mention I played Super Paper Mario this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, what'd you think?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it's pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just going through the games slowly.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's too fucking easy, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, the puzzles aren't that hard.
[SPEAKER_03]: For now.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think the difficulty ramps up a lot later on.
[SPEAKER_03]: More calls!
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, what's up?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's the Rob D. Hello, the Rob D. What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_09]: Uh, not too much.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're really quiet tonight for some reason.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wait, what?
[SPEAKER_03]: You're really, really quiet tonight for some reason.
[SPEAKER_03]: Can you turn up your mic?
[SPEAKER_09]: A little better.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_09]: I was saying that he doesn't stand for sucking my podcast that he does.
[SPEAKER_09]: Either way, I just had a
[SPEAKER_09]: Quick question for you guys about gaming.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, what's up?
[SPEAKER_03]: By the way, that podcast you're referencing, of course, This Day in Gaming, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, definitely.
[SPEAKER_03]: Great podcast over on All Games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Check it out.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, what's the question?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, you know, the Xbox Live Arcade and the Virtual Console both had a lot of time to develop so far.
[SPEAKER_09]: Which would you prefer at this moment?
[SPEAKER_09]: I was having this discussion with one of my friends earlier in the week, and I...
[SPEAKER_09]: I sided with the Virtual Console just because I like the idea of having a lot of classic games that are in their original form and are guaranteed to be good as opposed to the Xbox Live Arcade where you do have a few good games on there and it's nice to have these extra features but some of the remakes aren't that great and some of the games themselves aren't that great.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, but, and this is the big but here, um,
[SPEAKER_04]: The Xbox Live Arcade, you can download free demos, and you can check out the game and see if it sucks before you actually have to buy it.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Nintendo system, or the virtual console, or whatever, the Nintendo games, Genesis games, you may remember them, oh my god, those are so awesome, and you download them, spend your five bucks, whatever, and wow, that really sucked, now it's just gonna sit on my drive forever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, I hate the way the shop is set up, fucking running off of webpages with JavaScript is retarded.
[SPEAKER_04]: and it should have been built into the console anyways.
[SPEAKER_04]: And besides, I think the Xbox Live Arcade has a better selection right now and my god, PlayStation Network put out something because one release a month is awful.
[SPEAKER_03]: Notice how Rob D. didn't even mention them.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a reason for that.
[SPEAKER_09]: As far as Xbox... Well, I play Lemmings on the PC.
[SPEAKER_03]: Exactly, I played Lemmings on the PC like 15 years ago and it's just now coming out on PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyhow...
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, you know, I kind of have to side with Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think Xbox Live, just the technology itself is superior because here it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nintendo won't go online.
[SPEAKER_03]: Virtual console, I would give the trophy to in a heartbeat if I could play like Ice Climber online with my friends.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: I can compare scores.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, go listen to Part A when I got mad at PK or Uno because he has a slightly bigger Boom Boom Rocket score than I do.
[SPEAKER_03]: You don't get that on Virtual Console.
[SPEAKER_03]: Although Virtual Console, in the terms of the games they offer, yeah, you know you're getting good shit because these games were quality, for the most part, were quality games that came out many years ago.
[SPEAKER_03]: I could go to Jamie's house and play that shit because she still has them all, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, you know, I mean, all kidding aside, you know...
[SPEAKER_03]: The only reason I pretty much download these is just something about having them.
[SPEAKER_03]: They pretty much equate to impulse buys.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I gotta agree with you on most of those points.
[SPEAKER_09]: They are legitimate points.
[SPEAKER_09]: I would like to be able to play a timed demo or something on the Virtual Console.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't see why Nintendo didn't do that.
[SPEAKER_09]: But to me, in my opinion, and this is why I do side with the Virtual Console, the quality of the average Virtual Console title, again, in my opinion, is much higher than the quality of the average Xbox Live Arcade title.
[SPEAKER_09]: What I'd really like to see Nintendo do, though, is bring over some of those games like Bottom of the Lagoon and some of those other games that didn't make it over here.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'd like to see them translate those, localize those, and actually release them on the virtual console.
[SPEAKER_03]: Second Densetsu 3?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: Case point.
[SPEAKER_03]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: If that does it, I think it's game, set, and match.
[SPEAKER_03]: Exactly, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Second Densetsu 3 could single-handedly change my mind in all of this.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just... I get...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: And those ideas were out on the table a year ago.
[SPEAKER_03]: And yet, well, Sony, I don't know, they're just crazy.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know why they haven't adopted this stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: But Nintendo literally seems to be saying, we're just better than that.
[SPEAKER_03]: We just don't want to do that because we want to do this whole other thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: And although I applaud some of the decisions they made with the Wii, I feel like they're living in the 2600 era when it comes to online right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, they definitely got to do something with that for sure.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's horrible.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, that's all I got for you guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, Rob D., thanks for the discussion.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was definitely an interesting discussion and a good thing to talk about, so I appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not a problem.
[SPEAKER_03]: Have fun with your show.
[SPEAKER_03]: You guys have a great show.
[SPEAKER_03]: See you later.
[SPEAKER_03]: Will do.
[SPEAKER_03]: Take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm looking over to the chat room.
[SPEAKER_03]: PK or Uno says, My copy of iTunes is only giving me one review for the OLR podcast.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's a great point.
[SPEAKER_03]: I forgot to mention that only the U.S.
[SPEAKER_03]: store actually has 41 reviews because
[SPEAKER_03]: The reviews are separated by region.
[SPEAKER_03]: Last time I checked, there was one review in the Canadian store.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't see any in the British store or the Japanese store.
[SPEAKER_03]: That might have changed.
[SPEAKER_03]: The reviews are based by region.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you go to your iTunes store, if you're in a foreign country, that just means we need your help even more.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you're in a foreign country using their iTunes stores, please hype us up a little bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'd appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi, this is DMN and no, I'm not living in San Francisco or New York.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I figure this time I can since it's not really anything specific to the company.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: I haven't heard anything about this period up until a couple of people said, hey, are you aware your company's moving?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm like, huh?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, the way I read the story, it sounded like the sales department was moving, and people are, I don't know if they're jumping to conclusions or if there's just some evidence I missed, but it seems like people are just kind of saying, oh, all of Nintendo's moving because the sales department is moving.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you know, I work... I think it's some jag off in the, uh... I honestly think it's some jag off in the, um...
[SPEAKER_02]: Gaming Media, who's trying to spawn a story.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a bubble rumor.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that certain companies should decide to move to Sacramento instead of San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_04]: Real estate is a lot cheaper, and I need another job.
A better job.
[SPEAKER_03]: You just want to stalk me, Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just want a better job.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, well, okay, so thank you for clarifying that.
[SPEAKER_03]: You haven't booked travel to San Francisco or New York anytime soon.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not for business.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't want spoilers either.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will agree with you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Kirsten Dunst
[SPEAKER_03]: It was good.
[SPEAKER_03]: It wasn't great.
[SPEAKER_03]: I loved Kirsten Dunst.
[SPEAKER_03]: Shut your mouth.
[SPEAKER_08]: I kept wishing so hard that Mary Jane would die, and then why was Gwen in the movie at all?
[SPEAKER_08]: She served no point.
[SPEAKER_08]: She was there to piss off Mary Jane, and I personally like seeing Mary Jane pissed off.
[SPEAKER_02]: Emo Boy.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love Kirsten Dunst.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did you never see, like, Drop Dead Gorgeous or The Virgin Suicides or Interview with a Vampire?
[SPEAKER_03]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_04]: Granted, things changed, obviously, in the movie and stuff, but I laughed because I never really was into the comics for Spider-Man, but I laughed when they were talking.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, this is how nerdy I am.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was watching a Science of Spider-Man 3, like, these people were debating on how this actually could happen, but they were talking about how Gwen Stacy died in the comics or whatever, how her neck snapped, remember, because in the first movie, you know, it was actually MJ and stuff, and he caught her and saved the gondola and stuff, but, um, I was really hoping they would kill MJ that way.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, please, spoiler free.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's been out for years now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Screw you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought you guys were talking about the third movie.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I was talking about the first movie.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, my bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I was just saying I was hoping that her neck would snap in, you know, this movie.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll see it at some point.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just, again, I'm waiting for the teenagers to go away.
[SPEAKER_03]: So.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anything else, DMN?
[SPEAKER_03]: Did you play any games this week?
[SPEAKER_02]: Kevin the Groove will be our third host this week, so don't miss it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, any actual games you've been playing this week?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it's been a rough week, so I haven't really gotten a chance to play any games.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, well, then I expect a phone call next week with a full report.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Take care, DMN.
[SPEAKER_03]: Later.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you don't want to move to San Francisco anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: The traffic sucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: And I've used that 80 to 880 interchange quite a few times because I've gone to South Bay, you know, like Hayward and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have friends in Hayward.
[SPEAKER_03]: But that's about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've never used that one that actually collapsed because that's how you get from SF to Oakwood.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is where Super Mario Kart technology would come in handy because all you have to do is put one of those boost panel downs and a little, you know, a little jump there and boom, you're done.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can clear that gap, no problem.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, Loki, you kill me.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, well, that's about going to do it here for another episode of Orange Lounge Radio, but not before I ask for any last-minute stories.
[SPEAKER_03]: But of course!
[SPEAKER_04]: There's some interesting stuff coming out of San Francisco today, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: The play First Person Shooter has premiered tonight, and it's kind of going into a story we talked about a little bit earlier about how people are blaming...
[SPEAKER_04]: Video games for school shootings and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's kind of their commentary on that.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it should be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like I want to see that play because it's really not that far away, but at the same time I don't.
[SPEAKER_03]: Does that make sense?
[SPEAKER_03]: I feel like it's like, so what?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a play about video games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Big deal.
[SPEAKER_03]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just something for the bloggers to write about.
[SPEAKER_04]: And talk about in the realm of ridiculous, but the way things are going, who knows.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently there's been some investigation.
[SPEAKER_04]: Two Belgium papers were reporting that police were investigating a virtual rape that happened in Second Life.
[SPEAKER_04]: Where else?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, basically... Insert joke here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do I even have to try tonight?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean... Goddamn, you Second Life fans are getting shit on tonight's show.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm so sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_13]: Obviously he can't get any in his first life.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it begs the point, Regina Lynn over at Wired said, psychologically, the upheaval of virtual rape isn't anywhere near the trauma of real rape, and I can't see us making virtual rape a matter for the real life police.
[SPEAKER_04]: Personally, if it were me and someone said, yeah, this guy just raped me in my video game, I'd probably hang up on them.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'd be like, I don't give a shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why are you wasting my time?
[SPEAKER_04]: We're coming down to rescue you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just got raped in a video game.
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: If they start treating this shit as real, it's just like the whole taxing people on virtual commerce.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or that kid who got taken away for making the map of his school.
[SPEAKER_04]: People.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not real.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a fucking video game.
[SPEAKER_04]: They make money in the video game.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can't tax them on that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or if you're going to tax them, it has to be on game money.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not real money.
[SPEAKER_04]: And no, you shouldn't be able to tax them on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on a little bit here, DDR, coming to schools in Scotland.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that should be pretty cool, seeing that it's catching on in other places.
[SPEAKER_04]: For the Simpsons video game, they have a counter now, counting down the video game's release or release info on the launch.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have a mock site that's making fun of Grand Theft Auto 4, so that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: It says 22 on there.
[SPEAKER_04]: And let's see, what else we've got here?
[SPEAKER_04]: The people behind the wonderful game Puzzle Quest are actually making a new space-themed game called Galactrix.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm talking a little bit about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it looks pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're trying to make sure it's not just a Puzzle Quest clone.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's it, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anything from you, Miss DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: One time, I fed my snakes some beer.
[SPEAKER_03]: It cleared this way and that.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was all fucked up!
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for taking the IQ level of our show down a couple notches.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's always good to be humbled like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was going to talk about some stupid rumors that I read.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, this was funny, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember they banned some sort of theme on Xbox Live?
[SPEAKER_04]: The sexy girl theme or something like that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sexy girl theme.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if it's sexy girl, but yeah, it's some girl...
[SPEAKER_04]: Weird Girls You'll Never Have theme.
[SPEAKER_04]: Something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought that was funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: That and how people are saying that the next PlayStation model is coming out in 18 months.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Never going to happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's go around and get everybody's final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_03]: Drew, Nami, thanks so much for being here again.
[SPEAKER_03]: We appreciate you.
[SPEAKER_03]: You've been missing a little while.
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh, yeah, I've been doing some entertaining in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, I apologize, uh, we were actually originally, we were thinking about doing a match game tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mikulatov was trying to, he said he'd stay for the show if he could, we would do a match game tonight, but then we just did a match game like, you know, three episodes ago, so, uh, we're holding off on match game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Will you come back for maybe the next match game or next dumb little game we play here in studio?
[SPEAKER_03]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, Loki!
[SPEAKER_03]: Your final, oh wait, did I give you your final thought?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry, Duguru.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want pie.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_04]: Super Mario, or Super Paper Mario, I was going to say Super Mario RPG It's actually pretty cool, a little easy right now, but I'm only on the third level But I like it, it's growing on me I like there is a funny part, and it's kind of a spoiler a little bit, but in one of the third levels There's a power-up you can get that turns you into a giant version of 8-bit Mario Or whatever, and so you can go smash through stuff
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamboroo Boran
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't shoot fire in my face anymore.
[SPEAKER_03]: Please fucking ride.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tired.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want pie.
[SPEAKER_08]: It has no sugar.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you guys for listening to and supporting independent podcasting.
[SPEAKER_03]: You guys are awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: We really appreciate it if you tell two people you know about our program because that will help us dominate the world very slowly.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you tell two people.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, if you don't have any friends or anybody to tell, leave us a kind review on iTunes or on Podcast Alley, Yahoo, one of those sites where you promote.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll see you back here next week, and we'll see you in about three weeks at Faname 2007.
[SPEAKER_03]: Until then, my name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we're out of here until next week.
[SPEAKER_00]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_00]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_00]: For more information on our live and podcast programs, visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com See you next week!