Orange Lounge Radio
There's your hosts, DarkSakura, Sky, and Loko
Tonight, May 20th, 2007, Blizzard officially announces Starcraft 2
Halo 3 gets an official release date
Project Gotham 3 is mistaken for a Sony game once again
Orange Lounge Radio
I don't have to go to work tomorrow
And I didn't go Thursday or Friday
I was supposed to go to a wedding and we decided not to go
So I went and did nerdy stuff yesterday
And slept a lot
I had time off set to go on vacation to L.A.
Actually, I think I was supposed to go to Disneyland
But this was a couple of years ago
This was before Disneyland was the cool thing to do between us
And for some reason or other the trip got cancelled
We didn't end up going
But I just kept the time off of work
And that was the same week that Final Fantasy XI came out
Oh God
I remember that
I sat at home and played Final Fantasy XI for like four days straight
Early days of your addiction
Oh, it was horrendous
Just looking back on that
I did that when Final Fantasy VI came out
Well, three over here came out
When I was in high school
And I stayed home with the flu
I had a fever
And it needed more Final Fantasy
I have a fever
And the only cure is more treasure hunters
I hate, hate, hate, hate, hate, hate the flu
I need cure three
Alright, anyway
Uh, Loki, Techmaster Loki is here as well
Yes, I am
Have you ever called in sick or used your vacation to play a video game?
Yes
What was that?
I don't remember
But you remember taking the time off to play it?
Uh, yes
Alright
You don't remember what it was, but you took off
I think I may have done it for San Andreas
Oh, okay
Maybe
Alright, you gonna do it for Grand Theft Auto IV?
No, because we'll be playing it at work
So it's not a big deal
You know a lot of people were pissed off
Because there were a lot of people that took the day off for the Halo 3 beta
And we're gonna talk more Halo 3 probably in part B tonight
But you know the Halo 3 beta came out
And a lot of people called in sick to work that day
Because they were gonna sit at home and play the Halo 3 beta
And then the damn thing didn't show up for like 13 hours
And people were pissed
You know, because they'd taken the time off work
But it's hard
I know it's hard to get upset when it's like, you know, kind of free
And they never promised it on a certain day to begin with really
You know, it's kind of one of those tricky situations
I don't know
But I thought that was interesting
So anyway
Alright, so we're gonna get into some gaming news tonight
But first we're gonna start it off with a little bit of
How was your gaming week?
No special guests tonight, but we do have the chat room
chat.orangelaungeradio.com
Harvey's here, Rob
Look at what?
Harvey
Who's Harvey?
Did you see the movie?
No
Invisible Rabbit?
It was a Jimmy Stewart movie
Oh, what's, no, a little
The Wonder Hamster?
No
You need to watch some classic movies every so often, Rob
Once in a while I do
Broaden Your Horizons
I do, I've seen like Casablanca
And the Wizard of Oz is one of my favorite movies ever
I'm going to find the DVD of Harvey and buy it for you
And you're gonna watch it
And Hitchcock, I love old Hitchcock movies like Psycho
Casablanca is so like, you know, the simple life
It's just like
Oh my god, there's this war going on
Why is that the inconvenience me?
Wow, my headache just came back
Good job
Alright
I just swallowed like five Excedrin
I'm looking at our chat room right now to see what's going on
Of course we do tape live on Sunday nights
And then release this to our audio RSS feed is the technical name for it
But most people just call it a podcast or a blog cast or whatever
Let's see, anyway, look in the chat room, what's going on
Gaming week
Huh?
Yeah, we'll get to that
Can't we say hello to the chatters real quick?
No
Alright, well
ActDeaf says I hope OLR cheers me up
Well, not with Jamie's current attitude
Hi
She won't be
She happy, dammit
She won't be cheering anybody up there
Be of good cheer or I'll kick your ass
Let's see, PK, I'm sorry, I always say his name wrong
Peaker Uno, I think is how I'm supposed to say it
Says we need to have an OLR me we suck at Halo game
Yes, we do
GS68 said Rob floods go faster at night
I guess in response to chat going Rob, Rob, Rob
You know Sauce was at Disneyland Friday
Lucky
No, and she said they closed down Pirates for the premiere and then they opened it back
up
Oh, the Pirates premiere was going on, that's cool, fun
Alright, we're not a Disneyland podcast, so tell us about your gaming week
Well, I played something like seven hours of, no not seven, because I took a break
I played a lot of Marvel Ultimate Alliance because I had to start over because there
were fingerprints on the rental
We get free rentals from Hollywood Video, so I just played a whole bunch
And I was very pissed off because I played Iron Man on the Mandarin stage
Only I used the Ultimate Armor because it looks a lot better than his dorky, you know, asshole armor
Sorry, I've been reading, I read a lot of comics
And so there wasn't any of the dialogue and I was like, well this is crap
And so I just went back to playing a whole lot of Deadpool because he's funny
And god damn stupid computer
You know, I had my computer on Power Saver because I was moving files anyway
So I also went to Pen-a-Go-Go
Which was this, I want to say it was big, but it really wasn't
It was like in a warehouse in Dixon
Well, actually the big, you know, hall at the Dixon Fairgrounds
For our international listeners, how can we describe Dixon, California?
Podunk
It's like going to the country
It's the suburb of a suburb, right?
You have like this old town and then you drive like five minutes and you have farm
Like Davis is a suburb of Sacramento, right?
Where the school is, where the first season of sorority life was, right?
So most people know UC Davis
Well Dixon is a suburb of Davis, okay?
So that's, to put it in perspective, like it's not even as populated
I apologize if we have any listeners in Dixon
I do love Mary's Pizza Shack, which is in Dixon, but that's about it
I went to this sweet stuff place, I think it was called
And it was really yummy and I had banana ice cream
Anyway, sorry, Pen-a-Go-Go, pinball
Okay, yeah, I'm actually pulling up the list of the games I played at Pen-a-Go-Go
And this isn't all of them because I did play a bunch of really old, old, old machines
Like the ones from before
Like, these are so old that they had the flippy numbers, you know?
Where instead of, you know, you have your LED screen, you had the flippy numbers
Wow, like the counters
And there was only one of those that was worth mentioning, which is called Skylab
And the cool thing about Skylab is that you have this middle section
That's got a line in between them
And you have five pinballs in there
And you have to knock five onto one side of it
And then you get like some special thing, only I couldn't do it
So I played Black Rose, which is a pirate theme with this huge, you know, big old pirate winch on the thing
And it has cannons in it and you have to like shoot down a pirate ship
Cool, pirate winches
And Centaur, which was a cool older table
It was before they had the big, you know, LED, the big display, digital displays and everything
And it was just the numbers and all that
And I played the new Pirates of the Caribbean machine, which is actually okay
But it wasn't quite as awesome as I thought it would be
And I kicked Dan's ass at Theatre of Magic twice
I love Theatre of Magic, that's a kickass table
Theatre of Magic is the most sexy pinball table
I was about ready to offer the dude four thousand bucks on
I was like, hello, my retirement money, give me Theatre of Magic
But no, I had to use it on school
But he did win, though, on the third game
But that's okay because I also kicked his ass at Adam's Family
God, I wonder where I could find four thousand dollars to buy a Theatre of Magic table
It's so tempting
Apparently it's one of Dan's buddies that owns the machine
I played Demolition Man and I thought it would be a great machine because I love ramps
No, suck-tastic
Much like the movie
Actually, I like the movie
Demolition Man is one of my guilty pleasures
Kind of like Me and Showgirls?
Yeah
Okay, yeah, gotcha
Just because I love the whole scene when they're in the car scene to old Oscar Mayer commercials
You know who really brought down that movie?
Who?
Sandra Bullock
It ruins everything
It's like poison
Everything she touches is poison
The speed was good, the first one
It had Denis Leary in it, though
Denis Leary is the reason to watch Demolition Man
Sorry to interrupt your report, but I have to ask Loki, do you have any guilty pleasure movies?
Guilty pleasure movies?
I guess Wild Zero, maybe
Dude, I love that movie, too
But there's that one
I have a new one, though, possibly
I have to watch it, though
Yo Yo Girl Cop
Oh, wait, is that the Sukebon Deca?
No, that was not a cop
It's the one about this Asian chick who fights crime
She's like a cop by day, crime fighter by night, which is kind of the same thing
But anyways, she fights crime with this metal yo-yo
Well, the yo-yo started off as a weapon
That's amazing
So, it's interesting
Okay, well, there's more games
I played Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles, which is the worst machine ever
It's like it has action figures all over it
And the only cool thing about it is this rotating pizza spinner in the middle that will shoot the ball in different directions
I played Medieval Madness, but the guy who owned it put extra steep ramps in it
But I did break down the castle, that was cool
Pinbot
Fucking greatest pinball game of ever
No
Ever
But it was dingy
Actually, you need to come to my house and play Bride of Pinbot
Bride of Pinbot is actually better
I forgot you have Bride of Pinbot now
Yes, well, it's not technically ours, it's our friend Will's
But it lives in my apartment, my garage
Suddenly we're becoming a pinball podcast, but that's okay
Okay
Pinball is what I played before DDR, which is how I met all you guys
So, this is like going back to our roots
There's a few more worth mentioning
I played Hyperball
Hyperball is the worst pinball ever
Well, not really worst, it's the weirdest
Because you have this big open field and little holes around the perimeter of the thing
And you have to shoot the balls into the holes and they're like by the alphabet and it's really stupid
I played High Speed, which is one of the older ones
That was really fun
And Cyclone
High Speed was the other NES game that fucking no one played
They had Pinbot, and then Pinbot was so successful they made High Speed
But nobody played High Speed
But High Speed is a fucking awesome table
It is an awesome, that's why they made it a game
But Cyclone has, um
Now, Cyclone, it was one of the ones I used to play in Mobile at a Godfather's Pizza
And the marquee of it has a clown on it and this rollercoaster
And in the first row is Ronald Reagan and Nancy Reagan
But on the one in Mobile, someone duct taped over the clown because clowns are scary
And drew a beard with a big mustache and a cowboy hat on Ronald Reagan
So, that's always my memory of it
It's a cool table, I just hate clowns
There should be a pinball game where you just hit clowns in the face
That'd be fun
The biggest disappointment for me, well there's Fun House
Fun House is one where you can hit this
That's right!
I hate Fun House though, we almost bought one and I told Dan no because the freaking head scared the crap out of me
But the disappointment though is I wanted to see World Cup Soccer and apparently they sold it on Friday and I went on Saturday
Big Bang Bar, no one had any prototypes there
And Big Bang Bar is like, I've gotten to play a Big Bang Bar
That's the one where there's only like 20 of them in existence
And when Capcom closed down their pinball division
However, the rights to Big Bang Bar have now been made available
I think to Stern I think is going to be released
Don't quote me on that yet
But I think Stern's going to be releasing them
Time Machine is the other one I wanted to see
Jackbot, Black Knight 2000 and Doctor Who of course were the big ones that I wanted to see
Other than that, I've been playing stupid Flash games thanks to Loki
Sorry
That's okay, they're kind of addicting
I'm going to be doing that all day tomorrow now
Yeah, I was playing Flash games too
So what were you playing?
I played, actually, I played Crackdown
A little bit of co-op Crackdown, that was fun
I did try the Halo 3 beta once
It was okay
To be honest, it's exactly like the last Halo game
Gameplay-wise, they haven't really changed much
Which is fine, it was good to begin with
But I still really suck at Halo
I had trouble
The only thing I kind of regret is the loading screens
In some games, they usually show you what the button configuration is
I went in there and was like, how do I do stuff?
I had to kind of figure that out
And they still didn't really get the hang of it
Instead they have the message that says
Halo 3 Beta, love Bungie
I thought that was funny
So that was okay
I went back to playing Earth Defense Force 2017 again
And I got the fucking super awesome stationary guns
I'm going to be able to blow through Inferno difficulty now
Like, no problem
But those are cool
And then, what else did I play?
Oh yeah, I tried a little bit of that
What was it, Geasswing or whatever?
It was okay
Very bland, actually
The graphics in it were very kind of, ugh
Like I threw this together really quick
Dude, it was free
I don't care, I've seen better shit that's been free, okay?
You know
Warning Forever, that's free
And that looked a lot better
And there wasn't even any background on that
So
They should, simple, you know
They should have done all
Vectors would have been cool
Anyways
So, then beyond that stuff
I played a little bit of
Well, of course, Grand Theft Auto Vice City Stories
Still playing that
I'll still be playing that
Until, you know, Grand Theft Auto 4 comes out
I tried a little bit of Saints Row
That was fun
For some reason though, like
I really, I don't know if anyone has actually tried landing 360 systems
They are as finicky as shit
They will not land with each other if like something's different or whatever
Like Saints Row, we were trying to land it
One of the systems doesn't have the update for it yet
The multiplayer update that fixes the lag
One system does
It won't see each other
So that kind of sucked
Cracked down, we tried landing it again
And it won't see each other
Despite the fact that it's the exact same setup
And it worked the other day
So I don't know what the fuck's wrong with these things
But all I know is Microsoft did not make it fucking easy to land this shit
So
Fuck them
That's it
Alright, well, my gaming week
I also played the Halo 3 beta
And, you know, it's pretty cool
To me, my first, my initial impression was like
Okay, it's like Halo 2
Is prettier and with, you know, the shield
And other new X button features, right
That change up the game a little bit
But then I'm kind of thinking like
Okay, well Halo 2 is a pretty rock solid game
That people still play online
Like over and over and over again
Until their thumbs fall off
So if it ain't broke, don't fix it, right?
So I think, honestly, Halo 3 is going to be pretty cool
Now there were, like, I found the beta to be a bit confusing at first
Because I was trying to set up a game that would just be my friends and I
And like I couldn't, like, we could only like
Get the friends together to join other games
But I guess you can't really be picky choosy
Because it is a beta
They're probably trying to stress the stress
Yeah, it's probably what I meant
So I'm not going to complain about that
I was just like
Aw, darn, I wish I could have done it this way
But I did find that if I don't play ranked mode
If I just stay away from ranked mode
And play, like, the open mode
Generally you get people of a lower skill rank
Which is good, it's better for me to play on
So I played a couple games and it was a good time
Like the training stuff, or?
Yeah, I played, a random O.L.R. listener came in too
And I'm sorry, dude, I forgot your name
But somebody that was no O.L.R. listener
Came onto my friends list
We played a Halo 3 match together
We had a good time
I actually got more kills than him
So I was all, he's like
What do you mean you suck at Halo?
So I was all excited, but it was just luck
And sometimes it's just luck
Especially when nobody knows the maps
Because they're all new
But I thought it was really pretty
I like that map where you play in the snow
It was kind of neat looking
And the shields look pretty cool
Like, you know, it's kind of cool
The game's going to sell like crazy
It's going to be Halo 2 all over again
But just a whole new thing
It's going to be huge
I mean, I wish I wasn't so ignorant
When it comes to first person shooters
Because a lot of them feel all the same to me
Because I don't play a whole lot of them
Like, I've played Quake 3
And some of the other Quakes
And, you know, a couple here and there
But, you know, Halo's just always kind of stood out
I hope it has a great single player, though, too
For those that don't necessarily like to
Go online and play random people
But I can't wait to have the college buddies
And I play in the game
It's going to be fun
Yeah
Let's see, other games I've been playing this week
I've actually went back to my PlayStation 2
And picked up a game that I played a lot of
When it first came out
But then they just kind of stopped
And neglected it when the Wii came out
And that would be Final Fantasy XII
And what motivated me to play this game again
Is you might remember last week
I had a bit of an emo week
And Miklotov was here
And he talked about how he bought me the Balthier doll
Who is, like, the reason to play Final Fantasy XII
Because not only is he sexy
But he's just, like, the most interesting character in the game, right?
He's awesome
So, yeah, I decided to go back to Final Fantasy XII
Because I want to play it through to completion
But I'm kind of one of those people that's like
If I forget what happened in the story
And it's been, like, you know, a good five months
Since I've touched the game
I have to go back and start from the beginning
So I started back from the beginning
But, God, the battle system in that game is great
I mean, it's like playing an online game
But not online
Like, where you get total control over all the other people
It's great
I forgot there's a few other things I did play
I played Eternal Sonata
Which they have the demo for
That demo is amazing
I loved it
Did you like it?
Yeah, it was pretty awesome
It's awesome
Oh my God
The Xbox 360 needs a game like Eternal Sonata
So bad
It's one of the types of games that Microsoft has been lacking in
Ever since, like, Xbox One
And, yes, I know there was, like, Enchanted Arms
But, seriously, this is like a great role-playing game
It looks to be shaping up to be one
I was so impressed with the demo
To me, this is how Square Enix should be doing their Final Fantasy games
I don't know how Final Fantasy XIII is going to be
It looks a little weird
But, you know, this is the way I would see them doing it
Stick to what you know, you know, like Final Fantasy X was okay
And XII was okay
But just, you know, that same type of thing
You don't need to go all full 3D where you can adjust the camera and stuff
Yeah, I know
XII's cool, though
But I'm excited to see what they do for XIII
But the battle system in Eternal Sonata is pretty awesome
Because it's like, you know, you're on a live playing field
And you run around, like, a la Kingdom Hearts
You have, like, five seconds
Yeah, but you have five seconds from the second you touch the controller to move
And you make all your moves
And I thought it was just pretty cool
Jamie, you really should check this game out, Eternal Sonata
You have to have a Japanese account to download the demo
Or you should just come over here and play it or something
It's great
It's like a Japanese RPG
Okay
But on the 360
So it's really nice looking
I thought the graphics were great, too
And the weirdest thing about the Japanese demo
Is it wasn't the Japanese demo
It was the US demo
Because it's Eternal Sonata
It's Trusty Bell over there
And it's all in English
I'm not complaining
So I don't understand why they put it over there
But the other thing I played, of course
I totally hopped on your account and grabbed it
Good, because that's
Yeah, yeah
Love that update, Microsoft
Really blocked those other accounts out there
Well, anyways
But I did get to play some more Super Paper Mario
I'm almost finished with it now
But it's fun
Still liking it
I also finally picked up Catan
The Xbox Live Arcade game
Wasn't feeling it
I mean, like, I'm very happy these types of games are coming to Xbox Live Arcade
But this particular one, I just couldn't get into
They need risks
Yeah, I want something I'm a little more familiar with
Monopoly, Risk, Clue
Oh my god, Monopoly with pillars
I understand this game is huge among strategy circles
And I'm probably getting angry emails from some British listeners right now
Where the game is big
But, you know, I just
I wasn't all into, like, the trade, barter, that kind of thing
Although I guess Monopoly is kind of like that, too
But I don't know, it's different
Trust me
I guess maybe I was just disappointed
Because somebody told me
Oh, you should play Catan
It's like Civilization
It's nothing like Civilization
To be honest, Civilization is incredible
What was I going to say?
Eternal Sonata actually looks better than Blue Dragon
You know, sadly enough
And then really quickly
Because I know we want to get into some gaming news
I won't take up the whole time here
But I downloaded some retro classics
I downloaded Double Dragon
I downloaded Centipede
I actually paid for them
I don't know why I keep dumping all this money into them
I mean, the remakes aren't bad
But it's just, you know, I play them once
And I hardly ever play them again
So I really need to just play the demo and be happy with that
But I do like the high def graphics on Double Dragon
And it was somebody other than Digital Eclipse porting it
So I was excited
I laughed at that
You didn't like it?
It just didn't seem...
I mean, it was okay
It was kind of cool
It just didn't quite seem right
Yeah, it is a little weird at first
Like, I don't know if you played the Centipede one
But they really changed that one
They totally made that, like, HD
They didn't just, like, I don't know
Put the old school graphics in 720p
They kind of redid the graphics there
It's kind of interesting
But I don't know
I'm a sucker for classics and all the retro stuff
So what can I say
And that's why I actually kind of enjoyed Aegiswing
I guess, I don't know how to pronounce it
Aegiswing I think is what it is
Aegis, yeah
Aegis
It's free
The multiplayer stuff is cool
It's a good old
It's just like a Gradius type shooter
It's like a throwback to 8-bit shooters
I thought it was gonna be more frantic though
Like, more, you know, crazy Japanese shooter
Like Ikaruga or something
But that's okay
I mean, I like, you know, I can't complain
It's free
I would put it on par with Heavy Weapon, honestly
And I paid 10 bucks for that one
Yeah
I thought Aegiswing was pretty fun
Stupid Heavy Weapon
I liked Heavy Weapon
It wasn't bad
It was certainly one of the better
Probably the best PopCap game on Xbox right now
Is Heavy Weapon
Anyway
So that's it
I'll shut up about my gaming week now
Let's talk about some housekeeping
No live show next Sunday
This is important
Sorry live listeners
We love you guys
But there will be no live show Memorial Day weekend
That's Sunday, May 27th
Because we will be taping that week's show
Live at FanaMe
We're gonna be at FanaMe
And we'll be there taping our show live
On Saturday, the 26th
That's May 26th
We'll be there
I don't know what panel room it is yet though
I missed that little detail
Zero
Or whatever
Not on stage zero
We report to stage zero
To find out where we're gonna be
Yeah
So we're gonna be somewhere
Look in your programs
We're gonna be there two o'clock
Probably
I wouldn't see why they wouldn't
Last year there was like a big room and two small rooms
And we were in the big room
So I don't know why we wouldn't be in the big room again
I hope
We'll see
If not we'll just have to fill all the butts in the seats in the little room
It'll be fun
So it'll be 2 p.m. on Saturday at FanaMe in San Jose
Hopefully we'll be at the same time as the Masquerade
No
We got a better time this year I think
Because last year we were like the same time as the Masquerade
And that really screwed our attendance numbers
We had only a handful of people
We love those of you that came and showed up anyway
Even though we were at the same time as that
But this year we're like at two o'clock
And I don't think there's a whole lot going on then
It's like right during the high traffic point of the day
So I'm really excited
I think we got a good time
I'm excited to talk video games
We're gonna do Ask Orange Lounge live
We have a lot to cram in an hour
So we're gonna do that 2 p.m. on Saturday
F-A-N-I-M-E dot com
If you want more information if you'll be in the San Jose area
So again that means no live show Sunday
If you do happen to be here Sunday night
You will hear the premiere of that episode
We will have that edited and ready to play
At our usual 6 p.m. time on Sunday
So that'll be your first chance to hear it
Just won't have that live interaction element with the chat room
Instead it's live in person
So that was fun last year
I'm looking forward to that this year
It'll be amazing
Are you cosplaying this year, yes?
If I can get my costume sewn this week
I wanted to do Balthier so bad
But it's just too complicated a costume
I can't do it in time
Don't buy any sort of 3D
Yeah, so
I don't know
Maybe I'll
I think maybe I'll just wear a shirt
That says this is my cosplay or something
Does that sound like a good idea?
You're not going to cosplay either, right?
No, I am not cosplaying
Alright, so yeah, no show Sunday
So we'll be back here live
Though I believe the date is June 3rd
We'll be here live
And that's that
So let's go into some gaming news
Roll that beautiful bean footage
Of course the big, big, big, big, big, big news this weekend
Is that Starcraft 2 was officially announced
Blizzard officially rolled out the teaser trailer
For Starcraft 2 in Seoul, South Korea
And of course Korea is a huge
I mean just a huge place where
Starcraft is still popular
It's been 10 years since the original game if you can believe it
And of course there was much speculation leading up to this
And Starcraft 2 was one of the things people speculated they would announce
People thought it was going to be World of Starcraft
Diablo 3, a new IP, or this
So you know
It was never going to be World of Starcraft
Oh, why is that?
They're not going to compete with themselves
Not going to compete with themselves
But then again, Starcraft 2 is going to be online
We know this, right?
Both, so
Comprehensive website set up at starcraft2.com
You can look at some of the clip art from the game
And some of the stages in action
You can look at the teaser trailer
Which you know, doesn't really show a lot of the game in action
But they do have on the site, they have another trailer that you can look at
Which does have some of the in-game footage
No word yet when the game will be released
It is going to be a PC release
They are not touching the console releases
Their FAQs kind of made it very vague if they would ever go to consoles
But just kind of knowing Blizzard's history
They probably won't, at least for a long time
So Starcraft 2 coming to PC soon-ish
Because they haven't said when
It could be Christmas, it could be next year
Soon is the ultimate answer
I would say next summer would be my bet
I would say like next April
The game looks very complete-ish though
And they had demos and stuff going
Christmas seems a little soon though
Especially when you consider all these games have been getting delayed lately
Like Spore and stuff
I don't know
Well Spore is pretty massive as far as what's involved with that
True
I don't know
Sooner or better
Let's see, Nm64 in our chat room says
Starcraft 2 will come out when it's done
GS68 follows up with Starcraft forever
Jvmon says
Starcraft 2 gets released
Thousands of babies die inside hot cars in South Korea
That's sad
Chainsaw Juggling says
I think Starcraft 2 is being funded by North Korea
So they can invade South Korea because everyone will be playing the game
I'd like to know what our Korean listeners think about that comment
You can address those cards and letters to Chainsaw Juggling
On behalf of Mailbag at OrangeLaunchRadio.com
Starcraft 2, you guys excited? I don't know if you guys play these types of games
No, absolutely not because I really don't care
You don't play RTSs at all?
I don't play Starcraft
You know what's weird?
Starcraft is the one Blizzard game I've never played
I played World of Warcraft a lot, but I never
I kind of avoided Starcraft
I know, I lose total gamer cred in saying that, don't I?
But face it, guys, there's only so many hours in the day to play games
But I'll check it out, certainly, for nothing else
And the fact that my current boyfriend's addicted to Starcraft
And I'll probably have to play it for his sake
I suppose Dan's probably gonna play it, so
Yeah, so we'll probably see it that way
It looks just like Command & Conquer, Tiberium Wars
I'm like
There's not really much you can do with the RTS
I mean, great, it'll have the Starcraft characters
And races and units and whatnot
Yeah, it is the same three races from the original Starcraft
Protos, Zerg, and Terrans
So, I mean, it'll be cool
I mean, it's great, it needs an update
It's been a while, so
I don't know, really, how much more excited could you have been
From Warcraft 1 to Warcraft 2?
I mean, it's like, eh, it's new stuff
Who's kind of the same game?
Kind of, yeah, exactly
But Warcraft 2 to Warcraft 3 was a huge change
That was a huge change
I don't know
Alright, forget it, forget it
Whatever, anyways
Now, coming, GameTap is really becoming
You know, the central
For, like, anything that's
You know, episodic
Or, you know, a bunch of
They're actually using it now to launch a bunch of new games
Including a new series from American McGee
Which, I don't know if you can be excited about it
He had a hit with, you know, Alice
Had a flop with Bad Day LA
As sad as I'd like to say that
But he is going to be coming out with a brand new
24-part episodic series
That's going to be Grimm
And it's based off the Grimm fairy tales
That sounds cool
In fact, they had some little artwork
Showing Pinocchio, so that's kind of neat
Is Hansel and Gretel in it?
Because I still want to push the witch in the oven
I'm sure it will be, but they didn't really specify
What series, you know, what stories are going to be in there
But, of course, they're all going to be kind of dark
And, you know, very Alice-like
And it says it's supposed to start in 2008
So, that's kind of neat
GameTap's becoming pretty awesome
I mean, it's already been, like, a pretty good service
And I know, God, you must think I'm on their payroll at this point
But I do think it's a really great deal
They're a good service
If something's quality, why not tell everyone, right?
Exactly
This type of stuff's only enhancing it
And I guess people are so resistant
Because they feel like they're paying for emulators
But, you know, these guys know what they're doing
They're really putting their all into it
So, a lot of folks probably would have given up by now
I like them
Well
Let's hope the game doesn't suck
Well, in some news of other things that don't suck
Since we've been on the Blizzard tangent for a little while
On the patch 2.1.0 for World of Warcraft
We will be getting Black Temple as an instance
For anyone who doesn't know
It was involved in the Outlands
Which was a zone that was added for Burning Crusade
So, you're gonna have to have, like, a huge ol' massive, you know, raid party
To be able to do it
But, there you go
There's also tweaking the
Some of the newer stuff in the Burning Crusade expansion
A new PvP arena
And epic flying mounts
The Nether Drake
Will be available with that patch
Except I won't be able to play that because I'm not a high enough level yet
But soon, I'm 51
Jewids are going to have their own epic flight form
Yes
It will be epic
And it will be like the warlock and paladin mount quests
Alright
So that's pretty cool
By the way, I forgot to say World of Warcraft during my gaming week
We're on a very aggressive recruiting campaign for our guild
We don't call ourselves OL Army
We have a different name just because we want to kind of blend in
We don't want to be an obvious radio promo
But if you want more information, please go to our forums
If you have, like, a dormant character
You're thinking about transferring
We totally want some non-dickhead people to play with
If someone would give me Burning Crusade, I'd play
I have not even touched the content for Burning Crusade at level 51
I just want to draw an eye
But that's the wrong side
I want a blood elf too
Maybe if you're nice
Somebody will bring that to you for, I don't know, solstice or something
Okay
Alright
I'll buy chocolate
I was going to say, um
I heard that a bunch of people from the old Deathcake guild finally
A bunch of people from the old Final Fantasy XI guild finally made the jump
Yeah, it's pretty cool
I will never, never jump into that
You need to
That's because of the wife
But here's the other thing I want to say
We posted a plug for our guild in the official server forums
And, like, within five minutes
Some twat responded with some negative comment to my post
You know, I'm like
God, I hate web forums sometimes
I hate twats
I hate the internet
Alright, anyway
Sorry
We can talk about other stuff now
Like this
Hey, before there was the WoW addiction
There was the music game addiction
Which a lot of us are still addicted to
And one of the granddaddies of the music game genre
Parappa the Rappa
Created by Masaya Matsura
He has talked about the Playstation 3 sluggish sales in Japan
And he's saying that's because the thing's a monster
It's a huge game
Or it's a huge system
He says, quote
It's not the size of the hardware
But of the AC adapter when talking about the Xbox 360
Who fuckin' who?
Isn't that crazy?
Get over it
My God
The AC adapter's too big
I can't develop for that system
Well, but here's the thing though
He doesn't talk about the Wii at all
Because he says, quote
The Wii is a, quote
Very good piece of hardware
And noting that the controls are pretty awesome
And he has said that he's going to be developing a game for the system
Quote
Soon
Maybe
My God
He jumps on the complete bandwagon
Like a whole fuckin' year and a half late
Oh, the AC adapter's too big
Get over it
Seriously
My God
It
So what if the brick is huge?
It does not matter
The Xbox was huge
I mean, come on
No one complained about that
The fact the size of the controllers originally were like
I don't know
Their own houses
It is a little weird
That is kind of a weird comment
But whatever
I mean, that's
Anyhow
That's how he feels
Bitch and moan, people
But
So
Yeah
Apparently, BMG's got the rights now to distribute economic music online
I know you'll be seeing that popping up in iTunes and Rhapsody
And other online distributors
But of course
You'll be seeing stuff from Castlevania
Maybe some DDR
Maybe Silent Hill
Okay
So
I don't really have any specific dates on the releases yet, but
It's coming
That's pretty cool
Well, something that's a bit of a relief for a lot of people is that
They're saying that Rock Band is going to be affordable
Not the $150 to $200 that people were, you know, thinking that it was going to be
But there hasn't been anything specifically said about pricing
But it was said that they don't see a point in making a game that people are not going to be happy buying
So
Hopefully
I don't know what their idea of reasonable is
It'll be expensive
I could swing $100 for a game, but $150 maybe not
Well, I mean, if it has good peripherals, maybe
Let me put it this way
Okay, it's EA putting it out
EA has, as far as like, you know, pricing goes
Their games are a little on the high end
Even to retailers
But it's going to be expensive
They're going to milk any sort of money that they could possibly get out of this
Alright
Well, that's of course a game we're looking forward to in the far future
That game's probably, what, a Christmas release looking at?
Probably November-ish?
Yeah, probably November
Alright
Okay, so we're going to be looking at some media releases we have
We're going to run down some release dates
And we'll start in Japan
Because of course a lot of the games that come out in Japan we end up seeing here
Starting off on the Xbox
Or sometimes it goes the other way around too
It takes a while for the games to get over there
It just depends what system you're talking about
Starting off on the Xbox 360
Forza Motorsport 2 is coming out on the 24th of May
As well as NBA Street Home Court
Those are some popular titles over on this side of the pond as well
Coming out on the Wii
A giant name here
One patchy slap pachinko blah blah blah
Sammy's collection Fist of the North Star Wii
So I guess it's what?
Fist of the North Star pachinko games coming out from Sega on the Wii
You would think that they accidentally ran like two names together
But no, I'm looking at the box art
And it really is Fist of the North Star pachinko games on your Wii
Pretty awesome
That's crazy
If you like pachinko and you like Fist of the North Star
Hey, this is the game for you
Going on to some other systems on the Playstation 3
You're also getting NBA Street Home Court
For those of you that import your games that want NBA Jam for whatever reason
NBA Jam, sorry, NBA Home Court
Big difference there
Playstation 2, Killer7 coming out on the Playstation 2 by Capcom in Japan
I'm surprised it's not out there already
Medal of Honor, well that's on the Playstation 2, not the GameCube
Maybe it just took a while
Medal of Honor Vanguard, Shadow of Rome and State of Emergency Revenge
All coming out on the Playstation 2
As well as the King of Fighters Maximum Impact 2
But that's just moving into the best collection
That was already out there in Japan
State of Emergency Revenge
That's what it's called
Coming out on the DS you have a crossword simulator from Hudson coming out on May 24th
As well as Hoshigami is coming out on May 24th
Lots of DS games coming out including an Olympic training game it looks like
What is this called? Sansu Olympic Inkai-Koan, Tsuji de Kiteru Noriyoku Training
What is that? It looks like Olympic Training or something
Or maybe some other type of brain training game
It's definitely what it looks like there
Brain Olympics Training
Maybe that's what it is, Brain Olympics or something like that
So all those games coming out in Japan
I'm looking to see if there's anything on the PSP real quick this week
Oh yes a new Bleach game, Bleach Heat the Soul 4
Just what we need, more Bleach
More Bleach
Oh and my favorite title name of the week is actually coming out on the Sony PSP
It's Juiced Eliminator
That's great
That's actually a racing game and I think it might be something they have over here
It's already out over here
Yeah, Juiced Eliminator
I have a t-shirt
It makes it sound like your PSP will slice and dice
I still want WTF
Not Julian, you know, Eliminator
Anyways, this week the big game coming out of course
Will be Pirates of the Caribbean at World's End
Where you get to play as the whole crew
Including Jack Sparrow, which is not voiced by Jenny Depp unfortunately
You also get, of course, on 360, WarTech Second Orundo
It's kind of interesting
It's like a shooter game, but it's all boss fights almost
It's just one-on-one fights
Halo 2 for Vista, so that's kind of neat
Odin Sphere, I know a lot of people were waiting for this one
That one's finally making its way out here on PlayStation 2
Dawn of Mana, that's finally coming out as well
Got delayed a week
About time
Naruto Ninja Council 3, that's going to be coming out on the DS
Brooktown, hi, senior year
Yay, that's economic game
Please God, or whatever force is up there in the great beyond
Listening to our crappy little radio program
Please, I have one small request for you
Please, please, please God, who I pray to every night
Who is so great and holy
Please do not let Dawn of Mana suck balls like Legend of Mana
Please, please, please, blessed be thy name, amen
Okay, anyways, also coming out this week on the DS
Death Junior and the Science Fair Doom
And let's see, Marvel Trading Card Games also coming out on the DS
And the New York Times Crosswords on the DS
Hooray
Well, we got a bunch of other stuff coming out in the UK
Odin Sphere comes out on PlayStation 2 the 22nd
On the 25th, a whole crap ton of stuff
There's Crush for PSP, Custom Robo Arena on DS
Halo 2 Vista for PC
Mario Strikers Charged Football
Metal Gear Solid Portable Ops
Hopefully with the warning intact, the rating
Monster Madness on PC and Xbox 360
Naruto Uzumaki Chronicles 2
SpongeBob and Friends blah blah blah
Pirates of the Caribbean on multiple systems
And Valhalla Knights on PSP
I want to mention something real quick
I just happened to catch this on Kotaku
It happened to do with pirates
But if you happen to be going towards Disneyland anytime soon
And you have a copy of Pirates of the Caribbean at World's End for the DS
There are specially marked spots on the rides
Or near the attractions that if you have your DS copy there
It will actually download exclusive content for you for the games
I need to get the game and take it to Disneyland
That's kind of neat
That's actually a really neat kind of tie-in
I have to give them props for that
It's a little crazy, but I like that idea
Too bad it wasn't for a game I would play a lot more
But that's kind of cool
Wow, that's kind of smart, I like that
I'm looking at Chatroom here
And somebody was responding to my little prayer there
Unfortunately they have the generic O.L. Army recruit name
But O.L. Army recruit number 9148 says
Donamana does suck
Uh oh, we're in for trouble there
What can we do there?
Let's see, some of the folks talking about Halo 2
Let's see, some folks are saying here
Act Def says Critics on Halo 2 Vista, it stinks
Rama says the Critics don't know shit
Mind you these are the same Critics that talked shit about XP when it came out
So there you have
Or it could be The Critic because
The Critic also used to say it stinks
It stinks
Alright, there we go
So anyhow, moving on to other news
Going to Sony, we're on DS now
We're going to go over to Sony
Warhawk, what the hell is going on with Warhawk?
At the latest press event apparently
Warhawk is going to be back on Blu-ray now
There is going to be a Blu-ray disc version of Warhawk
After all, it's going to have extra materials
Developer interviews, behind the scenes footage
And a Bluetooth headset
But the weird thing is, there still is going to be a PlayStation Network version of the game
Yes
So that's kind of funky
But don't worry though, it's not that
It's only going to be like 40 bucks
Oh okay, well that's not so bad then
Yeah
Because the online one will probably be 20 or 30 anyway
Because they can kind of charge that
Yeah, like 25 bucks or something
So you get all this extra stuff
Well that's kind of interesting, that's an interesting way to do it
There's going to be a public beta of the game starting on May 24th
And if you want to sign up, you just have to head on over to the official site
warhawk.com
Already signed up, so I haven't been contacted though
Some good reviews of the game coming out of Sony Gamer's Day though
So we'll see
It'll be interesting to see what happens there
PlayStation 3 could use all these types of games
They need some good news very badly right now
And this is good
Again, I'm not trying to pick on Sony or anything
I'm a fan of all three of the gaming companies
But let's face it, Sony's kind of doing an uphill battle right now
So this is good, I'm glad
They need to kick it up a notch
Kick it up a notch
For their download content
I mean seriously, it hasn't really been that much on there
RawSteelUT in the chat room is dogging the game
Warhawk looks like a generic Battlefield clone
$40 for a game with no SP mode, fuck that
True, I'm not buying it, but you know, it's interesting
Anyways, if you like Warhawk and those online multiplayer only games
Guess what? SOCOM Confrontation is going to be coming out for the PlayStation 3
It's going to be an online only multiplayer game
And yeah, it's pretty much more Deathmatch and Captured Flag and all that fun stuff
But it's SOCOM and it looks pretty so
There you go
It will support I believe up to 32 players online
And yeah, it's just going to be
It's going to be very interesting
However, if you're not really into the multiplayer only SOCOM for PlayStation 3
There will be a single player game coming out later on
That will have online elements as well
So
I've never really gotten into this series
What is this all about?
It's just, you know, it's kind of like Ghost Recon
But, you know, sewing his own thing
It's, you know, Navy Seals military type first person shooter game
Before we get to the next story real quick
I just kind of want to pose this question
Because we kind of talked a little bit before
And I want to open this up to the chat as well
What kinds of stuff does Sony need right now?
Because we obviously have their Gamers' Day event
We have more news coming out of their Gamers' Day event
What sorts of announcements does Sony need to be making right now?
Or are they on the right track?
They need more releases
More content on their online service
If they can't do new games
Put out some demos or something
Or maybe some more, something that makes it interesting
Because right now they don't really have anything to download
It's been like one release a month
And it's been really slow
They need some more exclusives for sure
Because right now they're hurting
I mean, and I'm talking first party stuff
Not necessarily third party exclusives
They need more
Microsoft's kicking their ass as far as, you know, exclusives go
They've got at least one new exclusive every month
You know, one or two
And it's kind of hurting them
Because it's like, well, you know
There'll be a game that comes out on the 360
And then later on it'll come out on the Playstation 3
So you're actually
It's almost like that the Playstation 3 is Europe
The chat room is lighting up with comments on this one
Let me get their comments and I'll get to Dark Soccer's reaction if there is any
Looking at the chat room
Bandit says simply, a price cut
ActDef says more good games
Let's see
Jirardomo says hitstun Sony needs a game period
Because I guess hitstun said something about needing more games there
Let's see
Blaze says Sony needs a price cut
More download content
More big name titles
And needs to retain exclusives
Hitstun says actually Sony needs some Neo Geo CD backwards compatibility
Hell yeah
Let's see
Rossi says simply games
Who said
Somebody said something about more AAA titles
DustCap2 said more AAA titles ASAP
Kazurai says we're certainly not interested in gimmicks
I think that was GS68 changing their name there
So there you go
I think they need more triple X titles
That would work
They just need intelligence in there
Price cut seems to be the number one thing we're hearing in the chat room though
That's not likely
Chat.OrangeLaunchRadio.com
That's not likely to happen
It'll probably happen in the fall but it's not
I'd say Christmas
I think for Christmas to stay competitive I think you'll see it
I think they need more intelligence in their marketing
But I think the problem is I think Xbox will counter it with a price cut of their own
I'm just worried right now that they're getting hosed as far as exclusives go
Because it is Sony's fault because Microsoft actually is developing a lot of games in house for themselves
And they're not relying on third party exclusives
They've got their own
They've got themselves covered each month with a new game coming out from them
You know and you can't say that about Sony
I mean that's kind of the problem
It's like well we've got Halo 3
Well we've got Killzone 2 coming out
Okay great
I mean that's coming out eventually but that's way in the future
So I don't know
It's just kind of sad
I mean again you know I'm not trying to beat Sony when they're down or whatever
And I'm sure we've had enough of this on the program
Because I love Playstation 2
Such a great solid console
I'm still playing today
PS2 is awesome
You know I've been treating my Playstation 3 like my PSP
At one time I had quite a few games for it
I stopped playing them so I sold them back
And now I'm only playing like one game on it
Actually now on the Playstation 3 I'm not playing anything on it
I'm playing other systems
You know Motorstorm I got a little bored with it
And you know nothing new
I'm still playing lots and lots of Marvel Ultimate Alliance
Yeah but you're about ready to throw the six axis out the window right?
I know I'm ready to explode it into tiny bits
When I buy it I'm buying it on Xbox 360
Wow
Well you know I believe this week actually
I've got more controllers
I was going to say I think it was either this week or last week
That Marvel Ultimate Alliance Gold Edition came out for the 360
That's the other reasons I don't have to worry about spending the points downloading the characters I won
Because you know first thing I'm going to do is we can play through every level I can with Hawkeye
Our Sony fanboys can take comfort in this
I don't know how you guys feel
I'm the only one of the three of us that doesn't own a Playstation 3 yet
You're not missing it
I will go out and buy a Playstation 3 if Final Fantasy 13 stays exclusive to Sony
Because I'm that much a whore for the Final Fantasy series I will have to have it
And you know home looks cool and little big planet
You know those are all like extra yeas for me
With the things they want to do with Final Fantasy 13 I don't think there's processing wise a way it can be done on the other systems
And have it come out the way they want it to
So I'll be changing my tune single handedly by that game
I mean hell Final Fantasy 7 is the reason I bought a Playstation 1
Yep
So that ended up being an okay buy so hey why not
I need a new Jet Moto game
New Jet Moto
Less Sony bashing more stories
Let's throw a little bit of love Sony's way
Even so I'm not highly excited about this because I played the demo at E3 last year
But Heavenly Sword is they're stating that they may have multiplayer as downloadable content
Which is sort of interesting I guess
Still I mean they're saying that when they do it they want to make it you know full on multiplayer not just an afterthought
There's also rumors of you know a co-op and deathmatch but yeah
But the game right now though is from what I understand still on schedule for the September release
It looks awesome
Okay good good news there that's some very good news Heavenly Sword looks good
Yeah exactly they need to catch up with that September
It was like playing the singing level in Kingdom Hearts 2
Remember that was one small glimpse of the game it was like a year ago a lot could have changed
I hope I really hope
You know what's actually kind of exciting and this is kind of funny
Ratchet and Clank Tools of Destruction that game coming out
It's developed by the same people that did Resistance and they're actually using an improved version of the Resistance engine
It looks awesome so far it's very cinematic in the way that it plays and stuff
You know and I don't even I'm not really into that kind of you know Ratchet and Clank
But you know I'm almost kind of thinking to picking it up just because it looks awesome
Alright well sorry I promise that we wouldn't have much more negative Sony stuff
But I just can't not talk about this one and this would have to do with a recent PlayStation 3 promotion
And what happened is that there was an ad for
Okay basically it's on this Spanish website for Kia
Okay it was promoting the Kia car and I guess they're doing this promotion right now with the PlayStation
Because they're running this you know like I don't know maybe you enter to win a PlayStation 3 if you test drive one of their cars
But here's the thing in the ad they show the PlayStation 3 and then they show a screenshot on the TV
Of Project Gotham Racing 3 which isn't good because that's a Microsoft game
And is especially not good because this mistake has happened before on a different website
So wishful thinking maybe
Somebody needs to let the marketing department know that Project Gotham is not a PlayStation title
It gets even worse
Oh lord
Remember there's a Dutch magazine called Media Market that actually did a article on the PlayStation 3
And there's Project Gotham printed in their magazine
Damn somebody at Sony marketing needs to get fired right at Sony International Marketing
Well I think it's a lot of people because it's Kia but somebody I don't know where they're fucking up
It's just a bad mistake to make repeatedly like do it once and it's funny haha people forget
But do it now three times and people start to go what the hell seriously why can't people understand that Project Gotham is a Microsoft title
To be honest I'm going to get some hate mail for this one it's not even my favorite Microsoft racing title by far
You know there's just different types of titles
Do You For Speed Carbon was good
Really?
Yeah
I didn't play it very much I like Burnout that's my favorite I think is Burnout
Because I like to blow things up
There's a lot of need for speed
Burnout Paradise
Oh I fucking can't wait for new Burnout yay
I do like Burnout for exploding
Exactly Burnout has fire therefore it wins
I wish I could say the same for Full Auto although it wasn't bad sorry
So here's something else that's kind of funny a little story
Apparently there's some guy that uh some gamer that was kind of saying farewell to his Playstation 2
Because he has a brand new Playstation 3
I don't know why he decided to do this but he figured the best send off was to piss on it
And I guess he got drunk and you know pissed on his Playstation 2 and being the dumbass that he is left it plugged in
And basically knocked himself out after pissing on
Didn't mommy ever tell you don't piss on the electric fence
What was that episode of Beavis and Butthead where they were playing don't piss on the electric fence
No it was Ren and Stimpy
They were playing don't piss on the electric fence
Yeah there's a little song that goes with it I know
I remember the song
Dark Soccer you've had many consoles come and go throughout your house right?
Mostly just consoles come
Have you ever done this send off for a console have you ever you know pulled down your trousers and peed on a console to send it off
No because I'm not stupid
Especially if you're in your house why would you piss on it in your own house you stupid moron
God I'm gonna piss on it
You know usually when they break we gut them and try to do something neat with the husks
Seriously haven't you been paying attention to the internet the thing to do with consoles is to slam them with a sledgehammer
Put it on YouTube
And the best way to do that is to play the music from what was that scene in Office Space and recreate it out in the field
Oh with the copier yeah that was a good time
So anyway whenever we hear stories about dumbasses like this one it can make us feel anything else but anger and you know what that means boys and girls
N.M. 64 says Rob Roberts remember it's harder for females not really I mean you know she could take a dookie on it if she wanted to
Anyway dark soccer your F.U. of the week please
It goes to you I was going to say F.U. to the Pollen and Dixon for making me all stuffed up and getting all over my car
But no F.U. to Rob because you've never had to go out in the wild
You don't know that I went camping once
But you've never had well okay you've never been a woman going to the bathroom in the wild
Just squat behind a tree what's wrong with that
It's a lot it's not as easy as it sounds
You make it sound like some assembly is required
That's why I love living in the modern world where we have things called toilets
And not living in Japan where the public toilets are spot toilets
Rob you remember though it's not always a good idea to go behind Neil Bush and stuff especially if you're a woman because the drag queen fairy may come and turn you into a man
And then they'll make a movie out of that that's horrible
What movie was that again
I can't remember it was like penis envy that's what it was
Actually there's another thing it was a movie with Adam Sandler who's coming out
Oh is that the gay marriage one
The trailer already pisses me the hell off so fuck them
I'm willing to give the movie a chance to see what the message is in the end but yeah the trailer does make it look like I can't even describe it
It's very trivializing
Yeah it does
Draw Them Together did it first
Draw Them Together did it funny
I'll give the movie a chance but the trailer does not look promising anyway Logie
Screw all the software makers on the 360 for making it so fucking hard to do a system link game with your goddamn games
Stop having the patch shit so it's incompatible with unpatched shit
And then F.U. did my work for not actually having an internet connection in the one room there where we have the game consoles so I can just update them right there
So I have to take them home
Okay is it my turn to give an F.U.?
Well my first F.U. is to Draw Them
I don't like Draw Them
Nobody likes Draw Them and Draw Them is no fun
And then I have a second F.U. and this one's pretty serious so I have to kill the music here for a minute
I had to give an F.U. to myself because something really bad happened and it's kind of hard for me to admit this openly
But it's just a very difficult thing for me I have to give an F.U. to myself because I kind of like a Fergie song
I know I failed the internets completely I failed our listeners but I just like this new Fergie song this big girls don't cry
This is a song that's beautiful
So I like Fergie and for that I deserve to be mocked and made fun of openly by others and I hate myself
I'm pointing at you
Alright that's it more news
No I'd say we take an ice cream break
An ice cream break no we only have a few more stories six more stories we can do it
Fine fine fine well speaking of F.Us Sony is committed to the PS3 for ten years and beyond
Basically the S.C.E.A. president Jack Trenton is quoted saying we didn't get into PS3 for the first six months of 2007
We're into this for the next ten years and beyond a million units one way or another at this point isn't going to worry us
So this is what they're saying well our sales suck but we hope to make it up in ten years
Good luck
We're dedicated to this console to infinity and beyond
Has any console well I guess you know what it makes sense we kind of look at this and go oh ha ha ha
You know but come to think of it you know consoles live on even after the next generation I mean technically we are still in the PlayStation 2's life span right
They're still putting that crap for it
Exactly I mean and good crap we had God of War 2 we have this what the role playing game folks looking forward to Final Fantasy 12 is not that old all things considered you know it's console still got a lot of life left in it
So you know I could see how the console they can say it might be lasting that long before they you know put a bullet in it I don't know
Anyway sorry I was reading some chat room while Jamie was reading that story there and Mystic Gohan reminded me that big girls don't cry so I need to just suck it up here on the show
Also big girls and big boys alike love the Chronicles of Riddick or at least you know feel okay about it I don't know sorry bad segue but hey you know what even if you didn't like the movie the game wasn't bad there was a huge game that came out on the Xbox the Chronicles of Riddick game and guess what there is a next gen version coming out
The UK trade publication MCV has confirmed that Star Breeze is working on a new version of the game for next gen systems the game is called Assault on Dark Athena X and it's going to have a single player mode which is a little bit longer than last time
An all new multiplayer mode and a developers commentary mode so what does that mean you get running commentary while you're playing the game kind of like a DVD track
And man this part was such a bitch to program I swear code here and code this didn't quite work together so we had to do this to make them work and blah blah blah blah blah and the rest of us are going um yeah I don't speak your language
It's like Final Fantasy 7 and it's like yeah and then the scene where Eris dies oh crap that hasn't happened yet oh shit um forget I said anything about that that oh dammit
Good job Loki maybe hey maybe in that remake that they keep saying they're gonna do for you know the internet loves to rumor that one for the Playstation 3 maybe it can have developer commentary in it
And maybe my skin will turn blue
Maybe it will Jamie maybe it will
So Sony plans on bringing the pain to the Playstation 3 and actually the Playstation Network it's a game called Pain and it involves you launching a poor hapless victim into stuff
I'm gonna buy it
Wait is this the one where I saw a screenshot where it was just a guy on a like a slingshot and they were gonna fling him into a building or something
Pretty much and it has monkeys getting injured so injured monkeys people getting hurt sounds like a game I'm gonna buy so yeah that's gonna be coming out later on
It's like jackass but actually funny
Sort of um yeah I don't know it's just using the physics engine so you just you know launch your character into stuff to get him hurt as badly as possible
And they have different games like including like a horse mode or spank the monkey and mime toss
Hey I like that part
Dr. Burst in chat asks what's with the Sony bashing tonight dude this looks great pain looks great and we said the mystic sword looks cool
Heavenly sword and rat things
You're right I'm exposed I hate Sony haha got me
Well you know though speaking of games that I'm not buying Vivendi is putting time shift on PS3 so it will be up there with the PC and PC 360 I'm sorry Xbox 360 oh my did that slip out
Oh I was just gonna say I have a laugh sometimes with like gaming press out there they always make stories for themselves like this whole time shift is coming to PlayStation 3 it's always been scheduled to come out on PlayStation 3
You know even when when Atari had the rights for it but then it went away for a while
Thank you for reading the whole rest of the story for me
Oh sorry
You ass
I'm not on top of things
That's it
I only read my story
This is what you're gonna do Jamie you know what story he does next because you can see it so read ahead and when he starts reading it cut him off and finish it okay Jamie
You know I'm just gonna leave
No you're not you get about two minutes to prep because I have a story here first
No I don't care
It's about the PlayStation 3
Okay I'm gonna sit here and read my comics for the rest of the show
Alright
Here we go now this is something the chat room said earlier is that the PlayStation 3 needs a price cut and you know gamers have said this and you know you've written the magazines you've read it on your online game blogs and now it's publishers saying that the PlayStation 3 needs a price cut
Specifically Ubisoft and Yves Guillemont who is the president and CEO of Ubisoft has said that Sony will quote for sure have a lower market share than before because of the PlayStation 3's cost
And he said quote they have to decrease the price quite significantly
Very interesting
However Ubisoft is continuing to support the PlayStation 3 they're bringing an exclusive title to Europe
Don't know what that means it's an exclusive PlayStation 3 Europe title so those of you guys in Europe that always feel like you're getting pooped on and neglected Ubisoft is hearing your pain and is bringing you something exclusive
Of course we have absolutely zero idea what that is yet
Far Cry Cricket
Who knows Far Cry Cricket
It's Cricket in the Jungle
We'll see
Anyways so Sega is licensing the Unreal 3 engine yes the same engine that's been in practically everything lately but you know hey it's yet another game thoughts are though that it's going to be used in the upcoming I guess they're enhancing or remaking the Alien franchise
Like Alien Syndrome and that stuff?
No like Aliens as in
Oh the movies oh I didn't know Sega owned the rights to that
Now you know
Okay
Wait no that must be a different thing I'm thinking of
But they haven't made an Alien movie since the Winona Ryder one which was years ago
Well they made a crappy Aliens vs Predator movie and then they're making a sequel
Aliens vs Predator was fun
They're making a sequel
Speaking of guilty pleasure movies there we go
When Aliens make out with a black chick yeah
Or no I'm sorry that was a predator
I swear to god
Well at the end of the movie to spoil it for you the predator looks at the one chick and it looks like they're going to make out and then they don't
Oh so they don't actually kiss
They don't actually kiss
So you lied to me
It looks like they are
Thanks for spoiling the movie OMG spoilers
It's ridiculous it's a ridiculous movie
I would have liked to see like maybe Aliens vs Jason or something like that
Aliens vs Predator was like the big fan thing
Freddy vs the Predator
TigerClawnChat says the best Aliens was the arcade version from Konami
It was that's what I was thinking of
But Ross Steel UT says hey Tiger, Aliens vs Predator arcade by Capcom equals sex and act deaf degrees over in Capcom
No I was thinking of the Capcom one because it's all about playing through the game with Lynn Karasawa
With her freaking sword of death
Awesome game
Anything else about the unreal engine?
Sorry we cut you off but you deserved it
No it's going to be probably a first person shooter since people really like to think outside the box
Sonic 3D again
Did you happen to catch that video that was like the Sonic concept that they were going to do that was supposed to be based off the cartoon series?
Yes I actually did see that some YouTube-age I don't remember where I saw it posted
Where like Sonic moved a little more 3D but it was still like a platformer
That looked so fake to me that looked so incredibly fake
Because I cannot believe that they would make a game like that where Sonic moved like molasses
Because if you watch that video it was slow
I know which system they'd put it out on too, the CDI
It looked horrible
I don't know where did you see that YouTube posted?
Kotaku
Was it?
It looked fake I'm sorry it screamed of fakeness to me like they took some unknown game and sprited Sonic into it
I don't know I don't want to believe it because it looked horrible
Maybe that was the beginning of the end of Sega who knows
Let's see
I'm looking at what's in chat going on there
ActDeft wants to see a video game, Aliens vs Predator vs Marvel vs Capcom vs SNK
Well that would be the ultimate wouldn't it?
Alright and let's see
GS68 is kicking Sonic while they're down here
I tried the Sonic 360 demo and the controls nearly made me have a stroke
Heart attack, stomach acid overflow, HIV and loose stools all at once
You know what they need to have now that Sega is doing third party titles now?
Nintendo vs Sega
The fighting game to end all fighting
Dude Smash Brothers hello Sonic
No I'm talking about a bigger roster we're talking like hundreds of characters
We never did get the Namco Capcom game out here
Oh that's true the Namco Cross Capcom or whatever it was?
It was a big RPG I know someone who has it
I played the Playstation 2 Japanese one and I'm kind of glad that we didn't because it was kind of lame
It sounded so cool in theory
Bandit reminds us they do have Sonic vs Mario in the upcoming Olympics game
We talked about it a few shows ago
You know what I want?
I want another
Crap I just lost the game
I want another Strider
What was that ridiculous Sega fighting game that they had where you can actually play as a Daytona car and punch things?
That was in Fighter's Megamix which I have
That's the kind of ridiculous gameplay I want
I want you to be able to play as Rob the Robot or as one of the unicycles from Uniracers
This is something really ridiculous
Instead of Captain Falcon I want to play as the car
Exactly
I'll just turn around and use Nitro Boost
I want to play as a little spinny fire thing from Dungeons and Super Mario Brothers
I want to play as a Bob-omb
Where your final attack is explode
That's awesome
I guess it's break time boys and girls
We're going to take a quick break here
We'll be back with more of Orange Lounge Radio in part B
Lots of news coming up in part B tonight
We haven't even touched the Xbox 360 or the Wii
This has kind of been the Sony segment
We have lots of 360 and Wii news coming up in part B of Orange Lounge Radio
We'll be back right after this