[SPEAKER_05]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and released to our podcast stream twice weekly To listen to the first half of this episode visit www.orangeloungeradio.com for links to websites with listings of past episodes Now the conclusion of this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to talk a little more about some of the other consoles.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, of course, we need to start with the Xbox.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because huge news this week with Halo 3, of course, finally getting its beta.
[SPEAKER_04]: A little bit delayed.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, what, about 13 hours before the folks on Crackdown could get in there?
[SPEAKER_04]: Although Bungie said, okay, because, you know, we made a boo-boo in getting you guys in when we said we would.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to extend the beta for four days.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hooray.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you shouldn't bitch about things that are free anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, the beta was followed up immediately with the news that
[SPEAKER_04]: When Halo 3 is going to come out in Fall 2007, they mean September 25th, 2007.
[SPEAKER_04]: And for those of you guys in Europe that feel like you always get screwed, you have to wait one day.
[SPEAKER_04]: September 26th for you guys in Europe.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you guys finally not having to wait as long.
[SPEAKER_08]: So September 2007, which I... May I point out that September 26th will be occurring at the same time as September 25th here.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's an eight-hour time difference.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good point.
[SPEAKER_08]: At least between here and London time.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: So basically it's a simultaneous release.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not what?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's an eight-hour difference.
[SPEAKER_04]: As close as you can get to it, we should say.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's pretty rad for them.
[SPEAKER_04]: No word about Japan yet, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're probably not as anxious about Halo 3, although they can sell some copies of it there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, you've mentioned September before on this show, haven't you?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I haven't.
[SPEAKER_03]: There was a blog post which I took away during that whole... Yeah, when people were threatening to beat you up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Take you out of the back parking lot and beat you up if you keep squealing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was off by 13 days, but I was close.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's probably closer than most people, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good job, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, so there it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Get your pre-orders in now.
[SPEAKER_04]: September 25th is the date.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you want Halo 3... Especially get those pre-orders in if you're looking for the Legendary Edition because it's going to be fucking impossible to find.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just so you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, so yeah, immediately once the Halo 3 beta came out, people started, you know, the modders out there were already taking notice and trying to grab any sort of information that they possibly can.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, no actual word on what exactly that meant, but apparently they're looking at the code in the beta to see how they can exploit the game when it comes out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not surprising.
[SPEAKER_04]: What exactly are they doing to it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Not really sure.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess they're trying to rip code out of the, you know, like, I don't know, basically taking the demo that's on your, you know, or beta that's on your hard drive and just kind of trying to dissect it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, are they these typical type of multiplayer exploits where they're trying to make themselves invincible so they can go in there and just blow people up and no one can shoot them?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, lag stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think they're really going to be able to do much because it's a beta.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think anyone can really decrypt the games anyways, so that'll be interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, there is actually a little bit more in regards to the news.
[SPEAKER_08]: We were talking about the accounts on Xbox Live a week or so ago.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just another update for the same thing is that they are actually banning modified consoles from live.
[SPEAKER_04]: So in other words, the folks that are trying to fuck with their systems to do this beta by hack storing their consoles, they're getting the ban hammer.
[SPEAKER_07]: Pretty much.
[SPEAKER_07]: Smacking it down.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, they have this little text, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I remember Major Nelson, I was reading his blog earlier this week, had a post of the actual little picture that would come up if you are a recipient of the Banhammer.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it was interesting because it read to me like it was saying, don't call us, there's nothing you can do, you've been banned, F you, bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's basically what it said.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I was kind of like, what if you get banned accidentally?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, you'd be screwed.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because Microsoft basically says, screw you.
[SPEAKER_04]: If this ever happened to me and I didn't actually mod my console or whatever, I would be livid.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure this can't be 100% foolproof.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would think, though, that they're counting on there being such a minority of people that that happens to.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because honestly, if you haven't put anything in your system that doesn't belong there, I've never opened the case to do anything to it.
[SPEAKER_08]: What are the chances going to be that there's going to be some sort of flaw that comes up saying that you've modified your system?
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mystic Gohan in chat is talking about what's happened.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mystic Gohan says they unlocked the locked content.
[SPEAKER_04]: They found out that there's a vehicle called the Chopper in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Bandit says there's a band cannon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not a band hammer, but a band cannon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Band cannon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Instead of a man cannon, a band cannon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember the man cannon?
[SPEAKER_04]: I've yet to see one of those in the beta, the man cannon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you think this is an appropriate response to the hackers?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: I understand it, but I hope they're damn right every time.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think there ought to be some type of way to appeal just in case because if this ever happens to somebody who runs a podcast or a blog, it's going to be a PR nightmare for Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's just my opinion.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't really think they care.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess not, but, you know, still, if they ban the wrong person, it's going to be trouble.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, anyhow, you heard the fuss I made when I got the red rings.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope they don't accidentally ban me.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have to quote Raul Steele in here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hackers deserve to have their consoles bricked.
[SPEAKER_04]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_04]: But again, I just, as long as they are 100% positive that the people they are banning are those that deserve it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't hack your system until the next gen comes out.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, those of you guys that have not gotten your Xbox consoles banned, you have plenty to look forward to.
[SPEAKER_04]: Xbox Live Arcade is getting a Bomberman port, and if you're still crying in the corner in the fetal position over Bomberman Act Zero, fear not!
[SPEAKER_04]: This is a traditional Bomberman-style game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hudson's putting it together.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have confirmed after much speculation on the Internet, which I believe we talked a little bit about last week on the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: There was a trailer and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, Hudson has stepped out and said, okay, you got us.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is coming out, and it's going to have eight-player support online.
[SPEAKER_04]: Quote, this has been one of our most requested games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Our fans have been clamoring for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: We are thrilled to finally be able to deliver the game they want.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there you have it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's going to be pretty awesome there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also new to the Xbox Live Arcade version.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bomberman Customizability.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gamers will be able to design a unique bomber to identify themselves with online.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hudson promises enough options for 10,000 possible combinations, 9,900 of which are ugly.
[SPEAKER_03]: So anyways, something kind of funny coming out from Edge Magazine in the U.K.,
[SPEAKER_03]: And this is coming from Mark Reim.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they're talking about Gears of War and how they've modified it into a golf game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Apparently they were trying to sell the Unreal 3 engine to a Korean publisher that was looking to make casual games from it and possibly a golf game out of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: So what they did to kind of demonstrate this is they modified one of the levels of Gears of War to make it more like a golf course with holes and stuff like that and mounds.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then actually had their animator
[SPEAKER_03]: Create a golf swing for Marcus Fenix And, you know, kind of demonstrate it using the actual I think it was the grenade throwing engine in the actual game So, that's kind of neat Don't expect it to actually come to, you know, live or anything as download content But, you know, hey, if they wanted to do that, that'd be kind of neat Will Gears of War Golf, this tech demo here Become the Final Fantasy on Nintendo 64 tech demo of the future?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like one of those highly sought after things?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe not.
[SPEAKER_03]: It'd be fun to have a downloadable demo or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see a YouTube.
[SPEAKER_04]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wherever a story like this is to be found, there's soon a YouTube to be found.
[SPEAKER_04]: So let's see a YouTube of this in action.
[SPEAKER_04]: Marcus Phoenix on the golf course.
[SPEAKER_04]: Amazing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, this is actually something that makes me pretty happy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Recent submissions to the ESRB has been Echo the Dolphin and Summit the Hedgehog for Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that, you remember when we were talking about the Sega Vintage rumor that was going out?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, this seems to sort of support that theory.
[SPEAKER_08]: Although, it's not going to be called Sega Vintage.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sorry, they are going to call it Sega Ages something.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because that's just Sega.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because Ages is Sega backwards?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cute.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not cute.
[SPEAKER_08]: Rob, they've been doing the Sega Ages collection since the day of the Saturn.
[SPEAKER_08]: That name is not going anywhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: When was the last time there was a good Wayne's World reference anywhere?
[SPEAKER_04]: Come on, I had to do it not.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, sorry, I killed the joke.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, are you excited about this?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, this is like the five gazillionth time we've seen Sonic the Hedgehog.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have both of those games.
[SPEAKER_04]: But there'll be achievements and high-def graphics.
[SPEAKER_08]: How much do I give a shit about achievements, Rob?
[SPEAKER_08]: You've seen my Xbox Live account.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't you have like zero points?
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have one achievement, and that's from playing Uno and winning with a draw four.
[SPEAKER_08]: The one time I've played on live.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're not really a big 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: Where's all your Marvel Ultimate Alliance achievements?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm playing on PS3.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you're going to be playing on Xbox 360, yes?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, and then it'll have Cheater all over it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I'm going to be level 99, 100k, max out my characters.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: That'll be me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, if you are a fan of retro, are you interested in this, Loki?
[SPEAKER_04]: The Echo of the Dolphin?
[SPEAKER_04]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, KaneVM, guess what?
[SPEAKER_08]: I have Dragon Force.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: KaneVM says I want Dragon Force.
[SPEAKER_04]: Give me Dragon Force.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have it.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: on the Saturn going over to the Wii of course they love their virtual console stuff over on the Wii and again the ESRB spills the dirt on what we can be looking forward to on the Wii Virtual Console including Streets of Rage 2 coming to the Wii Virtual Console ToeJam and Earl in Panic on Funkotron boy they're really reaching with the Sega Genesis games now aren't they and World Sports Competition from Hudson
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Three games that are all but confirmed, basically, for the Virtual Console.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anybody downloaded anything on Virtual Console lately?
[SPEAKER_03]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess I'm the only sucker for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I got Legend of the Mystical Ninja because that game was awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was an awesome game.
[SPEAKER_03]: World Sports Competition.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's such a generic name.
[SPEAKER_04]: By the way, Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello, Nintendo and Squeenix.
[SPEAKER_04]: I am still waiting for ActRaiser.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you, Japan and Europe have had it how long now?
[SPEAKER_04]: And we're still waiting?
[SPEAKER_04]: What the hell's the holdup?
[SPEAKER_04]: Actraiser!
[SPEAKER_03]: On my Super Mario RPG!
[SPEAKER_04]: Now!
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, sorry, I'm done being a little kid.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, so something else we talked about on a previous podcast, which later disappeared into the Bermuda Triangle.
[SPEAKER_04]: which we will speak no longer of on this program.
[SPEAKER_03]: Namco Museum Remix is coming to the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: First time I've ever heard that.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I never heard you say this on a previous podcast at all that suddenly disappeared a few weeks later.
[SPEAKER_03]: Never heard it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Never ever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Never.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's going to actually, they're kind of remixing a few different things than you would normally expect like pack and rolls actually being remade into a Wii game.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's going to be on there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pac-Motos, which is going to be a Mario Kart type game, but basically Pac-Man knocks his opponents out of dangerous arenas.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rally-X Remix, they're redoing it in 3D, so it's a little bit different than the remixed ones on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_03]: Gator Panic Remix, which is like Whack-A-Mole.
[SPEAKER_03]: and then of course you're going to also see Galaxian, DigDog, Mappy, Xevious, Galplus, Super Pac-Man, Pac and Pal, Pac-Mania, and QQ.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll all have remakes and I guess, oh, no, the originals.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's set to release, I guess, it says in the fall.
[SPEAKER_04]: As much as I have issues with Namco lately for certain unsaid personal reasons, this game looks pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't let that get in the way of the fact that the game does look pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, you know, pack and roll on the Wii does seem like kind of a natural progression.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm a sucker for these retro things.
[SPEAKER_04]: What can I say?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just such a fucking sucker for this crap.
[SPEAKER_04]: And this looks kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, and unfortunately, it's going to be the only rolling game this year on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, I know you're a Namco fan
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: But are you excited about this whole remix thing on the Wii?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, is this something that should be remixed, or should Namco Games be untouched and preserved in a bubble forever?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, given that I was picking up the Sega Ages 2900, and you know what those are, they're all the touched-up, redone versions of the old Sega games, then I have absolutely no problem with this.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would love to see D3 release all the simple 2000 series over here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, there have been a few titles from the Simple 2000 series that snuck over.
[SPEAKER_03]: They just, of course, are different titles.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bandit says, bring me BurgerTime now, and Ross Steele has to remind Bandit the BurgerTime is by Data East, so it won't be in a minute.
[SPEAKER_01]: I can have BurgerTime now?
[SPEAKER_04]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: What the hell ever happened to Data East?
[SPEAKER_04]: Are they still around?
[SPEAKER_01]: They're doing pinball.
[SPEAKER_03]: They should remake Breakthrough.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was one of my first Nintendo games, and I loved it.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura loves to look at the internet up and down and all over every week and share her favorite website with you.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's DarkSakura's website of the week and she's going to tell you what it is right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: I decided not to do a website of the week, sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, really.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is one that was suggested by our very own Loki, and it's fucking addicting.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's Dofiblog, and let me see if I can read what this says.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, it just says Dofiblog in Hiragana, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a bunch of flash games.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's really crazy.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've been playing Cat with Bo Golf, which is crazy.
[SPEAKER_08]: And there's also Stick Remover, and Double Wires, Eggway, San San San, X Snow Cats, Neko Breakout, War of the Hell, Slug Slayer, New Rolling Omosubi, Rolling Omosubi, and a bunch of other weirdo games involving cats.
[SPEAKER_03]: I highly recommend...
[SPEAKER_03]: X Snowcats Eggway Double Wires Ishii.blog2.fc2.com
[SPEAKER_08]: Ishi, I-S-H-I dot B-L-O-G 2 dot F-C-2 dot com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which you have conveniently posted in chat for our listeners, I see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Of course I have.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you, DarkSakura, upstanding citizen.
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Data East, I looked them up on Wikipedia to figure out what went on.
[SPEAKER_04]: They went under on June 25, 2003 is when they filed for bankruptcy in a Tokyo court, and their intellectual properties were acquired in February 2004 by G-Mode, who is a Japanese mobile game content provider, which explains how we have burger time on cell phones, because I have seen that game in recent years.
[SPEAKER_04]: So maybe you'll see bad dudes in a few years on phones.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Are you a bad enough dude to have a milkshake?
[SPEAKER_04]: But Data East went under.
[SPEAKER_04]: They did have a brief stint in pinball, and they did some pretty good tables.
[SPEAKER_04]: Guns N' Roses, The Simpsons, Robocop.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have Guns N' Roses.
[SPEAKER_04]: And what else?
[SPEAKER_04]: They purchased Stern Electronics, and then something changed, and they made Stern Pinball, I think.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, no, Stern Pinball.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then they sold it all to Sega.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stern.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, pinball goddess.
[SPEAKER_08]: Stern is their own company.
[SPEAKER_08]: In fact, Stern is the company that released the Pirates of the Caribbean pinball like a couple months ago.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I think they also released the Family Guy pinball.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, I get it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Data East exited the pinball business and sold the factory to Sega in 96.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the USA division had already been transferred to Sega as part of a debt settlement.
[SPEAKER_04]: and then the Pinball Factory changed hands one more time with Gary Stern purchasing the factory in 99 and renaming it Stern Pinball.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what happened.
[SPEAKER_08]: And Stern is still giving us our pinball.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: But unfortunately, no more Data East.
[SPEAKER_04]: No more Kid Nicky Radical Ninja, I'm sorry to say.
[SPEAKER_04]: No more Bump and Jump Kids or Ring King.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love Bump and Jump.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, Bump and Jump was rad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, but you do get plenty of Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_04]: Brawl because that wasn't by Data East.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's by people completely different
[SPEAKER_04]: Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_04]: Brawl
[SPEAKER_04]: Tingle in it!
[SPEAKER_04]: Your favorite Nintendo character of all time, Tingle.
[SPEAKER_03]: Boo.
[SPEAKER_04]: From the Zelda series, of course.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tingle is the... He's every fairy's fairy, let's just put it that way.
[SPEAKER_04]: He goes around spilling rupees, and good times.
[SPEAKER_04]: I remember he was in the Four Swords game on GameCube.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that would be great if Tingle shows up in the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Has not been confirmed by Nintendo, it's still a rumor, but that would be pretty awesome if Tingle showed up in the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: If nothing else, but to drop power-ups in.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because, you know, it doesn't necessarily mean that Tingle is a character.
[SPEAKER_04]: It could be that Tingle, you know, because, like, remember how, like, Pokemon showed up?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, the Pokeballs would show up in the old one on GameCube?
[SPEAKER_04]: You could just throw the Pokeballs and you had random, like, you know, like, what were some of the Pokemon that showed up randomly?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, the Charizard and stuff would blow fire or whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: And with any luck, maybe Loki is secretly recording the voice of Tingle as we speak for this upcoming game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I am not recording the voice for Tingle.
[SPEAKER_03]: God.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's horrible.
[SPEAKER_03]: Horrible, horrible.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_03]: Apparently now, if you're flying Delta Air, you can check out some free demos for the DS.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because now they have DS demo stations right there.
[SPEAKER_03]: while you're waiting in line.
[SPEAKER_03]: And some demos you'll be able to try out, Brain Age, Cooking Mama, Elite Beat Agents, and Tomb Raider Legend.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, all those are free.
[SPEAKER_04]: Isn't this all the same shit that's in there usual?
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to say yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, yeah, I guess, I don't know, but this isn't much incentive to fly Delta because if you think about it,
[SPEAKER_04]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_08]: There is some good news for our friends in Europe.
[SPEAKER_08]: Final Fantasy VI Advance will be released on June 29th.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've actually got the game, although to be honest I have yet to play it.
[SPEAKER_08]: You have the Soul Shrine that gives you a bunch of monsters to beat up and...
[SPEAKER_08]: A Kaiser Dragon Boss, and a music player.
[SPEAKER_08]: But other than that, it's the same game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Except that you have no Vanish Egg Zone.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, they took Egg Zone out of the game?
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: You have no Vanish Egg Zone.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, the trick you used to do.
[SPEAKER_03]: The combo.
[SPEAKER_08]: No Vanish Egg Zone.
[SPEAKER_03]: What was the Vanish Egg Zone combo?
[SPEAKER_08]: What happens if you cast Vanish is that it makes the enemies disappear, but...
[SPEAKER_08]: It makes them, I think, vulnerable to all magic attacks, and then X-Zone sends them to another dimension.
[SPEAKER_08]: So basically, it ends the battle.
[SPEAKER_04]: X-Zone was like an insta-kill.
[SPEAKER_04]: X-Zone was an insta-kill, but it didn't always work.
[SPEAKER_04]: But if you used Vanish on the enemy first, it would always work.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: I always used to just, like, cast and reflect on all my characters and then just balancing the spells off there, even though I don't know if it did anything.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was just nice to see, like, lightning hit, you know, four times or whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_04]: Drew Nami would like to point out that Vanished Doom will also work.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Vanished Doom combo.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like, but still my favorite attack, though, in that entire game was Meteor, just because it looks cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I never used the Vanished Exon TD.
[SPEAKER_04]: I actually thought Exon was kind of a dumb spell, just because, I don't know, I like to kill in the old-fashioned way, by the hand of my sword.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, or spamming Ultima.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well...
[SPEAKER_08]: The other thing, though, that I really... Okay, what was... In the Final Fantasy games, overall, what would you say is your one most useful spell?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_08]: That isn't Cure.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I was going to say Cure.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cureaga?
[SPEAKER_08]: That isn't in the family of Cure.
[SPEAKER_04]: Protect.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I rarely use Protect unless it's Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_04]: The number one spell I would use?
[SPEAKER_04]: Fire III, I guess.
[SPEAKER_08]: Demi.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, where it has their MP every time?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, Demi quarters their HP every time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh yeah, quarters their HP.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, Demi I thought was... Demi was an HP attack.
[SPEAKER_08]: And you cast Demi 3 and it was like even more than that.
75%.
[SPEAKER_03]: What was the... And it would work on big enemies.
[SPEAKER_03]: There was one for MP.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't care about their NP as long as I could kill them before they hit me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jvmon says Demi and Bio for me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bio was the other one.
[SPEAKER_08]: I love Bio.
[SPEAKER_08]: But Demi was like my big favorite.
[SPEAKER_04]: Virus in 4 was pretty rad because it made that hideous noise whenever you cast it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It sounded like cats getting hit.
[SPEAKER_04]: It sounded like cats in a burlap bag being hit with a bat when you cast Virus on the enemy.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just like the chainsaw.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was rad.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's why I love 6, was that, you know, you did the little commands with, what was it, Saban was his name, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, that was Edgar, I think.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, Edgar, well, Edgar had the chainsaw, but Saban had the ones where you did, like, the... The Street Fighter stuff?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, the Street Fighter stuff, and he did special moves.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was so rad.
[SPEAKER_08]: He was really cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: God damn, that game is great.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're going to remake that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That'd be awesome if they do.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm still, you know, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't mess with something that ain't broken, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I am curious to check out this Final Fantasy 6 Advance.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, I need to buy the Advance one.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, GSucks68 in chat says, Demi sucks, especially against most stronger enemies since they're immune to it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not if you make them not immune to it.
[SPEAKER_04]: RawSteelUT says, virus equals bio, translations.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought it was virus and four and then bio in the later games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe it was translations, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it still made the dying cat noise.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you love Final Fantasy, then you must have this in your collection.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can get a Chocobo Magic Book Mug.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, of course, NCSX.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, I don't know how you guys feel about this company, NCSX.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you use them, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: NCSX is great.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Byrite is the one you hate.
[SPEAKER_04]: But they went under, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, hell yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: So NCSX.
[SPEAKER_04]: God damn it.
[SPEAKER_04]: NCSX.
[SPEAKER_04]: Live radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: is a place where you can buy these mugs for $18 a piece.
[SPEAKER_04]: These Chocobo mugs, and damn, they look cute.
[SPEAKER_04]: Look at that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Look at those little Chocobo mugs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't they look cute?
[SPEAKER_08]: It reminds me of my... I got you your Batsmaroo one.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, my Batsmaroo mug, which I do use once in a while for coffee for my Hello Kitty coffee maker.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe I should get a Chocobo mug to go along with this.
[SPEAKER_08]: You should get me one, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cute coffee mugs are awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I can drink out of a bird's head.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe I'm going to go on a shopping spree at NCSX any day now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I might have to think about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why should I buy a present for you?
[SPEAKER_04]: What have you done for me?
[SPEAKER_08]: What haven't I done for you?
[SPEAKER_04]: A lot.
[SPEAKER_03]: What have you done for me lately?
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, like most of those promo deals out there, there's a new one now to get a Wii for free.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the way you do it is Gamefly, they're running a promotion where you persuade five of your friends to sign up and in return they'll send you a free Wii six weeks later.
[SPEAKER_03]: What people are doing is having their friends sign up, giving them like $10 each to do that, and then canceling it after a set amount of time.
[SPEAKER_03]: And there you go, free Wii for $50.
[SPEAKER_07]: I did that for an iPod.
[SPEAKER_03]: So yeah, it's kind of like that scheme.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, my guess is they're going to catch on to this pretty quick, and they will change something.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that shit really works, huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like we can get the free Xboxes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I keep hearing this commercial on the radio for the free Xbox.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm always like, oh, schemes are so reek of shenanigans.
[SPEAKER_04]: But they really work, huh?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll tell you how I did mine.
[SPEAKER_08]: They had this Blockbuster online thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was like Netflix but Blockbuster, so it sucked.
[SPEAKER_08]: And if you sign up, they don't charge you for like two weeks during their trial, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: So, but it takes six days for them to transfer to the iPod site that you signed up for, so you cancel before they charge your credit card.
[SPEAKER_08]: And so me and five people did that, and I got an iPod.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then my iPod broke.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you got a cheap iPod.
[SPEAKER_04]: You got a refurb.
[SPEAKER_08]: I got one of the third edition iPods that they had the recall on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ah, that sucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, well.
[SPEAKER_04]: The first email comes from a French nun
[SPEAKER_08]: Bonjour, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_08]: And please pardon my bad pronunciation because I am way, way out of practice.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, Christ.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are all our emails actually in French this week?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, they're not.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was like, did they actually listen to you?
[SPEAKER_08]: Vous avez une très belle voix et j'adore vous entendre à la radio orange.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I'm really good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Basically said I had a really good voice and they like listening to the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, I have a general comment.
[SPEAKER_08]: I find your show a little Xbox 360 heavy.
[SPEAKER_08]: While I understand that there is little to talk about in the PS3 world, my PS3 is accumulating dust extremely effectively.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'd love to hear you chat, argue, fight about other platforms such as DS, PSP, cell phone games, and insert obscure platform here.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, the GDI.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: We did, didn't we?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Listen to Part A this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like nothing but non-Xbox 360 stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: I tune in to hear about stuff I know nothing about, and to be honest, I buy games you guys recommend.
[SPEAKER_08]: So talk about as many platforms as possible, fair enough?
[SPEAKER_08]: And then I'm going to translate this.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, thank you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, still, my reading is not so bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: And good luck with the new massage profession.
[SPEAKER_08]: And this is a French-Canadian listener who...
[SPEAKER_08]: Demands that we speak in French more.
[SPEAKER_04]: Parlez-vous freeze-pop?
[SPEAKER_04]: I know that.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, thank you very much for the well wishes, and I'm actually going to be going, when I go back to school, I'm actually planning on, I took, you know, a whole bunch of French, and I used to be fairly conversational, so I'm going to go back and finish French.
[SPEAKER_08]: and Robert M. I'm sorry, but this made me crack up.
[SPEAKER_08]: Poisson de Babel for Babelfish.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait, are you going on to another email?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm on another email.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait, can I respond to the last one real quick?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, the Rob D. in chat says, OLR should cover the Sega CD more.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe we should.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I just want to say about the Xbox 360 thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: You've got to realize, though, what platform has something coming out every week on it with the Xbox Live Arcade?
[SPEAKER_04]: There is the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: If you have a game you want us to talk about, email it and we'll talk about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: What is that?
[SPEAKER_04]: A taco.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, that's okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why aren't you on the show this week?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll take the stuff inside of it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because I got back too late.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I'm better than you guys.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll take the stuff inside the taco.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just start digging.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you have a fork?
[SPEAKER_09]: I do not, but I can go get you one.
[SPEAKER_09]: How was your gaming week real quick?
[SPEAKER_09]: I played a lot of Oendan 2, and I've already beaten it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh shit, nobody even mentions it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm so sorry to interrupt your mailbag, but we need to hear about Oendan 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: How is it?
[SPEAKER_09]: Let me first stress that I'm not a Japanophile in the least, so I don't care about J-pop, and I don't like J-pop, but I like these games.
[SPEAKER_09]: So the music for me is sorely lacking, but it's harder than Oendan 1.
[SPEAKER_09]: and... It doesn't quite have the same charm as the first game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Either Owen Don 1 or Elite Beat Agents.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I like it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I would still say Elite Beat Agents is my favorite of the three.
[SPEAKER_09]: But Owen Don 2 is better than Owen Don 1 and I like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's really hard.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did they change anything with the basic game mechanics?
[SPEAKER_04]: Or not really?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, but they brought over the cool features from Elite Beat Agents where you can skip the intro and the last stage is actually divided into two songs.
[SPEAKER_09]: And...
[SPEAKER_09]: Oddly enough, you can skip the endings for each song now too once you've beaten them, so it's kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like if you're just replaying to get a better score.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's good.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I've been playing Puzzle Quest also.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, how's that?
[SPEAKER_09]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to try that out before you leave.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, well I'm leaving like sometime tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, good.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I have a terrible backlog of DS games now.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have like six that I need to play or beat, and it's depressing because I keep finding more I want.
[SPEAKER_09]: How hard was it to find a copy of Puzzle Quest?
[SPEAKER_09]: It was hard for me at the time.
[SPEAKER_09]: I found it last weekend.
[SPEAKER_09]: I found one at Best Buy.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I went to EB and Best Buy this week, and yeah, it's not hard anymore.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, okay, good.
[SPEAKER_09]: So they finally put out enough so people can get it if they want.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, thank you, Mikotov.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_09]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: And can you get her napkins for her taco?
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, I'm going to eat it.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're just going to eat the taco?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's delicious.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to start back tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good job, Shane.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ruining diets everywhere.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I've been good all day, but I think my headache is because I had so much sugar for two days and then dropped all of it, so I need a buffer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie, you're a good-looking gal.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just eat the taco.
[SPEAKER_04]: You don't have to worry about that stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, I do.
[SPEAKER_04]: The chatters.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie needs some love.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tell her she has nice boobies or something.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I don't because I figured I dropped 80, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Right.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then I gained back 15.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I'm going to be going back to the gym and everything because I still have a little bit more to go.
[SPEAKER_04]: I need to lose some too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go to the gym with me.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki just did the most foul thing with his belly.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was disgusting.
[SPEAKER_04]: He like shook it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mailbag.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, Robert M., you're funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: And by the way, there was not.
[SPEAKER_04]: Look at chat.
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: There's Jamie Love.
[SPEAKER_04]: Look at that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's why you do this show, right, for your ego?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not starving myself.
[SPEAKER_08]: She's not, but... I eat... No, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, what I wanted to tell you guys is that diabetes, there's a tendency toward it in my family.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it's not a matter of aesthetics or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a matter of preventing disease on the way.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie, that taco's not going to give you diabetes.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know, but I'm...
[SPEAKER_04]: Mike isn't on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Say the joke again.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll give you something else that starts with a D. No, no.
[SPEAKER_08]: The whole reason being is that I'm cutting back on my sugars because my blood sugar actually was fairly borderline at my last blood test.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I'm trying to avoid diabetes.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that is the reason why.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry to get on the tangent and get all depressing here on the program.
[SPEAKER_08]: That and exercise is supposed to actually help with chronic fatigue syndrome because I'm also trying to get myself off my meds.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just eat the fucking taco.
[SPEAKER_08]: I will after I'm done doing the fucking email.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd eat it, but I don't like Mexican food, so, you know, this is kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_02]: Email!
[SPEAKER_08]: Bite my ass.
[SPEAKER_08]: And no, there was not a home release of Dragonflare on Laserdisc.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Was that the email?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, that was from... You didn't even read the poor guy's email.
[SPEAKER_04]: You just yelled at it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was in really bad grammar.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fuck.
[SPEAKER_08]: He said so himself.
[SPEAKER_08]: He's Babblefish.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: Poisson de Babble.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, next email.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, DarkSakura, Loki, and Skye.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_03]: Time out.
[SPEAKER_03]: GZDR4EV Dude, those boobs.
[SPEAKER_03]: One of those nipples is a fucking comma.
[SPEAKER_03]: What are you trying to say?
[SPEAKER_03]: One of her nipples is fucked up looking?
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Derail the whole show.
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: Was that how that was about my boobs?
[SPEAKER_03]: He was making asking nipples.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, you asked for an email in French, so you... Okay, whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: JVmon drew my boobs bigger than yours.
[SPEAKER_08]: You have special pumped up boobs.
[SPEAKER_04]: My nipples are the size of like dollars.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nights, um, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's more of a Christmas game for me, I think.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, because it has that kind of night Christmas.
[SPEAKER_03]: Didn't they have Christmas nights?
[SPEAKER_03]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it's more of a Christmas game for me.
[SPEAKER_03]: You think?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: You think Knights could be around Christmas?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, they should release a Christmas Knights as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I don't know if I've told, well, I've mentioned this several times.
[SPEAKER_08]: Christmas Knights is actually a tradition at my house.
[SPEAKER_08]: We break out the Saturn and we play Christmas Knights up until Christmas Day.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nerd.
[SPEAKER_04]: What was the other part of the question?
[SPEAKER_04]: Games that should be redone or something?
[SPEAKER_08]: RPGs that should be re-released for the DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: RPGs that should be re-released for the DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: Guardian Legends?
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, maybe that wasn't an RPG.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's still a game that I want.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's an adventure shooter.
[SPEAKER_04]: Close enough.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just want the Guardian Legend, love.
[SPEAKER_08]: So do I, oh my god.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I want to stop whining.
[SPEAKER_04]: How about the Illusion of Gaia series?
[SPEAKER_04]: Or the whole Enix Soul Blazer, what was it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Soul Blazer.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh my god, Shane, this is a good taco.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Illusion of Gaia, and there was a third one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Brain Lord, that's the other one, Brain Lord.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want that whole series on DS.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, next email.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Unless you had anyone that you wanted to seek him out?
[SPEAKER_03]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_07]: What RPG would you like to seek him out for the DS?
[SPEAKER_03]: Taco the RPG.
[SPEAKER_03]: For the DS?
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh, remake, remake.
[SPEAKER_03]: Super Mario RPG!
[SPEAKER_03]: Where the fuck is my game?
[SPEAKER_14]: Taco.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Juranami says it was not Brain Lord, it was Terranigma.
[SPEAKER_08]: Next up.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um...
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, with the Xbox 360 keyboard, do you think World of Warcraft will come to the 360?
[SPEAKER_08]: Why or why not?
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, no.
[SPEAKER_08]: And you don't need to know why.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's from Daniel.
[SPEAKER_03]: I kid you not.
[SPEAKER_03]: Every time the Vividi rep comes down to our work, we ask him that same question.
[SPEAKER_03]: When's World of Warcraft coming to the 360?
[SPEAKER_03]: And every time he says it's never coming to the 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ever.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think it's happening either.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think Blizzard, if they're going to do something on the consoles, they will make a game specifically for consoles.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think they're going to port their game.
[SPEAKER_04]: They don't really need to.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, everybody has a computer.
[SPEAKER_04]: People that don't even play PC games play World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, you're only seeing games that are ported to that when they need more users.
[SPEAKER_03]: World of Warcraft is not really having any trouble with
[SPEAKER_03]: Not a large enough user base.
[SPEAKER_04]: Blizzard probably figures, if you have an Xbox 360, you also probably have a computer capable of playing World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, and also, I mean, World of Warcraft runs on almost anything.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, as far as Linux, Mac OS, Windows.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, it's not like it's a graphically intensive game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Right.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the last email, oh my god, Rob, I'm so sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, the chat?
[SPEAKER_08]: I just got unbanned from... I'm just ignoring the chat now.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, this is from SakuraMax.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just got unbanned from Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_08]: Remember to plug that if you haven't.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I want to say, screw you, Rob.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jamie is cooler than you.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hate you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not even going to respond to it.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I think that the thing is, the signature is the funny part.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hopes Rob gets eaten by a Gru youngest OLR member.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wishes World of Warcraft would work on his computer.
[SPEAKER_08]: Pocky lover and Vietnamese otaku.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hell yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Rob Hart.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, is that all the emails?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you want to send us an email, mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com How about some Rob fan mail next week?
[SPEAKER_04]: After that email.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want some Rob fan mail that Jamie has to read word for word on the air.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rob fan mail in French.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or in Spanish or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: How about a language Jamie doesn't know that I know a little bit of?
[SPEAKER_04]: How about Spanish?
[SPEAKER_04]: I want Spanish love for me.
[SPEAKER_04]: No love for Loki ever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh...
What?
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on to, yeah, that's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on to another story talking about Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nintendo is following up a contest in some ways.
[SPEAKER_04]: Microsoft has recently said that they would like original TV pilots because something that they're going to distribute on the Xbox Live Marketplace.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, now Nintendo has come out and said they're going to be holding this contest called the Shortcut Shortcase.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the top three entries will be premiered at Rockefeller Center's annual Summer Film Showcase.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shortcase?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm thinking of Shortcake.
[SPEAKER_04]: I must be hungry.
[SPEAKER_04]: The theme is Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_04]: The movies can be action, comedy, drama, whatever, as long as it has Nintendo hardware or Nintendo characters.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there you have it.
[SPEAKER_04]: The first place winner gets $10,000 and a trip to New York for the premiere and a lunch meeting with the Tribeca Film Festival co-founder, Craig Hatkoff.
[SPEAKER_04]: The top three entries all get Nintendo goodies.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have until June 6th to get it together.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there's already a lot of Nintendo...
[SPEAKER_04]: There's already a lot of Nintendo fanboy stuff on YouTube, so this shouldn't be too hard for most people.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, get crackin' if you want to be a famous filmmaker.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anywho, so one person that's not going to be featured in an upcoming live-action Metal Gear Solid movie would unfortunately be the voice of Snake, David Hayter.
[SPEAKER_03]: He will not have anything to do with the movie Fangirls Cry.
[SPEAKER_07]: That makes me sad.
[SPEAKER_03]: Snake right now, because man, the dude needs a haircut.
[SPEAKER_03]: He looks like Joey Fatone.
[SPEAKER_07]: Snake was running around with a mullet.
[SPEAKER_03]: He looks like he's about ready to join a Ren Faire.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Snake was running around Metal Gear Solid 2 with a mullet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, but he has guns and he's not a real special op guy, so... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: Speaking of whatever...
[SPEAKER_08]: There's a next generation Wolfenstein in the works.
[SPEAKER_08]: And they're stating that it should be actually out in 2008.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's being put out by Raven.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that's happy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Will it be like the old school Wolfenstein 3D or the more meh Castle Wolfenstein game that came out later?
[SPEAKER_04]: What was that called?
[SPEAKER_04]: Return to Wolfenstein or whatever that game was?
[SPEAKER_07]: Return to Castle Wolfenstein?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I didn't care for that one.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh my god, Shane, this was the best taco.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was more like one of those, like, you know, War Sim games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just liked being able to shoot up like Hitler in the War Mac.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was awesome in the old school 3D game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Forget it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, oh boy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Speaking of things of a questionable nature, there was a Flash game created about the Virginia Tech Rampage.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was a Flash game.
[SPEAKER_04]: and this game was created by this guy, Ryan Lamborn.
[SPEAKER_04]: And this is interesting, is the response, basically, you know, he made a flash game that was basically, you know, it, you know, kind of glamorized the whole Virginia Tech shooting.
[SPEAKER_04]: You could, you know, take part in it, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Obviously, this is very controversial.
[SPEAKER_04]: But what's interesting is what this author chose to do in response to it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Quote, attention, angry people.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will take this game down from Newgrounds if the donation amount reaches $1,000 U.S.,
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll take it down from here if it reaches $2,000 US and I will apologize if it reaches $3,000 US.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, he never really says what the donations will go to besides his pocket.
[SPEAKER_04]: I believe Newgrounds ended up taking the damn thing down anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: But kind of interesting that he kind of blackmailed the internet to take his game down.
[SPEAKER_03]: He also said that he was joking about the whole, you know, wanting to collect money.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, unfortunately, a lot of people didn't really take it that way.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, he did.
[SPEAKER_04]: Later, there was an update
[SPEAKER_04]: The donation thing is there as a joke against all the people commanding me to take my game down.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't think anyone would donate money to it, and so far my PayPal account has proven me right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: That seems like an afterthought excuse, doesn't it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, he's just probably thinking, well, maybe some dumb sucker will, you know... If it was a joke, he would have probably not put his PayPal account on there.
[SPEAKER_03]: What a weirdo.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just some dumbass trying to get attention just like... I mean, I'm all for freedom of speech and all, but...
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: And in a way, the media just shouldn't even cover it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's really what it should be.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, if you don't want this guy to make any money off it, don't fucking cover it so people don't know about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think anybody would have found it otherwise.
[SPEAKER_04]: Media should take some responsibility.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even the gaming blogs and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't fucking cover it if it's in poor taste.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't write about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I probably shouldn't even... God, I'm being a hypocrite right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I probably shouldn't have said anything about it, but it's... Well, it sounds like the game's already down.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what I'm going off of, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we come full circle...
[SPEAKER_03]: GameTap has announced that they're doing an animated series called Revisioned.
[SPEAKER_03]: Each season is going to focus on a game series or game character.
[SPEAKER_03]: So for example, the first series that's up is Tomb Raider, and it's also going to be animated by Warren Ellis, Peter Chung, and Jim Lee.
[SPEAKER_03]: To give you an idea, it's basically Animatrix, but for games.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's yet another original thing that they're actually doing that's going to be pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'd like to see some DVDs for this, because that might be something worth checking out.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: I never even saw the movies, ever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Although, if you're interested in checking out to see what it's going to look like, they are going to have a little bit on the Tomb Raider GameTap collection website.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's tombraider.gametap.com You can check out a trailer for this new cartoon series.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ross Steel in chat says, Animated series on GameTap.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Captain N all over again.
[SPEAKER_04]: HitStun says, I think Tomb Raider Legend was going to be sold cheap on GameTap, if not free.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: is a toll-free number, but only in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_04]: and Canada.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you use the Skype line instead, you can be anywhere in the world and still call us for free.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's go to the phones, and we'll take this call right here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you are on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, am I kidding?
[SPEAKER_11]: It's DMN.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, DMN.
[SPEAKER_11]: What do you want?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I'm so glad.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's really you this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, I'm glad, too.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm out of impersonations right now.
[SPEAKER_11]: Um, however, I'm calling on behalf of DJ Tyrant, um, to say one thing, and, um, if you'll excuse me, I'll put the phone away from my mouth, because I don't want everyone speaking to it, so, one second.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, now we've gotten that out of the way.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why is, uh, DJ Tyrant so excited about StarCraft 2?
[SPEAKER_11]: DJ Tyrant is OLR's resident Blizzard fanboy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now I may actually watch the first ten seconds as opposed to the first five.
[SPEAKER_11]: I played StarCraft a little bit in my youth, you know, all those ten years ago.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm not a huge fan of the real-time strategy genre.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, you know, that's my problem.
[SPEAKER_04]: I never really played StarCraft because I wasn't a fan of the real-time strategy series.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll tell you, if this announcement, though, had been Diablo 3, I would have had a total fangasm.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, I think you and I both would have.
[SPEAKER_11]: I love Diablo, but seeing as the announcement was happening in Korea, I think everyone did their math.
[SPEAKER_11]: 2 plus 2 equals 5 and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I'm also calling to announce the Phoenix Down usage on SDFU.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, what's this all about?
[SPEAKER_11]: We put our show on hiatus, one, because I've been going through a lot of personal turmoil, and now that's kind of subsided and I feel my crazy normal self.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're revamping the format of SPFU.
[SPEAKER_11]: For any people who were introduced to my antics in the chat room earlier last year, you know I used to do a little around the horn thing and I scored people's arguments.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, now we're turning it into a show.
[SPEAKER_11]: DJ Tyrant and three chatters from OLR's chat room will face each other off each week, and the winner gets to finish the show with me.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, wait, now I know you have a lot of special guests that come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, you've had some of the Destructoid bloggers on the program, and you've had bigger names on your program than we've had on this program.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, are you going to invite them to play along with you guys?
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, absolutely.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I guess you guys can come play, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, we get to come play DMN's little game, too?
[SPEAKER_04]: How nice.
[SPEAKER_11]: Aww.
[SPEAKER_04]: Aww.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, maybe I don't want to play your game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I'll come on at some point, for sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't speak for the others, but I will.
[SPEAKER_11]: I can't think of anything else, so I guess it's time to hang up on me
[SPEAKER_04]: What's wrong with... What's... Wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_04]: What are you booing Pump It Up Pro for over here, Shane?
[SPEAKER_00]: No, I'm not.
[SPEAKER_00]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, I... Sorry, there's confusion in studio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Give Shane a mic.
[SPEAKER_04]: Damn it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I said, boo, Pump It Up Pro.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why boo Pump It Up Pro?
[SPEAKER_09]: Because it's by the guys that do In The Groove and the step charts suck from what I've seen.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, it's that one.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, and it's got crap music and it's terrible.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's alright though.
[SPEAKER_00]: Think about it.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's like In The Groove and Pump It Up having a love child.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shane, put it down for a minute.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're obviously biased.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to hear Zago's opinion.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_00]: Nah, I mean, I played it.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, it pretty much is step mania.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's like End of Mirror found step mania and found a good use for it
[SPEAKER_00]: and just mash Cowboy songs in addition to their banya and K-pop.
[SPEAKER_04]: So Pump It Up and In The Groove had sex and this is their baby.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, you pretty much have modifiers that you would normally find in Step Mania Mines.
[SPEAKER_00]: C400 speed.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, it plays pretty much better since it's on the breakout at the high-end cabinet for beta testing.
[SPEAKER_00]: So it has a nice high-def TV to go with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I was talking with Kyle on email like last month trying to get him on the show and we just lost time.
[SPEAKER_04]: I need to email him again and try to get him on the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'd love to have him and Shane on the same show.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be a good time.
[SPEAKER_00]: I doubt he'll be able to spill the beans.
[SPEAKER_00]: I know.
[SPEAKER_00]: He's pretty tight-lipped.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it'll still be fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, so what else have you been up to in your gaming world lately?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, as I said, not only does Aiden on the breakout pump it up for beta testing, but New Jersey also has 2DX Distorted and Poppin' Music 14.
[SPEAKER_04]: How is Poppin' Music 14?
[SPEAKER_04]: Jesus Christ, they keep cranking those things out.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, we're catching up to TGA at this point.
[SPEAKER_04]: What are you doing?
[SPEAKER_04]: Opening a candy bar?
[SPEAKER_00]: No, it's just an oatmeal bar.
[SPEAKER_04]: How is Poppin' Music 14?
[SPEAKER_00]: It's a lot better, though.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's a lot better than the one that I'm used to over in Queens, the Poppin' 8 that I go to.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you have a case of the Munchies right now?
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm almost, I'm not high though.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm just a little hungry tonight.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, besides that, just, you know, I just heard, you know, just, you know, pretty up over the whole StarCraft 2 thing.
[SPEAKER_00]: You heard about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you excited about StarCraft 2?
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you a big RTS fan?
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, it's been, yeah, it's been almost a decade since they actually, you know, it was actually released, the first one, so I've been itching to play it.
[SPEAKER_00]: The only thing that'll bother me is if Koreans, you know, the South Koreans start cheating on it.
[SPEAKER_00]: and start, you know, bringing it down and battling it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, Korea, no cheating.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, that's the only thing I worry about, but if anything, we'll just keep it to a land, you know, we'll just keep it to strictly land games.
[SPEAKER_00]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_00]: Like something you can do after work.
[SPEAKER_04]: I still wish it had been Diablo 3, though, but hey, I'll give it a try.
[SPEAKER_04]: Blizzard puts out some quality shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, seriously, what has Blizzard done wrong?
[SPEAKER_04]: They're really, I can't think of a lot.
[SPEAKER_00]: The only thing they need is World of Starcraft and that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, Saku, we've got to let you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: But have another oatmeal bar for me, buddy.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Later.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you just say whatever to me?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think you did.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's go to another call here on the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Raven Stolfen.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello, Raven Stolfen.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's on your mind, my friend?
[SPEAKER_10]: Let me turn down the thing, and I'll tell you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, rule number one of radio, turn down the speakers when you're going to be on the program.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't get that annoying ass echo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Live radio, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm sorry about that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm glad that you played that old To Go song from OLR, from OLR To Go, and the music break that no one knows about.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I was going to say, the podcast listeners have no idea what you're talking about.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yeah, we played during the break, because we do a break between A and B, we play some music.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can play a clip.
[SPEAKER_04]: Playing clips of music is okay on podcasts.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's a little clip of Gradius Full Speed.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is our old theme song.
[SPEAKER_04]: How was our old team music back in the day when we were doing a live show and a separate podcast?
[SPEAKER_04]: That was good times.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wasn't that good times when we'd be in the studio for like five hours?
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: What did you want to say about the song?
[SPEAKER_10]: It just brings back good memories of listening to you go like, Oh, it's the last radio to go, week of whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I'm like, Oh, it's the last radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's one of the really good memories.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's like a retro thing for you.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, and I didn't just call about that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I did call about Fear in Halo 3 Beta.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hmm, what about that?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I've been playing a lot of FPSs in Xbox, and I played Fear for the Xbox.
[SPEAKER_10]: I got it from Gamefly.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_10]: How was that?
[SPEAKER_10]: I thought the game was good.
[SPEAKER_10]: The thing I hate is about the corridors, and everything looks the same when you walk.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's the thing I hate.
[SPEAKER_10]: You always, like, have an hour of looking at it, and then you finally figure it out.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's what I hate about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you think that Halo 3 will outsell Halo 2?
[SPEAKER_04]: I do, I do.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because it has my favorite gun, the assault rifle.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just because of the assault rifle?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, just because of the assault rifle.
[SPEAKER_10]: Everyone's been bitching about it on the forums going, we need the assault rifle, we need the assault rifle.
[SPEAKER_10]: The battle rifle sucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Any other quick words here before we get to another call?
[SPEAKER_04]: Tech and Game Podcast, that's it.
Bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you want more of the Raven's Dolphin, he has his own podcast, Tech and Games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Check it out.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know he has an OLR community page, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: By the way, I dug up something out of the archive.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's what Raven was referring to.
[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition, week of July 11, 2005.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're tuned in to the Orange Lounge Radio to-go edition.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, good times.
[SPEAKER_04]: Old school memories.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: You don't miss the five-hour studio marathons?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, Rob.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I would go home literally sick with exhaustion.
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: Aren't you glad we're much shorter now?
[SPEAKER_08]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_04]: We picked up another call.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_13]: Hey, it's Dr. Burst.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, Dr. Burst.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do not recognize your name as a caller.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you a new caller?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_04]: New caller?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, I want to comment on the World of Warcraft on 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: World of Warcraft on 360, a very popular topic.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you want to say about it?
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, I just think, why not?
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, people want the game, and Blizzard makes more money.
[SPEAKER_13]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_04]: But do they make more money?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because, again, what about the argument earlier about most people that have an Xbox 360 probably have a computer, be it PC or Mac,
[SPEAKER_04]: It's capable of playing World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, I have a computer, and I tried the demo for World of Warcraft, and it doesn't work that well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe there's something to be said for the achievement point whores of the world, Loki, that might have fun just playing the game to get achievements from it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_04]: Anybody else in the room care to comment?
[SPEAKER_04]: Why not WoW on the 360?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'd actually be for it.
[SPEAKER_09]: because, like, it's kind of the same thing they did with Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_09]: I got it on the 360 because my computer, you know, it could run it well enough, but the 360, it's got a set, you know, spec for it, so they're putting it on a system knowing that everybody's going to have the same amount of... It's, like, optimized for 360.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, it's optimized for that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: And so, you know, if they did that with World of Warcraft, give me a keyboard and mouse, I like my TV better than I like my computer monitor, so I would do it.
[SPEAKER_09]: And voice chat built in right there too because you could just do your own little private room with your friend.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rumor is, rumor is that PC version is getting a voice chat patch, but that's a rumor.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, the thing is too, you probably couldn't do mods on World of Warcraft or 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, that's true.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, good point.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that, you know, one thing that PC gamers on their World of Warcraft love are all the mods.
[SPEAKER_04]: Spam Sentry I tried it on a demo
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm a Guild Wars player.
[SPEAKER_09]: The demo that you downloaded is leading other websites that sell gold to download those demos and spam us.
[SPEAKER_04]: You said you're a Guild Wars player.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why not Guild Wars on the 360?
[SPEAKER_13]: That too.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's just that because it's instance-based and there's so many load screens, it probably wouldn't work that well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, WoW has a lot of instances too, especially when you get into Endgame.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, I mean, I think about Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_04]: Final Fantasy XI had freaking loading screens every time you went to a new area.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's one of the reasons I like WoW is that it's very seamless.
[SPEAKER_04]: You only really do loading screens when you go into instances or new continent or when you go to the other continent.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, yeah, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, tell us a little more.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't often get new callers.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, Dr. Burst, what types of games have you been playing this week?
[SPEAKER_13]: Pretty much Guild Wars.
[SPEAKER_13]: Guild Wars?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm getting back on Guild Wars.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_13]: You guys should be looking for a guild.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've got one.
[SPEAKER_08]: I had one like five seconds after I made my account.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's not really a best class.
[SPEAKER_08]: I made the Doctor as a Mesmer.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was my dream.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the thing about Guild Wars is that every job, sub-job combination kind of makes sense.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, they kind of built it a little smarter in that regard.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, props to Guild Wars for that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, even the most hated class, Warrior Monk, still works.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, I think I played a Warrior Monk.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it was like Ghetto Paladin.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well, Dr. Burst, thanks so much for the call and have fun in Guild Wars.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if you see Jamie, you know, nuke her for me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wait till I'm at least a comparable level.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm five right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Keep working.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye, Dr. Burris.
[SPEAKER_04]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love new callers.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't you love new callers?
[SPEAKER_07]: For dinner.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not that I mind the old callers because I like the old callers too, but it's nice to get some new blood in once in a while.
[SPEAKER_12]: For dinner.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, it's Kane.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, Kane, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_04]: I can hear myself a little bit, so just make sure you turn down your speakers.
[SPEAKER_08]: We hear Rob all the time.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, it's too much of me.
[SPEAKER_09]: We should turn down our speakers.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe I'll just... I'm turning down my ears.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Screw you all.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will be quiet for this entire phone call.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've got to pee anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: You guys talk to the caller.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, caller.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who is this again?
[SPEAKER_08]: I know, it's too much of me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Rob, come here and fix it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, now we can hear you.
[SPEAKER_12]: I just want to talk about the whole...
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, it would probably be better for most users, but honestly, who wants to pay that extra money just because you have to pay for the subscription and Xbox Live?
[SPEAKER_08]: People do it for PSU.
[SPEAKER_09]: And they're idiots because PSU sucks.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, it does.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh my god, I played that game for like two days and canceled it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm a Phantasy Star fanboy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Leave that alone.
[SPEAKER_09]: PSO was great.
[SPEAKER_09]: PSU was terrible.
[SPEAKER_08]: PSO was awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: I played Blue Burst, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you're worried about paying an extra fee to play on Xbox Live, do it the smart way and pay for a year.
[SPEAKER_09]: Then you're not going to really worry about it anymore.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're not going to be thinking, oh, I'm paying this on top of my Xbox Live fee.
[SPEAKER_09]: It really works out nice.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, yeah, you've got the Xbox Live anyway, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: Who, me?
[SPEAKER_09]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I mean, if you're...
[SPEAKER_09]: You don't... Well, if you've got the silver... You got silver, and they made Final Fantasy XI, if I remember right.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you have silver, you could play it online.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why couldn't they do that with WoW also?
[SPEAKER_09]: Owned.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's what it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know if they will.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, at any rate, I don't think that it's that good of an idea, because... I mean...
[SPEAKER_08]: World of Warcraft already is... They don't even have any type of controller support on it for PC.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I think that it would be very interesting to see how they'd map something like that over.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, they're probably going to really, really screw up on it when they do.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not going to hold my breath on it.
[SPEAKER_12]: You never know until it happens.
[SPEAKER_08]: That is true.
[SPEAKER_08]: And Rob spent the entire time not in this room.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was playing like...
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm here now!
[SPEAKER_12]: And I'm going to break Rob's head.
[SPEAKER_12]: Rob and Loki yell.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did this guy just threaten to break my head?
[SPEAKER_08]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: I will break you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't break my head.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's not nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: For that, you get hung up on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for calling.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_11]: Hi, this is Chainsaw Juggling.
[SPEAKER_04]: Chainsaw, what's, uh, wait, what is his name?
[SPEAKER_04]: Chainsaw Juggling.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, I just wanted to say I have the new issue of games for Windows, and they have it confirmed that voice chat is coming.
[SPEAKER_04]: Voice chat is coming.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank God we don't have to buy a vent now, because our guild was seriously thinking about getting a vent.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, dear God, I can hear myself echoing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Am I really that loud?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, Rob, you are.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, because you have the speakers up right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, maybe that's why.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, I'll back up a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, oh, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: So they confirmed that for the next patch.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's good.
[SPEAKER_04]: So did they say about how long?
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, it's saying it's coming after the next patch.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then also that what they're going to try and do is make it so that the person's talking their name lights up and you can click on it and then heal that person or trade with them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Huh, that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wait, so is it...
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait, it's going to be voice chat even not in parties?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like in the Barrens, everybody could have voice chat?
[SPEAKER_04]: That could be horrible.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think it's supposed to be more than a party.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I don't want to be walking through the Barrens and then suddenly some asshole comes on with a Chuck Norris joke on the speakers.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would kind of ruin the game.
[SPEAKER_11]: That would probably be one of the worst things ever.
[SPEAKER_11]: It would make it better.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki says it would make it better.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: ChainsawJuggling, anything else you want to share with our listeners?
[SPEAKER_11]: They're adding guild names.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're adding what?
[SPEAKER_04]: A guild bank.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: So like the entire guild can share one bank?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, and it's supposed to be set up so certain members can only access certain items within the bank.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's kind of cool because some people are doing that already, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like they'll set up a dummy character that the guild members can log into.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to let nobody have access to our stuff but me.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're a jerk.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, come join our guild if you're a WoW player.
[SPEAKER_04]: We need more people.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, I've got to start over again.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't have a lot of time, but I'll do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: It takes like an hour to get to 10.
[SPEAKER_04]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're a casual guild.
[SPEAKER_09]: We don't want a lot of time from you.
[SPEAKER_04]: We just tell dick and fart jokes.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, we don't.
[SPEAKER_04]: It took me about a year and a half to get 40.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, snap.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, he's a player like me.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's a player like me.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's still cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can still come join us.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, thanks for calling Chase on Juggling, and we'll hopefully have you in the WoW guild at some point.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, see you guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have a good night.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, see you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks, you too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Lots of noobs tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is an interesting change here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's do one more call.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're on Orange Lawns Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_14]: Hey, it's Ranma.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's up, everyone?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_04]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_04]: Good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you all ready?
[SPEAKER_04]: For Fonamay?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hell yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm actually very excited.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you excited, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_08]: I am, but I have to find a sewing machine to put my... I'm not... I actually got the skirt for my Jessica costume.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it might not happen, so I'm going to focus on the ninja costume and do that one.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because if I knew enough people on the West Coast, I bet you a dollar one of them would be bringing their sewing machine to the con.
[SPEAKER_04]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, you probably have that anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, the only problem being is that I actually need the red ponytail wig, and I cannot find one.
[SPEAKER_08]: I do have, though, a long red wig that I'm thinking about just sort of pulling back into a ponytail and faking it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Cosplay!
[SPEAKER_14]: Are we still down for Part A?
[SPEAKER_04]: Why don't I bring my Patron from my last year's birthday?
[SPEAKER_04]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've been drinking some of it, but I can't drink all that tequila by myself.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know me and tequila.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know me and tequila.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't get along, so you'll be drinking it by yourself.
[SPEAKER_08]: Even good tequila makes me go crazy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Give me a bottle of Malibu.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Rob, let's put in some money for some Grey Goose.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, I got five on that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh, Rama, anything else besides liquor chat?
[SPEAKER_14]: Just about anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: See you next week, Rama.
[SPEAKER_14]: Next week?
[SPEAKER_14]: Let me see you Friday.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck, that's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: See you Friday.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hell yeah, later!
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to be 12.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're going to be 30-12?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm not going to be 30-12.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to be 24.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's terrible.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I'm actually going to go 22.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to go down a year.
[SPEAKER_09]: At least this year.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe next year I'll go back up to 23.
[SPEAKER_09]: But no, I don't have any plans yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: But in the hopes that I come up with something better than going to the anime, I'm going to ditch it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because I didn't have fun last year, really.
[SPEAKER_09]: So it's not my thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I want to buy stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Love Jahi, he's one of my favorite people ever.
[SPEAKER_08]: And Wendell, didn't he completely swear off Tequila because of this?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not going to embarrass him over the air, especially since I don't know if he's listening or not, but oh my god, I heard the story.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was monumental.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm so excited to drink with all my friends.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like seriously, during one part of the program, we just gave Jahi the mic.
[SPEAKER_04]: And for like an hour, he just spouted off these random insane babblings.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was incredible, riveting radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: And yeah, we really probably should wrap up the show now, huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because now we're starting to talk about stuff that... Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like all these personal stories.
[SPEAKER_08]: Afterbirth FTW.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: So anyway, we're going to wrap it up.
[SPEAKER_04]: So any last minute stories in studio, folks?
[SPEAKER_08]: I like beer.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm a level 11 wizard on Puzzle Quest, because it's really awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: But you're not a nerd at all.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dude, I just like playing the duels.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, what the fuck is that you're playing?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm playing Stick Remover.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sounds exciting.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's on the Duffy blog, the same one that had the cat golf thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Any last minute stories, Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: Um...
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, here's a few things.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can get free game.
[SPEAKER_03]: They just posted something on Kotaku about it called Echoes.
[SPEAKER_03]: It looks kind of like Geometry Wars and Asteroids, so that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: So check that out.
[SPEAKER_03]: King of Fighters is being made into a live-action movie.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dear God, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's being directed by Gordon Chan, a guy from Hong Kong who... Okay, then maybe it'll be cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: ...spawned other Asian martial arts flicks like The Medallion, starring Jackie Chan, Fists of Fury, starring Jet Li...
[SPEAKER_03]: And let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, then I have a little bit of hope.
[SPEAKER_03]: And also, it looks like Axis Entertainment's Joseph Cho, Appleseed, Ex Machina, and Convergence Entertainment's Tim Kwok of Wicked City, I guess, will handle the production.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sounds like it'll be out in Asia early 2008.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then also one game that's going to be coming out as well for 2008.
[SPEAKER_03]: Winning Eleven 2008.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Konami, apparently, this is coming from Game Wave, a print magazine in Germany.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's going to have, it says it will be released on multiple platforms, even on the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: Improved defense, more realistic and changed dribbling animations.
[SPEAKER_03]: One-on-one tackles and offside traps will have better results.
[SPEAKER_03]: Better online service, no lag, and full HD support with 18GB storage.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I guess you could dump the game onto the hard drive.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: Looks like that's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, and Microsoft is asking gamers for Xbox Live Arcade game ideas.
[SPEAKER_04]: LaserCat's the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dude, I'm so going to suggest that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I demand, no, I demand the OL Army to mobilize to this thread and request LaserCats the games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Where is this at?
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that on the Gamerscore blog?
[SPEAKER_04]: Wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't remember where it was.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, Activision wants your input for the next Spider-Man game.
[SPEAKER_04]: How about Don't Suck?
[SPEAKER_03]: How about Don't Make Another One?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: How about be able to set Kirsten Dunst on fire?
[SPEAKER_08]: That would be great!
[SPEAKER_08]: I want Kill Gwen Stacy the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: with special supplement KillMJ.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's go around and get everybody's final thoughts of the evening.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, since you have the mic right now, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_03]: My final thought is I want to play more Earth Defense Force.
[SPEAKER_04]: Miklatov, thanks for piping in for the last part of the show here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even though you've been playing Puzzle Quest the whole time, we will still give you an opportunity.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, I talked while you were in the bathroom.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Give your final thought.
[SPEAKER_09]: I really like that YouTube video of the little kid getting kicked in the face by the breakdancer.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because I've been watching it a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_09]: Good times, good times.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think I have no heart.
[SPEAKER_04]: On some really wrong LiveJournal community, I won't mention that I watch once in a while, there was a picture of...
[SPEAKER_04]: That, and it just said, Babality.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's stupid, because it didn't turn somebody into a baby.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was funny.
[SPEAKER_09]: Kick the baby in the head.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then there was a Street Fighter one, too, where they made it look like he did a little flash kick, and it said Guile.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to show it to you, maybe during the afterbirth.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, real quick, I was going to say, there was a funny thing that, this is on HMV, I guess, they're going to be doing,
[SPEAKER_03]: They're advertising their Manhunt 2 since it's coming out later this summer.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're adding in that little sticker on it that says, Jack Thompson becomes angry, but then again, he's always.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then it has the date.
[SPEAKER_08]: It just occurred something to me that I think part of the reason why, even though it's just to get his face all over everything, I think that lawyers are required to do a certain number of hours of things that are
[SPEAKER_08]: for the public good.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's exactly it.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I think that that might be his consideration.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, he's still a twat.
[SPEAKER_04]: He is.
[SPEAKER_08]: He's got like a yeast infection or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_08]: Pay me.
[SPEAKER_04]: My final thought is reject false icons and
[SPEAKER_04]: and DarkSakura never says it anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: And why don't you ever say that anymore?
[SPEAKER_04]: It makes me a little sad.
[SPEAKER_07]: Reject false icons, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: And my other final thought would be Balthier.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have a great week.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see you next time on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: And hey, thank you, as always, for supporting independent podcasts.
[SPEAKER_04]: You guys are awesome for supporting our program, All We Ask.
[SPEAKER_04]: You tell two people about our program.
[SPEAKER_04]: or leave us a kind review on iTunes or Yahoo Podcast or one of those awesome little sites there.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Pimp Podcast for a living.
[SPEAKER_04]: Word of mouth is how our show succeeds and makes us stand out amongst the 50 billion choices that exist out there for gaming podcasts.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you guys so much for supporting us.
[SPEAKER_04]: See you next time on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember, live at Fonamay next week, no live show.
[SPEAKER_04]: See ya.
[SPEAKER_10]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_10]: For more information on our live and podcast programs, visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com See you next week!