Orange Lounge Radio
There's a host, Dark Sakura, Sky and Loco
Tonight, May 13th, 2007
Could the Xbox Live Marketplace be set to compete with iTunes?
The easy release of Spore faces yet another delay
And a PlayStation series is revived on cell phones?
Orange Lounge Radio
Hello everybody out there on the internet and welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio
We are that podcast dedicated to video games, video gaming, gaming culture and the gaming lifestyle
My name is Rob Roberts and joining me as always say hello to Dark Sakura
But you might know her as Jamie Summers
I love salad
I heard your TV shows getting picked up by NBC after all
The Bionic Woman, the remake
What?
Yeah, they're making a remake of Bionic Woman
That's so fucking cool
Because I think of your name and everything
You know, your name, quote unquote
To recap for new people
My mom was going to name me Erica
And the little girl next door said, no, you should name her after the Bionic Woman
Name her Jamie
So my mom named me Jamie, only she spelled it right
And so that's why I took Summers as my last name for my stage name
There you go
Because I am named after, my mom showed her very small nerd roots
But you've been using that name on air for the past, you know, five years or so
I've been using it since under sedation
Yeah, so a long time, so it's just kind of funny that now the Bionic Woman is coming back, so
Do we get neat sound effects?
I don't know, well maybe
Dude, it will not be the same if we do not get neat sound effects when she runs
I do know that the people behind Battlestar Galactica have a hand in this
A new remake, so it should be pretty awesome
Because if there's one show I've been watching a shitload of lately, it's Battlestar Galactica
Finally, I'm like three years late, but I'm finally catching up
The last Battlestar Galactica thing I saw was on Robot Chicken
With the giant mecha things falling over
Alright
The Cylons
Yeah
And there's Techmaster Loki
That was a funny episode, that was like one of the first ones actually
I was watching the Optimus Prime with prostate cancer thing
Yeah
Well, Bionic Woman, that sounds kind of retarded actually
It could be cool though, I mean
What, is she going to run super fast with a cell phone in her hand, trip into laypeople and cause a super crash or something?
It's not the Bionic Soccer Mom
We can rebuild her, she will be even more, you know, destruction prone
It sounds like a horrible show
Bionic Man sounds even retarded
That sounds kind of dumb too
And Bionic Woman is like, I'm going to rage at you
That was the Six Million Dollar Man
I was going to say, they have the Six Million Dollar Man, so
Oh, well then that's lame, I don't even give a shit about the Bionic Woman
Well, I believe
Unless she has a claw that comes out of her hand and she can swing on things and fights Hitler
I believe
Bionic Commando
I believe I was reading in one of those websites that in this new Bionic Woman, she's a 50 million dollar woman
They have 50 million dollars worth of parts in her
Well yeah, inflation, you know, is a bitch
That'll buy a nice pair of tits though
Alright
It better for 50 million dollars
I want Rebecca Romain to play her
No, it's some British unknown
Somebody that isn't known here, but has been in some British shows
British, I know
Softy
I want someone who looks like Jane Fonda in the 60's
There's pictures, go to dig and look at the entertainment section and you can see pictures of the new Bionic Woman
Rob, I'm doing a show right now
Like that ever stopped you before
Alright
Anyway, also say hello, we'll get to video games soon, I promise
We have nerd stuff to get to first
Also say hello to a frequent guest of ours, but he hasn't been here in a while
Say hello to Miklotov
Hello
And where have you been young man?
I don't know
Where have I been?
The island of Pokemon
Yeah, you've been catching Pokemons
I'm tired
I just woke up
Alright
What's going on?
But I noticed that you're playing DS, you're playing Pokemon now
Yes
Still
Now, you started Pokemon and then you restarted your game
Why did you quit and restart your game completely?
Because I felt like I was doing too much trading and not enough playing
I was just not happy with my Pokemon, so I restarted
And I started with Chimchar, who I've named Homonkey
Like homo-monkey?
Like homo-monkey, yes
Like a Pokemon name, it's awesome
Shane, Miklotov, and I like to have naming contests for our Pokemon, like who can have the better names
Mine wins hands down, nothing's gonna top that, like nothing ever
No porch monkey would not fit, because he's not black
I liked, you named one of them Fancy Pants
Fancy Pants
Because it looked like it was wearing a big fur coat
And then it evolved into like this cyber grasshopper looking thing
It was ridiculous
It was ugly pants
I don't use it anymore
I like Muffins
Muffins is actually called Daddy Ore
What was the other one I just called it?
See the problem is, I don't know the real Pokemon names now
Because of my stupid names, because I named everything
Like I named one Sparkles, because it had a little thing on its tail
It had a little sparkle on its tail
My electric squirrel thing is named Ellinuts, because it's an electric squirrel
And I really got creative when I got that Ponyta
It's a fire horse, so I named it Hoarfires
So I just put fire in the middle of horse
That's it
That's very creative
It is creative
Good job
I enjoy it
Actually, I caught a Magikarp and named it Useless
I named it Fish Sticks
Alright, anyhow
Wow, we're nerds
Anyhow, also we have some nerds here in chat
Chat.OrangeLoungeRadio.com
If you want to join us live on this Sunday evening as we record
Kind of a busy Sunday, we don't have as many people as we usually do
I mean, we're up against Mother's Day today
You know, there's a lot of people out doing stuff with their moms
Happy Mother's Day if we have any moms that listen to our program
Also, we are up against the finale of Survivor
You know, somebody actually had the balls to come into chat
And say, oh, sorry, I can't listen to you guys tonight, Survivor's on
Goodbye
Shut up
Okay, A, this season of Survivor was spoiled a long time ago if you read the forums
I can tell you who wins, but I'm going to be nice
He's already told me
For listeners to TiVo'd it
But, yeah, it's just, I don't know
I used to be the biggest Survivor fan
Like, I had a party when the first Survivor was ending
Okay, I was that hardcore nerd
But now, like, the game's really gotten just old
I haven't really gotten into any seasons since, like, maybe
Palau was, like, the last one I watched, which was a while ago
So, anyway
Don't you love reality television, DarkSakura?
No
Then we ought to get into our gaming weeks
How was your gaming week, DarkSakura?
It was kind of neat
I actually just played a whole lot of pinball
You know
I looked at Cooking Mama once
Just to show somebody
But, really, I've just been playing a bunch of pinball
And, you know, I got Guild Wars
Which, um, right now
I'm having to be really slow with moving on to my new computer
Because I actually have to replace all of my programs
So, I haven't really been playing a whole lot
Well, we are, though, we've decided we're getting Marvel Ultimate Alliance on the Xbox 360
Because we have more controllers
That's the only reason
Party
Party game
How many, can four folks play simultaneously on that one?
Yes
That's pretty cool
I've still yet to play it
But I've already laid claim
Alright
Well, what pinball tables have been dominating your time lately?
Twilight Zone, that game's a bitch
But you haven't really been playing the pinball game on 360
The new downloadable one
No, Dan can play it, I don't care
It kind of looks sucky to me
The whole point of pinball to me
The last good virtual pinball besides for Alien Crush and Devil's Crush
Was, like, Revenge of the Gator on Game Boy
Back in the day
That game was awesome
Oh, Sonic Spinball, of course
But that's not quite the same
But, you know, Devil's Crush and Alien Crush are the pinnacle of video pinball
Anything else is just a pale imitation
I have to say that, for me, it's having the flippers and the noises and the ball
And having my machine go Powerball and getting that ceramic ball
That the magnets can't do crap to
I love Twilight Zone
But I've also been playing Rocky and Bullwinkle
I like the pinball FX, but, you know, I think I was getting into this last week
Nothing is a replacement for the real thing, sadly
Nothing at all
You feel the machine move
And that's, I think, the
Not even Revenge of the Gator, sadly
Not even Revenge of the Gator
Loki, how was your gaming week?
It was good
Finally got the damn systems to land with each other
Apparently the problem was Crackdown
Because Crackdown is a little bitch and doesn't want to land with other systems
Unless you do it its way
So anyways
So I've been playing a little bit of Call of Duty 3
And that was fun
We landed together and had a little multiplayer game
And then once the Crackdown update came out
With the new download content
That pretty much screwed any chances I had with playing anything else
So I've been playing that
And the download content is pretty awesome
Especially the free-for-all pack
Which is the free stuff that basically unlocks the keys to the city
Which is basically a debug mode for the game
You can adjust the agility of your character
You can give yourself super agility to jump even higher
Or run super fast and then super strength
Plus you can spawn vehicles, spawn explosive barrels
Have all weapons, unlimited ammo, god mode, that kind of stuff
Of course none of that stuff counts if you're playing the actual game
But it's just a little fun little mode to play with
And you can do that in co-op
Then of course there's also new weapons and new vehicles with the paid one
Including a spear gun
You can spear people in the head and stick them to the walls and stuff like that
Which is kind of fun
And then they have like a dune buggy vehicle that you can spin around the air like crazy
Just a bunch of little fun stuff
Plus now they have street racing in the game
Which adds a little bit of, you know, kind of a little extra minigame in there
But overall I think it's pretty awesome
And then of course, you know, fuck
Tomorrow we've got, you know, or I should say Monday
For those people listening on the podcast
The Halo 3, er, no I'm sorry, not Monday, Wednesday
The Halo 3 beta is going to be coming out, so
A bunch of people on my friends list are already playing it
We're just not special, nobody cares
Because, you know, they had those preview events in Frisco and New York
And they were giving out those codes to basically everybody that went to the event
So there's a bunch of people on live already playing it
But, you know, I don't care
I know, I'm like, eh, it's a beta
It's not the real game
And like, you know, the beta's going to have issues
Especially with everybody hitting it at once
I think people are getting a little too excited about the Halo 3 beta
If that makes sense
Like it's not the real game
I don't know, I think Microsoft's pretty ballsy to be doing this to be honest
Uh, they played Super Paper Mario some more
About halfway through the game now
And it's still very easy, I don't know
I've had like no trouble getting through the game at all
And I don't know if it's just
Like even all the secret stuff and the puzzles are just so fucking easy to figure out
I don't know
But it's fun, you know, don't get me wrong
It's a fun game
I just, I would really like them to do a new Mario RPG
Because, you know, even if you kept the same graphic style as this game
It could be so awesome
It's just very disappointing that they're not gonna
Alright
DarkSakura, some comments from chatroom
Toshin asked about Pokemon Pinball
Did you ever play that one?
Did you like that one?
Barely
I was a good one, I liked it
There was two of them if I remember right
There was one for the old games and the one for the advanced games
They did like two
Dude, Epic Pinball
On the PC, yeah, Epic Pinball was pretty awesome
I had another pinball simulator
I can't remember the name of it
Somebody had, I brought it up on a previous episode
Somebody named it
But there were some good PC pinball games too
Epic Pinball, of course, being one
Also looking at chatroom
RawstealUT says Halo 3 Beta
The only reason people bought Crackdown
That might be true, but they got a pretty decent game with it
It's a fucking awesome game
Even I like Crackdown
It's not usually my type of game, but I like it quite a bit
I would have bought it even if it didn't have Halo 3 Beta in there
There you go
To be honest, I don't even know
I mean, I may download it and might play it once
I don't think I'm going to play it much more than that
Because I'm not really a huge Halo fan
And as far as first-person shooters go
It doesn't really make, it doesn't seem like
That big of a difference in Halo 2
It's just like, eh, whatever
I'm going to get fucking murdered by everybody on there anyway
Because I suck at Halo like really bad
I want to know if there's any really really bad Halo players
That are excited about the Halo 3 Beta
Because we need to form a clan and just play with each other and suck together at Halo 3
I'm pretty awful, I've only played Halo 2 like four times
I'll play if you load me up on meclizine
Do you have the Beta? Do you have Crackdown or anything?
Can you get the Beta?
I got Crackdown
Okay, then you can get into the Beta
So we'll play an OLR We Suck night or something
But we only have a few weeks to do it, I think, so
We'll see
You can still, by the way, I was at Best Buy the other day
Randomly, and they still had Crackdown with the Halo 3 Beta in it
So, you can still find copies of it
So, get them soon if you want to get in
Well, this has nothing to do with Halo, but I did have an announcement
Okay
Um, probably in the next four months I'm going to be a published illustrator
Oh, how so?
Um, I'm going to be doing flashcards of bones and muscles if everything works out
Huh
For my flash therapists
That'll be fun
So, are you going to autograph them at different places for our listeners?
No, but I'm going to take deep tissue massage
That's cool
Well, good luck with that
Um, my gaming week
Let's see, I haven't really played video games this week
They're bad for you
I've been trying to avoid video games
Also, I don't eat at Wendy's anymore
Because they support the evil company that is Nintendo
And, you know, this lawyer guy told me that was bad
No, kidding of course
I had, all things considered, I actually had a pretty bad week personally this week
But, Miklotov cheered me up, which was really cool, because he bought me this
This Final Fantasy XII play arts
And this is great radio, by the way, when I go like this in motion
It's something that listeners can't see
But I'm telling you, it's a Balthier figurine from Final Fantasy XII
And Balthier is the sexy, sexy, sexy pirate from Final Fantasy XII
And, like, the best reason to play that game is him and Fran
Because they have the best interactions and steal every scene
So, I love them
And so I was very happy to get this figurine
And it kind of made me go, damn, Final Fantasy XII was one of those games I started
And just didn't finish because all the console launches were going on at that time
I really need to go back now that
I never even started it
I need to play it, it's such an incredible game
I need to finish it
And the characters are so awesome, so there you go
Um, let's see
And, um, also I played World of Warcraft
I got to level 51 because I don't have a life
And, uh, then I played some Xbox Live
I finally tried out Catan this week
And, uh, because somebody had told me it was like Civilization
Lies, lies, lies, lies
Catan, I don't know, Catan didn't really do it for me
I know there's a lot of people that are really into the strategy games
And, you know, really got into Catan
But it just, it just wasn't the kind of game I was looking for on Xbox Live
Um, and I hear it has some real crappy multiplayer
That people are getting disconnected and all that stuff
So, I don't know, I don't know
Try out the demo, see if it's your type of thing
It's way more complicated than Uno, certainly
But, what I do like about the game, what it does have going for it
Is because the game is a little more complicated
You have to really kind of learn it and think
It's a much more, like, thinking type game
Uh, the people that are playing it are pretty intelligent
So if you do play it online, you don't get a lot of the
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
type people, you know, the people, that's what they say
You know, in their headsets on Xbox Live, so that's kind of
Kind of, I guess, something the game has going for it
Otherwise I've been playing a little more Pinball FX
And, uh, Centipede and Millipede
For no good reason, other than I just really like retro games
So I was playing, uh, Centipede and Millipede
Oh, and Double Dragon, I bought Double Dragon
But, I was a little, well, it's not that bad
But the problem is that I really remember the Nintendo one
Much more, and there's big differences between the Nintendo one
And the arcade one
And namely that the arcade one was a lot harder
And some of the, like, the moves aren't quite the same
That they were in the Nintendo one
Like, with the Nintendo one, you, um
Gain these stars as your points went up
And that allowed you to do more moves
Like jump kick and punch people when they're on the ground
And stuff, and it doesn't really work the same in the arcade
Uh, version
But I thought
It's the first port I've seen of an old arcade classic
That wasn't done by that, what is it?
Digital Eclipse, is that what they are?
It was done by somebody else
And so it was kind of refreshing to see that there's other companies
Capable of porting over the old games
They did a pretty decent job, the high def graphics are really cleaned up
I mean, it looks nice for, you know, an arcade game that's 20 years old
So, it was alright, 5 bucks
Not bad
That's it, that's my gaming week
Miklotov, how about your gaming week?
Um, I played WoW a couple times
I'm level 56, so I have less of a life
Um, I also had the sudden interest
To start playing Bust A Move 2 again
Because I love that game
So I've been playing it like non-stop
And there's not like anything new I can do in it
Because I've already unlocked everybody, beaten it with every character
Always get the upper path
So, I don't know, it's just a little fun game to play I guess
Been slacking on Pokemon
Um, other than that
I don't think there are any video games I play
Hey, keep your cell phone off
Sorry, my cell phone went off
People forget I do this thing on Sunday night
And try to call me
Yes, and
I don't know, I guess
Kind of gaming related
I think I'm leaving Konami by the 4th of June
Okay
So hooray for me
Well, I mean, you'll finally be able to talk openly
About what you do during the day, that'll be nice
Oh, I can talk about it right now
I play Bust A Move 2 all day
That's pretty much what I do
I don't care
Alright, well there you go
There's no other games you've been working on by chance?
Sometimes I play Dance Summit
I kind of switch it out between the two
Bring that over, because I miss that game
Okay, I'll bring it next time, it's at work right now
I haven't played that in forever
And I've been trying to find a copy of it to buy
Good luck with that
I fell on eBay for 40 bucks
Oh, that's really cheap, that's definitely worth it
I'm looking actually right now to find a copy of Bust A Groove 1 US
Do you want to borrow mine?
No, I want one to own
I could probably sell you mine, because I have the Japanese ones
Oh really?
While you guys barter and trade over there
Jvmon says in chat
If Bust A Move 2 is on the Playstation 3 network
That would sell me a PS3
It would sell me one too
Or, you know what, if Squeenix decided to
Ever revisit that series
I don't care if they put a Final Fantasy
Character in it to ruin the game
I would still buy another one
I keep forgetting it was an Enix game
You don't think of that
You think of Squeenix, you think, oh, roleplaying games, roleplaying games
They don't do really anything else
I knew of Dragon Warrior, Quest, whatever
And I used to frequent the Enix boards
And I only hung out at the Bust A Groove section
That's all I knew Enix for
For the longest time
Well, I remember some of their old
Super Nintendo roleplaying games
Like Illusion of Gaia, Soul Blazer
Those were good games
An Act Racer was an Enix game, right?
I believe so
And then Square ruined them
SJ100Matt asks, what?
No Sweet Coden for you, Miklotov?
To play?
No, because
I guess, you know
I still care about the series
But after working on it
I kind of know everything that happens
In the last game
And I never even finished playing it
So it's like, there's nothing to surprise me
Is it kind of one of those things
Where like, you know
Maybe you're really excited
For many years to work at
I don't know, like let's say a
Taco Bell
Nobody's excited to work at Taco Bell
What the hell's wrong with you?
People are excited to work
At Great America, a theme park
People are really excited, they want to work at a theme park
And then when they get there and realize how everything
Really works, how the rides all function
And how the magic happens
Everything kind of loses its magic
Is it kind of like that, where now that you've been on the inside
There's no more?
No, it wasn't even that
It's just office politics go down
And then things completely change
And that's when it gets bad
Drama?
Drama, yes
Alright
Well speaking of drama
I want to get into some housekeeping this week
And this is a little atypical housekeeping for us
But we were asked by our buddies
Over at AllGames.com to relay the following announcement
Which is cool because
They have a live show on Monday nights
As well as Tuesday mornings over on AllGames.com
If you miss the live show on Sunday
You can always hear part A and B together on AllGames
And one of their other shows
The video game show, they had a little bit of drama
A couple weeks ago
And to make a long story short
A lot of folks think
That the show is gone
Because of something that someone on the show did
To the website and everything
And he's since apologized for it
I saw the apology and was basically like
I suck and I'm sorry
But a lot of people still think the show is gone
So AllGames is asking us
To put forward the video game show
They are not gone
They are still around
And they are now at www.videogameshow.net
So we know those of you who listen to Orange on the Radio
Probably listen to other independent video game podcasts
And we encourage you to do so
So if you're a fan of Chris Haas and Rich Bergen
They are now over at videogameshow.net
Check it out
Their show is moved over there
Also in housekeeping tonight
I wanted to mention real quick
Of course our FONOMAY appearance
Is going to be happening over Memorial Day weekend in San Jose
Saturday at 2pm
We hope to see you guys there
Speaking of FONOMAY conventions
We're going to talk about ACEN a little later tonight
Can I just say ACEN and the same thing?
What if I don't want to say ACEN?
Then no one will know what you're talking about
Jerks
Regardless, Chris called us
And we're going to hear her message a little bit later
Thank you to folks who've reviewed us recently
In iTunes
With 5 star reviews
I was looking at some of the more recent reviewers
And there's some awesome reviews
Some folks actually using some of the gags from our previous weeks
Somebody left a review that says
OLR the L stands for suck
That was pretty awesome
We just really want to thank you guys
Because we know probably every podcast you listen to
Says go vote for us here
Go leave us a review on iTunes
But it really really really does help
When you get more reviews
It gets you that exposure
When we first started the video game podcasting thing
A couple years ago
There was like maybe 10 shows at the most
So there wasn't much to pick from
That's how a lot of folks found us
But now there's like 10,000 video game podcasts
Out there
Because every freaking magazine has their own podcast
And every blog has a podcast
It's really tough to stand out sometimes
So we just kind of keep doing our thing
And hope people enjoy what we're doing
But we appreciate it when you guys help get the word out
So tell a friend
Leave us a review on iTunes
We do appreciate all of that
Alright enough blabber
Let's get into the gaming news
Who's going to start us off tonight?
Yes there's been a lot of news this week
Because everyone seems to think it's like E3 all over again
Because I mean hey about a year from now
Or a year ago we were pretty much at E3
I was just thinking of that
Bobby Blackwolf speaking of all games
Bobby Blackwolf had his birthday
I think it was yesterday
Happy birthday Bobby by the way
And that reminded me that
He had his birthday at E3 last year
So that was making me go
Shit it's been one year since E3
And it was kind of sad because E3
Sucks now
The E3 rave as we've been calling it
Because they're going to take you to an abandoned airport hangar
And unmarked vehicles will come pick you up
And escort you there
Don't worry though G4 will be there as their commercials say
Whoopee
One more reason I don't want to go to E3
But I do because
All the cool kids go
Except for G4
Well Jamie
Our very own
Jamie has an invite
And is basically saying
You know what I'm not going I'm too cool for this
I didn't say I wasn't going I just said I can't afford to go
Unless
Like the heavens open up and
God gives me money
We'll see
I have to get time off work too
I think you're just too cool for E3
I know
So because of that
There's been a whole bunch of announcements this week
Including some from Square Enix's
Own little party that they had
Celebrating the Final Fantasy
20th anniversary
And with that
A bunch of announcements for Final Fantasy games
And what not
Including a remake of Final Fantasy 4
Yes much like there was for the
Final Fantasy 3
Looks pretty sexy from what I've seen so far
Completely redone all 3D
Hooray
I don't know how I feel about this
Final Fantasy 4 is my favorite
Final Fantasy game
Mostly because it was the first one I ever really got into
And beat
So you know it's kind of weird to watch
That get changed into this whole new
3D thing
I think it looks good
I probably love it but you know
It's like somebody is messing with your baby
I hope it just doesn't turn out as bad
As Final Fantasy 3 did for the DS
Because that was no fun
You didn't like it? No
But did you like the original Nintendo one? Did you ever play it?
Like translation or anything?
Maybe I think so a little bit
The third one was great
It's kind of slow
I had fun with it
It's not slow in the story sense even though it is
Everything just seems really slow
In that game
I don't know it's not that fun
Well that's your opinion
I think it looks good
I think they needed to be doing
More of this on the PSP
That's for sure because
It's kind of lacking
But yeah keep it up
I want to see Final Fantasy 6 redone
As well
I'm looking at chat for comments here
JVMON agrees with you Miklotov
Final Fantasy 3 for the DS was boring as hell
I think Final Fantasy 3 DS was good
RasteelUT says Final Fantasy 4 DS was uber milkage
Let's see
SSJ100Matt says
I really want them to remake 5
Sephiroth1215 says 4
What was so great about 4? 5 and 6 are so much better
I can't explain the allure of 4
Sephiroth1215
Other than really the fact that it's the first one
I really played
I played the original one on NES
This is the first one I played all the way through
And it really just had a moving story
I think Final Fantasy 4 was really the first one
For me
Since we kind of missed most of the NES ones over here
I think it was really the first one for me
That had such a moving story
And the orchestral
The spoonie bard
Yeah and it had the spoonie bard
And dear god
Mark my words
If Final Fantasy 4 DS did not keep the spoonie bard lingo intact
Instant fail
On Square Enix's part
I will pick it
Screw that up
Give me my spoonie bard
It looks nice
At least it's not just a straight port
At least they're doing something with it
So
That's good
I'll give them that
I'm actually thinking I'm going to get that one
Because it was one of my favorites too
But I would prefer 5
The reason I liked 3 was because of the job change system
Gamezoo time
I was going to say if this sells well
What happens next right?
Let's hope so
Well at any rate there's some good news for our UK listeners
For anyone who is interested in SNK vs Capcom
Card fighters
For the DS
The little problem that was going on in the 9th level of the game
We were having this issue
Where if you
Fought the opponent
John you didn't get the card so you couldn't finish the game
That is being
Corrected for the UK release
And also
For our American listeners
SNK has offered
To replace all of your copies
It does though take up to 6 weeks
For your replacements to arrive
Aw we gotta actually do something
Instead of just re-releasing
Stuff what the hell
Making us work now? Seriously
I'm actually a victim
Of that
Not that I like card games or anything
I only bought it because it has Phoenix Wright stuff in it
So I'm not actually going to get rid of my copy
Because it's only on the new game plus
So take that
SNK
You're not getting my cartridge back
To be fair though they do have a new
Arcade game that's going to be
Coming out
Not that we really care
What Capcom vs SNK?
No SNK has actually got a new
King of Fighters
Sorry I lost interest in that series a while ago
But I liked Capcom vs SNK
That was kinda cool
A lot of fighting games but I liked Capcom vs SNK
My vs Chun-Li awesome
Epic
Well anyway speaking of epic
Loki and I were addicted
For many many many many
Many years to Final Fantasy 11
Actually not that many years
Oh yeah Miklata was addicted too
And it's your fucking fault
I went back like 2
How long ago was it? About 6 months ago?
That we went back when the 360 version came out?
Yeah and we played for like maybe a month
You bastard
Well Final Fantasy 11 fans
Those of you that have stuck with the game
You troopers you
Good news for you guys there's a brand new add on coming out
It's Wings of the Goddess
This was announced at
Square Enix Party 07
And there was a little trailer that went with it
I watched the trailer
I was not impressed because half of it was recycled footage
From all the expansions that are already out
Like the original opening movie
That's like 5 years old right?
And then the rest of it
I get was pretty much like
Miklata picked this out I didn't even pick this out
This looks the exact same as the areas that are already in there
Miklata was like oh yeah it's the areas
Like before
The game takes place because I guess this
Wings of the Goddess is some type of like
Prequel-ish thing or a time travel thing
Where you go back to the past
It's basically going back to the actual
Was it the war or whatever that they had?
The Crystal War
You know this is just an
Excuse to introduce a time mage class
That's what I think
Interesting theory. Are you going to go back to the game?
When this comes out?
Probably for a week
Well I went back every other time a new expansion came out
I'm not going to stop
It's just I won't play it much and then I'll be like
I'm too low of a level to do anything in the new area
And I just want to go get the new job classes
Just hold off
They're making a new fucking role playing game anyways
Seriously
Just as a friendly reminder
I'd like to go around and remind everybody
Why we quit Final Fantasy 11
Because there's probably some fans of the game who listen to the program going
You guys are so mean to Final Fantasy 11
I play this game
Okay we played this game between us all
We probably played this game for many many many years
Jamie why'd you quit?
I played for six months
And it was because the white mage is the party bitch
And I like playing white mages
So fuck everybody in that game
Loki why'd you quit?
I quit because I had a girlfriend and a wife
That became a wife
At the same time?
That's amazing
No that would not be fun
So I couldn't play it as often as I'd like to
And there was a big six month span
Where I didn't actually play at all
And it's just paying that kind of money each month
Even though it's 13 or 12 bucks
It's still money that's being wasted
I mean hell
If I was still single
Not seeing anybody
I'd probably still be playing it
Because it was fun
I had fun with it
But it's just you get to a point though
You work so hard in the game
And then it's just
You know you get in stupid parties
And the whole fact that you have to party with people
Really kind of sucks
I know it's an MMO
And you're supposed to party with people
But the fact that they force you to party
When you can't find a party
I mean that kind of fucking sucks
You go on the play
And you can't do anything
So that was lame
Well the main reason probably
Is that whole XP loss
When you die
But most recently it was because
Getting blue mage spells sucked sometimes
And me and
One of my friends in the game
We spent all night
Hours and hours trying to get this one spell
Never got it
So I was like screw this game I'm done
And the reason I did it was because
Squeenix did nothing about the gold farmers
For far too long and the economy in that game
Was fucked
And people were telling me to actually buy
Gill and I was like that's where I draw the line
Is spending that type of real world money
To buy fake money online
Just because you know
These people who are being paid
To sit here and camp these monsters
Are getting stuff before me
People were so elitist that if you didn't have these items
It's like you suck in parties
Even I had my elitist
Plus one everything
Fucking bard character
And I got nothing
No parties out of that
Alright so there you go
Plus everything charisma and all that stuff
What?
I was just going to say it's like
They want you to party in that game
But people have in their minds
The ideal party setup and if you don't fit that
Your job or anything then what's the point
Because you're not going to get a party
At least back when I played
And you know your job is worthless then
Heaven help you if you're a paladin who doesn't sub warrior
Yeah you have to have the right sub jobs too
So boo on you
Final Fantasy 11 boo
Let's see looking at the
Comments in the chat room here
RawsteelUT says healers are the party bitch
In every MMO
Let's see
Sephiroth1215 says I never liked Final Fantasy 11
But it does get addicting
Somehow when I stopped myself before I was an addict
ShadowFitSlayer says
Tetra Master is greater than Final Fantasy 11
Boo
Tetra Master was kind of fun
No it wasn't
I played my free month of Tetra Master
I had fun
It was fun for about 5 minutes
That's a very good idea actually Loki
Loki says put that on Xbox Live Arcade
Yes and no one will play it
Shut up I play it once
New story please
Anyways
I don't have time for me to read but
Parasite Eve 3 is apparently going to be
a cell phone title
You know obviously in Japan
where cell phone titles are more popular
You know it's not a big surprise
But over here though
I would hope that maybe a next gen version
of Parasite Eve because I like that series
I thought it was pretty good
Although then again I never did play the second one
But this was announced over at the Square Enix party
I don't know
Kind of disappointing
Hopefully you know
You know what they kind of tend to do with these kind of things
They'll port it over to the PSP or something
Later on
Here's hoping for a PSP version
PSP version would be hot though
RosteelUT who I'm quoting a lot tonight
But he's saying a lot of stuff here
I'm not going to tell him to shut up
He's saying a lot of good stuff here
Heartbreaks as he hears
PE3 is a cell phone title
I'm sure that's how most people feel
About that news
Because everybody was kind of waiting for
Parasite Eve 3 on Playstation 2
And then it just never happened
Well at least you know
Maybe they translate the book for us
Some of us who wants to read it can
I saw the Japanese movie and that was awesome
I've got it somewhere but my friends read the book
Like five times and keep telling me how awesome the book is
Ew, reading
Shut up
I like the book so I get the good story
Anyway
Well there is actually a bit of happiness
That came out of the Tokyo Game Show
And that was an announcement for
Kingdom Hearts
Well it's going to happen at the Tokyo Game Show
Still a few months off
Well that's what I said isn't it
No you said some announcement
It's coming out of the
Ok whatever
Pardon my context
Anyway it's going to be announced
At the Tokyo Game Show
So
I'm just sick of announcements of announcements
We have an announcement to make
We're going to make an announcement later
I completely refrain from here on out
To make announcements of announcements
You know what
It is an amazing trend within this industry
Is that hey stay tuned
For a really big announcement about
Something we're going to be announcing very soon
It's like
Shut up and make a game
Shut up and go make the game
Anyhow
Any hopes for what they're going to be announcing
Dark Sakura
Kingdom Hearts 3 maybe
Or do you think it's going to be like
Kingdom Hearts MMO
There's not going to be any way they can do a
Kingdom Hearts minus Disney
Then it won't be good
Let's see
Hostile1 in chat says
Please please please
Kingdom Hearts for 360
Save me the $600 for the Playstation 3
Except it's minus Disney and with
Hanna-Barbera instead
Yabba Dabba Doo
That'd be so horrible
Oh hooray I have Quick Draw McGraw in my party
And Droopy Dog
Oh but
Wow
Hey but Jetsons world would be pretty awesome
What do you think of that Jamie
Kingdom Hearts with minus the Disney plus
The Hanna-Barbera
They should do
Plus Warner Brothers
So we get the Animaniacs
Was that Johnny Quest 2?
Yeah that was Hanna-Barbera
Was it?
But then again that would also give us C-Lab
It could be worse they could do Kingdom Hearts 3 with
Adult Swim
I guess that's true
Kingdom Hearts with Robot Chicken
Let's talk about some games we know are coming out
We're going to do some release dates real quick here
I'm going to start off with Japanese
release dates and again it's been kind of
a slow month over there in Japan
There's not a whole lot of stuff coming out
But on the Nintendo Wii they are getting Marvel
Ultimate Alliance in Japan
So the Japanese version coming out from
Inter Channel
Also they're getting a game on the 17th of May called
Detective Conan
Suyoku no Gensu
You're yaying that I don't even know what the hell that is
Give me the top microphone
There is this show
on Adult Swim a long time ago
Case closed
It's just like this little kid who solves
Detective Conan
Here it was case closed
He just solves
crimes and stuff and if you like detective
things it's really cool
I like detective things so it's pretty awesome
I want that to come out here even though I'm not a fan
of anime whatsoever
On the Playstation 2
you get Shining Wind from Sega
on the 17th as well as Odin Sphere
coming out over there
I think that's about it
Let me see if there's anything on the DS real quick
You do get
Custom Beat Battle
Draglade is coming out
Oh and then of course Oh and Dan 2
I suppose that's important is also coming out this week
in Japan
Elite Beat Agents some of you know that here
You pre-ordered that didn't you Shane?
You pre-ordered it and you got
next day shipping or something right?
My shipping costs about the same as the game
because I care that much
to have it that early
I've watched that stupid demo that they put up on
YouTube from the download kiosks
in Japan a million times
and I watched the TouchDS
.JP videos a million times
I'm so excited
I don't know any of the songs except for one
So you spent like $80 on this game?
I would say closer to $90
Wow
I do want to say actually
one other game because I actually went and looked at the
PC and Macintosh releases
coming out and Korea
you know we don't talk a whole lot about what goes on
in Korea but they are getting a game
that's worth mentioning here this is my favorite title
of the week an adventure game for the PC called
Princess Maker 5
Princess Maker 5 coming out
in Korea looks like fun
in this game you get to it looks like make
princesses go figure
see there's all their little stats
in Korean which I don't understand
any of yeah it looks cute
looks all like chibi
looks like fun I want to play Princess Maker
they do make good MMOs
I can't knock the Korean developers
there you go
okay dancing games
well didn't Korea
wasn't the easy to
DJ series out of
Korea? yeah it was all Korea
okay well then they fucking rock music games too
anyways the US
it's not entirely exciting but there are
some things coming out
of the non-exciting
like the third is finally making its way out
same day as the movie
hurrah
but if you're not into really crappy games
then you might be interested in Dawn of Mana
which is going to be coming out this week on Playstation 2
that one looks pretty good
that's happy
also if you're interested in SNK
re-releases Art of Fighting
Anthology will be making its way out
on the PS2 luckily though
it's only $14.99
so it's a chibi
it's a mana game on Playstation 1
Secret of Mana?
Legend of Mana is one of the most disappointing
games I've ever played in my entire fucking life
try playing it in Japanese
oh that's just salt in the wound
right there cause that game
I'm sorry it sucked
it wasn't, if they would go back
okay what you should do
get an emulator and play the translation
of Seiken Densetsu 3
it's fucking beautiful
we need to have a game be like that
virtual console, hello maybe someday
but yeah I'm just saying that cause
Dawn of Mana, I don't know
approach with caution
if you haven't bought Marvel Ultimate Alliance yet
on the 360
and you're thinking about doing it
you definitely want to pick up Marvel Ultimate Alliance Gold
which is coming out this week as well
it's basically the same game
with the download codes for the extra characters
so that's pretty awesome
Innocent Life
a futuristic harvest moon
PSP this week
don't let that fool you it's exactly the same damn game
all over again
and let's see here
Etrion Odyssey
some RPG game coming out on
the DS and then
of course if you're a baseball fan
MLB 07 the show on Playstation 3
and then finally the rounded up
really strange game Touch the Dead
and that's coming out on the DS
think House of the Dead on the DS
I want to touch the dead
that sounds kind of kinky
and of course
last few things here
I was going to say on PC
is there anything interesting coming out
Resident Evil 4 is coming out on PC I guess
or doing a re-release of that
Nanny Mania
Nanny Mania?
is that like Diner Dash but with babies?
I don't know but
Nanny Mania
you know what that has me thinking of
mama mama mama mama mama
I love that stage
it makes me think of Super Nanny
on TV or Nanny
911 whatever those shows are
and then I was going to say
Naruto Ninja Council 3
is also coming out on the DS
I don't know how many Naruto fans are out there
too damn many
the Rob D in chat is picking a fight
with Loki here why does Loki hate
sequels?
and why is he not hating on MLB
Super 7 which is a giant rehash itself
I didn't say I didn't hate it
I said if you like
baseball what was I
hating on sequels for I said Shrek the 3rd
sucks I mean
Shrek the 3rd I mean obviously the games gonna suck
if it's Shrek the 1st it's still gonna suck
no we want more Shrek
go karts
I wasn't hating on anything
when did I hate on a sequel when I was talking there
there wasn't any sequels I hated on
except for oh Art of Fighting Anthology
because that's not a sequel it's just a re-release
the Rob D admits I'm mostly stirring up trouble
drama
well done drama
so well we have UK
releases like
on the 15th we have Freestyle
Street Basketball
for PC
and then everything else is Sony
we have Innocent Life
Legend of the Dragon and SoCom
US Navy Seals
Bravo 2 on PSP
and on Playstation 2 we have SoCom
US Navy Seals Combined Assault
and that's it
awesome
alright well let's get back into
some news talking about upcoming
releases Rock Band
is rumored to be coming out on the Wii
lots and lots of rumors going
around about this this week
apparently it's because
there's focus group testing going
on they've been testing with focus group
MTV's been asking about
packaging and pricing like how much would you pay
and then the Wii was also
one of the systems that they
said the game would be coming on of course Rock Band
coming from Harmonics who made
Guitar Hero but this is a joint
venture between Harmonics, EA and
MTV well of course MTV
owns Harmonics so you gotta state that
but that's of course going to be the game that has not
just the guitar but the drums and the singing
all in one so that should be very interesting
by the way during this
focus group the group was asked
what they would think about a bundle including
the game, a wireless guitar, a drum kit
and a microphone for
$200 didn't
go over well with the group
$175 went over a little
better $150 was when everybody
in the group got on board but that would be
pushing it for all it's stuff
it's supposed to be an actual drum set
can you imagine how big this box
is gonna be?
where the fuck am I gonna put that in my shit hole apartment?
I mean I'm just
what college dorm is
gonna fit that?
it's a cool concept for a game but you know
this is why they didn't have any arcade style
you know drum mania controllers
or anything you know they left it at
Guitar Freaks
said okay those controllers are big enough
we don't need to bring the huge fucking drum set
do you remember when we were younger
like in junior high or whatever
they had those drum sticks
that you could just hit anywhere in the air
they had a little speaker I think they were called
like hit sticks or something and you could play the drums
and the little crappy speaker that was attached
to them would go
like you could just wave the drums in the air
there was like $10 that could be the controller
you remember back in the day when I had the actual
cabinet and everything and I was talking
about how I was gonna make actual drums
you know a drum set for guitar
or Guitar Freaks drum mania
yeah I'm glad I didn't do that
for real Blaze says
those still exist I'll be damned
DJ Dark Knight says I had one
I think a lot of us had one
those things are pretty rad
did you have one of those Mikl Tov I see you nodding your head over there
my cousins didn't
I wasn't allowed to play with them because I was really little
but yeah
they were really awesome looking at the time
and kind of stupid though now that I think about it
they were pretty stupid in retrospect
but I'm thinking those were cheap
and they didn't take up any space at all
it's pretty awesome
I don't know I think this is getting a little crazy
with your obsession with music games
I mean the thing with Guitar
Hero I mean
$80 I almost said Guitar Freaks
$80 is a really
big investment I think for a game
and a $200
investment in a game you better hope this game
is fucking awesome because otherwise
you're gonna be fucking pissed
so I mean besides
if you wanna buy you know Rock Band
boy do we have a game for you the Eye of Judgment
it too will have a lot of
extra crap and it'll probably be expensive
great
anyways another game though
that's scheduled to be coming or rumored to be coming
out on another system would be
Table Tennis for the Wii Rockstar's Table Tennis
that is of course it's gonna be
scaled down graphically but hey
it's Table Tennis on the Wii
because everybody likes Wii Tennis so
of course this is gonna do well
right
how would that work because I seem to remember
I mean the gameplay mechanics would have to be
completely different if I'm not
mistaking well maybe not
because I seem to remember I haven't played Table Tennis
in a while but I seem to remember like you had to
look very carefully at the ball
to see what color it was glowing
cause that was showing you the type of spin that was on
the ball and that was very important for
how you could respond to that
better you know defeat your opponent
was to you know counter with the appropriate
type of spin how would you do that with the
Wiimote would you just have to use the 1 and 2 buttons or
the D-pad or something I don't know
here's what I've been thinking
people think because
people liked Wii Sports cause it was a
packing title and everybody loves the games that came
with it and stuff that
people would want to buy a game that does
exactly the same thing for more money
that's why I didn't understand I mean
Tennis itself yeah it was fun
you know bringing it out and people
come over and stuff like that I wouldn't buy a
Tennis game though just because I like playing
Wii Tennis but like fuck that shit I've got
a free game right here why would I buy another game
I'm reading chat room and there's some
comments on the previous story about Rock Band
GS68 wrote in all
caps Drummania is a blatant
rip off of Rock Band with crappy
Jap Techno and timing judgments and
cheats aka speed mods
you know and that's exactly how
X-Play will probably review it if the
game comes out next year from Konami for whatever
crazy reason
although they'll say that it came out they'll acknowledge
the fact that it came out but they'll say that
it's improved on it because this actually
teaches you how to play drums
to be honest though out of all the Bomani
series I think that's the only one that taught you how to do
something you know
it was pretty much closest to
Keyboardmania you could actually take
the real version in Keyboardmania
play them on a real keyboard and it would sound very similar
very similar
unless you played them easy like I did
well then you'd get something that sounded
kind of close
well I mean still though those games
it was pretty good it's like I saw you know for example
Lankystyle you know I saw him
start off on you know that I don't know if he was a drummer
beforehand but you know he got
pretty good by the end I mean and I've seen people
that just start playing Drummania and then you know you see
them about a year later they're just
busting out like a real drummer so I don't know
it does well and I've learned this
as a musician that half of playing
is you know the more you do it
it comes to a point where
you're you build the instinct
for it your hands will know what to do
you know that's what got me through
through band is that after a while
you train yourself to know how to do these
things so you know it's the same thing
JVMON has another interesting point in chat
ParaparaParadise taught Parapara
dancing sorta
but I remember when that game first
came out and people over here didn't know that it was
based off like the Japanese thing like people
used to rave on that like remember that one guy who used to do
all his like crazy rave dancing
that was funny
I'm gonna hang my head down now
did you do that too?
yes with your glow sticks
no
but I remember we'd get everybody
shadowing and that was great
especially when we ate the sign that said no shadowing
I wondered if it did that
that's right Golfland dared
to put a sign on the machine that said no
shadowing and we got a picture
of somebody eating it Rick ate it
we got a guy we said
this rule sucks and we
dared Rick to eat the sign so he did
he tore the sign off the machine and I'm not
kidding he fucking ate it
good times
and then we all shadowed
in defiance of Golfland's
neo-nazi policies
in Rick's defense I mean this is
the guy that didn't have like the challenges that they would
do where they would like either
I don't remember if they sniffed a whole bunch of
cinnamon or ate a whole bunch of cinnamon
some weird shit like that drinking a gallon
of milk you know that kind of weird crazy
shit so
GS68
has a great idea for a macro
if I could find that picture I know there's a
picture that exists with Rick with half
a sign in his mouth
I made you a sign but I eat it
cat macro that's beautiful
winner GS68
chatter of the evening congratulations
yeah you win a no prize
so I've got some fun news
you know one of my favorite games ever
is Soul Calibur right and I've told you
about Rod Calibur haven't I
using the fishing thing when you play it on Dreamcast
use the fishing rod to play Soul Calibur it's
hilarious I've also tried doing it with the
Dreamcast dance pads and the only
analog on there is the Konami symbol
but Rod Calibur
is the most fun I always thought Rod Calibur
was a different game I played with my Rod
you know what Rod let me finish the story
okay well now
and I think
that this is beautiful because
in my brain it's an homage to Rod
Calibur is Soul Calibur
Legends is coming out on the Wii
and
it's going to be using the
Nunchuck and the
Wiimote so I'm just seeing
Rod Calibur all over again
but you know what's fucking awesome about the game though
it's kind of like a beat
em up game except hopefully it's not
going to be like was that that
Tekken game with
what's-her-name Death by the Greaves
yeah hope it's not like that
maybe it's like the Tekken force mode from
Tekken 3 so Jamie to sum up
I will soon be able to play Rod
Calibur with my Wii yes
Rod Calibur with your Wii
fabulous right and
if anybody still has a Dreamcast and Soul Calibur
just you should try Rod Calibur if you never
have
alright well you know
I just want to mention real quick sure
there will be some fishing games coming out in
the fall for the Wii that actually have
a fishing rod controller therefore
Rod Calibur
for a whole other generation
well one person that won't be
playing Soul Calibur on the Wii
anytime soon or any derivative of the
game is this guy who emailed
Kotaku earlier this week and
this was a story here I'm just going to quote this story
from a Kotaku article here
buying a Wii was a big deal for me
seeing those 250 hard-earned dollars
and some change go flying from her hand
and into the water was painful
we would probably be together right now
if she had not thrown out my beloved Wii
but alas you can't talk a crazy woman
out of an idea of such magnitude
yes this guy's wife took
the Wii and threw it into a lake
during a heated argument
anyway and he goes on to say anyways
divorce is imminent I'm talking
to a lawyer tomorrow to get the process
started I'm not divorcing her just
because of the Wii throwing but that's the rather
large straw that broke
the Drome Dairy's back
I would have thrown
her right after that
throw her in the river
go get my Wii
what would you do if Nelly threw your Wii into the lake
I'd be pissed
would you file papers
I'd buy another one
buy another one? buy two? just piss her off
maybe
spend savings
there you go
GS68 says too bad the woman's going to win 100%
Craven's Dolphin says I'm with Loki
alright well there you have it
anyways
I don't know this
sounds pretty cool
last game that came out I know like this
the Rygar game
on Playstation 2 was pretty awesome
now they're doing Project Rygar for the Wii
and of course it's going to be
a brand new game exclusively
for the Wii and
no real details about that
except it's supposed to have
new characters, new enemies, new weapons, yada yada yada
but
one of the announcements from
Tecmo's party
that they did because everyone was having their
gamer's day or Tecmo's
night out 07
I don't know they have a pretty cool piece of
artwork that's the only bit of info
from the game so far
looks pretty guilty gear-ish actually
interesting
you know I never played the
Rygar game on Playstation 2 I somehow missed it
but I did enjoy the old NES one
that's like one of my favorite 8-bit games ever
even if it was really different from the arcade
well know what?
then probably when this game gets closer to coming out
Virtual Console
yeah that's pretty exciting
if I remember right the 8-bit one had no save feature
or password or anything
so you had to play it all in one sitting which sucked
but now with the Virtual Console
not a problem anymore
very exciting I hope that does come out
pretty cool
well speaking of Virtual Console
I do have the list for our UK listeners
and
that is released so far
Ninja Spirit
which was a TurboGrafx game
and also
NES Open Tournament Golf
I think that's it
wow sucks to be in the UK
because neither of those games really are that good to me
Ninja Spirit was a good game
I vaguely remember it
I think I played it once
Golf was more like crap
didn't it come out kind of in response to
Ninja Gaiden
which did really well on the NES
that's how a lot of TurboGrafx games were
where's Shadow Dancer?
it could have been Shadow Dancer because Shadow Dancer had the dog
I know but where's Shadow Dancer?
I know!
or Moonwalker I mean come on
it's so bad I mean it's such a bad movie
well it was a bad movie and a bad game
but the bar scene
the bar level in Moonwalker was pretty fun
because you do the leaning thing in advance
and all that was cool
D.Vay has a Mother's Day message in chat here
my mom rocked at Ninja Spirit
for some reason
don't know why I bought it
my mom never really played video games at all
I couldn't get her to play anything
so I don't know that whole experience
of walking in and your mom or your dad
is playing a video game of yours
Mom what are you doing?
oh I'm just beating the level 3 boss
anyhow
now one game that came out on the Virtual Console
not that long ago that was pretty exciting
was Tecmo Bowl
even if they did make some changes to it
to remove players names and stuff
but people were excited to see Tecmo Bowl make a return
and hey
that return might be forthcoming
like even bigger
because Tecmo has announced
that they have plans to revive
the Tecmo Bowl franchise
in 2008
Tecmo will be joining up with Visual Concepts
to make a new version of Tecmo Bowl
now note there is no NFL licenses
going on here but who cares
Tecmo Bowl was just fun
and actually I don't talk a lot about
sports games on the program because I don't get into
a whole lot of them but
Tecmo Bowl was one of the few sports games
I really really got into on the NES
because back then sports games were so simple
that you didn't really have to be
a professor of the sport to do well
at them
so I'm pretty excited that Tecmo Bowl
is re-coming out
except the weird thing about it is that they're not saying
what system it's coming out on
they're just saying
I can't tell you what platform we're making it for
but I can tell you
that it's probably not going to be on the platform
that you're expecting if that makes any sense
and I actually have no idea
what that means
does that mean Xbox Live Arcade?
I actually have a cell phone, Tecmo Bowl
I actually downloaded Tecmo Bowl to my cell phone
about a year ago and was very disappointed
actually they're not working with Visual Concepts
it's a little play on there
they're saying they
join Visual Concepts because Visual Concepts
is doing that All Pro 2K8 or whatever
and
basically they're comparing them because they don't
have the NFL license as well
so it looks like Tecmo is
going to be developing it by themselves
or at least with an unnamed developer
I'm going to guess that it's the N-Gage
that they're working on
because they are doing that whole
N-Gage 3 relaunch thing
or whatever so
that's the system I least expect it on
How about the
Atari 2600? That's the system
I would least expect it on
What about Virtual Console?
Nope, we already have Tecmo Bowl
on Virtual Console, kinda
Yeah, a new one though, you wouldn't expect that
Oh that'd be cool, but you know the weird thing is
it had this Tecmo Collection
or something like that, it was called
I don't remember, like a Tecmo Collection
that came out on Xbox and it had the old
arcade version of Tecmo Bowl on it
not nearly as fun as the NES one
and I realize a lot of people kinda only
know that as the Tecmo Bowl, but it was kinda
clunky to me
it didn't have that fast pacedness that the
NES one had, so there you go
Anyways
some interesting
stuff, another thing that was announced over
in
during the Square Enix
little Final Fantasy party there was that
they're gonna be bringing Chocobo Dungeon
to
actually to the Wii
exclusively, which is kinda neat
so that'll be kinda cool I guess
with, aren't they having the new
I wanna say they had Dragon Quest
Swords as well coming out
lots of stuff
for the Wii, lots of Wii love
good
I don't remember if any news about this
made our show roll, but isn't there information
as well about Crystal Chronicles that came out
of the event?
I know that they're in the DS
version, I think they may have
announced a date for that
Wasn't the Wii one supposed to be a launch title?
Maybe, maybe in Japan
but I know that
I distinctly remember seeing some type of
Crystal Chronicles stuff in
like, some of the early press things
for the Wii, like it was an early launch title
They announced, what was it, the DS version is gonna
be coming to Japan on August 23rd
that was the announcement that
I believe was there, I don't know about the Wii
version at all, I don't think there was anything
announced there
Alright
well, I don't know, are you excited about
Chocobo Dungeon on the Wii?
Nope, don't care, I couldn't give a crap when the DS
version came out, especially
didn't give a crap for the Japanese one
but uh
I don't know
Miklotov, have you ever played the Chocobo Dungeon games?
Are you excited about this new
Wii one at all?
No, but I'm excited about Crystal Chronicles
I'm very excited, because me and my friends
played the GameCube one a whole bunch
we never beat it, but we had a really good time
with it, because we had all the Game Boy
advances linked up, and it was just a really good
time, and I expect that the DS one will be
probably a little more fun
RossdielUT
says in chat, will Crystal Chronicles
require 4 DS's for multiplayer?
Of course
I hope not
You're going to have people share the DS
when they're playing, if it's just
the DS version, everybody's going to
need a copy and a DS to play
Is that maybe one reason that they've kind of
held off on putting this out on the Wii?
Is because there
hasn't really been a game that has the DS connectivity
yet, so they're waiting?
Probably, but I would really like them
to do a Wii one already, and the
DS one. Bring it square
Enix. So even though the
story was about Chocobo Dungeon, we couldn't help
throwing a little bit of Crystal Chronicles in there
Because we talked about a good game instead
Well there you have it
We have potential for something to be relatively
good
They are doing, actually
a Final Fantasy sort of
fighting game
Ergize 2?
Final Fantasy
Cecidia
And it's looking like it's going to be
more like a
a big
it sort of looks like it's more of a big
I'm sorry, the only thing I can really
think of looking at this is like
a sort of like
level of Power Stone, I think
you know, with the big levels and all that
just with versus
you know, versus each other's characters, but it looks like we've got
some Final Fantasy
9, some
7, 8
and I think 12
thrown in, yeah
Is this just
an excuse to give the fangirls
their Cloud X, Tidus
stories?
No, because Steffi is my bishie
Yeah
Wow, you're lame
Just kidding, hearts
I was a squall fangirl
Well now, if this ends up
being what the game is all about, you could have all
of those guys battling it out
I know, it's great
Alright, anyhow
Shadows Fits Lair in chat says
Super Smash Brothers Final Fantasy edition
Maybe, maybe
Alright, well one thing I should mention
is that Star Ocean 1
and 2 are being made
for the PSP
Of course, you know, it seems like Square's kind of getting
big on the remakes for PSP lately because
you know, of course Final Fantasy
that's there and then of course they did the
redone version of Tactics or whatever
So Square's been showing the PSP
a lot of love lately and they are continuing
Star Ocean 1 and 2
You may remember these games were originally on the Super Nintendo
and the Playstation 1, but now they are going to be coming
to the PSP. By the way
if you would like a new Star Ocean game
Star Ocean 4 is
confirmed to be under development and
will be coming out soon
but they haven't exactly said which
platform it's going to be coming out
to yet, I believe
Well, people
are assuming it's PS3 and Xbox 360
and most people are assuming it has to be
Playstation 3 because all the other games were
on the Sony platforms, but
you know, anything's possible, especially with
Square. They've jumped ship before
to other systems. I mean, hello, Dragon Quest
going to DS. Who would have thought
that was going to happen? Well, there you go
Well, I was thinking
It says
it was officially announced for next gen
consoles, so
Well, technically, I don't know
Again,
though, you can assume
it's the Playstation, but then they'll make a surprise
jump to Wii, you never know
There you go
Anyways
So, of more
I hate to sound like a broken record, but
more rumors
regarding the PSP getting a redesign
One, I had to laugh
at when I saw this story. There's a rumor
that the PSPs are going to be
now being shipped
with
with firmwares
with downloadable
prevention
Right
Like all the other ones
had it so you can download
I'm sorry, I don't think they're going to have it
where you can enable it not
to be able to be downgraded
But they're going to try, apparently
That's the rumor
So wait, what exactly are they blocking? You can't
download anything? What? No, they're downgradable
They're going to make it so you can't downgrade the
firmware. I don't see how that's going to happen
Well, don't they say that every other time
they release a patch? Yes
So, anyways
They're basically, that's the rumor
It's supposed to be happening
They said all new PSPs
shipping out as of next Friday
which is May 18th
will be a higher firmware
4 point something
It says they promised
to include, and this is coming from
a
EB Games regional manager
in Canada
So I don't know how much you can believe that
But anyways
What are you trying to say about Canada?
I'm trying to say something about EB
But basically, here's what they're saying
Sony was sending out emails to its commercial
retailers that all new PSPs
will be
sent out with
downgradable
prevention built right into them
All new PSPs will be shipped out
as of next week, Friday, May 18th
will be a higher firmware
4.XX
Specifics not released, it says
But they were promised to include new security features
to prevent hacks and downgrades
Apparently this will be
one of the first steps to start focusing
on the PSP again instead of diverting
all the attention to the PS3
I'll believe it when I see it
Isn't this just a challenge to hackers?
Yes, it is
It's not going to happen
At this point, no
It's not when they said
Blu-ray and HD DVD is uncrackable
and then the code is all over the front page of DIG
Let's just say
for example, if they do release this
firmware, whatever, that's for new
PSPs. There's a lot of them out there
right now that do not have that
So, big deal
That's about the equivalent of them
changing the $5 bill to a new
version that can't be counterfeited
but the old ones are still in circulation
and still being used, so
It's kind of dumb
Anywho, the other
of course, rumor that we've talked about before
is saying that a new PSP
redesign is going to become
and it'll be smaller
and a lighter weight version of
the handheld device
No release date
No price point
and no other info on that
It's a big, fat rumor
but I think people are thinking that it's going to happen
since, I don't know
that they haven't muggied with it yet
and that they can't do that with all their console systems
Alright
Well, we're going to get to a segment here
we like to do every week on the program
That is DarkSakura's website of the week
because DarkSakura likes to surf the internet
all back and forth
and around and through and find a website
that she wants to share with you
DarkSakura, where should the kids
be pointing their web browsers this week?
The website of the week is
MyCatHatesYou.com
and this is
a
big, massive collection
of pissed off cats
It's beautiful
It's just lovely
That's all it is, is pictures of angry cats
Pretty much
Our cat is doing naughty bad things
There's this one cat
The first thing is this cat
with a leather jacket on it
and a big cat looking all bad ass
It's also one of those bald cats
Interesting
There's also one of the black and white cats
by a thing that's already used
MyCatHatesYou.com
Your cat doesn't really hate me
though, right DarkSakura?
My cat doesn't hate anybody, she just looks offended
Alright, here you go
Alright, well one more
story for you for this segment
this part of Orange Lounge Radio
and that's about some homebrew
that's being made for the DS
This is
I don't know exactly how to
describe this game
I kind of look at it like a
puzzle type game, but the game is called
Virus DX
It's a puzzle game
but this puzzle game has hot anime
nurses with it
and I'm assuming they must get
naked if you do good
because this is being called
Triple X homebrew
available on the Nintendo DS
That's not all, they have strip rock
paper scissors, tickle girl and
teenage queen NDS
Yes, lots of fun stuff there
I like tickle girl, what's tickle girl about?
I'm thinking about buying stuff too
Wow, you actually see a picture
of a girl on the bottom screen there
and if you tickle her
with your stylus you can see her reaction
on the top screen and it will
utilize full motion video sampled
audio and looping background music
and
they're saying if you liked Feel
the Magic, you'll love this
Wow
I want to see strip rock
paper scissors
That's
like when you're trying to convince
someone to play strip poker with you
and they're like, but I don't know how to
play poker, so you say, okay
let's play strip high card
All it is is it's basically a rock
paper scissor and then they have
porn pictures that they've taken off
a website that's in a series or something
Why bother with the game, seriously?
Why not just have
DS porno?
Why bother?
I guess that's true too
But this is homebrew
this you can get for free, right?
Whereas the browser costs like 50 bucks
Actually, Teenage Queen
NDS is actually
pretty, it's all hand drawn
animation, that's kind of neat
It's a poker game, it looks like
Yeah, but that's
probably about as good as strip poker was
on the Commodore 64
Yeah
It's all about Custer's Revenge
Dude, it's all
about, you know, fucking
putting some more adult
games, what the fuck is that one game
that needs to play all the time?
Gals panic! They need to put gals panic on there
Oh, I thought the guy game
Where they would have the contest
between the women, like the video sequences
that you'd unlock
They have that now in Girls Gone Wild
It's kind of retarded
Alright, well anyway
that's going to do it here for part A
of Orange Lounge Radio, if you're listening to us
on your iPod or your Zune
or whatever device you have to go on the go
or you're just listening on your computer
or audio archive or podcast
you've got to wait a little while, just a couple days
because we like to spread the OLR throughout the week
so you'll see part B of our podcast
about Wednesday-ish, but for those of you guys
listening live, be it on OrangeLoungeRadio.com
or AllGames.com, we will be right back
with part B of Orange Lounge Radio
Orange Lounge Radio is taped
live on Sunday nights
and is podcasted to the world twice a week
Stay tuned to our podcast feed
for the conclusion of this week's Orange Lounge Radio