[SPEAKER_00]: Tonight, May 6, 2007, another DS game has the Bubble Bobble curse of brokenness, Microsoft locks down on region control, and an old Commodore 64 classic returns to the Nintendo Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hello everybody and welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: We are that video game podcast dedicated to gamer culture and the gamer lifestyle.
[SPEAKER_03]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_03]: Joining me as always, say hello to DarkSakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_03]: How are you doing, DarkSakura, Jamie Summers?
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, we'll leave it at that then, I guess.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, I'm goofy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did you have a good week?
[SPEAKER_01]: Sort of.
[SPEAKER_01]: The parts that I wasn't at work were okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's good.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will when I quit, because then I'll be working full-time as a massage therapist, which means I'll be working 13 hours a week, making $60,000.
[SPEAKER_03]: Shut up, don't rub it in.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love my job, I do, but, you know, that doesn't mean that I don't enjoy, like, you know, it's a very exhausting job, what I do, so, you know, I enjoy that time when I get to come home.
[SPEAKER_03]: And even massage therapy, I know that's really exhausting, because I remember when you were doing your test thing on me, you were, like, breaking out in a sweat when you were done.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I was just like, all you did was talk.
[SPEAKER_01]: It doesn't matter how cold it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was just because you're so hot and sexy.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's Tech Master Loki with his smart-ass mouth as usual.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_01]: Look at my wrist, you see?
[SPEAKER_01]: I have swelling on my wrist again.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know part of it was because I was so hot and sexy, but I did not know that DarkSakura touching my butt would make her break out in a sweat.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm going to go ahead and say this.
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, giving an hour massage is an aerobic workout as well as strength training.
[SPEAKER_01]: You actually burn close to 320 calories doing an hour of massage.
[SPEAKER_03]: It doesn't surprise me when you stop to think about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm like, oh yeah, when I give other people massages, you're doing... Why do you think I was fucking eating whatever I wanted to while I was in school?
[SPEAKER_01]: Because I was giving our massages at least four times a week, especially when I was doing my finals.
[SPEAKER_03]: DDR not needed for you.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hell no.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now I'm like, I've only been doing a couple of massages.
[SPEAKER_01]: I need to go play DDR.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, there's another smart-ass voice in studio tonight, and that could only belong to the one and only Drew Nami is back tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: Boys and girls, say hello to Drew Nami.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_03]: How are you doing?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I'm all right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Excellent.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, and we're here in Orange Lounge Radio's chat room, chat.orangeloungeradio.com, but I noticed my chat room hasn't updated in a few seconds, which might mean... Yep, I just got disconnected.
[SPEAKER_03]: Go figure.
[SPEAKER_03]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_00]: Live radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bye, guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just pinged out a chat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Live radio, boys and girls, what can you do?
[SPEAKER_03]: We do tape live Sunday nights at OrangeLaunchRadio.com where we run a fully functional 24-hour-a-day, 7-day-a-week station with other awesome programming.
[SPEAKER_03]: For instance, DarkSakura has a show she calls Pump Up the Volume.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sometimes.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sometimes I just call it crap.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Travis Donovan has a cool little sci-fi show on Saturday nights, Travis Donovan Live.
[SPEAKER_03]: And brand new shows being piloted right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Can't say too much more.
[SPEAKER_03]: Those of you that have been listening on Wednesdays know about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: But those of you that don't...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_01]: I did play some more Marvel Ultimate Alliance, and then Dan took the game back.
[SPEAKER_01]: But it's, like, fucking funny to play it with Deadpool.
[SPEAKER_01]: So that's all I've been doing.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I was supposed to get my Pokemans, but my husband didn't pull through for me and bring me my Pokemans.
[SPEAKER_01]: Fired!
[SPEAKER_01]: I know.
[SPEAKER_01]: I need to trade him in for a more attentive model.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, I love... What?
[SPEAKER_03]: Now you make it sound like you're trading Pokemans.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to trade a level 32 Dan for level 69 boobs.
[SPEAKER_01]: No.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'll trade in my Dan for your Drew Barrymore.
[SPEAKER_01]: No.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, you're David Tennant.
[SPEAKER_01]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_01]: But no.
[SPEAKER_01]: But it's... I've been listening to other people talk about their Pokemans and I want to show you mine.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't have mine yet.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I've been playing, I've been really, really fucking pissed off at Twilight Zone.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's a pinball.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because Twilight Zone is awesome, and I can get in the zone, and then it's like, you're in the zone, Drain!
[SPEAKER_01]: What?
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm supposed to have multiball!
[SPEAKER_01]: No, Drain!
[SPEAKER_01]: Bitch.
[SPEAKER_01]: And Dan finally fixed our little problem we had on our Guns N' Roses.
[SPEAKER_03]: Kyle Snyder is in chat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Kyle's been listening to us for a while, and of course we know him from the DDR days.
[SPEAKER_03]: He says, Pokemon is dead to me.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm wondering what happened.
[SPEAKER_03]: You should let me show you my Pokemans.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why?
[SPEAKER_03]: I wonder why.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why, Kyle, is Pokemon dead to you?
[SPEAKER_03]: A lot of folks have been eating this game up.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's been bringing a lot of people back into the series.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe some longtime fans feel it's just a little too much.
[SPEAKER_05]: I need a new Digimon game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why do people still play this damn game?
[SPEAKER_04]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, look, we added more monsters that look awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very similar to the other ones!
[SPEAKER_04]: Buy it again!
[SPEAKER_04]: To answer Tigerclaw, by the way, I've been... Buy our new Color of DS or something to go along with it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Tigerclaw, I've been playing on PlayStation 3, but we've decided to purchase the Xbox 360 version so that, number one, I don't have to fuck with the stupid 6-axis, and number two, we have more controllers already, so I can actually have multiplayer in my house.
[SPEAKER_03]: Kyle Snyder simply says, I got bored of Pokemon.
[SPEAKER_03]: SpiceWorld was fucking funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was a shitty game out of it too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my god, the Spice Girls video game is the best party game ever on the PlayStation 1.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you've ever played the Spice Girls game, it is so horrible.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because, oh my god, the funniest thing ever.
[SPEAKER_03]: You have the girls, you choreograph dances, and all the girls can do their dance.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, we made Stupid Spice.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, the blonde one.
[SPEAKER_03]: We call her Stupid Spice.
[SPEAKER_03]: What we did is we would have her always be a count late, and then halfway through the dance, she just gives up and does the little sway back and forth.
[SPEAKER_03]: and then you can have them actually lip-sync this on.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's the stupidest game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hours of entertainment, especially if you're intoxicated.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's all I have to say.
[SPEAKER_03]: Only Rob.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anything else in your gaming week, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_01]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_03]: How was it?
[SPEAKER_01]: One last thing, sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: Dan downloaded that pinball game, the demo of the pinball game, and it's okay, but it's very high def.
[SPEAKER_01]: Done.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pin Mame
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: You're just playing it on the actual table.
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, there is, in works, using widescreen LCD monitors to do an at-home full pinball emulation.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, exactly.
[SPEAKER_01]: Using two screens.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly as I was saying.
[SPEAKER_03]: Can I say a chat real quick?
[SPEAKER_03]: Chat saying, Fireboma says, Spice World is almost the worst game ever, to which Jared J says, you've obviously not played Night Trap.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jvmon says, Spice World is better than Sonic was for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Go ahead.
[SPEAKER_04]: But we've also been playing, I played a little bit of Boom Boom Rocket today, and that was kind of fun, and just working through some of the medium-level stuff, so I can get a little higher on the leaderboards there, and then a little bit of Crackdown.
[SPEAKER_04]: Crackdown's still fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, I think I still have a top 100 score on Boom Boom Rocket, like, you know, for the grand leaderboards, and yet still there is someone on my friends list who outranks me.
[SPEAKER_03]: PK or Uno, I am going to beat your ass at...
[SPEAKER_03]: Boom Boom Rocket, mark my words, I will keep practicing until I take down your score.
[SPEAKER_01]: SSJ100, Matt, the only great game on Sega CD apart from Sonic CD was not fucking Night Trap.
[SPEAKER_01]: There was Popful Mail, there was Silphid, Revenge of the Ninja, Microcosm.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, there was Sewer Shark, but that doesn't count either.
[SPEAKER_01]: And all the Lunar games.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, you know what?
[SPEAKER_01]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wait, he's saying...
[SPEAKER_03]: Night Trap was a good game?
[SPEAKER_01]: It was the only other good game.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm like, the fuck it was?
[SPEAKER_03]: Night Trap wasn't even a good game.
[SPEAKER_01]: It had Dana Plato in it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: It didn't have boobies in it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, because it was Dana Plato, but she didn't have very big boobies.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's instantly in the good game section.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I've got the 32X one, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, well, there you go.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, the Terminator game was good, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: The 32X is crap.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey, Chaotix kicked ass.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, it did not.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, it did.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_04]: Chaotix was awful.
[SPEAKER_01]: And Calibri.
[SPEAKER_01]: Did you play Calibri?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: And wasn't there an Echo game that was 32X compatible?
[SPEAKER_02]: There was, but it wasn't very good.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just mostly played Chaotix.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jamie?
[SPEAKER_03]: After Burner.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jamie?
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: I love you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Calibri sucks.
[SPEAKER_01]: Calibri was cute.
[SPEAKER_01]: But no, After Burner and...
[SPEAKER_01]: Uh, fuck.
[SPEAKER_01]: Space Harrier.
[SPEAKER_01]: For 32X.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they said it was a flop.
[SPEAKER_01]: And they were the actual arcade versions.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was really fucking cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was really lame.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was like, why the fuck are they chained to each other?
[SPEAKER_04]: And this is so awful.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just like a fucking anchor being dragged behind the guy.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was just, it was a horrible, horrible game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the Bionic Commando Factor.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sonic Crackers, anyone?
[SPEAKER_02]: That works, that works.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course more Grand Theft Auto Vice City stories because that game never gets old.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although we still get pissed off at each other.
[SPEAKER_04]: A lot.
[SPEAKER_02]: Me, I've been playing WoW off and on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some Neverwinter Nights 2 and some Unreal Tournament.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just kind of a return to old school stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I am not an addict.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I do not plan to be an addict, but I still play WoW.
[SPEAKER_03]: My gaming week was somewhat very similar to Drew Nami's.
[SPEAKER_03]: I played pretty much nothing but WoW all week.
[SPEAKER_03]: I made it to level 49.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess there's that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know, big WoW, huh?
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually have not been doing a lot of console gaming this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's kind of sad.
[SPEAKER_03]: I played the pinball game at least one more time, like twice or something, to just kind of see if I liked it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I tried the demo for the mini-golf game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hated it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've just never liked mini-golf games on consoles.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just not the same.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like pinball.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's my review for everything this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not the same as the real thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's the problem, though, with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: They really fucked up this whole thing when they went 3D Ultra Mini-Golf Adventures.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's really lame now.
[SPEAKER_04]: See, 3D Ultra Mini-Golf was pretty fun because you can play against other people.
[SPEAKER_04]: They even had some modes that people would create and stuff in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: My favorite was if I was doing bad, I just hit someone's ball across the entire course, and that was worth it right there.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, the game's okay, graphically, I mean, I like, it's very creative, a lot of the whole is very creative, it's certainly not your typical mini-golf game, but I don't know, I just, I couldn't, I wasn't feeling it, for some reason, so I didn't buy the full version.
[SPEAKER_03]: I really wanted to try Catan, but the demo wasn't working, and I guess they fixed it now, so I need to go back and try it, because I've heard lots of great things about Catan, and when somebody, it was either on my Twitter or LiveJournal, somebody compared it to Civilization, and I was like, sold!
[SPEAKER_03]: So I definitely want to check that out, because
[SPEAKER_03]: I tried the demo.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I got a new monitor for my computer.
[SPEAKER_03]: I finally got a widescreen monitor, which, by the way, is working out great for the show, because I can have, like, all the windows up at once.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I was like, oh, it's really pretty.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to download movies.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to download other games.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to see how... Because, like, widescreen and WoW, oh, fap, fap, fap.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's beautiful.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's so awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't even explain it.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I wanted to try, like, other stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I was like, oh, I'll try a driving game.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I tried to download the Need for Speed Carbon demo for the PC.
[SPEAKER_03]: Crashed on me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, I was about ready to get to where I'd actually race.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, like,
[SPEAKER_03]: I downloaded E-Duke.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, I have to ask your opinion on this, and I'm not sure who got the charm on this topic, but...
[SPEAKER_01]: JV Mon is saying I would cream for a Doctor Who MMO That's not entirely possible unless they set it before the current series because there's only one Time Lord now so you couldn't go around in your own TARDIS or anything What if they did something a while back or something else?
[SPEAKER_03]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_01]: If it was pre-movie it'd be possible but it wouldn't work
[SPEAKER_01]: And I really, really doubt that they'd let something like that out now, given the attention to continuity.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't you get a little nervous, too, when you hear your favorite shows or whatever are going to be turned into games?
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, you know, they're talking about turning Heroes into a video game now because, you know, the show's been very successful.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I love me some Heroes, but I get very nervous about a Heroes video game.
[SPEAKER_04]: If they said EA's making a Heroes game, that might be more confident in saying...
[SPEAKER_04]: SNK is making a Heroes game, which would never happen because that's neither, you know, Metal Slug, Art of Fighting, King of Fighters, it's none of those, and it's not a game that they've already made, so obviously that wouldn't be one of their games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, QY brings up a good point, 24 the game, like, okay, yeah, 24 didn't work out so well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, here's the problem, they made a game that took place between seasons 2 and 3 and it came out like after season 5 or 4 or something like that, so it's like, wow, this is a little old.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, before we get into gaming news this week, I noticed the chat room is all stuck on Spider-Man 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, you know, here we are, like, almost 20 minutes into the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're still talking about Spider-Man 3 as they were before the show started tonight, even though we're a video game show.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I see Spider-Man 3 is not a... The game got horrible reviews.
[SPEAKER_03]: Spider-Man 3 is a popular part of culture.
[SPEAKER_03]: Horrible reviews.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, the game, I was reading, like, PlayStation 2 game, they said it just looked like crap.
[SPEAKER_04]: The PlayStation 3 one, it was just getting average reviews.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was just...
[SPEAKER_04]: Speaking of things people love and turning them into bastardized video games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I mean, it had potential, but even they were showing the Wii version of it and stuff, and half of Brooklyn Bridge would be not even there.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: None of the buildings had textures on them and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I feel like one of the non-cool kids because I didn't bother to see the movie this weekend, but I hate seeing movies opening weekend.
[SPEAKER_03]: It used to be the cool thing to do, but I hate teenagers at the theater.
[SPEAKER_03]: No offense to the teenagers that listen to this show.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sure you guys know how to be respectful, but unfortunately not all teenagers of the world can be.
[SPEAKER_03]: It just ruins it for me.
[SPEAKER_01]: I went yesterday and I had a fairly quiet theater.
[SPEAKER_01]: There was one child that started crying and the parent escorted him out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good.
[SPEAKER_01]: And one phone that went off that everyone pretty much turned around and said, Turn that fucker off!
[SPEAKER_04]: I can top that.
[SPEAKER_04]: We had a work screening, and one dumb bitch at my work dropped her kids off at the screening, and one of her kids was recording the film with his camera phone, to which Nelly turned him in.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love your wife, I really do.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the manager came over to him and told him to turn off the phone.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was hoping that he'd be dragged out and parents called and stuff like that, but
[SPEAKER_04]: Unfortunately, that didn't happen.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because management is afraid to be mean because they'll get sued or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I'd punch the kid in the face and then drag him out by his hair.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: Instead of telling the manager, you should have called the RIAA or whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Get out of here real quick.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, the MPAA.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, boy.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to get hate mail for that mistake.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Enough about movies.
[SPEAKER_03]: Moving on to – wait.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm looking at – actually, I'm looking at chat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, Blaze says, I'm a teen and I hate a lot of teens that go to the movies.
[SPEAKER_03]: Footy Monster says, I hate, hate, hate, hate teenagers.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Jack Ransom responds to that saying, we hate, hate, hate you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh, come join in the love.
[SPEAKER_03]: Chat.OrangeLawnTrader.com live on this Sunday night, 6 o'clock Pacific time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I remember when I was their age and stuff going, man.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't act like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what I'm saying.
[SPEAKER_03]: Probably the people listening to this show, I would hope, if you're smart enough to download this show or listen live, you're probably smart enough to not be a jackass at the theater.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'm not talking about you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wait, Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm talking about... I don't know what the hell you're talking about.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was never a teenager.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is craziness.
[SPEAKER_02]: Calling me a teen.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are you 12?
[SPEAKER_02]: I was never a teenager.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's all about the jocks.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's always the jocks that are the problems of everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the nerds get the rap for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nerds.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did I ever tell the Grudge story on this show when I went to go see the Grudge?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think I was with you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Several times.
[SPEAKER_03]: Really?
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, then I'm not going to tell it again.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tell it again, though.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think it's great.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jamie, you tell it.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, I wasn't there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought you were.
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: When we saw the Grudge, were you there, Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: I was there.
[SPEAKER_03]: You tell it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, I wasn't even there and I don't remember this fucking story.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Somebody.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: So it was a sold out theater, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: It was a sold out theater and the jocks in the back.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I, you know, I don't know if it's the Rocky Horror Picture Show goer in me or whatever, but I'm not afraid to yell in a crowded theater.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I turned around and I yelled out with the man with the little penis in the back row, please shut the fuck up.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the entire audience started applauding, because you know they were all sick of it, they just didn't want to say anything about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I yelled that out, everybody applauded, and he shut the fuck up.
[SPEAKER_03]: And yet, you hear these girls in the back start going, Because his girlfriend knew it was true.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it was great.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was a good time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good time.
[SPEAKER_01]: That was poon.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe I should go to the movies more often on opening weekend, because I'm not afraid to yell at people while the movie's going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sometimes it is fun to yell at movies.
[SPEAKER_04]: I remember when we went and saw work screening again, because I wouldn't pay to see this, Charlie's Angels 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to see that.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I will never forget the one moment in the movie where it's just like, okay, you can kind of suspend disbelief for a lot of the movie and stuff, but when there's a boat exploding and they...
[SPEAKER_04]: Grab ahold of this rope and get pulled up through the ceiling and shrapnel from the explosion causes wood to splinter into snowboard-shaped pieces of wood to which the girls land on those and then grind down the ropes from the ship to the dock.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I was like, oh, really?
[SPEAKER_04]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, really.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was almost like a transporter, but the transporter, they expect that.
[SPEAKER_02]: You see, there are right movies to MST and there are wrong movies to MST.
[SPEAKER_02]: MST and Charlie's Angels?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Snakes on a Plane?
[SPEAKER_02]: Hell yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's some movies that you just have to see that are bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, you have to give some respect to movies like 300.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or the end of The Premonition where I started busting up laughing because it was so stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or the end of Fracture where it was just like, wow, nothing really happened in the entire movie.
[SPEAKER_01]: So next on Movie Chat... Sorry.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know what...
[SPEAKER_03]: It's alright to get off topic once in a while.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Embrace it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Remember, we don't give a shit anymore.
[SPEAKER_03]: Remember last week?
[SPEAKER_01]: Remember last time we tried not to give a shit and people hated it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, speaking of Mr. Santa's Year 3000, I got a new tape for, or not tape, a DVD from work.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently the guys that do it are starting a new series.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't remember what it's called now because I don't have the disc in front of me, but there is a new series coming out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have a website, but...
[SPEAKER_01]: Does it have Mike?
[SPEAKER_03]: Research it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Any chat feedback real quick?
[SPEAKER_03]: Bandit says, it might have been his mom laughing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I fucking love chat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Her jeans.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tigerclaw says, Sky, and they didn't yell back at you saying, you shut the fuck up.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, they didn't because the entire audience applauded.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I think that kind of, if that didn't happen, maybe they would have, but yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, there you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: Game News Game News Game News
[SPEAKER_03]: Over Memorial Day weekend.
[SPEAKER_03]: This year we only have one panel, not two.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're not going to do a general podcasting panel.
[SPEAKER_03]: But that's alright because we're still going to record our show live.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it happens at 2pm on Saturdays.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we hope that a lot of you guys will come out and say hello and make plans to come see us at Faname.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll all be there.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we're excited.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's get into some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_01]: I have some news, and this is very interesting stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now the PlayStation 3 store is starting to stock PlayStation 1 games.
[SPEAKER_01]: We have Two Extreme, Crash Bandicoot, Destruction Derby, Jet Moto, Jumping Flash, which I fucking love Jumping Flash.
[SPEAKER_01]: Medieval, Rallycross, Syphon Filter, which is actually a good game, Tekken 2, and Wipeout.
[SPEAKER_01]: So...
[SPEAKER_01]: You will actually be able to share your PSP games between the handheld and the PS3, so you'll keep your save games with you.
[SPEAKER_01]: You can play them at work, play them at home.
[SPEAKER_01]: It has not yet been confirmed for Europe, however, so we've just got to wait.
[SPEAKER_01]: However, these downloads are $5.99 apiece.
[SPEAKER_04]: They've had them up for the PSP for a while, and it's always kind of weird how you had to have the PS3 to download the ones for the PSP,
[SPEAKER_04]: which didn't make any sense and now with the new version 1.7 patch that they had for the firmware on the PS3 now you can actually play them on the PlayStation 3 instead of just on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just think it's good that your saves are going to work between the two.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well that's kind of nice and it's also nice that there's something to actually download on the PlayStation Network for the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know there was a system that tried to do this before not necessarily with having the handheld version but remember the Neo Geo tried to do this before with the arcade versions and with the
[SPEAKER_01]: AVS.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, there's also the TurboGrafx-16.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, the TurboGrafx didn't have an arcade compatibility.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, they have the TurboDuo, though, or the Turbo Express.
[SPEAKER_01]: The Turbo Express had no way to transfer the saves between the systems.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I thought it was on the cartridges, though.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, yeah, I mean, but that's like playing with your Super Game Boy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I guess it would be the same as a Nomad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it's the same as a Nomad.
[SPEAKER_01]: But in this case, though, it was having your...
[SPEAKER_01]: Bringing home your arcade game to play on your arcade version at home.
[SPEAKER_01]: Two different... Hello.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bandit in our chat room says, Great, now I can use my $600 investment to play really old PS1 games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Great, thanks, Sony.
[SPEAKER_01]: Dude, I love Jumping Flash.
[SPEAKER_01]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what it was.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, the...
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry to interject this real quick.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Film Crew is what the new thing is called, the new series.
[SPEAKER_04]: It stars Kevin Murphy, Bill, looks like Corbett, and Mike Nelson.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks, how about some game news?
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay now, Mr. Demanding.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways, so, also tying in with the PlayStation 3, Home Beta has finally kicked off in both the US and UK.
[SPEAKER_03]: Look, I just don't care if it doesn't have Tom Servo, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, so a lot of people are getting to try out the brand new free, you know, avatar system that's very similar to the Sims.
[SPEAKER_04]: And everybody's saying, oh, it's so much better than Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought they all had to sign an NDA to get in that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, well, they did.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, you know, they can still say that they're part of this, you know, service and that it's awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because, you know, awesome is not covered under the NDA.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, apparently also there's going to be some more entries into the beta coming out soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you really want to get into the beta, you need to make sure that you register your PlayStation 3 with Sony, which I haven't done yet, so I need to do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then it's all random from there.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, good luck.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hopefully you get to try out the home beta before everybody else.
[SPEAKER_04]: Personally, I don't really care.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll just wait for it to be done.
[SPEAKER_04]: It won't be working correctly when it is done anyways, because everybody likes to patch shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it is in beta.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's early.
[SPEAKER_03]: True.
[SPEAKER_03]: TheRobD, by the way, says, Kevin Murphy is Tom Servo, so he's trying to pwn me there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_01]: Does he have a giant underwear collection?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think not.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, moving on.
[SPEAKER_01]: Please do.
[SPEAKER_03]: Vib Ribbon
[SPEAKER_03]: Matsuura was actually hinting that possibly Vib Ribbon might be on its way to the PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_03]: Quote, Rhythmica is very similar in idea to Vib Ribbon.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's about analyzing audio and creating a game from that data, but it uses MP3 audio instead of CDs.
[SPEAKER_03]: We are discussing the possibility of making a downloadable version of Vib Ribbon for Sony, but I don't know yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sony only recently launched their downloadable service in Japan, so we kind of need to wait a while before releasing a title with that kind of appeal.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Vibribin, if you've never played it, is so friggin' cute.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm so glad I lucked into my copy.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because I paid enough for it, too, didn't I?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_03]: Didn't it go into best hits in Japan, though, eventually?
[SPEAKER_01]: I can't remember.
[SPEAKER_01]: I bought an original for like 50 bucks used.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then again... At the time, yeah, it was absolutely worth it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the cool thing about it, though, is that you could use any CD with it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And although the results were somewhat mixed, it was just kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: What did we try to do?
[SPEAKER_01]: We tried Max 300.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was better than Dance Factory.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, we did Dropout.
[SPEAKER_01]: That was what we used.
[SPEAKER_01]: We tried to play it to Dropout.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I hope this happens.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would be a really fun game for PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_03]: Certainly better than the Duck game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, there is, in process...
[SPEAKER_01]: Excuse me for a moment while I breathe again.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're talking about a new Dead or Alive, Mega Man, and Kingdom Hearts for PS3.
[SPEAKER_01]: In the last issue of EGM Magazine, there were these rumors coming out.
[SPEAKER_01]: So Team Ninja has an exclusive for a new Dead or Alive for the PS3.
[SPEAKER_01]: And there's also the notice that Capcom is working on a new...
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually not a new Mega Man, they were updating the original Mega Man with new graphics for a download.
[SPEAKER_01]: And Nipponichi is working on a new Disgaea for PS3.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's basically Mega Man, powered up Mega Man, except without a giant head, hopefully.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's hope.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because he had a giant fucking head in the game.
[SPEAKER_01]: And we're pretty much sure Kingdom Hearts 3 is going to be PS3.
[SPEAKER_04]: so there is some new stuff coming out also from Square actually they're talking a little bit about Kingdom Hearts and of course the next progression for it apparently is going to be a portable spin-off and not Kingdom Hearts 3 although I'm assuming Kingdom Hearts 3 is probably in the works as well but the next game you'll see will be a portable spin-off and no word exactly what it's going to be I'm sure we'll find out a little bit more after the whole Square Enix
[SPEAKER_04]: Press Party or whatever they have in Fan Party.
[SPEAKER_04]: So hopefully we'll hear a little bit more about that because I know it wasn't a Chain of Memories or whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Didn't that suck really bad?
[SPEAKER_01]: Chain of Memories is a different game.
[SPEAKER_01]: I do not recommend playing it on a DS Micro.
[SPEAKER_01]: Not DS.
[SPEAKER_01]: The Game Boy Advance Micro.
[SPEAKER_01]: But it wasn't that bad.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm actually looking forward to the PS2 version.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: They just
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't fuck it up, please.
[SPEAKER_03]: Most people play Kingdom Hearts Chain of Memory for the story, not the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I'm glad they play it for something.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, well, last week somebody listened to us, apparently, or somebody had the same idea, because remember when last week we talked about the whole God of War promotional thing in the UK?
[SPEAKER_03]: They had the goat with the head chopped off and all that stuff, remember that?
[SPEAKER_03]: And I said somebody should email PETA.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, somebody did.
[SPEAKER_03]: Somebody somehow told PETA what was going on.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know if that's because of this show or what.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sure somebody else had the same idea.
[SPEAKER_03]: But PETA did post in their, I guess, official blog.
[SPEAKER_03]: It looks like it's just one guy that runs it, but they have a blog over at blog.peta.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: Somebody actually posted about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And basically what it came down to is that they sort of said...
[SPEAKER_03]: PETA said they're kind of not going to do anything about it, that it's obviously an idiotic thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: They would not name the game in the blog entry because they have no desire to help them promote it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they noticed that Sony obviously apologized for it, and Sony is recalling the magazine and everything.
[SPEAKER_03]: But PETA was just kind of shaking their head disapprovingly.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, boys.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, you know how Taito had that big problem with Bubble Bobble?
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, you can't get past level 30?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, never heard of it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, we made fun of it endlessly on this show.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, it's happened to SNK and Capcom Cardfighter Clash for the DS.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, which is funny because my husband bought the game right when it came out.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I'm just wondering if he's hit that point yet.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm going to laugh.
[SPEAKER_03]: You just got bubble bobbled.
[SPEAKER_01]: Apparently, if you go to the ninth floor of the tower through the second playthrough, the game will crash after you talk to someone named John.
[SPEAKER_01]: You have to fight him to, of course, make it past that area.
[SPEAKER_01]: So you're pretty much just stuck.
[SPEAKER_01]: No...
[SPEAKER_01]: There is a message from SNK stating that we're going to hear something soon, but nothing as of yet as far as I know.
[SPEAKER_01]: So let's hope that, more than positive, they're going to recall it or do something for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is the message going to say something along the lines of, we're really fucking sorry we didn't beta test this game?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, because when things like this are announced, it makes me think that the game is so god-awful that not even their own internal QA department could play through the ninth floor.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, that's seriously the impression that I get about the game, is that if the game is so broken that not even their QA department was interested in playing it that far, what else am I left to think?
[SPEAKER_03]: Ouch.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it's good enough.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, hell, if the first couple levels worked, then the whole game's probably good.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, after all, they're not that much different.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you want me to play through the whole thing?
[SPEAKER_04]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, news about broken video games makes us a little bit angsty, and you know what that means when we get angsty.
[SPEAKER_03]: People die.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's time for the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, take it away.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, FU goes towards certain people in management positions at my unlisted place of employment.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it's not really, you know, again, it's not necessarily a... I'd say it was a misthought.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'll put it that way.
[SPEAKER_01]: Assuming that...
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't have enough work already to do with the one thing that I was already doing.
[SPEAKER_01]: True, I get a couple days a month where they don't, you know, open as many assignments to me to finish and I need extra things to do to keep busy.
[SPEAKER_01]: But, um, I told them right up front, I'm like, look, I'm not going to be able to do all this.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm one person and I'm sure as hell not going to work overtime.
[SPEAKER_01]: Unless you really want me to work overtime and pay me for it, sure, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: and, true enough, you know, I finally said, you know what, if they're gonna do this to me, then I'm just gonna let them know when I can't get it all done in one day and we'll see what they think of that.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, finally, the realization has dawned that, oh my god, she really is only one person.
[SPEAKER_01]: And while her productivity is amazing, not everybody can do all of this.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, yeah, we're gonna not let, you know, this employee go nuts and kill everybody in the company.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, it's getting taken care of.
[SPEAKER_01]: After we discuss the situation.
[SPEAKER_04]: My FU of the week goes to Survivor The Ride
[SPEAKER_03]: At Great America, where I was at yesterday, we took a trip for Extrovert Sisters.
[SPEAKER_04]: I vote this ride out of the park.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know, first of all, how the hell do you make a ride out of Survivor?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's pretty cheesy, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is it where you have to starve yourself?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, okay, you start off the ride, like when you're waiting in the queue, the little line before you actually get on the ride, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: They make you do, when it's your turn to go next, first you have to do this little tribal stomp, you have to do this stupid-ass...
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_03]: And I scream like a little girl because, like, seriously, like, Disneyland is one thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: When I get on the thrill rides where I'm going upside down and being, like, just being twisted up like a pretzel on some of those rides and getting fire shot in my face on a ride named after a TV show that jumped the shark five years ago.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, F you.
[SPEAKER_03]: I bet you'll do the dance next time now, won't you?
[SPEAKER_03]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll teach that fucker a lesson.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll do the damn dance next time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Stomp, stomp, stomp.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, seriously, when my first word to her when I got off the ride, I'm like, Jamie would like this ride because it shoots fire.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think I would.
[SPEAKER_01]: When you said shooting fire, I was like, hey, I like fire.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, you didn't find it funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think I found it funny as hell.
[SPEAKER_01]: Fuego es muy bien.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuego.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fireboma says Skye is used to things being shot in his face.
[SPEAKER_03]: Zing, my second FU of the week, goes to Fireboma.
[SPEAKER_03]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_03]: Drunami, your FU of the week.
[SPEAKER_02]: FU to DS Wi-Fi for being so damn temperamental around my router.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know it's not my router's fault it wants to be so restrictive.
[SPEAKER_02]: It must be Nintendo DS Wi-Fi.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, FU to the new patches that are coming out for WoW.
[SPEAKER_02]: Trying to go into the public test room.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god, Lactastic.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nothing works in my UI.
[SPEAKER_02]: They've got some serious stuff to fix before they release that publicly.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Lots of angst in studio tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know you're going to get a good show when there's lots of angst in studio tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, let's kill the music.
[SPEAKER_03]: And let's get back to some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_01]: Instead, let's go have ice cream.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ice cream sounds good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's have an ice cream podcast.
[SPEAKER_03]: I totally vote for ice cream.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Orange Launch Radio is canceled tonight due to ice cream.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, I already had ice cream today.
[SPEAKER_01]: You can't have ice cream for two weeks.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll have ice cream again.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, save us.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, well, the only thing in combat ice cream is TNA, and there is... Hey, that sounds great!
[SPEAKER_04]: Winner!
[SPEAKER_04]: I like TNA ice cream.
[SPEAKER_04]: TNA-flavored ice cream.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there's this wonderful game that's being touted as TNA Pong on Kotaku.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's actually from a website, I guess, WeMakeMoneyNotArt, and it's, I guess, some woman named Jennifer Chowdhury's.
[SPEAKER_04]: She has an intimate game controller, and apparently...
[SPEAKER_04]: She says it's like Pong, but it's not really like Pong, it's more like DDR, I would say.
[SPEAKER_04]: The whole game is basically, there's a woman has a bra controller where you, you know, grope her, and then the guy has, like, boxers where she grabs his ass.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you watch the screen, there's, like, first there'll be shapes coming up, so, you know, you can grab anywhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then later on, as you progress through the levels, there's shapes with other shapes on them, like star with a circle and stuff, and you have to grab certain parts and stuff, and supposedly...
[SPEAKER_04]: It's supposed to make you either, you know, piss off because you lose or go have sex.
[SPEAKER_04]: Personally, it looked very, very, very, very awkward.
[SPEAKER_04]: So this is a game where even when you lose, you win?
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: But hey, the way I figure it, you know, if you got some chick in bra and panties already and you're playing this game and grabbing her boobs, it can't be that bad of a game.
[SPEAKER_02]: This reminds me of that one boob twirling game they released like two, three years ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Where you had to make them twirl in different patterns.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was a fun game.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm watching the video on here, even though I'm not supposed to.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's really, really stupid.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, here we go.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to give the show an explicit tag.
[SPEAKER_03]: You ready?
[SPEAKER_03]: Warning, the show is intended for mature audiences.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, like, when you first started talking about this, I kind of pictured that maybe the woman, like, put a Wiimote in her twat.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, would you play Lesbian Pong?
[SPEAKER_03]: I need the female perspective here on the show for a minute.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, that's a yes, you would?
[SPEAKER_03]: Score, cut, print, saved archives.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, that's a wrap.
[SPEAKER_03]: OLR's over.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're off to go play games.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're off to go create new games for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nice knowing you for the past five years.
[SPEAKER_03]: Lesbian Pong has ruined this show.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good night.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, but seriously, though, they could put, like, what they could do is, like, I don't know, make some sort of a different game, you know, where they could put more sensors on their bodies or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Know what they need.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here's what... Yeah, but now we have an audio clip of her saying yes, so it's done.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, here's what they need to do.
[SPEAKER_04]: This kind of ties in with that really crappy Eye of Judgment game.
[SPEAKER_04]: They need to have something with the eye toy and the Eye of Judgment.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a sex game.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's already the brown Eye of Judgment.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, dude, the Eye of Judgment on a sex game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I get it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the Wiimote.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or Six Axis, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because Six Axis can detect how much you're rocking the boat.
[SPEAKER_04]: But see, then again, though, they have all the USB ports, so you can just hook it up with your usual USB-powered vibrators and shit, and it'll just, you know...
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Total sex package.
[SPEAKER_04]: Never will happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because it's a dumb idea.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who the fuck would set up all this shit to have sex?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's just retarded.
[SPEAKER_04]: But then again, though, they have all those sex board games, and I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: That could be fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wanted to say this real quick.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, the talk about the brown eye of judgment actually reminded me.
[SPEAKER_03]: I got a private message on my Twitter from a PK or Uno who was telling me about another game
[SPEAKER_03]: Aquarian Age Alternative
[SPEAKER_04]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: That proves, once again, Sony didn't come up with an original idea.
[SPEAKER_04]: Way to go!
[SPEAKER_03]: Copying something subscreened.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know how new or old this game is, but I hope... Well, let's put it this way.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to just pimp his Vox, because he has pictures and stuff all over his Vox.
[SPEAKER_03]: So if you want to see this, it's pkeruno.vox.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: P-K-E-R-U-N-O dot vox dot com.
[SPEAKER_03]: And he has this whole thing, Aquarian Age Alternative.
[SPEAKER_03]: Obviously, it's out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Eye of Judgment is not out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Therefore, this one came out first, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: They... Way to go, Sony.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thinking that we wouldn't find the thing that you copied, but there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Proves that you're still not original.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's still a dumb idea.
[SPEAKER_03]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm curious to play it.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, I'll try anything once.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, other famous Japanese arcade games may or may not be coming to the US.
[SPEAKER_03]: 2DX Gold, Beatmania 2DX Gold, of course...
[SPEAKER_03]: Tilt Arcade, GameWorks, Six Flags
[SPEAKER_03]: and really break down that we want to see Beatmania 2DX Golden Arcades.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it tells you what to say and everything.
[SPEAKER_03]: So hats off to this user, BrazoLienge, and I hope I didn't horribly mispronounce that.
[SPEAKER_03]: But hats off to you for breaking that all down.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I know we have a lot of music game fans that listen to this program because that used to be our forte a couple years ago.
[SPEAKER_03]: So definitely check out Bomani Style's forums.
[SPEAKER_03]: Check out the forums.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just don't let a golf land have it because you know they'll fuck it up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, don't let golf land have it because they'll break it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, for some reason your mic's not picking up, DarkSakura, is it?
[SPEAKER_01]: That's because it wasn't on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, that would be why.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know why it wasn't on.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, there you go.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, what I said was don't let Golfland have it because you know they're going to fuck it up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Check out the music game discussion forums on BamandiStyle.com.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, speaking of information that came out on a forum, there's a rumor going on that the DDR Supernova 2 North American Field Test is canceled.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was posted by Rye19 on Aaron in Japan's forums.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: I honestly myself don't put too much stock in something that I read on a forum until I see something official put out by the company.
[SPEAKER_03]: The only reason I would give a little cred to it is because they have done location tests there before at that same arcade.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I was willing to believe it, but I do wonder to myself, did Konami pull it back?
[SPEAKER_03]: to maybe further tweak the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe it wasn't ready to be tested because you know the internet is cruel and the game better be damn good or the internet will tear it apart.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, there was also a quote on here, apparently a quote from maybe Selenic Konami?
[SPEAKER_01]: And again, this is on a message board stating that in order to prevent dissatisfaction of SN2, we have canceled the North American SN2 test site as it may result in creating a better dance game.
[SPEAKER_03]: That sounds fishy.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know about that one.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I could be wrong.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why would a company admit that, oh, the game kind of sucks right now?
[SPEAKER_03]: We're going to go back and tweak it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know about that one.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're starting over.
[SPEAKER_03]: See you in ten years.
[SPEAKER_03]: We hope you have a nice play again.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: They need to just completely make the dance pads more durable.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ditter fans are going to have to wait a little long for their ditter.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what the story...
[SPEAKER_01]: You can diddle later.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, dinner later.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways, so certain... There's a few websites out there that got all excited after seeing an IGN mock-up of a Guitar Hero 3 controller, which I might add that is completely fake, by the way, and is no indication of what it's actually going to look like.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have basically a picture of a white guitar with the Wii remote in the neck of the guitar.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's
[SPEAKER_04]: Just like before when they mocked what the classic controller would look like.
[SPEAKER_04]: Completely mocked up.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know why I felt that was fake when I first looked at it?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's because of the way the Wiimote is strapped into that controller.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because basically what they have there is they have this guitar with the handle.
[SPEAKER_03]: What do they call the long part of that?
[SPEAKER_03]: The neck?
[SPEAKER_03]: They have the Wii thing snapping into the neck.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the thing is that if the Wiimote were to snap in...
[SPEAKER_01]: It breaks the infrared.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the plugs are on the bottom.
[SPEAKER_03]: You wouldn't snap it in like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: You'd have to snap it in either on the bottom of the guitar or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can't push it in and have it just snap.
[SPEAKER_03]: It wouldn't work.
[SPEAKER_03]: It would be too difficult to get in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: And besides, if I remember correctly, I think they've already said that if when they do release this, there's actually going to be a guitar that's sold separately.
[SPEAKER_04]: They'll hook up via USB or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, but that's not what it's going to be, it's not going to be something that you strap the Wii Remote into It's not like you have to plug the Wii Remote into everything Exactly, and, I mean, I don't know, it's going to be Guitar Hero 3, it's just going to be on another fucking console, so, woohoo I know, it's like, you've never played this game before
[SPEAKER_01]: Flyin' V Flyin' V Flyin' V
[SPEAKER_03]: Is it too much to ask for one freaking guitar to work on all consoles?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're all USB.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why can't they?
[SPEAKER_04]: Why can't they make one universal guitar?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know why, because they get to sell you fucking more guitars.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, well, the Queens of the Stone Age, you might know them, they're a band, and they have basically confirmed that they are going to be in some games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Basically, I guess there's a
[SPEAKER_03]: promo ad going around for the band and it's confirming that they are going to be appearing in Guitar Hero 3 and Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_03]: What song?
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't know, but you know the Queens of Stone Age are going to be in the games.
[SPEAKER_03]: By the way, they're also going to be in Madden 08 and NASCAR 08 if you are so inclined to play those games instead.
[SPEAKER_03]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_03]: EA tracks!
[SPEAKER_03]: That's right, EA tracks!
[SPEAKER_04]: And again, I like Junkie XL, so they always have a good Junkie XL track in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: And who doesn't love Avril Lavigne's girlfriend?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh wait, no one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nellie does.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey Mickey, you're so fine, you're so fine, you blow my mind Hey Mickey, just replace the word Mickey with girlfriend and that's pretty much the song
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_01]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's called Bible Fight.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's a flash game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Where it's like Street Fighter with Jesus.
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually played a little bit of this game last night.
[SPEAKER_03]: I should have included that in my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I battled Jesus versus Satan.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was epic.
[SPEAKER_03]: But what's great is that they have special moves.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like Jesus throws his thorny crown.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: You have Jesus, Eve, Mary, Moses, Noah, and Satan.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I can see if she's naked.
[SPEAKER_03]: She...
[SPEAKER_03]: Jamie, you've got issues.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, this is great.
[SPEAKER_01]: She has a snake on one arm with little leaves.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_03]: The typical depiction of Eve, where there's always... Mary looks like she's got PMS.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's always, like, an animal or a fig leaf or something just conveniently placed over their naughty bits.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's always kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: She's fighting with a halo over her head and fucking Baby Jesus.
[SPEAKER_03]: GS68 says, Baby Jesus is a weapon?
[SPEAKER_03]: Does that be awesome?
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow, we're going to get the hate mail tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: GS68 says, Westboro will sue.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, we didn't create it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Adult Swim did.
[SPEAKER_03]: Go take up your issues with them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways, so the NBA has just launched into Second Life.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently a lot of people are on Second Life like it's fucking real world or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ooh, the NBA is on there now.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, I mean, they're in the real world too.
[SPEAKER_04]: But apparently you can go there and, you know, play horse and basketball and suck it up really bad as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not surprised that, you know, people are going to make money off this second life.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's interesting nonetheless.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess you can play horse and get pelted by penises.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jesus, keep the first life out of second life.
[SPEAKER_02]: Damn, come on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pretty soon people are going to get... You should put that on a bumper sticker.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pretty soon... Seriously, that's a pretty good tagline for us.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because you're a Second Life player, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: From time to time, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought Second Life was just where people go to have virtual furry sex or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, not like to play basketball.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to go into Second Life, I'm going to play basketball.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then your friend goes, fuck that, I'm going outside and play basketball there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't have to worry about being pelted with flying penises.
[SPEAKER_04]: Drew Nami, response?
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't go play in a sandbox then.
[SPEAKER_02]: You don't get that shit if you play in a sandbox zone.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, so don't go playing in a sandbox because there's a virtual sandbox in Second Life.
[SPEAKER_03]: If I had that sound effect on this program, I would have just used it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't get it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, what the hell do you do in Second Life?
[SPEAKER_02]: Stop!
[SPEAKER_03]: Try to find a life?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I imagine there's lots of people.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, I play World of Warcraft, so I can't talk.
[SPEAKER_04]: Look at my cube I just made.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's so awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to buy it for $1,000?
[SPEAKER_03]: I play World of Warcraft, so I can't talk, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: But, you know, I guess people play it because it's fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what games are.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: Furry sex is fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, if World of Warcraft weren't set in some sort of fictional medieval time, I'm sure the NBA would be there, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Point of Second Life is simple.
[SPEAKER_02]: Step one, fly around.
[SPEAKER_02]: Step two, do shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Comments from chat room.
[SPEAKER_03]: TheRobD makes some comments.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is Tim Hardaway there to hate you if you're gay in Second Life?
[SPEAKER_03]: Making fun of some earlier controversy.
[SPEAKER_03]: RobD says, is Dirk Nowitzki there to suck in Second Life?
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: KevinTheGroove says, in second life, you waste your first life.
[SPEAKER_03]: Duh.
[SPEAKER_03]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: Responses from chat.orangelongeradio.com
[SPEAKER_03]: Now this is a little more interesting of a sports story, I think.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pro football players will be training with Electronic Arts Madden technology.
[SPEAKER_03]: The same technology that's used in Electronic Arts popular Madden games is now being used to create a training simulator for professional football players.
[SPEAKER_03]: XOS Technologies is licensing the TDT engine from EA Sports to use in what's called the Play Action Simulator.
[SPEAKER_03]: The play action of Family of Products addresses team demands to uniquely and effectively teach new plays and game plans, says Bob Simmons, who is the XOS Coaching Solutions president.
[SPEAKER_03]: As the current provider of coaching analysis and game planning solutions to more than 200 NFL and NCAA football teams, XOS thoroughly understands how teams prepare weekly for an upcoming opponent.
[SPEAKER_03]: The simulator is built on our TDT engine, which utilizes the same technologies.
[SPEAKER_03]: and gameplay found in our popular Madden NFL game franchise, said the general manager of EA Tiburon, Steve Chang.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you're a Madden fan, I bet that's pretty exciting.
[SPEAKER_03]: But my response would be, what about those poor players who train and then end up with the really low ranking in Madden?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because you know Madden ranks all the real players, and that's got to suck if you're the lowest ranked one.
[SPEAKER_03]: I seem to remember a story, either on this show or another show,
[SPEAKER_03]: What good is an actual simulator anyway?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, you know, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: It didn't help me become a better driver.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just played Ridge Racer.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was going to say, you have driving simulators.
[SPEAKER_03]: Cops do cop scene simulators.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Simulators are there to simulate the real thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: What good is that going to do versus actual real experience?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, keep in mind, there's a lot of strategy in football, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, not just the running around and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe, I don't know, maybe it has to do with strategy and processing.
[SPEAKER_01]: Do you just play Tecmo Bowl?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I do.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tecmo Bowl.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wanted the engine built on Tecmo Bowl.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, anyway.
[SPEAKER_01]: There is another... Why am I getting all the rumors?
[SPEAKER_01]: There's another rumor floating about that Nintendo of America is going to relocate.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was actually posted on Kotaku that employees were told on Thursday that they had until June 1st to choose to willingly relocate or accept a severance package.
[SPEAKER_01]: And the sites for new offices are rumored to be San Francisco and New York.
[SPEAKER_01]: So...
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm hoping for San Francisco!
[SPEAKER_01]: Me too, because I could have applied for all kinds of jobs.
[SPEAKER_01]: And in fact, I actually was going to apply for a number of Nintendo jobs when I thought I was moving to Washington.
[SPEAKER_01]: But now I'm not gonna.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I want jobs there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways, so we have GameStop over here, and of course they have Game over in the UK.
[SPEAKER_04]: And apparently Game has bought out its competitor, GameStation, for...
[SPEAKER_04]: The equivalent of $100 million US Approximately 74 million pounds Or euros, I can't tell And now it will increase So wait, GameStop is to game as GameStation is to EB Games?
[SPEAKER_04]: Something like that, yeah So now they are about over 200 storefronts And the largest chain in Europe
[SPEAKER_04]: GameStop is now a Monopoly?
[SPEAKER_04]: I wouldn't say it's a monopoly, but it's pretty much as close to a monopoly as GameStop is over here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, but GameStop gets, I mean, maybe that's the same perception as in Europe is that GameStop does compete with Best Buy and Walmart and online and the more, you know, the big box stores that carry more than just games.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's where their competition is now.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not like they're the only game store on the face of the earth, so I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because when I get pissed at GameStop, I go to, you know, either I go to GameCrazy or because that's kind of far, I'll go to Best Buy.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: My friend had a real horrible experience at Best Buy last week, and now I'm thinking I may not go there anymore.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fries.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fries, I could do.
[SPEAKER_03]: I could do fries.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like fries.
[SPEAKER_03]: What are you hanging out over there, Drew Nami?
[SPEAKER_03]: You had a problem with fries?
[SPEAKER_03]: Shitty service?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it's got shitty service.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry to hear that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why is it shitty service?
[SPEAKER_04]: I've had stuff that's, like, gone bad, went back there, and they're like, eh, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: At least it's cheap.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then they'll just give me a new one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, anyhow, moving on to another story, um,
[SPEAKER_03]: This is interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: This story somewhat struck a chord.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know about you guys, but this is really big in the news this week about a Chinese student who was attending Clements High School.
[SPEAKER_03]: And of course, because he's a high school student, they don't give us his name.
[SPEAKER_03]: But he was removed from the high school.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is located in Texas in the town of Fort Benz.
[SPEAKER_03]: Parents were complaining he recreated the school grounds in a game, which I believe was Counter-Strike.
[SPEAKER_03]: And he uploaded the map and all his friends were playing in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: and basically he now has to go to an alternate education school.
[SPEAKER_03]: The police called him a terroristic threat and so on and so on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, you can't help but think this is all partially due to the Columbines and the Virginia Techs of the world.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the reason why this struck a chord with me is that when I go back to 10 years ago, 1996, a little more than 10 years ago, my freshman year of college,
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Map editors came out, and what was the first map we tried to make in Duke Nukem?
[SPEAKER_03]: We tried to recreate our dorm in Duke Nukem, because we thought it would be funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, I tried to recreate Roundtable to play Duke Nukem 3D in Roundtable, but it doesn't mean I'm going to go shoot up the place.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's because it's a place you're familiar.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're like, damn, you're sitting there bored or whatever in high school, and you're like, damn, this would be fun to run around and play paintball in or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you can't actually do that, so you create a map that's familiar to you, and you go and play.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just like if you recreated your mall or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: The problem is these people are too fucking scared of everything that they immediately think, oh my god, it's Counter-Strike, you know, therefore he must be a terrorist.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, no, I heard the rumors also because he's Asian.
[SPEAKER_03]: D-Vay in chat says he actually went to jail.
[SPEAKER_03]: There was an update on the story.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks, D-Vay.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's so stupid!
[SPEAKER_03]: What crime did he commit?
[SPEAKER_03]: Seriously, what crime did he commit?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, here's what I'm thinking.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is there a component of this we don't know?
[SPEAKER_03]: Like,
[SPEAKER_03]: Why did the parents complain just about a map?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because my parents didn't know I was making... My parents thought I was doing Homeworld.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know why?
[SPEAKER_03]: They didn't even know I was playing Duke Nukem, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: You know why?
[SPEAKER_04]: They wanted to be the fucking people that fucking saw 9-11 coming and stopped it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what they wanted to be.
[SPEAKER_04]: They said, oh, look, he's recreated a map.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just like that Virginia Tech community.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's get the guy.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is what I'm curious about.
[SPEAKER_03]: Was there something else that we don't know, that the video game blogs aren't talking about?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, he did have a hammer in...
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what he could do with that hammer?
[SPEAKER_04]: He could hammer shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did he make a threat?
[SPEAKER_03]: Like people's skulls.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did he make a threat months ago?
[SPEAKER_03]: Was there something about his demeanor?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I'm stopping to think there's got to be something else.
[SPEAKER_03]: Are we really this trigger happy?
[SPEAKER_03]: No pun intended.
[SPEAKER_03]: Are we really this trigger happy to arrest people?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I'm thinking like, you know, I did this.
[SPEAKER_03]: You did this.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Drew Nami's raising his hand, you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I did it in Unreal.
[SPEAKER_03]: We were playing Laser Tag.
[SPEAKER_03]: and shoot people a lot in video games.
[SPEAKER_03]: I am not actually going to shoot a real person.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm a smart, intelligent person who knows the difference.
[SPEAKER_03]: And even still, 99.99% of the population is like me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Playing Counter-Strike does not make you a killer.
[SPEAKER_04]: It doesn't even teach you how to shoot a gun.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it's a video game.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_03]: More gaming news.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_03]: City of Heroes is, again, one of those games on my big list of games I would like to play, but I just don't find the time to play them.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I bet City of Heroes is a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: Have you ever played that?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, I want to.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was going to try a demo.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some point.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, at least I'll have this thing waiting for me whenever I finally play the damn game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Something interesting to come out.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a dance pad for DDR type games or music rhythm games that's using lasers.
[SPEAKER_04]: Instead of the normal pressure sensors or push button switches and stuff, this one actually uses lasers.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you cut the beam, it counts as a button press.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the brand new Laser Dance Matrix.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not a pad.
[SPEAKER_04]: And what's actually kind of neat about it is it wouldn't really break down, especially since you're not really
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, definitely, they should actually kind of do this with the arcade games.
[SPEAKER_04]: It would probably be a whole lot less teching of the pads.
[SPEAKER_03]: I never even thought of this idea, and it seems brilliant.
[SPEAKER_03]: How can this fail unless the laser goes dead?
[SPEAKER_04]: There is, yeah, seriously, there's no way that this laser would, I mean, there's no way for a button to press the fail.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, at all, unless you just didn't step far enough into the pad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or you kick a laser.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't understand.
[SPEAKER_01]: How could Blu-ray fail?
[SPEAKER_04]: This is different.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can give you a couple examples.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's not competing laser technology.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, maybe there is, but you know what I mean.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm joking.
[SPEAKER_03]: Laser is a laser.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: And that didn't cost anything.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think you can get those at 99-cent stores now.
[SPEAKER_04]: The only thing I could see that there would be a problem with is if you did happen to bump the laser or something, if it's not in a very protective housing, you could unalign it and then there's some calibration issues or maybe light interference from other things.
[SPEAKER_04]: But if it's able to detect a certain wavelength of light or something like that, then it probably would work pretty well.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: HitStun in chat says, doesn't anybody else here remember the Sega Activator?
[SPEAKER_03]: It sucked ass.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did that run on lasers?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's all infrared, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's infrared.
[SPEAKER_03]: Infrared's different, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Infrared's low frequency, and it would, you know, it's not exactly a beam.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's more of just kind of a light source, almost.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, isn't that like, um, because the Wii... It's like the Paraparaparadise pad.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or the Wii, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Isn't that little Wii thing that's on top of your TV?
[SPEAKER_03]: Isn't that infrared?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it's infrared as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why the fuck they don't have a calibration thing on that is beyond me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Come on, Nintendo!
[SPEAKER_04]: It makes sense!
[SPEAKER_03]: Now our chatroom is full of LaserCats jokes as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just, you know, everything from that sketch.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because, you know, we've talked about LaserCats the game on the program before.
[SPEAKER_03]: The one thing that will definitively end the next-gen war will be the console that can get LaserCats the game as an exclusive will be the winner of the next-gen war in the OLR book.
[SPEAKER_03]: Frickin' LaserBeans on some frickin' cats.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is that too hard to ask?
[SPEAKER_03]: What if it's like the PlayStation 2?
[SPEAKER_03]: Then the PlayStation 2 wins the next-gen war.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't buy any of them.
[SPEAKER_03]: Keep your PS2.
[SPEAKER_03]: It has laser cats.
[SPEAKER_03]: Seriously, whoever gets laser cats wins.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you're a winner for listening to Orange Lounge Radio, but we are going to take a break here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: And for those of you listening on our audio archive, also known as podcasting, we'll be back in a couple days with our Part B. This way we spread the OLR love throughout the week.
[SPEAKER_03]: those of you listening live don't have to wait quite as long we'll be right back after this with more Orange Lounge Radio