[SPEAKER_05]: We are live here at the E3 Outpost for this special Thursday E3 2006 edition.
[SPEAKER_05]: Welcome everybody to the Thursday edition of Orange Lounge Radio, live from the E3 Outpost, celebrating all things that is E3 2006.
[SPEAKER_05]: My name is Rob Roberts, you might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_05]: Joining me as always, say hello to my exhausted yet perky co-host, DarkSakura, also known as Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_05]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_02]: I slept on the thingy.
[SPEAKER_05]: On the bus?
[SPEAKER_05]: I hate LA traffic.
[SPEAKER_02]: It took long enough that I could sleep.
[SPEAKER_02]: I took a proper nap.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, say hello to the one and only Techmaster Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_07]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm good.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just ate a bunch of popcorn, chicken, and bacon out of these potato skins.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loving the catering at the E3 Outpost.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then I took the bacon and dipped it in barbecue sauce.
[SPEAKER_07]: Good people.
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what I can do.
[SPEAKER_05]: Prove super bacon to the next level.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Next time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, say hello.
[SPEAKER_05]: Joining us again tonight, our good pal, Bobby Blackwolf.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yo.
[SPEAKER_05]: How you doing, Bobby?
[SPEAKER_05]: Tired, my feet hurt.
[SPEAKER_05]: I am all weed out.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's probably how everybody feels about you after eating three today.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, wave hello to Mr. Lawrence Young, who is producing us tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: He doesn't have a mic, so he can't say hi back.
[SPEAKER_06]: But this is what he would say.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, first of all, for those of you guys listening live tonight, it's about, what, 7.50 and we were supposed to be on at 6.30?
[SPEAKER_05]: I apologize, especially to those of you guys on the East Coast.
[SPEAKER_05]: Crap happens.
[SPEAKER_05]: We were actually at a booth right up until 5.45.
[SPEAKER_05]: We had an appointment at a booth, and so we actually missed the first shuttle back here to the outpost, so we had to wait for the second one.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I apologize.
[SPEAKER_05]: It happens.
[SPEAKER_05]: Technical difficulties.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway...
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's talk about E3 and some of the stuff we saw today.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to play three interesting things.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, what's one of them?
[SPEAKER_02]: I went to the Kings of Korea, or whatever they called it, and apparently one of the companies is bringing out a new Kunio game.
[SPEAKER_02]: They said 2007, but they're basically giving rebirth to the Kunio franchise, which I thought was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: And he seemed absolutely surprised that I would... Is that a Kunio game?! !
[SPEAKER_05]: For those who don't know what that is, was that a popular anime?
[SPEAKER_02]: It was brought over as River City Ransom.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh shit!
[SPEAKER_02]: And Dodgeball.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's all I needed to hear.
[SPEAKER_02]: But overseas it was Hot Blooded Downtown Story and Kunio's Dodgeball.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's this new game they're doing?
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't really tell much about it because I don't read Korean.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's Kunio game.
[SPEAKER_05]: What did it look like?
[SPEAKER_05]: Were they playing a sport?
[SPEAKER_05]: Were they beating each other up?
[SPEAKER_02]: They didn't show any pictures of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was just like the artwork for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was like, Kunio game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I don't care.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Kunio.
[SPEAKER_02]: The same guy who I surprised was also surprised that I played Ragnarok Online.
[SPEAKER_02]: He was apparently one of the people who worked on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, very cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was like, hey, you're my hero.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have created my addiction.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you want to talk to DarkSakura about Kunio, you can join our chat room.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's chat.allgames.com for tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: But everything is actually filtered through Bobby tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I left the Ibyuk at home.
[SPEAKER_05]: I call it the Ibyuk after Bjork because I love her.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I have my Ibyuk back at the hotel.
[SPEAKER_05]: So DarkSakura and Loki and myself have no way of seeing chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Only Bobby.
[SPEAKER_06]: So be nice to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can see from here and I can laugh at people.
[SPEAKER_05]: We will take calls a little later on in the program, but if you're calling in right now, too bad, we're playing a game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just to say something to Fantav.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've been looking for Gravity every year so I can ask him where's Ragnarok Online 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wasn't Ragnarok Online 2 supposed to be last year's E3?
[SPEAKER_02]: I have no idea.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gravity never shows up.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're too busy banning people.
[SPEAKER_02]: There is actually a Wikipedia article up for Ragnarok Online, too, that has some of the features from previous information that's been leaked.
[SPEAKER_02]: So maybe you find something there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: There hasn't been a site.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have a site for it, but it's a placeholder.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Again, for those of you guys who are listening to us and going, God, those guys don't sound normal.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, that's because we're at the E3 Outpost, and you get that nice ambient, the little club going on in the background.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ooh, ooh.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who's DJing down there?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who's?
[SPEAKER_05]: Pretty funky.
[SPEAKER_05]: Lawrence is shaking his head.
[SPEAKER_05]: I am.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can probably check my player.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's get his card after the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, what was something you saw today?
[SPEAKER_05]: We heard about Korean Kunio.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's something interesting you saw today, Loki?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, something a bit more normal, I guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: We actually went and saw the Gears of War demonstration and that was pretty sexy, actually.
[SPEAKER_05]: I totally dig the way Microsoft has their theater set up.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's the way you do it right there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, the way Microsoft had their theater for Gears of War is that you actually went in and you would put these headphones on so that all the outside noise is blocked.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you can hear the Gears of War stuff clearly and that way you're not blasting the whole booth full of noise.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then there's also surround sound in the floor.
[SPEAKER_05]: So like when the guns went off, it vibrated your butt.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's exactly how this was last year.
[SPEAKER_05]: So if you want a free butt massage at E3, go check out the Gears of War demo.
[SPEAKER_05]: What did you think of the game itself, though, Gears of War?
[SPEAKER_07]: I thought it looked awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not really into a lot of first-person shooters, but it looked pretty solid.
[SPEAKER_07]: It looked...
[SPEAKER_07]: I haven't seen the Halo trailer yet, but I would say it probably looks better than Halo.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't do a lot of first-person shooters either.
[SPEAKER_05]: I do do Halo.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think Halo's awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: But Gears of War, what I liked about it is that it looked like it was really dummy-fied.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like a lot of one-button stuff, because when...
[SPEAKER_05]: And basically the developer or whoever was showing it to us went through the game twice.
[SPEAKER_05]: The first time, or the level.
[SPEAKER_05]: The first time they went through the first level and just like jammed through it.
[SPEAKER_05]: They just jammed through the level and I was like, wow, that guy's doing a lot of shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll never be able to recreate that.
[SPEAKER_05]: But then the second time he went back through the game and showed how easy it was to be hacking people with chainsaws and all the cool stuff he was doing.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a very violent game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very violent.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very, very pretty, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, and it was the only minor, minor bench I have is that there was some frame rate problems, but I'm hoping... I think that's just the video.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it's just a develop or whatever it is issue, and that'll be gone by the time it actually rolls out.
[SPEAKER_05]: For those of you guys that are into Halo, the fact that this thing has multiplayer, this is going to be your holdover for Halo 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it might even be...
[SPEAKER_05]: A real good, like, right up there competitor with Halo 3, like Half-Life, Quake, one of those.
[SPEAKER_05]: It might actually be coming out around the same time as Halo 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, they said 2006, so we're holding them to that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, Halo's supposed to be in 2006 also.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't believe it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I say Halo 3 not until next year.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, they said otherwise.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't give a crap what they say.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not true.
[SPEAKER_05]: They would have shown playable footage of E3 if it was true.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good point.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bobby, three interesting things, what's one of them?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I kind of spent all day in one place, so it's kind of hard.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, well you've got to have seen at least three demos while you were there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Where did you spend your whole day?
[SPEAKER_06]: I spent my whole day playing with my Wii and Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_06]: You guys suck with your booth design making me wait in line for two hours so I could sit in other lines watching people play 20 minute demos.
[SPEAKER_06]: So if there's four people in front of you, that's an hour just to play one game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hate Nintendo's booth this year.
[SPEAKER_05]: I absolutely hate it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not talking about the games in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: The booth?
[SPEAKER_05]: I hate it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is horrible compared to the past two years.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's atrocious.
[SPEAKER_05]: I could just...
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to do FUs of the week later.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did we bring One Week in Angel?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I didn't.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're going to sing it.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, no, later.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I did get to play a lot with the Wii, and I'll pretty much start.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, the first thing that I'll talk about here is probably the tech demos and some of the stuff that they're doing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, wait.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to help you here.
[SPEAKER_05]: What was the first thing you went for?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because you get in there, there's, what, 20 games in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: You must have went right to something.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: We Orchestra.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why did you pick We Orchestra?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because it was the first one in the little thing to go in.
[SPEAKER_05]: Were you just like, you're going to go in there like, I'm going to go around each and every one of these things?
[SPEAKER_02]: It wasn't quite set up like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: You had to get past this row of little mini living rooms, and then you got to the demo.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, see, and We Orchestra was in the living room.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was like the least packed living room.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm a music person, so...
[SPEAKER_06]: I did it, and for those since, you know, you guys don't, you know, here on Orange Songs Radio, you guys don't really know some of my background.
[SPEAKER_06]: I actually play symphonic percussion.
[SPEAKER_06]: I am in two wind symphonies in the Atlanta area.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I know how to conduct, because I have conducted before.
[SPEAKER_06]: But what I was trying to see is, I know Dance Dance Revolution is not a dancing simulator.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can't learn how to play guitar with Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can't conduct with Wii Orchestra.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was very hard.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was trying to use real conducting techniques and it's not that good yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: You do have to treat it like a video game.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's sometimes too sensitive, sometimes not sensitive enough.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it was interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: What did you learn about the Wii controller today?
[SPEAKER_06]: I learned the tech specs of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: What are the tech specs of the Wiimote?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't care what... I'm calling this the Wiimote.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura says Wiicon.
[SPEAKER_05]: I say Wiimote.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we're just always going to have this back and forth until Miyamoto can clear this up.
[SPEAKER_06]: By the way, Funnydale Final Furlong was right at the very end of the booth.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway...
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nintendo kept saying, making you think that it was kind of like a 3D mouse.
[SPEAKER_06]: It would be able to tell where it was in 3D space.
[SPEAKER_06]: You'd be able to put the controller on the floor and know it was on the floor.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it's not like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's accelerometers and an IR infrared blaster, just like your TV's remote control.
[SPEAKER_06]: So a lot of things, like people were saying, oh, it's so sensitive.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, when they were playing like the Duck Hunt thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's because it's an IR, and the receiver is that little sensor that has double-stick tape that you put under your TV.
[SPEAKER_06]: So the farther away you are from your TV, the less sensitive it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's how you fix the sensitivity.
[SPEAKER_06]: But since we were two feet away from the screen, it was very, very, very sensitive.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, also the thing is they're going to be adjusting the sensitivity in there.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're going to have an adjustment very similar to like calibrating a mouse sensitivity.
[SPEAKER_06]: Right, but I mean, what I'm saying is we could step back another foot and that would adjust the sensitivity as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they're not telling people that.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're trying to say it's some revolutionary technology.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tell me more about the sensor.
[SPEAKER_06]: You said it's just a little piece of tape?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it's a little piece.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, no, it's not really tape.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's got double stick tape.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's how it attaches to your TV.
[SPEAKER_06]: But you can put it on a table.
[SPEAKER_06]: As long, you know, because some people were asking, you know, okay, I have a projector and I project on my wall.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they're like, well, you know, you should mount it to the wall underneath where your screen is or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_06]: And stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it's not used in every game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Only in the games that actually use the IR sensor, which Excite Truck is not one of.
[SPEAKER_06]: That only used the accelerometers in them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, you know, some games don't even need that sensor.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can take that sensor away and still play Excite Truck.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was very interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think Bobby's going to win round one of three interesting things, because that was very interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, here's mine.
[SPEAKER_05]: My interesting thing I saw was Luminous 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: I went and saw Luminous 2, which was being shown at Buena Vista Games.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know why Luminous 2 is interesting?
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't see any damn difference from Luminous 1.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not a damn thing was different from Luminous 1.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, some of the themes were different and it seemed to have more video in the background and they've changed the look.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was surprised because Luminous Live on Xbox looks a lot like Luminous 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: As for new modes, whatever else, it wasn't in the demo, so I couldn't tell you.
[SPEAKER_05]: And nobody at the booth told me anything extra.
[SPEAKER_05]: So as far as I know, if you have Luminous, there's really no need to get Luminous 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: I imagine they'll announce other things later, but they're not in the demo.
[SPEAKER_05]: I started the demo from scratch.
[SPEAKER_05]: It takes you right in the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: In fact, some of the music was the same.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, some of the music and themes were the exact same.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, you got a second interesting thing for us?
[SPEAKER_02]: Star Trek Legacy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ah, yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, this is the show that made us late.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: We had a meeting with Bethesda to see their demo for that.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was pretty sick.
[SPEAKER_02]: You basically can pick from any generation of the Star Trek universe with the exception of, I think, Enterprise.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, Enterprise is in there all five generations.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, Enterprise was not there.
[SPEAKER_02]: As in the series Enterprise.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, the series Enterprise, not the ship.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, according to the trailer that they had, it included Enterprise.
[SPEAKER_02]: According to them, they had Original Series, they had Next Generation, Deep Space Nine, and Voyager.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was... They actually, on the demo, they recreated the battle from The Wrath of Khan.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: This game is a Trekkie's wet dream.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: They went all out.
[SPEAKER_05]: They have everything nailed down, like the ship specs, like you're saying, the recreation of certain scenarios.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, you know, if you're into Star Trek, you're going to think it's great.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have full range of motion in that game.
[SPEAKER_02]: On top of that, if you are a little bit...
[SPEAKER_02]: It's definitely a tactical ship game too.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually thought when we were going in there, I thought we were going to see the Star Trek MMO, which is nowhere to be seen.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess it's still in early development, but...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: It's definitely very complete for the Star Trek hardcore fan.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, they went to all these resources.
[SPEAKER_05]: And even for the casual Trek fan, it's going to have tutorial modes that ease you into it and easy scenarios type situations.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's very pretty to look at.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, it's a pretty, pretty game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was very impressed with Star Trek Legacy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thumbs up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, one interesting thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: I got to play more of the PlayStation 2 today.
[SPEAKER_07]: The interesting part... Why don't you come over to my house and play PlayStation 2?
[SPEAKER_07]: You mean PlayStation 3?
[SPEAKER_07]: PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: I played both today.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_00]: I got it only.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: I actually played two different games.
[SPEAKER_07]: And here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: The surprising thing is I'm not impressed by PlayStation 3 at all.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I played one of the games I've been looking forward to ever since I saw the video, MotorStorm.
[SPEAKER_07]: What...
[SPEAKER_07]: What did you like about the movie that you saw?
[SPEAKER_07]: What I liked about the movie, the movie made it seem like it's going to be burnout off-road type of thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Really fast, really crazy-ass gameplay where cars are just crashing and flipping all over the place and exploding.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fire, just lots of stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: And what was the reality of the demo?
[SPEAKER_07]: The reality of the demo was it was just an off-road game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Cars seemed to be driving extremely slow.
[SPEAKER_07]: In fact, you know, a lot of times you'd fall off a cliff or whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you did happen to crash, they would do a slow-mo instant replay of it, and it was very unimpressive.
[SPEAKER_07]: I checked out Gran Turismo HD and also not impressed by it at all.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, the paper people.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're back.
[SPEAKER_07]: In high def.
[SPEAKER_07]: 1080p.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're actually kind of 3D, but they don't move.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're just kind of stationary.
[SPEAKER_06]: In the Grand Canyon level, they do move.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, a little bit.
[SPEAKER_07]: But here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you drive past them, they're still looking behind you down the track like something's going to happen.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, let's give them a break, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's an early, early build.
[SPEAKER_05]: That all might still change.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's pretty.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll give it that.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're not the only game that uses paper people.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, let's look at MotoGP 2006.
[SPEAKER_07]: I played that today also.
[SPEAKER_07]: Same problem.
[SPEAKER_07]: The whole thing is, it's not impressive enough to get me to spend more money.
[SPEAKER_07]: This thing has got to be leaps and bounds better than the 360 in order for me to spend that kind of money.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm really not seeing anything really unique and revolutionary coming out for anything on the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's all just more of the same crap, just prettier.
[SPEAKER_07]: I did notice though that Sonic the Hedgehog and there's a few other games I think that were on both platforms looked a little better on the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Sonic looked a little bit better.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mobile Suit Gundam looked extremely better than the 360 version.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know if it's the monitors that they're playing on, but it looked like night and day for that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pretty Graphics can't make me forgive the botched job done on Sonic.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, Bobby, how's the chatroom doing?
[SPEAKER_06]: They're doing fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're bitching about G4 right now, actually.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're asking if we went by G4's booth and what was going on.
[SPEAKER_05]: I avoided it at all costs.
[SPEAKER_05]: I heard a bunch of monkeys outside the booth today going, Oh my god!
[SPEAKER_05]: What were they cheering for?
[SPEAKER_06]: Attack of the Show, I think, was live.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, Mom, I'm on TV.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, Kevin Pereira, I want to suck your dick.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, no, not for me.
[SPEAKER_07]: I kept running into them today.
[SPEAKER_07]: They have, like, group babes doing, like, weird things.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, you brought this up when we were walking around, that there was not a swarm of G4 people like there was in years past.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's because they're not a gaming channel.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, right, I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're off getting guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did they get you?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, that's their slogan.
[SPEAKER_05]: We get guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're all getting guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's why I'm asking you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did they get you?
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, good.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, they don't have me.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hid from them.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's the thing, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: I see swarms of GameTap shirts, which is okay because I like GameTap.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I was surprised at that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think they're working for GameTap.
[SPEAKER_05]: Was GameTap giving away something to shirt holders?
[SPEAKER_05]: They were giving away shirts.
[SPEAKER_05]: I missed that one out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, yeah, but you don't wear your shirts that you win the next day.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some people do.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's a freak.
[SPEAKER_05]: The shirts I get at E3, I wear to the gym, which isn't very often, but that's where they get used.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's my wardrobe is all my E3 shirts, and I haven't gotten a single one this year.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to be naked next week, and I'm a fat man, so that's not a good thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you for watching, and I'll see you next time.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: I got a clock from the Korean people.
[SPEAKER_05]: Pretty soon E3 is going to be online.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's fine, though, because I hate traffic here.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wish they'd move E3 to Vegas or somewhere that's built to hold a convention.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think they should bring it back to Atlanta.
[SPEAKER_06]: I loved it when it was in Atlanta.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, but you have selfish reasons for that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually wouldn't mind going to Atlanta.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wouldn't mind either.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sure it's a great place.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because then I can go to E3 and drive back to Mobile and hang out with my family and then fly home.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think you're right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dear ESA, please have E3 in Mr. Blackwell's backyard.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Speaking of Bobby, one interesting thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Another one, number two.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, another one.
[SPEAKER_06]: One thing, since more Wii, since apparently I played the Wii all day today.
[SPEAKER_05]: You played with your Wii all day long.
[SPEAKER_06]: I played with my Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's impressive.
[SPEAKER_06]: And here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: A lot of people are actually wondering about, and this is more about the IR games.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're like, oh, my arm's going to get tired when I play these games all that much.
[SPEAKER_05]: Your arm gets tired after you play with your Wii too long.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, WarioWare does make you do hula hoops and squats and stuff like that, but not all the games are going to really tire you out.
[SPEAKER_06]: And so I thought that was kind of interesting, you know, how natural I could actually be laying on the couch and playing some of these games.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think there actually need to be more games that wear people out.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura wants Wii Torture Chamber.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I don't want Wii Torture Chamber.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want, like, Wii Robics and, like, Wii Boot Camp.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wii Boot Camp sounds better.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wii Boot Camp.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I think about Dance Aerobics and I'm like...
[SPEAKER_05]: They could fully bring back Dance Aerobics on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hook up a DDR mat and then have the controller and there you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's pretty much the same thing with the eye toy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, but this is by Nintendo, so it'll be better.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it'd be awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know it and I know it.
[SPEAKER_05]: If they brought out a new Dance Aerobics, you'd play it once and that would be it.
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's me.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: My second interesting thing I saw today would be the Eye of Judgment.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you make your judgment on it?
[SPEAKER_05]: I did make a judgment on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: What a waste of fucking space at the PlayStation 3 booth.
[SPEAKER_05]: What a waste of fucking space.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm sorry to the guys that developed this because I'm sure they worked very hard on this, but now is not the time to be showing me the eye of judgment.
[SPEAKER_05]: The eye of judgment could have been done on the PS2.
[SPEAKER_05]: From my perspective, now granted I don't know any tech stuff about PS3, the Eye of Judgment, for those that don't know what the Eye of Judgment is, it's that thing they showed at the conference where you put the car down and whoosh, a monster comes onto the screen.
[SPEAKER_05]: It looked like Yu-Gi-Oh.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess it's supposed to be a game, but the people admitted that it wasn't really a game but more like a tech demo.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, you saw the Eye of Judgment.
[SPEAKER_05]: What was your thoughts?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: When basically you have to put down a card and the eye toy, or it wasn't really an eye toy, it was just a camera, would recognize these barcode light things on top and bottom of the card.
[SPEAKER_07]: And there's also like four triangles on it to kind of orient the card so it knows which direction it's facing because that's important.
[SPEAKER_07]: So basically it will spawn whatever monster based on what card it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now here's the thing that really kind of bugged me about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can cast spells on your monsters as well, but the spell card is put on top of the monster card, and you have to remember to take the card off after the spell is cast, otherwise it casts again, because it's stupid.
[SPEAKER_07]: and also if you're playing the game and happen to destroy a monster you have to remember to take it off the board otherwise it spawns the monster again because it's stupid.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, the Eye of Judgment has an IQ of about 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here's the other thing that the geniuses... They need a brain of judgment.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here's the geniuses that Sony didn't think about.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, this game uses actual cards like magic cards or something like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, if you're actually going to be playing this game, they're playing on selling expansion packs later on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here's the only problem here.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can probably scan those cards and print them back out again, and there you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: You have two cards because the camera's not going to know the difference between a fake and a real card.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bobby, who are those cats in Ken's show we saw the first day that are here tonight?
[SPEAKER_05]: NoVint Falcon.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, NoVint.
[SPEAKER_05]: N-O-V-I-N-T.
[SPEAKER_05]: Describe NoVint for the listeners real quick, and there's a reason I'm doing this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, NoVint Falcon, basically what it is, it's a PC peripheral, and it takes USB, and essentially it has touch sensitive, so it's a little ball, and I will link it in chat because I've got to go find it on Google, and I'll put the link in chat.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's NoVint.com slash Falcon.htm or something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: You put your fingers on this little ball, and say there is a ball on the screen, you actually push forward and it will stop at the ball.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can actually trace around the ball, and then if they have ridges on it, you can actually feel the ridges as you touch the ball.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or if you have balls, you can have a rubber band, and it will actually pull you around.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can feel your balls right there in your hand.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we have gone from the weed to the balls.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, but seriously though.
[SPEAKER_06]: Explicit tag, here we come.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I think we have to explicit this show.
[SPEAKER_05]: The point is that these are all tech demos.
[SPEAKER_05]: But this, they also have, what was it, Half-Life they were showing?
[SPEAKER_05]: They had Half-Life 2 and something else.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they are here tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: That, I went and played that and I thought, this is great.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why isn't this on a console?
[SPEAKER_05]: That is what Sony should be having in their little rooms right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Eye of Judgment is, it is not time for the Eye of Judgment.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would have been far more impressed if Sony had teamed up with those NoVent guys and were showing that thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not a smart name to be calling that either.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Eye of Judgment.
[SPEAKER_07]: I judge this crap.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is NoVent.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: We've got to keep things moving.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you guys are listening live, Gamer Andy will be on momentarily.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm looking right at him.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's sitting there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, Gamer Andy.
[SPEAKER_05]: How are you doing?
[SPEAKER_05]: We're starting to butt into his time a little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Ultimate Ghosts and Goblins on PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was pretty!
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, this is not the same as the Capcom Classics thing that also has Ghosts and Goblins, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: This is an all-new Ghosts and Goblins game.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's so funky new about it?
[SPEAKER_02]: You don't get golden armor, you get, like, blue pimp armor or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, like, one of the enemies, the new one, is these hands that reach out of the ground and grab you and, like, throw you into a vat of acid or...
[SPEAKER_02]: I did go on one of the bosses, because I actually knew weapons.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you have a refillable life bar.
[SPEAKER_02]: But when that's out, then you turn into the naked guy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: That seems to help the difficulty a little bit, I think.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually avoided them at first because I thought they were the holy water, and the holy water sucks.
[SPEAKER_02]: One of your weapons is a crossbow.
[SPEAKER_02]: You also have little bombs.
[SPEAKER_02]: You start off with the lances, of course, which I still think are the better weapon.
[SPEAKER_02]: You also get a vine whip, which really sucks ass.
[SPEAKER_02]: Another cool thing about that, this made me laugh, I actually took a little bit of video of this, sort of stealthily, is one of the curse forms that he can get is as a woman.
Wow.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which I would think that would be a blessing.
[SPEAKER_02]: What a curse indeed.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, hey, it actually made the boss fight better, because she is like in this big, she looks very...
[SPEAKER_02]: Peasant German, you know, like you see in the old history books.
[SPEAKER_02]: In a big dress, and she'd sort of float in the air, sort of like Princess Peach.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which was cool because you could still attack.
[SPEAKER_02]: She would just move slower, like a really huge woman.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you throw attacks while you're floating in the air, and you could still hit the boss.
[SPEAKER_02]: It actually ended up being more convenient, but of course when you get hit, you lose the form again.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I enjoyed it immensely.
[SPEAKER_02]: The music was still good.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was also right next to Tekken, so I was going between the two for a while.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, my, you know, and I actually wasn't too sure about it at first until I talked to Dan on the phone yesterday.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's like, you were going to go play Ultimate Ghosts and Goblins.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I did, and I had a good time.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I was almost hanging out with Julie, Custom E19, who she was over there playing Ace Combat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right on.
[SPEAKER_02]: She's like, I don't like this game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was like, go play Ghosts and Goblins.
[SPEAKER_02]: She's like, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: But no, it was great.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was fantastic.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, the surprising game that I saw today was this game that's probably from a company no one's ever heard of.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's actually by this group called On Games, and the game was called Wild Summer.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now,
[SPEAKER_07]: Basically, this game is like a sandbox game, very similar to Grand Theft Auto, but it's basically like kind of a plotline to American Pie.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're this, you know, trouble-starting teenager, you know, with hormones raging.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki, tell them why we went to look at this game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because I saw the game and I'm like, ooh, I gotta go play that because it looked like Laser Suit Larry.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I...
[SPEAKER_05]: I know I saw the poster and it showed this teenage boy that was stealing panties off a clothesline.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I was like, I have to see whatever that fucking game is.
[SPEAKER_05]: That looks too unreal to be true.
[SPEAKER_07]: So anyways, it looks amazing so far.
[SPEAKER_07]: They still have about a year and a half of development left.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's supposed to be coming out in fall of 2007.
[SPEAKER_07]: But the thing is, it's going to be... They've got a ton of different stuff in here.
[SPEAKER_07]: One of the things that they were showing was the kind of...
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, what was it?
[SPEAKER_07]: Like the free-running type of stuff in there.
[SPEAKER_07]: So you're jumping from buildings and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: You kind of have the same Prince of Persia, like, gameplay.
[SPEAKER_07]: It also has, you know, a bunch of mini-games, including, like, dancing, playing beach volleyball.
[SPEAKER_07]: But they have a dating part in it, too, kind of like a dating sim.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the way the dating sim is, it's going to be playing, like, Magic the Gathering.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're actually going to have, like, cards for, you know, pretend you're interested in her conversation, you know, get her drunk.
[SPEAKER_05]: Stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a very ambitious game.
[SPEAKER_05]: It sounds like there's a lot they want to do with it.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I was really impressed with the guy.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they were very nice to us, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: It looked like they've gone into a lot of detail.
[SPEAKER_05]: They've really thought out about what they want to do, like what their dream game is.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they're going and doing it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I asked this question.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Jamie, you might appreciate this.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I said, why would a woman ever want to play this game?
[SPEAKER_05]: I said, what is in this for a woman?
[SPEAKER_05]: And basically what they said is that we have women on staff helping us write this game.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're not out to make a tacky game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Leisure Suit Larry is now a tacky franchise.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're out to make a fun game.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's why there's no nudity in this game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's no nudity.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not perverted.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just silly fun, like the American Pie or Porky's movies, those types of things.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just a little bit of dumb fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: So they think that women might want to play it just because it's silly.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not meant to be a serious game.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not interested.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really?
[SPEAKER_02]: Take a look.
[SPEAKER_02]: I walked by it.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I was over there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not interested.
[SPEAKER_02]: What turns you on?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't see what fun it is to play a hormonal 16-year-old.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, you haven't been a hormonal 16-year-old boy, so... Exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have no interest in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's nothing that links it to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was spending my 16-year-old kicking off the horny 16-year-old boys.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_07]: They still have Desperate Housewives out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Desperate Housewives will teach you how to cook and gossip.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what I found out today.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was surprised.
[SPEAKER_05]: They actually go into extreme detail on cooking in that game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it's like, you know, you can pick from recipes and all this crap...
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't need a video game to teach me how to cook.
[SPEAKER_06]: I am so glad I'm on the edge of this stage so I can just run down the stairs as quick as possible.
[SPEAKER_05]: We've done this for years.
[SPEAKER_02]: And one of these days, I'm going to combust.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you'll be right next to me.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was actually surprised at how thorough the Desperate Housewives game looked to be.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was actually kind of surprised.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a really intricate game, but it's stupid.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a great game, but stupid.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's intricate, but stupid.
[SPEAKER_05]: Intricately stupid.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: What a waste.
[SPEAKER_05]: But Wild Summer, you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it'll be cute.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to see it.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're working on getting it on the 360, and to be honest, there's nothing like it out there, especially on the 360.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they had other games, too, that looked pretty good.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, we've got to keep it moving, guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bobby, one more interesting thing from today.
[SPEAKER_06]: Going for the Wii trifecta, because I just can't stop talking about my Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, wouldn't that be a Triforce, Bobby, a Triforce?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll be here till Friday.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: The virtual console.
[SPEAKER_06]: They actually had two demo units running of the Virtual Console with that new controller that they were showing that looks like a Super Nintendo controller with dual analog sticks.
[SPEAKER_06]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's a very light controller, very comfortable to me.
[SPEAKER_06]: They had five games running.
[SPEAKER_06]: They had one for each system, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_06]: They had Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_06]: on the NES, Super Mario World on the SNES, Super Mario 64 on the N64, Sonic the Hedgehog on Genesis, and Bonk's Adventure on the TurboGrafx.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Then I'll back off.
[SPEAKER_06]: The thing is, though, I haven't played a TurboGrafx in so long.
[SPEAKER_06]: I believe that Bonks worked really well.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it looked fine to me.
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't notice any glitches or anything, but I can't compare it to the original TurboGrafx.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did it tell you to press run?
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Chat room question from a while ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yes, please.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, chat room again.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't have the ibyuk, so we can't look at chat, Jamie and I. But Bobby, what's chat room say?
[SPEAKER_06]: CKY Mike, who thinks I should join you guys full time, asked what game... You want to move to Sacramento?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I'll move to Sacramento.
[SPEAKER_06]: How about that?
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: What game demos did you get to download at the PSP booth?
[SPEAKER_06]: I believe that's a Matt thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a Loki thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Capcom Classic Collection Reloaded Gangs of London
[SPEAKER_07]: was one of them.
[SPEAKER_07]: They had Lemmings.
[SPEAKER_07]: The one I played, Every Extended Extra.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, Every Extended Extra.
[SPEAKER_07]: E3.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that was okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: They had Ratchet & Clank Size Matters.
[SPEAKER_07]: I played that for a little bit.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then I can't remember what the last game was.
[SPEAKER_07]: It wasn't that standout.
[SPEAKER_05]: Every extended extra seemed okay to me.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was weird.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was a little weird.
[SPEAKER_05]: It wasn't what I expected from Q Entertainment, but I think it'll be a good time.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like how they reused some of the sound effects from Luminous.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, that was funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I have an honorable mention.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, yeah, let's do quick, real quick, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: We want to try and start wrapping this up.
[SPEAKER_05]: We are going to take a couple quick, quick phone calls, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bobby, tell them how to get in.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, you can call 1-866-880-0156.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Soul free number in the United States.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some quickies first, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_05]: WTF.
[SPEAKER_05]: The WTF game is amazing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I chopped rabbits in half.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was great.
[SPEAKER_02]: I did the wood chopping game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically, it's a bunch of really, really messed up mini games.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the ones that Julie and I actually played was the wood chopping game, where you chop wood for money.
[SPEAKER_02]: Only the thing is that the grandma lady will randomly put out an animal.
[SPEAKER_05]: The chicken sorting game was fantastic because you could do... It looks very WarioWare-ish.
[SPEAKER_05]: You sort them as boys, girls, or dead.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ha ha ha!
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I said, what, Heaven?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, Heaven.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because they're dead.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's why they go to Heaven.
[SPEAKER_05]: But that's great.
[SPEAKER_05]: That made me go WTF.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a great town.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, we've got to go.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was work time fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's go to the telephone.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, Seproth1215.
[SPEAKER_05]: Seproth1215, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_05]: We've got to make it quick tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, I was going to say, there has been a little bit of an update for the Imani booth.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: I did not hear, you said Guitar Freaks broke?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, Guitar Freaks was a response to Guitar Hero
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that they had the guitar freaks and the mania there to have people come over to their booth.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it was a press attention thing showing, I think they wanted to show, look at our arcade machines, look at, we are bringing the arcade experience home.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the weird thing about that, I don't understand the logic of a Guitar Freaks being there.
[SPEAKER_05]: I still don't, but maybe they want to show, hey, we've been doing this in the arcade for a long time.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not one to say why they have that there, if it is a response to Guitar Hero or what.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or maybe they're like me in seeing how non-innovative Guitar Hero is, because it's been out forever in Japan as Guitar Freaks.
[SPEAKER_05]: See, but I disagree, because I do think Guitar Hero is innovative, but in a different way than you do.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or you don't, I should say.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um...
[SPEAKER_05]: And what was the other part of that you said that they were reporting, Sephiroth?
[SPEAKER_08]: They said that 2DX was there because of...
[SPEAKER_08]: They wanted to show the press how cool it would be and the potential that it has.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would agree with that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why not show the press the arc- Because a lot of people, when the Beatmania trailer showed, it said bringing the arcade experience home, and a lot of people said, what arcade experience?
[SPEAKER_05]: And I think Konami just wanted to show what these games look like.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'll tell you what, there were lots of cameras filming both of those games.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what Konami wants, people filming their stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nothing wrong with a little attention, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, yeah, but the problem with that is they did say that they don't have any plans for another US sequel because they don't know whether or not it's sold well enough.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, the problem I have with that is if I look back on DDR, I mean, they went on for a while and probably didn't sell well until maybe at least Max.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, it did sell pretty well.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe that was the nice way of saying, we just can't tell you anything right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think, honestly, that was the nice way of saying, we can't talk about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hope so.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, we'll hope so too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Seproth, we gotta let you go to take another call, but thanks for calling, alright?
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, thanks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, we got another one already?
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, real quick, before we answer this.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I thought you had a comment.
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, alright, we'll go to the phone.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio, who's this?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, this is SilentWind96 again.
[SPEAKER_05]: SilentWind96.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nice to meet you last night.
[SPEAKER_05]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, thanks for getting me in, guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: No problem.
[SPEAKER_05]: What did you think of the E3 Outpost?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I loved it.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you're in the LA area, come on down.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're right off Santa Monica and 405.
[SPEAKER_09]: What did you call in about?
[SPEAKER_09]: I just want to extend my thanks again for letting me hang out with you guys.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm on my way home back to Bakersfield.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've got to be up at 3 o'clock in the morning to go to work.
[SPEAKER_05]: Poor guy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for the call.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm glad you had a good time.
[SPEAKER_05]: What was something fun you did while you were here?
[SPEAKER_09]: At the outpost, I was able to talk to some of the guys from Intellivision and
[SPEAKER_09]: Check out the demo for Lost Planet, which is awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Watch Bobby Platt kick in Uno by the computer.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, SilentWind96 brought us the full version of Uno for us to take a look at.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I love him for it.
[SPEAKER_05]: What did you guys think of Uno?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I had a little bit to drink.
[SPEAKER_02]: A little.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I was sitting back going, Uno.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was Uno.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had four Astro Smashes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Black Wolf?
[SPEAKER_06]: The computer is a cheese monkey.
[SPEAKER_02]: The computer is a bitch.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: The computer is evil.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think he went for...
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: That makes me warm and fuzzy and kind of ill.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was my thought, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to have to get my own gamer tag now.
[SPEAKER_05]: You should.
[SPEAKER_05]: Silent Wind, any other thoughts for our listeners?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, just that if you ever get a chance to go down there, that's a great place to hang out.
[SPEAKER_09]: I appreciate your support.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're a true buddy.
[SPEAKER_09]: And what do you think of the set here?
[SPEAKER_09]: I love this set.
[SPEAKER_09]: Silent Wind, what did you think of the set?
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, I love the NES.
[SPEAKER_09]: The NES set was awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: I did take pictures with Sky's camera.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, good.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll get those up on the site.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, Silent Wind, we've got to let you go because you're going to get more calls.
[SPEAKER_05]: So thanks for calling in, all right?
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, you take care now.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, you too, buddy.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was good to meet you.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, that was Silent Wind, our random contest winner from last night who got to come down here and be on the E3 Outpost.
[SPEAKER_05]: Check it out here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bobby, remind the kids how to call in if they want.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll do a couple more.
[SPEAKER_06]: Toll free number in the United States, 1-866-880-0156.
[SPEAKER_07]: I wanted to mention another cool game I played was Hot Pixel.
[SPEAKER_07]: That game was awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just basically WarioWare on the PSP with old retro Atari games in there as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: Friggin' awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Lots of good WarioWare type games coming to the PSP.
[SPEAKER_06]: You mean Atari was showing more than one game?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: HotPixel is fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the guy, I guess, who made it or whatever is a crazy-ass French guy.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, he has this weird skateboard with carpet on it and a fucking PSP holder in there.
[SPEAKER_07]: What a nut.
[SPEAKER_07]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: It was cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was nice to meet him.
[SPEAKER_07]: He actually has a podcast, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't even remember the name of it, but...
[SPEAKER_07]: Just a weird guy.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's kind of like Mark Echoes on Crackin' French.
[SPEAKER_05]: Eccentric guy, but I was surprised with Hot Pixel.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought it would suck.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it was actually kind of... It was cute in a... I don't even know how to describe it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was...
[SPEAKER_05]: Such a weird, quirky, but in a different type of element.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, the game is totally just like WarioWare, but the minigames are so different.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what I like about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have another quickie for you guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: 99 Nights, I thought was great.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought, it's just mass murder the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I loved it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a little bit of button mashing, but I mean, there's a lot of stuff going on on the screen and people... GamerAndy's doing a dance.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is this the 99 Nights dance?
[SPEAKER_05]: GamerAndy, say hi on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do a plug for your spiel and tell us about 99 Nights.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, GamerAndy.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_00]: Hi, this is Adam from GamerAndy Live.
[SPEAKER_00]: How are you today?
[SPEAKER_05]: I am great!
[SPEAKER_00]: That's great!
[SPEAKER_05]: What do you think of 99 Nights?
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, I played it at the Spring Preview and I honestly thought it was more along the realms of the button-mashing, Dynasty Warriors-esque sort of thing.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_00]: Which personally isn't really for me.
[SPEAKER_00]: You didn't like it?
[SPEAKER_00]: No, no dude.
[SPEAKER_05]: Didn't like the cutscenes?
[SPEAKER_05]: Didn't like any of that stuff?
[SPEAKER_00]: Um, you know, the cutscenes were alright, but honestly, I really just didn't quite get into it.
[SPEAKER_00]: It wasn't my groove, dude.
[SPEAKER_00]: Sorry to hear it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, you know, I mean, I wanted to like it, though.
[SPEAKER_00]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Give a quick plug for your stuff.
[SPEAKER_00]: Gamer Andy Live, tonight, after these guys.
[SPEAKER_00]: After Orange Lines Radio, which rocks, by the way.
[SPEAKER_00]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's drunk.
[SPEAKER_05]: We gotta give the mic back to JBL.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, um...
[SPEAKER_05]: I had business.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like 99 Nights.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a little bit of button mashing.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like Golden Axe, but like, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was what I was thinking about when I'm playing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm like, this is like Golden Axe, but with more.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I see Sonic.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mortal Kombat Armageddon.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did anyone else play this besides me?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hell no.
[SPEAKER_05]: You were a green vampire chick with an axe.
[SPEAKER_05]: Created character is always awesome in my book.
[SPEAKER_05]: And even though I'm a little disappointed Armageddon is only for the current gen stuff, I think created character was great.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course the created character that was in there when I loaded it up was a naked woman.
[SPEAKER_05]: But how many of those have we seen?
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, when I say naked, I mean, you know, bikini.
[SPEAKER_05]: But how many of those have we seen in video games?
[SPEAKER_05]: So I was going to make a fun female character.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I made a green vampire bitch with a huge meat cleaver as her weapon, and it was awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you won.
[SPEAKER_05]: I did.
[SPEAKER_05]: I kicked the shit out of whoever.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't even remember what I was playing against, some Ermac or something, but it was cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: I liked it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's a little like if you have the other two Mortal Kombat games from this current generation I don't think there's a lot else here but I mean if you're a fan of Mortal Kombat I think you'll have a good time any other oh we got a call let's go to the phones and answer the phones hi you're on Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey guys, Jason.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey Jason, what's up?
[SPEAKER_05]: How are you guys enjoying it down there?
[SPEAKER_05]: Good, this is Jason, our webmaster, Jason.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi Jason.
[SPEAKER_05]: We miss having you here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why I wish you were here, Jason.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why aren't you here?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not here, I'm not there because my truck demands me being here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I'm sorry, Jason.
[SPEAKER_04]: And insurance and all those, you know, things that actually require money for no good reason.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I hate that stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: What did you want to call in and say to our listeners?
[SPEAKER_05]: Besides the fact that you rock because you do our website stuff for us, it's a thankless job and I love you for it, you know that.
[SPEAKER_04]: What did you want to say to our listeners?
[SPEAKER_04]: You're very efficient.
[SPEAKER_04]: I heard about the existence of Guitar Man Live and I'm wondering if they've actually had a booth up and if you guys have got any more information on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Guitaroman Live, we got into a little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Guitaroman Lives.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a port.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the same thing as the PS2.
[SPEAKER_05]: It has duet mode.
[SPEAKER_05]: It has some little things, but if you're looking for new songs... No, no.
[SPEAKER_06]: But if you accidentally pause it, you can continue.
[SPEAKER_06]: You don't have to restart from the beginning.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything else, Jason?
[SPEAKER_04]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was hoping that it was mostly a new game, especially with the duet mode.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was actually going to further the storyline or anything along those lines.
[SPEAKER_05]: We were a little disappointed it's not a new game either, but at least the franchise isn't dead.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess that's the silver lining.
[SPEAKER_05]: At least they're still interested.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we'll see how it does on the market.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jason, thanks so much for calling in.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have a good one, okay?
[SPEAKER_05]: DJ Food Eater
[SPEAKER_05]: DJ Poo Eater Oh, DJ Poo Eater!
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey!
[SPEAKER_05]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_05]: You're breaking up a little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Get your thought out there.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't get that out.
[SPEAKER_05]: DJ Poo Eater, we're gonna have to let you go, buddy.
[SPEAKER_05]: DJ Poo Eater, we're gonna have to let you go because you're breaking up too much, but thanks for trying.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe try again tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, have a good one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, let's go to another call.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's try a different call.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, they have no time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, here it is again.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, this is Jaded2006.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jaded2006, what's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, nothing much.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is mainly a question for Bobby.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bobby!
[SPEAKER_05]: A question for Bobby.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bobby, taking over our show.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks a lot.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, what's up?
[SPEAKER_05]: What's the question for Bobby?
[SPEAKER_08]: What is your honest opinion about Wii Music?
[SPEAKER_06]: But all it was was playing the Zelda theme.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, you can cue other places.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can cue the back of the orchestra and they'll play louder.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can slow them down and start them up, but it takes a little while to get used to it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I only played through it twice.
[SPEAKER_06]: When you play that game, do you look as fruity as Miyamoto did at the conference?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I actually look, I look like a real, most people do, because they're like, you know, just waving their arms and like dancing around like he did.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, when I say Miyamoto's being fruity, I tease with love, because that's why we love him, is because he's just a crazy little man.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just to point out, though, you were mentioning about having a hard time actually conducting for real with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I did also, when I went through there, Koji Kondo was playing, and he actually, I could tell, wasn't doing true conducting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, you have to do it like, you know, it's really rigid, and it looks like it's actually, if you know anything about conducting, it's actually the up motion is what triggers it, not the down motion.
[SPEAKER_06]: I learned that right at the very end of my second thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm like, oh, it's going on the up.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jaded2006, any other thoughts for us?
[SPEAKER_06]: Is it as easy as Miyamoto made it look?
[SPEAKER_06]: How about that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, you're not going to be good at it, but yeah, I mean, it's, you know, waving your arms like people who've never done music stuff were able to get through it.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it does score you at the end.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jaded2006, we've got to let you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to start wrapping it up, all right?
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, thanks so much for the call.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_06]: You have a good one, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_06]: Poor Spirit Snare has been trying to call in for like the past 30 minutes, and somebody else always gets in.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, we've got the wrap-up sign, so we've got to start wrapping it up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Spirit Snare, tomorrow, buddy, call in.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll get you.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm so sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, of course, there's always the forums.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's LiveJournal.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is for anybody that wants to talk to us, but maybe is too shy to call in.
[SPEAKER_05]: Our Stuff blog, stuff.orangeballonsradio.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: even Myspace if you really want to.
[SPEAKER_05]: We've got all that stuff going on, so check it out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, really quickly though, real quick, I had to do this before the show's over tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: The FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bobby, give us a little bit of the... Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, do you have any FUs so far at E3?
[SPEAKER_05]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: Not really, actually.
[SPEAKER_02]: Really?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I've actually been pretty much okay with it, except I still think, and this actually really surprised me, my husband's actually pretty happy about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to say F you to Capcom, because why the hell are you going to put NES Strider on the PSP?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, they put NES Strider on the game?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that Capcom Classics Collection is the NES versions of Mighty Final Fight, Bionic Commando, which Dan was like, Bionic Commando!
[SPEAKER_02]: And the NES version of Strider, which actually isn't a bad game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's all based off of the Strider comics.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I was like, I have these at home, I can just play them at home.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why?
[SPEAKER_02]: Why do I want these on my PSP?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, so...
[SPEAKER_06]: But what about those of us who don't have those at home?
[SPEAKER_06]: Is it a bad thing to have?
[SPEAKER_02]: You can download it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it is a bad thing to have if we don't have those games at home?
[SPEAKER_02]: There's other ways to get it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just don't see any reason of, you know, they should have touched it up or, you know, made it a little bit cleaner.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it is the exact port of the NES ones.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some people like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: We gotta keep the angst flowing because we gotta wrap it up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, your FU.
[SPEAKER_07]: My FU goes to Nintendo for a couple reasons.
[SPEAKER_07]: The first, because their party wasn't exactly great, even if the Black IPs were there.
[SPEAKER_07]: And also because their booth sucks ass as far as the design goes.
[SPEAKER_07]: and it makes it nearly impossible to play anything new that they have.
[SPEAKER_05]: Notice I didn't talk about the Wii today.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's because I didn't play it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I tried to go to the line at 12.30 and they told me tough titty because they were doing a private party which was more important.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do your private party after hours, dummies.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bobby, your FU.
[SPEAKER_06]: My FU goes to three people, and one of them, his name is Scott Rubin, who was supposed to be the one that was picking me up at 8.15 in the morning at my hotel so I could get there by 9 o'clock.
[SPEAKER_06]: My second, but unfortunately he...
[SPEAKER_06]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_06]: who pulled some strings.
[SPEAKER_06]: He was standing in the Nintendo line.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was going to join him in the line and he pulled some strings and they went into the Nintendo booth.
[SPEAKER_06]: And my third FU goes to Lawrence Young for going with him and not waiting for me because they did the Jack Bauer time going, There's no time!
[SPEAKER_06]: And then for Lawrence Young, the last FU is for calling me and saying, Bobby B, I'm one foot away from Madden 07.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ha ha ha!
[SPEAKER_05]: And I was like an hour and a half away from getting in, so... I still love you, Lawrence, for whatever it's worth.
[SPEAKER_05]: You edit the show so I don't have to.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love you for that.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: My FU goes to the people that were waiting in line to see Paris Hilton.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah!
[SPEAKER_05]: Get out of my E3!
[SPEAKER_05]: Get out!
[SPEAKER_05]: Those are the people that need to be sterilized.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hope you all go sterile.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, may they never breed Alright, we gotta wrap it up Final thoughts, DarkSakura, your final thought Uh Nap Loki, your final thought My final thought is I'm gonna play Crackdown tomorrow because I forgot it was there Alright Bobby, thanks for being here again Your final thought, reject false icons Thank you I also forgot to mention, two nights in a row Superman Returns is fucking awesome and it would be a better Grand Theft Auto game
[SPEAKER_05]: My final thought is Enchanted Arms looked really pretty.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wish they'd let me play it.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_05]: We got to go, guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll be back here Friday night live at the E3 Outpost.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks to the E3 Outpost staff for having us.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you're listening live, Gamer Andy's up next.
[SPEAKER_05]: So don't go anywhere or he will come find you and disco dance in your living room.
[SPEAKER_02]: They can take a quick pee break if they need to.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, you can do a quick pee break, but be back here by 9.
[SPEAKER_05]: Be back by 9 Pacific.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Roll the credits.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're done.
[SPEAKER_01]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_01]: For more information on our live and podcast programs, visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com See you next week!
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!