This week statistics show that the PlayStation 4 is for porn.
No word on what genres are the favorite per platform, but some things may be better left
unknown.
This is just one of many headlines, stay tuned for so much more starting right now on the
show where every gamer has a voice.
Hello my friends out there on the internet, welcome back to another week of the show where
every gamer has a voice.
It is Orange Lounge Radio, live tonight January the 14th of 2018, episode number 714 of our
show.
My name is Rob Roberts, you might know me on Twitter at Skie, S-K-I-E, and joining me
as always by my side to talk about video games, gaming culture, the gamer lifestyle is Dark
Sakura or Jamie Summers.
Sup.
Hey how you doing?
I'm alive.
I'm here.
You're kicking, you're good.
I drove myself.
Yeah, good.
I can drive.
Yay.
I grown up.
Awesome.
Also say hello to Tech Master Loki.
Hello.
And how are you doing?
Good, I just want to make sure I didn't, oh that's empty anyways.
What, your In-N-Out cup is where you go tonight?
So you're one of those Californians who likes In-N-Out because some people-
I wouldn't say I like In-N-Out, I was driving here, I was like I don't know what I want
to eat and it was between In-N-Out or El Pollo Loco and I was like I had El Pollo Loco the
other day so.
My sister was visiting last night and she's from L.A. and we were kind of talking about
like In-N-Out and she kind of thinks it's like super overrated and I don't think it's
like overrated but I do find that like when people from the East Coast come out here it's
always like okay and one of the things we have to do on the trip, we have to go one
night to In-N-Out and I'm just like okay it's not that great but I mean it's good, it's
cool.
It's alright.
Yeah.
I'm not from In-N-Out but I'm not from your country.
I mean from your state.
There's nice fine dining options down, so we go to an independently owned place.
I mean yeah, you could go to In-N-Out but you could also go to the Sizzler.
Oh that's fine dining.
Alright anyway I could talk with Jamie and Matt and I will plenty throughout tonight's
show but we talk to them a lot throughout the other weeks of the show.
We have a lot of guests here in studio tonight and I want to get to them because I've been
promoting this for a few weeks now that we were going to be joined by some folks here
locally and we've talked about this on and off on the show a little bit about how a few
years ago I was reading Joystiq's blog and they're no longer around so I'll tell you
how long ago this was but they were talking about, they ran an article on this brand new
game that had just come out for iPhone that was on Android for a year or two prior and
it was a location based game where you actually played out in the real world with real places
that were near you and this game was called Ingress and so I downloaded it to my phone
and I've regretted that decision for the past four years but I've met some amazing people
thanks to the game and some of them are here in studio tonight so I want to introduce you
guys to starting us off tonight Jen how are you doing Jen?
I'm great how are you?
Good it's great to have you here.
It's great to be here.
Awesome so I'll introduce everybody real quick and then I'm gonna ask you guys some questions.
So also joining us tonight is Tori.
Hey how you doing?
Good Tori how you doing?
Good.
Good and then last but not least Snow is joining us tonight.
Hello audience.
Hi you don't normally sound like that.
No I don't sound like that.
No I wish when you played the game and were talking to us over we'll talk about how some
of this works later I wish you would use that voice.
Everybody start your clears.
Everybody get ready to drop those blockers in three two all right.
Pick up the phone.
All right so I did want to make tonight's show you know I know not everybody out there who
listens to the show plays Ingress.
I know this will be met with some mixed reaction to our crowd here but I know most of our audience
is super familiar as a lot of gamers are with Pokemon Go which released about a year and
a half ago and Pokemon Go Pokemon goes from the same company that did Ingress and you
may wonder like why are these random parks or why are these things that don't even exist
anymore in my town Pokestops like where did that come from and that was populated from
Ingress which was Niantic's prior game.
Yeah you're welcome Pokemon players.
That's right you're welcome and also sorry.
Anyway so let's talk about what is Ingress.
So if you guys were to describe Ingress to a new person like you're trying to do like
the sales pitch to try to get somebody to play the game how would you do this?
Jen what what is Ingress?
Well way back when when we all were Pokemon wasn't a thing yet we would call it capture
the flag sort of meets like I don't even know it I forget what we called it geocaching
and so really it's the kind of game that gets you going places seeing things that you didn't
know existed previously and that's kind of the draw for a lot of people is being able
to get out and learn more about their location.
Yeah I have to admit I had a lot of that playing the game you know even in my own neighborhood
I was always taken aback with there's like a ton of churches on this street I never realized
like just how many of them are like hidden.
So so many churches everywhere.
So many churches churches everywhere for sure.
But also lots of statues and parks parks that I like never even knew were around like oh
there's there's a park over here because there's a portal here now now I think oh I'll go back
there someday I never do.
So so so besides the exploration part of the game Tori let me let me call on you for a
little bit what what is the game element of Ingress?
What is the game part besides just the exploration?
Well the game it's basically two factions so two teams opposing each other and the
overarching goal is to try to cover as much territory as you can and the way you do that
is to create triangles by linking these portals or pokestops together and forming triangles.
Actually I can see the pain in your face when you say the pokey stops.
Yes but your your listeners can't so that's sorry sorry.
Now they can.
So the idea is basically to link those those together and make triangles and cover as much
area as possible and it's sounds pretty easy but it can be quite complex because you can
block said triangles by linking other portals together we try to link them together we try
to layer and try to not only cover a particular populated area but cover it with as many layers
as possible so you're playing in a in densely populated areas a lot that being said sometimes
you might play in very remote areas and I think that's one of the positives of the game it
literally can be played anywhere.
Yeah that's that's very true you know even though the triangles in a very rural part
of area like for example we're in Northern California so we'll say like I own okay is
a very remote type of city right.
Or Nevada city.
Or okay oh yeah Nevada city perfect for example is more remote and so when you do a triangle
in Nevada city it's not going to be worth as much as a triangle in downtown San Francisco
which can be worth a lot more because San Francisco is very populated.
Yeah their cemeteries have more MU than downtown.
Exactly exactly crazy right.
And they're all dead it doesn't seem.
Zombie units ZU I guess is how it works so so sometimes these triangles are very small
but sometimes we work together to make very big ones right yeah.
So Snow and I recently did a very large field over I don't know how many layers we had over
was it like 50 layers over it was it was in the LA area and that required I mean we we
had hundreds of agents and it was really fun.
And just quickly when you say layers that means like you take one triangle and then
you're putting basically more triangles on top of it by moving one of the ends of the
triangle out slowly.
Yeah exactly.
Across more pokey stops or portals.
Yeah those yeah those yeah yeah.
Stop calling them pokey stops.
Hopefully the listeners understand at this point.
We're going to burn this house to the ground.
But you guys so I actually let me let me ask about some of these like big like operations
just to give these guys some perspective the listeners about like well let me actually
let me backtrack let me back to this question for everybody.
How long have you been playing this game?
And I'll start with you Snow how long have you been playing in yours?
Jesus 1042 days my sojourner said so I've hacked the portal every day since I started.
Wow.
Wait was that badge even out when you started though?
Yeah it came out like two weeks before I started.
Okay so you've been playing for 1042 days.
I actually would have thought it was longer.
Tori what about you?
How long have you been playing?
I started playing the day that Robin Williams died which is why my name is Mork from Ork
because he's one of my favorites.
So that would have been I'm looking three and a half years ago.
That's a lovely tribute though.
Yeah I think so too.
What about you Jen?
I started shortly after the game came out so I'm coming up on five years.
How did you find out about it?
Well I actually was dating somebody on the other side who played it to start with and
I didn't play in part because I had an iPhone and they did not have the app for the iPhone
yet.
The only way to play it at that time would have been the illegal you know against TOS
app that people had made but that got you banned pretty quick.
Or you could tether your iPhone to an Android tablet which is what I ended up doing.
And I actually didn't start until after the person I was dating and I had split but a
friend that I had met through him really encouraged me to play and that's how I ended up playing.
And here you are.
And here I am.
All right.
Now to give our listeners an idea about like how you know because this is a lot of people
especially like gamers like most of our audience.
I'm gonna say all but most of our audience is very console based very PC based you know
playing things like you know I don't know Super Mario Odyssey on a console or maybe
something like World of Warcraft or Overwatch on a PC.
So I mean a lot of times people think of mobile games they think about oh Candy Crush or they
think about Pokemon Go or they think about Words with Friends you know these or HQ I
guess is the big new one right the trivia game show.
Two dots.
So I mean Ingress the scale of what is done in this game can really like surprise some
people sometimes right.
So give our listeners an idea.
What's like the biggest like accomplishment you've done in Ingress if you can think of
what that is.
What's like the biggest accomplishment you've done in the game.
I definitely have one and then I'll pass it to you Snow.
Okay Jen go ahead.
We there the Ingress or the Niantic will actually create sort of challenges.
And there was a challenge to put up a certain amount of MU the thing the amount of people
underneath the triangle large triangle.
And we had a challenge to cover three different places.
And it was just over a couple of days and we ended up being able to field in about 48
hours from Big Bend in Texas to Dunsmuir in the top of California up kind of near Weed
and all the way down to I believe it was Baja.
And we pulled that field together in just a few days.
It was like hundreds of agents that we were able to coordinate over four different states
I believe.
So to put this in perspective for our listeners who've never touched Ingress before again
Ingress is a location based game and to do these links and make these triangles you have
to hack these portals.
And so when you hack these portals you might get a key and a key is how you link two portals
together and then if you do a triangle out of your link.
So you helped with this or did you run it?
I did.
Okay I designed and ran it.
You led an organization to put a triangle with keys from Weed California it's like Mount
Shasta right to Texas to Baja California.
Yes.
And you pulled that together in 48 hours.
Yes it was just maybe a little bit over 48 but yeah.
Well we had some luck things happen.
The big thing is a lot of times you have you send out people too when you know they're
going to go to a certain place and say bring back keys for you know however many you can
get.
And so then the person will sit there and they will hack the portal or they'll you know
spin the pokey spot stop for Pokemon reference.
I don't play Pokemon so that's you know.
And you'll so those people will bring back those keys.
So for Baja you know that's one of those places that we would send somebody kind of regularly.
So we had keys there and Dunsmuir we actually didn't have keys for because we had not really
been there previously for fielding purposes.
But Texas.
Because nobody goes to Dunsmuir.
That's right nobody goes to Dunsmuir.
My dad my dad worked for the railroad he went to Dunsmuir all the time like can you imagine
if I played this I would have made my dad play this game.
You would have had it yeah.
I would have made my dad play this game.
That would have been great.
So but we had the luck of the draw of an agent named Mr. Kent flying into San Francisco from
Texas the day that the day before we needed to do the field and he had the Big Ben keys.
So we were able to coordinate people going to Big Bend who actually had Baja keys that
we had previously coordinated sending from with somebody traveling.
So and then Mr. Kent went up to Dunsmuir with us.
And that's how we did it.
That's how we coordinated that quickly.
So and I have to admit like when I first started playing Ingress you know for the first little
while I was a little bit of a loner and I was like okay whatever this is cool.
But then when I started getting exposed to this James Bond shit I was like wow this is
really impressive that it in some ways I almost feel like there's like because I played a
lot of MMOs in the past and I still do.
I play things on Final Fantasy XI, XIV, World of Warcraft and I actually do see some similarities
between World of Warcraft and Ingress right.
You have Horde versus Alliance.
It's a huge fetch quest.
In some ways yeah it's a big fetch quest.
You have Horde there's just no poop quest in Ingress yet.
But you have Horde versus Alliance and especially back in the early days of wow there's a lot
of passion behind that right like you kind of have an Ingress there's a lot of passion
behind the teams in Ingress.
And then you know you might get together and you might go PvP Ingress is a very player
versus player heavy game.
Or you might do this like raid and either you're raiding you know maybe a very for us
because we all play the green team.
We're being fair and balanced tonight by the way this is a fair and balanced presentation.
We're all rez players here playing on the green team they're all green.
But well that's you know that's also why we're talking a lot about like very I think everything
we're saying or things that you know rez I think would agree these are the parts of the
game that make it great and so forth.
So but anyway what was I gonna say with that oh and then raids might sometimes be we're
getting a big group of people together between Texas and you know every state in between
California to throw a gigantic effing triangle and that's that's just crazy like the lengths
people go to.
What about you Snow I'll check in with you what's your best accomplishment in Ingress
the time you've played?
I haven't murdered anyone.
Have you wanted to?
Yeah.
But I haven't like I won I beat I beat Ingress every day so you know.
How do you I didn't think you could beat Ingress I thought it was.
I win every day.
It was the song that never ends.
I managed to hack a portal.
I am proof you can rage quit Ingress.
It's it's like uh.
I haven't rage quit.
You've won by not rage quitting and I've gotten right to that brink where it's like I'm gonna
fucking quit I'm gonna fucking quit this bullshit but then I don't.
I have never wanted to quit.
Then Snow will show up at my house and she slaps me and she says you can't fucking quit.
I say you can quit.
Why would you want to quit?
Snow's not in jail either just throwing that out there.
I'm not in jail I have been super good the mountains have a lot of places to hide bodies
but I haven't murdered anyone in Ingress.
Okay just saying yeah that's just an Ingress just that's the qualifier.
All right so we have giant triangle and haven't murdered anybody.
Tori what about you what's your best accomplishment in Ingress?
I was gonna say giant triangle but I'm sorry.
Well I did my sack filled largely by myself my very first one which was pretty cool.
However one of my favorite moments I think was actually when there was a very large
resistance field the other team and I kind of quickly figured out what was up and was able to
go to a remote location basically block that field and for me that was kind of cool so it's
kind of the other side of the field I mean the other side of the fence is that you know on the
one hand we're making these triangles but on the other hand part of it is being able to block the
other team from from doing the same so that's part of the game and that is really a lot of what I do
and I love it. That's the cloak and dagger shit when you have to be predictive and I'm always
impressed you know having played with you for a while I've been very impressed at your ability to
not just call that a field is coming but you could generally you will get like at least two
of the three points that they're using. I love you for noticing that but it's true definitely
very good like when Tori says a field's coming like I believe it I do I'm in the car driving
a sluice house I am. All right so anyway I do want to introduce our chat room of course over
at live.vognetwork.com where we do tape every Sunday night at the voice geeks network vognetwork.com
six o'clock pacific nine o'clock eastern right after the bobby black wolf show and this might
be a familiar name to some of you here in chat we have a set is in chat tonight who's reminding
us that links can't cross each other and that's something we we kind of didn't I don't know if we
said that very clearly but wow is that way to go basic ingress well but it's like it's like
Ghostbusters the streams can't cross but that's important so if you're drawing what happens if
we cross the stream not very bad crazy cat lady has crossed the streams before shout out to Donna
well actually it you you could cross the streams if you throw the links at like the exact same
moment and the servers have problems yeah yeah ingress servers have and then there's no never
never and then there always works we do cry actually there's been yeah there's there's
been some crying over fields I'm not gonna lie that fucking blocker in time yeah exactly
uh let's see also in chat at live.vognetwork.com kaijuto in chat says this game sounds cool
I like the espionage aspect oh there is so much espionage speaking from a personal standpoint
that could be the best thing and that could be the worst thing because the worst thing is that
now like when I go into these completely public places and I steep see people staring at their
phones I'm like are they taking the portal are they and that was especially bad a couple years
ago but now it's like even worse because it's like no it's a five-year-old trying to catch a pikachu
that was me that was me at Disneyland though okay there is no paranoia like ingress paranoia like
right I don't care how high you are or what drug you're on there is no paranoia that was actually
what led up to my rage quit was at Disneyland and even after you leave the game you still get it
like I saw someone parked next to the church today looking at the hallway I suspect everyone they
can't see your face the park near my house what so tell me more about the rage quit I just got
really sick of losing like and it actually stemmed from losing my my home portal the the one that was
in my neighborhood that I would always walk to and go do and go back home and I was like one day
before whatever badge I was getting and someone took it and then I went to Disneyland angry
and I would see like other people on resistance playing you know at Disneyland and I'm like
fuck all of you I'm gonna steal them all they're my team that and then goddamn over and says you're
here for your birthday chill let's go watch world of color and I didn't pick it up until like what
about two months ago but that is that is one of the hard lessons I think a new player has
to learn about Ingress is that nobody owns a portal and I never the same way ever get
emotionally yeah don't ever get emotionally I don't give a shit be it just don't because
you know some people will use that against you well no just depending on who it is I was mad
this I was a day away from getting my badge uh oh well that's especially why you didn't you know
the only reason I call it mine is because it's in my neighborhood and I'm the only person in
that part of my neighborhood that plays sure but it's not you until you're not anymore because for
the first year and a half it belongs to the I was on a post in this neighborhood and then somebody
hardcore showed up and it's like okay this is just although I am gonna reclaim the one in my
work lobby although I do where I work I do like that one that's near my house just happens to be
just about uh level five x and p away so they take it all the time and I just ping it every
now then just to wake them up and I know that they have their notifications on because they
recharge on portals and I do that in the morning all the time they'll take they'll take a portal
that I can like fire it from my house and then I'll just fire at it all night with the lowest
level one I can reach it with and then like every hour I'll get up and go to the bathroom at two in
the morning I'll open Ingress and I'll fire a burster just see what happens and then I convince
hey sorry rez I convinced a rez player to recharge it when it started getting low and bump it and put
an axel on it so it wouldn't go down I just pinged them all the time so let's talk a little
bit about the badge denial thing actually for a minute because this is kind of part of what landed
ingress in the news in the gaming community in a wider sense a few weeks ago is that for those that
are unaware I guess you could say like achievements like xbox 360 achievements or trophies the ingress
game has badges built into it and the badges might be oh you linked x many links or you fielded this
many fields or you covered this many moo or you know or one of them is you held a portal for this
many days and the interesting thing about ingress is that in order to level there's 16 levels in
ingress right so to get from eight to 16 you actually need some of these achievements to level
now tell me about it now are you are you locked behind achievements right now that's where alan's
at but in the old school days of ingress like one of the easy achievements that you really needed to
get to level 16 was being able to hold a portal for 150 days um i don't think that's not really
the case anymore like especially if you can glyph especially if you play with your team and and work
recharge well or sojourner you know uh hacking so many days anyway there's lots of alternatives now
so it's not really the case but yet we still have this issue and where this led into was
uh where you probably saw this amongst different blogs out there is there was um our our opposition
had a a network called the brokers guild is what it was called it was basically a database that
was um scraping what's called the intel i don't even know how you can explain this right scraping
the intel and was showing that let's say it would show uh snow captured x portal on x day and so
they could say you know i am mad at snow i want to go figure out what portal she has them i would
take them all out at day 149 so she can't get her on 148 actually day 148 tell tell this story real
quick they all they all went out in the snow one day to do it snow to get snow right no they went
out to a low signal portal there's three of them because i killed their farm and they drove all
the way up which transparency may or may not have been related to brokers guild we don't know i
have to be transparent yeah no i'm well that's how they found it well but allegedly allegedly
yeah allegedly you know who you are i know you three you three know who you are and they went
up there and legit told me that we had a circle jerk near the portal which i thought was a little
weird um and tori was with me and we killed the farm and we showed up and i was like oh my god
someone killed my guardian and i did a little dance and i was super excited and tori and her
friend were like i am so sorry i was like why are you sorry i made three people drive into the middle
of nowhere in low signal to kill a portal they drove 45 50 minutes out of their way while i
killed their farm just to take this portal out and then they started laughing i don't i i don't
like the guardian badge i think it's dumb i think that guardian hunting is a dick move but at the
same time i use it to my advantage i'll make these i live really far from people so i put these
portals out there and i know they have to go kill them and i know they're in shitty signal and i
know these people have never been there so it's really fun when they pop up to the north of me
and someone goes oh so and so is north what are they doing i go oh they're probably trying to kill
my portal and then i'll just poke at them on com like that took you forever it took me five
minutes to deploy that what took you 20 minutes to kill it like all you had to do is fire bursters
tori you want to piggyback on this i just want to throw in that having been there that night
probably gave me such a different perspective that she has the most amazing healthiest perspective and
um on this whole guardian killing kind of thing and we've actually been now as a community we've
kind of adopted it um rather than using it as oh my god i've been denied a badge we look at it as
a way to control the opposition but it gets better than that one of the things we created was a
shared spreadsheet and uh we tell our stories you know such and such a person like my husband they
love to hunt my husband um my you know such and such a person went and hunted this person and
they spent this much to go there they drove 150 miles in the rain or whatever and then they said
these things and we kind of it's a shared sort of um uh collection if you will of of different
things and screenshots and things and in a lot of these people actually it's really not so much
about getting their guardian but just how much fun we're having about with with this i mean that
being said i do wish the the badge itself would go away but i think um there's different ways of
looking at it and i'd say snow's probably got the healthiest way i've ever heard and it's been a lot
of fun ever since then yeah ever since kind of i i kind of looked at it the same way and i i get a
kick out of the fact like oh who's gonna go drive to take it out and i i kind of get a kick out of
it you know and i've accepted i'm not gonna get the i was i was actually kind of mad when i got
platinum now granted i had to go get a portal i was actually i can say this now because the
portal's long gone i was at magfest in dc i will cry if i ever get onyx i will be in tears i was
at magfest in dc and one of my friends one morning was like i want to walk to mcdonald's in the 15
degree weather and we were like for some stupid reason i don't know if we were drunk we were like
okay and as we're walking i'm hitting portals like along and then i'm like wow nobody else is
playing out here and so i had a friend who's level 16 keeper charging this portal and they let me get
platinum and i was like oh well shoot but then then one day mysteriously i killed a farm and then
poof my my guardian disappeared just like it was the funniest coincidence how about that but i
laughed yeah they didn't even have anyone go out to my portal because my portal was at a farm that's
only open for like a month during the year because i went on a field trip one it wasn't open to the
public and they spoofed it to get it well let's let's talk about this movie thing for a minute
but first i do want to make sure you know in the interest of you know disclosing all sides there
was a similar database uh for green players that was called drunken frogs is that what we had
drunken frog now nobody in our team was involved with no nobody i believe most of it was europe
based although there was some people in the states right but to be fair cheaters have no
faction can we all agree with that absolutely absolutely can i just before we go too far
spoofing can i just ask am i the only one here with the black
badge i have a guardian no she definitely has a black you do have one okay she tried to throw
a field off of her oh that's right i forgot about this yeah and it would be you tried to get them
to kill it and they still didn't that's right i forgot about this it was my profile it is my
profile picture on g plus oh that's right when the entire time it was clicking as a guardian so
whatever it's gone now it's good i know when i um got mine i thought well what have i done
wrong here to not have them come after my portal i don't matter i want to mention
i don't matter over at live.vog network.com kaishido and chat says this sounds like a game
me and my friends played back in the 90s it was called tagging you pretty much wrote your name
all over the city and sometimes other taggers would come and write over your name fun times lol
isn't that illegal i think it is illegal um because i'm gonna play this game now it's basically
yeah it is pissing and marking your territory it's basically what this whole game is yeah
except virtually i know roseville player that pretends to piss on portals stop all right yeah
let's talk about spoofing so some people feel the need to cheat uh by and when we say spoofing we
mean that you're faking your location and yeah it's happened on all sides all teams unfortunately
yeah everybody does both sides unfortunately spoofers fuck it up for everybody um i don't i
don't know where we can really go with this topic but what do you think niantic can do about
spoofers if anything like what do you think they can do about it anybody well they're gonna have
to sort of ramp up their um their algorithms that spot spoofers um but the problem with doing that
is it ends up spotting legitimate players too when something wacky has happened like you have
a gps problem and it jumps you or something like that so they're in a really tough spot it's very
difficult for niantic to to be able to just catch to catch them in the act yeah if you have cricket
mobile you might look like a spoofer just because or maybe even sometimes t-mobile yeah sometimes
t maybe tijuana mobile yeah all right so anyway uh all right so spoofers you know don't don't
play this game you just you ruin it for everybody and it's like the point of playing a location
based game if you're gonna sit in your house like the whole point is to go out like that's what got
me into the game is i had to leave the house with my little tiny kids in my van and drive them to
parks and go to cemeteries and explore why would you want to do that from home i think some people
get their jollies off of hurting other people's accomplishments knowing that fucking people hike
in the mountains and people like take zero signal booster things i don't know what the troll game is
hardcore right zero i don't know what the hell i called it zero zero no cell no cell signal yeah
zc that's it zero zero cell yeah so they have their own name well whatever anyway but but loki
i mean they took so somebody spoofed your portal because this place was closed it closes in the
middle it was like in the middle of the night where was it did you uh it was fog willow farms
so we had a field trip they're only open in october for pumpkins and so we had a field trip
because they do science stuff for schools in april so i had put it down in april when i was there
with the class and it is untouchable because you can't hit it from the street there's no way to get
to it unless you trespass on their property and hike all the way across the farm to get it so it
could have been a legitimate kill but somebody actually trespassed it was two level sevens that
i'd never seen before that yeah it's kind of those telltale people people scream spoofer though a lot
when it's not a spoofer and people are just trespassing and they might not know that they're
not allowed to go or sometimes businesses have special openings for stuff or like we had a guy
who used to do um work like he didn't machine work on stuff and so he would go into closed wineries
and stuff but he wasn't he was there to fix things so i don't know it's it's you shouldn't
just scream spoofer unless you know for sure like it's it's hard to tell we can usually tell now
because we've been playing it was also it wasn't just that because i looked at their profile i'm
not saying that you're like i'm sure that there's a profile and just based off of their activity
right yeah it was like very very usually you can tell this it's very few portals hacked or visited
but a lot of glyph hacking or recharging lots of recharging you yeah you can usually tell a
spoofer by their um behavior on just in their own stats because no most people if you're intelligent
as a player are not going to use their real account so you wouldn't see one of our regular
res players who's level 16 spoofing for the most part you will see well some of them have but those
sure for the most part i said um you might you would usually see uh a player who's got a high
level account has created another account maybe or has hired somebody who's created another account
because that is also possible sell these services on ebay right yeah but i mean my point i was gonna
be with that whole story is okay so somebody spooked down loki's guardian but did you cry
yourself to sleep about it i bet you did no i was like oh man that's so close i know you just went
you probably just went what a fucking asshole and went to bed right that's that's it it's like you
know yeah it was i think i was doing something else so like i normally keep my ringer off so
you went to therapy for it didn't you oh yeah totally that's why i quit right there you rage
quit uh going to chat over at live.vog network.com um as that said paid spoof takedowns exist you can
buy a guardian portal kill that is very true uh some folks in chat talking about that the same
thing is going on in pokemon go uh sha100 matt saying it's not that beneficial to spoof gyms
and pokemon go anymore because you can only get 50 coins a day max um let's see uh i don't see the
value and spoof there's no game yet to pokemon go so i mean i don't either there's no score there's
no point in trying to i can't wait till we get pvp you can't even troll a five-year-old like when
i control five-year-olds i'll totally play more tiger claw and chat says i think the reason why
some people do this is because the world can be a scary place well yeah some people are assholes
that's just what it is let me let me actually transition to another ingress topic so fuck
spoofers yeah that's the game go play xbox tiny url dot fuck spoofers.com to report them yes
um let's talk about scary what's the scariest thing that's ever happened to you playing ingress
that's appropriate that's appropriate to talk about on the radio um i can talk about a time i was um
gps uh maps was kind of screwed me over we were trying to bring in a shard which is a whole
other fun topic of uh ingress it's one of the is sort of well i like that though that
niantic and quickly the niantic like yes you could say oh the way to play the game is to
make the most mu but for some people it might be about making the biggest field for some people
it's about the weekly cycles and you know winning those for some people it's about the niantic live
events like the shards and the anomalies we're doing missions to get the banners especially i
know some people on our team that like love missions i hate missions but other people love
they love the banners they love to do that stuff i love them but we don't have them where i live so
you know you can make them oh i'm really trying to find a picture i'm a really popular banner
creator would you like me to say i think we have some banner creators i took a picture of a floral
couch i brought it for you anyway uh my grandma passed away in the past year i thought it was a
lovely tribute thank you very much uh anyway uh what else was i gonna say with that uh
damn it oh so people have different ways to play the game oh i have a friend that um she listens
to this program and she started playing ingress because she heard me talk about on the show
and she's a big train rider and goes across the country she collects the keys oh that's all she
does is she just kind of like collects the keys and i'm like that's i love her yeah like well
right she's in the raider collection and throw fields can you please get me in touch with her
yes here's again but but um i kind of do the same thing one of my key lockers my my yellow one where
you hit and key locker is like where you can just like store keys i have keys for when i went to
pax west pax east i have keys from disneyland tori's saying why don't you just take a screenshot
do you feel like that's a waste of space rob i feel like that's a waste you know it's a waste
of space is the keys i've had from you to do a field can we layer through disneyland for like
a year and a half okay when you layer through disneyland you let me know this one is feasible
like the keys you're holding are feasible i've had them for like two goddamn years well then then
maybe push a little harder i will definitely fall on the sword and go to disneyland to support your
plan all right cool cool we're gonna do this disney layer so shards anyway yes shards scary
the moment when you said why am i playing this why am i playing this fucking game so uh shards
just as a quick background is this like side game and niantic puts on that we have to move
some item that sits on one portal through a link to another portal so in this case you don't need
the triangle you just need the one link um so we were trying to bring in a shard to the nevada area
up near reno um from utah and that was the most fucked up shard situation it was bouncing around
utah and airport for like i think two weeks or something stupid well our opposition has a strong
presence in utah utah yeah very strong yeah um and i mean it's slightly like less than it was
at that time but it definitely was just a shit show for our side and so i was directed to go to
this portal i'd never been to it was the middle of the night it was probably like midnight maybe 1
a.m and i had to work the next day by the way um and i i don't know what the hell happened with
my gps but it decided to take me up this like unlit mountainy kind of road thing and i was in
my shitty little subaru that didn't want to take these these like couldn't go over these boulders
and i just kind of got stuck in my car in the middle of nowhere in nevada at 1 a.m like and
it was terrible and i don't remember exactly how i mean sheridan for a field next to a meth lab so
i don't hear it hey listen i've been next to my share of meth labs for ingress too
i'm surprised we don't all do drugs that's that's ingress explore the meth labs around the world
they're all in sheridan uh tori i don't know if you wanted to share your story the xm comes from
you had a reaction when i said uh the time you were like why am i playing this shit is there
a story here there are a lot of stories um but i would say overall probably the the creepiest one
was has happened more than once and um i haven't shared this with a lot of people so now i'm
showing it with a whole lot of people um well to be fair it's a it's not that many here at orange
on radio all five people we're not game spot all five people so um it's happened it's happened with
my husband in town but it the most of the time it's happened has been when my husband was out
of town and now we're even when he wasn't playing ingress or too much uh we kind of understanding
how that happened now but um they would basically leave keys in my house um keys that were two
strategic portals that made it really obvious who they were and they would leave keys leaving
leading up to my house um and that's if i was to say the creepiest thing that's probably it
because her house is not somewhere you would go it's not a poor house no it's not a place you
would go ever it's on a remote area i get lost every time i go there remote but it's not it's
not on the way nowhere near a portal it's near portals but it's not super we would never go to
my house exactly to go from one portal to another no that would not happen um since then i've gotten
extensive security um extensive security we call it smurf cam but um but um hey rez rez if you're
listening don't go near her house seriously it'll be like that i won't even go near her house no
it's sad that it got that way and i'm sure there are a lot of resistance players that have
had that kind of thing happen it's one of the dangers and this important this is our perspective
what's happening here around the world we can't speak for our team members around the world
exactly so this is her experience anyway but what the thing with with alternative reality
types of gaming is that you have that's one of the dangers of it you basically have this idea that
you are you know you've got your home or your workplace and things like that and you're
you're playing in those places or you're you're living in those places and it's kind of where
basically the game is is sort of overlaid onto your real life and so those kinds of things can
happen um when people use tools and things to find out more information than they're entitled
to in the game that makes it more difficult but again that happens on both sides and it's
that's probably the creepiest thing there have been a number of real interesting things though
i don't understand that i don't understand why people would do that you know though and in that
i don't understand to intimidate those i know that but like why it's tried to scare you because you
said i almost quit because of this and that's what they want you are too targeted they want
you to quit but it makes me feel more so there's they keep trying to do it to me but they keep
missing my house they like drop the keys too far and i'm like that's not my house dickheads
like seriously though but they don't i don't care like i would if i they were there even if they're
people who are like super against me i'd be like hey what's up because i would invite them in for
a drink especially limoncello um but they don't they don't scare me like what are you gonna do
because i can have legal action if you do something really retarded sorry i shouldn't
say retarded really stupid retarded means an adult who doesn't think like an adult
for me anyway so like i that's a terrible word i shouldn't use it anyway so um no like but why
why would you do that why would you target people that doesn't even make sense like use your time
more effectively why are you wasting gas money i would say it's just creepy stupid stalker crap
well it's it is but you're gonna find that anywhere pathetic you're gonna find it anywhere
it really means they're pathetic to be fair it's a part of like internet culture i was almost gonna
say gamer culture but yeah a part of internet culture how do people want to get revenge on
other people by doxing people do things that are fucked up they're like swatting
that that article recently we're gonna get into that later in the show absolutely you don't know
about that you're looking at me so here's the deal with doxing i don't think that everything
is doxing like everybody screams doxing at the drop of a hat and i don't think so it's publicly
available information it's not doxing depends on what it is you know but i think people scream it
too soon just like they scream spoofer too soon i think that people no don't pull my mic don't
pull my mic like if you here's the deal if you do something stupid and you do something wrong
you should expect to get caught and you should expect to be exposed but i think that um the
doxing that they're talking about is more like in the the the publishing people's information
like publishing maybe where tori lives you know that kind of thing that would be doxing because
she didn't there's no reason for it she's not a politician or anything yeah so and they have and
she hasn't done anything wrong except for play the game in a way that they don't like yeah that's
totally doxing but like but if you do something wrong if you're cheating and someone says you
were cheating and they expose you for cheating that's not doxing that's you being a dick and
getting caught and here's the other thing that always kind of gets me if we all quit you're
going to be fucking bored right um yeah i live in a green area i'm not bored well no but i'm saying
i'm saying if everybody from the same team quits and this will go both ways if everybody's in the
same team quits y'all are going to be really fucking bored because this is about you need
both sides we're talking to you roseville and fulsomes well anyway no seriously no you're
right you would you would be really bored when my res don't play i'm bored yeah i don't understand
the point of playing when you don't have an opposition it's like playing pokemon i don't
know i wouldn't be bored if they would stop playing in my area our pal bobby blackwolf
in chat says uh i don't think broadcasting someone's personal information is appropriate
punishment for cheating in a video game exactly you have to follow them through town with a bell
yelling shame this shame shame this is no no not they're real no no no no not necessarily
their personal information more like their agent name like if you say this agent was cheating
that's not doxing that's not doxing no but if you put yeah if you put the real name and where they
work yeah that is doxing so i'm like very specifically like if you are in the game and
your in-game name is then told to people you cheated then you should expect it i'm glad we
could clarify that for people to register participation for this week's episode of
royan challenge radio at vognetwork.com use the passphrase game uh kaijuto in chat says get these
guests a show on vog all about ingress it's our lucky break jen we wanted it be careful what you
asked for we knew it we said this will be the start rob is going to hold us up and give us
our beginning to any opportunity for him to do another podcast he'll do it it's already being
planned anyway all right uh let's uh let me ask about this too i do want to we unfortunately can't
talk all night about ingress we probably could but let me ask about this let me ask about the
future of ingress because this is a little bit scary for some people um the game has been
for yeah primitives let's talk about primitives right so the game do you want to i said we were
not going to talk about ops spec or drama tonight but i think this drama would be okay drama it's
funny do you want to talk about why i'm dead to you jen would you like tell the story on yeah
he's dead to jen by the way okay tell why am i dead to jen rob is dead to me because
you know we have chatted with the others the um makers of the game niantic and they throw
anomalies every once in a while and there was just a sort of like hey we should have an anomaly in
sacramento again because we've had one previously and it was it was a good time and but i wasn't
there so it wasn't a real party right rob wasn't there i was only level seven and i i didn't get
to go and so um we had sort of a get together with um some of our mods and some of our our people
with in within the community and um snow and myself and another agent who was our designated
driver because snow and i had been drinking far too much at that time i decided to run to target
because i needed something very desperately it was not needed it was a pug pillow doorstop it
was desperately needed um but i come back and rob and all of the people in the party who are still
there 15 20 people in this party yeah um have decided to tell me that there is an anomaly
happening in sacramento in like what a month i think it was you said i think i think i said
jen have you checked google yes have you checked they just announced it in europe they're doing an
anomaly on february whatever i picked a saturday in february i said they're doing anomaly in
february and they're doing it i think i actually said i said they're doing it in mobile because
i thought about you mobile yes that's where i'm from okay that's where it came from i said they're
doing it in mobile and they're doing it in uh i think i just threw a rant i was like i think
they're doing i don't even like walla walla washington or something and they're doing it in
sacramento and it's called it's the ingress primatist and i kid you not i dropped my purse
she dropped her purse and i had to keep a straight face and everybody she dropped her purse and
started screaming expletive yes yeah and when you said mobile i said i'm calling bullshit on this
and i grabbed my phone and i started looking at the website at which point you did what
you lied faster and harder and snow was less drunk than me so for you know that particular
we had had the same amount so after about a minute of jen being like fully hysterical
i thought yeah well i said it was primatist primatist is the name of the series
optimist primatist i was singing a primatine and so because you'll need it after you hyperventilate
oh i definitely was hyperventilating it takes a lot to plan an anomaly and so one month i mean
we did it previously you don't want to do it in one month but it really really sucked and so i
was just like oh my god i couldn't believe it but i believed him and then finally after like a minute
when snow's like starting to look at her phone and look at me i turn around to everybody else
at the party and i say okay y'all get that on video and nobody did and nobody did which pisses
me off oh it's so great i'm so glad everybody everybody busts up laughing because remember
20 people had to like keep that a secret and then and they all stood there with the serious faces
oh it's awful i hate them like i thought someone had died i walked in i swear to you i walked in
and everybody was very solemn and it was like these sad faces and rob says something serious
has happened and i was like he goes you need to get you need to get jen in here right i went
oh okay and i turned around i went out there i go something's happened you guys like they're very
serious people look like they might cry at any second like what is going on we need to go in
and then rob dumped a bunch of bullshit all over us i'm so glad that it was you and not me because
i don't think i could have held it together nobody i think i don't even remember how that came
together like i i everybody wants to blame me but i really think it was dr graft that started that
whole thing like at least i'm gonna throw him under the bus i would not be surprised if it
was him who came up with but then like he kind of threw it out there and then like i ran with it
i'm gonna win the oscar for this shit you did you won an oscar for that i did well then i also won
a stabbing from jen he did i'm saving it for later the look that she gave me you guys the stitches
are healing i died i died in place it's like you called me more than just a son of a bitch
you screamed you screamed that he was dead to you you screamed fuck you it was bad it was it was
very dangerous she came over and did the drunk play hitting thing you know thing anyway so the
reason why i was able to get away with calling it primatist is because we know that there's this new
version of ingress coming that's been in the news lately called ingress prime obviously niantic has
had a lot of success with pokemon go and ingress although it's fun it's an aging game it's showing
its age you need to be able to change your direction on the map with one finger yeah right
right well and that's one of the that's one of the big things i know i hate that i have to use two
fingers what is wrong with you i guess that i can use one when i do pokemon because i'm i'm never
driving when i play but when i click to go to click on something and it spins the screen i get
mad why does pokemon have functionality that ingress doesn't have because people took the
feedback and put it in pokemon go you know what niantic we love you so much we want an anomaly
here but seriously let's get that fixed i've never noticed you need two hands yeah because no she
doesn't play any other games i know that okay controversial you guys but you could just make
it an option like a check yeah if they make it an option i would be pleased with that anyway so we
know they're gonna make a new version called ingress prime that's coming out soon trademark
tm soon tam when it is um tori and i at the san francisco anomaly last month we got to actually
kind of peek at this and see a little sneak preview of it and i thought graphically it looked
really cool part of the thing that drew me to ingress in the first place was that it looked
like tron and i was like you know but it was you mean like old school tron yeah fuck yeah old
school look at my hat today tron yeah i love tron but there was never and what always bugged me green
is my favorite color and it always bugged me there were no green people in tron they're all
blue or red blue is my favorite color is why are you green well i mean you know because when i
chose enlightened a my friend was green and i sat there looking at my phone she goes you have to
choose green i said no i don't hang on and i thought enlightened and i read the thing about
enlightened and i thought okay i think leonardo da vinci i think enlightened and then when i
looked at resistance all i could think of was the south park episode like law resistance lives on
like that whole thing right right so and i thought i'm sure they sing it when they right
and so in my head what i thought was if the first thing i think of when i think of resistance is
south park and a song i'm totally enlightened there's no fucking way like like or and whoa
hang on the second song i thought of by the way with resistance was from lay miz yeah the
resistance i'm like french sewers like no like all i'm thinking of is music i'm thinking of music
it's just right it's one question no it's one question no so like this is really what
happens so like i'm thinking i'm thinking of music i'm clearly enlightened so i press the
green okay usually i should tell you the story about when i asked shane to play ingress and
that if you would play ingress he would be more likely to get an invite to pokemon go
and he's like okay i signed up for ingress but i picked the blue team because i love blue and i was
like this isn't a fucking joke shane if you pick the blue what do you think this is i can't i
cannot help you shane why why but good news everybody good news he deleted and and did a
green account and then he got to level six and he was like i don't get it stop you don't play after
level six i'm not shane no he's not shane it's matt he still plays he's he's badge lock no shane
isn't here shane i'm talking really bad with names talking about him that's all about names
right shane's not here no shane's the worst like let's talk about shane i'll be sure to send that
to him this is stupid i need one more platinum to hit level nine i mean i need a silver so quickly
quickly because i do want to get into news because we're almost an hour in and we haven't talked
about a single video game yet uh besides excuse me besides ingress so what about uh ingress we
also talked about two dots okay what about ingress prime what what do you are you excited for ingress
prime are you scared i am both um i think it will be jesse spano i'm so excited i'm so i'm so scared
exactly i am hopeful that the functionality of it will be improved but i'm a little worried that
they're going to have a lot of um sort of problems with it you know launching and having a lot of
bugs but i mean we've dealt with bugs with ingress we've dealt with uh i think pokemon
people have dealt with bugs too so and harry potter soon that's right and the chat we just
brought that up too that we're gonna get harry potter i'm concerned that people with older phones
who play ingress are not going to be able to play ingress prime and that bothers me that's happening
with pokemon go pokemon go just that bugs me because you should have a game that doesn't well
first of all when i play pokemon even now my phone overheats and it's ridiculous that's because that
sucked as far as battery life is yeah no it's horrible like i already carry extra battery
chargers and cords and all kinds of crap but like why is my phone overheating i have to turn my ac on
and cool my phone off before i battle a gym that's right i remember beta testing uh pokemon go as
well yeah yeah like keep it right next same thing it would just overheat all the time no like i
beta tested and it was so bad when they used to have like the the like leaves that would blow the
grass that would blow yeah they had the leaves animation yeah so it overheated so i'm concerned
that they're they're focusing on the graphics and that it's going to cause phones to overheat
it's going to cause older phones to not work that that distresses me a little bit well even like
you need to make it so that everyone can still play regardless of what phone they have what
processor they have it's yeah it's nothing to do with the graphics the engine that runs in unity
is pretty lightweight i mean in the the stuff that they have in there is very just it's it's
nothing the phone should be able to do that it's how they're pinging the wi-fi and how they're
pinging the gps that overheats that thing tori what about you because you and i actually stood
in a line to see the game uh at uh the ingress event in december they were showing they showed
a little demo of uh prime and we got to see it what do you think are you scared excited um i
think i'm a little bit both um yeah i do think that um i think the graphics i mean improved
graphics are definitely going to be a plus improved functionality will be a plus yes i'm
concerned about people with older phones um i'm also concerned about something they said they
kept talking about it as a game reset or something like that and i'm wondering like are they some
people have said yes and some people have said no um are they gonna like seriously have us all start
over no that is no not from the beginning badges but i mean in terms of the map there was something
that oh about no they're not resetting the portal clarified that the portals will not be reset
oh good good good so that would be one thing it's the only thing that sweet krug did not tap dance
around well good because that would be one thing it would be like i mean that would be just like
crazy if everybody's sitting there going oh my god but um the other thing would be um i think
that i'm hoping is that there's maybe more stuff to kind of make the cheating less likely or more
traceable um i'm hoping that that will happen but i'm excited about it i think it's it's i mean we're
ready for a change we've done i'm excited for the people that are gonna you know because ingress is
kind of an older game we don't get a lot of people anymore the only new people we really get are
pokemon go players don't get me wrong because we have had some awesome new ones lately that came
from pokemon go because they want to submit they want to submit pokestops and then they realize
ingress is better and that really happened there's a guy right here in my neighborhood who we were
talking to at a raid and he's like i don't know i don't but then he finally installed the game and
then like a couple weeks later uh one of the other agents here and we all met up at a raid he's like
dude ingress is like way more fun ingress is way more fun than pokemon it really is
i it really is there's room in the world for both that's just me no i okay full disclosure
i'm level 36 in pokemon and i've got a higher level than me i've got over 17 000 pokemon so
like i play pokemon i do i play it a lot but i'm like a lot potter i don't know if i can do three
i can do harry potter i want you better let me beta test it hey niantic if you listen to this
i want to beta test i'm gonna do harry pot i'm gonna play the harry potter game as well i mean
i'm already playing animal crossing and mitomo at the same time that's not the same thing no
but i'm playing like five different games that i check every day but the prerequisite to beta
testing pokemon was to be level 16 in ingress and and have like no no that was something else
never mind i'm talking a little higher it was about 12 or so because i got in it i mean even
so when it comes out i'm gonna play it i thought you were level 10 rub no i finally leveled finally
after all these years i'm actually at 15 oh you get the fuck out i actually learned at 2 a.m last
night i was like the fuck out right i didn't learn but i kind of like remembered i was like wow you
get a lot of ap from fucking up farms yeah you do yeah uh yeah if i really wanted a power level i
guess i could shout out to the lord fu how do you think he leveled so fast he freaking burned down
novada county all the time all right uh going to chat at live.vognetwork.com as zet and chat says
i'm gonna beat you to 16 rob yeah probably yeah she is she totally is um and i'll beat you all
to 24. uh oh jen will totally beat us all to 24. oh act deaf says i found pogo way funder than ingress
i'm sorry but that's okay that's what act deft yeah we'll try again with your community like you
get to meet people in ingress i'm serious i do i i yes your your answer is incorrect to be fair
to be fair you get to meet people in pokemon go with this with the raids and everything not the
same it's not the same a little bit all right he tried at least a lot of people won't even try
i mean if he's in sacramento play with us he's actually he's in mexico he's not here so oh wait
we have some things for you to do in ingress if you could level the eight we you would love it you
would love ingress that's all i gotta say like you're in mexico we love you all right anyway
uh let's see oh this is a great question from zeba this is another hot issue in uh ingress
so we'll probably wrap up after this question get to the rest of the show uh zeba and chat says i
have a question did anyone there get in trouble for trespassing to get to portals no another
another you would never trespass i would never trespass i wouldn't i would not trespass so um
wait but i want to go back to shards before you end because i have something to say it's fine
go ahead all right i don't trespass i don't okay good good good girl what about you jen have you
ever gotten in trouble for trespassing i've never gotten in trouble for trespassing um we did have
some portals in my hometown that were on a um fire like at a fire station and we were was i was
with my son and we were trying to cap it and you could hear over the loudspeaker of them like
talking about us being there so we laughed very quickly it was that was probably in the first year
or so that i played though that was that's about the furthest the closest to being in trouble for
trespassing that i've ever met yeah like there were people out there like what are these people
doing out front why the hell were they on a loudspeaker i don't know okay not very secretive
they can't hear us the fire department needs to get their shit together tori how about the
trespassing issue for you have you ever been accused of it or you you had to do it or what
i haven't trespassed i don't think i've been accused of it i'm sure i'll be set straight if
i'm wrong about that but um the way i look at it is this if i trespass to take a portal it's it's
not legit so if i take it and i were to throw a blocker to it or use it for a field or something
like that it kind of casts doubt or i don't know it kind of puts an asterisk if you will um next to
whatever i do with that portal so that's why i really feel like any trespassing you know needs
to be any portals taken legitimately i've even gone out to take green portals that have been
spoofed green just to make them legit green so i kind of look at it like that so i i i don't
trespass no i don't either i i will say that i'm gonna admit to this because i think this is a gray
area i've been in a park after dark and yes i've played ingress but it's not it's such a gray area
because you know some people say oh well you know you will get screamed at in comms you know oh the
posted park hours it's like i am walking from point a to point b as a lot of night joggers do
and i just happen to have my phone out busting your shit and i'm not smoking marijuana like
that's why they have those hours right they have it for camping and that kind of thing what's wrong
with smoking marijuana it's 2018 now it's legal now but you're not doing crack all that stuff
aside but i also think some people forget that um there's some a lot of times there's more than
one way and this is on both sides i'm not accusing the other team of this because i've had to tell
our own people hey dial it back because sometimes there's more than one way to get to a portal
that's another big one is that there's some where people go that's behind a gate that's behind a
gate but it's like but did you know you could get behind it if you're willing to walk for half a
mile down a trail or did you do you know somebody who works there or any other things that's a big
one ask that our community members not trespass and and that is a big thing if we find out that
you're doing it repetitively it would be a problem for us but generally like if you're just walking
through like caesar chavez park what's our motto don't cheat no which thing yeah that's
got if you're gonna be our motto is don't be a dick sorry don't be a dick if you're gonna be at
caesar chavez park after hours like that's on you that's dangerous place that's on you it's not that
is not a great place to be capping portals in the middle of the night just don't but what's
interesting we're gonna assume you're buying heroin again because of pokemon go i mean right
now capital park is for is there's a thing nesting there called a wailmer which is a very
highly desired pokemon because you need like 400 of them to evolve it what's a wailmer exactly so
there's a lot of people at capital park it's my buddy just so you know it's my buddy there's at
all hours are trying to catch wailers so can i go really quickly over shards yes quickly okay
i hate them and why is that i fucking hate them because i don't sleep okay downyville i was in
downyville for two shards you're downyville is no you don't no you don't i do you do only because
of ingress does anybody else know where downyville is i've been no no did you know signal is famous
for the bubble wrap parade they will put bubble wrap also famous for mountain biking okay like a
legitimate thing mountain bike over the boat more about the bubble wrap i do they lay bubble wrap on
the street and then they have a parade and that's what they do instead of fireworks because you
can't have fireworks up there are you kidding me no yeah on the 4th of july they have a bubble
literally california will burn down again oh my god i want to go to there okay i literally
on fourth of july i literally taped i ducked duct taped bubble wrapped my floor and let my kids walk
on it so this is genius i love it i love it i've done this but downyville i was up there twice
twice for shards no i didn't sleep 48 hours no sleep every time horrible um yeah shards yeah
i don't know if our audience i was awake for fucking 72 hours rob you're making ingress
sound great no this is for shards shards suck by the way i played uh dragon age inquisition
there are shards no no there are shards and when i saw them when i saw the shards i said fuck shards
i hate shards and then all of a sudden i started collecting shards and let me tell you it's way
easier when you can do it from your couch true oops and not downyville although they're still
annoying no i love them because they're not in downyville and you don't have to drive
anywhere off that was on my end sorry i forgot to close google yeah what the hell my bad so anyway
shards and dragon age inquisition love them shards and ingress fuck you all right anyway
so i was just i was just gonna say how you really i don't know if we had effectively communicated
to the listeners just how hardcore you guys can be about ingress but thank you snow for your whole
like 72 hour binge story i think it's like the guy who had to get the camper toilet put in next
to his chair for playing world of warcraft wait a minute you can do that because i'm gonna do that
who did that how do you kill that which because that guy needs to play ingress
also catheters catheters are a thing guys hopefully on our team because the other team
has a lot all right uh whatever tori anyway you don't drink water when we hike any any last things
you guys want to say about ingress maybe something maybe like a pitch for for our
listeners who have not played this game maybe something you download and join the green team
or you know especially if you're in northern california you need to join the green team if
you're in other places you know whatever but yeah but no green team nothing california come on okay
so no there's play styles that are different in every area so before you join you should look at
the map well you can join yes okay shut up so join then look at the map and decide what you want to
do so in our area specifically the resistance are about like holding daily fields they call them the
blob like you hold your daily fields whereas enlightened about play however you want and we
want to win we'll throw big fields so i think there's just a play style difference so just
look at your area because if you're far away you might look at your area and say like i want to be
a part of a community and look at that or i want to be i want to be into the espionage and secret
squirrel stuff and then choose the opposite team but like look at your area first and also be
retired so you can play all the time oh my god no shit right look um look at um google plus i know
it's weird oh sorry barry i'm not a single mom stay at home mom my bad hold on hold on uh so for
for ingress ingressers are still using google plus because ingress started as a google or niantic
started as a big for yourself there's a lot but even on facebook i would put put your name
and then enlightened to start and see if it's a good fit for you
and then if it were me check check resistance as long as you're not in northern california
no i will say you know there was something happening with their g plus thing so there's
actually no ingress um g plus like group anymore as of today they said it was temporary we got rid
of it well if there's something wrong not saki and l but like the overarching ingress there was
something going on maybe like porn bots full disclosure don't try and join the enlightened
ingress or g plus group right no just ingress g all right yyr in chat says i can say for certain
that yes their level of ingress hardcoreism has been effectively communicated no i'm not i like
to microfield let me let me try ending on this note i'll start with you tori let me try ending
on this note what keeps you a fan of ingress after all this time why do you keep signing
into the app why do you keep playing it's in this room oh it really it is it's me you guys it's me
you know what i'll be honest there are times i feel tired and i'm just like oh you know there's
gonna be a day when this game isn't here and there there's really two things and i try to
imagine sometimes if i stop playing this game am i still gonna see these people and some of you
yes definitely um but it's this community and i've made so many friends and i that's what i love
about our faction i just think we have an amazing community the other thing is that is the places
that it brings you yeah i went to a part of hawaii the other day that without this game i never would
have ever thought it was very remote very obscure one lane road etc and oh my gosh the the amazing
kind of the crazy stories you'll tell and the places you've been i mean i think those two
things alone are really what keeps me going in this game so my day job recently expanded into
a lot of rural parts of california where now we service you know more parts of the state including
these rural areas and because of ingress now when like people are like i've never heard of this
place where is elk creek i'm like oh i know i've been there it's uh it's up north off i-5 you gotta
go left and it's like shit this game has like taught me things that i'm using in my day job
what is going on wait a minute you go to elk creek i went i went there because somebody in
this room isn't that where you got your yeah that's where i got my onyx yeah somebody in
this room set that whole thing up oh interesting all right anyway that was me but i no longer have
keys so it was me by the way you're welcome uh i think it was her that put that one together no
i thought it was the one that was me that was my solo sorry oh my bad wait that was the one
where it's like run toward the water i operated me yelling run towards all right i opt that solo
so we're talking all about bobby blackwolf says the real prize is the friendships we made along
the way as we all fight about who did what fact snow they literally it's the people it's the
people that keep you going every day yes it's the people i love the people i've met so many people
and the thing is i actually like a lot of the res unlike other people um i like a lot of the res
and i talk to them and they're nice and they're fantastic i love them the vast majority are nerds
just like me who picked a different color at the beginning of the game whatever right exactly yeah
and so i like the people and i like to be i even like the opposition but mostly i like my own
people because i talk to them every day even if i don't go i just go hack a portal and i'll throw
a field anything i'm able to keep in contact with these people and i've met them in person it's not
like a creepy internet relationship where you've never met the person like i've met them weirdly
at two in the morning in a dark park but it doesn't matter i've met them in person so it
matters to me jen what about you what keeps you going on ingress every day well on a personal
level i do really continue to to grind stats i really like that like personal challenge that
i set for myself but but um as both tori and snow said it is definitely the community um
i've been running ish this community for about the whole time i've been playing it was probably
around the time i hit level eight that i was brought in to be made a mod by the people who
are running it at that time and it's just been something that i've continued to do for almost
five years so it's i love meeting our new people i like seeing how people get excited over fields
i like how we help each other and people move each other from houses to houses and they do
personal things for each other yeah i catsat for a guy i met playing here in this neighborhood
exactly this is weird shit like that right this is not just like a game in many ways it's also
you you end up with a lot of friendships and like unfortunately christy who's not here tonight she
was going to be but she and i met in playing ingress it was not so oh i would thought you
guys were bifs beforehand no no we need to bail her out after the show we're gonna bail her out
from the er actually i got a message her son had fallen while playing pokemon of all things and
he's okay it's a dangerous game don't play it no um play ingress enlightened instead but anyway i
met i met christy um of all places playing ingress at the circle kind of near both of our works and
we see each other every single day twice a day during the work week and we are best friends and
i don't think that's ever going to change what about you and me oh second best friends that's
why you're allowed to have more than one bridesmaid all right all right so it's you and me tori um i
would actually say to the one thing that i think you guys didn't mention i'll close on this like
for me is the live events like the anomalies because you know the day-to-day weekly stuff
like you know there's just people out there that are more dedicated to the game than i am and
there's just you know there's just nothing i can do about that um but the live events really feel
like like they're big conventions they're big parties you know nerd awesome stuff even whether
we win or lose because no we went to chicago we got our ass kicked and i still had a blast yeah
i had a blast full no seriously when someone said anomalies to me the first time and they said a
bunch of people get together and you battle for portals and i thought you bunch of fucking nerds
i am not i will never go to an anomaly ever i think it's dumb like i am never gonna do that
oh my god it's so fun it is a giant party you can act like a kid it's great it is a snow and
i held hands and skipped down the street we totally skipped down the street to go capture
a portal together yeah and like rob said you can totally be losing like we went to utah uh
state salt lake city and we lost so bad and it was still so much fun and also kind of tying into
the last one of the other things tori said was you see new places i never would have gone to
salt lake city i don't know i never would have done that i've never lost anything ever stop
all right uh rock hat is in our chat over at live dot com rock hat what about me rock hat okay okay
so rock gave you the shirt quickly raw cat comes up to my house and we watch bad sci-fi together
we watched zoom zoombies which was the zoo animals who turned into zombies um it was
fantastic and it actually we watched it because of ingress because the um susanna moir oh she
in that she's in it oh i own right no no not yeah i own something but she follows me on butler yeah
she follows you on instagram you fucker she randomly followed me one day after i posted
everybody follow me mom mommy mommy is that i figured she followed everybody is that really
big deal account we have a sack enl account maybe she thinks hello i am you are cute oh stop
okay hang on so anyway what was i saying uh zoombies rock zombies rock hat is amazing he
comes we watched um the latest sharknado i think four or five i love sharknado i love bad sci-fi
i do and so i invite people over rob you haven't come yet i haven't been to your park you have
been invited you don't come up no i've been to your house i just have been inside i did
come to your house what the fuck yeah well you just i didn't is it because there's children
do you not like children i don't but i have three children what's the problem i don't either but i
have children you should come up all right anyway if you want to learn more about ingress and you're
welcome niantic for the hour-long free commercial but you know this is it's i think we talk a lot
about overwatch worker those other games i named but this is a whole nother thing that's happening
on mobile that i think a lot of people weren't aware of and i don't remember if i read this
comment earlier over in chat at live.vog network.com yyr in chat says i can say for
certain that yes their level of ingress hardcoreism has been effectively communicated no i i can help
anyone so like if you just start contact alternative facts or teeny hedgehog or mark from
orc and we will help you out we will hook you up with your local community res or enlightened
enlightens better um just saying but no like you need to hook up it's fun it's a really fun game
it gets you out of the house it gets you involved in other things it's really fun thank you for that
fair and balanced statement by the way i appreciate that you're welcome i will help it by the way i
will help resistance with things if someone enjoys resistance i will hook them up with the
right people if sacramento were to get an anomaly i would help the resistance to organize shit
because we need one niantic all right we're gonna shift gears here at orange launch radio and talk
a little bit as we do at the top of the show you top of the show huh uh an hour in here we're gonna
talk a little bit about our gaming weeks but we'll go quickly you guys we're gonna go quickly
through our gaming weeks and talk a little bit about what we've been playing this week and i
will include our guests because my understanding is there are some things they've been playing
that are not just pokemon go or what whoops and ingress uh dark sakura how was your gaming week
playing animal crossing um still playing uh the ragnarok online game um idle pouring mitomo
pokemon go ingress uh bust a move the new version for ios um what oh the oh the bubble game yeah
dance game no no not that one and i'm also playing a game called tabikairu which is by
the people who did um uh neko atame and basically it's just this frog who wanders around and you
feed him sometimes i i can only read about half of the japanese text so i'm still kind of guessing
my way through it but it's really cute it's it's actually i really super love the art style in it
so and of course i named him cairo which means frog so um it basically yeah then the the name
of the game is wandering frog so um i also um got another game that's kind of like a dating sim game
but it's to help you practice your japanese reading so i it's like called like kawaii
something or the other that's why i play all those games well i'm i'm actually set myself a goal that
by next year i will have passed the jlp t5 so i'm working on it um the that's for those who
don't know that's the japanese language proficiency test and the fifth level is the
intro level so wish me luck luck thanks um but i have also been um now that we've got three new
portals over by my house i've been playing more ingress to walk around but woohoo i think when
the weather doesn't suck i don't know if he's listening but uh one of my favorite agent names
oh dang you know the first person i met in ingress that wasn't you was um uh oreville
oh it's not anymore uh well it's complicated walking around the the park over yeah he's back
yeah i thought the old name was still effective yeah i don't know how much i'm allowed to say so
my favorite ingress name well well hung jury i like it my it's my favorite also res agent
like 300 wombats i love that because how do you come up with that there's also in washington
some drunk so your portal was taken by a some drunk in the middle of the night it's freaking
great there was an eight pound six what eight pound six ounce baby jesus there was there was
which bricky bobby yeah love it and anyway the other games i've been playing is um
i've i've um i quit my dwarf run on dragon age inquisition because it was boring i play nothing
but mages so um i i am on my 10th cullen romance now so yay um i actually back to playing mass
effect andromeda again too because i should finish the one with my pretty writer so i can romance um
uh uh crap vetra because turians are the best all right are we going dragon age inquisition
because i'm gonna play it again i'm gonna fuck everybody because seriously it's the dumbest
damn like why have romance enough i wanted to play a gay elf an elven male so i could romance
dorian and then i was like but i can't imagine him without bull and my ship my shipper head
goes i haven't seen him in bull yet you have to take them in your party for like a bunch of
things so that they start flirting with each other i haven't talked about strong armor so i'm afraid
to just take them both and run around and have them talk about bondage and they'll start fucking
perfect perfect no no okay tory tory you need to play dragon age inquisition
you can make the characters have sex with each other it does not look like team america world
police which i was hoping for but it is also not a straight fade straight it's not a straight cut
to porn so it's like in between you get some boobs and butt later skinamax is this like a
mix of like sims and uh game of thrones no not really yeah actually kind of some of it is but
like you can customize like your castle and all this that's the fun stuff but customize your tits
no is this unless you play on pc and have mods what the fuck is this pc or is this phone or
console and pc xbox one oh we have one which trust me if i could play it on my mac i'd be
playing it on my mac but my pc has a better graphics card in it the last game i played on
mac was dark castle all right i've been playing borderlands but i've been games yeah what what
other games robs me um and now i oh i'm trying to avoid the show going to midnight tonight i'm
restarting silent hill 3 excellent is that creepy are you doing the hd version or no i was i watched
a playthrough of the hd version to see if it was worth it for me to buy it um but i don't know no
because i like the voice acting in it but it's not pretty enough it doesn't look a lot better
the silent hill games in hd suck but i want a really good first silent hill hd remake that
would be awesome i love i love the psychological horror what's the one that's in the it's in like
an insane asylum and you're crawling around and like your light goes out is that outlast
outlast yeah yeah i have the best videos of my daughter playing that do you like to film your
kids playing scary games oh my god it's the best i'll show it to you in the break watching rob play
scary games is also funny oh god watching me play five nights at freddy's all right anything else
for your gaming week that's it all right loki how about you how much game a week you'll never guess
which game i played this week lego no ingress but yes um no i actually started stardew valley
oh shit is that because i was like i have all these games in my backlog let's try stardew
valley and it's i don't know it's just like um you can romance people in stardew valley it's
like for those of you not watching he shook his head like ants all right it's like animal crossing
but here's the best part about the game play it there's a character named shane that looks exactly
like shane like it's identical i think he i think he kind of likes that yeah what are you doing in
my game and apparently i think you can romance everybody in that game too you can so you should
i could romance shane if i want to i'm not going to you should yeah but no it's not awkward just
do it i have a cat so you're gonna romance the cat uh you know something did remind me actually
i bought the nonary games because of shane oh his visit and and my gift is not here i know i'm almost
like should invited by who's over here like he's the worst again shane has to get that bottle of
wine from my house because i can't drink anymore but yeah it's it's a pretty good game i like it
it's very relaxing it's just a very kind of i don't know it's very it reminds me so much of like
animal crossing if it wasn't real time so like you can play the game you're basically knocking down
trees and gathering resources crafting things and selling them running like a small little farm do
you get to explore a lot yeah there's a ton of stuff to explore in the game there's like um
this whole area that they go around and actually i think there's different starting areas you can
pick two so i just picked the basic one because it's my first time playing the game but they have
different starting areas that are different geography and stuff so it's it's all right i
mean it's a good relaxing game i guess um then of course yeah with the lego stuff i've been grinding
at lego marvel superheroes 2 to unlock everything in the game and i say grind because it feels like
you haven't unlocked at all no it takes me a while because my kids don't play it oh my kids play it
my kids used to play like believe lego marvel games all the time but they won't play any of
the levels so i have to go play through all the levels and lock everything and then they're like
i'll play all these characters and then get bored with it we have all three of your kids
they're like four and seven and a half okay similar to mine but mine are always like uh no
mommy go over here no no why why do i because that's where you have to go they know the whole
map no they just want to i honestly the lego marvel superheroes 2 i hate the open world map
they haven't actually lego avengers was better i think because at least they had manhattan in a
bunch of other areas yeah that was a good one but this one's like chronopolis and shit all around
but you know whatever i have a very important uh text message by the way i told shane he needs to
listen to olr this week because he's come up twice and he put why i said this time on how
loki says stardew valley shane is shane you he said everyone thinks that though except i'm not
an alcoholic like stardew valley shane sure you are sure you are valley shane is also kind of
mopey too so i know it's funny it's like hey shane it is all right anyway i just figured you'd
appreciate that update but yeah so that's what i've been playing and then a little bit of ingress
because i've been at parks how about more i don't see here's the problem i used to work later so
i used to work a shift that was like 10 30 to 7 15 or something like that so i would have like
about an hour and a half before i went from dropping my kids off to where i needed to be
the work and so i had all this time to play ingress and stuff and i just take a long time
coming home and then i do all that but now i drop my kids off and i have to be at work like
immediately and then coming home there's no time to play either because it's traffic and wake up
earlier i can't because i have to take my kids to school and they are slow as hell you're ready
no i gotta i gotta keep the show moving you'll have to do the sales pitch off air all right
anything else for your gaming week logan that's it all right um let me check out our guest jen
what kind of types of video games you've been playing this week well i always play uh like
mind teaser type cookie jam and two dots every day every week um don't look at me like that snow
in addition to ingress between cooldowns um but i in prep for the show i thought well i should
play some like regular games right some first person shooter type things and i'm notoriously
bad at these things like really really bad and uh so my kid set up his ps4 what is it that he has
right now ps4 yeah you hear how bad i am at this already right and um we were gonna play overwatch
and we had not even i had not even gotten out of the training when he said to me you should stick
to ingress mom um yeah it was really bad it was i mean i have a really hard time controlling your
both your like where you're looking and where you're going so my guy ends up looking up or down
a lot and then like sidewalking you know like everywhere he's going and falling off of mountains
because i didn't know that there was a mountain there because i was sidewalking you know so i
played overwatch for like 10 minutes and then he said he put me into a game like a live game with
other people that was humiliating and he's a higher level so of course i should look like i
know what the hell i'm doing and i don't i definitely don't so i said to him this is not fun and he said
you should go play ingress uh phantasm chat over at live.vog network.com says get good
that's what the kids tell each other who are bad rice did tell me that i needed to practice more
that's my son bryce the nice the nice way yeah yeah so tori told me she got destiny too because
her kid she actually she bought an xbox one don't get the wind out of her sail no call on
hang on i'm going to call her because no because she's really good at it and i'm not um so i started
playing it just because tori was going to play it i thought i'll play with my friend tori
we're going to play i'll play with our kids it'll be great except that i suck so i started playing
it and my husband sat next to me he goes this is embarrassing the whole time he was like this is
embarrassing you suck you need to practice your husband said this oh my god he was the worst
he was awful he was like you are horrible at this game you need to stop i can't watch this
and they left the room and i said all right fine so i started playing dragon age inquisition just
to get used to the controls because i figured i could run around there's quests and i'd get used
to the controls and then i could play destiny too turns out i still can't play it because they're
shooting at me and it makes me nervous so like i'm going around the corner and they're shooting
at me and i hide and he goes you can't hide just run in there and just shoot at them i can't
um i no i hide i just hide behind walls and stuff the whole time i'm like sneaking around
that's a good way to stay alive exactly that's my point cover cover is a good thing to do yeah
so then i duck down and i and i get my health back and i go shoot at them but i dragon age
inquisition then sucked me in and i'm like 140 hours or something crazy in two weeks like it's
insane i stayed up till like 5 30 in the morning one night because you know you just have to finish
this quest right quotes and it took forever but i love it i'm level 19 now it's like two weeks
and i played all the time and i just got admonished and told i can't play it while the
kids are awake so apparently i'm playing it too much so uh yeah that's my week you playing a video
game too much 72 hours in downyville right i know right now it's like i'm on my couch i'm
comfortable i have drinks available i have a bathroom right there it's fantastic so i like it
i'm good at it i'm gonna replay it again that got some similar shakes of the head from berry like
you're not playing this again i'm like yeah yeah i'm gonna play it again with a different character
all right so a little peek in your gaming week snow oh and i tried destiny 2 a second time
uh-huh i still hid i know how to control the character and i still hit i'm like they're
shooting at me and they're scary so i'm hiding all right let me go to tori and ask about your
gaming week tori i think you uh the snow spoiled it a little bit she pretty much you know what
yeah pretty much usual but uh well i got an yeah i got an xbox so that i could play with my kids
i've got two adult kids i want to throw in that i'm 57 years old uh and if y'all have ever seen
she does not look at she doesn't look 57 and you know what how i bet i bet our chatters would have
never known that if you hadn't said that because how awesome is that you are as hardcore as you
are about a video game but you kind of defy the stereotype of a gamer so snaps for you oh thank
you well but my eyeball i have adult kids and they both live out of state or two of them live
out of state and they play this xbox thing so have y'all ever seen those videos like when they
give a senior citizen an ipad and then they take video oh like elders react yeah yeah it's like
yeah elders react that's what it is so that's what it's like with me with the xbox controller
so i'm just like i want to shoot that thing and they're like no no mom don't shoot that thing
and so i do a lot of the you know like spinning around uh forward backward and side like
sidestepping but i do i have like jumped into the water a few notable times um it's it's a fun it's
it's really a fun game i'm i'm getting better but uh yeah that's pretty much it it's it's more
comical to watch me um but but i i enjoy playing and uh but yes ingress is gonna be more my thing
playing with my kids is what's best okay so ingress is always gonna be your main squeeze
but you know destiny is a good yeah perry potter might give it a run for its money though not sure
where that's when that comes out what's gonna happen now if we get to pick from the four houses
are you gonna be are you gonna be slithering with me or is it gonna be a new further in for life
are you gonna be slithering oh hell yeah i'm gonna be slithering i'm always sort of slithering
i'm gonna have to think about that this might be a family decision oh no oh i'm gonna do whatever
i want fuck y'all so you're a good slithering already i don't think i like there was a test
that i wasn't slithering i have one time tested ravenclaw i think i was raven i'm actually scared
like if the pvp in harry potter is as intense as it is in ingress like people that are my friends
today are going to become my enemies oh yeah you need to end those friendships right now yeah but
then it's but then it's good well jen it was great having you know you you know for a fact we're
gonna be like in the general channel like hey what is everybody choosing get out of our slack
get off my lawn oh but then but then long time get out of my house long time frenemies from ingress
may end up because we all thought that was gonna happen with pokemon go and then it turns out in
pokemon go either a you just hate it or b um the teams kind of don't matter in pokemon they don't
matter at all there's no scoreboards there's no game that's like hey look at all this stuff that
we're gonna put out we're gonna put out brand new games like when are you gonna finish the last
game you started because there's no game there okay i want to comment on that but i super want
to keep it quiet there was that one game with the money locked up in las vegas that never went
anywhere what was that thing called like end game oh end game yeah yeah that never happened no it
ended yeah all right i played a different game what was it um there was a bunch of one i beta
tested there's there's actually i became a little obsessed with ar gaming because of ingress i've
tried them all i tried garfield go oh my god did you really it's did you have a hairball what the
i tried munzi munzi was munzi was okay because it was kind of like it's just more geocaching
it's like geocaching gamified but the problem with munzi is that the the stops are all user
generated which is fine but they're all like they were all made in 2002 2000 or 2012 2013 and they're
all like the stickers are flooded away or they're gone so like all these things that the game says
are there are not there and it's really frustrating did you try delta t yeah i did i can't
yeah i did it's not on iphone no the mining the mining thing is ridiculous i didn't i had my
invite but i never got around to it i don't know maybe it went to my spam or something and i just
saw it the other day i was like oh i missed this no no i tried it i played your conus go just to
see and that was it was interesting i tried enclave legit oh is that an a i've heard that
enclave was cool the idea was really cool but it didn't pan out all right i'm gonna get to my
gimme week but i do want to first off i'm going to apologize for our chatters here because sometimes
they make comments but tori going back to the discussion we were having on uh you know your
age and you're you're a cool mom and all this stuff we have a con daddy in our chat room at
live.hognore.com says milf in the studio oh there's at least a few of us yeah my birthday's
tomorrow by the way happy birthday thank you are you snow i am 29 there you go oh it's just like
bobby it's uh bobby blackwolf here in the studio okay i'm gonna be 44 are you really yeah i would
have guessed that i know oh is this delicious black hair no it's all the work i put in
you have no idea i'm hiking in downyville no i tell much i pay to my dermatologist
all right i live through the power of retin-a so yeah right better living through pharmacology
quickly my gaming week not a lot of extra stuff i'm still playing world of warcraft here in the
workbook i know right i'm joining next week i know no i have a rejoining to join that a cd
there is a thing called world of warcraft widows and my sister is a world of warcraft my husband's
one uh wait he's a widow yeah because he's lost me to world of warcraft for a while
and then i play farmhouse c14 which is basically the same thing
said people don't know that one sorry i still have it except not as fun i've uh had a cough
for like six weeks he's full of it he's just laughing so as far as like a new game i did
try out the the open beta for final fantasy decidio because that's available on playstation
4 i haven't turned on my playstation 4 forever so finally try fall past decidio which is like
a fighting game with final fan yeah it didn't make any sense to me like i didn't understand
i've tried playing the tutorial and i was like i don't understand what i'm doing like okay i
need to hit the crystal to generate the summon power so i can summon things but like what what
button now here's the thing i'm sure it's great for some people and some people were really into
it but like i thought it was going to be like street fighter or tekken or one of those types
of games with final fantasy i thought it would be ur guys basically and it's not so that was it's
like complicated it was it was a little bit disappointing so that was that was i thought
about it i saw that and i was like maybe i should go download that and then i got lazy it's more
fun to watch playthroughs but i think you should you know it's because there is the open beta right
now you can make a decision for yourself hey barry there's an open beta for a game download it free
there you go i played the original on psp and it was all right and uh really get into it dragon
ball has uh that dragon ball fighter what's it called dragon ball fighter z they had an open
beta but it's had issues i think a lot of people have been having they've taken it back down i
think for a little bit no no that's right betas have problems that's what happens that's why
they're betas all right so that was a little bit of our game and it's all about beerus and that
makes me happy because he's my favorite new character uh you have to check out the beta
when it works and tell us all about it next week i am still keeping up on dragon ball super
uh housekeeping so uh i don't we'll be here over the next few weeks you can follow us on twitter
twitter.com slash olr facebook.com slash orange launch radio when i say next few weeks i mean
obviously we're not retiring anytime soon but um do you know how did you guys know how long we've
been doing this show did you know um 700 and something shows yes we heard that at the beginning
holy crap this is uh in june we will be celebrating 16 years of this damn yeah i know crazy right we
started how old are you um 29 oh no i'm girl you're older than i'm literally 39 literally
actually 39 not a not a lie for another age yeah so yeah really yeah rude and and you look younger
you do oh well thank you and i'm older than rob no no way everybody in here has really good
dermatologists and a lot of work done i'm i'm the youngest that's certainly not me you're the
youngest as usual the youngest person are you younger than him i don't know if you're younger
than him i'm 37 in a row remember me too i can do it to both of you i can go in a row
right 37 in a row clerks yep for the win try not to suck any dick on your way out
the crazy show tonight all right uh so you follow us on twitter and facebook and all that um when i
say we're not going to be or we're going to be here over the next few weeks uh that's because
the next show planned off is at the end of march i'm going to be going to atlanta at the end of
march not for dragon con believe it or not i'm going for other stuff uh other stuff what other
stuff uh i have to tell you because i don't know if it's ingress i'm gonna bring you keys from
your full of shit what are you doing atlanta i'll tell you off rarely because i don't know if i'm
allowed to talk about it openly or not so anyway yeah i'm gonna throw i'm gonna throw a field be
ready for it rez opsec all right he's putting tons of guardians there yeah that's right i'm
gonna plan on my guardians in atlanta so pay attention guys atlanta actually i i dropped an
eight on a portal in atlanta when i was there for dragon con somebody else owned it i just bumped it
and that portal was still up like for a good three months i think it finally got 149 down have you
tried detroit is that a good place to get guardian i don't know i'm guessing i i don't think it's a
good place for i want to go to button willow have you tried north korea go to north korea i don't
think they have portals there maybe they do we should check i got they do have portals in north
korea what about gilroy my 110 day portal was in washington fucking dc like it wasn't you know
it was just you had to kind of walk i got my i got almost 90 days just in the middle of sacramento
so i mean and i know like some of our rez will make fun of us for it but they've gotten
uh 150 in the area they'll get it next door to vernon sure yeah no i'm talking like on the river
dougie fresh got his on the river oh wow that being said we don't really scrape him here either
he was playing i know i love dougie fresh every dougie fresh 916 he's amazing um fantastic just
going to the demilitarized zone area so there you go all right uh let me move on uh into some gaming
news let's talk about what else is going on in the game world so we're gonna talk about some
stuff that's not ingress but some other games hopefully y'all are y'all are familiar with let's
see loki this is a big one yeah so they had that that you know rumored nintendo direct it was like
hey look we're doing one and here it is turns out some rumors are true yeah so there were some
rumors uh not a whole i mean there was some stuff you know announced nothing like really huge i
think so they had of course you know they're doing some additional content for super mario odyssey so
it's like this multiplayer mode basically you get to hide a balloon or find a balloon and so they're
going to have that um in the game and i guess based on finding those you get different outfits and
stuff so that's the thing um and then of course you know along with that lots of ports being
um announced for the switch so some of those uh the world ends with you final remix is coming um
the ease eight the lacrimosa of donna hyrule warriors is getting a port donkey kong country
tropical freeze and dark souls remaster obviously the big one so lots of ports um coming out pretty
soon um but that's you know considering the switch has already outsold the wii u uh in japan anyway
i mean that's it kind of makes sense especially for things like donkey kong tropical freeze i
think a lot of people missed out on it would be interested in i wasn't as into it as other people
but i understand why it's popular yeah i mean it's it's there's new stuff coming so that's kind of
cool yeah um and then of course they're also doing a brand new um snk fighting game that's
going to be coming to the switch as well so they have this um game called snk heroines tag team
battle and it's going to feature um the female cast from you know all their different fighting
friends yes all their friends from friends from friends yes monica and rachel are in there right
they're fighting you know what i'd really like is like a nintendo 64 style mario kart can we get that
well uh if nintendo switch would ever announce virtual console uh you might be able to get the
actual mario kart 64 i really want that i'm very good at that game you know what though seriously
try if you ever do decide to invest in a switch like if maybe your kid how much are they they're
not very expensive right uh 400 i think right now yeah you know why they're making this game i can
tell you right now based on these screenshots it's the cell the skimpy clothing dlc oh yeah
that's all there's a lot of nakedness going on right now it's all excels not here but in these
screenshots remember if there's the doa 5 game that they had that they had the one that was kind
of a piecemeal where you bottle the characters you bottle a dlc that's totally what this shit is
is just a cash grab at that don't get me wrong it's great that the women of snk have a fighting
game all to their own but let's be honest it's just to sell that dlc i was gonna say pod culture
and chad is correcting me that it's 299 for the switch what is dlc download content like add-ons
extra stuff you learn something new every day so yeah you get you get the base game and then oh
hey you want that bikini that looks like um pineapples well that's going to cost you five
bucks itty bitty teeny weeny yellow polka dot bikini basically itsy bitsy teeny weeny yellow
polka dot but anyway i was gonna say i didn't get to finish my thought with with jen uh get
mario kart 8 for the switch because even though it's like it's a lot of fun it's a lot of fun
and it'll remind you of the so it like christmas time we normally pull out the nintendo 64 because
we still have one that works but our new tv just like plays it black and white which is a very
difficult play him the rumors you know supposed to be uh that the nintendo 64 game board are gonna
be the next ones they're gonna classic mini four so they're gonna have really like that
exclusive so if you could make it happen or you can just totally get um raspberries
you can get a raspberry pie and stuff you can also what type of tv do you have um well it's
i think that it was at my parents house i think it's a fancy one like the 4k ones
because um we've got ours to work on a 4k tv oh did you um have to i think use like a there's
like a component converter oh you'd have to use i'll i'll see we'll exchange information and i'll
find what you need yeah because we definitely were frustrated like you can't play battle on
that going to best buy and ask they'll they might be able to help us this is the this is the rare
case where radio shack would have been really helpful right there's still a couple of radio
shacks in sacramento then that might be yeah yeah be the place to get them well my husband used to
manage one so i have a he jumped he got out of that ship when it was sinking i have a ton of
converters at home i don't remember if i have one that goes to hdmi i know i have several to go from
vga to component or hdmi i may have one the only problem that you're going to run into using those
converters because we also have one for our my husband and i have like 40 something video game
systems um and we run into that with our super nintendo and our nes because it gives you like
two seconds of lag in the game oh so which is fine like an rpg or something but when you're
playing something hardcore like the guardian legend which is my favorite game or mario kart
yeah that i'm sorry but we are hardcore okay listen me and my sisters i think there is a
retron that will do nintendo 64 i'll double check um jamie i want to ask you real quick though before
you check um because you like fighting games you like snk you do a lot of snk games what do you
think of the snk lady fighter game there's an snk lady fighter game you just mentioned it yeah
no i announced a new switch fighting game it's going to be all their lady fighters i'd be down
for that because yeah i mean i pretty much play all the lady teams anyway in kof so it's fine
because my team is is my king and athena i love my mine's my favorite now we just need a doa
snk and what the hell we can get uh rumble roses in there as well just cross game why not uh you
know mud ring battle you could do snk versus capcom ladies edition all right we got to move
on for time i'm going to go to the next story and talk about uh that nintendo although they
are announcing all these uh new ports and likely to kind of fill in the calendar
when they get their big big stuff like metroid prime 4 and all that uh one thing they're not
going to be doing though anytime soon is 4k and virtual reality and you know what nintendo kind
of does their own thing and they're doing really well with it hardware can't push that so exactly
well uh the company uh was talking with a french publication les numeriques uh and uh the nintendo
france uh had uh kind of reiterated that you know they're just he doubts vr is viable in a
mainstream way and that consumers aren't going to want something that isn't a total package
and it's the same thing with 4k the company does not see it as widely adopted as it should be
for them to invest in it now keep in mind if i remember right nintendo was the last company
to come around on hd tvs too the um the weu was the first hd because the we regular was only for
was only 480p it did widescreen it didn't really do hd which is too bad like because you look at
like the we games that they have and i mean i understand like in emulators you can upscale that
stuff really well and it looks nice yeah and that's you know and kind of unfunny enough 4k
you know they have the weu version of zelda um that is upscaled to 4k if you have the system
that can run it and it looks nice yeah so it wouldn't be a terrible thing to do that but
yeah i understand there's not a lot of people are going to be paying for a system that's that
expensive to run those games they'll put out 4k system like when everybody's jumping to 8k or
something like that okay i need a special edition of this snk heroines game because you can get a
terry bokor hat that says fatal cutie oh i love that oh and that's great uh dark circle won't
you go to our next story pikachu oh it's a pokemon story sorry guys but pokemon is much
more than a mobile game right no well there is going to be as if anyone's surprised by this
a 2ds xl that is going to be wait why did i say 2ds it's a 3ds xl um that is uh did i read that
right it's a 2ds it's a 2ds okay i thought i was misreading that for a moment but they're doing
an all pikachu one is got a cute pikachu face on it and it's even got a puffy pikachu nose on it
and is pika it's so cute although it would be cuter if it was pichu but yeah it's supposed to
come out on january 26th for 159.99 although if they did an animal crossing one i would drop
everything and get that so what is animal crossing it's the best thing ever you you move into a
on the new one anyway you went to the village and suddenly like oh shit you're the mayor
and you have to make friends with all the animals and do fetch quests for them and grow trees and
sell stuff and make your town better i have a perfect village still and i haven't played in a
year it's like the sims but they're all cute animals it used to be based off of a good game
where they actually had it where you could buy nes how do you feel about it okay the nes games were
only in that one version on the gamecube right and we all and we all love that game best for
some reason i do anyway well i i i i owned all of those games so i didn't care i could just go play
them on my nintendo what's the game with like the music and everything like all the jumps have to do
the music elite beat agents i think about jumps have to do with the music elite beat agents no
it's like a critter and it goes along and there's all kinds of rock music and rock fan if you can
no it's like a thing if you can jump like you figure out the the music the beat you can jump
to all the beats that is bit trip runner i think you're wrong never mind i'm wrong she's thinking
of the one that uh yeah the chat berry will tell us the playstation game the one where it's uh
it's got beck music in it i don't remember what the hell it's called it's not vibrant
not vibrant no it's uh
it's fantastic and it like it's all has to do with the music and my six-year-old is amazing at this
game spice world no you're wrong it's not spice world sound shapes no you're okay never mind this
is another good answer from yyr the music levels in rayman rayman that's it ding ding ding a cookie
for yyr bingo yes my six-year-old could beat the whole game he's amazing at it and i love when he
plays it because i like the music i love music and video games so do we that's how the show
just started we were all ddr people playing dance dance revolution years ago are you serious i am
what what what ingress is to all of us now like ddr was for the three of us years ago it's totally
rayman and i will like i will listen to any video game they play it has good music we need to
introduce you to like bust a move and i know we need no we don't we need to have a coach snow day
it's ps1 era but it's so much fun the music in that game is top notch i can already bust a move
but but it makes my kids cringe but i can do it you've got music from like all kinds of genre
and different dancers in the game that represent like okay you do have the fetish girl um is there
ice ice baby no ice uh uh actually one of the ddr's on we i think did have that song
yes right it's so good for embarrassing your kids right let me if jamie's all done talking about
the pikachu ds which somehow led to rayman uh snow you're very good at tangents you fit in
you fit in really well here one of us i'm a goddamn squirrel same with us i still want
this fatal cutie hat look see so is she so you know birds of a feather all right loki what is
what's our next story in the you know who asked for this news hyperkin is bringing back the duke
controller what's a duke controller controller is the controller can house a small family that
was part of the original xbox system oh the one that could be used as you know yes to inflict
blunt force trauma yes somebody's trying to take my portal i could throw one of these at them
so yes um apparently you can get one of those they're gonna be coming soon you could use it as
so yeah um neat i guess it's gonna be priced for 69.99 and be compatible with the xbox one
in pc expensive not for controller nowadays don't talk while you're eating this
so yeah that's kind of interesting um although another thing though that they are putting out
that people might be more interested in is they're doing their own game boy so it's it
actually looks exactly like an original game boy or game boy color i guess um and yeah i guess it's
gonna play the game boy games and everything i mean practically looks identical it's kind of
like a retron but for game boy it's the hyperkin's emulation is kind of crap yeah i mean i don't know
i think the attendant might be a little bit upset about this considering that i would assume that
they're gonna put out a you know game boy mini or something like that at some point i'm just
irritated because um one of the one of the pages and magazines i used to subscribe to was mental
floss and they said look the next console the next thing that nintendo is releasing is this
and i'm like no it's not it's hyperkin and it's going to be crap because hyperkin's emulation
is flawed if if the graphics aren't messing up the music is messing up if the music's not messing up
then it has something to do like you'll get artifacting on the screen their emulation is
completely wretched and i would just wait for nintendo to do their thing or get a raspberry pie
but honestly i'm considering how hard it is to find their systems and i don't know i would you
i love seeing how this turns out they apparently though it even has like i mean you can an optional
backlight on there so you can turn the backlight on and off and even they said they're customizing
to basically also work with uh you know artists that use these for chiptunes so build the you
know what is chiptunes it's like making music out of like the retro um sound chips that are
in these systems so everything sounds like you know music that was on the system can you get
it on spotify probably they have some probably artists that are on spotify just checking um
anyways they're saying that they're trying to aim for a price point under a hundred dollars
and should be coming out probably relatively soon um is that worth a hundred dollars oh hell yeah
for playing gameboy games can't find original gameboy anymore it has a six hour battery and
unless you go to the thrift store and have good luck snow snow this is an example of a chiptune
from a real popular band wait we gotta wait for it to take it let me fast forward here where it
kicks in this is endless fantasy by adamanaguchi for those that know uh so basically i could play
anything
yeah but i would not pay a hundred bucks for it well it's it's more of just a system a lot
of making chiptunes a lot of these artists will modify carts and stuff to be able to
generate those tones and they'll so they can use the actual hardware that's in the systems
but it's more for people to want to play games like tetris because that's whatever we use
i never should have let my ex take my game boy here's what i'm thinking like i like games i
might have an extra i'll take it that's why they like to do these retro things for people that
lost them uh orange right in chat at live dot vog network.com says fun fact that new duke controller
actually plays the original xbox boot up when you click the center button that's kind of neat
i like that if you ever did you ever have an original xbox yeah yeah it plays well no anyway
all right let's move on let's talk about noises because i was really excited about i hate noises
you hate noises i have three kids well your kids are probably going to be very interested in this
and this is something that you might be able to play on that uh new 3ds and this is the trailer
this is pokemon yes but this is pokemon that you might like i don't know tim don't tell me
you confused this guy for me did you that's detective pikachu with the fans we're trying
to get are you saying you're to be voiced by danny devito they didn't get danny devito but
they got a guy that sounds like him we can do this partner i'm the brains and pikachu is wrong
rob they're doing a movie over here as well and guess who's voicing him here ryan reynolds oh
ryan reynolds i will i will he is the only deadpool in my heart oh my god he's the only
person in my heart i mean sorry barry barry white is still your husband you're sorry barry you're
the best all right so anyway i had to close it but they're also coming out with an amiibo
so that's a detective pikachu amiibo do you know what amiibo is is it a plush an amiibo no okay
i want you to go in that living room and look no yes no go in the living room and look to the right
in that shelf do what rob tells you trick no it is not a primatist okay all right the cage and
traps are i have i have just a couple of amiibo and i wanted to be able to look at the collection
are they are they like stuffed animals um they're not stuffed well some of them are but uh they're
like little figurines they're little like gi joe's you can tap them either your your 3ds or on
that's not that's a stuffed animal snow found a giant pikachu there okay but did you see the
amiibo collection in the shelf can i get a selfie with the you can take a picture with it here
here's a any anyway you can tap them on um either a wii u or a switch controller or on a 3ds system
and certain amiibo will have a effect in a game like we've just been using like all of these
zelda ones that we have in breath of the wild and getting like bows and special armor and stuff like
that um and or an animal crossing a happy home designer you can get them as your uh your clients
to design houses for so all right yeah and they yeah the car there's the car i don't collect the
cards but i like the figures so i just like the figures i don't even care about the unlock stuff
although people will come over and bring their switch and be like i need to unlock everything
in mario kart with your amiibo collection tap tap tap tap then they do so what i didn't see things
you didn't see the amiibos in the shelf you didn't see figurines okay here's the deal what am i
looking for a giant collection that is should be larger than any human should have jamie is going
to go to the next story while i take snow on a tour of the house okay okay so for the people who
are still playing gravity rush um too you should all be happy that the uh shutting down their
server was postponed because people fussed online the way stuff happens they were gonna close it on
january 18th they announced this back in september but because of people fussing about it it will be
up until july 18th at 10 p.m pacific time um but when the servers go down you will no longer be
able to view leaderboards or collect any special content or send challenges um but basically
sony listened to the fans so um and this was all from a uh it looks like a campaign that started
from a fan uh community called gravity rush central so there you go that's good they actually
have a following for that game it's it looks neat i tried i think i like the art style some of that
i i vaguely remember but it was i don't know it's a different game but the whole hashtag was
don't forget gravity rush i'm glad it worked and that they were able to kind of save that i think
that's really cool because they pulled that fast so they're threatening to pull it really fast so
well september was when it was announced so that's a few months but i mean the game had only been out
like a year or so i mean yeah yeah okay so that a quick update on introducing snow to amiibos so
finally i showed her what she's supposed to be looking at and the first words out of her mouth
were oh so they're skylanders i'm like yes they're just kinda oh my god we had some of those then
she's like what do they do and i'm trying to explain it to her and she goes oh so it's lego
dimensions i'm like yes it's that so she knows what they are she's we have so many lego dimensions
there you go that's it's that i love lego games see i only want the lego dimension stuff just for
like having the figures they're just so expensive i want to buy all of them no no here's the deal
you go to target because lots of targets will put them on discount yeah i know i here's the deal
i got all of my lego dimensions including the entire system when it was 75 no wait sorry target
70 off and there was a cartwheel so i got them at like 90 off yeah some of those sets were at
the 99 cent store for a while there's right so like i got all these things and i pretended to
my kids that they were super expensive and then now they play them that's my fear i can't bring
that home because my wife would get pissed right pretending pretending that something was expensive
is 90 of being a parent you're right i would know i only have a cat all right we gotta we're two
hours into the show and haven't even gotten to the break yet so i do and we have a we have a
kind of a big deal about to happen here on orange long trade open i'm not gonna give it away we're
gonna get there soon so loki you up next all right so let's talk a little bit about uh the xbox one
again so they're going to be getting an update um that's adding some things including uh mini hubs
and a way to basically put yourself in a do not disturb status so like if you're playing your
games and people keep messaging you to do stuff you'll totally ignore all that or i guess that'd
be kind of helpful if you're watching netflix or something like that um so that's cool and of
course you know uh the mini hubs i guess that's basically now you can access the games hub content
shared by other players in the world without leaving your own game so i don't know why you
would need to do that but it's a thing now so cool you have that that's neat um then of course there's
a little bit of a rumor that's talking about the new system as well that perhaps they're going to
be adding a new system for achievements so they're saying along with they're going to add new
achievement system called careers to sell to basically go alongside the current system and
this is more for like players that play a game for a long time so like not only do you get
achievements for playing you know games and you max that stuff out but you can also get stuff if
you're continually playing a game um so with that they're also going to have i guess you know uh
focus based on that i heard there's a rumor also that they're saying that they're possibly going
to have avatar loot crates what does that mean a loot crate is basically when you buy something
within so like pokemon go i guess if you were gonna you know say like that or even ingress
because they have in-game currency in that so you buy this in-game currency and you get a box and
it's random what's in the box there's a chance you'll get something good there's a chance you'll
get something that's kind of like those doggies not no not free but cryptocurrency but like more
of like um think of it like the box like it's random it's like you're gambling you might get
something like awesome like a very rare link amp or you might get like 10 bursters i am super not
i am not doing that i don't like blue boxes either but anyway so basically what they're saying though
i don't think you can necessarily purchase those you just get them when you rank up in this thing
so you get additional like customization for your avatars because they have a whole new avatar system
um neat but i just hope that they don't use this to exploit you know paid paid loot boxes because
they kind of did that with forza and it wasn't very good so okay you know what pisses me off
in pokemon go yeah when i pay yeah i'm gonna tell you anyway so suck it up so like if i pay for like
the incense and a creature shows up and then it runs away fuck you i paid for that like why you
paid for the chance yeah no no i paid for the creature to show up it better not run away
that pisses me off it's like the raid pass you pay for the rate pass and you don't even catch the
stupid pokemon it runs away i have never done that that's right because you you said your your area
is too remote you don't get to do the raids no i do raids i just can't get legend oh i can't get
legendaries yeah no i can do raids but i can spin a ball like a motherfucker so like i always catch
the pokemon but like i get more creatures running away when i do incense than i do regular so i
don't even use it it's always the shitty creatures too like pikachu like no it's a goddamn pidgey
and the pidgey runs away like what the fuck i paid for you pidgey get in get in the ball
maybe one way you can help maybe one way you'll be able to find some people for uh these pokemon go
raids is through something that niantic rolled out this week i thought this would be a nice
bookend the ingress conversation uh niantic announced this week uh a community day for
pokemon go uh this is not going to be like their chicago event that was a total meltdown
they got a hundred dollars worth of pokey coins please make it like the chicago event
uh but what happened is on their blog they announced that january 20th would be the first
pokemon go community day where they're calling on players to meet up at local parks and landmarks to
meet up with people basically they want to capture the magic when the game first rolled out so they're
encouraging hey everybody meet up here at this place in time and to encourage you to go out
you will be able to catch loki's favorite a special pikachu this pikachu will know surf and
that's a special move that i don't know if it actually surfs or what it does that's a new move
apparently it does uh oh that's pretty rad though um so then also i guess uh increased xp or stardust
lure modules uh so anyway the whole thing is going to be from and these are that can vary depending
on the event uh the americas will see this event from 11 a.m to 2 p.m pacific time on the 20th so
uh we'll be out there with ingress flyers recruiting i'm just kidding although actually
it's not a bad idea i know yeah we were talking about if you play ingress please bump the park
if we're down at capital park it's not going to be that high in your park wouldn't you like your
eight there you go go to pioneer park and get your your people to by the way i'm safe i just
opened pokemon because you said that it says it's extreme weather conditions but i'm pretty sure
it's extreme cloud hazardous weather alert because it is too clear it's too clear outside it's an
extreme warning about wednesday's rain all right yeah exactly anyway one more thing about pokemon
go and this is a little bit controversial uh they are dropping support for older ios devices
so if you are unable to upgrade your phone to ios 11 you will not be able to continue to play
pokemon go note i'm not saying you have to have ios wait a minute phone it's just that i iphone
5s and prior will no longer work aren't they getting a lawsuit about not updating those old
phones that's the whole battery thing that came out it's not really related to pokemon go but
that was just that's just another thing that i guess i could say as a whole apple's trying to
work through right now and they put out a statement there are three pokemon in your driveway
yeah you know i get a lot of pokemon that spawn here it's it's exciting
jamie's instantly picking up her phone and trying to catch the boogaloo um i know this is not a
popular one not opening it by the niantic developers however it's not unheard of in the
gaming world um you know when they release new world of warcraft expansions although they try
to get as many games as possible to work they will say you know if you're not above a certain
benchmark the game's no longer going to work and i mean with consoles i think we kind of see that
inherently is like they stop making games at some point for the xbox 360 and you kind of have to
have an xbox one so this isn't but it's just i think this is weird for people because we haven't
seen this as much in the phone world so we're seeing it all the time in the world can we talk
about things we hate about pokemon go and it's not like a graphically intensive game it's
graphically intense it overheats my phone well that's because there it doesn't have to i don't
think it's so much the graphic side of it is it is the you know the internet and the memory usage
because you know it's the memory usage it's the it's really is the memory usage because there's
a lot of stuff going on under the hood i want to talk about creatures we hate and i won't even
catch fuck them all right no we got to move on i will not catch another one of those stupid
parasite things we got to move on because we're going to get to another segment here at olr we're
finally to the end of the first half and no it is it's time dark soccer i don't want to do it but i
promise it's time for the classic game of the week i just want to point out you all are here tonight
and you're not going to understand this but you guys you guys are witnessing history tonight okay
this is the classic game of wait no i swore i would never do this one but as i said last week my
my stepfather died on christmas eve and my mother doesn't have a job so i started to go fund me
to help my mother get her next couple of months of rent together so that she could afford to live
and i've taken over two of her bills so she could afford to live until she can get a job she won't
be able to collect any of my stepdad's pension until she turns 60 my mom's 59 so um that's
till november so i i put it out there that um if you know the listeners contributed 100 bucks a piece
you know and i get to 500 that's another month of rent for my month it's in alabama so it's cheap
another month of rent for my for my mom that i would swallow my pride and do halo as the
classic game in this community this is a call to you res and enlightened i'm i will give the the
the link on gofundme is i'll give it in a second but it's it's called michael mom but i'll i'll
put the link up um so yeah i'm doing halo the classic game of the week this week is
halo no really it's halo she picked halo because she's making good on a promise to all of you
that she would do halo well first i've got before you get into your usual segment because you're
going to treat this like any other game i am but um even though it sucks stop it but i just want
to say like personally though like i and you know i told you this last week i said jamie you know
what we're probably not going to get that kind of money from the listeners you might want to just
lower the expectations and all this stuff but like you all came through like you really did
and i'm just i am like so humbled that this show like and the people that listen to it like did
that i am i'm i'm like i almost i kind of i kind of had an ugly cry we're gonna put it in we'll
put it in our community and i will send the link to the res community as well thank you my goal
on the gofundme is 7 500 which would take care of my mom for a while she and i don't say this
she lives in a barn a literal barn does she leave the door open huh does she leave the door open
no no no because where you're born in a barn is a thing in my house but she she she lives in um
a little apartment is built into a former barn that's the storage building for the people in the
property and it's a really pretty property but my mom doesn't have a lot of money and a lot of
resources and certainly not any of the wonderful programs we have here in california that help
people because they voted for fucking republicans sorry anyway anyway so to dial it back let's
let's not um let's not okay i will so the game tell us about the classic game of the week halo
it is halo combat evolved um there actually something about halo is that when um my husband
had his bachelorette party it was basically just a bunch of people with a bunch of x-boxes all
hooked up on land playing halo that was his bachelor party we watched zanadu and barbarella
and rob was there and we went to a goth club that was my bachelorette party and it was fun anyway
um halo came out in 2001 it is a military themed sci-fi first-person shooter that was developed by
bungee and published by microsoft game studios um it is the first it is a franchise launcher and it
was the killer app for the xbox um come out on november 15 2001 it has sold more than 5 million
copies worldwide by 2005 um they've even done windows versions mac versions um a series of
novels comic books a live action web series and of course they're the spawned the one thing about
halo that i like red versus blue because red versus blue was fucking hilarious anyway um
it uh it has had a high death remake in halo combat evolved anniversary it came on xbox 360
and it was re-released as halo the master chief collection on november 11th 2014 for the xbox one
um it is set in the 26th century and you play as the master chief who has from what i understand
his whole thing that made him awesome has since been retconned now that bungee is no longer
in the picture rip um so he has an ai that that lives in his his suit or his brain or something
called cortana that microsoft has also adopted a cortana into their own little personal version
of siri which is not nearly as good as siri um you know for windows systems and you know
windows phones right um a lot of people have put it up there as one of their favorite games ever
and it is considered by ign to be the fourth best first person shooter ever made and if
if quake isn't the first one then i'll cry um and yeah there was a lot of machinima that came out
a lot of stuff that was supported by bungee and microsoft you know red versus blue being the big
one um so basically you've got like energy shields and you can drive tanks you can do a whole bunch
of shit that you're not supposed to in the game like super jumping using using your tank to get
to places that you're not supposed to go because that's all the stuff that i like um you know your
shields will recharge but you have to fight these like enemies called the covenant and they are
these different aliens that are bound together with some religion and you have to basically
fight you know what's the other one called the flood these insect creatures um but you're on this
world that is a quite literal ring and you're on the inside of this world um of the ring and
this i thought it was a really neat game graphically i wanted to like it
didn't like it sorry i suck at first person shooters especially like the nintendo 64 era
up through the xbox severe motion sickness motion sickness but um
but i mean you play you know your master chief who's named john i think um and you have cortana
and you've got you know the captain of the game you have like other people and there's
wasn't there a character who um crap who was it that they got someone to do his likeness
and then he came back in halo 5 i don't remember my husband pointed it out to me and i don't
remember um but i mean basically you are over on um on this planet for some reason i'm trying
to get to where the actual plot is because i don't know who cares about the plot kill everything
shoot it down did it move shoot it yeah basically you're trying to i guess take control of the halo
and figure out what its purpose is and so you go all over and shoot shit and then things are done
that's it all right that's it okay shooting all right but no wait there's more all right um it
did go through a pretty decent uh development cycle and they were actually going to in 1999
it was actually announced um at the mac world conference that halo was going to be released on
classic mac os and windows simultaneously um but there was a big uh non-disclosure agreement
that you know prevented anyone from really talking about it but it was shown um at a
private showing at e3 1999 and people like yay this is great um and then uh the first trailer
came out at e3 2000 and then you know basically from there it evolved um the soundtrack but i'm
combat evolving great i is not intentional um but it does have a really amazing soundtrack
i will give you that i mean the soundtrack for halo is something that i can listen to for a while
but i mean it had pretty great scores across the board it was well received and of course now we've
got so many other versions of it you know that have you know been released since then you know
like i said this was a franchise starter um and then of course um for machinima you had
red versus blue that came out um you had uh you know different you know types of mods that came
out for for the pc you have uh there were the novels that came out there was a prequel novel
other novels that came out one about the flood um comics all kinds of stuff that came out
in fact marvel did a uh a halo graphic novel that came out they also remade the game
and like i said it's had multiple re-releases so there you go are you happy yes yes
halo is classic game of the week i've watched my kid play a lot of halo it really happened
episode 714 halo really knows like my kids can play halo it's one of the games i'll let them play
yeah no even the six and eight-year-old they can play it hey rob well they're not having sex
chupa thingy so like it's okay chupa thingy chupa thingy what about chupa thingy it's got a ring to
it all right um but but um i know that some people wanted me to stream it so um as soon as i figure
out how to get that done i might make another incentive we may well i know you probably want
to do it for your own channel but you could always come over and we can stream we might have to fudge
it a little bit and do like the halo uh anniversary collection on xbox one i think people will still
be satisfied with the result we'll have you but i might make it another incentive and by the way
that 500 came from four people so the last donation was 200 and i i mean yyr was one of
our people we had a few other people who were in chat who said i didn't have to say their names but
you know all of you who donated to help my mom out i talked to her this morning and she was
elated so um oh yeah i was gonna get the link again make up time real quick that's right
somebody posted in chat somebody beat you to it and posted in chat why we already posted in chat
so okay thank you um but i wanted to say it aloud for people who are not in chat when they're
listening to this fair enough i i just pulled it up because i had sent it to snow i think it is uh
gofundme.com slash mmm now that oh go slash michael dash mom yeah michael dash mom not
michael's mom michael dash mom yeah because michael was the guy oh my gosh so you guys are
amazing thank you so much for helping my mom out i really appreciate it so yeah i even i like when
i heard about like all those donations i i almost cried and this isn't even my family but it is my
family you know i i heart jamie so and just as a side note i did donate to uh awesome games done
quick in the name of olr oh that's awesome what i could most of my side money is going to mom sure
sure i did do a quick a quick donation during the zelda run you know i was gonna bring it up when
we come back from the break but shit this segment's running long enough let's do it now i just wanted
to you know tip my hat for awesome games done quick because i know a lot of our million a lot
of our listeners are really into it and even i watch some of it too and i it's a good time and
it's a great like with all this bullshit about like swatters and you know people that ruin games
for other people and all these bad news i love these good news gamer stories and this is this
is a great one so thank you to everybody involved with awesome games drunk quick the speedrunners
people who donated people who went everybody who makes that a success yeah i can't afford 100 bucks
but i just donated 40 thank you any even five dollars it doesn't matter every little bit adds
up and it helps mom she's getting now that she has it set up she's just says i check my mail
and my bank has money in it and so she's been really happy minutes she's gonna have to play
halo so thank you all right girl and we've shared it to uh a our local community and also to a
community that is uh statewide thank you guys now i'm gonna go cry and i'm wearing a lot of makeup
all right so this may be the longest first half of the show ever sorry no it's fine i love it
two hours and 20 minutes and we're finally gonna take a break believe it or not there's more when
we come luckily it's a three-day weekend at least it's for me with martin luther king day tomorrow
i work for the state yeah so you definitely have the day off but also a tip of the hat it's my
birthday it's my birthday holiday it is that too but also to acknowledge martin luther king jr
and you know the reason why we have the day off tomorrow but uh we do have more show to uh go
when we come back uh we're gonna do some rapid fire news cover some releases and might even
get to your phone calls at orange lounge radio on skype now we're gonna find out if no we take
phone calls yeah we do oh hey you guys can you please text barry the number uh orange lounge
radio all one word on skype and who knows it's not a text number anybody can call we might this
might be the chance we hear from the opposition we'll see uh jim was saying i think we should
put this in calm i don't think that's a good idea no we're doing it we're doing it yeah we're doing
it oh yeah talk to her yeah i don't think it's good yeah all right all right all one word on
skype uh we're gonna come back uh after a quick break with more of the show bye
welcome back everybody to orange lounge radio live with episode number 714 already in progress for
this excuse me january the 14th of 2018 rob roberts here with you in studio with dark
sakura as well as loki so our guests tonight the uh lovely ladies here that play ingress locally
this is really funny so um the nearby portal not too far from here they had uh put their resonators
on it on their way in and uh it started getting attacked during the break so they actually ran out
there to go talk to the people that were attacking it and i don't know what they're doing out there
but they're uh they're out there playing the game right now um i think it's probably also going to
really kind of throw our competition for a loop like why are all these heavy hitters at rob's
place right now so uh it'll be fun to see what that's about but if they knew that i was
broadcasting then they probably thought oh they're all distracted right now let's go put blue over him
so we'll see what happens with that so that's actually what they're out doing right now is
having fun with that but we still have plenty more news to cover and i'm sure we'll hear all about
whatever's happening outside right now as they're they're actually playing the game right now but we
have some rapid fire news to get to uh let's get to loki all right so let's talk about games that
are going to be coming out pretty soon on steam and these are kind of cool because i've actually
played a few of these on my phone so space invaders extreme and groove coaster are going
to be heading to steam um so space invaders extreme is going to be coming to steam in february
and then groove coaster uh they don't have a date yet when that's coming out sometime in spring
though but two really good kind of music hybrid games uh or arcade kind of even arcade-y type
games coming to steam so i definitely will have to check those out when they come out because i did
like those um and then hopefully this makes this game even better and i still haven't gone back
since they've done all the updates but um no man's sky of course you know game it took a while to
kind of get back to the hype that they were you know how they were showing the game in 2013
well still not quite there but you know thanks to uh modders that may be not the case pretty soon so
there's um a mod out there called ray rods overhaul um it's a no man's sky mod that's supposed
to turn the game into something that appears to resemble what they showed at on the e3 2013 show
when they're i think it was the e3 i think maybe the game's um awards i don't remember when they
first debuted that but they have um an early version of it available now to download so you
can go check that out on moddb and there's basically a lot of interesting stuff they're
doing so new ecology and terrain more colors more random events more dynamic weather and they're
said right now though of course being that it's still very early um there's still some bugs in
there to work out um so they're still doing that it's only one guy putting it together so it might
take a while but at least it's kind of you know nice to see a little bit more variety in some of
the plans it creates so if you're interested in checking out like i said go to moddb to find that
mod sweet so i am very much looking forward to uh the the not to backtrack too much but i'm very
much looking forward to the space invader stuff that's coming out on steam yes i just didn't get
that out there because i'm texting the gals since they're playing chris um but uh yeah i really want
to check out because um i mean i love the game on on psp and i think express 360 and i just i think
it'll be fun to have on pc as well so because you know i love to buy games on multiple systems
and then um what was i gonna say um because i don't see this as part of the show role the
other thing i wanted to mention though um along with that um oh no it was actually part of it i
just forgot to mention it so aside from space invaders and um groove coaster there's another
game coming final fantasy 12 is going to be coming out on steam as well so definitely you know check
that out so uh pretty cool the zodiac age and that's coming out february 1st on pc and they
said that that version of the game will run at 60 fps include a new game plus a new game minus mode
the fuck's new game minus um i think that's something about like you don't level at all
because you can get through that game i think being at level one but it's hard huh yeah okay so
very cool lots of cool games coming out in the next few weeks yep all right let's get to uh
speaking of games coming out soon this is like a re-release i guess you could call it of final
fantasy 15. final fantasy 15 is getting a royal edition uh final fantasy 15 has been already rated
t and it's leaked via the esrb uh perhaps this is an unannounced collector's edition with the
base game and dlc episodes as the game has uh expanded into these different uh gladius and
prompto and ingus all have their uh ignis excuse me all have their little uh uh extra episodes that
are in the game so uh yeah they're probably doing like a okay now the game is finished collection i
think is what's going on there so uh yeah that's uh something to look forward to um maybe like a
summer e3 release i don't know that's a question mark it could be any time really during the year
so um we'll see what comes to that uh also um even though my link for this isn't working so
i'll just try to do this from memory loki you might have to help me out but i know assassin's
creed rogue got announced for a remaster and that's going to be coming to playstation 4 and
xbox one the one thing i don't have in front of me is is there a date for that i don't know i didn't
post that yeah and i'm not sure about that um so maybe somebody in chat over at live.vognetwork.com
knows the answer to that i don't think we had a date yet but it has been announced that those
games are getting remastered and that'll be exciting for uh people obviously the uh graphics
and assassin's creed have come a long way and that's what we're seeing in the xbox one and
playstation 4 versions right now so meanwhile let's move over to dark sakura well there is
going to be a star wars multiplayer shooter that's coming out on mobile phones uh star wars rivals
has already had a soft launch in australia and new zealand um but it will be out for ios and
google play um it's a little bit more on the overwatch side of gameplay but you can buy
something for 100 bucks in the game but it ain't darth vader you get him from the get-go
assassin's creed remastered our rogue remasters march 20th thank you and oh you had to give me
this um stephen spielberg is still working on a halo tv series and it hasn't progressed any
i gave that tour before i knew what the classic game of the week was going to be by the way because
i thought oh i'll work it in somehow i did that for y'all still in development nothing new
it's still happening eventually maybe allegedly all right our uh anger scouts haven't come back
from their portal battle yet i hope the uh opposition didn't kill them while they're out
there so we'll see i do want to take this on a small tangent since you're talking about tv
series did you guys see animaniacs is coming back yes i did the first seasons are on hulu and same
thing with the tiny tunes right yeah i heard though they might not have the same voice actors
i thought one of the voice actors tweeted or something that they weren't a part of it i i i
i'm going off memory and i don't have anything in front of me i thought i saw something on twitter
which obviously makes it true it was on twitter uh about that so um based on my uh my
coms stuff they're still battling the portal still still great all right well uh moving on
uh let's get to some release dates we're going to travel around the world and check out what
is coming out uh in a country near you uh we'll start with the us yes there's not a whole ton of
stuff coming out in january but there's a few things so starting off we have a game called
inner space that's coming out on windows mac the antenna switch playstation 4 and xbox one i don't
think this has anything to do with the old uh sci-fi movie about shrinking down to someone's
body um curveball space program enhanced edition coming out on playstation 4 and xbox one uh one
notable game that is coming out this week as well street fighter 5 arcade edition on pc and
playstation 4 and then we also have a game called a gintama rumble that's on playstation 4 world to
the west that's on nintendo switch and last but not least um a few more here death mark which is
for the switch and playstation 4 digimon story cyber sleuth hackers memory on playstation 4
nvita and finally on 3ds kirby battle royale traveling over to japan a lot of the same stuff
you just heard here in the us usually it's a little different but in japan on the playstation
4 this week in tama rumble is out there as well uh we also have street fighter 5 gets the arcade
edition in japan as well so that game is getting kind of a second chance i think with a lot of
people a lot more characters there with all the included stuff uh sheen is coming out in japan in
a regular and limited edition as well and a price reduction on senju novakiri a remaster
so that is something else to look forward to uh looking at the other consoles in japan real quick
i know sometimes the vita still gets releases in japan and we do have that gintama rumble is in a
regular and av edition on the vita this week as well they also have a game releasing on the vita
called ephemeral fantasy on dark that is also releasing in japan this week on the vita because
they still love the vita in japan even though it kind of disappeared and fumbled here it was
all right i wish they'd do it in console though i know uh this is kind of a big deal for japan
because we've had this game for a few months but this week japan is finally getting and it's the
lone release on the switch this week mario and rabbit's kingdom battle is making its way to japan
this week i didn't have that yet yeah i was surprised they didn't get that either but
considering that was a game developed over here i can see why maybe it's uh taking a little bit
of time and uh that's it no 3ds releases in japan this week uh nothing until uh actually it's it's
pretty empty honestly until we get to like february so 3ds slowing down a little bit in japan
in the meantime though we do have the uk on the 15th we have street fighter 5 arcade edition for
pc on the 16th we have beholder for ps4 and interspace for switch ps4 and xbox one on the
17th we have the vanishing of ethan carter for xbox one and on the 19th beholder for xbox one
of course the thing i care about is january 26th so coming soon dragon ball fighter z i know i know
all the hype is leading up to this moment and apparently the hype is worth it when they can
connect to the game yes in the beta all right beta uh go into our chat over at live dot vog
network dot com panda and chat agrees i wish they made more games for the vita yeah i mean
you can get some from japan and import them but yeah here uh they they just kind of they got they
slowly got rid of the uh playstation television they slowly kind of phased that whole thing out so
it's a problem with sony over there uh let's see also in chat at live dot vog network dot com um
oh rama says original voice actors for animaniacs were confirmed by rob paulson my mistake sorry
about that and that's regarding the animaniacs uh reboot over there so that's great all right
uh moving on let's get to uh the mailbag all two of them all right we get some emails from
you guys over at participate at orange lounge radio.com is the place to send your emails
i stole this nasty coffee i don't know why dear lord i think this formatted so badly
uh oh um actually never mind this isn't a real email oh spammy spam spam spam spam
spam yeah we don't need to excite our listeners you like them bored sorry was that the spam is
about exciting the listeners yeah it's already deleted i want to see that i want to see what
they're selling um i'm gonna go in there and look get to the other email whatever okay let me go
back hi yyr um hello lr on last week's show you mentioned the discontinuation of connect adapter
for xbox one i apologize for the length of this email but i need to express how disappointed i
am in microsoft for how they've minimized connect and their early adopters who still make use of it
some context i bought my xbox one on launch day and started using the connect voice commands
almost immediately at first they seemed silly but soon i was using them constantly to switch to
other apps or games to control my tv navigate streaming apps and more i only need needed to
pick up a controller if i wanted to play a game my voice could do everything else the most amazing
of these voice commands was xbox select this command assigned a number to every selectable
element on the screen you could then say item one item two etc to select any of those things
the awesome thing about this command was that you could use it almost anywhere from system settings
to browsing the store to browsing netflix or other streaming services you could do it all with just
your voice well you could for three years but just this past fall with no warning and no
explanation microsoft pushed a system update that disabled the xbox select command and all third
party apps it wasn't replaced it wasn't updated it was simply disabled the functionality totally
removed for seemingly no reason at all now navigating streaming apps is no longer possible
without a controller this is a slap in the face to the folks who came to love this technology
especially disabled gamers who had become accustomed to easy functional voice navigation
now we've just witnessed the discontinuation of the xbox one connect adapter but here's
something you may have missed the connect adapters have not been available for microsoft online store
since before the xbox one x came out this means that early adopters of the xbox one are now being
punished for also being early adopters of the one x because they never had
a chance to buy an adapter at all as an original xbox one owner who was considering upgrading to
an x i am now faced with the prospect of having to ditch what connect functionality i still have
or the prospect of never being able to upgrade to an s or x for a company that has embraced
backwards compatibility with software dating back two generations this seems awfully backwards in
a different way how is how is it that amazon apple and other others are expanding their
voice recognition technologies well microsoft seems bent on rolling theirs back all right
rant over back to testing super multitasking i guess thanks for listening erin yyr all right
i forgot to mention i played super multitasking this week as well that was something i played
still hard even with controller but yeah i totally agree this is kind of fucked up
so um i mean this is actually seems like they would have to either have something built into
the system for voice recognition or i don't know but i would expect there to be a slew
of complaints directed at microsoft for getting rid of you know voice recognition i mean
you've got players who and like i said that are disabled there are people who have poor vision
who use the console who might rely on their voice recognition to get them to
the game you know things like that i i totally agree yeah i mean this is it kind of ties into
the whole uh thing we were talking about just a minute ago with like sony has abandoned the
playstation vita right and so now microsoft has kind of like abandoned connect you know in a way
although not in japan with the vita but i guess with the connect it was never an issue in japan
but it's it sucks for the early adopters it really does you're you're a follow-up i was
gonna say um you can use the headset with a microphone for um voice control as well
but um the only exception is um hey cortana you know xbox on only works with the connect
so that's the only thing you can't do with the you know without the connectors turn the system on
well that's kind of helpful to have the machine on don't you think
isn't it always on sucking up your brain it's always listening it's always on you know
downloading those updates for quantum theory that all right so that's it for emails this week
all right sounds good all right we're gonna uh get back here so um snow is walking back into
the studio except she decided to bring mr smoosh with her because you loved a kitty don't you snow
a kitty don't you snow so okay so tell me what happened just now so you guys have been out so
obviously we're talking about ingress earlier in the show and clearly something is happening
because i'm going to our chat room over at live.vog network.com and i'm getting messages
on my phone right now they're saying and it's it's from somebody claiming to be and i don't know if
it is or not somebody must have gave her the link it's gonna be claiming to be pepper it is pepper
okay i almost said the full name but i don't know if i should say people's agent no it's her
is her agent name that's okay okay so uh but i got i got the message when am i flipping to blue
you're not you're not flipping needs to flip the green there you go that's what i'm saying i'm
saying come to the fun team she wants community we told her you had to come to green over and over
again all right we'll see repeatedly cross our fingers at least so i think repeatedly at least
once think they kind of have i don't know how much i should say i think there's kind of reasons they
went blue in the first place like relations and all that stuff family okay so how's your knee
what i told i did it no no we were we were running back to your house and i wore my converse because
did i expect to run no yes did i expect to run on mud no so i was running and then i it was really
funny and i fell all the way down and my shoes smell like some sort of mud so i left yeah that
park that park you're not going to find anything over that park besides mud and marijuana she got
up quicker than i could get my camera or there's someone close by girls are always there really
good weed it's all legal now oh not for teenagers not for teenagers no well 18 year old it's not
so there it is but you got up too fast i couldn't get my my you were laughing so hard laughing
really hard i got to get my like i couldn't concentrate to get my phone camera out that's
really funny i said jen run back to rob's and she's like can't run now here's my question did
they know you guys were all here no not like no they definitely did she said there are people
there were people on this portal oh right yeah yeah so it's because we dropped on on in what did
i tell you ingress makes people paranoid it does us it's the other team too so it's both yeah also
we're still on that portal you know i also got a new cap so thank you we're we're also allowed
to be friends outside of the game absolutely we'll just be sipping tea absolutely testing
happens what is there tea that i wasn't informed of you yeah what is tea that's what no i don't
want tea i don't like it what the hell is that what the hell is that i like tea i like tea oh
my god kids do this all the time why didn't i get this why didn't you give me tea and to do
okay fair i never get that you want some tea how come he gets to play that game and i don't
oh i just was curious because maybe i offered maybe i will take you up on that offer to switch
to blue where's the application oh snow just totally pantsed rob because she's been drinking
and if we don't have a camera so yeah again you didn't give me we're not on air we're online god
this is why the show is not video that's for sure i saw you buy berry once and i accidentally
no because underwear the the only blue i've got on right now is protecting you
what do you mean protecting yeah what if i want it what if i want it
omg what is happening here in this studio right now all right where's allen anyway so did you
guys have fun back there i saw him did you keep it clean out there no yes three why are you playing
grand theft auto wait define oh i just got that for my kid against my better judgment
what i sure did oh my god you have to punch a hooker to get your money back he doesn't he
assures me he's not punched any hookers yes i'm sure he hasn't i don't know man i don't know
apparently there's a clean version no no no no there's not so he's lying to me then yes if
you're listening i know you're lying to me now you are no longer playing grand auto if there is
i sure as hell i've never heard of it maybe there's a mod or something but i guess there was
he said there was something where there weren't any hookers i know okay he's okay so he's he's
doing what kids do and he's kind of like explaining the truth so the original version of grand theft
auto had like a scene that you could hack that was called the hot coffee scene that was basically
where you would end up having sex with a hooker oh my god but the esrb kind of found out about that
so they had to remove it from future copies of the game so is it the cleaner version sure because
they took that one scene out that you couldn't even access anyway without hacks but is the game
all so did so if you go back to him and you go why'd you lie to me a little shithead technique
shithead i call him that i didn't lie i didn't technically he didn't technically think grand
thought online i'm not sure if they have hookers and grand thought online i know the strippers have
uh bikinis on online whereas offline they don't have bikinis i'm pretty sure he's playing online
okay did anybody ever play leisure suit larry in the land of the lounge of course of course thank
you when i started the whole goal of the game is to have sex to the hooker yeah well in grand
theft auto there's like you can run into hookers with your car like that's a whole thing wait a
minute that's just in the game yes because i've done that in real life no you have it for the
record she has not done this i didn't say i hit them i said i ran into them but yeah no he started
playing that game in the last couple weeks i uh i apparently well i went out to on fat on black
friday and not knowing all of his games i just so racist in front of what black friday black
friday when you get all the deals racist no snow omg i'm gonna take that mic away yes please do
anyway i stood in front of the like you know deals at the of the video games at walmart and i just
bought every game that i thought he might not have that you went to walmart listen it's in my town
and so we um he actually did really well he only didn't have he only had one of the games that i
bought him so we exchanged that one for grand theft auto and again against my better judgment
i don't know i just let him do whatever he wants at least you sort of let him have an economic
lesson with that right i i'll put this up when i was a kid i've watched every movie i wasn't
supposed to see as a kid sure i played all of the things i wasn't supposed to play as a kid
and i listened to everything i wasn't supposed to listen to how many hookers have you run over
i've not run over a single hooker yet i ran over a squirrel once and that was sad but that
was probably i don't know rob you were there with me i was what you were wait what movies did you
watch like well okay my mom's last week my mom was forbidden to watch my mom took me to see star
wars when i was nine months old i've seen the exorcist three or every bit right i actually do
remember looking through the um the little glass door in the theater in the 70s
so i have the vague like i mentioned something my mom she's like you were nine months old wow
so um but i've seen yours about what i did i saw krull in the theater i've seen gremlins in the
theater i saw indiana jones i saw i think the exorcist three in the theater um what else i see
i've seen all the poltergeist movies in the theater which the for the first poltergeist
was my favorite movie as a kid okay so fact my dad okay so my grandfather was dying and my mom
went to san francisco my dad was watching us and he took us to the video store because you know he
didn't want to actually watch us so we rented a bunch of videos and there was this movie i had
been wanting to see forever and it had a black panther on the front of it it was called cat people
right that was the one with the with the the mom yeah and the cat people so my dad let us
happen to my show my dad talking about old shit and it was okay so in the movie the people had
sex and then they turned into black panthers had to kill someone and when they killed someone they
turned back into people so after that my mother found out we watched it and she didn't let my
own father watch us again so we had to have a babysitter that's a fact and marvel cinematic
universe is getting really weird i already watched it no but i mean it's just the thing you know and
then i've had friends who grew up so sheltered that they didn't know how to deal with anything
as adults yeah and i'm definitely not raising him as shelter like i wasn't i didn't have tv
until i was 10 but you had it young enough i mean i've i've got some people who are actually
still going through therapy because of really controlling parents i'm like we never even i
never my parents still have never had cable i didn't have a cable till i was in college
i feel like we need cable now vog psychiatry coming to you soon fridays on the network welcome
to vogcology all right uh we're gonna move on with the show though because obviously we're
running a little late now would be the time we're wrapping up we still got some news to come over
this is what happens when you have us over are you still good you guys still good to hang out
for a little bit yeah good as long as we patch up snow's knee yeah and you guys might have to run
out if uh the other folks listening decide to you know do something you come back and kill the park
we're going back out all right yeah you hear us you hear barefoot if i have to you know what's up
all right moving on though let's uh let's go on to uh some other news some other gaming news we
got to get to and then we're gonna get to you uh your calls here a little bit later on the show
all one word on skype but not yet we asked us anything to get to
loki no be quiet first off let's talk about vr because the ces was this week so they had lots
of new things to show off um one of the things of course that was coming out of everything um
actually not really from ces but with interview from um nikay basically saying that you know the
playstation vr library is expected to double in 2018 so from one game to two games no no they're
actually saying that the that it's going to go from about 150 to 280 games on the platform
that's not double it's almost double math is hard i know but technically i guess right now 150 games
there's a tendency to exaggerate things in gaming uh you know especially when like selling things
and marketing things uh just look at the ramp up for the game no man's sky there was a lot
of exaggerations there just like jen's kid is giving her exaggerations about how clean
to say that most of those games coming out are good because a lot of them are terrible but
there are some pretty good games on playstation vr um so yeah i'm looking forward to that you know
hopefully they don't release new hardware anytime soon although i have a feeling they're gonna do
something like that um and then of course you know speaking of hardware um htc announced that
they've got a new vive coming so this is the vive pro which has got a higher resolution screen in
it and then they also had a wireless adapter to go along with that so you can also take that and
make it wireless which is pretty awesome all along with the improved screen the vy pro is also going
to have a built-in headphones and their own dedicated amp dual mics and they even redesigned
the head strap and it looks blue it's fancy so um that looks awesome i definitely want to check that
out i still haven't picked up a pc vr headset yet but that doesn't look like a bad option i still
don't have a playstation vr and i kind of want to like i'm ready to adopt some sort of vr but it's
just honestly like and don't do it resist now that most of the uh uh ingress gals are seeing my house
for the first time tonight uh i don't need any more shit in this house is that correct you need
some tv trays yes i do need more tv trays i'm not used to having you also need a maid this show is
yes i definitely need a maid everybody needs a baby show is usually like three people four
people tops and tonight we have one two three four five six i was planning on seven so no one
really wants a tv tray to hold her drink i know it's a which by the way i have a tv tray to hold
my drink can i beg about can we talk about just real quick just uh you know here's a little here's
a little fun fact since uh now i know some members of the other team are listening here's a little
fun fact about sacramento enl so so um somebody decided to bring boxed wine no it's a box no it
was a box it was a boxed wine i i decided no it wasn't target wine it came from target target
why it was from walmart she just went there she said no i didn't go to walmart for the wine i
went to target for the wine excuse me excuse me okay so anyway so the important part is is that
you know i i get asked oh do you have a glass that i can put the wine in i'm sure i'm like sure i
have up here here's a wine glass no no no i said do you have a clean glass you know you said a
clean glass i give you a wine glass because that is what wine glasses for is wine no and then she
said oh i want that here a mason jar it's really hard to drink wine out of mason jars no it's not
you can't knock a mason jar over like now they are all drinking wine out of mason jars all did
tori drink you had wine too we're out of wine yeah i know that i'm really mad that's unfortunate but
i bought i've only brought two bottles you want to know what's sitting in my fridge though right
now that's a crime that i can't better be wine well yeah i have wine in my fridge too but i have
a bottle of my favorite milk stout because i'm a beer person what is milk stuff i feel like i
need to try this i don't it's it's it's a stout i mean like a beer like like a guinness's but
it doesn't have the same bitterness the the lactic acid in it makes it a smoother flavor so it's not
that sharp like it's very but it's it's fermented out of it so it's like gassy beer snow be quiet
no okay sorry it's not it's not quite like that but it's it's very smooth i mean it's it's
definitely got the the heft of a stout but um there is a brewery called belching beaver brewery
and they make it oh my god you know it peanut butter milk stuff i have tori is something
tori set off over here the peanut butter milk stout is my favorite but i have their plain
milk stout in my fridge which i also super like and i cannot drink it for another six months
i probably won't even be able to finish it and that makes me very sad it's sitting in
there taunting me like drink the beer i'll take your beer okay i i just want a little bit of it
i miss i miss my beer okay so we got from virtual reality to uh beer alcohol problems alcohol is
talking to us yeah i just was noticed she's listening so my phone is going off and what i
love is that i'm getting a message that says why can't we drink box and i said it was fine it's
fine you you i said why are you a bad frenzy remember i didn't buy box wine because remember
tip it in chemistry alcohol can be the solution i do believe 100 a certain person in the pacific
northwest is called the baron of boxed wine listen i almost bought boxed wine but no the
selection that i wanted to bring it would have been like really expensive so if i'm bringing
sutter's home or barefoot to an occasion is it really that different no it was some other brand
it was like a target brand of target one i told you it was no what i brought was apothic red
and some other one dark horse ros okay if you want to know what kind of wine i drink
because menage a trois has too much merlot i like the apothic red more than a menage a trois i'm
sorry all right really menage a trois is good to cook with okay so now we're on menage a trois and
i have a story about steam we're supposed to get to but jamie really got to get back to video
here but no red wine is as good as boujale all right video games well maybe uh you have found
uh over your just like there's many thousands of types of wines out there there's many thousands of
types of games available on steam in fact according to an unofficial aggregator called steam spy
in the year 2017 7 672 games were released on the digital service that's a lot of games a lot of
those are probably shit no literally it's probably poop simulator 2017 that's probably
what you know is this type of game is being released uh that is by the way 2472 more games
than the year prior and 40 of the entire steam library came out in the past year yeah getting
greenlight was a great idea so uh yeah now valve is stuck with do we curate steam games do we rely
on algorithms what do we do how how do you make sense of the mess that is the steam store quickly
because i know it's always algorithms that's always the answer that's what youtube does it
works so well for them too you don't you don't make the problem is that they've already opened
the floodgates it's already flooded with poop and so what are you gonna do it they need to bring
back green light again all right uh just a few more stories here and then we're gonna open up
the skype line at orange lounge radio all one word on skype but first dark sakura
oh yeah i got more shit to do don't i well this is happy news this is good news because
honestly i wish i could have found this person and punched him in the dick okay i'll help you
um not just punch him with my fist but like make the infinity gauntlet a real thing and punch him
with you know like the time gem or something so that they shrink up anyway um the guy who
did the swatting call that got someone murdered um has been charged with involuntary manslaughter
wait back up what all right do you know what swatting is snow has not been paying attention
to the news all right basically it's when you say that someone at a certain address
has like a what like a gun or bomb or something imagine if you're playing call of duty with a
friend and you make a one dollar and fifty cent wager and somehow you know that friend uh tanks
the game for you and so you get mad at them so the mature thing you do is you call in a fake
um hostage threat to the police that's not mature no of course it is you pay the buck 50 you will
know sarcasm it's it's you know the sarcasm is thick with it's reality so you you call in the
fakes the the fake um you know hostage or bomb threat so the swat team shows up at your house
and scares you or whatever except you know this person of course that's going to be the recipient
of this gives them a fake address they go to a person's house the guy's like what the fuck's all
this noise outside looks outside you know puts his hands up puts his hands down gets shot killed and
then his family has to walk over his dead body horrible yeah that's what happened with this guy
the one who made the clotting is not a fucking game that's a real thing yep yeah oh my god we
were just bitching about ingress like seriously that's why my reference earlier when i mentioned
spotting it's like you know the same kind of there's no reason for that shit no well what
happened with this guy the the guy's name is tyler barris he was charged in kansas for involuntary
manslaughter and two other counts after his um swat call uh led to the death of the 28 year old
in his home um he will be facing um a big fine and quite a lot of time in prison although it
can vary from case to case um but he had called saying that there was a hostage situation um on
december 28th that had his family at gunpoint in the house being doused with gasoline and he gave
them the address for a guy named andrew finch who was shot and killed by an officer when he opened
the door the officer is also an administrative leave now this is going to lead me to another
thing is that if the military has a stronger you know kill rule than the police does that's fucking
a problem right the fuck there wait a minute here so wait it wasn't the regular police it
was the military no it was i'm using as an example because we get a lot of these stories of cops just
shooting people and the military won't do is not allowed to do that sort of thing okay wait so
these people are acting on what someone else said yeah they don't have actual information they're
they're going well they're the guy that's on the phone is impersonating the person that's supposed
to be at that house so he's basically saying i have my family hostage i'm gonna shoot them
you know right and just so the police are going on what this guy says because they have nothing else
to go on correct right and on top of that yeah the guy who ended up being shot had nothing to
do with the dispute at all yeah and it was completely different person again i hate that
this is tied to video games because really the story at its core it really has nothing to do
with video games that's just assholes but but at the same time but at the same time you're right
we were talking about this a little bit when we're talking about like we were talking about
ingress like you know with as much as like other people in the game have annoyed me previously and
so forth i think we are all decent enough people to know you don't fucking do this right ever
absolutely because someone killed my portal that's ridiculous it's ridiculous oh i've never heard of
that and on top of that this bearish guy was also charged with another incident that happened in
canada so this guy's a serial swatter he's also called in bomb threats to evacuate what a fucker
okay wait a minute here hold up how old is he 25. bye that totally sounds like a like a 12 year
old thing to do right i didn't i wouldn't show when i was 12 i'm mad i know kids with more
maturity than this doing him doing something like that neither but but again you know not
only is the swatting a problem but it also has to do with the standards that the police are held to
yeah when we've got people being murdered just for raising their hand or going to grab their id
when the military has a stronger rule toward uh what is it the rules of engagement
then you've got a problem you have a fucking problem so this is a problem much bigger than
anything unfortunately we're going to solve on olr tonight but i think what we need to do is you know
the part we can do something about is continue to try to build a community that just you know treats
each other decently you know and if you lose a bet for a dollar 50 pay the goddamn dollar 50
it's not that hard i'm calling people to your house rob but what no oh oh you better pay me
two dollars all right dollars because i owe her two dollars all right low-key uh one more story
from you we're gonna get skypline here in just a moment okay so nintendo has um sued a mobile
developer in japan by the name of uh koappel i guess that's how you pronounce that and over a
patent that they have for using a touch screen as a virtual joystick so they filed the lawsuit
against them um i guess for a game called the white cat project um which i guess uses some sort
of free forming free floating uh touch screen as an approximation of a joystick that's such a vague
patent man i really hate companies having this kind of stuff but anyways lately at the very
least it's not for a ton of money they basically are seeking 39.3 million yen which is about 350
000 because of this alleged patent issue that's dumb that's really dumb that's another thing that
probably needs to be examined in this country is is a lot of the patent laws granted wait a minute
just try and patent like um virtual trade of items uh i don't think they bought a company
that does virtual cartoony things and people know it's like virtual virtual trade of items through
like i hadn't heard of that yes no they filed it hasn't been done yet so like if i drop you
a capsule of bursters like that idea of if no like if i wanted to be in japan and i wanted to
give you something else in the u.s there's like a virtual travel thing oh i bet that's for pokemon
it it is i'm sure so there's or ingress like dropping gear for stuff so they're trying to
patent that idea of of um like you have to use actual travel doesn't ingress doesn't need it
i mean you you know there was like a like they were like like traveling stuff from like like
train lines and stuff like that like if you wanted to drop gear for someone but they were
trying to patent that interesting so like i could go to a train station and drop the gear
to another train station although i really think like a locker i really think this is pokemon i
think it's nothing to do with ingress no it's totally they're trying they're trying to solve
the problem of how do we open up pokemon trading but make it so that you can use a patent they send
you a file google it like stupid yeah niantic like filed for some patent about like fucking
virtual virtual trade of gear over regular line i gotta read more about that yeah that's
interesting all right uh panda in our chat says that patent sounds dumb is that panda panda i
believe it is panda go buy a coin what about train swag panda's saying you need to use a link cable
to trade pokemon that's right back in my day get them cable get off my lawn panda six miles both
ways cable panda can you please tell us about picking up like a thousand keys this is modern
nintendo though it's gonna be it's gonna be several friend codes all right i got one more
story for you guys and we're gonna open up the skype line the last story tonight is about of
course pornography hooray you can totally have sex with people in um dragon age i i'm aware i'm
aware it's not pornography though in mass effect the whole reason somebody got me to play mass
effect because i was like oh shooty pew pew game i'm not gonna like it the whole way somebody got
me to play that game was to show me rob in this game you can have man-on-man action and i was like
in the witcher in the witcher three you can fuck on top of a unicorn i'm playing that
wait a minute witcher three really the future is here berry berry that's my new game why am i
wasting my time with ingress swear to god all right we need a rainbow with you replace blue
with hot pink i want to switch to the unicorn unicorn that's gonna happen all right uh anyway
oh yes porn uh so pornhub has talked about the top consoles when it comes to browsing the site's
content now i'm assuming they filtered out pc which and tablets which i would think would be
the most obvious things to uh but what consoles do you think access the pornhub the most uh snow
what console do you think access is pornography the most my daughter's phone it said no phone
oh i'm sorry my bad one my bad all right um i would know well i say ps4 56 playstation
dominated the traffic 32 on the xbox because now you're buying an xbox
edge is built into the xbox so you can access pornhub.com on the xbox this is interesting
information thank you for telling me your soft edge have you tried tori but there's bing and
bing is great for porn searches apparently now do they have an apparently really tab on that
here's here's the thing that blows my mind though guys i just need to know because i've got a 13
year old i want a pornhub yes there's tori tori back up here tori's asking if you have to put a
cartridge in or like some sort of tbd yeah it's a porn card no it's online the world is yours it's
a porn cartridge go to the go to walmart look no don't go to the guy i need a porn cartridge y'all
we live in the year 2018 if it has a screen it can have porn yeah like that's in fact see that
and also if it has mechanical parts it'll run linux five percent or accessing porn on the
nintendo wii u five percent on the ps vita get this one percent on the nintendo we
get the fuck out can you still watch porn on the wii remember we had pterodactyl porn on the wii
i remember i had a new year's there's pterodactyl there is every sort of porn that you wait what
does that number like rule 34 if you can imagine it it has been done it has been turned into porn
i think that is a good last story to end on but we're going to open up the skype line right now
orange lounge radio all one word on skype if you want to give us a call and talk about uh whatever
you does this mean they get to look at us ask no they can't see us it's no there's no webcam so
i put on makeup for nothing what for me and i appreciate it i straightened my you're gay
he's still good you know i appreciate it thank you there you go all right i'm also wearing a
profound amount of makeup so orange lounge radio all on word on skype if you'd like to uh talk to
our guests or really you can bring up anything i know a lot was going on this weekend actually
i have not even brought up ces consumer electronic show that because i don't think anything like
directly gaming related that was that vegas one yeah that's the one this goes on in vegas that's
where you know like the bigger there wasn't really anything super like exciting i saw dude
the last time oh you're right bobby blackwell says we did have one ces story the vr thing was
kind of related to the last time i went to vegas it was for like black hat something the last time
i went to vegas was for fantasy 14 fan fest all right we do have a call coming in let's get to it
hi you're on orange now just i want to warn our guests you might be able to see them but they
can't see you i can see you all right i actually know you're seeing a static picture that's just
hi you're on orange on radio who's this hey uh rob this is the raging nator hey rage nator what's
on your mind buddy uh no uh well first uh uh first things first now after you do my usual plug for
deals um you know it's probably gonna be a little too late for anyone that catches the show uh via
podcast but for the live listeners uh until you know tomorrow roughly about noonish you know or
1 p.m eastern time uh wherever that time may be you know for you know uh california um you know
gog is having like uh a new year sale uh going on is going to be concluding concluding then
that's a good place to buy witcher 3 just so you know because gog is the same company
the main witcher 3 so if you want to get the next one yeah unicorns yeah right on yeah yeah and
they do have a lot of good games they're you know uh people like this it's not just a clever name
yeah uh no no as for the main potatoes of my uh call as it relates to you know services like gog
and steam uh are there you know i you know i would have to ask uh you and everyone else in
studio are there any games that you know not currently on those uh services that you would
love to see sold on there you know that aren't currently sold there super multitasking but i
think i only have to wait a month i had to throw that out there because i know he's listening uh
let's see games that are i mean because when i okay here's the thing though rage when i think
about like that question i think like oh games available on pc that are coming over from console
and we got some big ones tonight honestly with mario odyssey then that's when people start to
go crazy like oh am i crazy well i got something for you in a second here nintendo games don't come
out on pc except china and video shield but that's different that's a whole different thing
so uh yeah that's just that's just not going to happen here but um oh what was i going to say um
oh that's what you thought what do you want to say loogie oh i was just going to say that there's
um just uh today actually they announced um the team behind the 3ds emulator citra has announced
yuzu which is the first nintendo switch emulator that does all the things they said that you didn't
need it to do and one of the games that they have rain on it already the legends all the
breath of the wild is already playable on it wait a minute here it does the things you didn't need
it to do it's a joke i don't know this what they said okay you know the you know the thing is with
emulators you know they're kind of a gray area in the sense that technically the emulator in of
itself as far as you know is legal but uh i kind of like into those two uh bombs you know you know
at least well except for like uh california and oregon and washington where marijuana is legal
right no well most here's even better example rage uh emulators are kind of like a gun it's
not illegal to own one it's illegal to shoot somebody with it um that you you know didn't
have a really good reason to do so so emulators and i think i think this goes back to the whole
bleem in the dreamcast and uh playstation era and that whole thing like the emulator itself
is not illegal uh it is the games on it because the games still remain the intellectual property
i'm not a lawyer wait a minute here did he just say like all of the states that marijuana is legal
well i mean it is that's also great and emulators are also legal but not for other places yeah no
well what i was trying to say is like well like for new york state where i live
you know they you can buy a bomb but you know the thing is uh they say you know they sell
it's for smoking tobacco but it's kind of like wink wink you can use this for pot too you know
yeah and so so that's the thing with emulators emulators are supposed to be for homebrew they
are um engines for you know independent developers to be have a sandbox to do their own thing it's
not supposed to be for you to be able to play mario brothers bayway we're diverting a little
bit from the original question which was about like are there games that are not currently on
the steam service that you would like to see their gog um you know i i think you would have
to go to probably some of the biggest console classics right now like things like horizon i
think a lot of people would get a kick out of that being horizon zero dawn specifically being
able to play that on pc um some people i'm sure would love it if blizzard would put their games
out on steam but that's just not going to happen they have no reason to not whatsoever wish i mean
it's kind of unnecessary but it'd be cool if minecraft was on steam okay why wouldn't you
put a game on steam because it's owned by microsoft and microsoft has their own
stoner front why won't cbs just put star trek discovery on netflix because why exactly why
because you'll pay to go to their service to watch it but then they have to pay also for people to
watch it right sorta i mean but they're making money because you're paying five bucks a month
for cbs all access so anyway sometimes sometimes it's to lure you to a specific place anyway let
me ask you this real quick and i want to i want to uh get back to the um get back to the uh phones
here but spazzinator um or excuse me rage nator i always get confused because your name your name
comes up different in the um uh skype uh rage nator i know you don't really play ingress but
did you enjoy hearing our guest tonight oh yeah yeah in fact yes great i don't own a smartphone
to play uh cell phone based games but you know i would i do enjoy hearing about
gay uh games i don't necessarily get a chance to play um case in point you know you know
to get a little off topic uh for the longest time you know as you already know i was a console
player i never touched pc gaming never thought i would ever touch pc gaming but i kept on hearing
you talking about steam and steam sales yada yada yada this is all my fault is what you're saying
yeah wait so it looks like jack black and i appreciate that yes thank you also all of
us English players are super hot so you should probably upgrade your phone is what i'm saying
oh my god i like your picture all right uh i'll have to give you um the contact information
offline but look out for uh the sasquatch that may have something to say about that
you can email snow directly all right anyway i'm gonna let you go so we can get more calls
but thank you oh sure have a good one take care buddy uh orange launch radio all one word on skype
if you want to give us a call seriously you look like jack black i like that well everybody puts
a really good picture no i like that in a person who do i look like my dream man i know you look
like some guy named rob we're getting another call that's coming in we're gonna uh go to the phones
and take this hi you're on orange launch radio who's this hey this is bobby blackwolf hey bobby
it's the guy who does the show before us here on sunday night it's always a pleasure i don't see a
picture that's probably for the she wants to know if you look like jack black bobby i actually do
look like jack black all right actually kind of like ryan reynolds i'd be happy all right anyway
bob no what's up bobby snow be quiet let bobby talk what's up so tonight was a very monumental
night uh because of the the retirement of the joke that i the inside joke i have been making
for years uh and it was for a good cause uh but i wanted to share my head canon of how i was going
to end the joke and and it's pretty clever and the joke we're talking about is the halo being
classic game of the week right yes because i also hate halo all right so that's why i was pushing
for it because i wanted i wanted to share in the misery all right i kind of never realized that but
why do you hate halo i don't hate it i think it's great i'm i'm terrible at first person shooters so
it's it's not because it's a bad game it's because i suck at the club all right let let the man talks
now all right so you you had your whole head cannon for how this big moment was gonna go down
yes so and and and jamie laughed so that's why i'm gonna share it but it would have been on a
night somehow like if i happen to be on the show live like in sacramento for like if i was in
out in the bay area for business or whatever we've talked about it it almost happened once
i remember yes it's almost happened a couple times uh but jamie wouldn't be there i'm like
oh i'll do the classic game of the week and don't worry jamie i will not pick halo and she would
believe me which she actually wouldn't but in my head cannon she did okay so that's where the
fiction is uh and i would have said okay tonight's classic game of the week is dead or alive 4 and
we'd start playing the music from dead or alive 4 and i talk about you know 30 seconds about
dead or life 4 and bring up one of the characters was spartan 117 and immediately the music would
change to halo and i would sit there for five minutes talking about the background of this
character in dead or alive 4 uh talking all about the halo series and what it's all about and then
at the end it would go back to do a form of music and i'd be like yep dead or alive 4 classic game
of the week and that would be the end of the second i think it's pretty clever using a character
in the game to inject uh the real topic at hand now it just tempts me that for classic games in
the future i'm going to be like okay how do we six degrees of halo this game that's right it's the
new kevin bacon it was on this console yeah halo was on this console by the way did you know that
this one particular artist went on to uh go make a game called halo exactly rob do they have a
website like that that'll that'll connect six degrees of video games rob yes i will alert the
world that mr smoosh is your next of kin that's okay if he is so cute if alan and i were to die
in a fiery car crash heaven forbid and we go we don't have kids or anything like that so i mr
smoosh can have it all would you like one of my kids one of your kids meaning your genes oh one's
adopted i'm just teasing they're all really good at video games just saying oh that's good no
we could we could uh we could build on that a little bit i will i can have whichever one isn't
irritating me that day i lost my train of thought so never mind that's okay that's okay bobby was
uh well now you're just gonna have to come up so now now what do we do bobby you need a new joke
do we i don't know we'll have to figure it out somehow i know you know what like most i have
to pick something else i'll never pick like most jokes on this show such as loki dressing up as
tingle i judgment i mean i did do miss nude world as well you know as these these long-running oil
oranges it will just be grown organically we'll figure it out eventually i need another game i
loathe maybe bobby can talk about um next year he'll fill up the time capsule with things that
make sense okay you should write down what it is you put in there before you actually
seal it i listened to that and i was like how did you guys not know i tried there like two months
previously or whatever i tried your shit together that's all right i slipped my stuff from last year
back in there so why did you not why did you not have a list of what you're putting why did you
tell us now when we could have found out we're gonna forget about it by the time we open that
y'all we have a caller on the line and we're running 40 minutes over so high collar so let
me uh bobby you're always so kind to have us on at the end of your show every week please plug
the bobby blackwolf show and where folks can find it we have new listeners tonight thanks to the
ingress connection so uh plug your show a little bit and uh tell us where we can find it yeah so
i i am here at vog network i i come i go on right before olr and usually like go into the olr time
so at about 8 p.m eastern 5 p.m pacific i've been doing it for um like a couple weeks now like i've
only been doing the podcast for a couple weeks so i hope it's good uh apparently episode 600
is next week it sure is happy birthday ish i guess can i be on your show
say no bobby i don't know if bobby rarely has well i mean he'll do like phone guests game developers
oh here you guys know make a game if you make a game you can get on bobby show i have so many
games that's all right i guess i can't ever have something loki can't even do all right hey someday
someday and then he could but he would not all right no y'all should listen to bobby blackwolf
because uh you know it's not just about vr but he likes a lot of the same classic game stuff we do
and it's it's it's just a good show damn it i'll listen all right you should awesome awesome all
right uh thanks bobby i'm gonna let you go to see if any more calls come through okay thank you
thanks bye uh we'll see if we squeeze in one more call orange lounge radio all one word on skype
this is the part though where i'm gonna ask uh if there was any um last minute stories
no i already read my last minute story what was that it's about the emulator for the switch
which i'm very excited about yeah because then i might actually get to play mario honestly
i i can't imagine that thing runs very well or it's gonna need like a heck of a computer to run
it why they run the we use stuff runs at 4k at 60 fps all right i guess i would assume that
to be fair i honestly honest to god haven't used an emulator on a pc
i mean the main cabinet is one thing but that's really it like i just i don't really play
emulators like i can run uh weu games at 1080p at full speed and they look nice so all right uh
again orange lounge radio all one word on skype if you want to give us a call uh i'll keep it
open for just a couple more minutes and uh then we'll go ahead and close up shop here if nobody
else calls in jen you really love mr smoosh don't you my gosh so much isn't he so adorable
it's because he looks like a pug but he doesn't stink or go he does he does do the thing
you probably might no not like a pug though he's so cute oh my gosh i need i need one well i should
give a cheap plug for mr smoosh's instagram then you can follow mr smoosh on instagram
instagram yeah mr it's spelled out m-i-s-t-e-r mr smoosh that's how you do it my instagram is
mommy needs a drink it's very appropriate anyone who is listening wants to follow me on instagram
and see my kids be crazy rob someone suggested i don't remember who that that midna and mr smoosh
have a play date i that'd be great i think cat play dates are a bad idea in general midna likes
other animals rob does that's mr smoosh he will not bite you but he will claw you so just be
careful i don't know because i haven't seen mr smoosh around other animals i don't want to show
too much leg here but that's that right here snow you want to see some leg this right here is from
mr smoosh okay i i i already pantsed you i'm sorry does he have no spaces does he have what no areas
like yes pet no yes someone is saying i still think mr smoosh's full name is little what is it
little betas smooshy face that's from bobbie who's just on the phone why do you think that's his name
because don't play me because we've we've what is that cannon oh that's a first i have not oh
oh mr smoosh is you're familiar going for like so if you had powers mr smoosh would be you're
familiar if you were a witch uh yeah it's just like sabrina except instead of um salem it would
be mr smoosh okay my my familiar is a serial killer but yours is a black cat and mine's a
serial killer so i love it all right one more shout out for the skype line last call orange
lounge radio all one word on skype i honestly think of a lot of our hey swatch killer or is it
a rocket you should call in pepper knows a lot with that pepper come on in orange launch radio
all one word on skype on skype do people have skype i don't have skype i don't have skype on
my phone really no that's because you have five thousand other apps to play one game
that is a fact it is it's like a free puppy ingress is like a free puppy it's like anytime
i go visit another town because i am fortunate enough that you know my travels have taken me
different places it's like i go to this city and they're like oh we use group me i go to this city
it's like oh group me group me group me has the best meme creators oh really but that's like the
only thing it has what is it group me in one area panda says rock cat went to bed and then is that
do it panda okay one of you needs to call in because that's pathetic
all right snow i'm only gonna give it a little bit and then panda there's no other last minute
stories no we're good no all right well then sadly the phone i've i've been i've been saying
it for five minutes it's not lighting up i think i think folks are going to bed so i think we're
going to wrap up here at orange launch radio a nice long show for the night here but i promised
one for the history books so there it is we're gonna wrap up here at orange launch radio tonight
and i want to thank you guys very much for listening i want to thank our guests for being
here it was such a fun show and even i think again like we were kind of asking uh rage nader
when he called it even for the folks that don't play the game i think they just like hearing the
stories and uh yeah it's great and i've always been i didn't really get into this at all but
one thing that always kind of made me like really like like happy about ingress and i thought was
really cool especially compared to a lot of other games i played is that like the people that are
running a lot of the shit especially in like in this town on our on our side are women and like
there's a lot of like strong women playing this game and i think when we have a lot of talks
in the gaming community especially you know because there's the overwatch league is going
through this right now about like out of 133 players in the league how do you not have one
woman you know and that's a whole nother topic for another show no globally globally in ingress
the majority of people who play are women and there's there's great men too of course but i
mean like you really see that the like equalness for sure if not a lot of the a lot of the people
that are running at least on our side a lot of people that are running the stuff for anomalies
or fielding all that it's ladies i'd say that like even on the other side of global leaders
are women yeah is run by a woman yeah so it's yeah it's not just even our team so yeah i think it's
great so uh yeah and um i just i just love that and i'm happy to support that and all that good
stuff so uh and i'm sure the listeners really loved hearing from you guys um of the stories
and all that good stuff so thank you guys all for being here we usually do a little part of the show
that's called our final thoughts so do you have any like last final thought a last word you want
to get out for the listeners tonight snow i'll start with you because you're probably gonna be
the longest you're an asshole also um no tell me games to play and i'll try them out because i
would love to try other games like i love ingress but i have certain things i'm really good at and
i love doing and other things i'm kind of bored with so i will play other games i'm sure if the
resistance is still listening they're going to recommend the most habit forming games wow go play
world of warcraft go play the things that will keep you out of ingress 2018 is the year of garfield
go in all seriousness no in all seriousness uh i would say because you've taken so well to dragon
age i think you would really like um mass effect i think i would do you have to start the whole
series though yeah and make your decisions so uh that would that would be my recommendation
so uh any other last thoughts you want to get out thank you for being here should i get like
a twitch account and like people can watch me play poorly that's what i do it's fun and then
they like you have to have like a headset where you can talk and be like well what what the fuck
is going on why am i dying do you have to have it no will you get more watchers if you at least are
able to interact with your audience absolutely you need to be able i can totally suck at any
game you guys give me so like and curse at it so i'm willing to do that there you go i'll take
that there you go so when you disappear from ingress we'll know it's to make your twitch
millions right my twitch millions all right anyway uh jen thank you so much for being here
thanks for having us you're welcome it's not like i had a choice because you all told me you're
coming right we said rob you're gonna have us on your show and you know since christie couldn't
come you have to do it again well you guys are like how hard you laugh you guys you guys are
gonna tape your pilot for your uh right for our new podcast christie i'm i'm bummed christie
could make it tonight so of course she's welcome anytime is snow stealing your microphone i'm
stealing because we're gonna have our own podcast remember and rob's gonna be straight man because
we're basically having like a morning radio show right right i'm rob straight man yeah let rob
have his mic back did she just call me a straight man she did she called you straight man uh first
off your cat is adorable um he was just like hiding under a bag by himself it was really cute
um but yeah either i just really like the chance to chat about ingress and you know in a sort of
collegial and informational way it was fun all right awesome tory i know you've been quiet this
half of the show but um thank you so much for being here and uh any last words you want to
say to our audience tonight i don't have time because i've got to go field sacramento
get on a checkpoint in 13 minutes get out there get on it uh oh peppers right now i'm gonna need
everybody to start their clears pepper messaged and said that since you didn't say that you
wouldn't switch she thinks there's still a chance that you'll what you're saying is there's still a
chance no i think she might have missed that part that no i'm i'm not i'm not gonna be switching
away from green i just i really can't do that to my buddies here on the green team right
we're we're waiting for you to switch to green there's always space on the green team you can
that you can have all the fields you want here they're just not gonna stand for long well it
won't be my fault all right anyway uh but also a nice compliment and that's that's good sportsmanship
too uh you guys were very charismatic something about being very charismatic i saw there
very nice thank you very good i'm glad we could bring you a fair and balanced view of the world
of ingress tonight that's right fair and balanced fair and balanced no alternative facts none
shut your face all right uh thanks again the ingress horse for being here and i will say at
the end of the show as i always do thank you so much for listening to orange lounge radio you
know we've been doing this for believe it or not coming up on 16 years uh that's kind of surprising
it took you guys this long to get here but i don't really i don't really shout it out in the ingress
community as i do this i can be here every sunday that's fault everybody found out about this rob
i can be here every single now that snow knows exactly where you live oh boy no uh so i want to
say uh a big uh um yeah a big thanks to everybody listening and if you liked what you heard here at
orange lounge radio a nice five star review on a site like itunes or google play or wherever you
found this podcast it would go a really really long way and uh also uh appreciate just tell a
friend tell a friend or two about the show as has been happening tell a frenemy as has been happening
tonight here uh about the show and help us spread the word because we're not a big website like igm
or game spot or anything like that we just have y'all word of mouth so um a quickly host final
thoughts tonight dark sakura we'll start with you ladies first um i will try to stream this week
hopefully wednesday if i can um so my twitch channel is dark sakura underscore olr and i can
finally take subscriptions so please if you can subscribe and also please give my mom more money
i mean and also thanks for folks who donated during the show i really really appreciate it
and um yeah i'm yeah i think i will piggyback on your final thought and just say like you know
we had a really fun show tonight we had a really long show tonight and we obviously had a historic
moment with halo being the game of the week finally but um you know i i think i am just so
like humbled about the community here and you know for for what it's worth the community in ingress
and the people i've met over there too to kind of tie the two bridges together just like you know
just the generosity of of awesome gamers and that's what we need to just hear more about and
less about these swatting asshole babies just bye so uh yeah thanks again everybody for being
awesome all right and uh loki last not least your final thought i would just like to take this
moment since i don't really have much of a final thought there was someone that posted a thing on
reddit they showed that their significant other um that she got stardew valley and so going down
the comments there so just tell her to stay away from shane such a dick i told her to tell
shane the fuck off well i already said earlier shane's the worst no seriously shane's awesome
but it is silly the next time you guys are here i'm going to invite him too and it'll be an
intervention you need to play ingress again night because i would that would be great for me i'd
have because alan can so rarely play with me anymore and he wants to play pokemon i wish i
had more time but i can't leave after the kids go to sleep because then my wife will be home alone
you're doing it wrong all right oh the bring them with me oh yeah that's a great idea i've done that
before daddy is taking so why are you sitting here why are we sitting at the park why can't
we go to the park why are we this is taking too long i want to go home and this is why i'm going
to murder you and this is why i'm never breeding this is my flight kids are like not the portal
game i got them tablets that have gps built to them so they could play ingress if they want to
do or play pokemon go they actually want to play pokemon go they're supposed to be 13 and they
never not anymore to do it they plays roadblocks it's roadblocks all the time you want to talk
about shitty games that's how it works you buy them a thing going you're gonna help daddy with
ingress and all of a sudden nope we're gonna go play pokemon go or blocks or whatever anyway
that's it we really are going to wrap up roll credits i hope you guys enjoyed the long show
tonight y'all deserved it you're a great audience thank you so much we'll see you next week we'll
be back in seven days to do it all over again unfortunately loki will not be here next week
i will maybe i may not be here today next week so we'll see it depends what the plans are so uh
we'll see we'll see who shows up next week maybe snow we'll be back we'll see well uh i'll uh i'll
go uh figure out i'll go meet pepper at the park and maybe she'll have some box wine to pass over
i'm moving in box wine all right that's it we're out of here have a great night everybody bye
you've been listening to orange lounge radio orange lounge radio is a production of olr
studios to join us for a live show tune into fog network.com sunday nights at 6 p.m pacific 9 p.m
eastern the views and opinions expressed in this program do not necessarily reflect those of the
staff of orange lounge radio or vog network but you know they were all still true
see you next week
you