[SPEAKER_02]: Tonight, May 21st, 2006, in an OLR exclusive, new evidence may have given us the release date of the Wii, Xbox's firmware is hacked and Microsoft responds, and a warning on E3 downloads.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello everybody and welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is episode number 184 for this May 21st, 2006.
[SPEAKER_02]: My name is Rob Roberts, but you might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_02]: Joining me as always, say hello to the one and only DarkSakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_00]: Wee!
[SPEAKER_02]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_00]: Tired.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tired?
[SPEAKER_02]: Long weekend?
[SPEAKER_00]: I went to see a friend and I actually just got back off the road literally 10 minutes ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: You drove right up into the OLR studio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Literally, she crashed into the building.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lots of damage.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_00]: I wouldn't do that to my baby.
[SPEAKER_00]: I ran into Loki's car.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought it was very interesting how you told me you were staying awake on most of the road.
[SPEAKER_02]: How were you staying awake?
[SPEAKER_00]: You gave me one of these little seized chocolate lollipop things.
[SPEAKER_02]: Seized lollipops are the best thing ever, except for the fact they got rid of peanut butter, so screw them.
[SPEAKER_00]: But I was chewing on it, and like, because it's like, there's reason ones you can't bite through.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right.
[SPEAKER_00]: And then like, sucking on them, and then like, a part broke off, and it had a sharp edge, and it cut my tongue.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ow.
[SPEAKER_00]: So yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry to hear it.
[SPEAKER_00]: And then, that lasted me from about, right before the 360 toll booth, not 360, the
[SPEAKER_00]: 680, totally.
[SPEAKER_02]: At least you're in a gaming mode, we know.
[SPEAKER_00]: Until without O. Davis, and then I was like... Is there a Highway 360 somewhere?
[SPEAKER_02]: I imagine there's got to be.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm sure there is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Probably somewhere on the East Coast where there's nothing but highways out there.
[SPEAKER_00]: There are highways here, there are freeways.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, also say hello to the one and only Techmaster Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello, I'm here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, you're here.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sporting your new Silent Hill t-shirt I like.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it's not new, but yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Where'd you get that?
[SPEAKER_02]: I got this from work.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, lucky you.
[SPEAKER_02]: I went into Hot Topic this weekend, you know, tease me if you want for going in there, but, you know, they sell some cool stuff sometimes, and also they had the Silent Hill Pyramid Head t-shirt, which rocked, so I had to pick that up.
[SPEAKER_00]: They finally got that in?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, they had it at the... I tried to get it before E3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, so did I, because I wanted to wear one to E3, but they have them now.
[SPEAKER_02]: and I'll see you next time.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_00]: Um, well, I actually played a lot of Kingdom Hearts this weekend from like 1 until 3 in the morning.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm trying to figure out why I couldn't get back to Agrabah on my game.
[SPEAKER_00]: Because I sort of skipped it.
[SPEAKER_00]: I went right from Pirates of the Caribbean to Halloween Town.
[SPEAKER_00]: And now I can't get back into Agrabah and the Pride Lands.
[SPEAKER_00]: But Dan somehow did that because he did that before he went to Halloween Town.
[SPEAKER_00]: So we're trying to figure out if I need to start my game over or just, you know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hey, if anyone knows, please let me know.
[SPEAKER_00]: Send me a PM in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_00]: And then we went to the Winchester Mystery House and there was an arcade there.
[SPEAKER_00]: I played Theater of Magic.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's one of my favorite pinball tables ever.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would say Baby Pac-Man, Pinbot, Theater of Magic.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although I do have a lot of love for Adam Stanley.
[SPEAKER_00]: Baby Pac-Man, Black Knight 2000, Theater of Magic.
[SPEAKER_00]: No love for Pinbot.
[SPEAKER_00]: I played X-Men vs. Street Fighter.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_00]: and their controller was broken so I called the manager because I was going to get my money back.
[SPEAKER_00]: I didn't really care about my 50 cents.
[SPEAKER_00]: I was like, the controller's broken on X-Men vs. Street Fighter so you can go to the gift table and get your money back.
[SPEAKER_00]: I was like, so are you going to fix it?
[SPEAKER_00]: And he's like, eventually.
[SPEAKER_00]: I was like, that's not good enough.
[SPEAKER_00]: You should go have a look at it.
[SPEAKER_00]: And he just wandered off looking pissed off and I was like, dick.
[SPEAKER_00]: I worked for an arcade, okay?
[SPEAKER_00]: I know that you can just take out the joystick, put in a new one, or you fix the contacts.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_00]: I own arcade machines now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did it feel just like it was a broken contact?
[SPEAKER_02]: Like the joystick felt fine?
[SPEAKER_02]: The joystick felt fine.
[SPEAKER_00]: It wasn't moving up or down.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's probably just a contact.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lame.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, so I was like, so don't play X-Men vs. Street Fighter at the Winchester Mystery House.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right.
[SPEAKER_00]: Other than that, Winchester Mystery House rocks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Speaking of our chat room, because you brought them up, OrangeLawnTrader.com, click on chat.
[SPEAKER_02]: We love being an interactive program.
[SPEAKER_02]: And DMN is winner because he went onto Wikipedia and quickly found Texas State Highway 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: So there is a Highway 360 in Texas.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of which we are not based in.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're in California.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_01]: It was good.
[SPEAKER_01]: I purchased an actual game for the DS, New Super Mario Brothers, and it was pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: Just plays like, I don't know, kind of a cross between Super Mario World, a little bit of, I don't know, some of the objects you have to get.
[SPEAKER_01]: It kind of reminds me of Yoshi's Island a little bit, and then Super Mario 3.
[SPEAKER_01]: So it's kind of a combination of those, but it's fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's just Mario, you know.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I played that, and of course I had a craving for Ridge Racer all week.
[SPEAKER_01]: Ridge Racer!
[SPEAKER_01]: So I played Ridge Racer 6, and that was fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then, um...
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_00]: Cheesy!
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm like, Dan?
[SPEAKER_00]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_00]: I was like, you've got a pinball machine.
[SPEAKER_00]: I was like, but, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: But seriously, I was looking at the rankings on my friends list, and Dan, of course, is number one.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's played well over a hundred matches on that game.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, seriously, he does, like, freaking tournament play.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my, that's sick.
[SPEAKER_00]: He actually has done the win the game with the wild draw seven.
[SPEAKER_00]: I also draw four.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got that achievement by total luck.
[SPEAKER_02]: Total luck.
[SPEAKER_00]: He's gotten, like, all kinds of crap on that game.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm like...
[SPEAKER_00]: It's Uno.
[SPEAKER_00]: I have in my car right now.
[SPEAKER_00]: I have a box of Uno cards.
[SPEAKER_00]: We could play real Uno and have our friends over.
[SPEAKER_00]: Dork.
[SPEAKER_00]: My husband's a dork.
[SPEAKER_00]: I love him to death, but my husband's a dork.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's part of why you married him, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: I bought Bejeweled 2 for Nellie to play, and she's been on that for a long time.
[SPEAKER_01]: I actually got to play a little bit of it today.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know if it's worth the 800 Microsoft points, which I think is about 10 bucks, so I'm not sure if
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't think I've seen a game with harder achievements than Bejeweled.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have puzzle mode on there and
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm going to cheat my way through Puzzle Mode.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's lame.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's how you know you're an achievement points whore.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because you're doing the lame game FAQs or whatever cheat through your bejeweled game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lame.
[SPEAKER_01]: You're what's wrong with America.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's more achievement points.
[SPEAKER_01]: What else did I play?
[SPEAKER_01]: I think that was pretty much... Well, Grand Theft Auto, of course.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's been fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: We need a new game now.
[SPEAKER_01]: New Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_01]: We're not going to a new game.
[SPEAKER_01]: We're just waiting for the next Grand Theft Auto to come out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sooner than later, hopefully.
[SPEAKER_02]: What about Saints Row or whatever that one was at E3 that's kind of like Grand Theft Auto?
[SPEAKER_01]: You can't really play that multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, okay, gotcha.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, that's the only thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: We need it on PSP.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'd be all down for playing multiplayer Grand Theft Auto and I hope to God that they have multiplayer in the Liberty City stories on PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't think they will, but if they do, that's going to be awesome because then I'll get to kick people's asses across the country.
[SPEAKER_01]: But right now, it's just... It's fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: We kind of mix it up a little bit, try to mix up the teams and make it really close.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then I played... Was it Astro Pop?
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't like that.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think anything PopCap sucks.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've been buying these games just to try them and...
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: I should probably just download the demo.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have a weird appreciation for Zuma on the 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know what it is, but maybe it's something about the analog stick control or something, but that one bugs me the least out of those PopCap stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: But Jeweled Control's fine, it's just I don't like how okay, no more moves, and you're fucked.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, that's not my fault that there's no more moves, it's the fact that there's random blocks, and I didn't quite
[SPEAKER_01]: And there's people cheating in the DS Tetris now.
[SPEAKER_01]: What the hell is that?
[SPEAKER_02]: I read about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not on the show.
[SPEAKER_01]: How lame is that?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think someone in our forum said it best.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm so sorry that I'm not crediting this person.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm too lazy to look at the forums.
[SPEAKER_02]: But somebody said, put a game online and people will cheat on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: End of story.
[SPEAKER_02]: Somebody will find a way to cheat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sad.
[SPEAKER_02]: How are they cheating?
[SPEAKER_02]: Weren't they giving themselves nothing but the line of four?
[SPEAKER_02]: Like how when you use the star item, you get nothing but the line blocks?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what this person did, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Pretty much.
[SPEAKER_02]: Damn cheaters in online games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cheat all you want offline, I don't care, but cheating online, bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, anything else?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Going to the chat room, NintendoManiac64 is amazed, Loki got Nelly to play a video game, because we know your wife hates games.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was tricky.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's amazing, that's good.
[SPEAKER_02]: You took the wife to see Silent Hill, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: What'd you think?
[SPEAKER_01]: She didn't sleep well.
[SPEAKER_02]: But she likes Pyramid Head?
[SPEAKER_01]: She didn't think he was that scary.
[SPEAKER_01]: She thought the Ash babies were more freaky.
[SPEAKER_01]: The Ash babies are hella freaky.
[SPEAKER_01]: I hated the people.
[SPEAKER_01]: I got dragged to the Da Vinci Code the night before.
[SPEAKER_01]: I saw that.
[SPEAKER_01]: We were going to go see three movies this weekend.
[SPEAKER_01]: We were going to go see Over the Hedge also, but we just didn't make it to it.
[SPEAKER_01]: We wanted to see Silent Hill before it left theaters, because right now it's only playing twice.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's either 2.10 or 9.40.
[SPEAKER_01]: So it's like, crap, you know?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: I hate that.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, I don't get it.
[SPEAKER_02]: DMN says, hell, look at hot coffee.
[SPEAKER_02]: No need to even have real sex anymore.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which I significantly agree with.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, disagree with.
[SPEAKER_02]: What we need?
[SPEAKER_02]: Apples to apples.
[SPEAKER_02]: That'd be great.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rumor is Texas Hold'em is on its way.
[SPEAKER_02]: Eh, lame.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see, what else was said here?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, Boss Tone says, who wants reality when you can have video games?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: Go outside once in a while.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a big, big world out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: Super Mario Bros. 4
[SPEAKER_02]: I played a little bit of it, and it's quite a fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: They have also the multiplayer minigames, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, the only thing that disappointed me was that the single-player minigames were, for the most part, all the Mario 64 games, which was a little bit of a, hmm, couldn't you have just done something new?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, I think they unlock more as you play through the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think so, too, but, you know, I was a little, there was that initial disappointment of, hmm, haven't I seen all this before?
[SPEAKER_02]: But, yeah, I'm not going to knock the game for that, because there's plenty else to do in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I do recommend New Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_02]: if you're a DS, if you have any fond memories of Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_02]: 1, 3, World, whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a great addition.
[SPEAKER_00]: By the way, you mentioning your addiction?
[SPEAKER_00]: I signed back up for World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_02]: Addict?
[SPEAKER_00]: No, not really.
[SPEAKER_00]: I played it once since I signed back up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, and then if you want to continue on my game a week, of course, I've been playing quite a bit of Final Fantasy XI because I'm just, you know...
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm addicted like that, yeah, hush.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Uno would be the other thing I've also been playing, is fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: I also downloaded the Lost Planet demo on Xbox 360, because, you know, I heard about all this stuff at E3, but since...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: That was our Gaming Week, so let's start to get into the news.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we're going to start it off with some bits on the Nintendo Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: First, let's set the stage a little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have kind of something really big we want to get into, but let's set the stage a little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, a big gaming news site, runs predictions for the Wii, yes?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, Kotaku, they had a little story about how EB Games is, I guess they have a placeholder for Madden on the Wii, and it says, I believe it was August 30th,
[SPEAKER_01]: and, you know, they're saying, you know, raises the question, are they gonna, you know, release it in the summer?
[SPEAKER_01]: Um, of course, you know, the track record of EB and stuff, they, I mean, I think they had PS3 stuff in there, like, a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_01]: And so, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: But, um, you never know.
[SPEAKER_01]: So right now it's just speculation, maybe summer.
[SPEAKER_01]: Summer.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right, interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, if you head on over to wiiNintendo.net, they're tracking, I guess, all the games that have been announced and what type of stuff is coming out on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, of course, they list all the basics, the remote, the nunchuck, the classic controller if you turn the...
[SPEAKER_02]: Remote on the side, the retro controller, the light gun that they showed in the case, which was kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then they get onto the games, and these are the games they're listing as launch games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Zelda, Twilight Princess, Metroid Prime 3 Corruption, Wii Sports, Red Steel, Tony Hawk Downhill Jam.
[SPEAKER_02]: Madden NFL 2K7, or sorry, 2007.
[SPEAKER_02]: 2K7 would be a different franchise altogether, sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dragon Quest Swords, The Masked Queen, and Tower of Mirrors.
[SPEAKER_02]: Super Monkey Ball Banana Blitz, Metal Slug Anthology, Trauma Center Second Opinion, which is a great title for the second Trauma Center.
[SPEAKER_02]: Elebits, Marvel Ultimate Alliance, Blitz the League, Rayman Raving Rabbits, SpongeBob SquarePants, Creature from the Krusty Krab, Disney Pixar's Cars is what they've got listed as the launch titles for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: So now,
[SPEAKER_02]: As you may recall, on Orange Launch Radio, a couple months ago, we posted a little bit of a spoiler on our website, so you could say, and that had to do with Castlevania Portrait of Ruin and the trio of new DDR games, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: And remind us, Loki, how did you find this information before any of the major gaming sites did?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, it's just stuff that the retailers let them know.
[SPEAKER_01]: As soon as they get updated dates on stuff, they will let their retailers know, and since I work in
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm able to see this information, whereas most people who work in the media industry, they don't work in retail or don't really have.
[SPEAKER_01]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_01]: DeathJuniorPSP DeathJuniorPSP
[SPEAKER_01]: DeathJunior2 DeathJunior2
[SPEAKER_01]: Avatar The Last Airbender
[SPEAKER_01]: which of course is a Nickelodeon franchise, Chicken Little Ace in Action, sequel to the Chicken Little game that came out, Metal Slug Anthology, and SpongeBob Creature from the Crust Crab.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now that's interesting because two of those games we knew about, the Metal Slug Anthology and the SpongeBob game of course, but the other two I hadn't really heard of before.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now of course I don't really follow Nickelodeon games, I imagine most people do, or don't, but I don't even remember...
[SPEAKER_02]: Reading about these anywhere.
[SPEAKER_01]: So those kind of showed up out of the blue.
[SPEAKER_01]: The other thing I also want to mention, though, is these are from three different companies.
[SPEAKER_01]: So if this is going to be taken as speculation, it should be... It's not just one company throwing their games in.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's three different companies.
[SPEAKER_01]: You've got Buena Vista, THQ, and I don't remember the last one.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, SNK.
[SPEAKER_01]: That was interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: So what are the dates?
[SPEAKER_01]: The dates for Chicken Little and Metal Slug, October 11th.
[SPEAKER_01]: And for Avatar and SpongeBob, October 18th.
[SPEAKER_02]: So there you have it.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Wii launch.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're speculating it's got to be in this time frame somewhere.
[SPEAKER_02]: But that's interesting, there's the two different dates.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have October 11th and October 18th.
[SPEAKER_01]: But they also, a lot of times, like for example, the 360 launch stuff comes out before.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's exactly what I was thinking.
[SPEAKER_02]: So when I read it, because you posted this in our private forum, we were talking about tonight's show, and my first thought was, okay, it's kind of like the 360, where some games came out a week before, and it looks like October 18th would be the launch of the Wii.
[SPEAKER_01]: And here's another thing about October 18th.
[SPEAKER_01]: Is this the clincher?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: October 18th marks the anniversary of the original Nintendo Entertainment System launch in the United States.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a very interesting coincidence.
[SPEAKER_01]: It is very interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, so what do you think?
[SPEAKER_02]: October 18th is the day?
[SPEAKER_01]: Maybe the 11th, but most likely the 18th.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think the hardware is pretty close to done, and launching a month in advance...
[SPEAKER_01]: against the PlayStation 3, I think it's probably going to happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, so devil's advocate here, why believe these dates in October versus the Madden date that we talked about just a little bit ago?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, from, like, retail sites, EA, for example, usually their dates, I mean, it could be, you know, a really early date, and especially, a lot of times they'll put in dates for, like, PlayStation 3, um,
[SPEAKER_01]: Madden 07 Madden 07
[SPEAKER_01]: That day, well the 29th I think it was, on all systems.
[SPEAKER_01]: On Xbox 360 and all the current gen stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: So that's probably why they have that date on there for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_01]: They just added another entry because they knew it was coming out on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_01]: Not necessarily meaning it's coming out on that day.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because obviously Madden came out last year, a lot later on the Xbox 360 for the launch.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm pretty confident on these.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: That makes perfect sense about the Madden thing because of all the other consoles around that same... You sold me.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think October 18th is the day.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe October 11th.
[SPEAKER_02]: The anniversary thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: They like doing those anniversaries.
[SPEAKER_02]: Especially with the virtual console and everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: It just makes too much sense.
[SPEAKER_02]: They'd get the jump on the PlayStation 3 just by a little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: And enough time for the hype to build up a little bit before the crazy shopping season starts the day after Thanksgiving.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it gives a chance for the hardcore gamers to get their systems and sell out, and then the crazy parents getting it for their kids would jump in in November, and it would sell out.
[SPEAKER_02]: It seems like a smart kind of launch strategy, this date.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like this date.
[SPEAKER_02]: It makes a lot of sense.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, yeah, that's what we've got so far.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, it'd be cool if they launched the system worldwide on the same day, because if that were the case in Japan, it'd be getting it in July.
[SPEAKER_01]: But, you know, I'm going with October.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's go into the chat room and see if there is any thoughts there on the October 18th date.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Blaze says, well, here's what I think.
[SPEAKER_02]: October 18th would be the day to release all the NES launch games on the virtual console.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that makes sense, you know, kind of the anniversary, but why not the actual console itself the same day?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think most of us were banking on November as it was, and we kind of thought, hmm, Nintendo, disruption, wouldn't they want to get their system out there in kind of a unique time frame?
[SPEAKER_02]: All the pieces fit together with this date for me.
[SPEAKER_02]: And although, yeah, it's not solid, it's not an official confirmation, we are going off a little bit of shaky evidence, maybe, because the dates do shift around.
[SPEAKER_02]: It just makes sense.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, and also the fact that we have three different companies agreeing on a date, pretty much, or at least a launch week window, because usually it's about two or three weeks.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm going to have to definitely say that it's looking that way.
[SPEAKER_01]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_01]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_01]: We'll find out pretty soon when the official date's going to be, but I wouldn't be too surprised if it's October 18th.
[SPEAKER_02]: So here's my other question.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why do you think Nintendo's sitting on this date now?
[SPEAKER_02]: If they kind of know, and they've told their third-party publishers what day they're planning on launching their system, what are they waiting for to tell the rest of us?
[SPEAKER_02]: What event do you think they're going to finally announce all this?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, I think they're waiting for maybe to see, because I guess the PlayStation 3, they could maybe try to get
[SPEAKER_01]: Maybe, you know, if they announce that they're going to be launching, you know, in November or something, and then kind of false sense of security for Sony or something like that, and then, you know, that way, you know, two months in advance, they're all, get the jump on them.
[SPEAKER_01]: That makes sense.
[SPEAKER_01]: Ha, bitch, we're launching fucking 30 days.
[SPEAKER_01]: Disruption.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, we'll see what happens, guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: October 18th, that's what we're betting on for right now, so.
[SPEAKER_02]: More official news to follow as soon as we hear it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Moving on to other news.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now we've got the release date.
[SPEAKER_02]: What about the price?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, rumor is flying around from Sweden, of all places.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Daily News in Sweden is saying that the Wii console will be between 2,500 and 3,000 kronor.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if you translate that into U.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: dollars, that's 340 U.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: dollars.
[SPEAKER_02]: But keep in mind...
[SPEAKER_02]: In Europe, they tend to get screwed on the prices of the consoles.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry, guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: But probably the Wii would then be in the $250 to $300 ballpark, which is a little higher than the $199 we're all assuming.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thoughts?
[SPEAKER_01]: I think it's $199.
[SPEAKER_01]: All their other systems have launched for $199, as far as my memory serves me.
[SPEAKER_01]: So...
[SPEAKER_02]: And if they're going to do the anniversary of the NES launch, why not do the price?
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think a lot of us are sold on $199.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's kind of the price that Nintendo's expected to meet.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm agreeing more with the $250 price point.
[SPEAKER_00]: Why is that?
[SPEAKER_00]: Just because it's still competitive without being, I would say, prohibitively... It's not going to...
[SPEAKER_00]: They can still make their money on it and yet still have it be generally affordable for most people.
[SPEAKER_02]: 250 or rather 249 would be cutting it a little close.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I think in that case, Nintendo would have definitely done the 199.
[SPEAKER_02]: But now that PlayStation 3 has really highballed it, maybe they can release it for 249 and it's still the cheap system.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's something about that 199.
[SPEAKER_01]: They might be waiting to see what Microsoft's going to do as far as dropping the price of their console.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's true, too, because Microsoft may have come out of that conference.
[SPEAKER_02]: They could have, hypothetically, come out of that conference and said, we're cutting the price of our core system.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that maybe was something Nintendo wanted to be prepared for.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's another thought, though, especially in this whole dual levels, the core and the premium and then the PS3, little drive and big drive.
[SPEAKER_02]: This has been done before with the original NES.
[SPEAKER_02]: You had the regular NES system.
[SPEAKER_02]: You actually had three levels, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: You had the regular NES.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then you had the, I don't know, was it the action pack?
[SPEAKER_02]: The one that came with the light gun and the duck hunt in Mario Brothers.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then there was the, I don't remember what it was called, the robot pack or some other type of pack.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was the one with Gyromite.
[SPEAKER_01]: Right, and it had Rob the Robot as well.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_01]: And wasn't there one also with the power pad and duck hunt?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, there was.
[SPEAKER_01]: Years later, yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're right.
[SPEAKER_02]: The world class track meet.
[SPEAKER_02]: So hypothetically, couldn't Wii possibly be launching $199, $249?
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe $199, I don't know, system controller, virtual console points only, and $249, all that plus Wii Sports.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think they want to simplify it, and they're not going to try to do that, because their market is for new gamers.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're not going to try to confuse them with two different price points and stuff, and trying to get you to buy the more expensive system.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't think they're going to do that.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, they haven't done that with
[SPEAKER_01]: Any of their consoles, you know, anything recent.
[SPEAKER_01]: And just, you know, I wouldn't see them doing that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, comments from the chat room.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lots of interesting thoughts on the price point here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Funnydale says,
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if Microsoft can afford to drop it that low right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Next year, maybe.
[SPEAKER_02]: This year, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It still seems... Microsoft still has the whole high-definition thing to sell the consoles with, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't think they need to drop their console price.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't think they... Because they know they're not competing with Nintendo as far as
[SPEAKER_01]: Next Gen, Nintendo's in their own kind of game.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was that whole endorsement.
[SPEAKER_02]: Both companies, Microsoft and Sony, have practically said, sure, get a Nintendo, as long as you don't buy Microsoft, Sony, whatever the competitor is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sure, get a Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: Very interesting thought here.
[SPEAKER_00]: I agree with that, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Spirit Snare has a thought.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sky, the core console wasn't changed.
[SPEAKER_02]: Those were merely bundles.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a good point, but, you know, and somebody else said, DMN said, you guys forget those were accessories.
[SPEAKER_02]: True, but the Wii has an assortment of accessories as well to play with, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: You have the classic controller, the light gun.
[SPEAKER_02]: So why not some of these things?
[SPEAKER_00]: But I think the point is that that's not really right to compare it to the way Xbox is doing their bundle and the way that Nintendo, because Nintendo's is actually different stuff on the system itself.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can understand that.
[SPEAKER_02]: All I'm trying to say is could Nintendo launch two different Wii, one at $199 and one at $249 with different stuff?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, right?
[SPEAKER_00]: No matter what, they could do different bundles.
[SPEAKER_00]: I honestly think that the way
[SPEAKER_00]: If they want to keep it at $199, what they need to do is to have a pack with this particular thing, a pack with this particular thing, a pack with this particular thing.
[SPEAKER_00]: You pick the one that you want to get based on the types of games you like.
[SPEAKER_00]: And then...
[SPEAKER_00]: You can get special deal with this thing for another X amount of money to get all the other accessories coming to a total of $250.
[SPEAKER_02]: And how Nintendo would this be?
[SPEAKER_02]: Release like a blue pack and a red pack and a, I don't know, white pack or something?
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, they have a white, black, and blue.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I don't think it's going to get that crazy because I don't think they're going to complicate it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But that's a good thought, though, that, you know, there's all different types of ways Nintendo could do this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, we could hypothesize until the cows come home, but we won't know anything for sure until Nintendo confirms, which hopefully will be soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, what else is coming with the Wii?
[SPEAKER_01]: It's going to be the only console out there with a web browser built into it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, since maybe the Dreamcast?
[SPEAKER_02]: Just in the interest of disclosure here, I think there's a story coming up later on tonight about the PS3 interface has been shown and there was a web browser integrated in the PS3.
[SPEAKER_02]: So just, you know, big deal.
[SPEAKER_00]: And the Dreamcast web browser was not actually part of the system.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was a disk.
[SPEAKER_01]: True.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, well, whatever.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, goody, the PlayStation 3 web browser.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, you know what, though?
[SPEAKER_02]: I applaud this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Applause, applause, applause.
[SPEAKER_02]: Having the Opera browser here because it shows... You know, I think... Well, I was already really sold on this, but it definitely shows Nintendo is embracing online.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good job, Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not quite.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, right.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're not really embracing online because Metroid Prime 3, not online multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's a lot of their...
[SPEAKER_01]: Sort of getting it, but not quite 100% yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think Nintendo has an interesting enough thing going on with the whole controller aspect that Metroid doesn't need to be multiplayer yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why do that when Metroid 4 can be online multiplayer?
[SPEAKER_02]: Halo, the original, wasn't multiplayer, but then again, Xbox Live wasn't quite what it was at that point.
[SPEAKER_00]: You could, though, land it.
[SPEAKER_00]: We've done the four Xbox hookup LAN parties on Halo.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it doesn't mean that they couldn't, yeah, and it doesn't mean that you couldn't maybe later on, you know, upgrade it or add a, you know, an update.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, the Metroid Prime 3 Corruption, you know, special edition with online multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_01]: Or just, you know, was it Nintendo Connect 24 or whatever?
[SPEAKER_02]: Ion671 says, so you can pay $500 to surf the web on the PS3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, yeah, but here's the thing, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: Xbox 360, this is one thing they're kind of lacking right now, which is surprising, seeing as Microsoft had the web TV thing a while back, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm kind of surprised that 360 doesn't have a web browser yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a little surprising.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's not the end of the world.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can surf the web on my computer, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: And maybe this is what Microsoft realizes, is that why put a web browser in here?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because, you know...
[SPEAKER_02]: Most people surf the web on their computers.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I think it's kind of a neat feature.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's something kind of neat about having a website right there on the television.
[SPEAKER_02]: And think about some of those games that have websites accessible from within the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like I know this is a real weak example, but Phantasy Star on the GameCube, you kind of went on the Phantasy Star website and you could actually like read the forums and stuff from the GameCube.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know it's kind of a weak example, but you could supplement games with websites right on the TV, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: That'd be cool too.
[SPEAKER_01]: Text entry on those websites via the DS.
[SPEAKER_01]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_02]: Didn't the Opera browser on the DS, isn't that supposed to have handwriting recognition?
[SPEAKER_01]: I seem to remember seeing that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: But yeah, so it'd be pretty good.
[SPEAKER_02]: SpiritsNair says, Sky, but web TV sucked.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, true, but the technology's there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Funnydale says, So what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Microsoft can offer a web browser free on Xbox Live next week.
[SPEAKER_02]: True, but they haven't yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: They can, but they haven't.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tiger Claw says, Very true, Sky.
[SPEAKER_02]: Many websites have Flash games.
[SPEAKER_02]: So why not play the Flash games on the TV?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, maybe Microsoft doesn't want that because then they wouldn't be able to sell Bejeweled.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay, in Louisiana, the House unanimously passed, basically, HB 1381 on Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was a bill that applies the Miller obscenity test to video games, sort of like the whole games as porn tactic that's been going on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right.
[SPEAKER_00]: I got some information from Game Politics on this one.
[SPEAKER_00]: Actually, a few interesting quotes.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's a lot of people who are just really pissed off over this.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think it's just as stupid as I do, probably.
[SPEAKER_00]: One of the editors for the Daily Comet...
[SPEAKER_00]: stated, and I quote, Why does the government feel the need to parent children?
[SPEAKER_00]: Amen!
[SPEAKER_00]: Thank you!
[SPEAKER_00]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_00]: Few will be persuaded that violent video games or movies have a negative effect on children.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's only a game.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's only a movie.
[SPEAKER_00]: People are smart enough to distinguish the difference, some believe.
[SPEAKER_00]: As for me, I believe I can give better guidance to my children than Baton Rouge or Washington.
[SPEAKER_00]: But there's another funny one on here, though, that...
[SPEAKER_00]: It made me laugh.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was actually by the editor of the Home I Care Courier.
[SPEAKER_00]: It says, I could watch football from now until the cows come home, but I wouldn't be able to throw like Brett, I guess it's Favre, F-A-V-R-E.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't watch football, so I don't really care.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I could play Grand Theft Auto for the next 12 years.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't think I would be looking for policemen to murder or prostitutes to pimp.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's because, and let me phrase this correctly so that even the Solons in Baton Rouge can comprehend the message, it's just a game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm actually reading the text of the bill here, which you can access on GamePolitik's website.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just kind of reading what they want to add into the law here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Prohibited sales of video or computer games to minors.
[SPEAKER_02]: A. An interactive video or computer game should not be sold, leased, or rented to a minor if a tree or
[SPEAKER_02]: If the Trier of Facts determines all of the following.
1.
[SPEAKER_02]: The average person applying contemporary community standards would find that the video or computer game taken as a whole appeals to the minor's morbid interest in violence.
[SPEAKER_02]: Vague.
2.
[SPEAKER_02]: The game depicts violence in a manner patently offensive to prevailing standards in the adult community with respect to what is suitable for minors.
[SPEAKER_02]: Vague.
3.
[SPEAKER_02]: The game taken as a whole lacks serious literary, artistic, political or scientific value for minors.
[SPEAKER_02]: What the hell is that supposed to mean?
[SPEAKER_00]: It's just another... It's basically... It's another just attempt of the government trying to control children.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, basically trying to have control over how children are raised trying to do the parent's job for them so they grow up to be nice little, you know, mindless sheep for them to have them later in the future.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who's going to determine that?
[SPEAKER_02]: The game lacks serious literary, artistic, political, or scientific value for minors.
[SPEAKER_00]: They've got established standards.
[SPEAKER_00]: See, they're trying to apply something...
[SPEAKER_00]: is not applicable for our game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, but you can't even really apply this to movies or even books.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, who's to judge whether this is of literary or artistic value?
[SPEAKER_02]: How can you judge art?
[SPEAKER_02]: Art is not meant to be judged.
[SPEAKER_02]: Art is meant to be interpreted.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, apparently that's their interpretation of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it stinks.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, then again, you know, with the, there was, remember the whole outcry they were having with the tour of the statue David going around?
[SPEAKER_00]: Because it's nude.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's art!
[SPEAKER_00]: That was actually a big deal when I was in Alabama.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't get that.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a penis.
[SPEAKER_02]: Half of America's already seen one, at least.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the other half probably did see one already.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, no, that's what I meant.
[SPEAKER_02]: They've seen their own, or they've probably seen one, one way or another.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's the big deal?
[SPEAKER_00]: I sort of put that in the same category.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's the whole closed-minded censure of things that...
[SPEAKER_00]: Their version of inappropriateness, but I really, I really, really think that there is an ulterior motive to all this.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think that, I honestly, as much as we're seeing this coming, especially, and Republicans don't, you know, get all upset with me or anything, coming out of the Republican camp and coming out of the Democrats too, because, you know, we've got Hillary spearheading all this bullcrap.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, we've got our two major...
[SPEAKER_00]: and DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: Our chatroom is just lighting up, like line after line after line on this here right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've never seen the chatroom scroll so fast.
[SPEAKER_02]: BlackWolf makes the smart-ass comment, Africa has artistic value.
[SPEAKER_02]: The PlayStation 3 title that made most of us go, what the F is this?
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: SpiritSnare says, artistic?
[SPEAKER_02]: You need to play fucking Mario Paint, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, very interesting there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Funnydale says, to all of the gamers who say that if we just ignore Jack Thompson, he will then go away, this proves this is not true.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting thought.
[SPEAKER_02]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, he was also a chief witness at that.
[SPEAKER_00]: Did you notice that?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I didn't.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, it's a comment here.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I'm going to do another quote.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's from the Shreveport Times.
[SPEAKER_00]: It says, The fact that Jack Thompson was testifying in favor of the bill should immediately set off alarms.
[SPEAKER_00]: Thompson evokes no one so strongly as Frederick Wortham, a psychologist whose 1950s book, Seduction of the Innocent, led to the congressional hearings on the dangers of comic books.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_02]: more comments in the chat room here GS191, I'm tired of game politics the politicians will never get video games I say let them pass their stupid laws it's going to be us that's going to gain control and take out the laws in the long run
[SPEAKER_00]: Not if they are successful.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's my thought, guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: If this makes you mad, don't write us a letter.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I mean, we of course want your feedback.
[SPEAKER_02]: Go ahead and write us a letter.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you need to be writing your congressman a letter, especially if you're over the age of 18.
[SPEAKER_02]: And here, I'm going to start your letter for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dear Congressman, I am a registered voter.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then go ahead and express yourself cleanly, please.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's just for all the people who say, though, that we are...
[SPEAKER_00]: We're going to be in power.
[SPEAKER_00]: The younger generation is going to be the one to overthrow that.
[SPEAKER_00]: Imagine what's going to happen if they're successful in censoring what that generation sees.
[SPEAKER_02]: Isn't that what everyone said in the 60s?
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wasn't alive in the 60s.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, but I'm just saying, you know, you kind of look back on that whole, you know, hippie movement and everything, and I have a feeling they were saying the same thing.
[SPEAKER_00]: There was a lot more to it than that necessarily, the hippie movement.
[SPEAKER_00]: That was around a whole war and... Okay, so I'm making a very broad generalization.
[SPEAKER_00]: And people were fucking like bunnies.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_00]: But I'm serious.
[SPEAKER_00]: I honestly do think that that's their agenda.
[SPEAKER_00]: from what it's looking like, this is just my own little conspiracy theory here I think that, you know, honestly I think that they're afraid of having an open-minded youth about having people there who's going to question
[SPEAKER_00]: instead of just blindly follow their lead.
[SPEAKER_00]: They lose power if you don't blindly follow.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some folks in the chat room are saying that they're too young so they'll just write us a letter.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, that's fine, but here's a better thought.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you're too young, talk to somebody who is a registered voter.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can still have an impact.
[SPEAKER_02]: I say talk to your parents about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it would be great to talk to your parents about your thoughts on that.
[SPEAKER_00]: You can still write your congressman.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_00]: You can still do it.
[SPEAKER_00]: You can say, hey, I am X years old and by this election I will be registered to vote.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's very true.
[SPEAKER_02]: I imagine most of you guys that listen to this show... Block the vote.
[SPEAKER_00]: Remember that?
[SPEAKER_00]: Trying to get people who were just turning 18 who were kids to... Vote or P. Diddy will kill you?
[SPEAKER_00]: You know what I mean, though.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was the same thing.
[SPEAKER_00]: You can still write in.
[SPEAKER_00]: You can still get your voice out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, I'm going to end on this note because Roz, I think, just won the chat room here.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've got to keep it moving, but Roz says, Dear Jack Thompson, you are a giant enemy crab.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hit you in your weak spot for massive damage.
[SPEAKER_02]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ridge Racer.
[SPEAKER_02]: Roz, I love you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Moving on to another story.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hacking and cracking.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: On the XB360.
[SPEAKER_02]: What happened?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, they...
[SPEAKER_01]: They actually were able to, as I think a while back there was a video of them hacking the 360 to play backups of discs.
[SPEAKER_01]: And now they were successful on some of the 360s.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because the 360 comes with either one of two optical drives, either a Toshiba Samsung drive or a Hitachi drive.
[SPEAKER_01]: And if you have the Toshiba Samsung drive, well guess what?
[SPEAKER_01]: You can actually mod your firmware on the actual optical disk drive and be able to play backups.
[SPEAKER_01]: And basically what it does is it kind of works the same way that they did with the Xbox One firmware and their disk drives.
[SPEAKER_01]: It patches the response to the media check into the disk drive.
[SPEAKER_01]: So basically when you pop in a game, it will check, okay, is this a burnt disk?
[SPEAKER_01]: Is this a pressed disk from Microsoft?
[SPEAKER_01]: Is this a CD?
[SPEAKER_01]: What type of media am I reading?
[SPEAKER_01]: and, you know, usually if you have a DVD plus R or something like that, it's not going to play it if it's a game.
[SPEAKER_01]: So what this does is no matter what the hell you put into it, it replies back to the system saying, yep, we're good, play the game.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, yeah, right now they're working on a way to be able to get to work on the Hitachi drives.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, what do you think?
[SPEAKER_01]: Microsoft going to be happy about this?
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, basically, they've issued an official statement to warn the 360 owners about messing with their system, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_00]: Basically, they're saying the core security system has not been broken.
[SPEAKER_00]: However, on some Xbox 360 consoles, the authentication protocol between the optical disk drive and the console may be attacked via complex software and hardware modification, which could allow people to play illegally copied and modified games.
[SPEAKER_00]: Um, so, pretty much what they're talking about is, yeah, you do that, you void your warranty.
[SPEAKER_01]: Isn't that the classic response?
[SPEAKER_01]: Don't void your warranty!
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, here's another thing, too, that they're working on right now, is they're actually having multiple BIOSes on the chip, on the actual DVD drive, so, basically, the flip of switch, I want to play it on live.
[SPEAKER_01]: Flip the switch over, runs off the original thing, you can't play the, you know, the copy thing, but you can, um, you know, and they might not even be able to detect, you might be able to break that, so it can't detect what your firmware is on the, um,
[SPEAKER_01]: GK128 Mess with your 360s, say goodbye to live, bitch!
[SPEAKER_02]: and DMN says, Dear 360 owners, don't fuck with your firmware.
[SPEAKER_02]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ridge Racer.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, we're full of comedians tonight in Orange Launch Radio chat.
[SPEAKER_00]: Is that going to become our new cake or death?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the new inside, or not really inside joke, but line of the week that's going to just get beat into the ground until you're all sick of it, if you're not already.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: PlayStation 3 Pre-Orders at GameStop and EB Games
[SPEAKER_02]: A rumor is I guess what they're trying to do is go or try to avoid what happened with Xbox 360 where they were taking pre-orders for a long time and it was too many pre-orders to fill essentially.
[SPEAKER_02]: They didn't get enough systems and when they couldn't deliver people's systems until February or March, who got the flack for that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Microsoft?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: GameStop and EB Games did because why aren't you getting enough consoles?
[SPEAKER_02]: People maybe didn't really know where to place the blame.
[SPEAKER_02]: So GameStop and EB are thinking this time, okay, if we only open it up for a certain window, then folks, we won't have such a huge list.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: If people find out the day the GameStop's going to start taking orders, people are going to be lined up that morning.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think, you know, the Sony fanboys anyway, you know, say what you want about whether you're going to get or not get a PlayStation 3, but the rabid launch fans, there's enough of them where, you know, there'll be a line going out the door the day they start taking pre-orders.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I think this will help that situation a little bit, but it's not going to, if Sony can't produce the systems, it's going to be the same thing all over again.
[SPEAKER_01]: Also, their launch windows, like, their launch games suck.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, you never know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, anyways, we'll get to that later.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Moving right along, DarkSakura likes to kind of look around at different websites, including those overseas, and UK reaction to the price?
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, according, there's actually been an official price released for the UK in particular.
[SPEAKER_00]: They're releasing it, basically they're releasing it for 425 pounds for the 60 gig model, but there's not any type of word if they're getting the 20 gigabyte model.
[SPEAKER_00]: of course, what's the point since it has no HDMI?
[SPEAKER_00]: No Wi-Fi.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, unless you don't plan on having an HDTV in the next few years.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, this is funny, though, because in euros, it's 599 euros for the 60 gigabyte, which goes to 405 pounds.
[SPEAKER_00]: So actually, they're not getting it for that good of a deal.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, it's off a little bit, but still going to be a little bit more expensive than the general price in euros.
[SPEAKER_00]: They're really trying to push the Blu-ray thing.
[SPEAKER_00]: Their managing director for Sony UK, Ray McGuire, is basically going around saying, Oh, Blu-ray!
[SPEAKER_00]: Blu-ray player is 600 to 700 pounds.
[SPEAKER_00]: You're getting a big deal.
[SPEAKER_00]: Blu-ray, Blu-ray, Blu-ray.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, where was the Blu-ray movie on the E3 show floor?
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm wondering that myself.
[SPEAKER_00]: On top of that, they're...
[SPEAKER_00]: I think there's a lot of negative reaction to it just from the nature of his statement.
[SPEAKER_00]: The point is that most people don't realize what they're actually getting with a PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's like, no, they're getting something that's not going to be what you're trying to make it out to be.
[SPEAKER_00]: And really, it's still going to be more expensive there than it is here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Very interesting comment in our chatroom from Funnydale.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, quick griping about the price of the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: People pay $500 for a fucking iPod.
[SPEAKER_02]: They pay $500 for a damn video card.
[SPEAKER_02]: They will pay $600 for a PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: I say, yeah, there are going to be people that will pay the $600 for a PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: I will.
[SPEAKER_02]: These are the same retards that bought DVHS also.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just because I have to have every system, I will pay $600 for the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not going to be happy about it, but I will do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the thing is, the iPod, if you want to make that comparison, didn't really achieve huge amounts of success until they released cheaper models that still got the job done.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_00]: I never bought an iPod.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you did the free iPod thing, right?
[SPEAKER_00]: I got a free iPod.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I'm sure they'll do a free PS3 if you want to go that route.
[SPEAKER_00]: They're already out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a controversial thing, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: If that's what makes it work for you, then go for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But...
[SPEAKER_00]: I like Bobby's comment.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, Bobby going for the jugular there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki paid $600 for an Xbox 360, didn't he?
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, that was $700 for a 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: So why all the PS3 hate?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because you think you're going to be paying $300 more if you end up going eBay or what?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, I just don't.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's not really any games for me that I want to get right at launch.
[SPEAKER_01]: Are you not going to get it at launch?
[SPEAKER_01]: I might not.
[SPEAKER_01]: I have to see what their launch games are going to be.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's really going to determine it for me because it's all about the games.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_01]: If they don't have that many...
[SPEAKER_01]: Good games at launch or if it's not what I like, I'll wait.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right now, I'm about an 80% yes on it because I know I can benefit from the Blu-ray being an HDTV owner and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: And again, a large part of why I'm saying this is because I have to have all the consoles.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want them all.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I realize everybody's not like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I say that now and you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, all the hype will start a month before and you'll be like, I have to have one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Paris Hilton has one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why can't I have one?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, it's just people are looking at like a game system.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, they're not seeing the long life that they might see in something else.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's just still.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's a comment from Ota G, who I haven't read anything from tonight in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_02]: OrangeLaunchReady.com, click on chat.
[SPEAKER_02]: The price of the PlayStation 3 isn't the problem.
[SPEAKER_02]: The fact that Sony hasn't justified it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_02]: Debate, Debate
[SPEAKER_02]: Mother 3 is going to get an English translation in Europe.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, hooray for Europe, but if you're in the United States, you're still not happy because E3 went by and still no Mother 3 announcement for the US.
[SPEAKER_02]: Import the bitch.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's no lockout guard.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, there's no region differences on these.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just import it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you're going to have to pay the higher price.
[SPEAKER_02]: Import!
[SPEAKER_00]: Amazon UK!
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, just to make it clear, the official Nintendo magazine in the UK is saying that it will come out in December in Europe and it's going to be released for the Game Boy Advance edition.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry, Game Boy Advance.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, you're right though.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you want to pay the extra bucks there, or import it through UK, just pay the slightly higher shipping fees, at least you get your English translation.
[SPEAKER_02]: So maybe it's not all bad news.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I know a damn lot of people that will do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I think Nintendo of America is kind of... I mean, I guess all the money goes to Nintendo in the end, but I think Nintendo of America at least, at least, if nothing else, print...
[SPEAKER_02]: A low run and do what you did with the electro plankton.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sell it on your website or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just release it in stores and don't advertise for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just can't believe something like this won't come out here, especially when an English translation is now done.
[SPEAKER_02]: But freaking Dr. Sudoku out there on store shelves.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't get it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Baffles me.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's because people are crazy.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm surprised how much...
[SPEAKER_01]: I remember seeing Sudoku in magazines and going, wow, I have to do math?
[SPEAKER_01]: Fuck that.
[SPEAKER_02]: They used to have a different name.
[SPEAKER_02]: They weren't always called Sudoku here in America.
[SPEAKER_02]: They used to print those in the penny press publications as crypto numbers or something like that.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're all over the place now.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now that I'm looking for them, I'm like, holy crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's the honest justification for Dr. Sudoku on the Game Boy Advance or whatever is because Nintendo wants to go after everyone, not just gamers, and
[SPEAKER_02]: I've seen it in the workplace.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've seen people that are not your typical types of gamers, you know, mothers and folks that you don't typically think of as gamers bring in their Sudoku magazines and they'll play Sudoku on break.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is a really good exercise for the brain, the whole brain training thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I can see why this is justified in Nintendo's eyes, but you know,
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just saying, come on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why give us this out there and not Mother 3?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't get it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I still think Nintendo's going to announce it later.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think there's going to be another Nintendo press conference.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, there has to be because they're going to announce all the Wii stuff and I think they're going to drop some of these bombshells too.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'm still hopeful Mother 3's coming to the US.
[SPEAKER_02]: But what do I know?
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: What do you know?
[SPEAKER_02]: Not much.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_00]: We have Cossacks 2 Battle for Europe, Jill Dozer for the GBA, Hitman Blood Money for a whole bunch of stuff, Rockstar Games presents Table Tennis, Rush for Berlin on PC, Super Princess Peach on the DS, About Damn Time, it's the PMS game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, if you want to control an overly emotional woman, have fun with Super Princess Peach.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't you know you can't ever do that?
[SPEAKER_00]: Of course you can't.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks to the wonder of technology of video games, now you can.
[SPEAKER_00]: So you think.
[SPEAKER_00]: Heart, love ya.
[SPEAKER_00]: And since this is the only other one on here, I'll go ahead and say it.
[SPEAKER_00]: On the 31st, Talk Man on PSP is coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Heroes of Might and Magic 5
[SPEAKER_01]: I know a lot of people like my magic, so don't be knocking.
[SPEAKER_01]: and then, of course, Rogue Trooper on PlayStation 2 and Xbox.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then my favorite for the week, Jaws Unleashed, where you get to play the shark and get to dismember divers.
[SPEAKER_01]: Finally!
[SPEAKER_01]: How long ago was that game supposed to come out?
[SPEAKER_01]: A long time ago.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't care how cheesy this game is.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's like Echo the Dolphin with rabies.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like snakes on a plane.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's the big deal with that movie?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because it's snakes on a freaking plane.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, you know, Jaws, the game, yeah, it might suck, but it's Jaws.
[SPEAKER_02]: You get to be the shark.
[SPEAKER_01]: You get to eat people.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: You get to destroy boats.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's Grand Theft Auto with fish.
[SPEAKER_00]: Shark edition.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, but anyways.
[SPEAKER_00]: Shark is tasty.
[SPEAKER_01]: And also SteamBot Chronicles is supposed to be coming out on PlayStation 2, which is eh.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, after all, they've got a mech known as Bumpy Trots, which sounds like a real bad ass disease or something like that.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've got to keep it moving because we've got a lot of stories and we're moving kind of slow tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lots of stuff to say since it's post E3 here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, was there any other release dates?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then Loki, tell us about a big name in the online community, Major Nelson.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's got his own little podcast over there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I'm sorry, blogcast.
[SPEAKER_02]: They don't use the word podcast in Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's got a blogcast.
[SPEAKER_02]: But what's he saying about the PlayStation 3?
[SPEAKER_01]: He's saying that their online service is not going to be free.
[SPEAKER_02]: And how does he know this?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, he's basically going off the slides that they had on during the press conference and when they were mentioning free things.
[SPEAKER_01]: Matchmaking and online play were not mentioned I think he says so basically it's going to be an equivalent to Xbox Live's silver level of service right now so you know basically you get to talk to people you know and you do chat and stuff but you can't play games against them for free which you know I don't know I get into the whole thing where I get kind of frustrated with
[SPEAKER_01]: Sony copying everybody anyways.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, if online play was free though, it would certainly help justify the price because they could say, hey, you're having to pay $50 extra on Xbox.
[SPEAKER_01]: He is right when he says that stuff wasn't mentioned on the free service.
[SPEAKER_01]: Free service stuff, video chat, latest info, friends list, ranking, account management, player profile, voice messaging, and text messaging.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't see gameplay on there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, moving on, another interesting story on the PlayStation 3, some stealthy video at E3 was shot, and I guess one of those demo rooms for the media only, I guess we weren't cool enough to get invited, but Joystick was, or somebody that ratted to Joystick because they posted some videos on YouTube of the PlayStation 3 interface, and guess what?
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks very similar to the PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: PS2 wasn't very interesting
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess that's true.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe simplicity is key.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess it makes a lot of sense when you think about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But what's interesting is that it really does kind of borrow from the PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a user's menu where I guess you can sign on as different users, a web browser, which we brought up earlier, and apparently you're going to be able to do multi-windows or tabs or something like that in there as well, and also a friends list, and there'll be voice and video chatting and gaming if you wanted to do that as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you want to check that out, I'm sure you can find it on YouTube very quickly or it's in Joysticks Archives.
[SPEAKER_02]: Check it out.
[SPEAKER_02]: What do you guys think about the interface?
[SPEAKER_01]: I think it's lazy like everything else that they do.
[SPEAKER_01]: Really?
[SPEAKER_01]: You know...
[SPEAKER_01]: I was talking with my friends at work the other day and just basically ripping off... I'm a huge Sony fanboy.
[SPEAKER_01]: I have a PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, I had a PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_01]: I have two PSPs.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, so, you know, don't get me wrong.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't hate Sony.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just, I don't like how they steal everybody's ideas, though.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's like nothing is original for them.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then they try to come out and, like, deny that they've ripped off these ideas.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, look at the PlayStation 1, for example.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, came out, doesn't have analog, doesn't have rumble features.
[SPEAKER_01]: Nintendo 64 comes out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Has analog, has rumble.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, look!
[SPEAKER_01]: Look, now we have the DualShock!
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, come on!
[SPEAKER_01]: Retarded!
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, now they come out with their controller design.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, by the way, look, now it has tilt features in it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, now ours has tilt features in it.
[SPEAKER_01]: And now it's copy Xbox Live, but not quite.
[SPEAKER_01]: They can copy, but they can never get it quite right.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'd be interested to see how things, you know, work out for them.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm kind of wary on their online service, because PlayStation 2's online sucked.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, to be honest.
[SPEAKER_02]: At least it was online, unlike Mr. GameCube, who had one game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: First, you GameCube.
[SPEAKER_00]: Paperweight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, wait a minute, though.
[SPEAKER_00]: PlayStation 3, paperweight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, okay, I thought you said GameCube, because I'm like, wait a minute, wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_00]: No.
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_00]: It's got a lot of attention in the past, but it hasn't gotten a lot of attention lately.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I am talking about nothing other than Weebles Stuff.
[SPEAKER_00]: W-E-E-B-L-S-Stuff.com Yes, it's the home of Badger, Badger, Badger, and Magical Trevor, and Kenya.
[SPEAKER_00]: The most recent one is Crabs, which I find incredibly hilarious.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do they have weak points?
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, it's about a mouthful of crabs.
[SPEAKER_00]: And there's lots of bleeding in it, which sort of makes me think of the whole YAY!
[SPEAKER_00]: thing from Rejected.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: There also is the home of Weeble and Bob, which are like two eggs that go, and they're speaking.
[SPEAKER_00]: And the last one was pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, go check them out.
[SPEAKER_00]: And make sure that you look for the ninja one.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know where it is, but the ninja one is somewhere on the site.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do it now.
[SPEAKER_00]: Right now.
[SPEAKER_00]: Mouthful of Crabs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Historically accurate, nonetheless.
[SPEAKER_02]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Those jokes will never get over.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's talk some movies.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've got a lot of movie and TV stuff, just a barrage of stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, start us off.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, let's start off with a really bad idea.
[SPEAKER_01]: Bad idea.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's called... Jerry Rockhammer has just signed on to produce a movie called Game Boys.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, it's not the true life story of the portable Nintendo system.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's a sci-fi action movie that's basically, the story revolves around two 30-year-old video game junkies recruited by the Department of Homeland Security, which is a joke anyways, to lead a geeky army of gamers in a battle against creatures that have come to life from a video game they have mastered.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sounds like an episode of X-Files to me.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, because I think they cover that.
[SPEAKER_01]: What I'm really surprised is that Homeland Security does not have a contingency plan for that type of scenario.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, come on!
[SPEAKER_02]: Going from a really bad idea to a really good idea.
[SPEAKER_02]: Metal Gear Solid movie was confirmed at E3 in case you missed it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Konami had a great parody.
[SPEAKER_02]: They put out the show Maybe in response to the show Daily.
[SPEAKER_02]: But something you don't want to miss in there, the show Maybe says, In a late-breaking surprise announcement, director Hideo Kojima revealed that his most famous creation, Metal Gear Solid, is getting the live-action treatment.
[SPEAKER_02]: He already said hell no to Uebol, so don't worry about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But he did say, I've received many offers to adapt Metal Gear Solid.
[SPEAKER_02]: It has taken a long time, but we have finally settled on an arrangement.
[SPEAKER_02]: False facts aside, a movie project is underway.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have finalized a Class A contract with a party in Hollywood.
[SPEAKER_02]: But that's about all the details you get.
[SPEAKER_02]: No directors, no stars, no dates.
[SPEAKER_02]: Paul Sams, Blizzard
[SPEAKER_01]: Dungeons & Dragons
[SPEAKER_01]: Apparently, the group that they're working with is called Legendary, and they want to basically make this really big budget movie.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've never heard of Legendary, ever.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, when I think of big blockbuster movies, I don't think, hmm, Legendary.
[SPEAKER_01]: No.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, who the hell is Legendary?
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, I've never heard of them.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't really, I follow games, not movies.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, and I should really be following movies.
[SPEAKER_01]: After all, I do work at a goddamn movie distributor.
[SPEAKER_01]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hopefully it doesn't suck.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, I guess it's going to be Warner is working with them.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, Warner I've heard of.
[SPEAKER_02]: So there you have it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, I think I have heard of Legendary, come to think of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think I've seen that little animation at the beginning.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm sure they've done good stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: When you think about movies, you think DreamWorks.
[SPEAKER_01]: You don't think of the small company that put it out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Just, you know...
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's not like big movie studios haven't put out stinkers before.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: This isn't quite a movie, but DarkSakura, an interesting idea nonetheless.
[SPEAKER_00]: They're planning on doing an Animal Crossing, as it is in Japan, Dobutsu no Mori animated movie in Japan in December.
[SPEAKER_00]: To be out in December.
[SPEAKER_02]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm guessing it's not live action.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's why I said animated.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Missed that part.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's no real information about if it's actually going to have a plot, because really the game has no plot.
[SPEAKER_00]: You paid off your house drama.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I would hope a movie would have a plot, but is the plot going to be you run around the village and run errands and deliver mail?
[SPEAKER_02]: There's got to be something.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think it's going to be, oh, tragedy has hit your forest, and blah, blah, band together, save, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_02]: The man is trying to bulldoze Animal Forest, you know?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because Animal Forest, right, is the translation in Japan, right?
[SPEAKER_00]: Right.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think that the Japanese DS one was called Aedeo Doubutsu no Mori, I think it was.
[SPEAKER_00]: I have to think.
[SPEAKER_00]: But at any rate, the director for the movie will be Shimura Joji, who worked on Master Keaton and Shin Angyou Onshi.
[SPEAKER_00]: Sorry, I'm all tongue-tied today because I'm all bleh.
[SPEAKER_00]: But Nintendo's talked before, though, that they want to get in the animation business.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think the Animal Crossing is going to be a really good way for them to bring that goal together because it was actually stated by the former president of Nintendo, Yamauchi Hiroshi, stating that they were trying to put funds together to create an animated film project.
[SPEAKER_00]: So maybe that's this in particular.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_02]: Spirit Snare in our chat room says, what did he say?
[SPEAKER_02]: Animal Crossing live action would be a WTF.
[SPEAKER_02]: It would be more like furry crossing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ew.
[SPEAKER_00]: They do a claymation.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, and here you go, Loki, and this would explain where I've seen the legendary pictures before.
[SPEAKER_02]: GK128 posted a little linky in our chat room to the profile on Internet Movie Database, and here you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: They did Batman Begins and Superman Returns.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, well... You want to take back what you said before?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a little bit better.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, there you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if you were in the midst of writing an angry email to Loki, we got it cleared up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, legendary pictures, okay by us now.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, they get to make a thumbs up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki's bad.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like I said, see, you think Warner though.
[SPEAKER_01]: Warner and DC, you don't think legendary when you hear of those films.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Try to defend yourself best you can.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just giving you a hard time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, this isn't about a game turning into a TV show, but it's about games showing up on a TV show, yes?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: A show that I am not watching this year.
[SPEAKER_01]: Me neither.
[SPEAKER_01]: It makes it a little tough.
[SPEAKER_01]: But apparently on The Apprentice last week, they did a kind of a competition to design the best Xbox 360 display in Walmart.
[SPEAKER_01]: and from what I hear, both of them sucked really, really bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: From what I read on the internet, one team didn't finish in time and they were missing something that held their tent up so it was like falling over and they won anyway because the other one was so freaking bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the review team apparently recognized what they were trying to go for and liked it better.
[SPEAKER_02]: One thing I want to point out though, some folks were saying, oh, this is why Jay Allard wasn't at E3 because he showed up in this week's Apprentice.
[SPEAKER_02]: These Apprentice things are taped long in advance.
[SPEAKER_02]: About a month ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually longer than that.
[SPEAKER_02]: This season of The Apprentice was taped in November.
[SPEAKER_02]: So these boosts that they were designing were for the launch, most likely.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it has nothing to do with why he was or wasn't at E3.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just want to point that out because some folks are forgetting that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like Survivor, all that crap is taped long in advance.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, well, apparently, you know, whatever the case may be, the winner, I guess, their displays were displayed in 1,500 Walmart stores.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, I haven't seen a 360 display in, you know, Walmarts.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Were they that bad?
[SPEAKER_01]: Apparently so.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, one more story for this part of the show, and then we're going to go to a little break.
[SPEAKER_02]: And this has to do with the Booth Boys of E3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now you hear a lot about Booth Babes, but with Booth Babes essentially getting, you know, forcing to tone down a little bit this year, and now we have news on Booth Boys.
[SPEAKER_02]: And this comes from a blog called Wonderland is the name of the blog.
[SPEAKER_02]: The author here wrote down their list of the top boys of E3, and in the list here they have
[SPEAKER_02]: Peter in the Namco booth, who has a little pack head there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Brian from Brothers in Arms there, ready for action, a little military guy there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see who else is in here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Another, just a couple of Webzen folks there.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Poker Dealer over there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Martin Lung, the video game pianist.
[SPEAKER_00]: I actually got a video of him.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, he was a very talented guy.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got to meet him.
[SPEAKER_00]: He actually blindfolded himself with someone's t-shirt.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fatality, who had his own booth this year, and taking the show though, the number one booth guy according to this blog, Adam West.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, what I thought was interesting is that there was another website who ran a story on booth guys, and they distinctly showed a picture of the guy at Nokia's booth.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I guess amongst all those girls in the white t-shirts and stuff, there was actually a guy who was a pretty good-looking guy that was there at the booth.
[SPEAKER_02]: I remember we saw him.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't remember seeing him.
[SPEAKER_01]: Or someone mentioned him.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think Miklatov mentioned him.
[SPEAKER_01]: Probably, probably.
[SPEAKER_02]: Leave it to him to point out something like that, definitely.
[SPEAKER_02]: But no, I totally missed it.
[SPEAKER_02]: My thought was when I first saw it, maybe he was there to... He just worked for the company and just happened to be pretty good looking.
[SPEAKER_02]: But maybe he was in there amongst all the women.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't spend time in Engage's booth except to walk through it to get around the masses of people watching the Metal Gear Solid 4 trailer at Konami.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_01]: Plus they have that mist coming down, so if you're hot, you're just like, ah, mist.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know they have those Namco hats at the Namco store?
[SPEAKER_00]: The Pac-Man hats.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want one for my birthday.
[SPEAKER_00]: You can buy them.
[SPEAKER_00]: They're $30.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want one for my birthday.
[SPEAKER_00]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_00]: I want a giant puka.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, that's going to do it for this half of the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll be back in a little bit with Part B, which will include news about Final Fantasy VII Remake, more PlayStation 3 news, and much, much more right after this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and is podcast to the world twice a week stay tuned to our podcast feed for the conclusion of this week's Orange Lounge Radio