[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, we are here live at Foname 2006, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're taping our podcast here in front of, you know, dozens and dozens of people.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dozens and dozens of people.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what though, there's more people in here now than listened to the very first episode of Orange Lounge Radio, so it's alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Technically there's dozens of people in the other room in front of us.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, listening to the rock concert, so it counts.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, my name is Rob Roberts, you might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_04]: Joining me as always, say hello to Dark Sakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yo.
[SPEAKER_04]: And what are you dressed up as today, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_07]: Temari from Naruto, only in the manga so far.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's cosplaying today, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_04]: And isn't, though, the Naruto thing kind of played out when it comes to cosplay?
[SPEAKER_07]: It isn't when you only have a week to make your costume.
[SPEAKER_04]: Excuses, excuses.
[SPEAKER_04]: Next year, you need to... Next year is going to be a lot.
[SPEAKER_04]: This dude's got an interdict costume back there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Tim is always the best.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, how is that?
[SPEAKER_07]: We have our Starblazers costumes.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also say hello to Tech Master Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: So this is actually the second time we're recording the intro.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks to Tech Master Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that's okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Through the magic of radio, it'll all be brought together.
[SPEAKER_05]: At least we figured that out about 10 minutes in and not all the way in.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like an interview I did at E3 a couple years ago with Jason Enos.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: I still hate you for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki asked Jason Enos.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jason Enos is the guy who produces the DDR games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Asked him point blank what he thinks about In the Groove.
[SPEAKER_04]: and the answer's lost forever thanks to yours truly.
Whoops!
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, anyway, we like to start off the show talking about our gaming week and what we've been playing.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, DarkSakura, what kind of stuff have you been playing this week on the game scene?
[SPEAKER_07]: I played Metal Slug 5, big shock to everybody, on Friday.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have they increased the graphics yet on Metal Slug?
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_07]: But you can shoot more people and stab people and get heavy machine gun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cool death.
[SPEAKER_07]: More often.
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently they have Metal Slug 6 in the e-gaming room, so I have to go check that out later.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right on.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I played Ragnarok online, I played World of Warcraft, I'm still level 7, go me.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then I played some Kingdom Hearts, and I've played a little bit of everything.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Dana's still playing Uno.
[SPEAKER_07]: Uno.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've been tempted to go back to World of Warcraft a little bit.
[SPEAKER_07]: You should.
[SPEAKER_07]: Be a noob with me.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't want to play two MMOs.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm playing two MMOs.
[SPEAKER_04]: My link shell on Final Fantasy XI is going to hate me if I don't play more and get up to level 70 so I can do Dynamis with them.
[SPEAKER_07]: But also, we got another pinball machine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ooh, what'd you get?
[SPEAKER_07]: Johnny Mnemonic, which pisses me off because we were supposed to have a Doctor Who.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, please tell me the Johnny Mnemonic table is not as crappy as the movie was.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's supposed to be a pretty good table.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was too upset with it to look at it.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkNight2000 DarkNight2000
[SPEAKER_05]: New Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: And played a little bit of Ridge Racer 6, which is really cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then, of course, Ghost Recon Advanced Warfighter on the 360 because, yeah, it was fun shooting people.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let me guess, easy achievement points, huh?
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki's an achievement points whore.
[SPEAKER_05]: But then, I think that's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_05]: A little bit bejeweled just because we have it now.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know why I bought that game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nellie likes it more than I do.
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: I bought it for you.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, see?
[SPEAKER_07]: For everyone hearing only half of this conversation, we've got Nellie looking a little bit upset.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or a little bit WTF.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, so anyways, yeah, that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, my gaming week's been interesting because I actually am playing a sports game, which if you know me, I don't really get into a lot of sports titles because, you know, I don't get mad.
[SPEAKER_04]: And yeah, the last like sport game I really got into is probably Blades of Steel.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I'll tell you what, there's a great sports game out for the 360 right now that I'm having a lot of fun with.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Rockstar Table Tennis.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, that's funny because I thought you said sports and table tennis in the same sentence.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who would have thought that Rockstar, who made these Grand Theft Auto games, would make such a fun little sports title?
[SPEAKER_04]: I like it because it's really easy to pick up.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's easy to kind of get into it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's got a really good training mode with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: The only downside is that I would have liked... It's table tennis?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it's fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: It didn't have any character creation.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm wondering how they have time to make games when they're busy being sued.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who, Rockstar?
[SPEAKER_04]: But they're not going to get sued over table tennis.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can't.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's no... Unless there's a hidden sex scene.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm suing them over table tennis.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, what if there's a hidden sex scene?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because you know what girls can do with ping pong balls.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, but I don't think that's in there, so forget it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I've been having a lot of fun with it, and it's really easy to pick up, and the online mode plays pretty well.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was actually playing against some guy on the East Coast this morning, and it was cool because I haven't really played a lot of games on Xbox where people have been nice to talk to, because if you play Halo 2, you get a lot of little kids on there going, I'm going to kick your ass.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, but on table tennis, I had some pleasant conversation.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because if you say I'm going to kick your ass in table tennis, that sounds retarded.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, no, the guy asked me if I actually played real table tennis or if I was just playing the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_04]: He probably plays real table tennis.
[SPEAKER_04]: He does.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, my God, they made a game for me, finally.
[SPEAKER_04]: He told me he plays real table tennis, and I'm like, this must bug the hell out of you that you can't control the characters.
[SPEAKER_05]: All those people that play table tennis and own a 360, the demographic has finally been realized.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what's great about it, though, is it's cheap.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's relatively cheap for a 360 title, and it's fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: I liked it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's definitely something you guys should rent.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it's not going to be a game for everybody, but rent it, check it out, read the reviews, see if it's something that sounds like you'd be interested in, and I think you'd be surprised.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or wait and buy Hitman, which also came out the week after, which is probably a far superior game.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's killing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's get into some news.
[SPEAKER_04]: We only have a little bit of time here.
[SPEAKER_04]: We want to talk about the Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, last week on the program, we made a bold prediction stating that October 18th would be the release date for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Loki, remind us real quick for the crowd here who may not have heard the show, why did we come to an October 18th speculated date?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, a couple things.
[SPEAKER_05]: First off, we have a few dates actually from three or four different publishers right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: and S&K, THQ, and God, I can't remember the last one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyways, they've all agreed that the date is going to... Well, they have games coming out on October 11th and also October 18th.
[SPEAKER_05]: And usually, you know, you have games come out before the release date and on the release date.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, when you say we have dates...
[SPEAKER_05]: You're talking about your distributor?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: The other thing is that October 18th happens to mark the anniversary of the original Nintendo Entertainment System.
[SPEAKER_05]: What a nice way to celebrate the virtual console with the 8-bit downloads, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course, and so of course it makes perfect sense that they're going to release it on the anniversary because Nintendo likes doing things like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now by itself that doesn't seem like compelling evidence, but when you consider that you've got three publishers who've all targeted the same date and put it in the distributor system, that's too much of a coincidence to ignore.
[SPEAKER_04]: and you know I read another story on the internet this week that was from I think a British site that was talking about they're anticipating the release of the Wii to be November 20th over there because I guess Red Steel showed up and some computer over there is November 20th which is a confirmed launch title and typically there's a one month delay between US and Europe so you roll one month back from November 20th and you're just barely there within that same time frame so makes a lot of sense
[SPEAKER_04]: Now granted, take this with a grain of salt, somebody called into the show last week who has ties with Nintendo who said, nope, October 18th can't be the date, we haven't seen enough of it here, but the coincidences keep piling up, don't they, Loki?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, because Konami also gave us just this week information about Elebits and...
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, funny enough, it's coming out on the 18th.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of October.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: More and more coincidences.
[SPEAKER_04]: What about prices?
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you guys get info on prices?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, we're actually THQ on their two games, both the SpongeBob Creature from the Krusty Krab and Avatar The Last Airbender.
[SPEAKER_05]: Both those games are going to be priced at $49.99.
[SPEAKER_05]: It seems to be keeping the same price points that you'd see now in current generation titles, but hopefully they'll go down a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, first party titles typically run a little cheaper than third parties though, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Usually.
[SPEAKER_04]: So possibly we might have Mario Galaxy for $39?
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_04]: Zelda Twilight Princess, $39?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: If they can milk more money out of Zelda, I think they'll charge $49.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't you?
[SPEAKER_04]: Definitely.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Takahashi Keita Katamari Damashii
[SPEAKER_04]: That guy is kind of eccentric, isn't he?
[SPEAKER_04]: A little.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's like, I'm not going to do video games anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to go design playground equipment for children.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, a quote of his is, I'm not really interested in the Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't think a controller should have that much influence on the enjoyment of games.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, he's basically going on saying he understands that, yeah, they're excited.
[SPEAKER_07]: The controller will allow this to happen and this to happen, but they're putting too much emphasis on the controller.
[SPEAKER_07]: He has also confirmed that he is no longer working on any Katamari Damacy games.
[SPEAKER_07]: However, Namco is releasing more without him.
[SPEAKER_07]: And if the PSP one is any indication, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, I could agree with that, though, that, you know, right now it looks like the Wii is all emphasizing on the motion.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, you know, that's a selling point.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you think about Nintendo, when they first showed the DS, they had a lot of touch-heavy things that were going into that.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it seemed like Nintendo was going to whore the touchscreen.
[SPEAKER_04]: And to an extent, the launch titles did.
[SPEAKER_04]: But now it's settled down a little bit, and you look at a game like New Super Mario Bros., it's a perfect balance for the DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: And so I think the Wii will go that route, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, he did make another semi-announcement, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ooh, what's that?
[SPEAKER_07]: About what he's doing next.
[SPEAKER_07]: He says, all I can say is it'll be on a next-gen console, and it will be fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's all I can say.
[SPEAKER_04]: So he is doing games still.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's doing games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Didn't he say he wasn't going to do games?
[SPEAKER_04]: He's going to do Playground Designer Tycoon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Playground of Doom.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sim Playground.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, well, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, let's talk about the PlayStation 3 for a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, no, this has to do with the Wii, too, doesn't it, Loki?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, there was a survey done for Fumitsu Magazine, which they were basically polling their readers to which next-gen system they were looking forward to.
[SPEAKER_05]: And interesting enough, the Wii pretty much won out.
[SPEAKER_05]: 73% of the vote was towards the Wii, with PS3 coming in second at 22.6%, and the 360 only getting a measly 4.4%.
[SPEAKER_05]: One of the things, though, that they were also questioning was the price of the system.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's quite funny that most of the readers of Fumitsu found that the PS3 was way too damn expensive, and even they wouldn't pay for that.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I find that kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's interesting that the Xbox is trailing so much in Japan, and yet it seems to, after E3, the kind of general feeling I have is it seems to have...
[SPEAKER_04]: All the inertia here in this country right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, the Wii did such a huge showing too, but it's definitely a different order here in the US.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, after having spoken with a few of my friends in the UK, I've only talked to one person who has any excitement at all about the PS3.
[SPEAKER_07]: Everything has been Wii, Wii, Wii, Wii all the way home.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you know, I think part of that might be because Nintendo didn't make a whole lot of promises in the outset, but PlayStation 3, you know, last year at E3, Sony came out and said all these promises.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, we're going to have two HDMI ports, we're going to do all this stuff, and here's some games that didn't even come back the next year.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, so I think Sony's press conference felt a lot more like, hmm, hmm, hmm, let down.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whereas, you know, Nintendo's press conference was kind of like, hmm, hmm, hmm, you know, kind of a little more.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was all Zelda.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, the audience just said Super Smash Brothers Brawl.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, that's kind of stole the show there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, speaking of which, who saw VG Cats lately?
[SPEAKER_04]: What did they do in that?
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, it had a snake sneaking up in the box behind Mario and going...
[SPEAKER_04]: It was like blood, decapitation?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh yeah, it was blood and decapitation.
[SPEAKER_07]: Then Kirby's like, uh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, we've got to keep them moving.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've got 30 minutes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, the PlayStation 3, now this could be very good for them.
[SPEAKER_04]: If they see something popular, they ought to do something just like it, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to have downloadable games just like Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what we're thinking right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's actually a job posting that showed up on Craigslist.
[SPEAKER_04]: That game company, that's the name of them, that game company, they're looking for a superstar engineer with a strong graphics background to develop an unannounced downloadable title for the PlayStation 3 launch in November.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there it is right there on Craigslist that they're doing some type of
[SPEAKER_04]: Downloadable title that's going to be available on the launch.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now I guess some IGN who picked up this story actually contacted somebody that worked for the game company and found out that they are going to be having a service that has downloadable casual games just like Xbox Live Arcade and it's going to be available on the launch day of the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, the game is going to be just like their current free web game called Flow, that I guess has a lot of addictive qualities about it, although I've never played it, so I couldn't tell you.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, not a really big surprise there that Sony's going to be doing something similar to the Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nintendo's kind of doing it too, just in a different way with a virtual console, but they've also said before that they're going to allow folks to come up with their own stuff, not just classic 8-bit titles.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although I would like to see some of those horrible Mario ROM hacks show up on the virtual console.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that would be fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, what else about PlayStation 3?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, the first PS3s off the production line are actually going to be the ones for the UK.
[SPEAKER_05]: That could be good or bad, actually, because, well, anyways, this was confirmed by the Sony Computer Entertainment president of Europe, and also he happens to be the CEO, David Reeves.
[SPEAKER_05]: He confirmed that the first PS3s off the production line will be the PAL units, and
[SPEAKER_05]: What's kind of interesting about that is usually the first units off the line are the ones that are the buggiest.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that's funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, shifting gears a little bit, moving away from the PlayStation 3 for a minute.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank God.
[SPEAKER_04]: As I mentioned before, we kind of started here as a music-based station and then kind of grew into other video games.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's been some news lately on Guitar Hero, possibly making a move to the arcade.
[SPEAKER_04]: There was kind of a post that was floating around some of the big Bomani forums talking about that in the Trocadero, of all places, there is a prototype machine for playing Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's actually being manned by live people, and what they do is they just take your money and then you get to play it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, I don't know if they were trying to make money off of PlayStation 2, but supposedly the people who were running the thing were saying...
[SPEAKER_04]: that someone wants to see if the game has viability as an arcade machine.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that could be interesting considering we have a lot of arcades here that already have guitar freaks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Couldn't they just say, oh, the guitar freak's successful?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, since we copied them, why not just copy them in the arcade?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, wait a minute, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: In Japan there was also an Unjama Lami arcade game.
[SPEAKER_07]: There was also Namco had a guitar game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I still disagree with you, because I think in certain arcades, I think there's a lot of room where Guitar Hero can deliver that Guitar Freaks can't, especially when it comes to the song list.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think people kind of walk by a Guitar Freaks machine, and most people, meaning family with kids, don't recognize the stuff that's playing on a Guitar Freaks machine, but they walk by a Guitar Hero machine, they're going to go, hey, more than a feeling.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's going to be successful.
[SPEAKER_04]: If they want to do it, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, anyways, the other thing that they were saying is that it's going to have about 40 to 50 songs in the final arcade release, and that the controller would obviously be more sturdier, a bit larger, and a bit more like Guitar Freaks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I would hope so.
[SPEAKER_05]: And also that they were saying that there's going to be a tilt sensor in there so they'll know if you're left or right handed.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's very cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: See, that's something interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: They love us.
[SPEAKER_04]: They do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dark Sakura, kind of moving on to Microsoft and Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_04]: We talked a lot about Sony.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, Bill Gates was actually talking about the various motion-sensitive controllers like the Wii controller and the flippy gyroscope crap DualShock-looking thing on the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: And he's actually saying that the average gamer, and I don't know if this is something that we should all be insulted by or not, because basically he's insinuating that the average gamer is just really lazy.
[SPEAKER_07]: He said, who wants to move around a lot?
[SPEAKER_07]: Who can sit absolutely still?
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, who's going to have that kind of motor control to hold a controller out and be able to follow without just wanting to set it down.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, in fact, the quote in here is like, it's tough because sometimes you want to move the controller and you don't want to fly into the ground.
[SPEAKER_07]: You just want to put the controller down.
[SPEAKER_07]: People aren't that good at totally standing still.
[SPEAKER_07]: Even pilots actually sit in a chair when they do their flying.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's a lot to be learned about these controllers.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, pilots don't, you know, freaking play games while they're flying, I hope.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, basically he's going back to the future of video games, is online gaming, is mobile content.
[SPEAKER_05]: All the stuff his company's doing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Listen, we want you to sit down and play the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't get up because that takes away from your game time.
[SPEAKER_07]: We've now put in Halo, we have, you know, slash pizza.
[SPEAKER_07]: Another interesting quote on here.
[SPEAKER_07]: This actually makes me think back on the origami.
[SPEAKER_07]: Over time you have to say you will carry in your pocket a media device and a phone and a gaming device and say a tablet device for reading.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's natural for them to be combined into one device.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dude, that thing is too big.
[SPEAKER_05]: It'll never fit in a pocket.
[SPEAKER_07]: It'll fit in maybe like one of those Bible carriers.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's his point of view.
[SPEAKER_07]: Some of us disagree.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, what else has Microsoft got in store?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, they've got an Xbox Live update, and I'm going to do a brand new dashboard, including downloading in the background.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you can actually do other things while you're downloading demos or whatever other junk they have on there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, they're going to be adding, you can actually stream music and DVDs and stuff while you're downloading from the marketplace.
[SPEAKER_05]: Another thing they were saying, too, is that they're going to actually have it where it will remember your play.
[SPEAKER_05]: Say, for example, you're playing a DVD and you pop it out and go back to a game and then go back to your DVD later, it will actually know where it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, yeah, that's great.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sort of like my Mac does already.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, that's nice.
[SPEAKER_07]: My laptop does that.
[SPEAKER_07]: My laptop's PC.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, I love the Mac.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think these are things, you know, it would have been nice to see these a long time ago, but at the same time, you know, at least Microsoft recognizes that people want this stuff, so they're putting it in.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're offering the downloadable upgrade.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I think it's going to be pretty cool to just be able to download a lot of stuff and fill up my hard drive, although my hard drive's pretty much already full because Final Fantasy XI takes up, you know, like 25 million.
[SPEAKER_04]: So much room on there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, wasn't there something about fan content?
[SPEAKER_04]: Are they going to be putting like
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, like things that Microsoft likes that you're going to be able to download as well, like Red vs. Blue episodes and stuff?
[SPEAKER_04]: They already do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_05]: They already do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't, oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can actually go to redvsblue.com and download it too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Weren't they putting it in their own section?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, but you can't watch it on your HDTV.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, they're going to better organize the content that's already on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good, because it's live.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's why you use up your laptop to your TV.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're also going to let your friends know when you're idle.
[SPEAKER_05]: And so, you know, when you're not playing a game or anything.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, so people aren't sending you messages, hello, hello, are you ignoring me?
[SPEAKER_07]: They can speculate why you're idle.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, moving on to the Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: This was going around the internet this week that WiiKaraoke.com was registered on the internet by Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that kind of has all this rampant speculation going that, oh my gosh, the Wii's going to have a karaoke game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be their answer to SingStar, Karaoke Revolution, all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: but also kind of interesting because that means that that controller not only has a speaker but has a microphone in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that would be very interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: But they didn't stop there.
[SPEAKER_04]: They registered a ton of other domain names.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, the list is huge.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's this big old list of domain names they registered.
[SPEAKER_04]: WeCooking.com, WeSports.com.
[SPEAKER_07]: WeFitness.
[SPEAKER_04]: WeFamily, I'm sure, WeVC, but that makes sense, Virtual Console, not just WeConnect24.com, WeActive24, WeAnimation, maybe that's new Mario Paint, I don't know, WeAlive24.com, yep, there's WeFitness, WePuzzle, and here we go, WeBeauty.com, but here's my favorite, ShallWe.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not making that up.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not a joke.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's really there.
[SPEAKER_04]: So those will all actually just forge you right on over to Nintendo's site.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, one of the ones that they have on there, there was speculation on this website, MegaGames, that they were saying that WiiChannel.com might actually be kind of like a content channel that you can pick up through the Wii, almost like their own TV station.
[SPEAKER_04]: As long as Comcast doesn't try to ruin it, I'll be fine with that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait, what is this?
[SPEAKER_04]: WeBreeding.com?
[SPEAKER_04]: What is this?
[SPEAKER_07]: WeBreeding.
[SPEAKER_04]: WeBreeding?
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess there might be some interesting features coming to the next Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you know, the Nintendo Wii controller is a very phallic device.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's disgusting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, back to Microsoft, please, quickly.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_05]: Gotta love when I lose my place.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's so much fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Does the Wii controller vibrate?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, it does, actually.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Wii controller does vibrate, and I don't know why that would be important.
[SPEAKER_04]: Your wife just let out a cheer there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Finally, I'll get a use out of the gaming systems.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, res for Wii, huh?
[SPEAKER_05]: One thing that you will not find with the 360 is that a price drop is not coming soon.
[SPEAKER_05]: Basically, they've seen that the PS3 is going to be damn expensive, and you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: They don't have to change things.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're going to be paying the same prices on stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't believe that, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think there'll be a price cut come the next holidays.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I think Xbox was waiting to see what Sony was going to do when they announced the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if PlayStation 3 had come out and said, hey, we're going to release our console for $399, then Xbox would have been backed in the corner and they would have had to cut it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because Sony came out and said, hey, you're going to have to sell your firstborn to get our system.
[SPEAKER_04]: The original Xbox, though, will probably get price cut.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, the original Xboxes are on their way to a flea market near you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, they're about to be extinct pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're going to be running.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's like no first party titles coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is there?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, so when things don't get cut in price and we have to pay more money, we get a little bit angsty.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that takes us to one of our favorite segments called the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's two people that listen to this show in a room.
[SPEAKER_07]: Insert one wing in here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now that got a response.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everybody knows that one.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, DarkSakura, what's your FU of the week?
[SPEAKER_07]: My FU of the week goes to cosplay, as in the preparation that goes into cosplay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, shut up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Damn, I thought you were going to make some people mad for a minute.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, I'm going to go into the whole scope of things that piss me off about cosplay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Number one.
[SPEAKER_07]: Can't use props.
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: I have a good prop.
[SPEAKER_07]: As I was saying, first of all, it goes into the whole
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, when you have finals week and there's an anime convention the week after finals, when are you going to have time to finish your costume?
[SPEAKER_07]: You're going to spend a whole week working on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sleep is for the week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then imagine having to sew and you find good linen on sale, nice black linen, and three sewing machines break while doing it.
[SPEAKER_07]: So you have to get someone to sew it about six hours before you're supposed to be at said convention.
[SPEAKER_07]: and then having to deal with paint and having to deal with your cat walking all over your fan while you're painting it and your husband playing pinball while he's supposed to be holding down the other end for you and then let's get into the people who man fade that's all I have to say
[SPEAKER_07]: There are some people who do not have the physical characteristics to carry off certain costumes.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're picking a fight.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think that there's such a thing as tasteful.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you are built like a freaking booth babe, by all means, show it off.
[SPEAKER_07]: But if you're of an average build, in short, like me, you wear a kimono.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, you're FUSB.
[SPEAKER_05]: My FE of the week, very themed for Fanime, is to ugly chicks who dress up like hot anime chicks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Listen, if you're a 7, do not try to dress up like a 10, because nobody wants to see that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nobody.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not anybody.
[SPEAKER_05]: So if you're not looking that hot, keep the clothes on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, the same thing goes to guys, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Same goes to guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's some really ugly guys out there dressing up like, you know, I don't know, studly anime characters.
[SPEAKER_05]: Unacceptable.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have no problem with cross-play.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, if you are a really, really pretty guy, you can pull... Like the Utena from AX three years ago.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know AX.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gentlemen, please don't wear anything that might give you a uniball.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because, damn.
[SPEAKER_05]: And also, please...
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, everybody loves the mainstream characters out there, but my God, how many Vashes, how many Clouds, how many Sephiroths do you really need in the world?
[SPEAKER_07]: How many people, who has counted at least five Naruto in one room today?
[SPEAKER_07]: Everybody raises their hands.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, I'm going to go ahead and explain.
[SPEAKER_07]: The whole reason I cosplayed Tamari is, again, I had a week.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is her lazy cosplay.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is cosplay in a week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ta-da!
[SPEAKER_04]: This makes for great radio, by the way.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, moving on because we're getting pressed for time.
[SPEAKER_07]: That and all of my other costumes are too big for me because I made them when I was 80 pounds heavier.
[SPEAKER_04]: My FU of the week goes to my roommate, Extifer, because he left out the Silent Hill 2 on the Xbox, and it's all scratched up now, and if my Pyramid Head scene starts skipping, somebody's going to get an ass kicking.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can borrow mine, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because Pyramid Head is a rock star.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can borrow mine, because I've had your Silent Hill 4 for like three years.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, that works.
[SPEAKER_07]: Before it was out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, moving on, we've got to get to some more news, because this, oh, this is so great.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who doesn't have memories of seeing the movie The Wizard on the big screen?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, guess what?
[SPEAKER_04]: You can relive those memories all over again.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Wizard is coming to DVD August 29th.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, of course, Fred Savage, It's So Bad, the Mario 3 previews and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wasn't Christian Slater in that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, Christian Slater's holed up in a hotel room and he gets addicted to Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's supposed to be looking for Fred Savage and they never leave the hotel room.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: On the second, we have a whole bunch of stuff coming out.
[SPEAKER_07]: We have Final Fantasy IV on Game Boy Advance, Nintendo of Europe.
[SPEAKER_07]: We have Half-Life 2 on PC.
[SPEAKER_07]: We have Pac-Man World 3 on PSP, Super Monkey Ball Adventure.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did it take this long?
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Tourist Trophy, The Real Writing Simulator.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_07]: And we also have Zoo Tycoon 2, African Adventure.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, do you have U.S.
[SPEAKER_05]: dates?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_05]: This week, not a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_05]: But definitely in the month of June, you've got Grand Theft Auto Liberty Histories on the PS2, finally.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's some mixed-in stuff there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not a whole lot of good games coming out in June.
[SPEAKER_05]: July is your month, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: July you've got Chromehounds, which is awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Naruto Ultimate Ninja, if you're an anime fan.
[SPEAKER_05]: And also, man, I really wish Dead Rising was coming out in that month, but that's August.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love how DarkSakura always has her list very planned out, and then Loki's like, man, you know, there's...
[SPEAKER_04]: A bunch of crap coming out this month, maybe a couple cool games.
[SPEAKER_04]: There is, honestly.
[SPEAKER_05]: Seriously, is anyone going to buy Cars the Game?
[SPEAKER_05]: You, sir, are a loser!
[SPEAKER_05]: But anyways, Cars the Game and One Street Ball is coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, if you have the PSP, Gradius Collection.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hooray, games for the PSP!
[SPEAKER_04]: That is newsworthy.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, we've got to jam through these last few stories here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, a new game by Sony of an old franchise.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, coming to the UK, SingStar Anthems.
[SPEAKER_05]: More crappy songs on another karaoke game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like SingStar.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's actually one of the few games I've ever seen.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_04]: Isn't this supposed to be like the gay and women-themed SingStar game?
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because if you look at the list, it has like We Are Family and Scissor Sisters.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, we've got Queen, Radio Gaga, Cher, if I could turn back time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it's a gay one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Cher, I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Steps, because The Steps are in every single music game in the UK.
[SPEAKER_05]: Deeper Shade of Blue.
[SPEAKER_05]: You spin me right around.
[SPEAKER_05]: By Dead or Alive.
[SPEAKER_05]: Gloria Gaynor, I Will Survive.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Pussycat Dolls for some reason, don't ya?
[SPEAKER_05]: Leanne Rimes can't fight the moonlight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Charlotte Church.
[SPEAKER_04]: By the way, the minute this game comes out, we will have Loki live on the show singing Don't Ya.
[SPEAKER_04]: It'll be great.
[SPEAKER_04]: Never.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's vice applauding.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, somewhat gay theme.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Out Magazine, they actually had this, I don't know, best of list that was lately in their magazine, and they just named Link the hottest video game character in Out Magazine.
[SPEAKER_04]: When darkness enshrouds the land, this is a quote from the magazine, when darkness enshrouds the land, Nintendo's sexy farm boy turned wolf sets out to save the day in this upcoming game.
[SPEAKER_04]: his weapons, a sword, a bow, arrows, and kick-ass grooming skills.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's the gayest thing I've ever heard.
[SPEAKER_04]: I am a gay gamer myself, and I don't get the big ear thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: They must love big ears over at Out Magazine or something, because I don't find that very sexy.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what they say about a guy's ears?
[SPEAKER_07]: He can hear really well.
[SPEAKER_05]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: Next, please.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, next, please.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think we talked about this before.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Wii microphone, yeah, might have it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Great.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, if it's not actually in the controller, they do have that stupid port in the bottom that they could add one on.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, yeah, microphone coming out for the Wii, great.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought there was another part to it.
[SPEAKER_05]: What about voice over IP?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh yeah, voice over IP because they've already got that on the DS so why not on the Wii?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because talking into a giant remote looking thing would be cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know if they're trying to market this to mom and dad, that might be a feature that sells them on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow, I wish I could talk into a retarded looking microphone thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: That'd be great.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the only thing missing from my life.
[SPEAKER_07]: We like retarded microphone looking things, don't we?
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: Hugo Chavez, the president of Venezuela, thinks that Mercenaries 2 is an example of psychological warfare preparing everybody for a real invasion of Venezuela by the United States, apparently.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, we want their oil.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's true, we do want their oil, but...
[SPEAKER_07]: But basically they're taking steps to have certain video games now with that type of theme in mind banned in Venezuela.
[SPEAKER_07]: One of their lawmakers, Gabriela Ramirez, added, sends a message to Americans, you have a danger next door here in Latin America and action must be taken.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a justification for imperialist aggression.
[SPEAKER_04]: That sounds like they're going to invade us.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, we don't have anything they want.
[SPEAKER_07]: We just have beer.
[SPEAKER_04]: People.
[SPEAKER_07]: We have bad beer and hot dogs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Blood spilling in the streets.
[SPEAKER_07]: and they don't have that there.
[SPEAKER_07]: They can get it in their own backyard.
[SPEAKER_07]: But no, basically there's a law proposing that they're trying to prevent violent video games in Venezuela now.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's all over the world.
[SPEAKER_07]: The infection has spread.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jacob, why does Loki hate Apple?
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, why do you hate Apple?
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, where do I begin?
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, listen, that computer, it may look pretty, but it does nothing.
[SPEAKER_05]: It gets you on the internet, and that's about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Mac OS is such a nice operating system.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's nice if you want to browse the internet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Video editing.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: A PC can do video editing just as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_07]: Explain why things done in Photoshop on a Mac look better than they do on a PC.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mac is good for print.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Print media only.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, online web media does not matter.
[SPEAKER_05]: What about the lack of viruses?
[SPEAKER_06]: What about the lack of games?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh!
[SPEAKER_06]: Who games on a Mac?
[SPEAKER_06]: Nobody, because a Mac can't game.
[SPEAKER_07]: World of Warcraft?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is just where you guys, the Mac lovers, look, I love Mac too, as you can see, but you're just not going to change his mind.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry, guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anybody else?
[SPEAKER_04]: Anybody?
[SPEAKER_04]: Ask us questions.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_04]: Video game questions.
[SPEAKER_04]: E3 stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're sadistic.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think I see a dude getting up and back.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, we're masochistic.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Come on down.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're the next contestant.
[SPEAKER_07]: Welcome.
Woo!
[SPEAKER_04]: How are you doing?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a big room.
[SPEAKER_03]: You win air.
[SPEAKER_04]: Your name, sir?
[SPEAKER_03]: Michael.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I see you're wearing a Squeenix shirt.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's your question for us, Michael?
[SPEAKER_03]: How many times do you think by the end of the year that the Blu-ray technology will crash because of various problems reading different... Because the difference between reading a DVD semi-sequentially and maybe having to grab different things from all different parts of a game disc, I think is going to be a big problem for the PS3.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I was wondering what you guys thought about that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let me ask you a question as an answer.
[SPEAKER_07]: How many times does a person blink in a day?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's how often it will crash.
[SPEAKER_03]: A lot of them.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's why I'm not getting a PS3.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've been looking forward to it until I saw the price point and then saw what it was.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sony's press conference was depressing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think Sony kind of just made a grave mistake in not putting the Blu-ray movies out there on the show floor.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think what they should have done is they should have on the show floor had, here's a Blu-ray movie playing next to a regular DVD.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is why you need to upgrade the Blu-ray.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_05]: We've tried that before.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, they did.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, how many people in this room actually have an HDTV capable of that high resolution?
[SPEAKER_07]: That's about a half of the room.
[SPEAKER_04]: A third half.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, but of course we're all... Yeah, you all are nerds, so of course you have an HDTV.
[SPEAKER_04]: We all love our games.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're in here because we're gamers and anime fans, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: So we want to make them look pretty.
[SPEAKER_07]: But... That's okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: But seriously, how many people though across the world in the areas that would, you know, they're going to market the PS3 and do you think are actually going to be able to take advantage of that level of technology?
[SPEAKER_04]: Japan, yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Could they be setting themselves up for the long run?
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe it's not so much about launch day, but it's about what's going on a couple years in advance?
[SPEAKER_03]: That might be a mistake given the Xbox 360 has been out a year already.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I've already got a person who hates Microsoft gaming, but has already said that Microsoft may be making leaps and bounds towards somewhat evening the console wars between the two sides.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what it sounded like to me.
[SPEAKER_05]: And even if Blu-ray doesn't take off, it's not like that's ever held Sony back with the fact that they've had a failed media format.
[SPEAKER_05]: MiniDisc, the UMDs, Beta.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, Beta was good.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think Microsoft's learning from their lack of diversity on the first Xbox, at least if E3 is any showing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think they're really finally starting to learn what the rest of us really want.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I'll tell you, games like 99 Nights and stuff were pretty hot.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, we got another question here.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's your name, sir?
[SPEAKER_01]: Willie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Willie, and Willie's got a DDR Freak shirt on.
[SPEAKER_04]: We got a lot of buddies over there.
[SPEAKER_01]: That looks like one of the old school DDR Freak shirts.
[SPEAKER_04]: Willie, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, I did want to hear Loki rant, but he got that taken care of.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I was wondering what you guys thought of the arcade here.
[SPEAKER_07]: I haven't checked it out yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: I actually got here about an hour before we had to get up here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is there anything left at Miggle?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because it just looks like they moved Miggle over here, Milpitas Golf Land.
[SPEAKER_04]: OnCampus Entertainment brought all this stuff over here.
[SPEAKER_07]: So what games are in there right now?
[SPEAKER_04]: DDR Extreme, Parapara, Initial D, and Wangan, and all that air hockey.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, I'm going to get my cards out and freaking play some Long God Midnight.
[SPEAKER_07]: I will challenge anybody in this room.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: They've got the right games for this crowd.
[SPEAKER_04]: They do.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, you know, they left.
[SPEAKER_05]: They really have enough room left for some actual go-kart racing.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's why I thought that the only thing was missing.
[SPEAKER_04]: That room over there is kind of empty.
[SPEAKER_04]: You could be doing Mario Kart Live around the arcade.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, there's a lot of room over there.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_07]: We should get the people to cosplay the initial D cars again and run around the room.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is the last question, guys, because we've got to wrap it up.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't want to be rude to the next folks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Your name, sir?
[SPEAKER_04]: Ricardo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, Ricardo.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's your question?
[SPEAKER_02]: Aside from the idea of the new Guitar Hero Arcade, what new music game do you guys think ought to come out that will get the crowd up and amped again?
[SPEAKER_07]: I want Sax Mania.
[SPEAKER_07]: Clarinet Freaks.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, we need more Parappa.
[SPEAKER_07]: We need another Um Jammerlammy.
[SPEAKER_07]: that utilizes the Guitar Hero controller.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you talking arcade or are you talking console?
[SPEAKER_04]: He says arcade.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, arcade.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a tough one because I would like to see something new.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sega needs to hop up and make me a Universe Harrier.
[SPEAKER_07]: They need to freaking bring Planet Harrier out on some system or the other.
[SPEAKER_07]: We need Planet Harrier on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what we need.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would like to see something like frequency amplitude type stuff in the arcade.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that would be pretty hot because I like those games.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: and you know with Harmonix having that formula work so successfully now that they've just attached a guitar to it they ought to go back and revisit the idea of doing one of their you know trancy techno type games so that's my answer I want to see like a frequency amplitude type thing in the arcade you want Technic beat on arcade no Technic beat was kind of lame alright that's it one more story one more quick story here and then we're going to wrap it up Loki yes a perfect story to end on basically you know you know a company's got a really dumb idea when they come out with this
[SPEAKER_05]: Co-masters, they're coming out with a game called The Turds.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right, you play crap.
[SPEAKER_05]: Excellent.
[SPEAKER_05]: What exactly are The Turds, you might ask?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, this is from the official website.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is this the sequel to Boonga Boonga or whatever that thing was called?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyways, here's from their official website, hopefully going to answer the question.
[SPEAKER_05]: On a winter's night in 2001, during a heavy drinking session at home amongst friends, I decided to stumble off to the toilet for what I was going to...
[SPEAKER_05]: for what was going to be a good pan-splitting chunder.
[SPEAKER_05]: For some reason, and don't ask why, I brought a small lump of brown plasticine with me from our studio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whilst performing my toilet bowl opera and singing my guts up for the toilet gods, Hugh and Frank, I managed to crush the plasticine into a pulp.
[SPEAKER_05]: Once I delivered the goods and that wonderful feeling of calm sank in, I found myself looking at the plasticine.
[SPEAKER_05]: I decided to take that pulp and create a turd with a face.
[SPEAKER_05]: As I played with my new friend on the side...
[SPEAKER_04]: This is why you don't drink that much.
[SPEAKER_04]: Put that person in a jacket and put them in the back of the van.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, I wonder who spiked this person's beer with, like, antifreeze.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was that guy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, as I played with my new friend on the side of the toilet seat, I knew this was the start of something special.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, I just want to say, Mac fans, what I'm going to do for you guys is we'll crop what he's saying right here, so we'll have little sound bites that you can download.
[SPEAKER_05]: History was made that night.
[SPEAKER_05]: The turd world was born.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just like... I don't know what the hell... So anyways, I saw the pictures of the website.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like these giant turds with guns.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: More power to you.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, if you really want to play a game that's crap, there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Somebody just yelled it out.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like worms.
[SPEAKER_04]: Worms with turds.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the sequel, Ringworms.
[SPEAKER_04]: And on that note...
[SPEAKER_04]: What a good note to end this show on, a poop.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, very fitting, don't you think?
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's go around and get everybody's final thought.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_07]: Reject false icons.
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't get a PS3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ooh, harsh words.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're going to laugh, but the first part of the show didn't tape.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I guess this won't be going up on the podcast stream or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, the first part of the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: We missed like about ten minutes or so.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see what we can do with it.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll fake it.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll fake it like a woman.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nellie, here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hit your husband.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you guys for coming out and watching the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: We appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Until next time, check us out at OrangeLoungeRadio.com We do this stuff every Sunday and it actually tapes the whole way through.
[SPEAKER_07]: Join our live journal community at Orange Lounge and look at us on MySpace where we start to cry.
[SPEAKER_05]: We also have a panel tomorrow night about podcasting if you're interested.
[SPEAKER_05]: How we became internet rock stars.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, we are the celebrities of the internet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: End of show.
[SPEAKER_04]: See you guys later.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for wasting an hour with us.
[SPEAKER_00]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_00]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_00]: For more information on our live and podcast programs, visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com See you next week.