[SPEAKER_01]: Message for you, son.
[SPEAKER_07]: Attention!
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you want to hear the most annoying sound in the world?
[SPEAKER_01]: You're listening to Orange Lounge Radio, the Monty Talk, and then some.
[SPEAKER_01]: Orange Lounge may contain adult content.
[SPEAKER_01]: Orange Lounge may contain many four-letter words.
[SPEAKER_01]: Orange Lounge may contain a scene of nudity.
[SPEAKER_01]: Orange Lounge may contain hot monkey sex.
[SPEAKER_15]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_15]: Orange Lounge will not contain hot monkey sex.
[SPEAKER_07]: In this episode... Hey, any balls down there?
[SPEAKER_10]: That's the biggest bear you've ever seen, Jingleberry.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's your favorite scary movie?
[SPEAKER_12]: Showgirls.
[SPEAKER_07]: Absolutely frightful.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's yours?
[SPEAKER_07]: There are no stupid questions, just stupid people.
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't torture yourself.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's my job.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now's the time our sprockets made me dogs!
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll get you, my pretty, and your little dog, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know Kung Fu.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry, but all questions must be submitted in writing.
[SPEAKER_11]: Why did they have to take the word gay?
[SPEAKER_07]: Nobody expects a Spanish exposition!
[SPEAKER_07]: It's Kendo.
[SPEAKER_07]: Kendo!
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura Shut up!
[SPEAKER_02]: Where's my gun?
[SPEAKER_02]: This is my boomstick!
[SPEAKER_17]: Sky Come on girls, it's time to drop the bomb!
[SPEAKER_17]: Loki I can't for the life of me get the hooker to have sex with me.
[SPEAKER_07]: What kind of warped human being would find that funny?
[SPEAKER_15]: Orange Lounge Radio We are live and this is episode number 32 for February the 9th of 2003.
[SPEAKER_15]: No humming tonight, we hope.
[SPEAKER_15]: Except from Jamie.
[SPEAKER_15]: You're tuned into the B-Money Scene's most slutty radio station of all things B-Money.
[SPEAKER_15]: My name is Rob Roberts, for you who might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_15]: Joining me as always are my awesome co-hosts in this corner, the happiest bunny on the farm, Miss Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know her as DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_18]: I've had lots of coffee, ha ha ha ha ha.
[SPEAKER_15]: In that corner, say hello to our tack, tack, tack, our tack master.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm a tack, tack chick.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, you're tack's bitch.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's, uh, hello, our mics went off.
[SPEAKER_15]: You're tack's bitch.
[SPEAKER_18]: Rob, anything going off in your hands is natural.
[SPEAKER_15]: Say hello to our tech master, Loki.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hug.
[SPEAKER_15]: Don't look at me like I'm freaking Frankenstein.
[SPEAKER_15]: Give me a hug.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hug.
[SPEAKER_15]: Also known as Matt.
[SPEAKER_15]: We haven't come up with a stage name for Matt yet.
[SPEAKER_15]: We don't want to use his real life.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's the Matt.
[SPEAKER_15]: He's the Matt.
[SPEAKER_15]: He's just Matt.
[SPEAKER_15]: He's like Cher.
[SPEAKER_15]: Only one word.
[SPEAKER_15]: Only one word name.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: Also with us tonight, say hello, we've got tons of guests here with us tonight.
[SPEAKER_15]: Say hello to Zero in the corner.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hi, Zero, how are you doing?
[SPEAKER_15]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_15]: I went too far back in the intro.
[SPEAKER_15]: Also, we've got... Wait, we'll do him last.
[SPEAKER_15]: We've got Dave's back after a long time.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hey, Scott, say hello.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_15]: Scott's one of the Rocky Horror folks.
[SPEAKER_15]: He's here.
[SPEAKER_15]: You brought back my TV, yes?
[SPEAKER_15]: Good, thank you.
[SPEAKER_15]: Now we can play Animal Crossing again.
[SPEAKER_15]: He's eating nuts.
[SPEAKER_15]: Also here, Brad.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, EOSFBB has a great stage name for Matt.
[SPEAKER_15]: His name could be Matt Comes A Lot.
[SPEAKER_15]: How does he know?
[SPEAKER_15]: I almost read that as come slut, but... Oops, my bad.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, and also, way in the back corner, one of my bestest friends in the whole wide world who doesn't know shit about these DDR games, but that's why we love having people on this show that aren't really into these games.
[SPEAKER_15]: They just sit here in horror at this... They do a radio thing on the internet these days?
[SPEAKER_13]: Say hello to Billy!
[SPEAKER_13]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_13]: How are you, gentlemen?
[SPEAKER_13]: Very good.
[SPEAKER_13]: I kicked you in the foot.
[SPEAKER_13]: I kicked you in the foot!
[SPEAKER_13]: Not in the foot!
[SPEAKER_13]: I kicked you in the balls!
[SPEAKER_13]: Not in the balls!
[SPEAKER_13]: Are you spitting the nut?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm spitting my nut.
[SPEAKER_15]: We'll be talking to everybody more a little bit later, but first we're going to take a quick break.
[SPEAKER_15]: And any other thoughts from the opening panel?
[SPEAKER_15]: Will I tune something up?
[SPEAKER_15]: Cue something up, I should say?
[SPEAKER_00]: I'll play you some TAC.
[SPEAKER_15]: Play you some TAC?
[SPEAKER_15]: How about first we're going to do something from Dance Mania EX3.
[SPEAKER_15]: Brand new Dance Mania album that just came out.
[SPEAKER_15]: We're going to play something from that.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm sorry, EX2.
[SPEAKER_15]: My bad, my bad, my bad.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'll take the Rapist for 500.
[SPEAKER_15]: We're going to play...
[SPEAKER_15]: We're going to start this break off with Erotic, and then Tack.
[SPEAKER_15]: We'll do Erotic, then Tack.
[SPEAKER_15]: How's that?
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: We're going to do Erotic.
[SPEAKER_15]: This is Fred Come to Bed, the 2003 mix.
[SPEAKER_15]: Word, and it sounds just like Max Don't Have Sex With You Guys.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because all Erotic songs sound the same.
[SPEAKER_15]: So we're going to play this.
[SPEAKER_18]: Sorry, this doesn't sound like Erotic.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because Charlene is actually missing heart.
[SPEAKER_12]: Wait.
[SPEAKER_15]: I found that out.
[SPEAKER_15]: Does he have the flute part?
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_15]: We'll find out.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because that part kicks ass.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, we're going to play it right now.
[SPEAKER_15]: We're going to play Fred Come to Bed, then we're going to do something tack, and then we'll be back.
[SPEAKER_15]: We are doing the match game tonight.
[SPEAKER_15]: We're going to do it kind of early in the show.
[SPEAKER_15]: Probably first or second segment.
[SPEAKER_15]: When we come back, actually, we want to talk about the pre-show and something, a new contest we're going to do that relates to the pre-show we did tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: And porn.
[SPEAKER_15]: And porn, of course, because we are Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_15]: But we'll be right back.
[SPEAKER_15]: Thanks for tuning in.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: Come to bed, cause my max had sex with a sexy ex-old friend
[SPEAKER_01]: And now it's time for Erotic Pop Idol, where we will find the next singer for everyone's favorite perverse Bomani band, Erotic.
[SPEAKER_00]: Do it all night.
[SPEAKER_00]: Do it with me.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, no, that was awful.
[SPEAKER_00]: Bloody terrible.
[SPEAKER_00]: Do you take vocal lessons?
[SPEAKER_00]: Kill your teacher.
[SPEAKER_00]: In the heat of the night.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, God, I think my ears are bleeding.
[SPEAKER_06]: I liked it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Shut the bloody hell up, Paula.
[SPEAKER_13]: Next.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, that was cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: Do you even know why you're here?
[SPEAKER_13]: That was just bloody pathetic.
[SPEAKER_00]: Next!
[SPEAKER_07]: Come on, do it with me.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes, yes, that's it!
[SPEAKER_15]: We have a winner!
[SPEAKER_01]: A Star is Born, here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_15]: A star is born here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: You say that every fucking time.
[SPEAKER_15]: I know, that's why I have to say it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because Dave pointed that out one day.
[SPEAKER_05]: You say that every goddamn time you play at Provo!
[SPEAKER_12]: I didn't say it in that tone though
[SPEAKER_15]: Everybody watch the American Idol.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, we're going to start.
[SPEAKER_02]: We need our funky 70s porn music.
[SPEAKER_15]: We're going to start off with the match game first thing here tonight, but we're going to need to get some contestants.
[SPEAKER_15]: So the trivia question we're asking tonight to get some contestants for the match game.
[SPEAKER_15]: You got something that people will get pretty easy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: First two people to private message me the answer.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm known in the chat room tonight as Sky Chat Room Slut.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, this is a question.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's actually a trivia question about myself.
[SPEAKER_02]: What is the one beverage... No, I can't do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: First two people with the correct answer are our contestants tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: What is Jamie's favorite tax song?
[SPEAKER_15]: Ooh, that's going to be a hard one, don't you think?
[SPEAKER_15]: If they pay attention, you think?
[SPEAKER_02]: If they pay attention, I'll get it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, Jamie's favorite tax song.
[SPEAKER_15]: Send it to me over private message.
[SPEAKER_15]: And the first two people who got it right get to participate tonight.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, in the meantime, while we wait for those answers to come in, what do we want to talk about?
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh yes, let's talk about the contest.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_15]: First of all, what inspired the pre-show that we did tonight?
[SPEAKER_02]: I ran out of ideas.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, for those that just joined us and missed the pre-show, tell us what we did tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Old TV show theme songs.
[SPEAKER_15]: Old TV show theme songs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Many of which were donated by DDR Angel and Stresa.
[SPEAKER_15]: Next week you should play Eurobeat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, I will.
[SPEAKER_12]: Eurobeat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh!
[SPEAKER_12]: Beat, beat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not the song.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll just play the whole Parapara soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_02]: How's that sound?
[SPEAKER_02]: Like all music from Initial D. Okay, I lost all 17 of my Initial D soundtracks.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, next time Jamie takes a week off, you can do pre-show.
[SPEAKER_15]: How's that, Matt?
[SPEAKER_02]: Am I going to take a week off?
[SPEAKER_15]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, next week's pre-show is Strong Bad Things.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, so let me think.
[SPEAKER_15]: What else?
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh yes, the contest.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, great idea.
[SPEAKER_15]: We have to give thanks to Dark Tetsuya for this idea.
[SPEAKER_15]: This is a great idea.
[SPEAKER_15]: Orange Lounge Radio is going to be hosting our own DWI contest.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because we're going to do this right, goddammit.
[SPEAKER_15]: We're going to do a DWI contest and it's going to kick ass.
[SPEAKER_15]: And the theme is, you have to do a DWI complete with backgrounds, basic trick and maniac steps,
[SPEAKER_15]: and banners, the whole nine yards, to any old TV theme.
[SPEAKER_15]: Or actually, no, any TV theme you want to do.
[SPEAKER_15]: Two minutes at the most.
[SPEAKER_15]: If it's longer than two minutes, you better crop it down.
[SPEAKER_15]: Any TV theme.
[SPEAKER_15]: You want to do a DWI too, send that in.
[SPEAKER_15]: And the winner's going to get, can we get a prize pack for the winner, Loki, you think?
[SPEAKER_15]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_15]: Just a small one, maybe?
[SPEAKER_15]: Something small, yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, so we're going to get a prize pack, one of Loki's infamous prize packs for the winner.
[SPEAKER_15]: In case somebody is like, small, uh?
[SPEAKER_15]: When Matt says small, it's really not small as you think.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let me see, wait, let me see.
[SPEAKER_15]: We've got EvilNauki2DX in the chatroom.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let me see.
[SPEAKER_15]: Would Calibimani.com be willing to host this contest with us?
[SPEAKER_15]: So we can get some place to have the files and some more promotion here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, you've got your site too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, okay, you're going to host RDDOS?
[SPEAKER_15]: I still want more promotion.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let's see if we can get Kali Bamani to go in on this with us.
[SPEAKER_15]: A joint contest here.
[SPEAKER_15]: More promotion.
[SPEAKER_15]: But you will host all the DWI files on the new Leech from Loki site.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, my new Leech from Loki site.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh yeah, I need to finish that.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, I get a yes.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, so this is it.
[SPEAKER_15]: The KaliBamani.com slash Orange Launch Radio DWI contest.
[SPEAKER_15]: Must be TV theme song.
[SPEAKER_15]: Deadline.
[SPEAKER_15]: When do we want them done by?
[SPEAKER_17]: Uh...
[SPEAKER_17]: We need a tentative deadline right now so we can iron out all the rules and shit.
[SPEAKER_17]: You need to iron out what the rules and stuff would be.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, so we'll just tell everybody they're going to have to look on the forums for the information.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, American, Canadian, or British.
[SPEAKER_15]: So...
[SPEAKER_15]: This is the deal.
[SPEAKER_15]: We don't know how we want to submit these yet, but that's okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: Just go work on them, and we'll have more details for you next week.
[SPEAKER_15]: Next week's show, by the way, Jamie's going to be here, and Loki, you're going to be here too, yes, next week?
[SPEAKER_15]: I will not.
[SPEAKER_13]: I will.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm going to be in L.A.
[SPEAKER_15]: at the Cyber Beat Tournament.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'll set it all up.
[SPEAKER_17]: I've already got a way where they can send the files to me.
[SPEAKER_15]: Great.
[SPEAKER_15]: So we'll set something up, and we'll have more information for you next week.
[SPEAKER_12]: And if anyone still remembers leachfromloki.tk, do not go there.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because that is the most disturbing picture I've ever seen in my entire life.
[SPEAKER_12]: Whatever, blah blah blah.
[SPEAKER_15]: That was funny though.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, whatever.
[SPEAKER_15]: Anyway, but the correct address for Loki's site is www.willddrforfood.net slash leachfromloki.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, anyway.
[SPEAKER_15]: So now you know, we're doing a DWI contest.
[SPEAKER_15]: And the judges will be, of course, myself, Jamie, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's because we're cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're cooler than everybody in the world!
[SPEAKER_17]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_15]: Halleck
[SPEAKER_15]: Hollick is Jamie's favorite tax song.
[SPEAKER_15]: Congratulations to Black Lab and USFBB.
[SPEAKER_15]: They are our contestants tonight.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: And by the way, my second favorite is DXY.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, close though.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, everybody that sends us some good stuff.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, so, here we go.
[SPEAKER_15]: Our two contestants for tonight's episode of the Match Game.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let's introduce the celebrities.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi, Dad.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm in jail.
[SPEAKER_15]: Celebrity number one.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like it here.
[SPEAKER_15]: Celebrity number one is, uh, you know her because she's on this really popular internet radio talk show, and she bitches a lot about things.
[SPEAKER_15]: Say hello to celebrity number one, Miss DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_15]: Celebrity number two is a DWI horse, and he's a whore for porn.
[SPEAKER_15]: Or so everybody thinks.
[SPEAKER_02]: And he likes to beat his wild pony.
[SPEAKER_15]: Say hello to Loki, celebrity number two.
[SPEAKER_15]: He loves you, baby.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, celebrity number three.
[SPEAKER_15]: If you thought I was gay, you have to meet celebrity number three.
[SPEAKER_15]: Say hello to Billy.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hello to Billy.
[SPEAKER_15]: Celebrity number four is another familiar face from around the Sackbomani community.
[SPEAKER_15]: He's just cool, and he wears a hat that says hookups.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't know if he's like trying to mack and get some hookups.
[SPEAKER_15]: Are you trying to get hookups?
[SPEAKER_15]: It's like clothing.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's clothing?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: Celebrity number four is zero.
[SPEAKER_15]: Give it up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, how's it going?
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: Celebrity number... Are you participating?
[SPEAKER_15]: No.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: And celebrity number five...
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, we have a team.
[SPEAKER_15]: We have a tag team for Celebrity 5.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_15]: Is Brad and Dave.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, whatever.
[SPEAKER_15]: And then Celebrity number 6 is the coolest person in the entire world.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's me.
[SPEAKER_15]: Fuck no!
[SPEAKER_15]: All right, so six celebrities tonight.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let's play a match game.
[SPEAKER_15]: If you don't know how we play a Vamani match game, I'm going to ask a question.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we're going to burp.
[SPEAKER_15]: And there'll be a blanket.
[SPEAKER_15]: And the contestants tonight, Black Lab and the OSFBB, will have to try to fill in that blanket.
[SPEAKER_15]: And for every celebrity they match, they get a point.
[SPEAKER_18]: Blanket.
[SPEAKER_15]: Wonderful.
[SPEAKER_15]: A few things you should know about the celebrities.
[SPEAKER_15]: You already know myself, Jamie, and Loki pretty well if you listen to the show on a regular basis, which I know both Black Lab and EOSA TV do.
[SPEAKER_15]: Billy?
[SPEAKER_15]: Billy's played DDR a couple times, but he doesn't get it, this whole obsession.
[SPEAKER_15]: But he's a big fag, so... And he loves Britney.
[SPEAKER_18]: But wait, he doesn't live in the main hall of Rosen Village.
[SPEAKER_17]: If anybody can guess his favorite DDR song, they get... nothing, but yes.
[SPEAKER_15]: Zero, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_15]: Zero's kind of a wild card.
[SPEAKER_15]: What will your answers be like, Zero?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know, they'll just be whatever they look like.
[SPEAKER_15]: They'll be the right ones, okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: And then Brad and Dave are both very crazy, so their answers will be crazy.
[SPEAKER_15]: They're crazy people!
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, first question.
[SPEAKER_15]: We haven't done this in a while, so here we go.
[SPEAKER_15]: First question!
[SPEAKER_15]: Ted the Terrorizer.
[SPEAKER_15]: Love to make fun of people that play DDR.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to spell Terrorizer.
Shh.
[SPEAKER_15]: They don't know that.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's radio.
[SPEAKER_15]: Here, look.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'll right click and do spell check right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_15]: Terrorized.
[SPEAKER_15]: Ted the Terrorizer.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: Damn it.
[SPEAKER_15]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_15]: Can I ask a question?
[SPEAKER_15]: Ted the Terrorizer loved to make fun of people that played DDR.
[SPEAKER_15]: He liked to yell to the goofy people stomping on the game, Hey, stop stomping on the arrows and go blank!
Oh, hi!
How about you?
The answer should be in here.
Just pick something.
[SPEAKER_15]: Don't say it, write it down.
[SPEAKER_15]: What's the first thing that comes to mind?
[SPEAKER_15]: Write it down.
[SPEAKER_15]: Stop stomping on the arrows and go blank.
[SPEAKER_15]: Are all the other celebrities locked in?
[SPEAKER_05]: Ding!
[SPEAKER_15]: Is that your final answer?
[SPEAKER_15]: Billy, you got one?
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, do you guys have one?
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, great, we're ready.
[SPEAKER_15]: I have both the contestants locked in too.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I had Stressa send me something.
[SPEAKER_15]: Did he send me an answer?
[SPEAKER_15]: Stressa, you're not a contestant, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_15]: Although that was a good answer.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, let's see, here we go.
[SPEAKER_15]: Black Lab said, Stop stomping on the arrows and go get laid.
[SPEAKER_18]: Lovely.
[SPEAKER_15]: Lovely.
[SPEAKER_15]: EOSFBB said, Stop stomping on the arrows and go watch porn.
[SPEAKER_15]: Good answers.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let's see if we get a match.
[SPEAKER_15]: Jamie, Ted the Terrorizer said, Stop stomping on the arrows and go... Fuck me in the ass.
[SPEAKER_00]: Bard girl.
[SPEAKER_17]: Goddamn you for taking my answer!
[SPEAKER_15]: Fuck me in the ass, bar and grill.
[SPEAKER_15]: Wing this one.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, it's not a match, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_15]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, go... Okay, she had my answer, so, um... Let's see, uh... Go eat baby fetus.
[SPEAKER_15]: Go eat baby fetus, I'm sorry, that's not a match.
[SPEAKER_02]: You mean that the baby itself is pregnant and has a fetus?
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, well, there's... yeah, whatever.
[SPEAKER_17]: I had fuck me in the ass, but, yeah, alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: Billy!
[SPEAKER_15]: Stop stomping on the arrows and go... homo.
[SPEAKER_15]: Stop stomping on the arrows and go homo.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, I'm sorry, that's not a match.
[SPEAKER_15]: Zero, stop stomping on the arrows.
[SPEAKER_08]: and GoFuckYourself.
[SPEAKER_15]: And GoFuckYourself.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's the obvious one.
[SPEAKER_15]: Nobody guessed that.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: Stop stomping on the arrows and go... Fuck a sheep.
[SPEAKER_15]: Or your sister.
[SPEAKER_15]: Or yourself.
[SPEAKER_15]: You brain-dead redneck asshole.
[SPEAKER_15]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_15]: Stop stomping on the arrows and go fuck a sheep, your sister, or yourself, you brain-dead redneck asshole.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_15]: That was not a match.
[SPEAKER_15]: But it was funny.
[SPEAKER_15]: My answer...
[SPEAKER_15]: My answer, hey, stop stomping on the arrows and go shove a bottle of Propel up your ass.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's a very good observation, Brad.
[SPEAKER_15]: They all have to do with penetration of some sort.
[SPEAKER_18]: Not necessarily.
[SPEAKER_15]: Billy's is implied, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just because you're gay, you don't have to fuck me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that's right.
[SPEAKER_15]: Just because you're gay doesn't mean you have to fuck people in the ass.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I think that you can be gay and not a slut.
[SPEAKER_00]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_00]: You're a party.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, so...
[SPEAKER_15]: So sorry kids, no points.
[SPEAKER_15]: The score is all tied up with a big fat zero.
[SPEAKER_15]: Next question.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's no winners except me.
[SPEAKER_15]: Next question, here we go.
[SPEAKER_15]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_15]: JB, the Jenny Rom Whore, and for those that don't know who Jenny Rom is, Waka Laka, the Waka Laka song, or Blonde Girl, it'd be a Blonde Girl, okay, that's Jenny Rom, or Senorita, she'll be a Senorita, okay, here we go, JB, the Jenny Rom Whore, love to order things from SciFam, that's the record label that puts out all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_15]: He gasped in horror one day, though, when SyFam didn't send him the album he had ordered.
[SPEAKER_15]: Instead, they had sent him a CD of blank.
[SPEAKER_15]: JB the Jenny Romhor loved to order things from Jenny's record company.
[SPEAKER_15]: He gasped in horror one day, though, when he didn't get the album he had ordered.
[SPEAKER_15]: Instead, they had sent him a CD of blank.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm waiting for both contestants.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: JB gasped into horror when he did not get the album he had ordered.
[SPEAKER_15]: Instead, they sent him a CD of blank.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, do we have all the, do we have all the, uh, do we have all the celebrities?
[SPEAKER_15]: Just about, okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm still, okay, there's the other, great.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, so we're just about ready here.
[SPEAKER_15]: Great.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let's see what our, uh, contestant said.
[SPEAKER_15]: Black Lab said he was shocked when they sent him a CD of midget porn.
[SPEAKER_15]: Midget porn.
[SPEAKER_15]: The buffer, by the way, just got to JB because it's all, hey!
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, so Black Lab said he was shocked to get midget porn.
[SPEAKER_15]: EOSFBB says he was shocked to get kids butchering pop songs, a.k.a.
[SPEAKER_15]: Kids Bop Max.
[SPEAKER_15]: WTF?
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alrighty.
[SPEAKER_15]: KidsBotMax.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know what KidsBotMax is, Billy?
[SPEAKER_15]: Billy, of course, Billy the Fag with no kids bop max.
[SPEAKER_17]: Does that mean you suck dick too?
[SPEAKER_17]: Jesus.
[SPEAKER_17]: No, it's on Nickelodeon, man, and I watch Invader Zim, ass.
[SPEAKER_17]: Are you a racist?
[SPEAKER_17]: Do you like to suck cock?
[SPEAKER_02]: Why do you think I don't watch TV?
[SPEAKER_15]: Kids bop max.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, so let's see if we have any matches.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: Starting off.
[SPEAKER_15]: Starting off with DarkSakura, JB was shocked when he got a CD of... Yoko Ono's Greatest Hits.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yoko Ono's Greatest Hits!
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, good answer, but not a match.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm sorry to say.
[SPEAKER_15]: Loki, who's giving me glares for insinuating that he was a homo for knowing about kids' bop.
[SPEAKER_17]: Anyways, so he was shocked to see the CD that he got because... It doesn't matter because Jenny Rom sucks, okay?
[SPEAKER_15]: Ooh, you can send those cards and letters to Loki.
[SPEAKER_15]: Care of willddrfood.net slash leashfromloki.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: Billy, he was shocked to see that they sent him a CD of The Original Artists.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, I think Billy gets a zing for that.
[SPEAKER_15]: The original artists.
[SPEAKER_15]: That was a funny.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, but not a match.
[SPEAKER_15]: Good answer though.
[SPEAKER_15]: Zero, he was shocked to see that they sent him a CD of... The best and worst of American Idol, which is pretty much the same.
[SPEAKER_15]: The best and worst of American Idol, which is pretty much the same.
[SPEAKER_15]: Good answer, not a match.
[SPEAKER_15]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_15]: Our dynamic duo over here, Brad and Dave.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm Batman.
[SPEAKER_15]: Shocked to see...
[SPEAKER_15]: Shocked to see that he got a CD of Rafi Rafi He used to sing children's songs on stage
[SPEAKER_02]: No, The Elephant Show!
[SPEAKER_08]: Banana phone, doo-doo-doo Banana phone, doo-doo-doo No, there's one.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, it's Rafi.
[SPEAKER_15]: You guys won the match game just for that alone.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: My answer actually has a musical cue to go with it.
[SPEAKER_15]: He was shocked to see that they sent him a CD of Avril Lavigne speed covers.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm gonna go kill myself now, bye.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a bottle of Propel you can choke on.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: He was shocked to see they sent him a CD of Avril Lavigne's speakers.
[SPEAKER_15]: I got slapped on the wrist for that one.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay, you lose.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, Shine lose.
[SPEAKER_00]: You are a loser!
[SPEAKER_15]: So it's all tied up.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's all tied up, zero to zero.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: Next question, here we go.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let's see if we can get one on the board here.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: Jamie loves Propel more than any drink in the whole world.
[SPEAKER_15]: She decided though one day to write the company and tell them, Dear Propel, you really need to make blank flavor.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, I like ass flavor.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, we're waiting for the contestants to walk in.
[SPEAKER_15]: Are all the celebrities in?
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, they're singing.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, Dear Bro Pal, you really need to make blank flavor.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, it makes me think of... And today's contestants take home Rice-A-Roni, the San Francisco treat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ding, ding!
[SPEAKER_02]: Ass-A-Roni, the San Francisco treat.
[SPEAKER_15]: Our contestants are locked in.
[SPEAKER_15]: How about the celebrities?
[SPEAKER_15]: Still thinking?
[SPEAKER_15]: Just think, what's a flavor of Propel that Jamie would want?
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yes, actually, thank you for that.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, we're still waiting on a couple celebrities.
[SPEAKER_15]: Zero's writing.
[SPEAKER_15]: Billy, come on.
[SPEAKER_18]: I would have to do my best to answer my last.
[SPEAKER_18]: I should answer last.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, well, I'll have Jamie answer my last.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, I'll answer on my turn.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I'm the best, the greatest.
[SPEAKER_02]: And everyone loves me.
[SPEAKER_15]: The chat room's got a lot of good answers here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, like what?
[SPEAKER_15]: Bukkake.
[SPEAKER_11]: No!
[SPEAKER_11]: Swooncream.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sort of salty.
[SPEAKER_02]: Schoolgirl?
[SPEAKER_02]: Probably like sweaty palms.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: Billy's locked in.
[SPEAKER_15]: Good.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let's read the answers.
[SPEAKER_15]: First, EOSFVB.
[SPEAKER_15]: EOSFVB goes first this time.
[SPEAKER_15]: Dear Propel, you really need to make ass flavor.
[SPEAKER_15]: Ass flavor.
[SPEAKER_15]: Beautiful.
[SPEAKER_15]: BlackLat says, Dear Propel, you really need to make tack flavor.
[SPEAKER_15]: Ah, very good.
[SPEAKER_15]: Tack flavor.
[SPEAKER_15]: Good answer.
[SPEAKER_15]: Also matched with Angel and Dark Tetsuya.
[SPEAKER_15]: Both said that in the chatroom at different points.
[SPEAKER_15]: But you don't get a point for them.
[SPEAKER_15]: and Ohio Bomani makes a good point.
[SPEAKER_15]: Lemon-flavored is ass-flavored.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, Jamie, you are going to go first.
[SPEAKER_15]: And this would be the correct answer, hypothetically.
[SPEAKER_02]: As much as I enjoy the thought of tax-flavored Pocari Sweat, my answer is Pocari Sweat.
[SPEAKER_15]: Ah, Pocari Sweat-flavored.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: Good, good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which, you know, is actually going to be mentioned in my puppy of the week later on.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right, moving on.
[SPEAKER_15]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, see, I had Blood of a Virgin on there as a flavor, but I'm just going to go with Vanilla Coke flavor.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry, Blood of a Virgin wouldn't be good because I don't want to do that next time.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right, so we had Vanilla Coke flavor.
[SPEAKER_15]: Not a bad answer, not a bad answer.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right, Billy.
[SPEAKER_15]: Cream of some young guy.
[SPEAKER_15]: Cream of some young guy flavor.
[SPEAKER_15]: Good answer, but not a match, sorry.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: Zero.
[SPEAKER_12]: Sadly enough, I did write ass.
[SPEAKER_12]: Wait.
[SPEAKER_12]: Wait, did Billy say some young guy or some... Oh, I thought it was like some young guy.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's like, is that some Japanese food or something?
[SPEAKER_12]: No, I just... No, I have seen it.
[SPEAKER_12]: I just... I didn't comprehend it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Answer!
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: I want to say what?
[SPEAKER_18]: I speak just as well.
[SPEAKER_12]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: I speak just as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: Ours was okra flavored.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mmm.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okra.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like gumbo.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: And my answer, because I guess that Jamie ate a lot of it when she was younger and maybe she wanted to relive her youth, I put paste flavored.
[SPEAKER_02]: I never ate paste flavored.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although, what I would do is I would take school glue and pour it on my hand.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then when it dries, it dries clear.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then I would go up to people and peel it back.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god, my skin!
Ah!
Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: Or paper.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, we had a point.
[SPEAKER_15]: We did get finally one point.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, EOSFBB takes the lead by one point.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's not about being right, it's about being funny.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_15]: Next question.
[SPEAKER_15]: Two more left.
[SPEAKER_15]: We've got a five question game.
[SPEAKER_15]: Billy the Big Homosexual loved to play gay Bomani songs.
[SPEAKER_15]: He really wished that they would put blank into DDR Billy the Big Homosexual loved to play Gabe Imani songs He really wished that they would put blank into DDR I have mine Just fill in the blank with whatever you want
[SPEAKER_15]: Billy the Big Homosexual loved to play Gabe Imani songs.
[SPEAKER_15]: He really wished they would put blank in the DDR.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_15]: I didn't say it was you.
[SPEAKER_15]: How many people are named Billy?
[SPEAKER_15]: Are you insinuating something?
[SPEAKER_15]: Is everybody locked in?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yes, is Billy locked in?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, answer.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, both our contestants are locked in.
[SPEAKER_15]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_18]: Are you guys locked in?
[SPEAKER_18]: Dynamic Duo?
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's that name?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Robin.
[SPEAKER_15]: Black Lab says, I really wish that they would put some lamb into DDR.
[SPEAKER_15]: Lamb.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, good answer, but no.
[SPEAKER_15]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh!
[SPEAKER_15]: The OSFBB says, I really wish that they would put some bars that rape you back into DDR.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's a good one.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, let's see if there's any matches.
[SPEAKER_15]: Jamie.
[SPEAKER_15]: Billy really wishes that they would put... Back That Ass Up.
[SPEAKER_15]: Back That Ass Up in the DDR.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, not a match, but a good answer.
[SPEAKER_15]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_17]: From last week, Temple of Butt.
[SPEAKER_15]: Temple of Butt!
[SPEAKER_15]: Billy's all, ooh!
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, Billy, now this would be the correct answer, supposedly, in a perfect world.
[SPEAKER_15]: Billy, what should they do?
[SPEAKER_15]: Insert any Kylie song here.
[SPEAKER_15]: If you knew Billie, you knew just go with Kylie Minogue.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's all you had to do.
[SPEAKER_15]: Now, this is the funny thing.
[SPEAKER_15]: Kylie Minogue shows up on all those Dance Mania albums, but they have not put her in DDR yet.
[SPEAKER_15]: What?
[SPEAKER_15]: Dancing States Party Edition, remember, had... The British version, the British home version, had Can't Get You Out of My Head On It.
[SPEAKER_15]: Billy Says, which goes to show it's America's Awesome.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: Zero.
[SPEAKER_15]: I really wish they'd put Naoki Naked.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's good.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_15]: Sorry, I'm just checking.
[SPEAKER_15]: I know, I'm just... Dynamic Duo.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm sorry, I was just closing private message rooms.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yes, Dynamic Duo says, Billy wishes they would put some... Dolphin Cry.
[SPEAKER_15]: Dolphin Cry.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's a sexual position, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yes, Dynamic Duo is a good one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, I said, um...
[SPEAKER_15]: My answer was Billy the Big Homosexual loved to play Gabe Imani songs.
[SPEAKER_15]: He really wished they would put more Para songs into DR. Yay, you're a B!
[SPEAKER_15]: More Parabar songs, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not a match.
[SPEAKER_15]: Shine loose to both our contestants.
[SPEAKER_15]: The OSFBB is still up by one.
[SPEAKER_15]: Black Lab, this is your last chance to catch up.
[SPEAKER_15]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, we had a request to hear the dolphin cry one more time.
[SPEAKER_13]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_13]: They call him Flipper.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right, thank you.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, here we go.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right, last question.
[SPEAKER_15]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_15]: Last chance to catch up, Black Lab.
[SPEAKER_15]: We predict on next week's drunk show, Jamie is going to get so drunk that she ends up blank.
I have it.
La la la, I'm still thinking.
Why did I put this question in there?
This is a hard one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, the contestants aren't locked in yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: They still haven't sent.
[SPEAKER_15]: We predict on next week's Drunk Show, Jamie's going to get so drunk that she ends up blank.
[SPEAKER_15]: We're waiting on the contestants.
[SPEAKER_15]: All the celebrities are in?
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: We're just waiting for the two contestants.
[SPEAKER_15]: Any day now, you two.
[SPEAKER_15]: One's in.
[SPEAKER_15]: Waiting on one more contestant.
[SPEAKER_15]: Are you waving your Raybar light around?
[SPEAKER_15]: I wonder if we're getting a big long paragraph or something.
[SPEAKER_15]: Jamie knows it's all in good fun, but she reserves the right to cut you.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_15]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_15]: We'll start off with the person in the lead.
[SPEAKER_15]: We predict on next week's Drunk Show, EOSFVB says Jamie is going to get so drunk that she ends up lesbian.
[SPEAKER_15]: That got three blinks.
[SPEAKER_15]: Black Lab says... Black Lab also says lesbian.
[SPEAKER_15]: She's gonna get so drunk she ends up lesbian.
[SPEAKER_15]: Is that because we all get gay when we drink?
[SPEAKER_15]: Do I go straight when I drink?
[SPEAKER_15]: Actually, I kinda do.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, don't you people know that I already have made the vow that if Dan and I ever break up, I'm getting a girlfriend?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I hate men anyway, mostly.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just don't find anything about that as funny.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because men love lesbians.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: Jamie's gonna get so drunk she... Ends up saying...
[SPEAKER_15]: Ends up sane.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's a good answer.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: Next up, Loki.
[SPEAKER_15]: She ends up... Mine's always... Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: I said... I said lesbian, dammit!
[SPEAKER_15]: So they get a point each.
[SPEAKER_15]: They get a point each.
[SPEAKER_15]: Too bad it's... They answered the same thing.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: Billy, she ends up... Naked.
[SPEAKER_15]: Naked.
[SPEAKER_15]: Good answer.
[SPEAKER_16]: Zero, she ends up... I thought I was going to be original with this, but lesbian is what I came up with.
[SPEAKER_15]: Two points.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, it's too easy.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's the easy answer.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's the cop-out answer.
[SPEAKER_15]: Brad Dave put... Do the lead-in.
[SPEAKER_15]: Jamie's going to get so drunk that she... Ends up... Ends up... Using the microphone.
[SPEAKER_14]: Use your imagination.
[SPEAKER_18]: Put out your hand.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm starting to hurt.
[SPEAKER_15]: Now, mine's, amazingly enough, I think I have the most PG-rated answer.
[SPEAKER_15]: Jamie's going to end up so drunk that she ends up making out with a Happy Bunny doll.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, mine was.
[SPEAKER_02]: I said same.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, that's true.
[SPEAKER_15]: You said same.
[SPEAKER_15]: You had the G-rated answer.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just kicked you.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, the final scores.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let's tally them up.
[SPEAKER_15]: Black Lab has two points.
[SPEAKER_15]: EOSFVB wins tonight with three points.
[SPEAKER_15]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_02]: You win a bottle of Propel.
[SPEAKER_15]: You win nothing.
[SPEAKER_02]: You win a bottle of Propel, but you have to go buy it yourself.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, great.
[SPEAKER_15]: Beautiful.
[SPEAKER_15]: Thank you to all the stars.
[SPEAKER_02]: This show was brought to you by Propel and Balls.
[SPEAKER_02]: Somebody needs to come and bring me some balls.
[SPEAKER_15]: No rave, please.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: The light switch was installed so you could turn the light on and off.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not so you could throw light switch rave.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, I think we're going to go to another break.
[SPEAKER_15]: I have to ask JB some questions.
[SPEAKER_15]: JB sent me a remix.
[SPEAKER_15]: No rave, please.
[SPEAKER_15]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_15]: JB sent me a remix.
[SPEAKER_15]: Is this one you did yourself, JB?
[SPEAKER_15]: That's what I want to know.
[SPEAKER_15]: Can you let me know that?
[SPEAKER_15]: Because we're going to play that going into this next break.
[SPEAKER_15]: CageMatch, we'll do what?
[SPEAKER_15]: You want to do CageMatch next?
[SPEAKER_15]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_15]: We can do CageMatch in a little while.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll do CageMatch next.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, we'll do CageMatch next.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, we're going to do CageMatch next when we come back.
[SPEAKER_15]: We'll take a quick break.
[SPEAKER_15]: I think we're just going to do a one-song break.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I just want to know if this is... I already know that I'm going to win.
[SPEAKER_15]: I just want to know if this is JB's own remix or not.
[SPEAKER_15]: I already know that I'm going to win.
[SPEAKER_15]: So that was a fun match game.
[SPEAKER_15]: We haven't done a match game in a few weeks.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's been about a month since we've done a match game.
[SPEAKER_12]: Is there a topic for Listless yet?
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't win last time.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't know if we'll do Listless now.
[SPEAKER_15]: We might take a week off from Listless.
[SPEAKER_02]: Didn't I get dethroned by the cussing song last week?
[SPEAKER_15]: The what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Didn't the cussing song win last week?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, the cussing song did not win last week.
[SPEAKER_02]: I won, didn't I?
[SPEAKER_15]: Remember, Jenny Bean had the tiebreaker vote.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, you brought a cage match song and everything?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I can dethrone it myself.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, we'll just play Jamie's song at some point during the show during another break.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I'll pick a different song.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, so... What do we just play during this break?
[SPEAKER_15]: You just want to play your song?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, why not?
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: Then we'll save, because I haven't gotten the answer on JB's mix if it was him or not, so I'll wait on that.
[SPEAKER_15]: And in the meantime, we'll play... It's the song that Puppy sent me.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: So what is it?
[SPEAKER_15]: Describe this for us, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think it needs any description.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just play it.
[SPEAKER_15]: No description needed, huh?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just a cool song.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, we're going to play this and we'll be right back.
[SPEAKER_15]: We'll play this and another quick song and then we'll be back on Orange Lounge Radio with the Cage Match.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hi-ho, Kermit the Frog here, informing you that today's broadcast of Orange Lounge Radio is brought to you by the letter B, the letter A, and the number 59.
[SPEAKER_06]: Can you tell me how to get, how to get to Sesame Street?
[SPEAKER_15]: We are back!
[SPEAKER_15]: Oops, I accidentally had the repeat thing on.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, we're just trying to recover from that Magic Game segment.
[SPEAKER_15]: Billy left.
[SPEAKER_15]: He says goodbye to everybody.
[SPEAKER_15]: He had to go fuck somebody in the house.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, we're back and we're chilling.
[SPEAKER_15]: How are y'all doing?
[SPEAKER_15]: How was your week?
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't know what they're doing in the other room.
[SPEAKER_15]: I hope my roommate's not trying to sleep, is he?
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, good, he's not.
[SPEAKER_02]: My week was a big pile of ass.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why, what happened?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I don't know, it was okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got some hanging out and did lots of busy, rocky things.
[SPEAKER_02]: I went costume hunting a bunch.
[SPEAKER_02]: I still couldn't find a damn globe.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, we haven't done our fuck-yous.
[SPEAKER_15]: We'll do the fuck-yous a little later.
[SPEAKER_15]: We always do the fuck-yous towards the beginning.
[SPEAKER_15]: I figure we'll save it towards the end.
[SPEAKER_02]: And last night was just insane.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that I don't remember much of last night because I was not feeling happy.
[SPEAKER_15]: Last night was crazy.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yes, yes, definitely.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you were fabulous.
[SPEAKER_15]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_15]: For those that don't know, we're here in Orange Lounge World Radio headquarters in Sacramento, California.
[SPEAKER_15]: A lot of us that are involved here with the show are also involved with the local production of Rocky Horror Picture Show, so we were doing that last night.
[SPEAKER_15]: and that was a lot of energy.
[SPEAKER_15]: So if we seem a little dead tonight, we're still kind of recovering from last night.
[SPEAKER_15]: However, Jamie was kind enough to go to Walgreens and get some double shots drinks of those coffee things.
[SPEAKER_02]: Starbucks double shots.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: So actually this episode of Orange Lodge Radio not only is brought to you by Propel and Ass.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or Ass Flavor Propel.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's brought to you by Starbucks double shot vehicle, you know, drink.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bitter Ass Coffee.
[SPEAKER_15]: How was your week, Loki?
[SPEAKER_17]: I went and played Cuser last night.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, didn't you have a story about this?
[SPEAKER_15]: You've got plenty of FUs besides this.
[SPEAKER_15]: Come on, tell the story.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yesterday was interesting.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, Zero went with me, so he can, you know, okay.
[SPEAKER_17]: It was great.
[SPEAKER_17]: It was good.
[SPEAKER_17]: Vacaville, you know, it's really close, a lot closer than Concord or Pleasanton.
[SPEAKER_16]: Stay away.
[SPEAKER_17]: It was nice.
[SPEAKER_17]: Now, the bowling alley, it's actually in Sars Entertainment.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's like a bowling alley type place.
[SPEAKER_17]: They've got, like, a nice restaurant in there and, like, pizza and an arcade and stuff.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm sure I'll go into this with my FUs later on, but they had Fifth Mix and Max 2 there, both in really poor condition.
[SPEAKER_17]: Very poor.
[SPEAKER_17]: Everything was broken there.
[SPEAKER_17]: Even the soda machine was pretty much all randomized.
[SPEAKER_17]: You'd pick one soda and get something else.
[SPEAKER_16]: The soda machine was like roulette.
[SPEAKER_16]: If you touched it, you didn't get what you wanted.
[SPEAKER_17]: And then, um, now the Cusar was the worst run Cusar I've ever seen.
[SPEAKER_17]: The arena was awesome, the packs were in good condition, but it was the worst run Cusar.
[SPEAKER_17]: Ever.
[SPEAKER_17]: And there was annoying people there.
[SPEAKER_17]: Vacaville was full of hicks and wannabe gangstas.
[SPEAKER_16]: Loki, what's a syringe?
[SPEAKER_16]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_17]: We'll go into that later.
[SPEAKER_17]: But, uh,
[SPEAKER_16]: It was interesting.
[SPEAKER_17]: It became more fun later on when all the stupid people started leaving.
[SPEAKER_02]: It sounded like ass.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_17]: Very much.
[SPEAKER_17]: So that and the lack of sleep I've been doing the last few days because I've been going to bed at like 6 in the morning and getting like 3 hours of sleep.
[SPEAKER_15]: As far as my week goes, I've been kind of getting ready for Rocky 2.
[SPEAKER_15]: I've done a lot.
[SPEAKER_15]: I went out and played Bomani, I think, one time this week.
[SPEAKER_15]: I found that I'm suddenly, all of a sudden, I'm really into DDR Extreme.
[SPEAKER_15]: Like, all of a sudden, I'm into DDR again.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I think a lot of that has to do with Jamie on Lomi, her fifth mix, so I can make some link data.
[SPEAKER_15]: So I can make some new link data for Extreme.
[SPEAKER_15]: And now, like, I have something to accomplish.
[SPEAKER_15]: Like, oh my gods, I've got to get a double A on this.
[SPEAKER_15]: We need to re... I'm sorry, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_02]: We need to set our night where we do nothing but DDR.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm looking at the audio.
[SPEAKER_15]: We kind of used to do those on Friday night, but that physical... Well, we used to, way in the day, we did it on Wednesday night, but then I started going to karaoke, except I'm not even going anymore, so maybe we could just do Wednesdays again.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, maybe that'll work.
[SPEAKER_16]: I need to get a copy of Fifth.
[SPEAKER_16]: I need to start making edits so bad.
[SPEAKER_16]: I do fourth edits all the time, and they're getting kind of old now.
[SPEAKER_15]: We can probably get you a copy of Fifth one way or another.
[SPEAKER_15]: If Jamie lets me keep her copy a couple more days, I'll make you a copy.
[SPEAKER_16]: I brought you, like, ten CDs to burn stuff on.
[SPEAKER_16]: Cool!
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, whatever works.
[SPEAKER_15]: We don't endorse pirating on this show.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, we don't.
[SPEAKER_15]: Actually, I'll be honest.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'll be honest.
[SPEAKER_15]: We never really talked about this on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let me talk about my views on pirating games.
[SPEAKER_15]: As far as DDR is concerned, and the money stuff.
[SPEAKER_15]: Never the US ones, always the Japanese ones.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I say it's okay, because I think...
[SPEAKER_15]: The price you pay to import this stuff is just outrageous.
[SPEAKER_15]: To import this stuff from Japan.
[SPEAKER_15]: And honestly, if they wanted me to buy it, they'd release it in this country.
[SPEAKER_15]: So I figure if they're not going to release it in this country, if they're not going to take that effort to satisfy our demand by releasing it here, then I'm going to pirate it.
[SPEAKER_15]: But I have bought every U.S.
[SPEAKER_15]: Bomani release.
[SPEAKER_15]: Every one.
[SPEAKER_15]: Even the very crappy first USA mix, I bought it just because I wanted to support Bomani.
[SPEAKER_02]: And reserve them at GameStop.
[SPEAKER_02]: The one at Arden Fair Mall.
[SPEAKER_15]: Another plug.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, even still, I think it's kind of crap that you have to buy their shit that they release in order for them to hopefully bring out better stuff later on.
[SPEAKER_17]: I think that's really stupid.
[SPEAKER_15]: They did, but DDR Max was pretty good, you have to admit.
[SPEAKER_17]: It was pretty good, but like, USA, the first one sucked ass.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, and I played it maybe twice, but I felt, okay, this is kind of the way I felt, I said, okay, I played all those Japanese ones for free, so I played all these songs for free.
[SPEAKER_02]: But did you see the first one they released in Japan?
[SPEAKER_02]: It was kind of bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, the one, well, but it had strictly business.
[SPEAKER_02]: In comparison, though, to everything since, you know, you have to start somewhere.
[SPEAKER_15]: I mean, this is an old, old debate that goes, you know, back about a year now.
[SPEAKER_15]: Was that when USA was released, about a year ago?
[SPEAKER_15]: More than that.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, that was a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_15]: The Disney mix, the USA one, I played that one time.
[SPEAKER_15]: I just don't even really play those songs, but I bought it just because I had played Disney's Rave a lot.
[SPEAKER_16]: So it was kind of my conscience.
[SPEAKER_15]: I think Somni Magus has my copy and doesn't realize it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have the Japanese version sitting right in front of the US one in my collection at home.
[SPEAKER_15]: So I think I played it one time so I could get the maniac steps.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I wanted to see how hard the ten-footers were, and then I was unimpressed.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dance magic, enough said.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, it's all about dance magic.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, um... Yeah, I say it's okay to pirate the Japanese ones.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is this your yo-yo?
[SPEAKER_15]: No, it's Brian's.
[SPEAKER_02]: Brian's yo-yo sucks.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm gonna get you a yo-yo.
[SPEAKER_15]: You can buy Brian a yo-yo.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll buy Brian a yo-yo.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: So... I want a yo-yo ball right now.
[SPEAKER_15]: Do you want to talk Sim stuff?
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, Sim.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, you want to talk about this?
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: This was just announced this week.
[SPEAKER_15]: Konami in Japan's making a brand new game.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's called Aerobics Revolution.
[SPEAKER_15]: Tell me it doesn't remind you of an old school 8-bit game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Dance Aerobics.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's Dance Aerobics.
[SPEAKER_15]: I swear to God, it looks just like it.
[SPEAKER_02]: With DDR steps.
[SPEAKER_15]: But basically, it's going to be an aerobics game that uses your DDR mat.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know what you love it?
[SPEAKER_15]: And it looks like it has a little DDR sim mode.
[SPEAKER_15]: They're kind of taking diet mode and making it its own game, I guess.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_15]: We don't really know much about this.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks like it's a home one.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, it's going to be a home release for PlayStation 2, and it's going to be out March 13th.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jamie's getting this.
[SPEAKER_15]: And it looks like it's going to follow the Shadow Dancers, kind of like a power mode, so it's probably got aerobics routines in it.
[SPEAKER_06]: That looks cool.
[SPEAKER_15]: And it'll probably keep track of how well you're doing by the feet.
[SPEAKER_15]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_15]: Dance Aerobics was very similar, I thought.
[SPEAKER_15]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_15]: We'll compare.
[SPEAKER_15]: When this aerobics revolution comes out, we'll see how similar it was to dance aerobics.
[SPEAKER_15]: I did play dance aerobics one time back in the day.
[SPEAKER_15]: I borrowed a power pad from my best friend in elementary school.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have a power pad and I have dance aerobics.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you?
[SPEAKER_15]: In track and field.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_15]: On one week on Orange Lounge, we need to have a power pad night.
[SPEAKER_15]: We need to have the power pad Olympics on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: I kicked your ass.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, we're going to do that one night.
[SPEAKER_15]: We'll get a crowd here and we'll move the show out into the other room.
[SPEAKER_15]: We'll have the Power Pad Olympics.
[SPEAKER_15]: How's that sound?
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, cool.
[SPEAKER_16]: It looks like that Dancerobics looks like he uses all the buttons, too.
[SPEAKER_16]: All six?
[SPEAKER_15]: It looks like there's almost one in the middle.
[SPEAKER_15]: You see how this one has it lit up?
[SPEAKER_15]: But I don't think there's a button on the... I don't think they would do that.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_15]: Maybe it's just showing where your feet are supposed to be.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe you're using one foot forward.
[SPEAKER_02]: See that?
[SPEAKER_15]: A lot of this is speculation.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's move to the chat room.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, we'll link the chatroom to this just in case you guys haven't heard about this yet and you want to look up the site like we're looking at right now.
[SPEAKER_15]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_15]: And if you're not in our chatroom, why the hell not?
[SPEAKER_15]: Get over to our website, orangelounge.skie.cx and click on chatroom.
[SPEAKER_02]: This game actually does look pretty interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm definitely going to get it when it's out.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, you might get a full review from me.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_17]: Whatever the fuck happened to Marshall B.?
[SPEAKER_15]: Wasn't, okay, I've seen the Marshall Beat Machine once in Arcade Infinity.
[SPEAKER_16]: They do have a home version of it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Don't they have a home version of it?
[SPEAKER_16]: They do, I played it just this week.
[SPEAKER_16]: Pretty much.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's, it's like, it's horrible.
[SPEAKER_16]: It has sensors on your hands and legs.
[SPEAKER_16]: There's a link to it, if you go, there's someone selling a bunch of them on eBay, and they'll send you to the Konami site where they actually talk about it.
[SPEAKER_16]: It looks so retarded.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's like you're fighting in Dance Beat.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's interesting.
[SPEAKER_15]: When Loki and I were at AI a couple weeks ago when we were off one week from the show, we were at Arcade Infinity.
[SPEAKER_15]: We saw a Marshall Beat Machine and not a damn person playing it the whole night.
[SPEAKER_15]: I thought I'd look like an idiot playing it.
[SPEAKER_17]: There's actually two versions of it for the home now.
[SPEAKER_17]: They have the first one, and I guess they just released the second one recently.
[SPEAKER_16]: I think they made the sequel before they made the first one.
[SPEAKER_16]: It was pretty bad.
[SPEAKER_16]: That just sounds like utter ass.
[SPEAKER_15]: Marshall Beat is missable, basically, is what we're all kind of coming to a consensus on.
[SPEAKER_17]: Was there any songs that weren't in DDR?
[SPEAKER_17]: Punch Mania.
[SPEAKER_17]: Crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Gun Mania is cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gun Mania is cool.
[SPEAKER_15]: Gun Mania is cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the pellet shooting game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gun Mania.
[SPEAKER_02]: They had an AI, but it's always broken.
[SPEAKER_02]: I made a joke that I was going to move in there and build a bed in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because it's large enough.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's huge.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_14]: Moving right along.
[SPEAKER_15]: We'll look into that after the show, what we're being told in the show right now.
[SPEAKER_15]: What else is going on in DD World?
[SPEAKER_15]: Is anything going on in SimWorld, Loki?
[SPEAKER_15]: You want to talk about sim stuff, Loki?
[SPEAKER_17]: Uh, okay, I guess.
[SPEAKER_17]: Let's see, they've got another style 2003 still going on.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's that other DWI contest thingy.
[SPEAKER_17]: My site is coming up someday, so that'll be it.
[SPEAKER_17]: But my site is releasing more of the DDR Extreme sim files.
[SPEAKER_17]: You can find them with the backgrounds and all that wonderful stuff.
[SPEAKER_15]: Are they still having Jesus Complex about it?
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't know, I don't care anymore.
[SPEAKER_17]: Um, they're also doing a full re-release on all the, uh, old, uh, official sim files, and they're doing them with, uh, CD, um, what was it, the, uh, little CD banner things on there also.
[SPEAKER_17]: Um, and then, see, actually, all the, um, DDR Extreme ones have been released with banners, just not by Romani style.
[SPEAKER_17]: They're on another site, but I can't remember which one.
[SPEAKER_17]: So no help there.
[SPEAKER_17]: Just look on DDR Freak.
[SPEAKER_17]: Or not DDR Freak.
[SPEAKER_17]: DDR Maniacs.
[SPEAKER_17]: You'll find a link for it, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_17]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_17]: Other than that, not too much going on at all.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's been incredibly slow.
[SPEAKER_17]: No real sim updates.
[SPEAKER_17]: I mean, they had a CSB snapshot update of Step Mania that they're working on that was released back on the...
[SPEAKER_17]: D.W.I 2.4
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_17]: There's nothing going on.
[SPEAKER_17]: Just forget it.
[SPEAKER_17]: Slow.
[SPEAKER_17]: Just watch DDR Maniacs and BomaniSims.com for homemade stuff because you'll find the most released stuff there.
[SPEAKER_17]: Bomani style, you'll find the official stuff there.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_17]: Check the Japanese sites because there's always all these Japanese sites you guys are missing and they have really cool shit on there.
[SPEAKER_15]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_15]: And of course, the most notable news in the DWI sim file world, Orange Lounge Radio is doing a contest.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, we're doing a contest.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, so why not, let's do the cage match now?
[SPEAKER_15]: Shall we?
[SPEAKER_15]: Sure!
[SPEAKER_15]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, well I gotta queue up some stuff, so fill time while I queue up all the cage match stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Filling time, filling time, filling up the time.
[SPEAKER_15]: What was the funniest thing that happened to you this week, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_02]: I saw Robin drag.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like a big old queen.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it was great.
[SPEAKER_02]: You were great.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm beautiful, dammit.
[SPEAKER_02]: You definitely lit the stage.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm gonna set this stage on fire.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yep, it was flaming all night.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, so, let's start off.
[SPEAKER_15]: Just one second, we're gonna get to... We need our theme song.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yes, here's the theme song.
[SPEAKER_15]: Which, if you were paying attention, you know is Jamie's favorite tax song.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm now wet.
[SPEAKER_15]: Last week in the Orange Lounge Cage Match, for the second week in a row...
[SPEAKER_15]: Vincent Damore won it with Eternity.
[SPEAKER_15]: So this is the first song you can vote for in tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_15]: By the way, if you're new to this, you join our chatroom, you send me tonight.
[SPEAKER_15]: My name is Sky Chatroom Slut.
[SPEAKER_15]: Or you can email them to OrangeLoungeRadio at Yahoo.com.
[SPEAKER_15]: Email the song you like best out of the three you hear.
[SPEAKER_15]: We don't accept votes until the end of the third song when I say send votes.
[SPEAKER_15]: And the winner gets put into Orange Lounge rotation for the whole week.
[SPEAKER_15]: And this song has been in for two weeks now.
[SPEAKER_15]: Looking for its third week.
[SPEAKER_18]: This is the second time this has happened to me.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, Jamie's requesting I play a certain part of this song, hold on.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, that's song number one you can vote for.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's Vincent Damore with Eternity.
[SPEAKER_15]: Now, I noticed Loki's got something.
[SPEAKER_15]: He's trying very hard this week.
[SPEAKER_15]: He might do it to throw in Eternity.
[SPEAKER_15]: If any song's going to do it, it's going to be this one.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't even know why I'm going to bother tonight.
[SPEAKER_17]: But, Loki, read it out.
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright, this one's a brand new track.
[SPEAKER_17]: Loki vs. ZZ featuring Sun Decade.
[SPEAKER_17]: This is the debut of the finished version of The Legend of Trance.
[SPEAKER_15]: Here it is, the Legend of Trance, Loki's cage match pick tonight.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, that was Loki himself versus ZZ featuring Sun Decade with the Legend of Trance.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, what did you guys think of it?
[SPEAKER_15]: Jamie?
[SPEAKER_15]: That was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, you're looking very pleased with yourself.
[SPEAKER_17]: Of course, I made it.
[SPEAKER_18]: You're looking giddy.
[SPEAKER_17]: I like that song.
[SPEAKER_18]: Get a nine.
[SPEAKER_18]: Are we on?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, we're on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, you get nine.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alrighty.
[SPEAKER_12]: Zero.
[SPEAKER_16]: Well, like, I actually had a chance to listen to it last night on the way the views are.
[SPEAKER_16]: I mean, I definitely give it a nine.
[SPEAKER_16]: It was a great song.
[SPEAKER_15]: Loki, what'd you think?
[SPEAKER_15]: Dare I ask?
[SPEAKER_17]: He gives himself a 69.
[SPEAKER_17]: I like it.
[SPEAKER_17]: I, you know...
[SPEAKER_17]: It can always be better, but yeah, 9.
[SPEAKER_17]: Find a 10, because I can!
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm sure he doesn't have a big ego now.
[SPEAKER_12]: Um, it was very well done.
[SPEAKER_12]: I give it a nine.
[SPEAKER_15]: Ooh, nines across the board so far.
[SPEAKER_17]: Brad?
[SPEAKER_17]: I think the earlier version of it gets a nine.
[SPEAKER_14]: This, he cleaned it up.
[SPEAKER_14]: This gets a ten.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, a ten from Brad.
[SPEAKER_15]: Wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_15]: For the Legend of Trance.
[SPEAKER_15]: Never mind.
[SPEAKER_15]: It was crap.
[SPEAKER_15]: I give it a zero.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right, um, Loki, what...
[SPEAKER_15]: What can I say, Loki?
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm your biggest fanboy, but I'm not going to inflate your ego by giving you a 10, so you get a 9.9.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, damn.
[SPEAKER_15]: So he gets a 9.9.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, there is your first two songs, Eternity from Vincent D'Amore and Loki with the Legend of Trance.
[SPEAKER_15]: I've decided, since both of those two are very kick-ass songs, there's no way in fucking hell I was going to win with my original pick, so I'm going for Broke.
[SPEAKER_15]: Forget this trance stuff.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm just gonna play something that's fucking cool.
[SPEAKER_15]: So my pick for tonight's cage match comes from a little movie you may or may not have heard of.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's a musical, because everybody loves musicals.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's from a little story about a boy who's a girl.
[SPEAKER_15]: And it's called Hedwig and the Angry Inch.
[SPEAKER_15]: So my pick for tonight's cage match is Angry Inch from the movie Hedwig and the Angry Inch.
[SPEAKER_15]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_15]: This song really would make a kick-ass guitar freak song.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, fuck you!
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, enjoy.
[SPEAKER_15]: This is Hedwig and the Angry Inch.
[SPEAKER_09]: Angry Inch.
[SPEAKER_09]: One must give up a little part of oneself.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: When I woke up from the operation, I was bleeding down there I was bleeding from the gash between my legs It was my first day as a woman, already that time of the month Two days later the hole closed out, you know The wound healed and I was left with a one inch mound of flesh Where my penis used to be, where my vagina never was, it was a one
[SPEAKER_10]: And I left space It was just a little buzz, there was nothing I could hear Six inches forward, five inches back The train is coming and I'm tired of the track I try to get along but I can't get no slack I got one here and here, and here and here And I got an active four, five inches back Stay on the job until the night turns to night I got my inch, I'm set to attack
[SPEAKER_15]: We got a lot of dots from the chat room.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, how do we get the Angry Inch with Angry Inch?
[SPEAKER_05]: Jamie gives it a 10.
[SPEAKER_15]: Loki, it's 0.
[SPEAKER_16]: She just wants to give it a 10 so her song works again.
[SPEAKER_16]: I don't know about that.
[SPEAKER_16]: I guess I'll give it like...
[SPEAKER_16]: It was funny as hell, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_16]: I will see the movie one day and then I'll give it something higher maybe.
[SPEAKER_12]: I give it an 8 because it had colorful lyrics.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, I give it an 8.
[SPEAKER_15]: I would actually go to Roseville Golf Line and play that for when the parents bring their little children home.
[SPEAKER_02]: You may start sending in your votes now to myself in the chatroom, Sky Chatroom Slut, or you can send those over email to orangebossradio at yahoo.com.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let's review, shall we, really quickly.
[SPEAKER_15]: Choice number one, Eternity by Vincent Damore.
[SPEAKER_15]: Choice number two, Loki with The Legend of Trance.
[SPEAKER_15]: Choice number three, Hedwig and the Angry Inch with Angry Inch.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, there they are.
[SPEAKER_15]: Vote now.
[SPEAKER_15]: We'll tally those votes up during the next break.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, wow, that was a fun cage match.
[SPEAKER_15]: We had an old favorite trance song, a new favorite trance song, and an anti-trance song.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anti-trance.
[SPEAKER_15]: Good, good, good cage match.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, what else is up?
[SPEAKER_02]: I need to do my request of the week.
[SPEAKER_02]: You need to do your request of the week.
[SPEAKER_02]: For any aspiring person who wants to make a mix of anything, I want the Safari trance mix.
[SPEAKER_15]: You want a trance mix of the Safari?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, my request is still out there.
[SPEAKER_15]: I played the Safari today and I failed very badly.
[SPEAKER_02]: We need to play the Safari during the break.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, we'll play Safari during the break.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember, for whoever makes this for me, I'm going to reward you in some form or fashion if it's cool.
[SPEAKER_15]: Dark Tetsuya was reminding me of something I need to play for y'all just to get what your thoughts are on this.
[SPEAKER_15]: For y'all.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought I was the southern chick here.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm just a southern bale in a boy's body.
[SPEAKER_15]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can get you one of those trail maid dresses.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm being told that this is a clip from a new song in Poppin' Music 9.
[SPEAKER_15]: Tell me if this sounds a little familiar to you guys.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right, that's the clip we got.
[SPEAKER_15]: Dude, I would play that in Drum Mania.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't know the story behind that, where that came from.
[SPEAKER_15]: I guess I'm being told it's Poppin' Music 9.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't know enough about Poppin' Music to know if that's true or not.
[SPEAKER_02]: Check the Japanese site, the music list.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, from what I remember, the original URL that was posted from was from Bomani Cell.
[SPEAKER_15]: Ah, all right.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, yeah, Guitar Freaks version.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't know about Poppin' Music.
[SPEAKER_15]: Sounds more Guitar Freaks to me, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, you have Dyke and Ty, I mean, from, uh... True.
[SPEAKER_17]: True.
[SPEAKER_17]: I mean, that's... Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: The freaking Cutie Honey theme song in pop music.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's labeled as not as absolute as... It's labeled as avatage.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's what they had on there.
[SPEAKER_17]: They were talking about, like, if they were to make lyrics for it, like, if we drink a real in for a hot limit, it was Icy Frozen Lightning Bolt.
[SPEAKER_15]: I have very few votes registered in right now for the cage match.
[SPEAKER_15]: I hope you all are voting.
[SPEAKER_15]: Send those in, or we'll kill you.
[SPEAKER_17]: Vote or you get kicked.
[SPEAKER_15]: Vote or you, yeah, vote or you get kicked from the chat room.
[SPEAKER_15]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or we slap you with a trout.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, no, but seriously, you guys only have a few more minutes to send votes.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, I promised we would play this last break.
[SPEAKER_15]: We didn't get around to it.
[SPEAKER_15]: But this is a JB mix.
[SPEAKER_15]: We've heard something from Loki.
[SPEAKER_15]: One of our other regulars, JB, made a remix of...
[SPEAKER_15]: Guess what?
[SPEAKER_15]: A Jenny Rom song.
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_15]: But you know what, JB?
[SPEAKER_02]: Hide the children.
[SPEAKER_15]: JB did some good shit with that Sega thing, the Sega CD BIOS music.
[SPEAKER_15]: So I'm actually looking forward to hearing this.
[SPEAKER_15]: I think this will be very cool.
[SPEAKER_15]: This is a remix of Jenny Rom with Do You Wanna Flirt?
[SPEAKER_15]: It's called the Modern Dub Remix, and I'm looking forward to hearing it.
[SPEAKER_15]: And you should, too.
[SPEAKER_15]: This is a remix by JB in our chatroom.
[SPEAKER_15]: Here we go, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, my apologies to JB because that's the modem mix.
[SPEAKER_15]: Modem dub mix, not the modern dub mix.
[SPEAKER_15]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_15]: Jesus.
[SPEAKER_15]: So that's the modem dub mix.
[SPEAKER_15]: Nice job.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, back to break.
[SPEAKER_15]: We'll be back.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't turn me
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's listen in on an Orange Lounge Radio staff meeting.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do you want to be accepted by Hollywood?
[SPEAKER_10]: No!
[SPEAKER_07]: Do we care what people think of us?
[SPEAKER_07]: No!
[SPEAKER_07]: Do we want people to kiss our ass?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_01]: Extreme Bobani Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's us.
[SPEAKER_01]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because I love it when people kiss my ass.
No!
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah!
[SPEAKER_15]: Sounds like rejected.
[SPEAKER_06]: I say we let him go!
[SPEAKER_06]: No!
[SPEAKER_15]: Best movie ever.
[SPEAKER_15]: Pee-wee's Big Adventure, when he gets kidnapped by the bikers.
[SPEAKER_15]: Did you know that that's Elvira?
[SPEAKER_15]: The female one that grabs him by the neck and goes, I don't remember what she's... That's Elvira, the chick.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, next time, pay attention!
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, you slapped somebody with a trout.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, I see.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, you made me slap somebody.
[SPEAKER_15]: Ha ha!
[SPEAKER_15]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_15]: Now the whole chat room is joining in.
[SPEAKER_15]: Great.
[SPEAKER_02]: I should start trends.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're such a trendsetter.
[SPEAKER_02]: Be like me!
[SPEAKER_15]: Um, let's see.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, yes, the cage match.
[SPEAKER_15]: The winner of the cage match tonight was absolutely no contest whatsoever.
[SPEAKER_15]: Why sure ever?
[SPEAKER_15]: Why sure ever.
[SPEAKER_15]: Why don't you announce it, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_02]: The Winner is the Great Space Coaster
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, so Legend of Trance wins this week's cage match, and we'll probably win for the next four weeks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who needs someone to do Legend of Cumshot next?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, we need somebody to make one of those erotic... Well, uh... Get some porn noises.
[SPEAKER_15]: I got porn, I could rip audio from that, I suppose.
[SPEAKER_15]: I suppose.
[SPEAKER_15]: I got some gay porn in the other room.
[SPEAKER_15]: Lots of Cumshots and gay porn.
[SPEAKER_15]: Jamie's all, you do?
[SPEAKER_15]: Just kidding, I actually only have one.
[SPEAKER_15]: Irene bought it for me for my birthday.
[SPEAKER_17]: I can just say it now, instead of like, the fly, you know, and like, the birth, it's like, ooh.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know what, they've been wanting a Skies voice remix, so I can do my voice, I can go, it flies.
[SPEAKER_15]: The sticky.
[SPEAKER_11]: Cream of some young guy.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, we'll work on that.
[SPEAKER_15]: We'll work on Legend of Kumshock for you guys.
[SPEAKER_17]: And then when it's all fear, it's like, Ugh!
[SPEAKER_15]: Queer!
[SPEAKER_17]: Queer!
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: We'll work on that.
[SPEAKER_15]: It'll be a present for our loyal listeners.
[SPEAKER_17]: I almost memorized the whole lyrics for a superstar.
[SPEAKER_17]: Why?
[SPEAKER_17]: Because I was going to do a rap and went... Okay, this really sucks.
[SPEAKER_17]: I was going to do a rap, okay, and they wanted... They had this thing for my work.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's a promo thing because we're promoting 8 Mile.
[SPEAKER_17]: and, um, they were doing this, like, wrap-off thing, and it was so you could win $100.
[SPEAKER_15]: I think you actually told us this story two weeks ago, but that's okay, tell us again.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, anyway, so I was gonna do that, and so I memorized, you know, most, I got Superstar, but I ended up not doing it, and a lot of our company people did it, but they made their own wraps for, um, like, our work stuff.
[SPEAKER_17]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_17]: But this one guy did it out of the blue.
[SPEAKER_17]: He just came up with it right on the spot.
[SPEAKER_17]: That was kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_17]: But instead of having the contest be where you could win $100, everyone that did it got $100.
[SPEAKER_17]: But not me because I didn't do it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Don't!
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, well.
[SPEAKER_14]: That sucks.
[SPEAKER_14]: What else do we have to talk about?
[SPEAKER_15]: I had something that I wanted to ask or talk about and I totally forgot.
[SPEAKER_15]: It slipped my mind.
[SPEAKER_15]: Damn!
[SPEAKER_15]: I hate that.
[SPEAKER_15]: Bad radio.
[SPEAKER_14]: Damn!
[SPEAKER_15]: I need to write this shit down.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's too much work, though.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's more effort than I desire to put into this show.
[SPEAKER_15]: As Jamie files for nails.
[SPEAKER_15]: FUs of the week?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, why don't we just get to the FUs of the week?
[SPEAKER_15]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_15]: How's that sound to you, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_15]: Jamie's nodding.
[SPEAKER_15]: She's got some angsty things she wants to say.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know, we've been getting advice from some people because the FUs always seem to go on for a long time that we ought to cut back the FUs of the week to like once a month or something.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, then they wouldn't be the FUs of the week, now would they?
[SPEAKER_15]: Then how long would you think that would be?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, that would be a whole month's worth of it.
[SPEAKER_15]: We'd have to do a whole show.
[SPEAKER_15]: We'd have to have, okay, last Sunday of each month is the FU show.
[SPEAKER_17]: I promise to cut back on the repeat FUs for drivers and stuff.
[SPEAKER_17]: We know that they suck all year round, and there's nothing going to change there.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, you know, maybe we'd have to just instate quotas on the chatroom FUs.
[SPEAKER_15]: So we'll punish you people that bitch.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, you don't get any.
[SPEAKER_17]: Come on the show and you get to be angsty as much as you want.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, but for tonight, no, we're just teasing.
[SPEAKER_15]: We're giving you guys a hard time.
[SPEAKER_15]: We'll do the FUs like we always do.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, send us those FUs to me.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm Sky.
[SPEAKER_15]: Am I still chatroom slut?
[SPEAKER_15]: I think I am.
[SPEAKER_15]: So send those over private message to Sky chatroom slut.
[SPEAKER_15]: Jamie, terror or original?
[SPEAKER_15]: Terror.
[SPEAKER_15]: Cause you're terrifying.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I had to let it start.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, here we go, FU's the week, you know it, you love it.
This is fucked up.
Okay, my FU's the week.
First of all, I'm sorry, I think he's moving his leg.
[SPEAKER_18]: Um, my first one gets more drivers, because it's not, oh shit, it's not moving his legs.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry, Matt Hedlund on the back.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, yeah, bad drivers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Especially old people drivers who tailgate.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hate them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, the next one goes, uh, to, uh, Sack of Imani.
[SPEAKER_02]: To our server.
[SPEAKER_02]: That always goes down.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we're moving.
[SPEAKER_06]: Eventually.
[SPEAKER_06]: Right?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_14]: As soon as we possibly can.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, $1hosting.com gets the big finger of the year.
[SPEAKER_18]: They're actually good enough.
[SPEAKER_15]: Them and their stupid pirates, Ark.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, Ark.
[SPEAKER_18]: Um, and I've been listening to you for this in Buffy for two weeks, but you stayed before me, right?
[SPEAKER_15]: I did.
[SPEAKER_15]: I hope, hopefully my roommates didn't believe me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay, back on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, another one goes toward me for ignoring my Animal Crossing village and my villagers moving out of me.
[SPEAKER_02]: But they still love me.
[SPEAKER_18]: I got Camo Frog.
[SPEAKER_18]: You got Cube.
[SPEAKER_18]: Cube's rare.
[SPEAKER_18]: Cube's a penguin.
[SPEAKER_18]: What's Cube?
[SPEAKER_18]: Penguin!
[SPEAKER_18]: It's an Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_18]: We're still talking Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, I had another one, oh yeah, another one goes toward last night, me being really sick and out of it and not eating anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, another one goes toward just about every store in this town except for this one ghetto mart in Trader Joe's for not having orange juice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, another one goes toward oatmeal cream pies for being an addictive food item.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then one goes toward Walgreens for not having peach propel.
[SPEAKER_02]: But however, they did have propel, but I wouldn't get one for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, another one goes toward a lot of stores in town for not selling balls, because I like blue balls.
[SPEAKER_18]: And, um, another one is going toward, um, my box for being too big.
[SPEAKER_18]: Because I got my slip in my shoe and it really makes me dry.
[SPEAKER_02]: And my big FD of the week goes toward JList.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: I put in my order a month ago for loose socks and Bacari Sweat in soft blue.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's still at night in my house yet!
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, uh, F.U.
[SPEAKER_18]: goes on tour on my Jungle with Taka for the album, and uh, making me spend money.
[SPEAKER_18]: I bought, um, Mega Ranger vs. Car Ranger, on my Switch, and Mega Ranger vs. Ninja Ranger, on my Switch.
[SPEAKER_18]: And other F.U.
[SPEAKER_18]: discs, if you'd like them to play my TV series.
[SPEAKER_18]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_17]: Did you say hentai TV series?
[SPEAKER_18]: It's hentai!
[SPEAKER_17]: You have special music tonight, Loki, am I correct?
[SPEAKER_17]: Yes, special music, this goes for with my F.U.s.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright!
[SPEAKER_17]: Most of these F.U.s come from last night.
F.U.
[SPEAKER_17]: to Vacaville, because you suck!
[SPEAKER_17]: F.U.
[SPEAKER_17]: the white trash that lives in Vacaville, I really hate you, I don't like you coming up and talking to me.
[SPEAKER_17]: One person in particular is a stupid cowboy...
[SPEAKER_17]: Skater.
[SPEAKER_17]: You can't mix those two genres together.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's like oil and water.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, but this jackass comes up to us, starts talking to us, puts his hand... Okay, now, obviously this is going to be bad radio, but he goes up to the table and goes, hits the table and he's like, How you doing?
[SPEAKER_17]: And I'm like, Go away!
[SPEAKER_17]: And then he kept staying there and talking to us and got into a conversation with us and eventually we ended up bringing up the DDR solo thing.
[SPEAKER_17]: He's like, Uh, what's a syringe?
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, maybe if you weren't such a dumbass, you'd know what that is.
[SPEAKER_17]: Then... Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, what about Ecstasy?
[SPEAKER_16]: Then, he tried to hug Brian.
[SPEAKER_16]: Awww, he just wants a hug!
[SPEAKER_16]: He was trying to hug on everybody.
[SPEAKER_16]: He just had this problem.
[SPEAKER_16]: He said this one kid was his lover.
[SPEAKER_16]: He was like a 12 year old kid.
[SPEAKER_16]: You got a problem with that?
He was like 17 or 18, the kid was 12.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's like Michael Jackson.
[SPEAKER_02]: First of all, now you know the reason why I love this song.
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright, and, finally, FU2, their machine conditions at that arcade, they suck ass.
[SPEAKER_17]: DVR, the fifth mix, fucking all the arrows are broken, and Max 2, the arrows were set in about one quarter inch into the pads, so it's like, you can't play on that, it sucked.
[SPEAKER_17]: So that's like, their fucking soda machine is broken, okay?
[SPEAKER_17]: I wanted a fucking Sierra Mist and I got a Mountain Dew.
[SPEAKER_16]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_16]: Then, then, to add that on top of...
[SPEAKER_17]: for all that, then we get to Cusar, okay, there's, the way they have that working out there, it totally sucks, they, the employees don't know what the fuck they're doing, employees aren't really working, they need to put people there, their briefing room's an empty room, they don't have half-day passes, empty room, not painted, empty room, they don't have half-day passes, they don't have half-day passes, they fucking suck, so, yeah, empty to them, um,
[SPEAKER_17]: That's pretty much it, that's all I had, you know, I really was trying to come up with a huge list, I had a bunch of stuff last night, but after a while at QZAR, we had some people come talk to us, they were really nice, and they made me less angsty, so that was cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, he was tech.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's it, I'm not too angsty at the moment, if anything comes to me later, I'll take it then.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_15]: My turn.
[SPEAKER_15]: I changed my song last week for those who weren't paying attention.
[SPEAKER_15]: My FU for this week goes to Drama, because I've seen too much of it this week.
[SPEAKER_15]: And, like, it needs to go away.
[SPEAKER_06]: I second that.
[SPEAKER_17]: One more FU and I'll keep this music.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, this is kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_17]: Let's just say I'm going to give an F you to Twen just because he thinks he's funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_17]: Twen thinks he's all cool because he went and changed the redirect on my site to some stupid tubgirl.com picture or whatever.
[SPEAKER_17]: Some stupid chick shooting shit out of her ass and into her mouth, which is all photoshopped anyway.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, it's all photoshopped.
[SPEAKER_17]: But anyways, that's not the point.
[SPEAKER_17]: Haha, look what I found on the internet.
[SPEAKER_17]: The whole point is...
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't care, because I don't use that site anymore, you jackass.
[SPEAKER_17]: What you did was just, that'd be like someone messing up my GeoCDs webpage.
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't give a fuck.
[SPEAKER_17]: I thought it was funny, I laughed, and I laughed at you for trying to be funny.
[SPEAKER_17]: Or just attempting to insult me in any way, guess what?
[SPEAKER_17]: You ain't still getting those fucking CDs, and you're a loser.
[SPEAKER_17]: So, oh, there'll probably be a little special gift for you later on, on the websites, but that'll be later on, so, enjoy.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is very funny, but you still don't know all of it.
[SPEAKER_17]: I know, it's hilarious.
[SPEAKER_02]: I totally, you know... Did you see that bullshit in his live journal, by the way, his username is Twin316?
[SPEAKER_02]: On live journal?
[SPEAKER_02]: Go read that.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's fucking hilarious.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because he's so stupid that he thought that... I'm sorry, that was... I was literally reading that going, oh my god, how fucking pathetic his life was.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, he truly has no life.
[SPEAKER_17]: You put rape from Loki.
[SPEAKER_17]: Ah, you're funny, man.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wait, I mean, I want to know how, and normally I don't talk shit about people, but he really deserves to be talked shit about because he's so stupid.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you know me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do I talk shit about people?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm talking shit about him, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: First and foremost, first and foremost, anyone who feels the need that they have to do impersonations to try to coerce somebody into saying something that they end up not saying anyway, that's a part of the process.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can do a better job than that!
[SPEAKER_17]: If you're gonna fuck up my site, at least put some effort into it.
[SPEAKER_17]: That was stupid.
[SPEAKER_18]: My god, shit, how long does it take to fucking put a- You know what's even more disturbing?
[SPEAKER_18]: You gotta think about his mental state.
[SPEAKER_18]: If he knew where to find that efficient site, oh my god.
[SPEAKER_17]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_17]: That was weak, Twain.
[SPEAKER_17]: Shit, man, you could do better than that.
[SPEAKER_17]: What the fuck is that?
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, you put as much effort into that as your fucking remixes.
[SPEAKER_17]: I mean, shit, man, you need to, like... How about this?
[SPEAKER_17]: I'll tell you what.
[SPEAKER_17]: Why don't you go get banned from a couple more chat rooms, and then, you know, come talk to me.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, wait, you can't because I banned your fucking address.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, darn.
[SPEAKER_17]: Don't give a fuck.
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't understand why people don't like me!
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm likeable!
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm a likeable person!
[SPEAKER_17]: I should have tons of friends!
[SPEAKER_17]: The society's messed up!
[SPEAKER_15]: All I have to say is, you ain't bad, you ain't bad, I run with gangs, I run with gangs, I go to school and I kill people.
[SPEAKER_02]: And now I have to say this, because I think we've gotten it out of our system, you have to laugh every time his stupid bullshit comes up.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's not even worth talking about.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's a waste of breath.
[SPEAKER_02]: It should be pushed chocolate or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: So... Ouch!
[SPEAKER_02]: Why don't we just say... Twin no longer exists.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_15]: Agreed.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: Can I do my FUs now?
[SPEAKER_06]: Fuck you!
[SPEAKER_15]: My FU... Oh!
[SPEAKER_15]: Wasn't I saying my FU goes to drama?
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: My other F you goes to superficial people that don't call you because you won't put out on the first date.
[SPEAKER_15]: I hate that shit!
[SPEAKER_15]: Fuck you!
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's why I've given it an FU.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, I'm done.
[SPEAKER_15]: I've had enough.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let's go to Zero.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let's hear if he has any FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_16]: Mine, the same, also pretty much spawned from last night.
[SPEAKER_16]: That little cowboy skater guy, that was just the greatest ever.
[SPEAKER_16]: You should see him play when he plays DDR.
[SPEAKER_16]: He was playing, what was it, Killing Vision?
[SPEAKER_16]: Like, doing a hoedown to it.
[SPEAKER_16]: He was doing the whole like, oh yeah, era, he was doing the whole like, can't stamp down, jumping around, jumping around, jumping around, jumping around, jumping around, jumping around, jumping around, jumping around, jumping around, jumping around.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, and the fact that, okay, he's, um, the other person who went on the, you know, he had a foot on, so it's a VR thing, right?
[SPEAKER_16]: So he's always, you know, here, and all of a sudden he goes and picks up this, like, ratty-ass World Industry skateboard, and, like, it's like he's surfing, like, surfing or something, and it's a great VR thing, and it's, like, a good thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that was just, like, it absolutely worked.
[SPEAKER_18]: First of all, I'm going to state this, and I ask that I have the right to do this as a moderator on DDR Freak.
[SPEAKER_18]: DDR Freak does not endorse that guy's skateboard.
[SPEAKER_18]: I feel that I'm justified in saying so.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what's really sad about that arcade?
[SPEAKER_15]: You can tell where they have their priorities.
[SPEAKER_15]: They have their DDR machines in really shitty conditions.
[SPEAKER_15]: But wait, what's this in the corner?
[SPEAKER_17]: 18-wheeler in the giant... It's like an actual size cab of an 18-wheeler truck.
[SPEAKER_17]: I played that once at whatever Riptide Arcade was before it was Riptide Arcade at Pier 39.
[SPEAKER_15]: I played that once.
[SPEAKER_16]: Another thing, don't exactly plan on drinking from the drinking fountains.
[SPEAKER_16]: You go over there, and there's, like, hamburger and cigarette butts smashed into the drake.
[SPEAKER_16]: Burger butts?
[SPEAKER_16]: Burger and cigarette butts smashed into the drake.
[SPEAKER_15]: Did you ever see that episode of Married with Children when Al was barbecuing hamburgers and using cigarette butts and ashes for the... Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: And then somehow the dead mother got mixed in, I don't know, anyway.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: Married with Children is the shit, by the way.
[SPEAKER_08]: And where those drinking pouts were, you'd be afraid to go use them anyway, because they're like... You'd be afraid of getting gang raped or something if you tried to go step back there.
[SPEAKER_17]: and it would be even better if they had another separate bathroom.
[SPEAKER_17]: But in front of the doors were arcade games blocking the doors.
[SPEAKER_17]: Like, you gotta go to the bathroom and get through there.
[SPEAKER_18]: Hey, I have an idea.
[SPEAKER_18]: Why don't we look up to the health board and have it sit down?
[SPEAKER_16]: It's basically like CCL because they have a nice sign on the side of it.
[SPEAKER_18]: Well, the CCL actually is pretty...
[SPEAKER_02]: This is for Irene, even though she's not listening.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, hello, police?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, um, I'm in a wheelchair, and...
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, actually, Loki gets mad.
[SPEAKER_15]: Never mind.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'll tell you guys later.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'll tell you guys off the show.
[SPEAKER_16]: The highlight of the night was driving there and driving home.
[SPEAKER_16]: Pretty much.
[SPEAKER_16]: I mean, the actual arena at Fusar was cool, and that was about the only time you had fun, was when you were playing the game, except we had to wait for an hour for us to get our first game, and then, like, 45 minutes for the second one, when they were just standing around doing nothing.
[SPEAKER_02]: You just need to have that good trip for both of them to get there.
[SPEAKER_17]: or just go back to VacVille.
[SPEAKER_17]: VacVille's fine, it's just they have really bad organization.
[SPEAKER_17]: Once you, if you're there and demand to go into the game, that's pretty, you'll go in and you'll have a good time.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's just that they have some really retarded people crowding around the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: and you get the one guy who, you give him your tickets, like the place, your name, and he says, I'll remember you in the future.
[SPEAKER_08]: And so we have, yeah, we're like, he's like, I'll remember you, and we come back, and like, we're like, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, this is way more important than Vacaville.
[SPEAKER_15]: I got corrected by VidTawa.
[SPEAKER_15]: He said, actually, Peggy spilled Al's barbecue charcoal, and then she told Kelly and Bud to go find some ashes for her, and Kelly goes and steals Darcy's dead mother's ashes, and gives it to Peggy, and then Al cooks the burgers with the dead Darcy ashes.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's right, because ashes make the burgers taste good.
[SPEAKER_15]: But I could have sworn there were cigarettes without ashes as part of the joke.
[SPEAKER_15]: Maybe that was another show.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm getting my wires crossed.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right, sorry to interrupt, but you know, Mary just showed me some shit and all.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know if I can just answer, but after we hear that, you're going to have to stop recording.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, yeah, yeah, maybe that'll... Yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right, are you done, Cyril?
[SPEAKER_15]: All right, moving on to Dave.
[SPEAKER_15]: And the chat room is getting a little upset because we're not that angsty right now, so you better have some angst in you, Dave.
[SPEAKER_15]: No pressure.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'll try.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, and thank you, Rob, for giving this up.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, um, well, just to let people know I got my license like a week ago or something, and I'm happy about that, but, what, no, I don't have my car, I'm driving my brother's car, right now I'm driving my car, anyway, and fuck the DMV for being the biggest piece of shit ever, oh my god, it's like you get outside and go to Inline and
[SPEAKER_12]: The line is like a rollercoaster line.
[SPEAKER_12]: It goes, curves around four times, then goes outside the door, and then, so we wait in line for about an hour and a half, and we're late for our, you know, then we get there, oh, you're waiting in the wrong line.
[SPEAKER_12]: Go wait in that line, and there's two people in that line, and there's only two people in that line, and so then it's like, shit, I could be out of here by now.
[SPEAKER_12]: So then after we go there, and I get my appointment, I'm angsty, and then I have to go wait in another line, which is you drive your car up, turn the power off, wait 15 minutes, move one spot, wait 20 minutes, and then after about two hours, I finally finish, and so the DMV fucking pisses me off.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck you, DMV!
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm angsty!
[SPEAKER_04]: Wah!
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry, I was going to go on the front like this.
[SPEAKER_16]: I knew that old people drove slow.
[SPEAKER_12]: I knew that old people drove slow.
[SPEAKER_12]: But I didn't know that all keyboards are stupid.
[SPEAKER_12]: Like, they drive, and they see a red light maybe 100 meters up.
[SPEAKER_12]: They start slowing down, and they're going 30 at the time in a 45 zone.
[SPEAKER_12]: And they start slowing down to about 5 miles an hour.
[SPEAKER_12]: The light's still red, they've got about 50 meters to go until they hit the red light.
[SPEAKER_12]: And they're going at, you know, 5 miles an hour.
[SPEAKER_12]: And then the light turns green, they pull to a complete stop, and then they go, like it's a stop sign.
[SPEAKER_18]: And then when they stop behind you, they appear like they're in the background.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, I was actually hit, like, half by an old person, but I didn't want to say anything.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, but you ain't seen nothing yet.
[SPEAKER_17]: There's also the young drivers, no offense to you, man, but there's young drivers that are just stupid, like Prince and Snape.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_17]: I was parking right here at San Juan.
[SPEAKER_17]: There's police cars going everywhere, okay, lights, sirens on.
[SPEAKER_17]: Two police cars behind this dumb bitch, and she's just standing there, like, she's sitting there at the red light, and they're honking their horns, and she's, like, waving her arms, going, I don't know what to do, I don't know what to do!
[SPEAKER_17]: Drive forward, you fucking dumbass!
[SPEAKER_17]: You're trying to go someplace!
[SPEAKER_17]: So then finally she pulls forward a little bit in front of my car, and they nearly hit her ass, and I wish they did because I would serve her right.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, anyway, back to my FUs, and I'm kind of scrounged for them, but I think I had a couple more, um, wait, let me think, on 2DX, just fuck all the songs that I can't pass, that's not big news, and fuck Legend of Max for me not being able to pass them yet.
[SPEAKER_12]: and damn it, fuck my memory for doing this a lot and forgetting what I was going to say about fucking other things.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, shine, lose, you're finished.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, I'm done.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: Chatroom FUs are going to get through these quick, I promise.
[SPEAKER_15]: 23rd Mac... Oh, Jesus Christ.
[SPEAKER_15]: You send me so many every week.
[SPEAKER_15]: You're going to get quoted first.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: King-sized fuck you to parents who think that since they like auto shows, you like auto shows, bitches.
[SPEAKER_15]: Don't drag me to Autorama again.
[SPEAKER_15]: Bite-sized F you to failing DXY Maniac.
[SPEAKER_15]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_15]: I passed it in my sleep on The Sims and on Conomics.
[SPEAKER_15]: I go to Scandia and fail.
[SPEAKER_15]: Londo F you to loose rivets on the Max 2 at Scandia.
[SPEAKER_15]: I now have a round indentation in my right knee when I tried knee dropping.
[SPEAKER_15]: Thank you, Max 2.
[SPEAKER_15]: I mean, fuck you.
[SPEAKER_02]: What the fuck were you doing knee dropping anyway?
[SPEAKER_02]: Just...
[SPEAKER_15]: Zero in the back says, don't miss the panel.
[SPEAKER_15]: And an Actdeft view to being 17.
[SPEAKER_15]: God damn it, I can't even leave my freaking house.
[SPEAKER_15]: Give me a break already.
[SPEAKER_15]: At least drive me to Scandia once a week.
[SPEAKER_15]: Is that too much fucking much to ask?
[SPEAKER_15]: DarkTetsuya, fuck being single.
[SPEAKER_15]: Still, second the fuck to Sekpamani server and fuck Civ 3 Play the World for not letting me play online.
[SPEAKER_15]: And lastly, fuck the cold that won't go away.
[SPEAKER_15]: Loki, it could be worse.
[SPEAKER_15]: Laser Force, two words.
[SPEAKER_02]: You mean Laser Ass?
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, EOSFVB says, Fuck you to CompUSA for not selling individual bottles of balls, and fuck you to whoever recorded this MacGyver theme that I just got, and fuck you to people that were thinking about using the MacGyver theme for the contest.
[SPEAKER_15]: And fuck you to whoever made the subtitles for the verses of Spirit of the Way that I have, because the translation is shitty, and fuck you to people who don't like chicken and a biscuit.
[SPEAKER_15]: He's done in English Chicken and Biscuit is the shit I agree, fucking school don't like Chicken and Biscuit Good Power says F you to waiting at Burger King for 20 minutes and making me miss Orange Lounge as a result of it F you to teachers yelling at you F you to teachers making you pay for stuff Welcome to college And a huge F you to my eyeglasses breaking on Friday JB F you to saying my remix's name wrong Yeah, F you too, buddy Um
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, that's it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Uh, Snub Dispenoid says, okay, that's too long.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, F long things, I guess.
[SPEAKER_15]: Angel says, fuck you to my cold, which refuses to go away, it's been a week.
[SPEAKER_15]: Black Lab says, fuck things that get in your eye and irritate it to the point that you can't see out of it, and fuck long-ass programs that suck to code.
[SPEAKER_17]: I can just say something really, yeah, I think I will, uh, well, you better watch out when you're giving head.
[SPEAKER_15]: MoreThanJake says, um, fuck you to long FUs, they only make your headaches worse.
[SPEAKER_15]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_15]: EvilNauki2DX says, I want to say fuck you to boredom, and I want to say fuck you to people who upload email scripts that rape servers.
[SPEAKER_15]: Fuck spammers.
[SPEAKER_15]: 23rd Magus says, I was breaking in my new shoes, that's why I was e-dropping.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, meh.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, there's JB's FU, I didn't scroll down to see it.
[SPEAKER_15]: FU to not having cable so I can download Azumanga Daioh.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let's see if we got a fee over at the mailbox, over at Orange Lounge Radio at Yahoo.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nope, nothing in the mail.
[SPEAKER_16]: If you can't e-drop and hit the panel, then just don't e-drop.
[SPEAKER_16]: You won't bitch about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alrighty-dighty.
[SPEAKER_15]: Uh, break time?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, let's break.
[SPEAKER_06]: I gotta pee.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let's break.
[SPEAKER_15]: Bath and break.
[SPEAKER_15]: What do we want to hear this break?
[SPEAKER_15]: Wasn't there something we wanted to hear earlier in the show?
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's do a disgusting break.
[SPEAKER_15]: A disgusting break?
[SPEAKER_15]: Like bad music break?
[SPEAKER_15]: Like lots of Eurobeat.
[SPEAKER_15]: Ooh, Eurobeat break.
[SPEAKER_15]: Uh...
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, I know, we don't want to lose all the listeners.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, um, alright, I got it, I got it, I got it.
[SPEAKER_15]: We can do some of those shitty things from Dance Maniacs, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, we're going to do, uh, well, what did you get, though?
[SPEAKER_15]: You said, I got it, I got it.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, you want to hear that?
[SPEAKER_15]: We're going to hear...
[SPEAKER_15]: We're going to hear the Long Train Runnin' version by Xtreme, the band that did A Minute and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do Let the Music Play.
[SPEAKER_15]: This is not the same Long Train Runnin' that Bus Stop did, which is in Max 2.
[SPEAKER_15]: This is Xtreme's version of it, and it doesn't sound a goddamn thing like the original.
[SPEAKER_15]: And after that, we're going to let it go right into Bus Stop with Let the Music Play.
[SPEAKER_15]: By the way, this is funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually like this mix.
[SPEAKER_15]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_15]: Jamie, headpicked.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shannon, let the music play.
[SPEAKER_15]: Shannon, let the music play.
[SPEAKER_15]: And lo and behold, now we have Bus Stop doing Let the Music Play.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, and then I'm supposed to play one of these new promos that some of our fans worked on, so I'll get that in there too.
[SPEAKER_15]: I want to dance!
[SPEAKER_17]: Welcome to Orange Launch Radio, where love is orange.
[SPEAKER_17]: Shaving monkeys is always permitted.
[SPEAKER_17]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_17]: But... But it's... You scare the monkey, you don't come in.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, no, I'll just bring Shermie.
[SPEAKER_00]: If Shermie doesn't like you, leave.
[SPEAKER_00]: Proceeding, as always, was brought to you by Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, that was Bus Stop, we'll let the music play.
[SPEAKER_15]: We're going to do one more song from Dance Mania EX2 because we decided we want to do a list list when we come back and we need time to make our lists.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, one more song from Dance Mania EX2 and I'll tell you what.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's something disgusting.
[SPEAKER_15]: You're going to love this song or you're going to freaking hate it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Y'all know Creamy, they're the band that did I Do, I Do, I Do in Dance Revolution Extreme.
[SPEAKER_15]: I do, I do, I do.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't, I don't, I don't.
[SPEAKER_15]: Anyway, Creamy did a cover of The NeverEnding Story.
[SPEAKER_15]: And it's so cute, it'll make you barf.
[SPEAKER_15]: So enjoy.
[SPEAKER_15]: This is Creamy with The NeverEnding Story.
[SPEAKER_15]: It has a mix name.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's actually the Manhattan Click Extended Remix here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_15]: Enjoy or despise, you be the judge.
[SPEAKER_15]: And we'll be back with Listless.
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_15]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_15]: Is this thing on?
[SPEAKER_15]: Testing.
[SPEAKER_15]: Testing 1-2.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm looking in the index, but I don't see anything for how to run a radio show.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't understand this.
[SPEAKER_15]: Does this thing work?
[SPEAKER_02]: This thing reads like stereo instructions.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is this on?
[SPEAKER_02]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_01]: Orange Lounge Radio, Broke Down Ghetto Bomani Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: What the?
[SPEAKER_15]: Hi, we're back.
[SPEAKER_15]: You're listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_15]: As we promised during that last one, I was creamy with the never-ending story from Dance Mania EX2, so it could be on DDR very possibly.
[SPEAKER_15]: And of course, we had some people, we had DDRholics, says it's so cute!
[SPEAKER_15]: And what did she say that was really funny?
[SPEAKER_15]: It was something about, uh... God, what was it?
[SPEAKER_15]: It was really funny, she said.
[SPEAKER_15]: Something about hamsters dancing in the sky or something like that.
[SPEAKER_15]: It was really funny.
[SPEAKER_15]: I can't find it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh well.
[SPEAKER_15]: And then of course we have Arcadian says it sucks and EOSFVB says this song should be banned.
[SPEAKER_02]: This song gives me an aneurysm.
[SPEAKER_15]: Won't be in regular Orange Lounge rotation anytime soon but we reserve the right to play it during any fuck off we want.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_15]: The address is right in the topic of our chat room.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's also linked from our website, orangelounge.skie.cx.
[SPEAKER_15]: And then you just click on forums.
[SPEAKER_15]: It'll take you right there.
[SPEAKER_15]: Or if you need the website, here it is, www.calibermani.com slash NBOR3.
[SPEAKER_15]: And we merged with the Naoki Boards of Randomness because they rock and we're a part of their forums.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, you need to get your ass over there to the Orange Lounge forums Because this was an idea that came from the listless suggestion thread And who would have thunk it?
[SPEAKER_15]: Dave was the one that suggested this topic Yay So you should go post in that listless suggestion thread if you think you have an idea Because we're doing this one tonight It was Dave's idea Best warm-up song for DDR
[SPEAKER_15]: So what exactly would be a warm-up song?
[SPEAKER_15]: You don't have to name it, but describe a warm-up song.
[SPEAKER_15]: What defines a warm-up song?
[SPEAKER_12]: The first song you play as a warm-up for your other songs that might be more physically demanding.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that when we say what our pick is, we should say why we like it as a warm-up song.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_12]: And it's basically, I would... There goes the mic.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I would basically think that it would be something very fun and easygoing and not too challenging because... Just starting.
[SPEAKER_12]: What?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes, it depends on what you're... If you're warming up for Legend of Max, you might play Max 300.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
Ah!
[SPEAKER_15]: We have a request before we get started.
[SPEAKER_15]: Angel wants you to say, we.
[SPEAKER_15]: We.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: And do the Black Mage.
[SPEAKER_12]: Wait, what does he do again?
[SPEAKER_12]: Do the bolt thing.
[SPEAKER_15]: Never mind.
[SPEAKER_15]: Forget it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let's just get into it.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right, Dave, you start.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: My first one is...
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh yeah, I'm being lazy tonight.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, Jamie, you need to memorize all of these.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't want to erase the erotic ones.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'll just do it underneath, though.
[SPEAKER_15]: Do it on this page.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, here we go.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, I think... Yes, Rob?
[SPEAKER_15]: Sorry, I'm just laughing.
[SPEAKER_15]: DDRholic already gave us a suggestion for Jane Jonna because it's so smooth and it makes you want to pinch your butt cheeks.
[SPEAKER_15]: What?
[SPEAKER_15]: Never mind, I just thought that was funny.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, go ahead, go.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anyway, my first one is Moonlight Shadow because it was really fun and I played it on doubles all the time right before I played Oops, I Did It Again.
[SPEAKER_12]: Fired up mix.
[SPEAKER_12]: Did it.
[SPEAKER_02]: La Copa De Vida
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god, you suck.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, Changers.
[SPEAKER_15]: La Coba De Vida, because it's pretty easy to perfect attack, yet it has kind of a lot of different things in it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Triplets, eighth notes, and you know what?
[SPEAKER_15]: People cringe when they hear a Ricky Martin cover, but the song, it actually isn't that bad.
[SPEAKER_15]: I mean, it's, yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: Dude, that song kicks ass.
[SPEAKER_12]: That was my first choice, but you suck.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes, Jamie, sure.
[SPEAKER_02]: My number three pick is Kakumei Maniac.
[SPEAKER_15]: Kakumei!
[SPEAKER_02]: Maniac.
[SPEAKER_02]: Specifically.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kakumei Maniac.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I, alright, a lot of people notice that I don't play with freezers and I do it for a legitimate reason because of my ankle being weak.
[SPEAKER_02]: If I have to hold my foot in one position for entirely too long, especially when I'm stepping the other way, it hurts.
[SPEAKER_02]: The thing I like about Kakumei is that it's very easy.
[SPEAKER_02]: as the gallops help me, you know, warm up my legs and everything and get my knees to where they don't hurt and then it, at the end of the song it goes into their run so I'm building up into something better.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually have legitimate reasons.
[SPEAKER_17]: Good pick, good pick.
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright, Zero.
[SPEAKER_16]: Um,
[SPEAKER_16]: My number three would be doing Miracle Moon on doubles on the heavy.
[SPEAKER_16]: Mostly because it'll work me up into doing my freestyle stuff like Let the Beacon.
[SPEAKER_15]: Do you want to specifically say doubles heavy or just Miracle Moon?
[SPEAKER_16]: Miracle Moon double.
[SPEAKER_16]: Because it's not very hard on singles.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: Miracle Moon.
[SPEAKER_15]: Loki, your number three pick.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's all about superstar heavy.
[SPEAKER_15]: Superstar.
[SPEAKER_17]: Dammit.
[SPEAKER_15]: I knew that would happen.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's why I didn't put Superstar.
[SPEAKER_15]: I stayed away from that because I knew you guys would totally be putting that.
[SPEAKER_15]: Dave, your number two pick.
[SPEAKER_12]: My number two pick is Senorita.
[SPEAKER_12]: Senorita.
[SPEAKER_12]: I always play that right after I play La Copa De La Vida.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because it gets me really happy, and then I can play a heart song.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, it makes you happy.
[SPEAKER_13]: Happy, happy, happy.
[SPEAKER_15]: I feel happy.
[SPEAKER_15]: My number two pick, because this is just great, and everybody loves it when I play this song, and you all love to listen to it, and you know it.
[SPEAKER_15]: My number two pick is this Rain of Men.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, that's not a surprise.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because it's not too difficult, and it's fun.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's happy.
[SPEAKER_15]: And it makes people turn their heads.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's happy.
[SPEAKER_15]: And it's happy.
[SPEAKER_15]: So it's Rain and Men.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, my number two.
[SPEAKER_02]: Your number two, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Someone took my number one, Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: My number two is Share My Love, Maniac.
[SPEAKER_02]: Share My Love.
[SPEAKER_02]: It makes you watch.
[SPEAKER_02]: It starts you watching the arrows.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's more like a mental warm-up.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a mental warm-up.
[SPEAKER_15]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_15]: Zero, you're number two pick.
[SPEAKER_16]: My second one is Little Bitch.
[SPEAKER_16]: Little Bitch!
[SPEAKER_16]: Because not only does it match the specials shirt I just got the other day, but it's a good warm-up for going into my Ska routine that I'm working on.
[SPEAKER_16]: It'll be good when I get it done.
[SPEAKER_15]: So we're talking about the original Little Bitch, not Bus Stop's one-two Little Bitch.
[SPEAKER_16]: No, the original, original specials.
[SPEAKER_15]: Cool!
[SPEAKER_15]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_17]: Let's see, Let's Groove...
[SPEAKER_17]: Let's screw up tonight
Oh, hello.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, Dave.
[SPEAKER_02]: Earth, wind, and fire, you ain't.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anyway, my number one actually has a story kind of behind it.
[SPEAKER_12]: And, um, it was a long... The story is that your real number one got taken.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, that was the story for my number two, but now it's moved on up the list.
[SPEAKER_12]: And because I can't think of anything else off the top of my head.
[SPEAKER_12]: And it was, I think, a year or a year and a half ago, maybe two years.
[SPEAKER_12]: Wow, Jamie's holding a lighting pen up to her forehead so she can see the lights.
[SPEAKER_12]: And it was the first time that I ever met Rob and Jamie and all these other people.
[SPEAKER_12]: that I thought were really weird at the time.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I played with Rob the first time before I'd met him on a fourth mix at Roseville Golf Land and he picked
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know, was it Bumblebee or something like that?
[SPEAKER_12]: You know, one of the songs that my brother plays with me.
[SPEAKER_12]: And then I picked Dropout.
[SPEAKER_12]: And that's my choice.
[SPEAKER_12]: Just Dropout.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because it was so fun.
[SPEAKER_12]: And Rob was just like gasping for breath.
[SPEAKER_12]: He's like, this is my first game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I was like, sorry.
[SPEAKER_12]: And then I picked Afronova afterwards to fuck with him.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, but Dropout because it's really fun.
[SPEAKER_12]: And yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, alright It gets me warmed up, you ass Alright That made me think though, I left one off my list I really want to put it on here, but I guess next time But the number one, and it deserves to be my number one Because this was the ultimate warm up song Especially back in the day, I always played this first song You know it, this song is the shit Oh Nick, please not so quick God, all the fucking time We got the fourth mix, you were like Oh my god, I love you, Onik I want to help the machine
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see if I can fit in the coin slot.
[SPEAKER_12]: Please.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually remember you saying that once.
[SPEAKER_15]: It wouldn't surprise me at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was right before my birthday, come to think of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: My number one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, my original number one got taken, so my number two moved up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: And everyone knows that I've been starting off with this a lot lately.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cowgirl Maniac.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just because the little Skippy Hops.
[SPEAKER_02]: I normally suck at Skippy Hops, and now I can do Skippy Hops really well.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Skippy Hops.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because they're not the true... I don't consider them true gallops like in, you know, Saints Go Marching or like in Rhythm and Police.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're Skippy Hops.
[SPEAKER_02]: Skippy Hops!
[SPEAKER_02]: Sounds like a breakfast.
[SPEAKER_15]: New Cowgirl Skippy Hops.
[SPEAKER_02]: Grassy Sod Klops.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was on Ren and Sippy.
[SPEAKER_02]: With that freshly mowed lawn flavor.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_17]: Zero, your number one choice.
[SPEAKER_16]: Um, yeah, I'm surprised that guy over at, uh, Vacaville didn't play that song.
[SPEAKER_16]: Anyways, uh, my number one, all together, is doing Spin the Disc, single, heavy, because it works into my main freestyle routine.
[SPEAKER_16]: So I definitely will have to pick that.
[SPEAKER_15]: Spin-ta-disc!
[SPEAKER_15]: Last one, Loki, what is it?
[SPEAKER_15]: Number one warm-up song.
[SPEAKER_17]: I played this yesterday, but the pad was fucked up.
[SPEAKER_17]: This stupid fucking pad.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's moving on!
[SPEAKER_17]: Moving on!
[SPEAKER_17]: Moving on from fifth mix.
[SPEAKER_17]: It was the only mix it was in, and it was so cool, and they took the... Oh, no...
[SPEAKER_02]: We have Moonlight Shadow, La Copa De Vida, Cockamamaniac, Miracle Moon Doubles, Superstar, Seorita, It's Raining Men, Share My Love, Little Bitch, Let's Groove, Dropout, Nick, Please Not So Quick, Cloud Girls, Spin The Disc, Whip On
[SPEAKER_15]: Brad.
[SPEAKER_15]: Now, songs we forgot.
[SPEAKER_15]: It didn't hit me until part of the way through when Dave was reminiscing about 4th Mix.
[SPEAKER_15]: I forgot Bakwa.
[SPEAKER_15]: That used to be the ultimate warm-up song.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, me too.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm remembering my usual set on 1.5.
[SPEAKER_02]: It would always start off with Boom Boom Dollar.
[SPEAKER_02]: Trick.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, I used to play that a lot, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: It would always be Boom Boom Dollar, and then My Fire, and then it would be Brilliant COG.
[SPEAKER_12]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, but I was thinking about doing Synchronized Love, because it's really fun, and it's kind of, but no.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anyway, so I have to take one off, huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: Damn, these are all pretty good choices.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I play them all fairly...
[SPEAKER_12]: A lot.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: But, um... Damn it.
[SPEAKER_12]: No.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, I like that song too much.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think Let's Groove.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's Groove goes bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: Too slow and not enough fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just saying, Let's Groove is sort of one of my cool-down songs if I need to take a breather.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's more of a cool-down than a warm-up.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I'd let the beat hit them in the same category.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, same.
[SPEAKER_12]: I do one of those songs in between playing like an extreme edit and doing my PA for Legend of Max qualifier thing.
[SPEAKER_15]: Anyway, so, these are all pretty good picks.
[SPEAKER_15]: However, I'm just a bitter little asshole.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm taking off dropout.
[SPEAKER_15]: What the hell are you smoking?
[SPEAKER_15]: Dropout is a warm-up?
[SPEAKER_15]: I mean, I guess so.
[SPEAKER_15]: I mean, especially, you know, as the bar's kind of been raising and raising, I remember when most people used to go, oh my god, you can pass Dropout Maniac?
[SPEAKER_15]: And you were like the shit if you could pass Dropout Maniac.
[SPEAKER_15]: And now it's nothing, you know?
[SPEAKER_15]: So I can see where it's kind of gone to that level of warm-up.
[SPEAKER_15]: I know, but I mean, for some people, for some people, I'm saying for the people that it used to be, oh my god.
[SPEAKER_15]: I know, but I'm saying for the people that it used to be, oh my god, now it's like, you have to be able to pass Max...
[SPEAKER_15]: 300, Three Speed Shuffle
[SPEAKER_12]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was fun in Samba de Amigo, but sucks for DDR.
[SPEAKER_12]: Did you see my routine to it?
[SPEAKER_12]: Where I do the pelvic thrust for the whole song?
[SPEAKER_12]: Drive you insane, yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's all the more reason for me not to see it.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're too young.
[SPEAKER_15]: Moving on!
[SPEAKER_15]: Zero, oh yeah.
[SPEAKER_16]: I would probably take on Seorita, because I don't really like a lot of those songs that sound like that on DDR.
[SPEAKER_16]: Because they just get kind of boring.
[SPEAKER_15]: Seorita comes off the list, and JB's crying.
[SPEAKER_16]: One of my old favorite warm-up songs that a lot of people don't like is Lupin the 73rd.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know if I consider that a warm-up.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah, but not the maniac stuff, but the easier, the beginning.
[SPEAKER_02]: By the way, it's Lupin the Third.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lupin the Third was anime.
[SPEAKER_15]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_15]: Loki, last one.
[SPEAKER_15]: What's coming off?
[SPEAKER_17]: You know, I hate this song on Maniac Doubles, and it can kiss my ass, because that is no six, bitch.
[SPEAKER_17]: Moonlight Shadow.
[SPEAKER_15]: Moonlight Shadow?
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, I don't know about a warm-up.
[SPEAKER_15]: I think the singles, Maniac... Actually, the singles makes a really good warm-up, I think.
[SPEAKER_17]: You know what we forgot to add onto the list?
[SPEAKER_15]: What?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, oh, Ghost was a good one.
[SPEAKER_15]: Very well.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, you think of them after...
[SPEAKER_15]: You think of them when you, uh, when it's too late.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, so, there's the list.
[SPEAKER_15]: Send me your votes right now, now, now.
[SPEAKER_15]: Jamie, read it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, oh, I was just thinking that people, our people should be in DDR, but nevermind.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, Cockamamaniac, Miracle Moon Double, Superstar, It's Rainin' Men, Share My Love, Little Bitch, A Nick Who's Not So Quick, Cowgirl, Spin the Disc, and moving on.
[SPEAKER_02]: By the way, I was supposed to specify Cowgirl Maniac.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, my bad.
[SPEAKER_15]: And Cock, yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh well, people get the idea.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, mine are maniac.
[SPEAKER_02]: So share my love.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, so... Vote.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Vote, bitches.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, my dear people.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: And in the meantime, we're going to take a break.
[SPEAKER_15]: So you only have like a minute to send me your votes.
[SPEAKER_15]: So send them now or we'll boot you from the chat room.
[SPEAKER_15]: Just kidding, we won't.
[SPEAKER_15]: But, you know, please participate.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let's do something old.
[SPEAKER_15]: Something old?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, let's go for Brilliant to UOG.
[SPEAKER_15]: Brilliant to UOG.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Boom Boom Dollar.
[SPEAKER_15]: Brilliant to you, OG, and Boom Boom Dollar.
[SPEAKER_15]: And Bad Girls.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, that's it.
[SPEAKER_15]: You heard it here.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's what we're going to hear right now.
[SPEAKER_15]: We're going to hear Bad Girls, Boom Boom Dollar, and starting off we have Brilliant to you, OG, send me the votes now.
[SPEAKER_15]: You have until the end of Boom Boom Dollar to do it.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's when voting's closed.
[SPEAKER_15]: We'll be back.
[SPEAKER_07]: Boom, boom, money, signing, dollar
[SPEAKER_06]: From StepSquad to Orange Labs, this PDR sucks!
[SPEAKER_06]: Holler!
[SPEAKER_06]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_06]: T.T.P.O.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hi, we're back.
[SPEAKER_15]: Jamie, you want to do a shout out?
[SPEAKER_15]: You want to do a shout out?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shout out!
[SPEAKER_15]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_15]: Ow.
[SPEAKER_02]: My shoutout goes to Jahi for staying with me while I was going insane driving around, so thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you, Jahi.
[SPEAKER_02]: My blood sugar sucks.
[SPEAKER_15]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_15]: Jahi is the man.
[SPEAKER_15]: He's the shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: And he has very interesting things to say late at night.
[SPEAKER_15]: Everybody needs to know a Jahi.
[SPEAKER_15]: He needs to be on the show.
[SPEAKER_15]: Like, here.
[SPEAKER_15]: He's been via tape.
[SPEAKER_15]: He's never been here, but hopefully soon, right kids?
[SPEAKER_15]: He's been talking about moving, maybe.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't know if that would happen.
[SPEAKER_15]: During a drunk show.
[SPEAKER_15]: Maybe you should get him next week.
[SPEAKER_15]: Jahi would be a suitable replacement for me.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because, you know, we're so alike.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that Jahi would be as difficult to get drunk as me.
[SPEAKER_17]: That'd be interesting.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, it's a three hour show.
[SPEAKER_02]: A three hour train wreck.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, you want to hear the winners of this list?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yes, you do.
[SPEAKER_15]: Best warm-up song?
[SPEAKER_15]: I need drumrolls, people.
[SPEAKER_15]: Third place!
[SPEAKER_15]: That's the most unenthusiastic.
[SPEAKER_15]: That was you slapping yourself.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, applause, whatever.
[SPEAKER_15]: There you go, there you go.
[SPEAKER_15]: Third place is... The audience is now deaf.
[SPEAKER_15]: The audience is horny.
[SPEAKER_15]: Third place is... Spin the dick.
[SPEAKER_15]: Spin the disc.
[SPEAKER_15]: Spin my disc.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, spin the disc is number three winner.
[SPEAKER_15]: Number two winner is...
[SPEAKER_15]: Superstar, Wee, and the number one winner, and I must say this even surprised me, but it's beautiful.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, Nick, please not so quick, is the number one best DDR warm-up song.
[SPEAKER_15]: Amazing.
[SPEAKER_15]: How did that happen?
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_17]: But it is the best DDR warm-up song.
[SPEAKER_17]: Very close call, though.
[SPEAKER_15]: More than Jake's very pissy because Little Bitch didn't get in there, but it was very close.
[SPEAKER_15]: It was very close, but... Sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just explained something to Zero.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: What'd you have to explain?
[SPEAKER_02]: When you said, oh, Nick, please not so quick, wondering how it got into DVR, I said, so small.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, the Chimpoco Mine episode of South Park.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just explained to Zero what Chimpoco means.
[SPEAKER_02]: It means small penis.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, so Evil Now Q2DX is celebrating by humping 3rd Korean machines across the United States.
[SPEAKER_16]: Caution off of whatever version of 3rd it was, 3rd Korean whatever, that was a good song.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, you know what the best fucking 3rd Korean song is ever?
[SPEAKER_15]: No, Wah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wah is the shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, Wah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Face.
[SPEAKER_15]: Face is okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: By the way, speaking of... No!
[SPEAKER_15]: Beel!
[SPEAKER_15]: I remember the fucking guy at Golfland that used to be able to do Beel backwards.
[SPEAKER_02]: Enrique.
[SPEAKER_02]: He was one of our originals.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I remember that guy.
[SPEAKER_15]: He used to do Beel backwards.
[SPEAKER_15]: We'd all go like, ew, Beel.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was like, oh my god, he can do it backwards.
[SPEAKER_02]: He would do the perfect boy band dance to it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, he does.
[SPEAKER_15]: He had a perfect boy band dance.
[SPEAKER_15]: That was great.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: That just stopped the show down the track.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: We're reminiscing about Beul.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's when you know we're desperate for material.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, and now we should do our other favorite segment.
[SPEAKER_15]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: Ask Orange Lounge!
[SPEAKER_15]: Haven't we beat this segment to the ground?
[SPEAKER_15]: Haven't they asked all their questions?
[SPEAKER_15]: Let's just story time with Loki.
[SPEAKER_15]: You have a story?
[SPEAKER_15]: It's something that reminded me... Alright, great, we get to do Storytime with Loki.
[SPEAKER_15]: If we can do a really quick Ask Orange Orange to me.
[SPEAKER_15]: How about this?
[SPEAKER_17]: Sir, send in questions, and it'll be a really quick story.
[SPEAKER_17]: And it's unfortunately not porn-related, so... Aww, what fun is that?
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm sorry!
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, so... I was just going to talk about how retarded Q's are, player.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't know, what are we going to... Let's... Storytime with Loki, what... I know, but that's our...
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, whatever.
[SPEAKER_17]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_17]: This is going to be so quick anyways.
[SPEAKER_17]: We'll do it.
[SPEAKER_17]: We'll do this one.
[SPEAKER_17]: This will be funny.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, anyways.
[SPEAKER_17]: So let me go ahead and just start anyways.
[SPEAKER_17]: I was going to tell you guys about this one person we used to play Cuesar with.
[SPEAKER_17]: Now, this woman is like... She had to be in her 30s, if not older, in her 40s or something like that.
[SPEAKER_17]: And she's still playing Cuesar.
[SPEAKER_17]: And she was like, this is what happens...
[SPEAKER_17]: This is what happens when... This is what happens when retarded people grow up.
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright?
[SPEAKER_17]: And they serve no purpose in society other than just to annoy you.
[SPEAKER_17]: So this bitch, looking to find where she fit in, she thought she fit in with Cusar.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, she was terribly wrong.
[SPEAKER_17]: She sucked ass, she's played for like five years, and the reason she likes playing is because the packs vibrate.
[SPEAKER_17]: And she liked vibrating packs.
[SPEAKER_17]: And she would only, and she got pissed off and would, we'd shoot her up, which we'd always use the, you know, aggro, like hell, you know, because she was retarded.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's not nice!
[SPEAKER_17]: And that's my story, and that's it.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's my story, and she bought a pack and built her own little mini arena in her house, and she sucks.
[SPEAKER_17]: And her name was ZapZap.
[SPEAKER_17]: Her husband's name was ZipZip.
[SPEAKER_15]: I get to go to a bachelor party at some point, I think in the next few months, so we'll have some definite stories from that.
Can you take something from me?
[SPEAKER_15]: What's the thing you have behind your back?
[SPEAKER_15]: Show me.
[SPEAKER_15]: What do you have behind your back?
[SPEAKER_15]: What'd you take out of my pocket?
[SPEAKER_15]: What were you doing?
[SPEAKER_15]: You're not nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was smooth and deadly.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't smoke.
[SPEAKER_02]: Smoking is bad for you, kids.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, yeah, y'all are funny, huh?
[SPEAKER_15]: These cigarettes have been down your legs?
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tastes like crack.
[SPEAKER_15]: Quite a few questions tonight for Ask Orange Lounge, so let's get to it.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm surprised.
[SPEAKER_15]: Usually I have to berate people for questions.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, kiddies, it's time for that segment.
[SPEAKER_15]: Tell us about Ask Orange Lounge, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_15]: Basically, I'm buying time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ask us a question.
[SPEAKER_02]: You might get an answer, but you might not always like what you hear.
[SPEAKER_17]: This segment was born from the fact that we've run out of things to talk about.
[SPEAKER_17]: And so we rely on you, the audience, to, you know, kind of jumpstart the show again.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, that wasn't a question.
[SPEAKER_15]: I was excited.
[SPEAKER_02]: You must ask a question in the form of a walrus.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_15]: More than Jake543, uh...
[SPEAKER_15]: What do they do, they do, they do love me?
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't like scary stalkers.
[SPEAKER_02]: They just make themselves in the self-love.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're admitting to being public masturbators.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: Like Creamy, you know that song, I do, I do, I do?
[SPEAKER_15]: What are they doing?
[SPEAKER_02]: Where did they get their name from?
[SPEAKER_02]: They're all Creamy.
[SPEAKER_15]: By the way, you know they're like a couple of 16-year-old girls, right, Creamy?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, I make them creamy.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have a question for you, Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: Sometimes you just feel not so fresh.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, right now.
[SPEAKER_15]: And he also wants to know, hey, what's that rash from?
[SPEAKER_02]: Dry rot.
[SPEAKER_15]: Ew.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, dry rot.
[SPEAKER_15]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_15]: EOSFBB has a question.
[SPEAKER_15]: Previously on Orange Lounge Radio, I recall somebody mentioning Chocolate Cool Whip.
[SPEAKER_15]: However, when I went to my local supermarket, they didn't have it, and the Cool Whip website didn't have it either.
[SPEAKER_15]: Can you confirm the existence of Chocolate Cool Whip?
[SPEAKER_02]: I can indeed, because I used to buy it in Medioc.
[SPEAKER_02]: It may only be sold in these customers.
[SPEAKER_02]: But what I bought at Ralph's was Chocolate Ready Whip in the spray can.
[SPEAKER_02]: The...
[SPEAKER_15]: Ah, so, okay, so Chocolate Ready Whip is what you can easily find out.
[SPEAKER_15]: Now, I have seen Chocolate Cool Whip, except I don't know if it was Chocolate Cool Whip.
[SPEAKER_15]: I think it was Chocolate Generic Cool Whip.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it was Chocolate Cool Whip.
[SPEAKER_15]: Really, okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: It may be discontinued.
[SPEAKER_02]: This was a few years ago.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'd like to know what EOSFVB is going to be doing with Chocolate Cool Whip.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I was just with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was making ice cream.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had a creme brulee and I was bored.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: Also, EOSFBB asks, where can I find females to say something for my porno music I made?
[SPEAKER_15]: These things need to be said sensually through the word I've been using is orgasmically.
[SPEAKER_15]: Always, all that I've asked have declined mentioning that they were not whores.
[SPEAKER_17]: Offer to pay them money to say this word, and then be like, okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: What's the word?
[SPEAKER_15]: My suggestion... What's the word?
[SPEAKER_15]: Orgasmically, I don't... I'd close the window.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't know, he just needs dirty phrases said.
[SPEAKER_15]: I would say, honestly, my suggestion, Yahoo.
[SPEAKER_15]: There's tons of freaks on Yahoo.
[SPEAKER_15]: Go to Yahoo.
[SPEAKER_15]: You'll find women that'll do anything on Yahoo.
[SPEAKER_15]: Take that money, rent some pornos, and rip audio from them.
[SPEAKER_15]: I know.
[SPEAKER_15]: This will work.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not boner, it's boner.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, I have the bona fide trick that'll work for you, SFEB.
[SPEAKER_15]: Tell the women you're gay, because then they'll do anything for you.
[SPEAKER_15]: They really will.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then he'll never get a date again.
[SPEAKER_15]: But no, because then you go, oh gosh, you know, as much as I love, you know, anal sex and blowjobs, I really want to try a pussy someday.
[SPEAKER_15]: And then all the women will go, oh, me, me, me, I'll help you out.
[SPEAKER_17]: Really?
[SPEAKER_17]: I'll have to remember that if I ever become single again.
[SPEAKER_17]: Phil, you know, I'm, like, gay and all, but would you, like, suck my cock?
[SPEAKER_17]: Would that work?
[SPEAKER_17]: I'll just pretend you're a guy, and, yeah.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, moving on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Last week's Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_15]: EvilNauki2DSX asks the question, Why are there no poppin' music machines in NorCal?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because we suck.
[SPEAKER_02]: How do you get hemorrhoids the size of melons?
[SPEAKER_02]: You get really constipated and then try to take a big shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Eventually, after having a whole life of nothing but bad constipation and trying to push your intestines out through your ass, you'll grow a hemorrhoid.
[SPEAKER_15]: Beautiful!
[SPEAKER_02]: Also work a desk job.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, I know this because I was looking up stuff on the internet, medical stuff, and I found hemorrhoid advice.
[SPEAKER_15]: Beautiful.
[SPEAKER_15]: Vidpower asks, will my American PlayStation 2 peripherals work on a Japanese PlayStation 2 and vice versa?
[SPEAKER_15]: Will his American PlayStation 2 peripherals work on a Japanese PlayStation 2 and vice versa?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Goddamn.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I've been using a Japanese NetCon for like years to play Wipeout on my American PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: And he also wants to know, do we Yahoo?
[SPEAKER_15]: I would like to say once again the email address if you ever want to send your comments or suggestions to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yahoo.com Orange Lounge Radio at Yahoo.com Yahoo!
[SPEAKER_15]: 23rd Magus wants to know, original or extra crispy?
[SPEAKER_15]: Extra Crispy, bitch.
[SPEAKER_15]: I would vote Extra Crispy as well, sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then again, if I get chicken, I usually pull all the skin off of it anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't eat that crap, you know?
[SPEAKER_02]: You know how bad that crap's for you?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's nothing but flour and grease.
[SPEAKER_15]: Mmm, mmm, grease.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: Also, 23Romangos has a specific question for Loki.
[SPEAKER_15]: Loki, what would you do with two quiet Jap girls and a bucket of chocolate ready whip?
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't like chocolate ready whip.
[SPEAKER_17]: No, if we're talking regular ready whip, that's a whole different story.
[SPEAKER_17]: I would have them perform a wonderful little strip tease while I eat ice cream.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's two things I enjoy, strip teases and ice cream.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god, Rob, you're matching your shirt.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob's wearing this lovely red shirt that says, I hate myself and I want to die.
[SPEAKER_02]: And he's matching it now.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's my Nakari shirt.
[SPEAKER_15]: You're glowing.
[SPEAKER_15]: That was quite possibly the funniest thing that's ever been said on this program, in my opinion.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would watch guys do that.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, now Loki.
[SPEAKER_15]: 23rd Mega says another question.
[SPEAKER_15]: I do want to know, why don't they serve ice cream in a fucking strip club?
[SPEAKER_13]: Why don't they?
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, let's open up a strip club.
[SPEAKER_15]: And it'll be ice cream and boobs.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want ice cream and dick.
[SPEAKER_15]: And on Wednesday could be like banana split night.
[SPEAKER_15]: And they serve spotted dick.
[SPEAKER_17]: What?
[SPEAKER_17]: It's a British delicacy.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to make phallic sundaes.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to come up with desserts that look like, you know...
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, man.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's just like, they serve all this greasy food and you feel sick to your stomach.
[SPEAKER_17]: You want something, like, comforting like ice cream.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, anyways, what's the other question?
[SPEAKER_15]: The other question is, what would Rob do with two quiet Jap girls and a bucket of chocolate ready whip?
[SPEAKER_15]: But he's asking you what I would do.
[SPEAKER_17]: What you would do?
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_17]: You'd send the girls over to Matt's house and... I know what Rob would do.
[SPEAKER_02]: He would just have them stand there with their boobs out and eat the ice cream.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because Rob likes boobs.
[SPEAKER_15]: DarkTetsuya wants to know, you think the arcade would be a good place to find a girl?
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, I met a guy who I dated for about a month when I worked in an arcade.
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright, I should let you finish your story, but anyways, I was going to say, meet women where you like to meet.
[SPEAKER_17]: I mean, basically, like, say for instance, you're in the arcades or that kind of stuff, or you're into this, you'll find people that are into the same kind of stuff in those places, you know?
[SPEAKER_17]: Just not home.
[SPEAKER_15]: Don't meet women at home.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, don't meet women at home.
[SPEAKER_15]: Even if you like to be home, don't meet women at home.
[SPEAKER_02]: Online is sort of okay, because nowadays you can kind of find out... I met Dan, and we're celebrating our five-year anniversary this Friday.
[SPEAKER_17]: But, no, if online's alright... It's just risky.
[SPEAKER_17]: Online's risky.
[SPEAKER_17]: Jamie took a gamble and she won.
[SPEAKER_17]: Online, yeah, online's kind of risky.
[SPEAKER_17]: Now, if you happen to be within, like, say, the 18 to 21-year-old range...
[SPEAKER_17]: I happen to know, because I was looking for my friend, my friend, um, Sean, okay, on Yahoo, the personals.
[SPEAKER_17]: Man, there's some crazy people out there.
[SPEAKER_17]: There's some women that are damn hot, and they're like, you know, wanting people to go out with them.
[SPEAKER_17]: Except for the one chick, because she was, uh, her best friends were her parents.
[SPEAKER_17]: But she was hot, so I feel like I'd overlook that, just for that.
[SPEAKER_17]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_02]: Go to college.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, college.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, definitely.
[SPEAKER_02]: Go to college.
[SPEAKER_17]: College, yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, next question.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's good advice.
[SPEAKER_15]: Find women where you like to be.
[SPEAKER_15]: Angel says, just a side question really, did you ever find the ferret?
[SPEAKER_15]: No, we didn't.
[SPEAKER_15]: I didn't even think to look for it this week.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm going to be cleaning up this room pretty good the next couple days because I promised Brian I would.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, shut up.
[SPEAKER_15]: So we'll see if we find it.
[SPEAKER_15]: But no, we haven't found it yet, amazingly enough.
[SPEAKER_02]: I found Game Boy games from the store.
[SPEAKER_15]: The games aren't actually in there, it's just the boxes.
[SPEAKER_02]: And whatever this is.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's conversion for the mouse.
[SPEAKER_15]: Anyway, moving on.
[SPEAKER_00]: Let's see what's in Rob's drawers.
[SPEAKER_15]: No.
[SPEAKER_15]: More than Jake wants to know.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm not going to tell the dead baby joke.
[SPEAKER_15]: That was so two weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_15]: What would you do for a Klondike bar?
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, go to the store and buy one.
[SPEAKER_15]: I know, go to the store, put a dollar on the counter and say, Give me a Klondike bar!
[SPEAKER_02]: Bitch!
[SPEAKER_15]: Ah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know you got a Klondike bar!
[SPEAKER_02]: And nice titties!
[SPEAKER_17]: I have sex with a very fine Asian woman.
[SPEAKER_15]: DDArk, DDArkoholic wants to know, boxers... Oh, you found the ferret!
[SPEAKER_15]: Yay, we have found the ferret.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hooray.
[SPEAKER_15]: It was way up there, it almost fell behind the thing.
[SPEAKER_15]: Uh, DDArkoholic wants to know, boxers or briefs?
[SPEAKER_15]: We'll start with Jamie.
[SPEAKER_06]: What do you like?
[SPEAKER_15]: No, what do you like to wear?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, I like... I would say in general, I prefer briefs on a guy, because they show more.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, the boxers need more accessibility.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, there was this one time where my friend's boyfriend was asleep in her bed in her dorm room.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I turned back to say something to her and his flight was totally open.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was like, you need to leave him because he's really tight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god!
[SPEAKER_02]: I used to go in their dorm room and sniff the air.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I was like, oh, you just got done.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going out now.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I would go in, it would be like in the morning, I would go in and say hi, because I would just go over there and hang out.
[SPEAKER_02]: But if it had that particular sponsor.
[SPEAKER_02]: This smells like humping.
[SPEAKER_15]: Moving on, who wants to go next?
[SPEAKER_17]: I wear both, actually.
[SPEAKER_17]: Not at the same time.
[SPEAKER_17]: That'd be weird.
[SPEAKER_17]: It just depends.
[SPEAKER_17]: Boxers are comfortable to sleeve in and stuff, but when you're playing DDR or something like that, you don't exactly want... I don't like boxers because they end up riding up into your ass.
[SPEAKER_17]: Especially when you're working out or some shit like that.
[SPEAKER_17]: That pisses me off.
[SPEAKER_17]: But then again, more accessibility, that's always good.
[SPEAKER_17]: And my girlfriend looks hot in boxers.
[SPEAKER_17]: Actually, women look hot in boxers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember the 80s, though, when it was really popular for girls to wear men's boxers?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's still popular, man.
[SPEAKER_17]: Boxers and a short cut-off shirt.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have to say, though, that getting an oversized pair of men's boxers are the most comfortable thing to sleep in.
[SPEAKER_02]: Really comfortable.
[SPEAKER_14]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_16]: Okay, um, on me, I particularly like boxers, but on a girl, see, I'd have to flip it around, and I would say Kong.
[SPEAKER_16]: That's all I got to say.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um... To that note, what's so good about walking around with a wedgie?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: Uh, as for me, neither!
[SPEAKER_15]: Ha ha ha!
[SPEAKER_15]: No, um, boxers, you get wedgies too easily, so reason.
[SPEAKER_17]: Or boxer reason.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll go ahead and speak for Dan, because I'm sure he would say this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_02]: He wears briefs, because he prefers security.
[SPEAKER_02]: But they make these boxer briefs.
[SPEAKER_02]: And those are cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because you get the best of both worlds.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, um, but as far as now women's underwear thing, thongs suck!
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, so I'm going to flip around the question and ask DD Archaholic, granny panties or thongs?
[SPEAKER_02]: There is a wide variety of women's underwear.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: See, for guys, it's usually either or.
[SPEAKER_02]: But for women, there are so many choices because, you know, we need more choices.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're complex.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right, let's go on to the next question.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, buying underwear has to be a monumental decision.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_15]: EOSFVB, do all women have bust sizes that are even numbers?
[SPEAKER_15]: Because I recall somebody mentioning that bras only come in even numbers.
[SPEAKER_15]: This is funny, because think back to the last question.
[SPEAKER_15]: Like, briefs only come in even numbers, too, and boxers and pants only come in even numbers as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: So the waist sizes are usually... Underwear.
[SPEAKER_02]: Underwear comes in single numbers, 6, 7, 8, etc.
[SPEAKER_02]: Boss sizes, though, are only in even numbers.
[SPEAKER_17]: Pant sizes are not only in even numbers.
[SPEAKER_02]: If they are juniors, they are in odd numbers.
[SPEAKER_02]: If they are misses, they come in even numbers.
[SPEAKER_17]: And boxers and briefs and stuff, they're normally like 36 to 38 or something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because they're elastic, right?
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, but what about bras, bras specifically?
[SPEAKER_02]: I hate underwear.
[SPEAKER_15]: They're all even, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, I want to know.
[SPEAKER_17]: Of course, you've got two.
[SPEAKER_17]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_17]: I want to know why they have double D and not E
[SPEAKER_02]: But they do sell bra sizes up to G because I was watching Geraldo.
[SPEAKER_02]: And these women were like... Geraldo's been cancelled for like... This was a while back.
[SPEAKER_02]: This was a while back.
[SPEAKER_02]: These women were on this show with these just humongous knockers.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they had them... No, I mean they were like the size of watermelons.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they... You all need to see this.
[SPEAKER_02]: But no, they were novelty models and they were all, you know, normally sized bodies.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some of them were actually too small.
[SPEAKER_02]: But they had their breasts enlarged to this humongous size.
[SPEAKER_02]: They look like a bad doujinshi.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, I don't understand with women getting that kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_17]: You know what I don't understand?
[SPEAKER_17]: And I keep seeing these on stupid porno pop-up ads.
[SPEAKER_17]: What is up with the freaking, you know, monster cock thing, okay?
[SPEAKER_17]: Why do they Photoshop, like, you know, zoomed-in versions of cocks on these normal people?
[SPEAKER_17]: Because it looks stupid.
[SPEAKER_17]: They have the same thing with, like, uh...
[SPEAKER_17]: You know, like, also with women getting these breast sizes that are like larger than D or double D and shit, like V or, I don't even know how high it goes, but it's like, you get more breast mass than you do actual, you know, woman.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah, it's almost, I don't know, like, I was sort of watching some of those talk shows for a while, and it's like, I think after a while they just start making up letters and numbers, so I'd like a QQRJ3.
[SPEAKER_16]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you know, there's one other thing, though, about that,
[SPEAKER_02]: Down the line, those women are going to have some serious back problems.
[SPEAKER_02]: Serious back problems.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're going to be tripping over their own boobs when they're 80.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, I've got to get things moving here because we're almost to the end of the show.
[SPEAKER_15]: Three more questions.
[SPEAKER_15]: No more.
[SPEAKER_15]: Don't send us any more questions.
[SPEAKER_15]: We've got the last three right here.
[SPEAKER_15]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_15]: Stresso wants to know, Hey Jamie, how about ice cream on dick?
[SPEAKER_02]: Too sticky.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_15]: No.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's just you.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, Naoki's both.
[SPEAKER_15]: And everything.
[SPEAKER_15]: And nothing.
[SPEAKER_15]: I guess this is a good one.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'll let one more in because this is a good one to end things on.
[SPEAKER_15]: MoreThanJake543 wants to know why.
[SPEAKER_18]: I guess I said so.
[SPEAKER_15]: Beautiful.
[SPEAKER_17]: Hello, ice cream on a penis.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, it's cold.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, it doesn't like the... How about a hot fudge sundae?
[SPEAKER_17]: That's fucking hot.
[SPEAKER_17]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's like pouring coffee on your dick.
[SPEAKER_02]: The whole purpose of foreplay, the whole purpose of foreplay, correct me if I'm wrong, is to get the dick hard.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it can do the job.
[SPEAKER_02]: It doesn't cold make it shrink?
[SPEAKER_17]: Hello, I want to know, why would you need an excuse sandwich?
[SPEAKER_15]: Sweetie, that works both ways, though, because, you know, to get the cock and the mmm, haha, you need to get the haha little, you need to get things going down there, you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, yes, I mean, but I mean... You need to turn on the sprinklers.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I mean in terms of dick.
[SPEAKER_02]: The purpose is, and for a guy, the purpose is to get the dick hard, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Isn't ice cream to feed that?
[SPEAKER_17]: It seriously would.
[SPEAKER_02]: Unless you're going for rigor mortis.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't know if things have changed since the last time I've had sex, because it's been a while, so they might have changed things, but last time, I do remember those were the rules.
[SPEAKER_17]: Last time I checked, I didn't bring in, like, a whole bunch of, like, condiments and fucking dessert items into the bedroom and shit.
[SPEAKER_17]: I mean, first of all, okay, let's just say, say you're getting up to that point where you're going to put ice cream on the penis.
[SPEAKER_17]: You have the ice cream sitting there on the side of the bed or whatever, melting away, like, dribbling all over.
[SPEAKER_17]: You know how much of a mess it's going to make?
[SPEAKER_17]: Holy shit.
[SPEAKER_17]: I know, seriously.
[SPEAKER_16]: What if it's a flavor you don't like?
[SPEAKER_16]: I know, it's like your favorite flavor, and it's just melted on the floor.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's kind of pointless.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, it's time to wrap up the show.
[SPEAKER_15]: We're going way over, and the fortune cookie message is three and a half minutes tonight, too, which doesn't help, so we're going for a record here, but that's okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: Final thoughts?
[SPEAKER_15]: Jamie?
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't put ice cream on dick.
[SPEAKER_15]: Zero.
[SPEAKER_16]: What kind of propel do you like?
[SPEAKER_16]: I almost bought you some.
[SPEAKER_16]: Peach.
[SPEAKER_16]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: Peach.
[SPEAKER_15]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_17]: The audience is way too young to be hearing this stuff.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's all I gotta say.
[SPEAKER_15]: and my final thought is the audience is horny.
[SPEAKER_15]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_15]: Good night.
[SPEAKER_15]: Thanks for listening to Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_15]: Visit our forums, calibamondi.com slash mbor3.
[SPEAKER_15]: Visit our website, orangelounge.ski.txt.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't forget next week, Drunk Show.
[SPEAKER_15]: Whore up our listening hours, please.
[SPEAKER_15]: Drunk Show next week.
[SPEAKER_15]: I will not be here.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, my God, we didn't even announce these other things that we're going to do.
[SPEAKER_15]: The long version lunches and the long version late nights.
[SPEAKER_15]: Every day from noon to 1 and from midnight to 1 a.m.
[SPEAKER_15]: Long version songs.
[SPEAKER_15]: That starts this week.
[SPEAKER_15]: That starts February 12th here on the station.
[SPEAKER_15]: So be sure to give me your CDs by then.
[SPEAKER_15]: February 12th.
[SPEAKER_02]: Next week's special guest, Shrek's Girl.
[SPEAKER_15]: Also, we're kind of cramming this all in at the last minute.
[SPEAKER_15]: Don't forget, required logins to Live365.com starts on February 13th.
[SPEAKER_15]: If you access the station directly through Winamp, you're not going to be able to do that anymore.
[SPEAKER_15]: This was not our decision.
[SPEAKER_15]: This is something that Live365 is doing to all of their stations.
[SPEAKER_15]: If you're afraid of signing up for a registration because you're going to get spam, I suggest you sign up for a Hotmail account, just a dummy account, and send it.
[SPEAKER_15]: I know.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't endorse spam at all, but Live365 swears up and down they will not sell your email address to spammers.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, and Zero says he hasn't gotten anything.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't get anything, so I do believe it.
[SPEAKER_15]: They're just wanting your age and that stuff so they can track, hey, 18-year-olds like to listen to Orange Lounge Radio or whatever.
[SPEAKER_15]: Gosh, we have a lot of 12-year-olds listening to this station that talks about pornography.
[SPEAKER_17]: They won't sell your, you know, name.
[SPEAKER_17]: But here's what they'll do is they'll go ahead and give them to the companies and then have the companies leave the money in the normal drop spot.
[SPEAKER_15]: And Tuesday we have a possibility of a fuck-off show for me.
[SPEAKER_15]: Cool, Tuesday Possibility of a Fuck Off show.
[SPEAKER_15]: In a couple weeks, we will have the CyberBeat special.
[SPEAKER_15]: We're going to do a whole special for the CyberBeat Nation trip that I'm going on this next week while I'm not going to be on the show.
[SPEAKER_15]: We're going to do a whole special, a couple hours, maybe an hour or two, I don't know yet, of just interviews, journal things, and who knows what.
[SPEAKER_15]: It'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_15]: So we'll be airing that soon.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, that was all the Orange Lounge news crammed into about two minutes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Stay tuned for the afterbirth.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yep, stay tuned.
[SPEAKER_15]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_01]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_01]: Orange Lounge Radio is hosted by DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_01]: If you'd like to leave us a comment, send us an email at orangeloungeradio at yahoo.com And now, here's your fortune cookie message of the day.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some things in life are bad, they can really make you mad.
[SPEAKER_03]: Other things just make you swear and curse.
[SPEAKER_03]: When you're chewing on life's gristle, that grumble, give a whistle.
[SPEAKER_03]: And this'll help things turn out for the best.
[SPEAKER_03]: Always look on the bright side of life.
[SPEAKER_03]: Always look on the light side of life If life seems jolly rotten, there's something you've forgotten And that's to laugh and smile and dance and sing When you're feeling in the dumps, don't be silly chumps Just purse your lips and whistle, that's the thing Hey, always look on the bright side
[SPEAKER_03]: Always look on the bright side of life For life is quite absurd and death's the final word You must always face the curtain with a veil Forget about your seat, give the audience a grin Enjoy it, it's your last chance anyhow So always look on the bright side of death
[SPEAKER_03]: Just before you draw your terminal breath Life's a piece of shit when you look at it Life's a laugh and death's a joke, it's true You'll see it's all a show, keep on laughing as you go Just remember that the last laugh is on you And always look on the bright side of life
[SPEAKER_04]: Always look on the bright side of life Come on boys, cheer up!
[SPEAKER_04]: Always look on the bright side of life Always look on the bright side of life First things happen at sea, you know
[SPEAKER_03]: What you gonna lose?
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, you come from nothing, you're going back to nothing.
[SPEAKER_03]: What you lost?
Nothing!
[SPEAKER_04]: Nothing will come from nothing, you know what I say?
[SPEAKER_04]: Cheer up, you old bugger!
[SPEAKER_03]: There you are!
[SPEAKER_03]: See?
[SPEAKER_03]: End of the film!
[SPEAKER_03]: Incidentally, this record's available in the foyer.
[SPEAKER_03]: So much for the limit roll, you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, it's a lot.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's get this place out there.
[SPEAKER_03]: We can charge this man for the next three weeks.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you think plays for us, brothers?
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you very much for listening and we'll see you next week.