[SPEAKER_16]: Do you want to hear the most annoying sound in the world?
[SPEAKER_01]: You're listening to Orange Lounge Radio, the Monty Talk, and then some.
[SPEAKER_01]: Orange Lounge may contain adult content.
[SPEAKER_01]: Orange Lounge may contain many four-letter words.
[SPEAKER_01]: Orange Lounge may contain a scene of nudity.
[SPEAKER_01]: Orange Lounge may contain hot monkey sex.
[SPEAKER_27]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_27]: Orange Lounge will not contain hot monkey sex.
[SPEAKER_27]: In this episode...
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry, but all questions must be submitted in writing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why did they have to take the word gay?
[SPEAKER_18]: DarkSakura, Sky, Loki, Orange Lounge Radio,
[SPEAKER_27]: We are live, and this is episode number 31 for February 2nd of 2003.
[SPEAKER_27]: You're tuned into the Bomani Scene's most grounded radio station of all things B-Money.
[SPEAKER_27]: My name is Rob Roberts, you might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_27]: Joining me as always are my awesome co-hosts.
[SPEAKER_27]: In the invisible corner is the happiest bunny on the farm, Miss Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_27]: You know her better as DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_27]: She's running in here like a chicken with her head cut off.
[SPEAKER_27]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, okay, cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: Did you?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yay, thank you.
[SPEAKER_27]: All right.
[SPEAKER_27]: And you get... We have horrible mic noise again tonight.
[SPEAKER_27]: And I swear to God, I fixed this problem before the show started.
[SPEAKER_27]: It's pissing me off.
[SPEAKER_27]: I'll see what I can do.
[SPEAKER_27]: I'll see what I can do during the first break.
[SPEAKER_27]: Also, say hello to our other lovely co-host.
[SPEAKER_27]: I should say more handsome co-host.
[SPEAKER_27]: I don't think he likes to be called lovely.
[SPEAKER_27]: Our handsome co-host.
[SPEAKER_27]: Say hello to our tech master, Loki.
[SPEAKER_27]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_27]: Also with us tonight, we have a whole buffet of guests in studio.
[SPEAKER_27]: Say hello to Brad.
[SPEAKER_27]: Buffet.
[SPEAKER_27]: Mmm.
[SPEAKER_27]: And pancakes.
[SPEAKER_27]: And we haven't had this gentleman on the show before, but say hello to Zero.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hey, how's it going?
[SPEAKER_27]: and also out in the other room playing Animal Crossing's Irene.
[SPEAKER_27]: She probably won't be on the show because she always plays Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_27]: Bitch!
[SPEAKER_27]: Pancakes.
[SPEAKER_25]: What?
[SPEAKER_25]: Dave, are you listening?
[SPEAKER_25]: You should be over here right now.
[SPEAKER_25]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_27]: That is a good question.
[SPEAKER_27]: Where has Dave been?
[SPEAKER_27]: He hasn't been here for a few weeks.
[SPEAKER_26]: Where's Puppy and Tal?
[SPEAKER_27]: Puppy and Tal are at Scandia.
[SPEAKER_27]: They were there for Tal's birthday and they were supposed to be here by now.
[SPEAKER_26]: But they're not.
[SPEAKER_27]: So that means punishment.
[SPEAKER_27]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_27]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_27]: So, we're going to talk about a whole bunch of stuff tonight.
[SPEAKER_27]: We have interviews from the tournament that happened on Friday at Milpitas, Milpitas Golf Land.
[SPEAKER_27]: We've got those.
[SPEAKER_27]: I know tons of you are just looking forward to that.
[SPEAKER_27]: And we'll get to everything else a bit later, but first we're going to take a quick break.
[SPEAKER_27]: And I thought we'd start off this first break with some...
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, any other opening thoughts from the folks here?
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, did the missing people just show up?
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, let's say hello to them.
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, there they are!
[SPEAKER_22]: You're late!
[SPEAKER_27]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay, we have Tau.
[SPEAKER_27]: Say hello to Tau.
[SPEAKER_22]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_27]: And then we have Puppy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Puppy's here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_27]: And then, in the back, there's Ryan.
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, shut the fuck up.
[SPEAKER_27]: What?
[SPEAKER_22]: Shock of Duval, I don't know, you know what I mean, right?
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay!
[SPEAKER_27]: Shock of Duval!
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, I'm, uh, I received a message from the chatroom, snub, just once told me Dave is in Houston, visiting the grandparents.
[SPEAKER_27]: Really?
[SPEAKER_27]: That's where Dave is.
[SPEAKER_27]: Well, we were asking where Dave is.
[SPEAKER_27]: Dude, what the fuck is that?
[SPEAKER_27]: What happened?
[SPEAKER_27]: I heard a can of soda opened.
[SPEAKER_22]: The Mountain Dew's not supposed to smell like that, yo.
[SPEAKER_27]: It's always exciting here at Orange Mountain.
[SPEAKER_19]: The Red Mountain Dew smells like a fart.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_27]: What the hell is this?
[SPEAKER_27]: D&L?
[SPEAKER_27]: It's 7 Up Upside Down.
[SPEAKER_27]: What is this?
[SPEAKER_22]: DNL is basically, it's like the opposite of 7up, as in the logo is upside down, and instead of being a green bottle with clear liquid, it's a clear bottle with green liquid inside.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's caffeinated, instead of just being, like, fucking normal.
[SPEAKER_22]: It tastes like 7up with a kick of Mountain Dew, and it's actually really good.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, but this shit I've been drinking, like, day and night.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's, like, better than blue.
[SPEAKER_27]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_27]: It's alright.
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay, we're gonna take a break now.
[SPEAKER_27]: We'll come back and talk about all the, uh,
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah, Surge was what I was going to say.
[SPEAKER_27]: It's kind of like Surge.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_19]: I like Surge.
[SPEAKER_19]: We'll take a quick break.
[SPEAKER_19]: I hate knowing you.
[SPEAKER_27]: And we'll be back to talk about all sorts of fun things, get to those interviews, maybe play some of the money match games, some of our favorite stuff, and taking your calls.
[SPEAKER_27]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_27]: We still have the phone.
[SPEAKER_27]: We'll be back.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_27]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_27]: We put your thing down, flip it, and reverse it.
[SPEAKER_27]: Hi, we're back, and you're listening to Orange Lounge Radio, episode number 31.
[SPEAKER_27]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm eating a golden stream.
[SPEAKER_27]: Mmm, you're munching on a golden stream, huh?
[SPEAKER_19]: I didn't have my nuts today, so now I have my golden stream.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yum.
[SPEAKER_27]: Tell us about golden stream.
[SPEAKER_27]: What is this?
[SPEAKER_19]: It's a brand of trail fish.
[SPEAKER_19]: And I don't like the apricots with the raisins in it, so I'm eating everything else.
[SPEAKER_27]: Ah, okay.
[SPEAKER_27]: No apricots for you.
[SPEAKER_27]: I love coconut.
[SPEAKER_27]: Last night at TGI Fridays, I had the coconut chicken strips.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yum.
[SPEAKER_27]: Delicious.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_27]: What?
[SPEAKER_27]: What are you giving me?
[SPEAKER_27]: Ooh, I get coconut.
[SPEAKER_27]: Mmm, yum, yum, yum.
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, happy birthday, Tao.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_27]: How old are you now?
[SPEAKER_27]: I'm 22.
[SPEAKER_27]: And has anybody given you spankings yet?
[SPEAKER_27]: Uh...
[SPEAKER_27]: Is anyone giving you spanking chat?
[SPEAKER_22]: Let's see, I was spanked in Beatmania, I was spanked in, uh, fucking playing Civilization the board game, I was spanked in Street Fighter, every game I played against other people yesterday I was spanked in, if that's what you mean.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah, sure, that's what I meant.
[SPEAKER_27]: Well, open up your present.
[SPEAKER_27]: Loki's given, given, uh, Tal a present here.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's got, it's got tape on it, dude, I'm not that lead.
[SPEAKER_10]: Use your nails, dammit.
[SPEAKER_22]: Use your keys or something.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have a knife, right here.
[SPEAKER_19]: We have a holy shit.
[SPEAKER_22]: Gee golly-ness.
[SPEAKER_22]: Wow, there's like so much anime in here.
[SPEAKER_22]: Wow, why are you still thinking that in my face?
[SPEAKER_27]: Because we want to hear what you've got.
[SPEAKER_22]: Name an anime and it's probably in here.
[SPEAKER_22]: Or at least ones that haven't come out yet, like Noir and KKNJ, or I'm sorry, In America, his and hers.
[SPEAKER_22]: Stupidest goddamn translation of a name ever.
[SPEAKER_22]: Nuku Nuku!
[SPEAKER_22]: Ooh, now what is this shit here?
[SPEAKER_02]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_02]: This thing is rad!
[SPEAKER_22]: But the big box that it came in has got cool anime people on it and it looks tight.
[SPEAKER_22]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_22]: What?
[SPEAKER_27]: Someone needs to bring Crossfire to this show and we're going to have a Crossfire tournament.
[SPEAKER_26]: Alright, that game right there, that is Beyblade.
[SPEAKER_26]: It's Fighting Tops.
[SPEAKER_26]: Can you believe that they made an anime about people fighting tops?
[SPEAKER_26]: It's the most retarded thing ever.
[SPEAKER_22]: You believe this chick has missile boobs.
[SPEAKER_22]: No, allow me to read the back of the Beyblade DVD.
[SPEAKER_22]: As a young Beyblader, Tyson has a dream to be the best blader in the world.
[SPEAKER_22]: Feeling confident with his technique, Tyson decides to challenge Kai, the leader of the undefeated Blade Sharks.
[SPEAKER_19]: Did they challenge God?
[SPEAKER_22]: Kai.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, so now they have a Digimon character in here.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_22]: Unfortunately, Tyson is crushed by the awesome power of Kai's blue blade.
[SPEAKER_22]: Vowing revenge, he begins his quest to rebuild his Beyblade.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh my god, this is the fruitiest goddamn thing ever.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yes, we did talk about GoldenStream.
[SPEAKER_27]: So, why is it that, like, all you Bomani freaks are into anime?
[SPEAKER_22]: Why is it all the anime freaks turned into Bimani is what you mean, right?
[SPEAKER_22]: We were here first.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, I mean, it's like, um... What the hell is Black Lion?
[SPEAKER_22]: I haven't even looked at it yet.
[SPEAKER_25]: You don't know Black Lion?
[SPEAKER_25]: Man, old school.
[SPEAKER_25]: Well, not really old school, but it's still pretty old.
[SPEAKER_26]: You know, if you'd only entered the edit contest, you would've probably won that.
[SPEAKER_26]: What edit contest?
[SPEAKER_26]: The one that was on Friday?
[SPEAKER_26]: The one that you missed?
[SPEAKER_26]: I went to go play TDX, my headache was.
[SPEAKER_25]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_25]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_25]: Sheesh.
[SPEAKER_25]: I can't make edits.
[SPEAKER_25]: My edits are like... My edits are like the Monty Ruler edits.
[SPEAKER_25]: They're crappy.
[SPEAKER_19]: If I make you an edit, you give me some porn.
[SPEAKER_25]: Uh, okay.
Yeah, there you go.
[SPEAKER_19]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_27]: Rob, put this in your butt.
[SPEAKER_27]: Hi, what's up?
[SPEAKER_27]: Sorry, I'm trying to work on that sound problem.
[SPEAKER_19]: Nice hosting job, Rob.
[SPEAKER_27]: We've got background issues today, so I'm trying to get rid of some of that background noise for you guys listening.
[SPEAKER_19]: Does everyone else hear it?
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah, I hear it a little bit.
[SPEAKER_27]: They're also having a little bit of a hard time hearing you, Jamie, so you've got to give head.
[SPEAKER_19]: How's that?
[SPEAKER_19]: Is that better?
[SPEAKER_27]: I'm going to turn down our volume a little bit so that...
[SPEAKER_27]: I'm going to turn down our mic volume, but everybody's going to have to talk super loud or they're not going to be able to hear you, so we'll go down a little bit.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's not a problem.
[SPEAKER_27]: All right.
[SPEAKER_27]: Beautiful.
[SPEAKER_27]: Let's talk to the person that hasn't ever been here before.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh, great.
[SPEAKER_27]: What's up, Zero?
[SPEAKER_23]: Nothing much.
[SPEAKER_27]: So what brings you here to the studio tonight?
[SPEAKER_23]: You invited me last week.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_22]: So how did you get... Isn't Zero X old?
[SPEAKER_22]: What do you mean?
[SPEAKER_22]: Wait a minute!
[SPEAKER_23]: I feel great now.
[SPEAKER_27]: So how did you get into this whole stupid arrow smashing game?
[SPEAKER_23]: Um, found it one day when I was on a vacation down in Santa Cruz, then heard RPG all night.
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh god, you started playing at the boardwalk?
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh shit.
[SPEAKER_23]: The worst of the world.
[SPEAKER_19]: Isn't that where they film The Lost Boys?
[SPEAKER_23]: Yep, it sure is.
[SPEAKER_19]: My, um, one of my fiance's friends is a DJ there.
[SPEAKER_23]: Really?
[SPEAKER_23]: DJ Trip.
[SPEAKER_23]: Heard.
[SPEAKER_23]: I haven't, like, heard of him, but I've heard.
[SPEAKER_23]: Anyways, yeah, I started playing there, and then I heard, like, the horrible-ass RBGL had it, so I started playing there when it was good, and then... Well, it wasn't horrible-ass back when we started.
[SPEAKER_23]: Not back then, but nowadays, that's why I said it was good back then.
[SPEAKER_27]: 23rd Magus had a funny new nickname for Roseville Golf Line.
[SPEAKER_27]: Could you post that in the chatroom so I can read it, because it was funny.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, I mean, RBGL, when we started, dude, it had, like, you know, the fourth mix, the USA and stuff, and it was fun to play.
[SPEAKER_22]: I mean, like, the first time I saw Kick the Can doubles, it was like, oh my god, there's someone playing doubles, and it's Kick the Can, hardest song ever.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_22]: But, you know, things happen, and people change, and then they get Max, and instead of getting our fourth plus or our fifth mix, and then they get Max 2, and we still have the USA and Max 2, and they get, what is it now, fourth plus and Extreme?
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_27]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_27]: I don't follow that crap.
[SPEAKER_27]: Of course, I got yelled at on... Because, you know, there's been kind of in the Sacramento community, and Orange Launch World Headquarters happens to be in Sacramento, and I know there's a lot of you not in Sacramento listening, but of course, if you listen to this show enough, you've kept up on Sacramento politics, because all we ever do is bitch.
[SPEAKER_27]: That's what we're best at.
[SPEAKER_27]: A lot of us are boycotting Rosso Golf Land because we're sick of their shit and they don't upgrade their games.
[SPEAKER_27]: I got bitched at on DDR Freak because I...
[SPEAKER_27]: Subtitles by the Amara.org community
[SPEAKER_27]: You know, how am I going to pass up DDR?
[SPEAKER_26]: It's like this, okay?
[SPEAKER_26]: I'm going to go to Golf Land because I have tons of tokens I bought down in Impetus Golf Land.
[SPEAKER_26]: No, I'm not going to drive two hours to go spend these tokens at another Golf Land.
[SPEAKER_26]: They can go, you know, kiss my ass for that.
[SPEAKER_26]: I already spent the money at Golf Land.
[SPEAKER_26]: Golf Land already has my money.
[SPEAKER_26]: It would be a waste if I didn't.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's exactly what my point of view is.
[SPEAKER_22]: Like, if I've still got tokens at Golf Land, you know, there's a Drum Mania machine there that works on occasion.
[SPEAKER_22]: And when it works, I can pump tokens in and, you know, fuck it up and then leave.
[SPEAKER_19]: I've used up all mine, and now that my car is tested and fixed and everything, I'm going to be heading my butt to Milpitas to play the horsey racing game.
[SPEAKER_27]: Speaking of Golfland and Milpitas Golfland, if you're just joining us, we do have the interviews from Milpitas Tournament that took place on Friday, and we'll get to those a little later when we're ready.
[SPEAKER_19]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_27]: Let's talk more to Zero.
[SPEAKER_27]: So, are you a PA or a freestyler?
[SPEAKER_23]: Freestyler.
[SPEAKER_23]: I wanted like 50.
[SPEAKER_27]: So what kind of freestyle do you do?
[SPEAKER_27]: Here's the next big question then.
[SPEAKER_27]: Are you an improver or a routiner?
[SPEAKER_23]: I would kind of say more routine than improv.
[SPEAKER_23]: Just because it's stuff I know.
[SPEAKER_23]: I freestyle what you guys all call like 18, like all the old stuff.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh, you're old school.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_27]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_27]: So you like to like rate bars?
[SPEAKER_27]: No, I don't touch the bar.
[SPEAKER_27]: Really?
[SPEAKER_27]: How do you do 18 freestyle without touching the bar?
[SPEAKER_22]: See, A-Team is all about the bar and the knees, bro.
[SPEAKER_22]: Bar, knees, and hands.
[SPEAKER_22]: I do knees, I do everything else, but I don't touch the bar.
[SPEAKER_22]: Dude, today I saw Loki doing his XC edit again, and he did the little freeze bit and then dropped his knees down, and you could just see his face just go like, oh, motherfuck.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, it's like my thing, I mean, like when it comes to swinging my knees, my legs over the bar and stuff, I just don't touch the bar when I spin.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_23]: Because I hate the bar.
[SPEAKER_23]: The bar is icky and slimy.
[SPEAKER_23]: Because everyone else does it.
[SPEAKER_27]: I know, and everybody's, like, all sweating because they're playing DR, and then their little mitts are all over the bar, and then they have, like, a lot of bars have those little black padding things on them that just soak up all that crap.
[SPEAKER_23]: I watched a guy wipe his head on those bars.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh, gross.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's why, I don't, that's the reason I don't touch them.
[SPEAKER_25]: I once put them between my legs and I rode them, and it was good.
[SPEAKER_25]: And that's why we don't touch the bars.
[SPEAKER_19]: I saw someone get nutted on one.
[SPEAKER_19]: We were there for that, when Rick flipped Timmy.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_27]: I got that nickname for Roseville Golf Land, by the way, from 23 Magus.
[SPEAKER_27]: He's calling it Runny Venereal Goo Land.
[SPEAKER_23]: That was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah, haha.
[SPEAKER_27]: We're so mature.
[SPEAKER_27]: Did you hear that one, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_27]: Runny Venereal Goo Land.
[SPEAKER_10]: That made me smile.
[SPEAKER_27]: USFVB, I have to ask a question to this, because this is kind of a running question about freestyle on the show.
[SPEAKER_27]: Zero, why is it that throughout all the routines that we've seen, nobody ever whips their cock out at the end?
[SPEAKER_23]: I think somebody would probably call the police or something if you get kicked out.
[SPEAKER_22]: You know, it's a whole thing of the pants you wear to DDR just don't come down so quickly.
[SPEAKER_22]: If they came down quickly, you'd fall over yourself.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_19]: Depending on the cock, I'd give them a high score.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's probably why most people don't do it.
[SPEAKER_22]: You know, there's a lot of people who say that there's a lot of gay people in the DDR community.
[SPEAKER_22]: This is probably why.
[SPEAKER_27]: If there's girls that can get up there and push their boobs together and call it a routine, then you know.
[SPEAKER_27]: Last message.
[SPEAKER_27]: That was all inspired because the OSFBB was suggesting that someone could whip their cock out and rub it on the bar.
[SPEAKER_23]: That would be sick.
[SPEAKER_27]: That would be bar raping.
[SPEAKER_23]: Another reason you don't touch the bar.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh my god, that's so true.
[SPEAKER_22]: I have little mini bars running around soon.
[SPEAKER_22]: But, damn, dude.
[SPEAKER_27]: Wouldn't it be funny if somebody got up there to do a routine and then, like, you know, whipped out, like, a cooler with all this liquor in it and said, look, I'm holding on to the bar.
[SPEAKER_23]: That was interesting.
[SPEAKER_27]: The bar?
[SPEAKER_23]: Yes, I get it.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's when you hit gongs.
[SPEAKER_22]: I want to do an episode of Orange Lounge with a gong.
[SPEAKER_22]: Dude, we would be fucking whacking that thing left and right.
[SPEAKER_27]: No little gong either.
[SPEAKER_27]: I want to wheel a giant gong in here and put it in the back.
[SPEAKER_26]: We actually have one at our work.
[SPEAKER_26]: Every time someone gets a new customer, they hit the gong.
[SPEAKER_26]: I kid you not.
[SPEAKER_26]: You can talk on the phone and it's sitting in your ears.
[SPEAKER_26]: What was that?
[SPEAKER_26]: What are you talking about?
[SPEAKER_26]: I didn't hear anything.
[SPEAKER_26]: It's hilarious.
[SPEAKER_22]: Speaking of which, tonight I'm going to be uploading a few pictures from Orange Lounge Radio because of the fact that I've got my digital camera here and I've got a website that was given to me nicely enough.
[SPEAKER_13]: Why don't you whore out that site?
[SPEAKER_22]: Not yet because it's not up yet.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'll let you guys know by next week when all my shit is up and ready.
[SPEAKER_22]: I believe Jamie is pulling her eye down and sticking her tongue at me in the Anime Girl fashion.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm not sure why, though.
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah, I'll get around to mine when I get around to mine.
[SPEAKER_26]: No more deadlines.
[SPEAKER_26]: I don't like being imposed, you know, all these deadlines enforced on me.
[SPEAKER_26]: They'll come up whenever, you know.
[SPEAKER_22]: But yeah, I'm going to take like a handful of pictures because I've been taking pictures for my whole birthday weekend in Chitton, so I figure if I grab a few from here, I'll stick them on there.
[SPEAKER_27]: Besides, what was I going to ask?
[SPEAKER_27]: We've been getting a lot of listeners through that Leech from Loki site, so where are you advertising that site besides this show?
[SPEAKER_27]: Because you're already getting a lot of hits, apparently.
[SPEAKER_26]: Everyone that emails me goes, why aren't you updating your site?
[SPEAKER_26]: Because there's a new site.
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, you know what?
[SPEAKER_27]: Did you hear that I started a new sim file, even though I haven't finished the old one?
[SPEAKER_27]: What'd you start?
[SPEAKER_27]: A new one.
[SPEAKER_27]: I'm not going to tell you what song.
[SPEAKER_27]: But, you know, I'll tell you what song off air.
[SPEAKER_26]: Well, obviously the listeners will know later on, but I did a remix today.
[SPEAKER_27]: Ah, yes, we're going to hear that, huh?
[SPEAKER_26]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_26]: And there might be a wicked sim file to go with that.
[SPEAKER_26]: Well, you'll have to listen to it.
[SPEAKER_27]: You'll find out, won't you, little boy?
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah, okay.
[SPEAKER_26]: Hey, why don't you give us a sim update, Loki?
[SPEAKER_26]: Well, I wish there was something to update on.
[SPEAKER_26]: There really isn't much going on.
[SPEAKER_26]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_26]: BomaniStyle, DJ Paranoia's taking a break.
[SPEAKER_26]: I'm putting up the DDR Extreme files because he's tired.
[SPEAKER_26]: I can understand that.
[SPEAKER_25]: What?
[SPEAKER_25]: Do you know what happened to the DDR Extreme files that were on BomaniStyle?
[SPEAKER_25]: They're gone.
[SPEAKER_26]: They're re-uploading them with backgrounds and sync steps and full steps and that kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_26]: But if you're looking for DDR Extreme stuff, there's some people are uploading stuff to BimaniSims.com.
[SPEAKER_26]: You can find stuff there.
[SPEAKER_26]: It's kind of like another site that was doing the exact same thing as I was doing, which is going to have people being able to upload their own files.
[SPEAKER_26]: Of course, it's kind of very basic, and they just have a CGI script, which you can do stuff.
[SPEAKER_26]: Of course, I'm going to be making full, beautiful web pages as soon as I get my site up.
[SPEAKER_22]: Sure you are.
[SPEAKER_26]: I am.
[SPEAKER_26]: I'm just working on downloading, uh, er, I'm working on sorting 2,000 files, you know.
[SPEAKER_26]: It's kind of difficult.
[SPEAKER_22]: Simply, you just put them in, um, alphabetic order by, um, game and song and artist and... No, it's not gonna work.
[SPEAKER_22]: ...and BPM and... What did you do?
[SPEAKER_22]: Jamie's been taking random pics with my digicam, and from... She... Oh, my God, she's doing the dancer pose.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's so... Hey.
[SPEAKER_22]: Ha ha ha.
[SPEAKER_22]: Hey, that's not a bad picture.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_26]: There's some cool stuff I got.
[SPEAKER_26]: Like, last night I got the Axifoli Techno theme.
[SPEAKER_26]: That was kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_27]: DWI 2.40?
[SPEAKER_27]: Did that come out?
[SPEAKER_26]: Well, it might have, but I don't use DWI anymore, so that means nothing to me.
[SPEAKER_26]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_26]: But for those who do, there's, like, been new DWI versions coming out.
[SPEAKER_26]: There's actually some... Actually, DWI now supports Winamp plugins, I believe, for, you know, visualizations and that kind of shit.
[SPEAKER_26]: So that's out.
[SPEAKER_26]: Plus, you know, they've been supporting, you know, lyrics for a while, which is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_26]: Then there's going to be the new version...
[SPEAKER_26]: There's going to be the new Step Mania that they're working on right now.
[SPEAKER_26]: It's going to be supporting what's done in QDX and Beatmania.
[SPEAKER_22]: Dude, if you haven't played Be Lovin' on Xtreme, you've got to play it.
[SPEAKER_22]: Greatest fucking song ever.
[SPEAKER_26]: Oh my god, play Be Lovin' at the commercial break.
[SPEAKER_22]: You have to play Be Lovin' at the commercial break.
[SPEAKER_22]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh my god, it's on Beatmania fucking 7th Mix.
[SPEAKER_22]: OST.
[SPEAKER_22]: Greatest song ever.
[SPEAKER_22]: It seriously is.
[SPEAKER_22]: You have to play it.
[SPEAKER_22]: Like, play it now.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, dude, I played Little Bitch's Oni Steps today.
[SPEAKER_22]: They're hella fun.
[SPEAKER_22]: I was, like, surprised that they were actually really well done.
[SPEAKER_22]: I mean, all of the Oni Steps were, like, these stupid gay songs, like... I'm sorry, not gay songs.
[SPEAKER_22]: Rather, these old songs from DDR First Mix, and they're... The Butterfly Oni Steps are pretty cool-looking.
[SPEAKER_22]: The Little Bitch Oni Steps are cool.
[SPEAKER_22]: The Dom Deer Rom Oni Steps are cool.
[SPEAKER_22]: They're not... There are no Oni Steps for Dom Deer Rom.
[SPEAKER_22]: Okay, well, the Dom Deer Rom video is cool.
[SPEAKER_22]: But it's amazing these old school songs that they put Onis to and shit like that.
[SPEAKER_26]: No, it's because they fucked up the other steps the first time.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, no, dude.
[SPEAKER_22]: Butterfly Basic is still one of the best ever.
[SPEAKER_22]: Is something like Beat on Extreme?
[SPEAKER_26]: Uh, no.
[SPEAKER_26]: Shit.
[SPEAKER_22]: What about, uh... Anyways, so, um... Yeah...
[SPEAKER_26]: Um, there's a, yeah, um, let's see here, what else?
[SPEAKER_26]: Oh yeah, DWI Insanity, I think I mentioned this last week, um, they've got Easy to Dancer, um, sim files now, or they're DWIs for Easy to Dancer songs.
[SPEAKER_26]: So, check those out, um.
[SPEAKER_26]: Ternimix 3
[SPEAKER_19]: And now?
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah, and the really crappy DDR extreme skins for Step Mania.
[SPEAKER_26]: I mean, it's alright, but I think the one for DWI looked much better.
[SPEAKER_23]: One problem with Step Mania is, instead of saying Perfects and Greats, it says Hi Guys and Bye Guys, and all this crap like that.
[SPEAKER_23]: It is so horrible.
[SPEAKER_23]: I laughed for a month on just one.
[SPEAKER_27]: It's the skin thing.
[SPEAKER_27]: You're going to hear about this during the interviews because we talked to some of the folks from Killer Pals.
[SPEAKER_27]: That's their whole little in-joke.
[SPEAKER_26]: See, the thing is, that can be easily fixed.
[SPEAKER_26]: Actually, I'm still playing off of the SM Max 2 skin because that's my favorite one so far.
[SPEAKER_19]: And now this kicking of Rob was brought to you by Propel.
[SPEAKER_27]: Hey!
[SPEAKER_27]: Ow!
[SPEAKER_27]: You suck.
[SPEAKER_19]: They had ass-flavored Propel.
[SPEAKER_19]: Damn it, we should give the fuck you some.
[SPEAKER_27]: Why do they have ass-flavored Propel?
[SPEAKER_27]: Lemon.
[SPEAKER_27]: That's all they had at Walgreens earlier today was lemon.
[SPEAKER_27]: Blech.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, it's not that bad.
[SPEAKER_27]: I spit on lemon.
[SPEAKER_27]: Blech.
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay, you want to do FUs of the week?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, we'll take a break and then do FUs.
[SPEAKER_27]: How's that?
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, we're going to take a break.
[SPEAKER_27]: We'll come back and do the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_27]: So you can send those to me over private message in the chat room or to our email, orangelounge.radio.yahoo.com And if you're not in our chat room, why the hell aren't you?
[SPEAKER_27]: Get over to our website, http://orangelounge.skie.cx And after the FUs of the week, we'll think about doing those Mopedus interviews.
[SPEAKER_27]: How's that sound?
[SPEAKER_27]: We will be right back.
[SPEAKER_27]: By request from Tal, because he's such a baby, we're going to hear Be Lovin'.
[SPEAKER_13]: Fuck, fuck, fuck.
[SPEAKER_27]: And Daikin Kai.
[SPEAKER_27]: All right, we'll be back.
[SPEAKER_27]: Fuck.
DJ Ranma S
[SPEAKER_20]: Thank you for watching!
DarkSakura, DarkSakura
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi, this is Mel B of RTF.
[SPEAKER_03]: And for an extra $1.99 a minute, my girlfriend Mel B can join us on all the fun together.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, if you're a broke ass like I am, why don't you come to the one place that costs absolutely nothing to go to and still the fun is just as great.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's Orange Lounge Radio, Sunday nights.
[SPEAKER_03]: Kick it with me and you just might realize the best things in life are free.
[SPEAKER_27]: Hi, you're listening to Orange Lounge Radio, and I need some folks to fill time while I fix the chat, because we've bumped out of the chat room during that break, so hold on just one sec, I've got to get us back in.
[SPEAKER_19]: If anyone can talk, I'd be you.
[SPEAKER_22]: Of course I can.
[SPEAKER_22]: We were in the car today and talking about live journals, and Black Lab got me on his friend list for some reason, and I was like, how did you not get on your friend list?
[SPEAKER_22]: And Somnia was like,
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, Tal, it's not like you ever update your live journal anyways.
[SPEAKER_22]: I mean, no one talks... When you update, it's like, oh my god, you updated for the first time.
[SPEAKER_22]: Being, of course, facetious, given how much I update, especially my, what is it, verbal vomit lately.
[SPEAKER_19]: Your post is starting to look like mine.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, I've had a bad week, okay?
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm not normally angst-bubbled.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's Triforce.
[SPEAKER_22]: Isn't that a cool Triforce?
[SPEAKER_22]: My uncle made it for me in India.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's like that silver and stuff.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'll think of it.
[SPEAKER_22]: You can't pick them up and post it later.
[SPEAKER_22]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_22]: So yes, are we still filling time for you?
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, it like bombed out quite some time ago, but we cut out the chat room we pinged out of during the break, so we got kind of screwed up there, so we're back now though, but you can reset your FUs to us if you're in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_27]: So, send those FUs to me over private message.
[SPEAKER_27]: And if you sent it while I was gone, obviously I didn't get them.
[SPEAKER_27]: So, I only have FUs from Stress 23 Magus, Dark Tetsuya, and DCB at this point.
[SPEAKER_27]: So, if you're not on that list, send them to me over IRC or... Email.
[SPEAKER_27]: Email, orangeontheradio at yahoo.com.
[SPEAKER_27]: So...
[SPEAKER_19]: I say we go ahead and get started.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_19]: We're going to do TerraMix.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, you want TerraMix this week?
[SPEAKER_27]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, we're going to do the FUs of the Week.
[SPEAKER_27]: Since we have some new listeners tonight, because earlier today I spammed the DDR Live Journal community, so I know we're going to have some new listeners tonight to explain what the FUs of the Week is all about.
[SPEAKER_19]: This is where we get angsty, bitchy, and we tell you all about it.
[SPEAKER_19]: But you get to participate too, but you don't get to say it yourself.
[SPEAKER_19]: We do, because we have a microphone, and therefore the power.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_19]: Very well.
[SPEAKER_27]: Very well put.
[SPEAKER_19]: But this is, um, just start it.
[SPEAKER_19]: They'll figure it out.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_19]: Because they're a complete moron.
[SPEAKER_19]: Starting with the one and only.
[SPEAKER_19]: We're not morons.
[SPEAKER_19]: If you're listening to us, you're not a moron.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is fucked up.
[SPEAKER_19]: I always have to wait for that, that's crazy.
[SPEAKER_19]: Um, anyway, my first fuck you of the week goes toward Walgreens, so not having berries, or peach-flavored Propel, and having only lemon, which is the ass of all flavors of Propel, although not that bad, because it's still propel, and everyone can see, it's not the best, so, ass is ass, and that certainly is the butt track.
[SPEAKER_19]: Um,
[SPEAKER_19]: My other Fuck Me of the Week goes to this ugly bitch that was driving behind me yesterday when I was following Jabberwocky running errands.
[SPEAKER_22]: Dude, DarkSakura goes psychotic in the car.
[SPEAKER_22]: It is awesome.
[SPEAKER_22]: In the two minutes I was in there, I was just like, wow, waiting for the, you know, big, hella hard level 3 super to come out and turn us all into ash.
[SPEAKER_22]: But the light went forward, something, something, something.
[SPEAKER_22]: You know her... The Dark Sakura Super!
[SPEAKER_19]: The Haruka Super.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, and it just kicks your ass seven ways from Sunday.
[SPEAKER_19]: Hey, I'm trying to be angsty here!
[SPEAKER_19]: Gimme that!
[SPEAKER_19]: Ooh, two microphones!
[SPEAKER_19]: Ah!
[SPEAKER_19]: Um, a fuck you goes toward, um... Bullshit.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't know what else to... Oh yeah, I was talking about the ugly bitch behind me.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_19]: No, not you.
[SPEAKER_19]: You were here.
[SPEAKER_19]: Anyway, I'm trying to keep following distance, you know, which is how you are supposed to drive.
[SPEAKER_19]: By law, you have to keep a three-second following distance line.
[SPEAKER_19]: This woman, every time I stop, she's right up on my bumper.
[SPEAKER_19]: And I always leave, you know, about a foot...
[SPEAKER_19]: Welcome to California.
[SPEAKER_22]: Here's your license.
[SPEAKER_22]: She was fucking ugly, though.
[SPEAKER_19]: And I would look in my rearview mirror and there'd be this face.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay, and me, normally, I'm not one to say about how people look.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm normally not that superficial.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't care how big somebody is.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't care what they look like.
[SPEAKER_19]: The chicken last message looked like a horse.
[SPEAKER_19]: But I am not superficial like that.
[SPEAKER_19]: But I'm sorry, this woman scared me.
[SPEAKER_19]: She had this epic condition.
[SPEAKER_19]: She looked like a... A skin condition or like missing a nose condition or what?
[SPEAKER_19]: She looked like a rhinoceros.
[SPEAKER_19]: She had these folds of skin where skin should not have folds.
[SPEAKER_19]: And then her eyes were shrunken deep into her head.
[SPEAKER_19]: and like her eyes looked swollen and then she had like really ugly hair that was like really curly and she would bump my car so finally I hit a stop sign and I just stayed there I stayed there for three minutes
[SPEAKER_19]: and I didn't let her go.
[SPEAKER_19]: She was starting to turn, I would just ignore it and then she turned.
[SPEAKER_19]: So then I went on my way and eventually the bitch turned and someone got in the way and I was like, and then this other ugly person got behind me.
[SPEAKER_19]: She was almost as scary, but not quite as bad, but she was just the baddest driver.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh my god, I hate people here.
[SPEAKER_19]: Not really hate everybody.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then... You're not supposed to, it's my fucking use.
[SPEAKER_27]: Is that it?
[SPEAKER_27]: Or do you have more?
[SPEAKER_19]: I had another one, but just remembering that woman's face sort of gave me an involuntary lobotomy.
[SPEAKER_19]: Not actually having the front lip of my brain broken, but just having it written in art.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_19]: And by the way, you can look up inert at www.gardenationary.com.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's spelled I-N-E-R-T-I-N-T.
[SPEAKER_10]: I, N, E, what?
[SPEAKER_10]: Moving on, next FB of the week.
[SPEAKER_27]: Loki, let's hear it.
[SPEAKER_26]: Okay, first F.E.
[SPEAKER_26]: of the week goes to the stupid news coverage of the space shuttle.
[SPEAKER_26]: Listen, to be honest, you're dumbass.
[SPEAKER_26]: So, some retard that was building the space shuttle forgot to put a freaking heat-sensitive tile on the wing.
[SPEAKER_26]: And that, oh, I guess caused the shuttle to burn up at Mach 18.
[SPEAKER_19]: Not to mention that the Columbia is the oldest space shuttle.
[SPEAKER_19]: It was in operation...
[SPEAKER_22]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_22]: They're going- 20 fucking years old.
[SPEAKER_22]: That thing should not be retrofitted.
[SPEAKER_22]: It shouldn't be ins- SHUT UP!
[SPEAKER_22]: I'M TALKING!
[SPEAKER_22]: Not you!
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm talking.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm more important than you are.
[SPEAKER_26]: Stop talking.
[SPEAKER_26]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_26]: Anyway, so, um, yeah, what do they not know?
[SPEAKER_26]: It was actually Al-Qaeda.
[SPEAKER_26]: They sent a CAC.
[SPEAKER_27]: The people that I felt bad for were the people who were actually involved with it, like NASA, the government, the families.
[SPEAKER_19]: and the friends that I had, the friend I had who saw it happen.
[SPEAKER_22]: Anyway... And my cousin who knew them all.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, don't care, okay, anyways... Hold on, so, uh... I feel bad for the government.
[SPEAKER_26]: LET ME FINISH, GODDAMNIT, OR YOU'RE GONNA BE ADDED TO THE LIST!
[SPEAKER_19]: You're gonna have to pay for this, and it's gonna come out of our pocket.
[SPEAKER_26]: Okay, anyways, so the shuttle sucked, people burned up and are dead, and they're looking for the remains over three states.
[SPEAKER_26]: So you know what?
[SPEAKER_26]: I say hooray for human failure.
[SPEAKER_26]: Now, second one on the list is... Can you address those cards and letters to Loki?
[SPEAKER_26]: The second one on the list is kind of related, is Yahoo News.
[SPEAKER_26]: I like to call them Captain Obvious.
[SPEAKER_26]: Okay, they're like, the headline's all, The trouble started on the left wing.
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah, they've been saying that ever since the stupid thing blew up, we had censor failure in the left wing.
[SPEAKER_26]: Maybe the trouble started on the left wing?
[SPEAKER_19]: Yahoo is ruder.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's a British news reporter.
[SPEAKER_26]: It doesn't matter, they still suck.
[SPEAKER_26]: They're still covering people that are getting hurt imitating jackass stuff.
[SPEAKER_26]: Even though the show's been off the TV for like, you know, over a year now.
[SPEAKER_26]: So... Yeah, and the commercials where they have just the freaks down there.
[SPEAKER_26]: So, screw Yahoo.
[SPEAKER_26]: Um, let's see, what else here?
[SPEAKER_26]: I know there was something else.
[SPEAKER_26]: Um, oh yeah!
[SPEAKER_26]: Um, American Idol Rejects.
[SPEAKER_26]: Okay, listen you people, I don't know why hundreds and thousands of you, you know, thought you could sing, or, I don't even know why you, I don't know, your parents decided to breed, because you're like some of the weirdest inbred freaks I've ever seen.
[SPEAKER_26]: And like the guy that was quote-unquote the worst- Like a bad guy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_26]: Cut for the very first time Okay, now I'm sure you're more on key than you were probably
[SPEAKER_26]: Anyway, I'm sure that, you know, at the time, the freak experiment with the cow and pig genes brought together to make some weird human.
[SPEAKER_26]: Thought it might have been a good idea at the time, but no it wasn't, and you really suck, and I'm also sick and tired of the secret people that are whining because they're like, I partied and I can't sing now, I'm famous already!
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm gonna be famous no matter what!
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright, enough of that.
[SPEAKER_19]: Now we're gonna go back to the reoccurring FDU of stupid drivers.
[SPEAKER_26]: Listen, old people should not drive cars, let alone large vans coming towards me.
[SPEAKER_26]: Listen, when you're turning, you're not supposed to turn into the oncoming traffic.
[SPEAKER_26]: You're supposed to turn into, you know, traffic going the same way.
[SPEAKER_26]: So, I don't like you looking at me and all of a sudden, Oh!
[SPEAKER_26]: I'm not supposed to turn in that lane where there's a car!
[SPEAKER_26]: But yeah.
[SPEAKER_26]: So, yeah, and F you for me missing, uh, stupid, uh, raffle in Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_13]: My girlfriend, she was part of my game.
[SPEAKER_27]: My turn?
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, yay.
[SPEAKER_27]: As of this week, I have a new FU theme.
[SPEAKER_27]: I've ditched Bakwa for something much better.
[SPEAKER_27]: Dancer, ladies and gentlemen, is my new FU, because I love this song.
[SPEAKER_27]: And actually, Tal suggested it.
[SPEAKER_22]: Dude, this song is like the fucking shit.
[SPEAKER_22]: I mean, my uber-goth industrial head roommate sits there and like, oh my god, if DDR had more songs like this instead of that fucking poppy shit, I'd play it all day and night.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway, can I get my FUs?
[SPEAKER_27]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_27]: My FUs are actually Bomani-related.
[SPEAKER_27]: Well, I have one Bomani-related FU, because coming back from the Milpitas tournament, which we'll get to the coverage of in a little bit...
[SPEAKER_27]: whoever built that merge where 680 and 80 meet
[SPEAKER_27]: Fuck you!
[SPEAKER_27]: Whoever designed that a two-lane freeway should have to merge three times to get back on the 80, causing traffic to back up for like five miles, you're a cunt, and I don't like you.
[SPEAKER_22]: Dude, you take the fucking exit that takes you by South Scandia to the A if you want, you can stop there, but B, you can get back off the highway and skip that whole thing.
[SPEAKER_22]: This is the problem, Tal.
[SPEAKER_22]: Everybody knows about that, so it's not much better.
[SPEAKER_27]: That is true.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway, so F whoever built that.
[SPEAKER_27]: Puppies!
[SPEAKER_12]: Why aren't you playing Animal Crossing?
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, because you're coming to do the FUs?
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, you okay, Ryan?
[SPEAKER_27]: F Ryan for ruining my chair?
[SPEAKER_27]: I'm putting you back in the closet where you belong, Ryan.
[SPEAKER_27]: I have more FUs, I'm trying to think of them.
[SPEAKER_27]: F Tom Nook, because he was giving away crappy shit in the Animal Crossing raffle yesterday.
[SPEAKER_27]: F people who don't like Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_27]: Starting with Tao.
[SPEAKER_19]: Rob, Rob, it's called fuck.
[SPEAKER_19]: Say it with me.
[SPEAKER_22]: Fuck you!
[SPEAKER_22]: That's the fact that I still can't get a date.
[SPEAKER_22]: That sucks.
[SPEAKER_22]: Fuck that!
[SPEAKER_27]: Fuck that no one will fuck me.
[SPEAKER_11]: Fuck that.
[SPEAKER_27]: All right, I'm done.
[SPEAKER_27]: Dude.
[SPEAKER_27]: All right, Tal, you have so much to say.
[SPEAKER_27]: Let's hear it.
[SPEAKER_22]: Actually, you know what?
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't really need to give an F you because I can just sit and rant on my live journal and people can not read it because I post so much.
[SPEAKER_22]: You know, F my fucking nature to talk so goddamn much.
[SPEAKER_22]: It gets so annoying to other people, doesn't it?
[SPEAKER_22]: Fuck.
[SPEAKER_22]: Fuck that shit, man.
[SPEAKER_22]: No, F the fucking Counter-Strike guy for fucking... Fuck that shit, man.
[SPEAKER_22]: But yeah, you guys have all heard the Counter-Strike song, right?
[SPEAKER_22]: Where the dude is like, being blacked by his buddy.
[SPEAKER_22]: Uh, we're gonna hear it later.
[SPEAKER_22]: Greatest song ever.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's my cage match pick for tonight.
[SPEAKER_13]: Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
[SPEAKER_13]: I just made up music.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_22]: Fuck the F letter in the opposite.
[SPEAKER_22]: Fuck the Daredevil movie for being gay.
[SPEAKER_19]: Fuck them for having a cracker-ass Elektra.
[SPEAKER_19]: You know the only thing that would make that movie cool is if they had chemistry fighting.
[SPEAKER_19]: Because Kevin Smith can take any piece of crap and make it cool.
[SPEAKER_27]: Like Scary Movie 3, which is happening, by the way.
[SPEAKER_19]: I thought they already did that.
[SPEAKER_22]: Didn't they do, like... Oh!
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, no, it was Scream 3 that had Jay and Tyler Bob in it.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oops.
[SPEAKER_19]: As I said, Scream 3 had Jay and Tyler Bob.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yes, they were in the background.
[SPEAKER_19]: I hate Jay and Tyler Bob.
[SPEAKER_22]: Great, who's gonna talk now?
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, I'm sure you'll figure out some way to fill three hours.
[SPEAKER_27]: Bye, Tal.
[SPEAKER_27]: Thanks for coming.
[SPEAKER_27]: Happy birthday.
[SPEAKER_02]: Everybody sing to Tal.
[SPEAKER_02]: Happy birthday, fuck you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Happy birthday, fuck you, Tal.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck you, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Happy birthday, fuck you.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, get out.
[SPEAKER_26]: Oh, yes, and I do expect presents on my birthday, just so you know.
[SPEAKER_22]: Bitch, you're getting all this shit for free.
[SPEAKER_22]: All right.
[SPEAKER_26]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah, it's the thought that counts.
[SPEAKER_27]: Moving along.
[SPEAKER_27]: Let's get to Black Lab because I have this song queued up already.
[SPEAKER_27]: So you have any, I'm sure, need I ask if Puppy has any FUs of the week?
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, yes, you don't need to ask me.
[SPEAKER_24]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_24]: First of all...
[SPEAKER_24]: A big, large FUCK YOU to that damn ECS project that I had to do this week because I was working on that shit probably a good 36 to 40 hours straight and I still did not get it done before the deadline.
[SPEAKER_24]: I got help from a bunch of people and I still could not get it done.
[SPEAKER_24]: And it just would not fucking work and I was ready to freaking put a knife to my throat because it was that fucking bad.
[SPEAKER_24]: And then, yeah, then I slept in that.
[SPEAKER_27]: Just make sure if you're going to slit your wrist, go with the vein.
[SPEAKER_27]: So many people do it against it, and that's not the way you do it.
[SPEAKER_27]: When you cut more... Anyway, yeah, anyway, sorry.
[SPEAKER_27]: We don't want Puppy to kill himself.
[SPEAKER_24]: Well, let's see.
[SPEAKER_24]: Actually, it was from the craft, so... Fuck sudden hailstorms, because I was... Yesterday...
[SPEAKER_24]: Loki, shut up, I'm trying to talk.
[SPEAKER_24]: You're distracting me.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm still trying to continue.
[SPEAKER_02]: You want to talk about suicide.
[SPEAKER_02]: Go kill yourself and I'll take over the show.
Happy?
[SPEAKER_24]: Come here.
[SPEAKER_24]: No, thank you.
[SPEAKER_24]: I can run.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm creeping closer.
[SPEAKER_19]: He's just gonna kick me, I know that.
[SPEAKER_24]: No, I'm not gonna kick you.
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_24]: Down, boy.
[SPEAKER_24]: Look at my hat!
[SPEAKER_24]: No!
[SPEAKER_24]: Not my hat!
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay, I have... No, don't get it!
[SPEAKER_24]: Kid Puppyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyy
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah, it fucking hurt!
[SPEAKER_24]: I had to bail underneath a gas station.
[SPEAKER_19]: That looks like why you call Mike Tyson's a sissy.
[SPEAKER_19]: What?
[SPEAKER_19]: Is that why you look like a sissy?
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, that's why you call him a sissy.
[SPEAKER_19]: What?
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't have... What was I just talking about?
[SPEAKER_24]: I have absolutely no clue what she was talking about.
[SPEAKER_19]: Is there a door?
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm a nerd.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright, I just got a couple quick ones.
[SPEAKER_23]: Number one, fuck you to my DVD player for not letting me play Vulgar.
[SPEAKER_23]: I have been waiting forever to get a hold of that DVD and my DVD player has died.
[SPEAKER_23]: Another one, fuck you to Evil once again who can't drive.
[SPEAKER_23]: I'm on my way walking here, and a guy can't wait long enough for me to cross the road, so he comes in like inches for trying to kill me, because, you know, he's brilliant at everything.
[SPEAKER_23]: He's some little ghetto boy or whatever.
[SPEAKER_23]: And another one, fuck you to all the jocks who have to make fun of everybody who plays DDR.
[SPEAKER_23]: I'm really getting sick and tired of it.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's when you kicked him in the balls.
[SPEAKER_23]: You brought me balls!
[SPEAKER_23]: That's all I got.
[SPEAKER_19]: No, that's what you do.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's handy that you freaking tell them what happened and they will throw their ass out.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's handy that they will.
[SPEAKER_27]: Jonas just got here, so we're going to go ahead and let him do FUs because he brought balls.
[SPEAKER_27]: Jonas, you've got to keep it quick this week.
[SPEAKER_19]: I've never had balls.
[SPEAKER_19]: I have to say, sorry for anybody who wants to hear any more FUs.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't have any today.
[SPEAKER_27]: What?
[SPEAKER_27]: You mean you're in a good mood?
[SPEAKER_27]: What's this about?
[SPEAKER_26]: Thank you for the balls, we appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_26]: Oh shit, here we go.
[SPEAKER_26]: Well, since I missed the deadline, fuck's cool for costing me to get the whole bunch of delays.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll put them in the header for my content of the contest.
[SPEAKER_26]: And it doesn't.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I missed it.
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_26]: But I missed the deadline.
[SPEAKER_27]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_27]: Chatroom FUs time.
[SPEAKER_27]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_27]: I'm going to run through these really fast because I've seen... There's more chatroom FUs tonight than I've ever seen before.
[SPEAKER_27]: So we've got to run through these.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, kids.
[SPEAKER_27]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_27]: Starting off.
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_27]: A continued FU to his ex.
[SPEAKER_27]: Maybe she'd find nothing but sorrow and pain in the arms of others.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yes, my own personal curse there.
[SPEAKER_27]: Next, I want to send an FU to Megan, you little fucking bitch.
[SPEAKER_27]: Die already.
[SPEAKER_27]: Also, I'd like to further the FU with an FU to myself.
[SPEAKER_27]: Fuck me for being so hung up on my ex.
[SPEAKER_27]: Save me, somebody.
[SPEAKER_19]: Fuck balls, because I think it might have been going to hell.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_27]: Uh... F you to politicians as a whole.
[SPEAKER_27]: Gray Davis especially deserves to die.
[SPEAKER_27]: Secondly, government headquarters and Saksucks ass, they make things so hard for me to get my job with sudden rule fucking changes.
[SPEAKER_27]: I also wanted to send F you to everyone that thinks what happened yesterday was terrorism.
[SPEAKER_27]: The shuttle was under huge security before and during launch.
[SPEAKER_27]: So, F that.
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_27]: 23rd Magus says, F you to gangster rap fans with no taste in music.
[SPEAKER_27]: I played maybe two tack songs the whole time.
[SPEAKER_27]: Let's review the rules the crowd used.
1.
[SPEAKER_27]: If you play anything with a guitar in it, anywhere in the song you get mobbed by gangster rap fans.
2.
[SPEAKER_27]: If you play anything with a synthesizer in it, anywhere in the song you get mobbed by gangster rap fans.
3.
[SPEAKER_27]: If you play anything without lyrics, you get mobbed by gangster rap fans.
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, but it gets a lot better.
[SPEAKER_27]: Four, if you play anything done by a white guy, you get mobbed by gangsta rap fans.
[SPEAKER_27]: If you play old school rap, MC Hammer, Sir Mix-a-Lot, you know when rap was good, you get mobbed by gangsta rap fans.
[SPEAKER_27]: Seven, if you play anything without a drum track, everyone mobs you.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_27]: Moving right along.
[SPEAKER_27]: Dark Tetsuya says, fuck being single.
[SPEAKER_27]: Amen.
[SPEAKER_27]: DCB says...
[SPEAKER_27]: Fuck you to EX's Random for making me freestyle to Secret Rendezvous during the Milpitas Tournament.
[SPEAKER_27]: And fuck you to Loki for making fun of Keith from American Idol, says DCV.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry?
[SPEAKER_27]: I heard, you're going to hear this during the Milpitas Golf Land interviews that we have that we're getting to later, but they all got behind the machine and did a big, like, Shiva Buddha thing.
[SPEAKER_27]: You'll see, you'll see.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_27]: The best, though, was Lil B had to do a routine of Butterfly.
[SPEAKER_19]: That owned.
[SPEAKER_27]: Just wait for the video, that's all I got to say.
[SPEAKER_27]: And then Oki.
[SPEAKER_27]: Oki did this whole rejected thing to Lemoria.
[SPEAKER_27]: It was funny.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_27]: Who got first?
[SPEAKER_27]: A guy named JC, I believe.
[SPEAKER_27]: I don't know, I wasn't there.
[SPEAKER_27]: I was playing movie.
[SPEAKER_27]: We'll talk about movies in a bit.
[SPEAKER_27]: Let's finish up FUs.
[SPEAKER_27]: Moving right along.
[SPEAKER_27]: ESFBB says, Fuck you to NASA for ruining Saturday morning cartoons.
[SPEAKER_27]: Word.
[SPEAKER_26]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_26]: I was like, ah, spatial crash.
[SPEAKER_26]: Okay, SNL.
[SPEAKER_27]: Fuck irc.eggheads.org for not letting me reconnect.
[SPEAKER_26]: Jacko on his backhoe.
[SPEAKER_27]: Fuck people that drive the wrong way in parking lots with angle parking.
[SPEAKER_19]: First of all, I woke up at like 1.30 in the afternoon.
[SPEAKER_19]: Look at my Yahoo go, oh, fuck, my live show is going to be going to shit.
[SPEAKER_27]: Moomahimer says, fuck my idiot friends, you cannot keep his damn mouth shut about every little thing anymore.
[SPEAKER_27]: Tells him he should go die.
[SPEAKER_27]: Fuck Smarties for being so addicting.
[SPEAKER_27]: Smarties, Smarties are the shit.
[SPEAKER_27]: The blue ones, especially.
[SPEAKER_27]: They make you bark, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_27]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_27]: Fuck Bomberman Online for not only being addicting but completely in Japanese which makes playing adventures ten times scarier.
[SPEAKER_27]: Fuck this dude at my school's basketball game who tried to beat up two of my teachers.
[SPEAKER_27]: He definitely should die and yay for GCHS.
[SPEAKER_27]: I second that being single.
[SPEAKER_27]: Fuck you.
[SPEAKER_27]: Skyline, DC505, says, fuck you to Nickel City for not having the other floors open.
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh man, that's Nickel City in Sacramento, by the way.
[SPEAKER_27]: SnubDisfinoid says, fuck you to the sick fuck who made the extreme dropout edit for making it way too fucking hard.
[SPEAKER_27]: Is that you looking?
[SPEAKER_27]: know that you can blame the Fifth Mix databank for that one.
[SPEAKER_27]: Fifth Mix at a databank.
[SPEAKER_27]: Fuck that.
[SPEAKER_27]: Fuck you to the people who stole my wallet.
[SPEAKER_27]: I don't know how badly you want a fucking burrito, but I hope that 40 bucks you stole from me buys your own misery.
[SPEAKER_27]: And fuck you to the college board for making the SOT one so fucking boring.
[SPEAKER_27]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_27]: BRP Ohio Bomani says, fuck you to Frankie Bones' plane for being stranded in New York and making the show be rescheduled until February 24th.
[SPEAKER_27]: Arcadian42 says, fuck you to my foot for starting to hurt like a bitch yesterday so much that I couldn't make it to Tal's party at Scandia today.
[SPEAKER_27]: It's okay, because everybody got there like three hours late and there really wasn't a party.
[SPEAKER_27]: We're all here now.
[SPEAKER_27]: SoCalKicks, hey, oh my god, I thought he was dead.
[SPEAKER_27]: He's like alive and listening to the show, hooray.
[SPEAKER_27]: Uh, fuck you to XTCC bots that take forever to send.
[SPEAKER_27]: FU to Weekends for being too short, FU to Owen for being a dick the entire week, but made up for it in the weekend, when you do give your head, and FU being broke.
[SPEAKER_27]: I want DMC2, Wind Walker, and other games, but I have no money, plus I have to pay for driver's ed classes, and I have to pay for soccer fair share.
[SPEAKER_27]: 320 bucks altogether.
[SPEAKER_27]: VidPala says, FU to the 8Kead server that just dropped me like 30 minutes ago, and MIRC wouldn't tell me, and finally, I'd just like to wish everyone out there a happy Chinese New Year.
[SPEAKER_27]: DCB says, fuck you to the fuck you segment for being so long.
[SPEAKER_27]: Let's check the eaves real fast and make sure we aren't missing anything.
[SPEAKER_19]: Um, you know, um, what you just pointed out was really cool.
[SPEAKER_19]: Balls bottles should be used for porn.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_27]: That brings an end to the FUs of the Week segment.
[SPEAKER_27]: So, how you doing, Jonas?
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, thanks for joining us tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: No problem.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anything you want to say tonight?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I was supposed to bring Bombay here today, but I wasn't sure where he was yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: I tried to look over for Scandi, but he wasn't there.
[SPEAKER_23]: He'll be here another show.
[SPEAKER_23]: He was pretty much supposed to be everywhere all weekend.
[SPEAKER_23]: He was supposed to be at Scandi the other day, he was there for like a half hour, and then he was supposed to be there at night and he left.
[SPEAKER_23]: He was, like, he was mostly out with Shane or something, and now I don't know where he is.
[SPEAKER_23]: He was supposed to go home today, but he didn't, because he lives in my house and stuff, but he just, like, he never showed up, so I don't know what he's doing right now.
[SPEAKER_27]: Where is Johnny Dun-Dun-Dun?
[SPEAKER_27]: Gone, John, Johnny, Bombay, whatever you call them.
[SPEAKER_27]: Where in the world is Silent Bombay?
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway, if you have never been in our chat room before, you should get your ass over there because I know we've got a lot of new people listening tonight.
[SPEAKER_27]: Go over to our website, orangelounge.skie.cx and click on chat.
[SPEAKER_27]: and we've got a lot of people in chat tonight.
[SPEAKER_27]: Thanks you guys for being here and supporting Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_27]: We love you!
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, we're going to take a quick break and when we come back, you've been waiting for it, the Milpitas Golfland interviews are coming up.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have balls.
[SPEAKER_27]: You have balls.
[SPEAKER_27]: Are they big?
[SPEAKER_10]: They're blue.
[SPEAKER_27]: They're big and blue.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's yummy.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, and we'll do the cage match a little later on, get to an FU segment, yada, yada, yada.
[SPEAKER_27]: I'm going to play something I saw requested in the chat room, I just got to find it real fast.
[SPEAKER_27]: Jamie, fill time.
[SPEAKER_19]: You have to play something for me, too.
[SPEAKER_27]: What do you want to hear?
[SPEAKER_19]: Because it's that time again.
[SPEAKER_27]: What is it?
[SPEAKER_19]: Guacamole Del Taco.
[SPEAKER_27]: Guacamole Del Taco it is.
[SPEAKER_27]: We'll play some guacamole for Jamie.
[SPEAKER_27]: We're going to play another request.
[SPEAKER_27]: We're going to start this off with another request I saw in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_27]: Enjoy, you guys.
[SPEAKER_27]: Thanks for supporting Arnold Finals Radio.
[SPEAKER_27]: We'll be right back with the Milpitas Golf Land interviews.
Thank you for watching!
I turned on the lights, the TV, and the radio Still I can't escape the ghost of you What is happening?
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_01]: Please listen to Orange Lounge Radio Because real radio makes Captain Jack cry
[SPEAKER_27]: Hey, we're not back just yet.
[SPEAKER_27]: We're going to play one more song.
[SPEAKER_27]: It was by request.
[SPEAKER_27]: Something from the Dance Mania album.
[SPEAKER_27]: This is from Dance Mania 20.
[SPEAKER_27]: It's Faye Wong.
[SPEAKER_27]: You might know her.
[SPEAKER_27]: She did Eyes On Me.
[SPEAKER_27]: But she also did this song.
[SPEAKER_27]: This is a great song from Dance Mania 20.
[SPEAKER_27]: It's Separate Ways here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hiho, Kermit the Frog here, informing you that today's broadcast of Orange Lounge Radio is brought to you by the letter B, the letter A, and the number 59.
[SPEAKER_13]: Can you tell me how to get, how to get to Sesame Street?
[SPEAKER_27]: Hi, everybody.
[SPEAKER_27]: You're listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_27]: We're back.
[SPEAKER_27]: And if you were asking what that song was, that was Separate Ways by Faye Wong from Dance Media 20.
[SPEAKER_27]: Brad's back in the house.
[SPEAKER_19]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_19]: No, that wasn't.
[SPEAKER_19]: That was the Sesame Street song.
[SPEAKER_25]: This is Brad being oblivious.
[SPEAKER_25]: Did you guys do the interviews yet?
[SPEAKER_19]: Balls!
[SPEAKER_27]: Thank you for bringing it up.
[SPEAKER_27]: We're going to start those interviews right now.
[SPEAKER_27]: I'm so glad you asked, Brad.
[SPEAKER_27]: As you may or may not know, on Friday I took an adventure over to... Would you like to feel my balls?
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, you're stroking Jamie's balls live on air?
[SPEAKER_27]: Can you explain the G-rated version of what balls really are?
[SPEAKER_27]: Because they may not sell balls everywhere, so I need you to explain what balls is.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay, I've been seeing people with this drink behind, I've been moderately curious.
[SPEAKER_27]: Maybe I should have Jonas plug, because he's the one that really is the master of balls.
[SPEAKER_19]: I used to work at GNC.
[SPEAKER_06]: The drink that has high caffeine and it's very good tasting.
[SPEAKER_19]: Guarana is what they put in all of those ones with ephedra, like in those little natural weight loss things.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's not necessarily caffeine, it's very like caffeine.
[SPEAKER_26]: Dead or Alive Volleyball, best game ever.
[SPEAKER_19]: Actually, it's the game that makes men act like girls.
[SPEAKER_19]: And I explain it this way.
[SPEAKER_19]: Because they have to go shopping and buy accessories and know what their favorite colors are and their favorite foods.
[SPEAKER_19]: And then they give presents to other girls.
[SPEAKER_26]: Borderline dating sim.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's a dating sim for lesbians.
[SPEAKER_26]: Sweet.
[SPEAKER_19]: It makes men act like lesbians.
[SPEAKER_19]: DOA Volleyball.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you like DOA Extreme Beach Volleyball, show the upcoming game that's probably going to come out this year for the Xbox.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's called NUDE.
[SPEAKER_19]: I have that BMX XXX game.
[SPEAKER_19]: They sent it to us for free.
[SPEAKER_07]: How's that game anyways?
[SPEAKER_19]: Actually, as a game, it's not that bad, but it's not the best either.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, but we, because Dan manages GameStop, we get all kinds of neat free video games and all kinds of cool swag.
[SPEAKER_19]: Like, you know, I don't know if you saw my keychain, I have a GameCube keychain and a GBA keychain.
[SPEAKER_19]: Lovely Brad, lovely.
[SPEAKER_19]: In case people missed it, Brad belched.
[SPEAKER_19]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, are you guys ready to get to the interviews?
[SPEAKER_19]: No.
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_19]: But we get free games every so often.
[SPEAKER_19]: And we get, like, porn games.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, you guys ready?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_27]: We're going to do the Milpitas Golf Land interviews.
[SPEAKER_27]: Enjoy.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_18]: Do little buttons in front of you and it's a whip and a hold or something, a bridle, I don't know what that crap is.
[SPEAKER_18]: And you sit there and you whip the hell out of your horse.
[SPEAKER_18]: And if you win, you get really excited.
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay, I don't know what happened at the beginning of that interview.
[SPEAKER_27]: That's weird.
[SPEAKER_27]: It kind of cuts in the middle there.
[SPEAKER_27]: But we're talking to Melody, also known as Shark's Girl, about Derby Owners Club.
[SPEAKER_27]: That's kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_27]: She's explaining what Derby Owners Club is all about.
[SPEAKER_27]: Sorry about that.
[SPEAKER_18]: You say, I want to do it again.
[SPEAKER_18]: And if you lose, you say, I have to do it again because I have to win.
[SPEAKER_18]: And suddenly, you're down $100.
[SPEAKER_27]: I won a race earlier and I nearly wet my pants.
[SPEAKER_27]: I was so excited.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, and you beat me.
[SPEAKER_27]: I'm sorry, but I beat my horse more than I beat you, if that's any consolation.
[SPEAKER_27]: I leave the beating to somebody else.
[SPEAKER_18]: I guess I'll forgive you for that, and I'm just going to leave that comment right alone.
[SPEAKER_27]: You're so kind.
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, isn't there some DDR thing going on here today, too?
[SPEAKER_27]: A DDR tournament?
[SPEAKER_27]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, yeah, there's a DDR tournament going on in the other room.
[SPEAKER_27]: Is that why you're here tonight?
[SPEAKER_27]: Are you going to be participating in anything?
[SPEAKER_27]: Are you just here to cheer people on?
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm just kind of here to watch.
[SPEAKER_18]: This time I'm not doing anything.
[SPEAKER_18]: Not going to do that for a little while.
[SPEAKER_18]: But yeah, I just kind of wanted to see what's going on and catch more Xtreme because I still haven't heard many of the songs on it.
[SPEAKER_27]: I think that's pretty much me too.
[SPEAKER_27]: You know, if you listen to Orange Lounge from Monty Music and more, you're going to hear lots of stuff from Xtreme.
[SPEAKER_27]: Wink, wink, nudge, nudge, plug.
[SPEAKER_18]: Well, you know, I kind of have this little thing called a life that really keeps me... Hey!
[SPEAKER_18]: Hey!
[SPEAKER_27]: I don't like where you're going with that, Missy.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay, well, how about this?
[SPEAKER_18]: I have a really slow freaking connection.
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_27]: Fine, be that way.
[SPEAKER_27]: Fine, we understand.
[SPEAKER_27]: I don't want to talk to you no more.
[SPEAKER_27]: Let's talk to this person sitting across the table.
[SPEAKER_27]: Say hello.
[SPEAKER_17]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_27]: What's your name?
[SPEAKER_17]: Uh, Ron.
[SPEAKER_27]: And do you have an online name that you buy?
[SPEAKER_17]: Uke Bondage Boy.
[SPEAKER_27]: Right on.
[SPEAKER_27]: What brings you to today's lovely tournament?
[SPEAKER_17]: Being cheerleader for my aniki.
[SPEAKER_27]: Right on.
[SPEAKER_27]: So you're not going to be participating?
[SPEAKER_27]: Are you going to get up there and actually cheerlead while there's a routine going on?
[SPEAKER_17]: No.
[SPEAKER_27]: Do you think Parapara is anything like cheerleading?
[SPEAKER_17]: Somewhat, yeah.
[SPEAKER_27]: Do you own any boots?
[SPEAKER_27]: Boots?
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah, you know, like Parapara boots, the big silver boots that come up to your knees?
[SPEAKER_17]: No, I have big black boots with lots of buckles.
[SPEAKER_27]: That's where you go.
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, hence the name Bondage.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_27]: So why do you go by Bondage Boy?
[SPEAKER_27]: Is it just, you like...
[SPEAKER_17]: It was actually a joke because most people when I talk to them online, I don't tell them that I'm female right away.
[SPEAKER_17]: Because a lot of Yaoi fans are female and they're all into the whole female-female relationship.
[SPEAKER_17]: So I don't need any extra baggage like that.
[SPEAKER_27]: So you're into the Yaoi, huh?
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_27]: So is the lovely Jamie who couldn't be here tonight.
[SPEAKER_27]: I'm sure you two could talk about Yaoi all night long.
[SPEAKER_17]: We often do.
[SPEAKER_27]: Right on.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yes, yes.
[SPEAKER_27]: What's your favorite Yaoi?
[SPEAKER_17]: Um, I don't have a favorite right now.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm like really into Xenogears because I just started playing it and Initial D. Initial D. Cool.
[SPEAKER_27]: What if they did like Initial D Yaoi that's like kind of role playing?
[SPEAKER_27]: Would that be like the shit?
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, I already kind of do that.
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, right on.
[SPEAKER_27]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_27]: Well, anything else you want to say to lovely listeners of Orange Launch Radio?
[SPEAKER_17]: Have fun listening.
[SPEAKER_17]: I can't listen.
[SPEAKER_17]: My computer doesn't like streaming.
[SPEAKER_27]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_27]: We forgive you.
[SPEAKER_27]: But thanks for being on the show.
[SPEAKER_17]: Not a problem.
[SPEAKER_27]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_27]: Also joining us, we're joined by a few good men here at the table.
[SPEAKER_27]: Say hello, everybody.
[SPEAKER_27]: I hope he doesn't mind me shoving the microphone in his face.
[SPEAKER_27]: It's Mr. Wendell.
[SPEAKER_27]: You just say that so erotically.
[SPEAKER_27]: I was coming off a yaoi high.
[SPEAKER_27]: What can I say?
[SPEAKER_27]: I said coming.
[SPEAKER_27]: You make my nipples so hard now.
[SPEAKER_27]: So are you going to be participating in today's tournament?
[SPEAKER_27]: I will participate...
[SPEAKER_27]: I'll be it, not necessarily be all that great, but hey, hey, that rhymed.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah, I'll enter improv freestyle just for the heck of it, you know.
[SPEAKER_27]: I'm sure it'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_27]: Now, how do you approach improv freestyle as opposed to routine freestyle, with the obvious exception of you don't really plan in advance?
[SPEAKER_27]: Do you go in a different mindset when you get there?
[SPEAKER_12]: You never really know what song you're going to get.
[SPEAKER_12]: You just got to go with what you got, try to do what you can.
[SPEAKER_24]: Let's hear that comment for the listeners.
[SPEAKER_27]: I fuckin' forgot.
[SPEAKER_27]: And who are you, good sir?
[SPEAKER_27]: I want that one, Bobby!
[SPEAKER_27]: Shut up, dude.
[SPEAKER_27]: That's a hella cool name.
[SPEAKER_27]: Fuzzy Hat.
[SPEAKER_27]: Hello, Fuzzy Hat.
[SPEAKER_27]: What brings you to today's tournament?
[SPEAKER_27]: Um, it's either this or go to Dave & Buster's.
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, you're here for Derby Owners Club, too, then?
[SPEAKER_27]: No, I get Derby Owners Club for free at Dave & Buster's.
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh!
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, I see.
[SPEAKER_27]: Are you going to be participating?
[SPEAKER_27]: Are you going to be participating in Improv 2?
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_27]: Now what happens if you get Baby Baby Love Me?
[SPEAKER_27]: It'll be hella awesome.
[SPEAKER_27]: Will it be erotic and sensuous?
[SPEAKER_27]: No, it'll just be hella awesome.
[SPEAKER_27]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_27]: Well, good luck to you both.
[SPEAKER_27]: Good luck.
[SPEAKER_27]: Also over here, let's say hello to an old favorite of the show as well.
[SPEAKER_27]: Say hello to MLB.
[SPEAKER_27]: Hello, buddy.
[SPEAKER_03]: And what brings you to today's tournament?
[SPEAKER_03]: Intrigue.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just kind of interesting to see after all the ranting and raving there's been going on between preparedness and improv routines, there's a competition catered to the improv kind.
[SPEAKER_03]: So do you think something like this was needed for the community?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think improv is...
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just as important to freestyle as prepared routines are.
[SPEAKER_03]: There are some people who prefer the former over the latter.
[SPEAKER_03]: There are some who think that someone who has raw talent should be able to win every tourney.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is one for argument's sake, if nothing else.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you're not going to be participating, though?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I would, but it's like, I gotta save my goods up for the CBN coming up in a couple weeks, and it's like, if I, you know, blow my wad now, I'll be shooting blanks at CBN, and then, you know, what happens there?
[SPEAKER_03]: Heaven forbid, Mel Blank.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, that's what the B will stand for.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's all, folks!
[SPEAKER_27]: On that note, I think this interview is going to come to a close, but do you guys have any final thoughts, anything you guys want to say to listeners, Orange Ons?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, uh, go out there, have some fun, and where's the beer?
[SPEAKER_27]: Where is the beer?
[SPEAKER_27]: That's a very good question.
[SPEAKER_27]: Jamie, Jamie's, the lovely DarkSakura, who couldn't be here tonight, unfortunately, is going to be getting drunk on the show, I believe, the next week's show.
[SPEAKER_27]: While I'm away at CyberBeat Nation, she's going to help me get drunk.
[SPEAKER_27]: I love you, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_13]: You should have been here.
[SPEAKER_27]: Wait, Jamie, I want to interrupt and say something.
[SPEAKER_19]: Um, I will be getting drunk and DarkSakura will be getting drunk with me.
[SPEAKER_27]: Word.
[SPEAKER_19]: And our static problem got worse.
[SPEAKER_27]: Damn it, our static problem.
[SPEAKER_26]: I won't be getting drunk, I don't think, because I don't drink and I'm kind of afraid to drink because since I'd be such a lightweight, you know, getting sick and then possibly violent, you know, who knows.
[SPEAKER_27]: You're going to be around two drunk women.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_19]: We're going to be, like, laughing our asses off.
[SPEAKER_27]: Too bad there's no, like, attraction or anything, or you could be in the middle of a lesbian sandwich.
[SPEAKER_27]: No!
[SPEAKER_27]: All right, back to the interviews.
[SPEAKER_27]: It's called work, and it's evil.
[SPEAKER_27]: Any final thoughts from LB?
[SPEAKER_03]: RTF World domination.
[SPEAKER_03]: Give us your finest meats and cheeses.
[SPEAKER_03]: Any final words from Shark Skrull?
[SPEAKER_18]: Say no to derby owner crack.
[SPEAKER_27]: And even though I already asked her anything from Bondage Boy?
[SPEAKER_17]: Um...
[SPEAKER_17]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_27]: I love your hair, by the way.
[SPEAKER_17]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's fake.
[SPEAKER_27]: It's smurfalicious.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_27]: All right, more interviews to come later.
[SPEAKER_27]: And now joining us at the table, the ever so lovely tonight's, introduce yourself, kind lady.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hi, I'm Jenny Bean.
[SPEAKER_00]: What's up, everyone?
[SPEAKER_27]: How are you doing tonight?
[SPEAKER_27]: What brings you to Milpitas tonight?
[SPEAKER_00]: The wonderful tournament that Milton's running.
[SPEAKER_27]: Right on.
[SPEAKER_27]: Are you going to be participating?
[SPEAKER_27]: Are you judging or what's going on?
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm judging.
[SPEAKER_27]: Now, okay, I haven't talked to a judge yet.
[SPEAKER_27]: What are you going to be looking for in tonight's improv?
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know, it's harder to judge improv, I think.
[SPEAKER_00]: But, um, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm just looking for a good flow of routines and all that.
[SPEAKER_00]: The normal stuff.
[SPEAKER_27]: Now, I know you can't play favorites.
[SPEAKER_27]: Was there any particular person you're looking forward to seeing do an improv routine?
[SPEAKER_00]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_00]: Actually, I guess Fuzzy Hat, because I like his improv routines.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think he's pretty good at them.
[SPEAKER_27]: He does some pretty good shit.
[SPEAKER_27]: We're hoping he gets Baby Baby Love Me.
[SPEAKER_00]: That would be cool!
[SPEAKER_27]: Anything else you want to say to the listeners of Orange Launch Radio?
[SPEAKER_27]: And DarkSakura and Loki, they're in the studio, couldn't be here tonight.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hello to all of them and hello to everyone who's listening.
[SPEAKER_27]: Any words of wisdom for Bomani players out there?
[SPEAKER_27]: Any new people that want to start improv freestyling?
[SPEAKER_00]: Watch videos.
[SPEAKER_27]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_27]: All right.
[SPEAKER_27]: More interviews to come.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, a little bit of time has passed, and PA's over now, and I had a second to step outside with this fine gentleman.
[SPEAKER_27]: Introduce yourself for all the Orange Islands listeners.
[SPEAKER_27]: I'm Milton, aka Maple, the tournament organizer of NorCal.
[SPEAKER_27]: Right on!
[SPEAKER_27]: So, what made you decide to do a tournament today?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, Xtreme came out a month ago, and I promised Paul, as well as a lot of other people, that I'd throw a tournament one month after we got Xtreme.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, a month later, tournament.
[SPEAKER_05]: How's it going?
[SPEAKER_05]: You guys happy with the turnout?
[SPEAKER_05]: Turnout, yes.
[SPEAKER_27]: We didn't think it would be this many people, but then people surprised us.
[SPEAKER_27]: Last minute people come and, you know.
[SPEAKER_27]: Right on.
[SPEAKER_27]: So what made you guys decide to do an improv freestyle as opposed to the typical routine freestyle?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, honestly, out of all my tournaments, I've never run improv.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's always been routine freestyle.
[SPEAKER_05]: And a person, Jason Rain, or Rain on the boards as you may know, he brought to my attention that, you know, there should be improv, just improv against routine.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I decided to throw improv freestyle, and then a lot of people entered, you know, people supported, some people didn't support it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And besides, I didn't want to have a routine freestyle with CBN coming up so soon.
[SPEAKER_27]: That's what a lot of people have been saying, is that they're kind of glad that it didn't happen because they're saving their routines for CyberBeat, so I'll be going.
[SPEAKER_27]: So you're going to be going to CyberBeat?
[SPEAKER_27]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, looking forward to that.
[SPEAKER_27]: So how many tournaments have you, in the past year, how many tournaments have you had a hand in running, do you think?
[SPEAKER_22]: In running or helping with?
[SPEAKER_05]: Both, if you can recall either.
[SPEAKER_05]: Everything from Fremont to now, excluding Spiegel 2.
[SPEAKER_27]: Everything.
[SPEAKER_27]: I'm pretty sure.
[SPEAKER_27]: In NorCal.
[SPEAKER_27]: That's a whole lot of tournaments.
[SPEAKER_27]: Wait, you haven't actually judged a tournament in a while, though.
[SPEAKER_27]: That's kind of a break for you.
[SPEAKER_27]: Well, I judged MGL Evil Tournament 2, which was December 13th.
[SPEAKER_27]: What kind of things do you think the judges will be looking for tonight in Improv Freestyles post-routine freestyle?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, for...
[SPEAKER_05]: We're from Freestyle.
[SPEAKER_05]: This time I have seven judges, and they're each judging a category.
[SPEAKER_05]: For example, one of them is judging on energy, one of them is judging on power moves, other one is judging on arrow flexibility, which is how to use the arrows.
[SPEAKER_05]: Any other upcoming events you want to let our listeners know about?
[SPEAKER_05]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_05]: The only thing I know about is CBN in February, and then March Madness in March, and then Pride V3 in May.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think May 18th and 19th, I'm pretty sure, or the weekend around there.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then as for summer, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I think Spiegel 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right, Corey?
[SPEAKER_05]: Supposedly.
[SPEAKER_27]: Supposedly.
[SPEAKER_27]: Big question mark.
[SPEAKER_27]: You're here first.
[SPEAKER_27]: Or second.
[SPEAKER_27]: Or third.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anything else you want to say to listeners?
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay, yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: What about the other 13 categories you mentioned to me earlier?
[SPEAKER_05]: What do you mean by them?
[SPEAKER_05]: You said you had 20!
[SPEAKER_05]: I had 20, yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I had to cut down.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't want more judges than there are entries in the tournament.
[SPEAKER_05]: I understand.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dismissed!
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you for joining us today.
[SPEAKER_05]: No problem.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good luck with the rest of the tournament.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, thanks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, so we got another interview here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Introduce yourself for our listeners.
[SPEAKER_06]: Axel?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_27]: Hi guys.
[SPEAKER_27]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_27]: Where you from?
[SPEAKER_27]: Stockton.
[SPEAKER_27]: What brings you to the Milpitas Tournament this evening?
[SPEAKER_23]: To see my buddy Milton and John, Virtue.
[SPEAKER_23]: Don't lie.
[SPEAKER_23]: The rest of the Killer Pals and Samantha.
[SPEAKER_23]: Are you participating in anything tonight?
[SPEAKER_23]: PA?
[SPEAKER_23]: Improv?
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh yeah, I did PA.
[SPEAKER_23]: How'd you do?
[SPEAKER_06]: Lost first round to Tigger.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dope.
[SPEAKER_06]: Very dope.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, I'm off then too.
[SPEAKER_06]: What was the song?
[SPEAKER_06]: What was it?
[SPEAKER_06]: It was a gentle stress.
[SPEAKER_27]: Bummer.
[SPEAKER_27]: So you're not going to be doing freestyle?
[SPEAKER_27]: You're watching?
[SPEAKER_23]: I'm leaving.
[SPEAKER_27]: You're leaving?
[SPEAKER_27]: Is it hard to get to?
[SPEAKER_27]: You said you were having problems getting a ride over here?
[SPEAKER_27]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_27]: No one is willing to really take me.
[SPEAKER_27]: Tell us about the DDR scene in Stockton because we don't talk to many people from there.
[SPEAKER_27]: We've talked about Stockton Golf Land on the show because we refer to it as Ghetto Golf Land, but...
[SPEAKER_27]: It is pretty ghetto.
[SPEAKER_27]: If you want to get shot, then that's the place to go.
[SPEAKER_27]: Have you ever seen anyone get killed at Golf Line?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, but I've witnessed a shooting.
[SPEAKER_27]: Have you ever wanted to kill somebody at Golf Line?
[SPEAKER_23]: Not me.
[SPEAKER_27]: Those little kids are fucking mean.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_23]: Every day I want to kill them.
[SPEAKER_23]: They ask for tokens.
[SPEAKER_23]: I give them to them.
[SPEAKER_23]: They're intimidating.
[SPEAKER_23]: Anything else you want to say to our listeners this evening?
[SPEAKER_27]: Bye, guys.
[SPEAKER_21]: Says it all.
[SPEAKER_27]: All right, we are back with somebody who was on the show a couple weeks ago when we were at his tournament, but now he's here at the Milpitas tournament.
[SPEAKER_27]: Introduce yourselves to the listeners.
[SPEAKER_27]: Hi, guys.
[SPEAKER_27]: I'm DCB.
[SPEAKER_27]: Hi, DCB.
[SPEAKER_27]: What brings you to Milpitas today?
[SPEAKER_27]: One word.
[SPEAKER_27]: Shades.
[SPEAKER_27]: That's another interview I've got to get later if I can.
[SPEAKER_27]: So...
[SPEAKER_21]: What kinds of stuff are you doing here today?
[SPEAKER_21]: Are you participating in PA?
[SPEAKER_21]: I was one of the three people that didn't qualify for PA.
[SPEAKER_21]: Dope!
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, I'm that leet.
[SPEAKER_21]: You're in a special club?
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, there's like three of us, so that's cool.
[SPEAKER_27]: Did you come in dead last?
[SPEAKER_21]: Nah, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_21]: Ask Milton.
[SPEAKER_27]: Well, that's something.
[SPEAKER_27]: At least you didn't come in last.
[SPEAKER_27]: Or if you did, hey, last place or something.
[SPEAKER_27]: So I hear you got a joke for the listeners.
[SPEAKER_27]: Knock, knock.
[SPEAKER_21]: Who's there?
[SPEAKER_21]: Bob.
[SPEAKER_21]: Bob who?
[SPEAKER_21]: Bob Saget.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh!
[SPEAKER_21]: Ha.
[SPEAKER_21]: Dot, dot, dot.
[SPEAKER_21]: Ha, ha.
[SPEAKER_21]: I think if you were on Star Search, they would have given you one star, but that's all right.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'd rather be on American Idol, because Simon is sexy.
[SPEAKER_21]: You want to audition for American Idol right now?
[SPEAKER_21]: You want to sing us something?
[SPEAKER_21]: No.
[SPEAKER_21]: Sing us something from DDR.
[SPEAKER_03]: Come on, Cartoon Heroes.
[SPEAKER_27]: We are the Killer Pals.
[SPEAKER_27]: Hi, guys.
[SPEAKER_27]: Explain to our listeners.
[SPEAKER_27]: I don't think we talked about this in Fremont.
[SPEAKER_27]: Tell us about the Killer Pals.
[SPEAKER_27]: What is the concept behind Killer Pals?
[SPEAKER_21]: and plug the website.
[SPEAKER_21]: We really don't know.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's just like all my friends and we call ourselves the Killer Pals.
[SPEAKER_21]: Do you kill people?
[SPEAKER_21]: No, we don't kill people.
[SPEAKER_21]: We're actually nice kids and we get good grades in school and we drink our milk every night.
[SPEAKER_27]: I was going to say, I noticed you changed from Kirk Cameron to Bob Saget.
[SPEAKER_27]: What brought this on?
[SPEAKER_21]: Kirk Cameron is just old.
[SPEAKER_21]: He didn't want to be my friend anymore.
[SPEAKER_21]: But Bob Saget, he's fresh.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, he's cool.
[SPEAKER_22]: New ideas.
[SPEAKER_21]: New ideas.
[SPEAKER_27]: Dirty Works is one of my favorite movies of all time.
I like Full House.
[SPEAKER_27]: Hey, did you hear the Olsen twins are going to college soon?
[SPEAKER_13]: I did it.
[SPEAKER_27]: That one's for you, bro, too.
[SPEAKER_27]: Who's your favorite Olsen twin?
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah, anyway.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anything else you want to say for our listeners?
[SPEAKER_21]: I just did the shittiest routine ever in a DDR tournament.
[SPEAKER_09]: Can you say shittiest?
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes, you can say anything you want on the fucking internet.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, it sucked real bad.
[SPEAKER_21]: I didn't know what I was doing.
[SPEAKER_21]: I tried popping and locking all those cool kids, but I'm too white to do it.
[SPEAKER_21]: And then all the other killer pals got behind the machine and started making designs with their arms.
[SPEAKER_21]: And I don't know, I was just trying not to fail the stupid song.
[SPEAKER_21]: Were you leading everybody in the wave?
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't know what I was doing.
[SPEAKER_27]: What song did you get?
[SPEAKER_21]: Secret Rendezvous.
[SPEAKER_27]: Secret Lovers.
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, is that the concept behind Killer Pals?
[SPEAKER_27]: No, I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's between me and Bob Saget.
[SPEAKER_27]: Well, you know what they say about Bob Saget.
[SPEAKER_27]: All right.
[SPEAKER_27]: Any final words for listeners?
[SPEAKER_27]: Bye, guys.
[SPEAKER_27]: How did I know?
[SPEAKER_27]: All right.
[SPEAKER_27]: I'm just going to move right over here to somebody who has been piping in.
[SPEAKER_27]: Because he always has something to say.
[SPEAKER_27]: Say hello.
[SPEAKER_27]: This is, what, the fourth or fifth time you've been on the show?
[SPEAKER_27]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_27]: Conquered.
[SPEAKER_27]: Just tell us who you are.
[SPEAKER_27]: I'm God, I mean Virtu, Tori, Max300, yeah, oh my god, it's the Max300 guy, yeah, um, no, no, Max Unlimited, and Legend of Max, and DDR, or Dance Dance Revolution, and you're, DDR, and you're telling me about AAAs today?
[SPEAKER_27]: Yes, I have 20 heavy AAAs in two weeks, you're almost a Yasu level there, no, no, I'm scared of Yasu, what would you do if you showed up at Cyber Beat Nation?
[SPEAKER_27]: I wouldn't enter, what?
[SPEAKER_18]: Bye, guys!
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh, wait, say hello to our listeners.
[SPEAKER_18]: Who are you, young lady?
[SPEAKER_18]: Hi, I'm Samantha.
[SPEAKER_27]: Hi, Samantha.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anything you want to say?
[SPEAKER_27]: I have a Fakuk shirt, too.
[SPEAKER_27]: It's one of my favorite clothing brands.
[SPEAKER_18]: Everybody loves Fakuk.
[SPEAKER_27]: Everybody loves to Fakuk.
[SPEAKER_27]: I have an Evo.
[SPEAKER_27]: Well, bye!
[SPEAKER_27]: Hey, back to Virtue.
[SPEAKER_27]: Before I was so rudely interrupted... Calm down, buddy.
[SPEAKER_27]: Well, we were like, oh my god, a chick that plays DDR, so, you know, we had to...
[SPEAKER_27]: We had to break.
[SPEAKER_27]: News bulletin.
[SPEAKER_27]: Of course, we've got DarkSakura in the studio right now.
[SPEAKER_27]: I know Chick plays DDR, but, you know.
[SPEAKER_27]: So, yes, do you have questions for me?
[SPEAKER_27]: Do I have questions for you?
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah, what the hell are you doing here today?
[SPEAKER_27]: You doing Perfect Attack?
[SPEAKER_27]: You doing Freestyle?
[SPEAKER_27]: I'm losing to Tigger.
[SPEAKER_27]: As Perfect Attack's over, you lost to Tigger?
[SPEAKER_27]: Final round?
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_27]: What was it?
[SPEAKER_27]: What'd you have to fight him on?
[SPEAKER_27]: Perfect Attack.
[SPEAKER_27]: Fucking holic.
[SPEAKER_27]: Piece of shit.
[SPEAKER_27]: Motherfucking cocksuck.
[SPEAKER_27]: How bad did he beat you?
[SPEAKER_27]: 93 Marvelous?
[SPEAKER_27]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_27]: So you're not going to be doing a freestyle today?
[SPEAKER_27]: I did my freestyle with the Killer Pals.
[SPEAKER_27]: I made the design.
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_27]: What was the design?
[SPEAKER_27]: What design were you a part of?
[SPEAKER_27]: I was the arm.
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_27]: So any other... You know that Buddha thing that has all the weird arms and like 50 legs?
[SPEAKER_27]: We made that behind the machine.
[SPEAKER_13]: And the machine was the body.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just had a picture of like all the fobs in the crowd, just like on their hands and knees worshipping Buddha, but they didn't realize it was a DDR machine.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it's now BBR, Buddha Buddha Revolution.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you rub its belly?
[SPEAKER_05]: I fucked its belly.
[SPEAKER_05]: Side note, he's going to hell.
[SPEAKER_05]: Are you going to hell?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not Philippine, I mean Viet like you.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're all going to hell for laughing.
[SPEAKER_20]: Bye guys!
[SPEAKER_05]: Anything you want to plug?
[SPEAKER_05]: Um...
[SPEAKER_04]: www.bmoneystyle.com, as always, the7.net for my web space, which is almost gone, Killer Pals, I don't know the website because it's too damn long, maple.org, because he has the best blog in the world because he doesn't do anything on it, coryinamerica.com, soon to come, because I triple A'd tears,
[SPEAKER_03]: and B-11 on my second try, which is also my first 9-footer.
[SPEAKER_27]: Did you send those pictures to Aaron?
[SPEAKER_27]: Aaron wouldn't take my B-11 because it wasn't the result screen, fucking cock.
[SPEAKER_27]: The views and opinions dispersed on Orange Line.
[SPEAKER_27]: I... You can address those cards and letters to Virtu, care of the Max 300 King's Palace.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, my address is... Sunnyvale Golf Land.
[SPEAKER_05]: 1984, East El Camino Real, Golf Land 94068.
[SPEAKER_05]: How much time would you say you spend at Sunnyvale Golf Land a week?
[SPEAKER_04]: Since...
[SPEAKER_04]: Extreme came out.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've been there every day practicing for Cyber Beat Nation because I want the fucking controller and I need $400 so I can go to fucking Magic 5 up in Seattle and then go to Midwest Showdown 5 over in Michigan.
[SPEAKER_12]: You're a silly DDR kid.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, you can suck my cock.
[SPEAKER_12]: He is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, I got a bigger cock than you.
[SPEAKER_05]: And on that note, any final... I'm not going to respond to that because we all know that I have the bigger one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, Milton?
[SPEAKER_27]: I'll...
[SPEAKER_27]: to be settled on a future episode any final thoughts for the listeners?
[SPEAKER_27]: write down the chat where everyone's going dot dot dot dot dot dot dot dot dot dot dot dot dot oh my god, the imagery, the imagery alright, right now I'm picturing fucking Twin saying like, what the fuck and then there's fucking I'm gonna beep that name out because we don't talk about that you're gonna beep Twin out?
[SPEAKER_27]: yeah, we're gonna beep that name out what?
[SPEAKER_03]: you can't talk about retards on your show?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, okay, I guess we can make a decision.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just because you're Vertu.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yes, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_19]: By the way, I encourage leaving that intact.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yes, so thanks to Jamie, we didn't beep it.
[SPEAKER_27]: Jamie convinced me that we shouldn't beep it.
[SPEAKER_27]: You're welcome, Corey.
[SPEAKER_27]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_27]: Moving right along.
[SPEAKER_27]: I'm going to be honest with you, your channel is almost as bad as DDR Maniac.
[SPEAKER_27]: Why is that?
[SPEAKER_27]: Because it's filled with twin.
[SPEAKER_27]: Not anymore, we banned his ass like a month ago.
[SPEAKER_27]: That's how long I've been gone because Twin's been.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jesus Christ.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello, welcome to 5 Minutes Ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, any final thoughts?
[SPEAKER_04]: See you guys at CeraVeat Nation.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm expecting another interview at CeraVeat Nation.
[SPEAKER_26]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_27]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_27]: How much if I bribe you will I get an interview?
[SPEAKER_27]: Maybe if I get to play that controller that you win.
[SPEAKER_21]: We're just listening to Virtue.
[SPEAKER_21]: We want to hear some Kyle Snyder.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it's all about me.
[SPEAKER_27]: I mean Snyder.
[SPEAKER_27]: Why don't we interview this fellow over here?
[SPEAKER_27]: Actually, before we interview that fellow over there, Jamie wanted to read something for all you folks.
[SPEAKER_19]: This is an email sent by Twin bragging about all the channels he's been banned from.
[SPEAKER_26]: Actually, this was an email sent by Twen because I told him to fuck off for trying to start shit last week.
[SPEAKER_18]: And the dumbass, he emailed me back and was like, Oh, please, please, please, can you send me the arcade disc for DDR Extreme?
[SPEAKER_26]: Like, I'm going to say, Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_26]: I'll just totally forget that.
[SPEAKER_26]: But instead, he's like,
[SPEAKER_26]: Hey Loki, this is the only other way I know how to get in contact with you.
[SPEAKER_26]: He sent me an email through my website because there's a form.
[SPEAKER_26]: Since I'm banned from DDR Mania X, It Music, Bomani Style, DDR UK, and Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_26]: Congratulations!
[SPEAKER_19]: Congratulations, you suck.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, moving right along with the interviews.
[SPEAKER_27]: Let's interview this fellow.
[SPEAKER_27]: I'll be right back.
[SPEAKER_27]: BRB.
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay, in the meantime...
[SPEAKER_27]: How are you, gentlemen?
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_27]: Introduce yourself for our listeners.
[SPEAKER_27]: You don't even know what the hell you're getting into.
[SPEAKER_27]: This part sucks because this guy didn't want to be interviewed, so just bear with us.
[SPEAKER_27]: You don't have anything you want to say?
[SPEAKER_27]: No.
[SPEAKER_27]: All right.
[SPEAKER_27]: I cry.
[SPEAKER_27]: All right, we'll be... That's what I wanted to say.
[SPEAKER_27]: Hi, guys.
[SPEAKER_27]: All right, we'll come back whenever Virtue gets back here with his surprise.
[SPEAKER_27]: Wait, you have an idea?
[SPEAKER_27]: We're still rolling.
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_27]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_27]: I'm just going to let Virtue do this interview.
[SPEAKER_27]: Why, thank you.
[SPEAKER_27]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Would you like to hold my stuff?
[SPEAKER_27]: Yes, I will hold your stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: It gleams with sex.
[SPEAKER_27]: You have Melody's camera.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have my camera.
[SPEAKER_05]: I had it before me.
[SPEAKER_05]: I had it before her.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, so what's your name?
[SPEAKER_13]: Alex.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alex, what's your... Mr. Cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mr. Cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mr. Cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: And what's it supposed to mean?
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, I got it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a nickname.
[SPEAKER_08]: During class one day, we were talking about rappers.
[SPEAKER_08]: I said something about mystical.
[SPEAKER_08]: One of my friends misunderstood me for Mr. Cool, so that's pretty much how I got the name.
[SPEAKER_27]: That's funny that happened in school, because, like, be cool, stay in school.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_27]: Did you stay in school?
[SPEAKER_27]: I didn't stay in college, but, you know, I'm not a role model, so it's okay.
[SPEAKER_27]: You're not cool.
[SPEAKER_27]: I know.
[SPEAKER_27]: I drink and smoke crack.
[SPEAKER_27]: But anyway, I'm sorry, I'm not being interviewed.
[SPEAKER_04]: He oozes sex as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, what are you doing today at the tournament?
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you running PA, freestyle?
[SPEAKER_04]: Freestyle.
[SPEAKER_08]: Improv freestyle, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's the motive you're going with?
[SPEAKER_04]: Mode?
[SPEAKER_12]: Motive.
[SPEAKER_08]: Any theme?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I'm just... No.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm just hoping I have a fast sign, just like do whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you plan to do hand drops and hand plants and knee drops?
No.
[SPEAKER_08]: What was that?
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: Are you praying for Dynamite Rave?
[SPEAKER_08]: Definitely.
[SPEAKER_08]: As long as I get that song, if not, I'll argue.
[SPEAKER_08]: Can we see a bar hop in your routine?
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, we can't see any bar hops?
[SPEAKER_08]: I think I'll get disqualified.
[SPEAKER_08]: The bar is your friend.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like the bar.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jump over the bar.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you have any final words for the listeners?
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay, that's you.
[SPEAKER_27]: I'm better than you.
[SPEAKER_27]: Peace out.
[SPEAKER_27]: Hey, alright, the tournament's over now, but I got one more interview tonight.
[SPEAKER_27]: Because I missed him at Fremont.
[SPEAKER_27]: I promised to interview this guy at Fremont, and I completely forgot because I'm an asshole.
[SPEAKER_27]: But, here he is.
[SPEAKER_27]: Introduce yourself for our listening audience.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm Ben, aka Chubbs, and that's all I got to say about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_27]: I'm not bad, I guess.
[SPEAKER_27]: What brought you to the Milpitas tournament tonight?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I was judging, so if I didn't come, I think Milton would be angry with me.
[SPEAKER_27]: Sounds pretty reasonable.
[SPEAKER_27]: So what kinds of things were you looking for tonight in the improv routines?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, my specific category as a judge was looking for their charisma.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that was the only thing I was judging on.
[SPEAKER_27]: What were some of the good qualities that you saw tonight, the better charismatic things that you saw tonight?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, Lil B was facing the crowd pretty much the whole time, and that was pretty good for Charisma, and he looked like he was having a pretty good time too.
[SPEAKER_04]: JC also, like those two in my book were pretty close.
[SPEAKER_04]: Those are probably the only good ones.
[SPEAKER_27]: What do you think about judging improv versus judging routines?
[SPEAKER_04]: Judging routines is probably easier because there's not just one specific thing you judge.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just judging the whole routine.
[SPEAKER_27]: At least when you see a bad one, it's not so painful when it's improv, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, because they have an excuse.
[SPEAKER_27]: Right on.
[SPEAKER_27]: So what other kinds of events are you going to be attending in the near future?
[SPEAKER_27]: Anything you want to plug, or I don't know?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just going to go to pretty much every tournament in the future.
[SPEAKER_04]: Back to basic, CBN, and I don't know what's after that.
[SPEAKER_27]: How'd you do in Perfect Attack?
[SPEAKER_27]: Did you do Perfect Attack today?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I got third.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not too shabby.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kind of.
[SPEAKER_04]: See, Milton fucked up, and he forgot to have the third place match between me and Chaos.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, yeah, we're splitting third.
[SPEAKER_27]: That's all good.
[SPEAKER_27]: It works.
[SPEAKER_27]: So, any other final thoughts you have for the folks out there listening?
[SPEAKER_27]: No.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, that works.
[SPEAKER_27]: I think we're all tired as hell and it's time to go home.
[SPEAKER_27]: So, that's it.
[SPEAKER_27]: Milpitas Golf Land, we're out, bye
[SPEAKER_27]: Don't forget, Lovefist are in town right now.
[SPEAKER_27]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_27]: Lovefist is in town.
[SPEAKER_27]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_27]: I flunk school because I'm hardcore.
[SPEAKER_27]: What?
[SPEAKER_27]: I've never even said that shit in my life.
[SPEAKER_27]: What is... Is it from Vice City?
[SPEAKER_27]: And that guy supposedly sounds like me or something?
[SPEAKER_27]: Somebody was telling me the other day that I sound like some guy in Vice City.
[SPEAKER_19]: Rob's famous.
[SPEAKER_27]: That's scary.
[SPEAKER_27]: I'm famous.
[SPEAKER_19]: Infamous.
[SPEAKER_27]: That is me, dammit!
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah, right.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay, yes.
[SPEAKER_27]: We're going to take a break.
[SPEAKER_27]: When we come back, we're going to do a list list.
[SPEAKER_27]: And that means you all get to participate.
[SPEAKER_27]: And you're going to vote.
[SPEAKER_27]: So here's a hint, you guys.
[SPEAKER_27]: During the break, you're going to get a big hint as to what our listless topic is tonight.
[SPEAKER_27]: Enjoy.
[SPEAKER_27]: I'm supposed to say hi to Strong Brad and apologizing for not interviewing him at Miggle.
[SPEAKER_27]: We'll get him next time.
[SPEAKER_27]: The next interviews, by the way, will be at Cyber Beat Nation in a couple weeks.
[SPEAKER_27]: There might even be a whole separate special out of that, like a different aired tape thing.
[SPEAKER_27]: I'm not sure yet.
[SPEAKER_27]: We have to talk about that, all the hosts.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway, I do not sound like Cookie from You Don't Know Jack.
[SPEAKER_27]: Fuck off.
[SPEAKER_27]: Shut up!
[SPEAKER_27]: All of you, shut up!
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, we'll be back.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, do it all night.
[SPEAKER_16]: Do it with me.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'll take you to heaven if you make me feel free, babe.
[SPEAKER_16]: Do it tonight.
[SPEAKER_16]: Do it alright.
[SPEAKER_16]: Just take me and shake me till I burn up inside.
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_16]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_01]: Easier to dance to than that freaking catch-up song, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_27]: Hello kids, welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_27]: I missed an FU that came in over email.
[SPEAKER_27]: What happened is I'd actually read it before the show and then forgot to get back to it when the show was going on.
[SPEAKER_27]: So fuck me for missing it.
[SPEAKER_27]: I'm sorry, sorry.
[SPEAKER_27]: And it's from DDR Angel, who's a huge supporter of this show, and I feel bad because I missed it.
[SPEAKER_27]: So let's get to her FU.
[SPEAKER_27]: FU!
[SPEAKER_27]: HerFU is, fuck you to my graveyard shift co-worker who didn't bother to call me once last night to tell me he was going to be late to begin with.
[SPEAKER_27]: Fuck you to parents for not understanding your children even though you think you do, you're not us, haha.
[SPEAKER_27]: And finally a nice fuck you to earthquakes that have been pestering us all day long.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, so, my bad, I missed that earlier in the show.
[SPEAKER_27]: Please accept my apology!
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, um...
[SPEAKER_27]: And does anybody know the final results from MGL?
[SPEAKER_27]: Good question.
[SPEAKER_27]: First place in Perfect Attack was Tigger, second was Virtue, and third was Chubs and Chaos, I believe, tied.
[SPEAKER_27]: I hope I didn't fuck that up.
[SPEAKER_27]: Freestyle, Improv Freestyle, first was JC, I believe his name was.
[SPEAKER_27]: Second place was, oh, I can look it up on DDR Freak, that's a good idea.
[SPEAKER_27]: I know second place was Lil B, third place, third place was somebody else, I don't remember who third place was, let me look.
[SPEAKER_27]: I know Oki, Oki was in fourth, oh, I think, yes, yes, because Fuzzy Cat won money, he was excited he won money.
[SPEAKER_27]: Fuzzy Cat was third, you're right, thank you.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, thank you, you guys, uh, hey, and even, one of the judges is in the chat room, I'm so retarded, I didn't even think to ask, but she's, Jenny Bean does confirm that yes, hello by the way, Jenny, uh, JC, Lil B, and Fuzzy, one, two, and three, right there.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright, now we get to our favorite part of the show.
[SPEAKER_27]: Uh, Angel also says fuck you to her head cold.
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, my second favorite part of the show, actually my favorite part of the show is the fuck you to the weak, but, our other favorite part of the show.
Yay!
[SPEAKER_27]: Yay, it's the listless, and tonight, the topic, it's the listless.
[SPEAKER_19]: You should do a theme song.
[SPEAKER_19]: No.
[SPEAKER_27]: Sing us a theme song.
[SPEAKER_27]: It's a listless shame.
[SPEAKER_27]: You're on a roll there.
[SPEAKER_26]: We'll get... We'll get... Everybody... That's what the fucking song is.
[SPEAKER_27]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_27]: We're gonna get...
[SPEAKER_27]: No, this is not dancer.
[SPEAKER_27]: I'm blowing out people's speakers.
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, where were we?
[SPEAKER_27]: Yes, list list.
[SPEAKER_27]: Tonight's list list.
[SPEAKER_27]: Title or song that erotic needs to do.
[SPEAKER_27]: A possible title for a new erotic song.
[SPEAKER_19]: This is actually coming from my fuck off show from Tuesday, was it?
[SPEAKER_19]: Where we were like coming up with erotic song titles in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_19]: Which I'm actually doing one of them on my list.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, so these are all songs that Erotic hasn't done, but they should.
[SPEAKER_27]: So, starting off, we've got, who's all participating in the room?
[SPEAKER_27]: Raise your hands so I make sure I don't miss everyone.
[SPEAKER_27]: One, two, three, four, five, six, okay, we've got six people participating, so we've got quite a few.
[SPEAKER_19]: Ryan is reading for Ryan.
[SPEAKER_23]: I'm reading for someone else, so these aren't mine.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, and then we have the other Ryan, we have Puppy Ryan.
[SPEAKER_27]: You're not, you aren't Ryan, you're Puppy.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, who's starting?
[SPEAKER_19]: Me!
[SPEAKER_27]: All right, Jamie, your number three pick for an erotic song.
[SPEAKER_19]: Watching my ex have hot man sex.
[SPEAKER_27]: Watching my ex have hot man sex.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's definitely erotic style.
[SPEAKER_27]: All right.
[SPEAKER_27]: Watching my ex have hot man sex.
[SPEAKER_27]: Can you sing a bar from that?
[SPEAKER_27]: I'm watching my ex have hot man sex.
Okay.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, now Ryan is reading for Ryan.
[SPEAKER_27]: These aren't his picks, but they're the other Ryan's.
[SPEAKER_19]: We were singing that to the tune of Love on the Phone.
[SPEAKER_27]: You're right, I was.
[SPEAKER_23]: Alright, I have no idea which order this is in.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, we'll just pick one that's number three.
[SPEAKER_23]: Okay, Loose Like a Rubber Band.
[SPEAKER_27]: Loose Like a Rubber Band.
[SPEAKER_27]: Can you sing us a bar from Loose Like a Rubber Band?
[SPEAKER_23]: It's not mine.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, number three erotic song title.
[SPEAKER_26]: I have to give credit to Brad for this one, but...
[SPEAKER_26]: Gimme E and I'll make out with everyone.
[SPEAKER_27]: Brad, could you sing us a bar from Gimme E and I'll make out with everyone?
[SPEAKER_25]: Just play Sandstorm, okay?
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_27]: Puppey, your number three pick.
[SPEAKER_27]: Use the back door!
[SPEAKER_27]: Jonas, your number three pick.
[SPEAKER_27]: In Between My Legs.
[SPEAKER_27]: It's almost like underneath my clothes.
[SPEAKER_07]: In Between My Legs.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's my hand.
[SPEAKER_27]: There's a scary forest in between my legs.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, the dark black forest.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, my number three.
[SPEAKER_27]: My number three pick for a possible erotic song title, Passion Gerbil.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay, my number two.
[SPEAKER_27]: Here's your number two, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_19]: Is the Kiss Me reprise, Eat Me, Beat Me.
[SPEAKER_27]: Can you sing us a bar of Eat Me, Beat Me?
[SPEAKER_19]: To the tune of Kiss Me because it's the reprise.
[SPEAKER_27]: Eat me, beat me.
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, alright.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_27]: Ryan, reading for Ryan.
[SPEAKER_23]: Okay, um, D2O2SuckCock, featuring Naoki.
[SPEAKER_23]: D2O2SuckCock?
[SPEAKER_23]: D2O2SuckCock.
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh!
[SPEAKER_23]: O2O2SuckCock, I get it.
[SPEAKER_19]: And it's featuring Naoki.
[SPEAKER_27]: Featuring Naoki, sorry.
[SPEAKER_27]: Wouldn't that be featuring PoliTerry?
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, Erotic hasn't done anything with Naoki that we know of.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah, Erotic's never done anything with Naoki, but they could.
[SPEAKER_27]: But they could.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_27]: Loki, you're number two pick.
[SPEAKER_26]: The question is, would she be talking about him?
[SPEAKER_26]: I mean, is he too old to suck?
[SPEAKER_26]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_27]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_26]: Alright, um...
[SPEAKER_26]: This one's called Taking It From Mr. Ed, and in parentheses, Hungry For Horse Cock.
[SPEAKER_27]: Was that on Derby Owners Club?
[SPEAKER_27]: DCB reminds me of a quote from yesterday, because I named one of my horses Politary.
[SPEAKER_27]: Politary needs new bedding!
[SPEAKER_27]: That should have been one of my picks.
[SPEAKER_27]: Puppy, your number two pick.
[SPEAKER_24]: Smells like fish, the pink taco picks.
[SPEAKER_27]: We're so mature on Orange House Radio.
[SPEAKER_27]: Smells Like Fish, the pink taco mix.
[SPEAKER_27]: Jonas, your number two pick.
All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Orgasmic Fantasy, parentheses, for extreme.
[SPEAKER_07]: With three X's.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dead air, dead air, dead air.
[SPEAKER_19]: Dead air ain't much fun.
[SPEAKER_27]: My number two pick.
[SPEAKER_27]: My number two pick for a possibly erotic song title.
[SPEAKER_27]: Temple of Butt.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_13]: My number one?
[SPEAKER_27]: Come into the Temple of Butt.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_27]: Your number one choice.
[SPEAKER_19]: Jacques, don't eat his cock.
[SPEAKER_27]: Jacques, don't eat his cock.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's mine.
[SPEAKER_25]: Jamie's number one pick, Jock, Don't Eat His Cock.
[SPEAKER_25]: I'm going to have to read this one for Ryan because he's not here.
[SPEAKER_25]: Too shy, huh?
[SPEAKER_25]: Just hurry up and shoot it in my eyes so I can get paid for doing this damn porno flick and go home.
[SPEAKER_13]: That was great.
[SPEAKER_27]: I'm shortening that to just hurry up and shoot it in my eyes because that's too long.
[SPEAKER_27]: We got a lot of great, great suggestions in the chatroom.
[SPEAKER_27]: Too many words!
[SPEAKER_27]: That's too many words, too many words.
[SPEAKER_27]: Loki, your number one pick for a possible erotic song title.
[SPEAKER_26]: I'll keep it simple.
[SPEAKER_26]: 100 Midget Gangbang.
[SPEAKER_27]: 100 Midget Gangbang.
[SPEAKER_27]: Could you sing a line from 100 Midget Gangbang?
[SPEAKER_27]: Would that be like the We Are the Lollipop Kids song?
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_25]: Come into the temple of butt.
[SPEAKER_25]: It works, because all erotic songs sound the same anyway.
[SPEAKER_25]: Alright, come on.
[SPEAKER_25]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_27]: Puppy, your number one pick for... Oh, you're rewriting.
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay, Jonas, you're number one.
[SPEAKER_07]: Crouching Cocker, Hidden Pussy.
[SPEAKER_27]: Crouching Cocker, Hidden Pussy.
[SPEAKER_27]: Great, that's beautiful.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_19]: Puppy's still rewriting his.
[SPEAKER_27]: My number one then, while Puppy is rewriting his, The Legend of Cumshot.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was bad.
[SPEAKER_27]: That's my number one.
[SPEAKER_27]: The Legend of Cumshot.
[SPEAKER_27]: All right.
[SPEAKER_27]: Puppy, your number one pick.
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'll regain my composure.
[SPEAKER_27]: The Ladies' Night Eat Out.
[SPEAKER_27]: Ladies' Night Eat Out.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, let's hear some suggestions.
[SPEAKER_27]: Before we erase things from this list, we're going to read some suggestions in the chat room because they have some fucking great ones in here.
[SPEAKER_27]: We've got Fish Tacos Are Our Favorite, XXXPannyShotRateFree, Nocturnal Penile Turcescence, Al Don't Fuck Your Pal, She Winked Her Sphincter, Rock My Cock,
[SPEAKER_27]: So deep in my ass.
[SPEAKER_19]: Rob, two of the ones from the other night when I did my fuck-off show, it was Bruce, I want your juice.
[SPEAKER_19]: And Sam, lick my clam.
[SPEAKER_27]: Sam, lick my clam.
[SPEAKER_27]: I like that one.
[SPEAKER_19]: Should we trade out the don't eat the cock?
[SPEAKER_27]: We'll look in the list in a minute.
[SPEAKER_27]: Be gentle with the placenta.
[SPEAKER_27]: Insertion, boy on boy mix.
[SPEAKER_13]: I like that one.
[SPEAKER_27]: Pump it up the poo chute.
[SPEAKER_27]: Flashed in the Night, Ryan You're Not Even Trying, I don't know if that was a song title or just, I don't know, Jake Don't Wank Your Snake, alright, I think that's a, I think I'm actually going to change, there's some good ones, okay, you want to change one of yours, Jamie, yes, I'm going to change Jack Don't Eat His Cock to Sam Lick My Clamp, Sam Lick My Clamp,
[SPEAKER_27]: So, all right, here we go.
[SPEAKER_27]: Here's the list.
[SPEAKER_27]: I'll read it.
[SPEAKER_27]: Here's the list so far.
[SPEAKER_27]: We have a lot because there's six people, but the elimination round's coming up.
[SPEAKER_27]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_27]: Watching my ex have hot man sex, loose like a rubber band, give me E and I'll make out with everyone, use the back door, in between my legs, passion gerbil, eat me, beat me, the kiss me reprise, D2O to suck cock featuring Naoki, taking it from Mr. Ed, the hungry for horse cock,
[SPEAKER_27]: Smells Like Fish, the Pink Taco Mix, Orgasmic Fantasy for Extreme, Temple of Butt, Sam Lick My Clam, Just Hurry Up and Shoot It in My Eye, 100 Midget Gang Bang, Crouching Cocker, Hidden Pussy, The Legend of Cumshot, and Ladies Night Eat Out.
[SPEAKER_27]: All right, here we go.
[SPEAKER_27]: The elimination round.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm going to remove Loose Like a Rubber Band.
[SPEAKER_19]: Loose Like a Rubber Band comes off the list.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's just not very exciting sounding.
[SPEAKER_27]: All right.
[SPEAKER_27]: Wait, wait, we gotta get Ryan.
[SPEAKER_27]: Even since the other Ryan's not in here, Ryan gets to pick one off the list.
[SPEAKER_23]: I'd say get rid of that shoot it in my eye one.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, that's a little long.
[SPEAKER_27]: Just hurry up and shoot it in my eye.
[SPEAKER_26]: It comes off the list.
[SPEAKER_26]: Sadly enough, I'm going to take off the last one of his.
[SPEAKER_26]: D2 old to suck cock.
[SPEAKER_27]: Poor Ryan.
[SPEAKER_26]: There's no age limit for sucking cock.
[SPEAKER_27]: Puppy, what's coming off the list?
[SPEAKER_24]: Well, first of all, I don't think anybody wants to think of Naoki sucking cock, okay?
[SPEAKER_19]: Remember, Naoki's flexible enough to suck his own cock.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't want that image, okay?
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway... Uh, let's see.
[SPEAKER_27]: I can't see the list, you're blocking me.
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_27]: My bad, my bad.
[SPEAKER_27]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_27]: Ah!
[SPEAKER_27]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay, um... Here are the passion gerbils.
[SPEAKER_27]: Passion gerbil!
[SPEAKER_27]: Aw, you suck!
[SPEAKER_27]: Jonas, what's coming off the list?
[SPEAKER_07]: I've got to say, Gimme Ian, I'll Make Out With Everyone.
[SPEAKER_27]: Gimme Ian, I'll Make Out With Everyone.
[SPEAKER_27]: All right, that comes off the list.
[SPEAKER_27]: I'm going to take off... Pants.
[SPEAKER_27]: No.
[SPEAKER_27]: I'm going to take off... The strap-on.
[SPEAKER_27]: This is kind of hard.
[SPEAKER_27]: I'm going to take off Crouching Cocker Hidden Pussy.
[SPEAKER_27]: That's a porno title, not an erotic song title.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_27]: All right.
[SPEAKER_25]: So here's the list.
[SPEAKER_25]: Guys, guys, I heard about this Legend of Cumshot song.
[SPEAKER_25]: You have to double a temple of butt to get it.
It's going to go...
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_27]: You guys can vote now.
[SPEAKER_27]: Send me a private message in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_27]: And Jamie's going to read them this time.
[SPEAKER_19]: Watching my ex have hot man sex.
[SPEAKER_19]: Use the back door in between my legs.
[SPEAKER_19]: Eat me, beat me, the kiss me reprise.
[SPEAKER_19]: Taking it for Mr. Ed, hungry for horse cock.
[SPEAKER_19]: Smells like fish, pink taco mix.
[SPEAKER_19]: Orgasmic fantasy for extreme sex.
[SPEAKER_19]: Temple of Butt, Sam Lick My Clam, 100 Midget Game Bang, The Legend of Cumshot, and Ladies Night Eat Out.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, and I gotta post that again to the chat room, because Chat Cookie, uh, Chat Cookie kicked me for flooding, so I'm gonna de-op it and repost the list, so I don't get, so I don't get, uh, kicked again.
[SPEAKER_27]: So there we go.
[SPEAKER_27]: You can vote now in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_27]: In the meantime, here's some inspiration for you, and we'll be right back.
[SPEAKER_27]: Uh, any other comments for anybody?
[SPEAKER_19]: Um...
[SPEAKER_19]: That's just like the nastiest list ever and I love it.
[SPEAKER_19]: Damn it.
[SPEAKER_27]: Chat Cookie's flipping out.
[SPEAKER_27]: Chat Cookie's being an asshole.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, alright, thank you.
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay, in the meantime, let's see.
[SPEAKER_27]: I said I'd give inspiration.
[SPEAKER_27]: I'm trying to find another erotic song we haven't played yet.
[SPEAKER_27]: Sex on the Phone?
[SPEAKER_27]: I don't even know.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, yes I do.
[SPEAKER_27]: We have Max Don't Have Sex With You.
[SPEAKER_27]: Find something, damn it.
[SPEAKER_27]: I'm finding it, I'm looking, I'm looking, give me a minute.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_27]: We'll be right back after this quick song and we'll reveal the results.
[SPEAKER_27]: So vote now!
[SPEAKER_27]: Vote, damn it.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, last call for votes.
[SPEAKER_27]: Send them in now.
[SPEAKER_27]: In the meantime, we're going to play a remix from Max 2.
[SPEAKER_27]: And hurry it up.
[SPEAKER_27]: Send in the votes.
[SPEAKER_27]: You only got like 10 more seconds.
[SPEAKER_27]: So send it now or never send it.
[SPEAKER_01]: And now it's time for Erotic Pop Idol, where we will find the next singer for everyone's favorite perverse Bomani band, Erotic.
[SPEAKER_16]: Do it all night.
[SPEAKER_16]: Do it with me.
[SPEAKER_16]: No, no, that was awful.
[SPEAKER_10]: Bloody terrible.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do you take vocal lessons?
[SPEAKER_10]: Kill your teacher.
[SPEAKER_10]: In the heat of the night.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, God, I think my ears are bleeding.
[SPEAKER_16]: I liked it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Shut the bloody hell up, Paula.
[SPEAKER_10]: Next.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do you even know why you're here?
[SPEAKER_10]: That was just bloody pathetic!
[SPEAKER_10]: Next!
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, that's it!
[SPEAKER_10]: We have a winner!
[SPEAKER_01]: A Star is Born, here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, we have the results for what has been one of our most popular, I think, I think it's one of our most popular listless segments we've ever done here on this show.
[SPEAKER_27]: It was fun, that's for sure.
[SPEAKER_27]: You remember that adult content disclaimer at the beginning of the show?
[SPEAKER_27]: I hope y'all were listening.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, pay attention.
[SPEAKER_27]: And when I posted about this on the DDR Community Live Journal, I put, you know, warning, there's some adult content on this program if y'all are like 12 years old.
[SPEAKER_27]: Everybody wants to hear, some!
[SPEAKER_27]: Don't you ever talk about DDR on that show?
[SPEAKER_27]: All you ever talk about is porn.
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh yes, the list.
[SPEAKER_27]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_27]: I'm going to give Jamie the distinct pleasure of getting to read these because we all love when a woman is saying these dirty things to us.
[SPEAKER_27]: Number three.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, the number three winner is... I like it in the ass.
[SPEAKER_27]: No, that wasn't one of the choices.
[SPEAKER_27]: Last week on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_19]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_19]: We don't even do this anymore.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_19]: Number three is Temple of Butt.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay, Temple of Butt.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_19]: Number two, 100 Midget Gangbang.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay, 100 Midget Gangbang, yay.
[SPEAKER_19]: And number one is...
[SPEAKER_19]: Sam Lick My Clam.
[SPEAKER_27]: Sam Lick My Clam.
[SPEAKER_27]: Wow, that was a last minute entry too.
[SPEAKER_19]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_27]: What?
[SPEAKER_19]: It's all three of us.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's the host circle.
[SPEAKER_27]: Ah, that's true.
[SPEAKER_19]: With of course me being number one because I'm the best.
[SPEAKER_19]: And you all love me and worship me like the goddess I am.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yay, okay, so Sam Lick My Clam is where I still like Temple of Bud.
[SPEAKER_19]: See, Brad's bowing down to me.
[SPEAKER_19]: I still like watching my ex have hot man sex.
[SPEAKER_27]: That was a good one.
[SPEAKER_27]: That was very close.
[SPEAKER_27]: It was very close.
[SPEAKER_27]: That was almost in there.
[SPEAKER_27]: Brad, can you sing us Temple of But one more time?
[SPEAKER_27]: What?
[SPEAKER_24]: The Temple of Butt.
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_27]: Coming to the Temple of Butt.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, anyway.
[SPEAKER_19]: I was thinking it's the Winnie the Pootie.
[SPEAKER_27]: We still have a cage match.
[SPEAKER_27]: We still have a cage match to do.
[SPEAKER_19]: Temple of Butt.
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay, we want to do this?
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_27]: Loki, talk about this.
[SPEAKER_10]: Pootie, pootie, pootie, pootie, pootie, pootie.
[SPEAKER_10]: Temple of Butt.
[SPEAKER_10]: Pootie, pootie, pootie, pootie, pootie.
[SPEAKER_27]: Guys are weird.
[SPEAKER_27]: Suddenly I'm in preschool again, and we're all, everybody's sitting here going, poopy, pooky, caw, caw, caw, ha, ha, ha.
[SPEAKER_27]: I popped back out again.
[SPEAKER_27]: I still think this DNL thing is like the weirdest thing I've ever seen, that upside down seven.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm so fucking hyper right now because of the goddamn balls.
[SPEAKER_25]: Jamie's high on balls.
[SPEAKER_19]: No, I've been cutting back on all my caffeine and sugar.
[SPEAKER_19]: and Ellen Piper.
[SPEAKER_26]: Okay, this is a remix I did.
[SPEAKER_26]: I worked on it most of today.
[SPEAKER_26]: The end is fucked up because it's not finished yet and I had to hurry to get it done so you'll notice that the rest of the song sounds cool in the end.
[SPEAKER_26]: You're like, huh?
[SPEAKER_26]: So this is a sort of trance remix of Legend of Max
[SPEAKER_27]: Now, why did you do this?
[SPEAKER_27]: Just for the hell of it?
[SPEAKER_27]: Or did you do it for that little contest that's going on on MyStyle?
[SPEAKER_26]: Or what's this about?
[SPEAKER_26]: I didn't know.
[SPEAKER_26]: I did it because I found the song that they got the vocals out of for Legend of Max, and that's the whole reason why.
[SPEAKER_26]: And I was like, woo!
[SPEAKER_26]: Vocals!
[SPEAKER_27]: So, are you going to enter this?
[SPEAKER_27]: You should enter this in the 2DX remixing contest.
[SPEAKER_27]: I know Legend of Max isn't a 2DX song yet, but, you know.
[SPEAKER_26]: You could call it a Max 300 mix, probably.
[SPEAKER_26]: For one, they canceled that contest.
[SPEAKER_26]: What?! !
[SPEAKER_26]: Hey, can you make me a trance mix of something?
[SPEAKER_27]: Make me a trance mix too!
[SPEAKER_27]: Come on, I want a trance mix!
[SPEAKER_27]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_27]: I want someone to make me a trance mix of the Safari.
[SPEAKER_27]: We want to hear what you guys think about this in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_27]: So post your thoughts.
[SPEAKER_27]: You all can be a judge on American Idol right now and judge Loki.
[SPEAKER_27]: Won't this be fabulous?
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay, this is Legend of Trance here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_19]: That was cool.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, let's pretend it was a cage match song.
[SPEAKER_27]: Let's go around the room.
[SPEAKER_27]: Everybody give your thoughts and give it on a scale of 1 to 10.
40.
[SPEAKER_25]: I'm wet right now.
[SPEAKER_25]: Yeah, I'm going to give you 100.
[SPEAKER_23]: Change your pants.
[SPEAKER_23]: Already off the scale, but I'll give it a 9.
[SPEAKER_26]: Since it's my song, the end still needs work, especially that one, the second slowdown there where it says the death, and then the fly, I need to really work on that from there on, that needs work, but yeah, I like it, it's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, let's just say it's off the scale, this one kicks hella ass, I can't really give it a number, because it's over 10 or over... Just to say, do be continued on the numbers scale.
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay, AAA then.
[SPEAKER_27]: You know, to be honest, it didn't sound a lot remixed, but like enough, so that like, you know, the paranoias aren't really remixed that much either.
[SPEAKER_27]: So, I think that fits into DDR very well.
[SPEAKER_07]: Compared to most of the damn mechs I've heard online.
[SPEAKER_26]: Actually, to be honest, I thought it was like hardly any Macs in there.
[SPEAKER_26]: I don't know, I just kind of heard the melody.
[SPEAKER_26]: Most of the stuff's off of TransAddict.com.
[SPEAKER_26]: I believe the song I used was called I'm Alone or something like that.
[SPEAKER_26]: That was for most of it.
[SPEAKER_26]: Then there's another song called, by the Deep Project, that's called The Fly, which is where they got most of the... Really?
[SPEAKER_26]: I've got the MP3 on there.
[SPEAKER_26]: It's like nine minutes long, but that's where they got the samples for that, unless that's a royalty-free sample that...
[SPEAKER_26]: Hey, I'll buy you dinner if you make me, like, an Ambia Trance remix of the Safari We'll see Safari kicks ass Anyway We'll see, okay, shit Dinner
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, speaking of the cage match, I think we ought to get to this week's version of it, shouldn't we?
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, so, let's get into that.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yes, so, I'm finding the cage match theme music here.
[SPEAKER_27]: Somebody requested it earlier in the show, we specifically not play.
[SPEAKER_27]: What are you taking that out for?
[SPEAKER_27]: We need that, don't we?
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, mine's on there, but yours is on here.
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_27]: We'll do yours first, Loki.
[SPEAKER_27]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay, put yours in.
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay, never mind.
[SPEAKER_27]: We know what we're doing.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway, yes, last week.
[SPEAKER_27]: Last week on the Orange Lounge Cage Match.
[SPEAKER_19]: Repriced from last week, KK Cockmaster.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, wait, wrong week.
[SPEAKER_27]: We had, the winner was, Jamie brought in a Vincent D'Amour song, and it pretty much swept the floor.
[SPEAKER_27]: and it won, so we'll play a little clip of that.
[SPEAKER_27]: The way the cage match works, by the way, since I know we have a lot of new listeners tonight, each host brings in one song and we pick them all against each other.
[SPEAKER_27]: And so we have the winning song from last week and then two new ones that go head-to-head.
[SPEAKER_27]: The winning song goes into rotation on the Orange Lounge Radio's Bomani Music & More program, always on this station when we're not here, live.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_27]: Head to Head.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yes, that's what I said.
[SPEAKER_27]: I said Head to Head.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway, last week, this was the winner.
[SPEAKER_27]: So this is the first song you can vote for in this week's Cage Max.
[SPEAKER_27]: We're just going to play a clip because the winner only gets a clip played of it.
[SPEAKER_27]: This is Vincent Damore with Eternity from last week here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_27]: And now...
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, that was last week's winner.
[SPEAKER_27]: That was Vincent Damore with Eternity, last week's winner.
[SPEAKER_19]: I just had a happy moment with that song.
[SPEAKER_27]: Already the chatroom is kind of slamming on Eternity.
[SPEAKER_27]: They don't know if they care for it anymore.
[SPEAKER_27]: I think they're done with it.
[SPEAKER_27]: So let's bring on the challengers.
[SPEAKER_27]: I don't know, Jamie looks concerned.
[SPEAKER_27]: She's giving the chatroom the finger.
[SPEAKER_26]: Alright, well let's see.
[SPEAKER_26]: I would have to say that this song falls on a completely opposite scale of that song.
[SPEAKER_26]: This is going to be, once again, the Secretions, a local Sacramento punk band, with their song, I'm Gonna Get You So Laid.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, so this is the next entry you can vote for.
[SPEAKER_27]: This is a very short, DDR-sized song, but if you want to vote for it, do it.
[SPEAKER_27]: This is the second pick in the Orange Lounge Cage Match.
[SPEAKER_27]: This is the Secretions with I'm Gonna Get You So Laid.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_11]: Take it to the money shop, boys!
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you very much for coming tonight.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, that was the secretions with I'm Gonna Get You So Laid.
[SPEAKER_27]: Let's go around the room and see what everyone thought of that.
[SPEAKER_27]: Jamie?
[SPEAKER_11]: We're talking about pain.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway, the secretions.
[SPEAKER_27]: What about the cage match pick?
[SPEAKER_19]: Um, cool.
[SPEAKER_19]: Um, seven.
[SPEAKER_27]: Seven.
[SPEAKER_27]: What'd you think of that, Zero?
[SPEAKER_23]: Um, since I've heard that song before and I enjoyed it, I'll say an eight.
[SPEAKER_23]: An eight.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, Loki?
[SPEAKER_26]: I'll give it a nine, but I know a lot of the chat room doesn't listen to punks, so they won't appreciate it as much as I do.
[SPEAKER_27]: Well, gee, aren't we elitists when it comes to music?
[SPEAKER_26]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_27]: All right, and Jonas, your pick.
7.5.
[SPEAKER_27]: 7.5.
[SPEAKER_27]: I'm going to give it a 5.
[SPEAKER_27]: I've heard better punk.
[SPEAKER_27]: It was all right, but Little Bitch is better for DDR, but Pain is better than that.
[SPEAKER_27]: It was alright.
[SPEAKER_27]: If I was at a concert, I'd want to punch somebody to that song, so that's cool.
[SPEAKER_27]: But it's not for Orange Lounge, though.
[SPEAKER_27]: It ain't for Orange Lounge, I don't think.
[SPEAKER_27]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, so that's your other pick.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_27]: We have Vincent Noir with Eternity, The Supretions, and I'm Gonna Get You So Late.
[SPEAKER_27]: And here's the third pick.
[SPEAKER_27]: And I don't have an artist for this one.
[SPEAKER_27]: I'm trying to get that this week.
[SPEAKER_27]: But this was actually given to me by our buddy Tal, who was here earlier in the show.
[SPEAKER_27]: He had this posted on his website.
[SPEAKER_27]: This is a song called The Terrible Mr. Grimshaw.
[SPEAKER_27]: And what this is, this is...
[SPEAKER_27]: They recorded some guy playing Counter-Strike or Half-Life or one of those life-killing games.
[SPEAKER_27]: And they taped this guy playing it and swearing, and then they did a techno remix of it, and it kicks ass.
[SPEAKER_27]: So you guys have to hear this.
[SPEAKER_27]: This is my pick for the cage match this week.
[SPEAKER_27]: This is the terrible Mr. Grimshaw here on Orange Lounge Radio.
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: Goddammit!
[SPEAKER_09]: Fuck!
[SPEAKER_09]: Motherfuck!
[SPEAKER_09]: Goddamn!
[SPEAKER_09]: Don't shoot at me!
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, come on!
[SPEAKER_09]: I hate that!
[SPEAKER_09]: Did I even get anyone?
[SPEAKER_09]: Did I ever fucking kill anyone?
[SPEAKER_09]: Dude, what the fuck?
[SPEAKER_09]: How did I get fucking shot?
[SPEAKER_09]: Just quit shooting me the fucking fucking assholes, dude.
[SPEAKER_09]: What the fuck happened?
[SPEAKER_09]: Bullshit.
[SPEAKER_09]: I fucking shot you like 50 fucking times!
[SPEAKER_09]: Fuck!
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, my head!
[SPEAKER_09]: Shit!
[SPEAKER_09]: Fuck!
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, I'm not fucking playing with any of you.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, that was, I'm being told the name of the group.
[SPEAKER_27]: Ooh, that's too loud.
[SPEAKER_27]: Hi, I'm back.
[SPEAKER_27]: The name of the group is the Murder Simulators, and that was the terrible Mr. Grimshaw.
[SPEAKER_27]: Jamie already expressed her disgust for this song, but let's hear it.
[SPEAKER_19]: If it had a good background music, I would give it a higher score.
[SPEAKER_19]: If it was insecure, I would give it a higher score.
[SPEAKER_19]: But I hear that all the time, just hanging out with Dan.
[SPEAKER_19]: And hearing him talk shit on MechaSold on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_19]: So I give that a 2.
[SPEAKER_19]: You give it a 2.
[SPEAKER_19]: Because at least parts of it weren't keyed.
[SPEAKER_23]: Alright, 0.
[SPEAKER_23]: I don't know, I've played quite a bit of Half-Life and Counter-Strike, so I can understand the guy's frustration.
[SPEAKER_23]: So I'd say I'd give that a 6.5, purely by his frustration.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yeah, lead it, honky!
[SPEAKER_26]: Love that line.
[SPEAKER_26]: I'll give it like a 6 because it didn't even really, it doesn't look like they paid, they just were trying to put his samples in there just to make it like a song, but they didn't really pay much attention to the actual background music, so it's like, I don't know, 6, yeah.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, Jonas, what'd you think?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll give it like a 4.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, first of all, there's really not much to the song at all.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want to make a band and call it Slagwork.
[SPEAKER_19]: If I started doing mixes, I would just go as flag one.
[SPEAKER_27]: Vote now for the Orange Lounge Cage Match winner.
[SPEAKER_27]: Here's your choices.
[SPEAKER_27]: Last week's winner, Vincent Damore with Eternity.
[SPEAKER_27]: The secretions with I'm Gonna Get You So Late.
[SPEAKER_27]: And it's queuing up right now.
[SPEAKER_27]: La la la.
[SPEAKER_27]: Hurry up.
[SPEAKER_27]: Dammit.
[SPEAKER_27]: Shit.
[SPEAKER_27]: Fuck.
[SPEAKER_27]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_26]: Oh shit.
[SPEAKER_27]: I can sing it.
[SPEAKER_26]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that song just broke Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_27]: Don't!
[SPEAKER_27]: Fuck.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_27]: So... Boy, we're kind of screwed here.
[SPEAKER_27]: Hold on just one sec.
[SPEAKER_27]: I didn't do it!
[SPEAKER_27]: Someone fill time here.
[SPEAKER_26]: It wasn't me.
[SPEAKER_27]: All right, so did Winamp close?
[SPEAKER_27]: Hurry up.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, shit.
[SPEAKER_27]: All right, hold on.
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay, we're not going to be able to play a... Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_27]: Did the whole computer just freeze up there?
[SPEAKER_27]: Shit.
[SPEAKER_27]: Loki, you broke Orange Lounge!
[SPEAKER_27]: Here, pop the CDF.
[SPEAKER_27]: This is bad.
[SPEAKER_27]: This is fucked up.
[SPEAKER_26]: Dude, move.
[SPEAKER_26]: And let me pop the fucking CD out.
[SPEAKER_26]: Where is it?
[SPEAKER_26]: Right there.
[SPEAKER_26]: Top one.
[SPEAKER_27]: Top one.
[SPEAKER_27]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_27]: We got technical issues.
[SPEAKER_19]: We're sorry.
[SPEAKER_19]: This broadcast of Orange Challenge Radio just got fucked up by Loki.
[SPEAKER_19]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_27]: All right, there, finally, it's out.
[SPEAKER_19]: The media has escaped.
[SPEAKER_19]: Loki pulled it out, hooray.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yay, we're fixed.
[SPEAKER_27]: All right, so you can vote for the song that broke Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_19]: We can now no longer breathe.
[SPEAKER_27]: Or you can vote for, and now I, damn it, now, okay, or you can vote for the song with the swearing, The Terrible Mr. Grinchon.
[SPEAKER_27]: You don't get to hear a clip of that either because I'm lazy.
[SPEAKER_27]: I can hear mine, though.
[SPEAKER_27]: Fuck, shit, cock!
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, so vote now, send those over private message to me, I'm Sky in the chatroom.
[SPEAKER_27]: And if you're not in the chatroom, get your ass in there right now, orangelounge.skie.cx Alright, so, moving right along.
[SPEAKER_27]: What do you guys want to talk about now?
[SPEAKER_27]: There's a half hour left to show here.
[SPEAKER_19]: I like liquor.
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay, wait a minute, what?
[SPEAKER_24]: I just started myself a little character in Jamie's Animal Crossing Town, and I can't get Irene to get off so I can play.
[SPEAKER_27]: Go in there and tell her it's your goddamn turn, and that she plays it every time she's over here, and it's your turn, because you only get to be here like once every month, so... Yeah.
[SPEAKER_27]: Ha.
[SPEAKER_27]: Go lay the smack down, puppy.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_27]: Show him your bark.
[SPEAKER_27]: Irene needs to be on the show.
[SPEAKER_10]: Take it.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah, we need more female input on this show.
[SPEAKER_27]: Hey!
[SPEAKER_27]: Jamie has to make up for everybody.
[SPEAKER_19]: I have tit power.
[SPEAKER_27]: I can pick a few females.
[SPEAKER_27]: Let's have an all-female Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_27]: Loki and I will leave town for the weekend.
We already did that.
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, yeah, we did that.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_19]: But Ross was there.
[SPEAKER_19]: It was me and Jessica, but we had Ross and Dan.
[SPEAKER_19]: Hey everybody, do you want Dan to be on the show again?
[SPEAKER_19]: Samir Boots.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_19]: You know Dan's going to be on there when we do the show at my house.
[SPEAKER_13]: Buy my parrot hang gliders.
[SPEAKER_26]: Oh, oh, oh, I know what I want to talk about.
[SPEAKER_26]: This weird email I got.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay, now... Okay, you people fucking have no taste.
[SPEAKER_19]: My God.
[SPEAKER_26]: Okay, whoever you were, you have taste.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_19]: Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck
[SPEAKER_26]: Sorry, that's the twin mail.
[SPEAKER_26]: No, twin mail.
[SPEAKER_26]: Okay, here goes.
[SPEAKER_26]: Dear friend, I know this email will reach you as a surprise, but need not to worry, as we are using the only secured and confidential medium available to seek foreign assistance.
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah, secure and confidential yet is going to someone else, and I got the email, supposedly.
[SPEAKER_19]: Matt, why is your butt in my face?
[SPEAKER_26]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_26]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_26]: So, following the sudden death of my husband, General Sonny Bacha, the late former head of State United... Give us a Cliff Notes version.
[SPEAKER_26]: Okay, some guy died.
[SPEAKER_26]: I want you to move my funds into the United States.
[SPEAKER_18]: You made me snort my Propel.
[SPEAKER_26]: I'll give you $21.5 million for doing that.
[SPEAKER_26]: And all you have to do is send me your full name, your company name and address, and phone numbers and fax numbers.
[SPEAKER_26]: And you're sold.
[SPEAKER_26]: To my lawyer.
[SPEAKER_19]: And a big black cock.
[SPEAKER_26]: So that was the dumb email they got.
[SPEAKER_26]: I thought it was all special and stuff, but then other people got the same email, so I guess not.
[SPEAKER_26]: But yeah.
[SPEAKER_26]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_26]: That's all.
[SPEAKER_26]: Pretty stupid.
[SPEAKER_27]: Spam sucks.
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, that's what I was going to give an F you to this week and I forgot.
[SPEAKER_19]: I got to see Robin drag.
[SPEAKER_27]: Don't talk about that on this show.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, you can talk about it if you want.
[SPEAKER_19]: I got to see Robin drag.
[SPEAKER_19]: It was cool.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm scarred for life.
[SPEAKER_19]: We have dead airspace!
[SPEAKER_27]: Sorry, I'm having to correct people that are voting for Loki's Legend of Max mix.
[SPEAKER_27]: That wasn't the cage match!
[SPEAKER_27]: That was a... We were just rating it like it was a cage match, but that wasn't really... We should have picked that as my cage match.
[SPEAKER_26]: Damn it.
[SPEAKER_26]: Oh, I gotta get Jahi's vote, because Jahi actually voted in the main charm, so he voted for that.
[SPEAKER_27]: Ooh, it's... Down the wire!
[SPEAKER_27]: Let's see, let's see.
[SPEAKER_27]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_27]: Now it's tied.
[SPEAKER_27]: We need people to hurry up and send their votes.
[SPEAKER_27]: Jahi, I got your vote, so you don't have to send that over a message.
[SPEAKER_27]: I already got it.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_19]: We need... I mean... No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_27]: We gotta wait and see if there's any more votes coming in the chatroom.
[SPEAKER_27]: Because there's still some people in the chatroom who haven't voted yet.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, vote.
[SPEAKER_19]: Vote for me.
[SPEAKER_27]: So, it's... Oh, there's one.
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, let's see.
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, well, let's keep it open for a few more minutes.
[SPEAKER_27]: We'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_19]: We'll give it ten seconds to get really good at it.
[SPEAKER_19]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_27]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_27]: Let's talk about something else.
[SPEAKER_19]: How cool Vincent D'Amore is.
[SPEAKER_27]: Vincent D'Amore is cool, but he doesn't swear in his songs.
[SPEAKER_19]: He could swear in Icelandic or something.
[SPEAKER_27]: He'd be cooler if he did.
[SPEAKER_19]: No, just because something has swearing in it doesn't make it cool.
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_27]: SoCal Kicks brings up a good thing we should talk about.
[SPEAKER_27]: I briefly mentioned this after the Milpitas Golf Land interviews, but we are going to be going to Cyber Beat Nation, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_27]: Well, at least I'm going.
[SPEAKER_19]: Fuck them for scheduling it on Valentine's Day.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah, you know what?
[SPEAKER_27]: Since I'm the single one, Valentine's Day doesn't matter to me this year, so I'm going to go to L.A.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's my five-year anniversary with Dan.
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, congratulations, you guys.
[SPEAKER_27]: That's really cute.
[SPEAKER_19]: Give us presents.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_26]: Well, some other Bimani-related stuff.
[SPEAKER_26]: They released a second code for DVR Extreme, if anyone cares.
[SPEAKER_26]: You know, it releases Sync for Extreme, Twinbee, and also Burning the Floor Momo Mix, which is... Got the retarded speed-up in the middle.
[SPEAKER_26]: That song would do very good in Tourney Mix 3.
[SPEAKER_26]: Unnecessary speed-up.
[SPEAKER_26]: But, you know.
[SPEAKER_26]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_26]: That's all.
[SPEAKER_19]: Somebody else vote.
[SPEAKER_27]: Jenny Bean hasn't voted.
[SPEAKER_27]: Make her vote.
[SPEAKER_19]: Jenny Bean, vote.
[SPEAKER_19]: Who else hasn't voted?
[SPEAKER_19]: North Thailand hasn't voted.
[SPEAKER_19]: Vote for your fellow staff squad person.
[SPEAKER_27]: Who hasn't voted?
[SPEAKER_27]: Who am I going to single out here?
[SPEAKER_27]: Excel hasn't voted.
[SPEAKER_19]: Did Jahi vote?
[SPEAKER_27]: Jahi did vote.
Um...
[SPEAKER_27]: Did VidPower vote?
[SPEAKER_27]: No, he did.
[SPEAKER_27]: Slinky didn't vote.
[SPEAKER_19]: Slinky, vote for me.
[SPEAKER_27]: All right.
[SPEAKER_27]: We're naming people now who haven't voted.
[SPEAKER_19]: We're singling you out.
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_27]: We got one from JB.
[SPEAKER_27]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, that wasn't a vote.
[SPEAKER_19]: JB, vote.
[SPEAKER_27]: JB, vote.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's all on your shoulders.
[SPEAKER_27]: Next vote is the final vote.
[SPEAKER_27]: And it's going to be the tiebreaker vote, possibly.
[SPEAKER_27]: So everything is tied and the next vote breaks it.
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay, here comes JB.
[SPEAKER_27]: Damn it, that wasn't a vote.
[SPEAKER_27]: Jenny Bean votes for... She didn't put anything.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, that's it.
[SPEAKER_27]: Jenny Bean breaks the tie.
[SPEAKER_27]: The page match is over.
[SPEAKER_27]: For the second week in a row.
[SPEAKER_27]: It wins.
[SPEAKER_27]: Nice try.
[SPEAKER_27]: USFEB tried cloning himself to vote again.
[SPEAKER_27]: Nice try, but you were five seconds too late, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_27]: So, Eternity wins again for the second week.
[SPEAKER_27]: And, uh... The Grimshaw one will just have to be saved for the occasional fuck-off show.
[SPEAKER_27]: Sorry, kids.
[SPEAKER_27]: But yes, I'll send that to you guys that wanted it after the show.
[SPEAKER_27]: Or you can visit Tal's website.
[SPEAKER_27]: He has it, but... Ask Tal when he comes back in the chatroom where his website is, because that's where I got it from.
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_27]: So the cage match is over.
[SPEAKER_27]: Eternity wins again.
[SPEAKER_10]: Play it again.
[SPEAKER_27]: What do you mean, play it again?
[SPEAKER_10]: Play it again, Rob.
[SPEAKER_27]: I'm not going to play it again.
[SPEAKER_27]: It already won, dammit.
[SPEAKER_26]: If you want to take a huge break, we can play E-Fly.
[SPEAKER_27]: I don't want to play that 9 minute song, no way.
[SPEAKER_27]: I don't think any of us will say this.
[SPEAKER_26]: Alright, here it is.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, we got it.
[SPEAKER_27]: Hey!
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: You're just jealous.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yes, that's right, I am jealous.
[SPEAKER_19]: Fuck!
[SPEAKER_19]: Shit!
[SPEAKER_19]: This kick to Rob's knee was brought to you by Propel.
[SPEAKER_19]: Ow!
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anyway, moving along.
[SPEAKER_27]: Moving right along.
[SPEAKER_27]: Moving on up, moving on up to this Muppet movie.
[SPEAKER_27]: Mmm, tastes like Muppet.
[SPEAKER_27]: Anything else?
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, that's a good erotic song title.
[SPEAKER_27]: Tastes like Muppet.
[SPEAKER_27]: Um, what else?
[SPEAKER_27]: Is there anything like... Treat me like a Muppet and stick your hand up my ass.
[SPEAKER_27]: Puppet like a Muppet.
[SPEAKER_27]: I'm sure you guys could be very creative.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ah, such a busy schedule.
[SPEAKER_27]: EOSFBB says, taste like Muppet.
[SPEAKER_09]: Rock the cock.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, we did the erotic thing like an hour ago.
[SPEAKER_27]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_19]: You know that candy cane still makes me think of that Jay and Silent Bob comic.
[SPEAKER_27]: What?
[SPEAKER_27]: What one?
[SPEAKER_19]: The one where Dante went to see Caitlyn in the asylum and started fucking her with a candy cane.
[SPEAKER_19]: And she woke up and chased him out.
[SPEAKER_27]: I need to watch the Clerks cartoon series again, just because it rules so much.
[SPEAKER_27]: Is it safe?
[SPEAKER_26]: It's very safe.
[SPEAKER_27]: Has anybody seen any- Let's see!
[SPEAKER_26]: Is it safe?
[SPEAKER_27]: Has there been any DDR on TV lately?
[SPEAKER_27]: Like on a show?
[SPEAKER_10]: No.
[SPEAKER_27]: Like I heard it was on Fastlane like three months ago, but that's such old news.
[SPEAKER_25]: They're gonna be airing a Slurpee Nation commercial on TV.
[SPEAKER_27]: On TV?
[SPEAKER_27]: Where?
[SPEAKER_27]: It's a commercial, but that doesn't mean it's a real commercial.
[SPEAKER_27]: It just seemed like a DDR ego thing.
[SPEAKER_27]: I thought that was just an online commercial.
[SPEAKER_27]: I don't think they're actually going to air it, no.
[SPEAKER_25]: Where would they air it?
[SPEAKER_25]: Assfucker?
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh my god though, I did download a cool, I mean it's an old commercial, but it was like the one of this Nike shoe that they're wearing in Japan.
[SPEAKER_19]: No, Nike.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's this guy walking past a gigantic shoe in front of a billboard, and all of a sudden the shoe transforms into a robot and flies off.
[SPEAKER_19]: And the guys are standing there going, blink.
[SPEAKER_19]: But they made a toy of that, like ten of them.
[SPEAKER_19]: And they were giving them to executives and had one in a giveaway prize, I want one.
[SPEAKER_23]: That was also in a magazine for, uh, Spin Magazine.
[SPEAKER_23]: It came with the little flipbook, and it had, like, had it turn into a football player, though.
[SPEAKER_23]: But it was pretty much the same thing.
[SPEAKER_23]: It also, like, turned into, like, a Gundam.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's what the football player looked like, though.
[SPEAKER_23]: And he, like, jumped up and flew away for no apparent reason.
[SPEAKER_19]: This guy's just standing there on the other side of the fence going, Well, what do you know?
[SPEAKER_19]: Shoot turned into a robot.
[SPEAKER_27]: Ask Orange Lounge
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_27]: While you're waiting.
[SPEAKER_27]: All right, all right, fine.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think it's in there still.
[SPEAKER_13]: Is it already in there?
[SPEAKER_27]: All right.
[SPEAKER_27]: So send us those questions to me in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_27]: You can ask Orange Lounge, or you can ask Zero, you can ask Jonas, or alternatively, you can ask Brad and Irene out in the front room.
[SPEAKER_27]: You can ask any of us.
[SPEAKER_26]: Actually, I have a better song.
[SPEAKER_27]: Or Puppy, or Ryan.
[SPEAKER_26]: The Fly isn't that good.
[SPEAKER_26]: We can play, I've got Gennaro in there that's really good.
[SPEAKER_26]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_26]: That was going to be my Cage Match song, but it's nine minutes long.
[SPEAKER_26]: Well, you know what?
[SPEAKER_27]: No, we're doing our Journey to the Wonderland song, so that's what we always do.
[SPEAKER_26]: All right, fine.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, so ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_27]: Send me those questions in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_27]: You can ask Orange Lounge or you can ask any of our guests.
[SPEAKER_27]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_27]: Really?
[SPEAKER_27]: Why am I so fly?
[SPEAKER_27]: Why am I so sexy?
[SPEAKER_27]: Is that why you're asking?
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright, well let's...
[SPEAKER_19]: Why are you so fly for a white guy?
[SPEAKER_27]: My last name is white man.
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay, first question.
[SPEAKER_27]: And people, don't send me your questions over slash notice.
[SPEAKER_27]: It's got to come over slash MSG because I might miss them.
[SPEAKER_27]: But I caught this one, so we'll start with this question.
[SPEAKER_27]: SoCalKicks wants to know, Can SoCalKicks be a special super duper derpity derp host at CBN?
[SPEAKER_19]: He can be our local chorus watcher.
[SPEAKER_27]: I don't see why not.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah, he can be the local...
[SPEAKER_27]: This is what I'm thinking.
[SPEAKER_27]: I'm thinking since there's going to be so much to talk about, so many different people to talk about Cyber Beat Nation, to maybe make it its own... We could be an intern.
[SPEAKER_27]: Well, I'm thinking of having the Cyber Beat Nation interview be like its own show.
[SPEAKER_27]: Like, not normally, not a normal Sunday at 6.30.
[SPEAKER_19]: By the way, because we said we would, before I forget, we do have to introduce Black Lab as our foreign correspondent for the People's Republic of Davis.
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, yes, good.
[SPEAKER_27]: Is there any news to report from the People's Republic of Davis foreign correspondent?
[SPEAKER_27]: Um...
[SPEAKER_24]: It's still as boring as ever.
[SPEAKER_27]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_27]: Um... I heard you almost got run over by a cop.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_24]: Damn cops.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's all a conspiracy.
[SPEAKER_24]: See, they're trying to take me out.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's because, um... A couple days ago when I was going out late, and I had to go to the A.M.
[SPEAKER_24]: P.M.
[SPEAKER_24]: to get food.
[SPEAKER_24]: Because the damn dining hall was closed early.
[SPEAKER_24]: Um...
[SPEAKER_24]: I was leaving on my bike, and three cop cars come screeching into the gas station parking lot with no lights or sirens on, and one of them almost hit me.
[SPEAKER_24]: And, yeah, things suck.
[SPEAKER_19]: Remember, it's the People's Republic of Davis where they'll find you for reading.
[SPEAKER_27]: This is CBN.
[SPEAKER_27]: What I'm thinking, and I need to know what the other hosts think of this, instead of airing the interviews during a show, maybe have it be its own special that airs Friday night or something.
[SPEAKER_13]: Sure, why not?
[SPEAKER_27]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_27]: I'm thinking of doing like a reality radio thing.
[SPEAKER_27]: Like actually doing a journal.
[SPEAKER_27]: Like saying, hey, it's Friday morning and we're leaving.
[SPEAKER_27]: Because I'm going down there with Mel B, and he's always a colorful character to have on the show.
[SPEAKER_27]: Brad and Irene might possibly tag along.
[SPEAKER_27]: We all know Brad's funnier than hell, and Irene will probably be playing Animal Crossing, so she won't say anything anyway.
[SPEAKER_27]: But I'm thinking about doing that.
[SPEAKER_26]: I wish I could go, but I'm having an empty house the whole weekend.
[SPEAKER_27]: So yes, SoCalKicks, you can be some kind of special, super-duper correspondent there.
[SPEAKER_19]: and in the background we'll have the Atari 5200 going.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_19]: But I have one of those too and I do have combat.
[SPEAKER_27]: EOSFBB wants to know when will Orange Lounge have the next match game?
[SPEAKER_19]: We were going to do one tonight.
[SPEAKER_27]: But everything else ran too long because we had the Milpitas interviews and the fuck yous went on forever.
[SPEAKER_27]: So we'll try and get to one next week.
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_27]: We'll do one next week.
[SPEAKER_27]: We'll do one next week for you.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll show.
[SPEAKER_27]: All right.
[SPEAKER_27]: Snub Dishnoid wants to know, how would one go about passing Rhythm and Patty?
[SPEAKER_26]: Oh, is that an edit?
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, that's the edit.
[SPEAKER_27]: Loki, tell us about this.
[SPEAKER_26]: Rhythm and Patty, or R and Patty, was Orange Beanie's third place winner, I believe.
[SPEAKER_26]: Third place for the Hell edits.
[SPEAKER_26]: If you want to try passing it, play it in the first stage, and play your first stage on Beginner.
[SPEAKER_26]: You cannot fail Beginner, the first stage.
[SPEAKER_26]: So just play the edit, make sure it's set to beginner mode, and you can try it as many times as you want on the first stage, and you can't fail it.
[SPEAKER_26]: But he did it, and I was surprised, like holy shit, he like got an A on it or something.
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah, so it's a lot of stamina, but that's about it.
[SPEAKER_19]: I still think the one for Era was cooler, because it followed the 2DX steps, well, whatever, the rhythm of the keys.
[SPEAKER_19]: I was like, I heard it, and I was like, oh my god, it's 2DX.
[SPEAKER_26]: Well, what won it over the other ones was the crowd reaction for it, because, you know, everyone was around like, oh, that's so cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, yeah, it's cool.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, moving on, next question?
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, next question, this one comes from Jahi, Jay Kinetic, our buddy.
[SPEAKER_27]: Jay Kinetic wants to know, when did Rob first get laid and how was it?
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, we did pass your virginity on the way to SoCal.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yes, for those that don't know, my virginity is actually two exits before Milpitas Golf Land.
[SPEAKER_27]: And this is really ironic, no, this is really ironic.
[SPEAKER_27]: I've lost my virginity the same weekend I saw DDR for the first time.
[SPEAKER_27]: Like, many years ago.
[SPEAKER_27]: Like, it was 1.5 minutes.
[SPEAKER_27]: Like a long... Like two.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_27]: So, uh, and how was it?
[SPEAKER_27]: Uh, sorry to say, I've had much better since.
[SPEAKER_27]: So, you all can wave when you're past Mission Boulevard.
[SPEAKER_27]: There's a Motel 6 right there.
[SPEAKER_27]: Just wave at it.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_27]: I can't believe I just said that on the radio.
[SPEAKER_27]: My mother's crying somewhere.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_27]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_27]: Jenny Bean.
[SPEAKER_27]: Can DCB and I be special non-Cyberbeat Nation interview hosts if we figure out how to record them for the people that don't know, that don't get to go to Cyberbeat Nation?
[SPEAKER_27]: Ha ha ha.
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay, sure, why not?
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, you guys want to record something?
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm not going by choice because I have my 5th year anniversary and I'm going to.
[SPEAKER_26]: I'm just going to get laid.
[SPEAKER_26]: Anyways, yeah, gee, I wish I could be crammed into a nice small Korean arcade with tons of people there and it being all hot and stuff and crowded.
[SPEAKER_26]: Wait, no, that was... No, sorry, don't want to go.
[SPEAKER_26]: All right, so I wanted to go just to go to the Price is Right.
[SPEAKER_26]: God damn it.
[SPEAKER_26]: That's the only thing.
[SPEAKER_26]: I don't think Mel and I are going to have time to go to Price is Right.
[SPEAKER_26]: So...
[SPEAKER_27]: We have our Olivia back!
[SPEAKER_27]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_10]: Olivia's gone!
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm so happy.
[SPEAKER_27]: We have Olivia back and she's going to give me lots of stuff.
[SPEAKER_27]: We got Lee back.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm so happy.
[SPEAKER_19]: Good.
[SPEAKER_19]: You can have the bitch.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_27]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_27]: Happy day in Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, happy day.
[SPEAKER_19]: You can have that little chick back.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_27]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_27]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_27]: Quit traveling between villagers.
[SPEAKER_27]: We're going to lose all of our villagers if you guys keep doing the traveling.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_27]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_27]: Shadow.
[SPEAKER_27]: Hey Loki, can we make you into one of those Virtu thingies for Step Mania?
[SPEAKER_27]: You and your burning hair jumping out from the left hand side of the screen.
[SPEAKER_26]: Oh, let me grow my hair.
[SPEAKER_26]: Yelling toasty.
[SPEAKER_26]: Well, let me grow out my hair a little bit longer so it's like really messed up and stuff.
[SPEAKER_26]: You can get me dressed up for like, um, cause in Phantom Man I'm gonna be cosplaying as Oolong the bunny.
[SPEAKER_26]: So, so, so you can get a picture of me with a pancake on my head and, uh, yeah, that'd be funny.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'll cosplay as Oolong too.
[SPEAKER_19]: Rob, do you mind if I cosplay with you?
[SPEAKER_26]: Go right ahead.
[SPEAKER_19]: We're going to cosplay as Ulan, and you know what?
[SPEAKER_19]: I found those old rabbit fur coats from the 80s.
[SPEAKER_19]: Since they're already dead and made into coats, we can just cut them up.
[SPEAKER_19]: That'd be cool.
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh my lord.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, Strong Brad wants to know, can we spot him for Cyber Beat Nation?
[SPEAKER_27]: No.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_27]: Sorry, you know, we're poor enough, it's hard enough for me to get down there, Christ.
[SPEAKER_27]: VidPawa wants to know, how are your guys' PlayStation 2s modded, if they are modded at all?
[SPEAKER_27]: Also, if they are modded, did you do it yourself or did someone else do it for you?
[SPEAKER_19]: Pierre?
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm not cheap.
[SPEAKER_19]: I bought a JPS2.
[SPEAKER_27]: I also bought a JPS2.
[SPEAKER_26]: I attempted to mod mine with a plug mod that's internal.
[SPEAKER_26]: And ever since I tried doing that, every now and then it doesn't want to load my GameShark CD and I have to reboot it.
[SPEAKER_26]: But I have three plug mods that are supposedly going to work in some version of the PS2.
[SPEAKER_26]: I just don't have one.
[SPEAKER_26]: I need to get rid of them.
[SPEAKER_27]: The money you're going to spend attempting all those various mod chips, you might as well just crack and get the JPS2.
[SPEAKER_19]: Keep in mind this, is that for every mod that comes out, with every new game that comes out, it has protection.
[SPEAKER_19]: So, like, say that you want the next 2DX to come out, it ain't gonna work.
[SPEAKER_19]: Just, you know, save yourself some time.
[SPEAKER_19]: You can get a Japanese PlayStation 2 for cheap.
[SPEAKER_19]: And from what I understand, if anything ever happens to a network video, just serve a secret JPS2.
[SPEAKER_27]: Uh, word of advice, don't use mod chips on your PS2s because, exactly what Jamie said, Sony can fuck them up.
[SPEAKER_27]: I'll laugh at you.
[SPEAKER_27]: So, you know, maybe there'll be a super special secret one that'll get through someday, but honestly, just get the JPS2 and save yourself the headache.
[SPEAKER_19]: They're going to have one that works for everything after the system's already obsolete.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_27]: Which it is, technically.
[SPEAKER_27]: Moving on to EOSFBB.
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, dear God.
[SPEAKER_27]: He's giving us a website and asking us the impressions of the site.
[SPEAKER_27]: And I'm really scared whenever EOSFBB sends me a fucking website.
[SPEAKER_27]: All right.
[SPEAKER_27]: Kama Sutra Animated.
[SPEAKER_27]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_27]: I will.
[SPEAKER_27]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_27]: We'll look at it more in depth a little later.
[SPEAKER_27]: We've got a bunch more questions to get to.
[SPEAKER_27]: I like the animated picture of the right in the cock there.
[SPEAKER_27]: That's very interesting.
[SPEAKER_27]: That might be my new icon on TDR Free.
[SPEAKER_27]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, wait.
[SPEAKER_27]: I might get a point for that.
[SPEAKER_19]: It'd get removed.
[SPEAKER_19]: You'd have 24 hours to remove it.
[SPEAKER_27]: Damn it.
[SPEAKER_27]: Well, for that 24 hours, it would be hilarious.
[SPEAKER_27]: All right.
[SPEAKER_27]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_27]: 23rd Magus, can we call you a boo-boo kitty fuck?
[SPEAKER_27]: If you were asking that question to Loki, sure.
[SPEAKER_26]: Actually, that's my backup name for when my name was taken or something.
[SPEAKER_26]: That's where it appears at.
[SPEAKER_19]: Actually, someone in the Fruits community's name is BooBooKittyFuck, the legend community.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah, I remember seeing a name called BooBooKittyFuck.
[SPEAKER_27]: All right.
[SPEAKER_27]: DCB has a question, and it's, hi, guys.
Hi.
[SPEAKER_19]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_27]: This is the police.
[SPEAKER_27]: DCB, put the joke down.
[SPEAKER_27]: Step away from the joke.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi Dad, I'm in jail.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_27]: SoCalKicks wants to know, will you buy me a PlayStation 2 Japanese?
[SPEAKER_27]: No.
[SPEAKER_27]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_27]: Damn it, the Matrix is 102 days away, it's 102 days too long.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, Jay Kinetic wants to know, Does anyone know where I can get Japanese hip-hop and R&B romanji lyrics?
[SPEAKER_27]: Where is the Lucifer pic that DarkSakura was supposed to send me, and who's hotter?
[SPEAKER_27]: Yoji Kudo or Irvine Kinase?
[SPEAKER_27]: I fucked that up because I'm too honky, sorry.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright, here's what I have to say.
[SPEAKER_19]: As far as the lyrics, I had stuff, but I'll have to go find the sites again.
[SPEAKER_19]: As far as the pic of Lucifer, my hard drive was broken a few weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_19]: So that means that I have to find it for you again.
[SPEAKER_19]: But just look up Angel Sanctuary.
[SPEAKER_19]: There's actually a really good Japanese set.
[SPEAKER_19]: They've got tons of good Lucifer pictures.
[SPEAKER_19]: And as far as Yoji or Irvine... Irvine, dude!
[SPEAKER_19]: Just the hair, the trench coat, the shotgun hat... The only redeeming quality of playing Final Fantasy VIII.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah, I agree.
[SPEAKER_27]: Irvine's hotter, because that was the only redeeming quality of Final Fantasy VIII.
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, Squall was pretty hot, even though he had the personality of a pancake.
[SPEAKER_27]: Squall was a panty, okay!
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, DCB claims that I love Derby Owners Club more than I love us.
[SPEAKER_27]: Meaning Orange Lounge, I suppose, or more than the Killer Pals or something like that.
[SPEAKER_27]: To be truthful, yes, I do love Derby Owners Club more than any of you.
[SPEAKER_27]: Sorry, it's just the way it is.
[SPEAKER_27]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_27]: Nice question.
[SPEAKER_27]: It's just a game.
[SPEAKER_27]: Sure, I spent 20 bucks on it the other day, but hey, you know.
[SPEAKER_26]: Why can't they have Hookers Owners Club, okay?
[SPEAKER_26]: I want to be a pimp and be able to raise my hookers to be the best prostitutes in the world.
[SPEAKER_26]: Why can't they have that?
[SPEAKER_26]: I could totally see that if it would be this golf land.
[SPEAKER_27]: Ah, good question.
[SPEAKER_27]: Angel is asking this, but he says it's actually Jay Kinetic's question that I liked, but he didn't send it over PM.
[SPEAKER_27]: What's everyone's favorite sushi among the Orange Lounge Radio staff?
[SPEAKER_19]: Gold or nigiri.
[SPEAKER_27]: Either.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay, for rolls, my favorite roll would have to be, at this point, the twin dragon roll at Shia, which is like six types of fish wrapped around, of course, the rice, the nori, and fried lobster tail with this really yummy sauce.
[SPEAKER_19]: And then my favorite nigiri roll is, at this time, I would have to say toro, which is patty tuna.
[SPEAKER_26]: I like toast.
[SPEAKER_26]: No, I don't like sushi at all.
[SPEAKER_26]: I've never tried it, but, you know, me being a picky eater, I don't like sushi.
[SPEAKER_26]: It just doesn't look good to me.
[SPEAKER_27]: Sorry to hear that.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, we're going to take the last few questions here.
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_27]: What's your favorite roll?
[SPEAKER_27]: My favorite roll is Sacramento rolls, deep fried California rolls, because they're fattening and good.
[SPEAKER_27]: What's your favorite single roll?
[SPEAKER_27]: Favorite single roll?
[SPEAKER_19]: Have you had any before, like a nagi taco roll?
[SPEAKER_27]: Like the sashimi?
[SPEAKER_27]: Um, I'd say unagi.
[SPEAKER_19]: Rob likes the eel.
[SPEAKER_27]: I do like the eel.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's long.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, we're closing the question asking now.
[SPEAKER_27]: We're going to take the last few questions here.
[SPEAKER_27]: Ooh, dead air.
[SPEAKER_27]: Sorry about that.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright, last question.
[SPEAKER_27]: Aw, dammit, it's another will you buy me question.
[SPEAKER_27]: RYC3 wants to know, will you buy me a Universal PS2?
[SPEAKER_27]: No, there's no such thing.
[SPEAKER_27]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_27]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_27]: No more questions, although I want to put in this website that DCB just posted.
[SPEAKER_27]: I'm kind of scared of it, though.
[SPEAKER_27]: Columbia, the shuttle tragedy.
[SPEAKER_27]: It's a screencap from CNN.
[SPEAKER_27]: It says, shuttle traveling nearly 18 times speed of light.
[SPEAKER_19]: Do the salt and pepper shakers on Blue's Clues actually hold cocaine and heroin?
[SPEAKER_27]: That's a total inside joke from Friday, yes.
[SPEAKER_19]: I want to watch Buffy.
[SPEAKER_27]: DarkTetsuya wants to know a good place to pick up girls.
[SPEAKER_19]: Online.
[SPEAKER_27]: and last question, last question there are no girls online, they're all 40 year old men last question, SoCalKicks wants to know do you think Ali Larder would be a good Samus for the Metroid movie?
[SPEAKER_27]: that chick from Final Destination what movie was that?
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't watch that movie I didn't even hear of Final Destination was she in Bring It On?
[SPEAKER_27]: no she wasn't in Bring It On what other movie was she in?
[SPEAKER_19]: there was another big I watched movies that don't suck Final Destination wasn't that bad
[SPEAKER_27]: What else was she in?
[SPEAKER_27]: Would she be good, Samus?
[SPEAKER_27]: Eh, she'd be okay.
[SPEAKER_27]: It would be better than fucking Angelina Jolie or Mira.
[SPEAKER_27]: Just fucking... We need to get away from those people.
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, thank you.
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay, Allie Larder wasn't Jay and Silent Bob.
[SPEAKER_27]: She was the chick that farted.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh!
[SPEAKER_19]: No, no, she's too... You know who?
[SPEAKER_19]: They need...
[SPEAKER_19]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_19]: First of all, Samus has green hair.
[SPEAKER_27]: They're going to be making a Metroid movie, yes.
[SPEAKER_19]: Samus needs to be a freaking powerful looking woman.
[SPEAKER_19]: Samus is supposed to be like seven feet tall.
[SPEAKER_19]: China.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm wondering why... Dude, China would be a fucking kick-ass Samus.
[SPEAKER_27]: Lucy Lawless.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_27]: or the chick that played Gabrielle.
[SPEAKER_27]: I want my Samus to have lesbian connotations, Samus.
[SPEAKER_26]: No, I was wondering why... I mean, I've seen a lot of really shitty-ass movies.
[SPEAKER_26]: I mean, for instance, I've given out some of those for the... Black Ninja, okay?
[SPEAKER_26]: Really shitty-ass movies.
[SPEAKER_26]: Why hasn't the DDR movie come out?
[SPEAKER_26]: I mean, even some really cheap-ass studio could pick this stuff up.
[SPEAKER_26]: I mean, for next to nothing.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm just surprised that it hasn't been, like, released.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm still voting for Lucy Lawless to be Samus.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah, Lucy Lawless would kick ass.
[SPEAKER_27]: And SoCalKicks is stomping and pouting because he said he saw the end of Metroid Prime and she's a blonde.
[SPEAKER_19]: Um, actually, so in Super Metroid, but I'm referring to the first Metroid, if you put in the code, Justin Bailey, Samus has green hair.
[SPEAKER_27]: So, eh.
[SPEAKER_19]: And, you know, Justin Bailey is not actually a name.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's actually referring to just wearing underwear.
[SPEAKER_19]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_19]: It's an Australian.
[SPEAKER_19]: Ow!
[SPEAKER_19]: Because Bailey is a piece.
[SPEAKER_19]: So that's where it came from, Justin Bailey.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yes, I'm full of old video game knowledge.
[SPEAKER_19]: Sue me.
[SPEAKER_19]: I have to go through my list, but no one cares.
[SPEAKER_27]: Hurry up.
[SPEAKER_27]: Go through your list.
[SPEAKER_27]: Do it.
[SPEAKER_19]: It would take me a long time.
[SPEAKER_27]: You want to save it for next week, then?
[SPEAKER_19]: I'll go through the list.
[SPEAKER_19]: Who wants to know what I have?
[SPEAKER_27]: Do it.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_19]: I do not have Jaguar.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay, starting with the Nintendo products, I have a Virtual Boy, I have one in a nice plastic case too, I have a Nintendo, both styles, Super Nintendo, both styles, I have an old style Game Boy, Game Boy Pocket, Game Boy Color, two Game Boy Advances, one of them's Japanese, because we got it before the record, anyway.
[SPEAKER_19]: I have, um, we're getting the new one too.
[SPEAKER_19]: The new GBA.
[SPEAKER_19]: Um, and, okay, what's this mix?
[SPEAKER_19]: Sega?
[SPEAKER_19]: I have three Master Systems.
[SPEAKER_19]: I have two Power Base Converters.
[SPEAKER_19]: I have a couple of Genesis, Genesi, Geneses?
[SPEAKER_19]: Um, I have a Nomad.
[SPEAKER_19]: I have a Game Gear.
[SPEAKER_19]: Um, and then, I have Saturn.
[SPEAKER_19]: I have two Saturns.
[SPEAKER_19]: We have the battery pack and AC plug.
[SPEAKER_19]: I have an Atari Lynx.
[SPEAKER_19]: I have a 2600.
[SPEAKER_19]: New style.
[SPEAKER_19]: The kind that's more comfy.
[SPEAKER_19]: We got it for five bucks.
[SPEAKER_19]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_19]: I have a Sega CD and a Sega CDX.
[SPEAKER_19]: No.
[SPEAKER_19]: Actually, I might have Night Trap.
[SPEAKER_19]: For Atari, I have 2600, 250, 200s.
[SPEAKER_19]: I have the 4-port and the 2-port 5200s.
[SPEAKER_19]: I have the Lynx.
[SPEAKER_19]: I have Click-A-Vision.
[SPEAKER_19]: I have the Expansion Module 1 and 2, so I can play Turbo.
[SPEAKER_19]: I have an Intellivision.
[SPEAKER_19]: I have a Turbo Duo.
[SPEAKER_19]: Um, think about TurboDuo, it's awesome.
[SPEAKER_19]: As long as you use good quality CDs, you can play a game no matter, you can copy games on them, no matter the country code.
[SPEAKER_19]: Because there's no country lockout, no copy lockout.
[SPEAKER_19]: So, I had, let's play Dracula, I actually have Dracula X now in original.
[SPEAKER_19]: Um, I have, um, a Nintendo 64.
[SPEAKER_19]: Somewhere.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't know what I did with it.
[SPEAKER_19]: I think it's paperweight somewhere.
[SPEAKER_19]: I have an Xbox.
[SPEAKER_19]: I have a GameCube.
[SPEAKER_19]: Um, no, I didn't melt it.
[SPEAKER_19]: I have a Dreamcast, I have two Dreamcasts.
[SPEAKER_19]: Um, two PlayStation 2s.
[SPEAKER_19]: I've got a stack of old-style PlayStations, including the first model.
[SPEAKER_19]: I have a PS1.
[SPEAKER_19]: I have, what else did you name?
[SPEAKER_19]: I have an Xbox.
[SPEAKER_19]: Um, I have, I do not have a 3DO, but we almost bought a CD-i right before Game Masters went out of business.
[SPEAKER_19]: Um, I have a Kinectrix.
[SPEAKER_19]: We're looking for a Vectrex.
[SPEAKER_19]: Um, Mattel?
[SPEAKER_19]: Which one did Mattel do?
[SPEAKER_27]: Wasn't that the Intellivision?
[SPEAKER_19]: I almost bought a Pico.
[SPEAKER_19]: I thought that was the Intellivision.
[SPEAKER_19]: The Sega Pico?
[SPEAKER_19]: Because they were selling it for 10 bucks when I was at Mobile.
[SPEAKER_19]: Um, I have a Neo Geo cartridge system.
[SPEAKER_19]: I have a Neo Geo CD.
[SPEAKER_19]: You know how Dan got that?
[SPEAKER_19]: Dan got our Neo card by trading a Sega CD for it.
[SPEAKER_19]: Back then, they didn't know, because of the thing.
[SPEAKER_19]: And we actually are still picking up our cartridges, plus we picked up this KOF 2000.
[SPEAKER_19]: How much was that?
[SPEAKER_19]: We got it for just over $300.
[SPEAKER_19]: What else do I have?
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh yeah, I have a Wonderswan color.
[SPEAKER_19]: We have two Neo Geo Pocket colors and a Neo Geo Pocket.
[SPEAKER_19]: and, um, I might have exhausted the list if there's anything else I don't remember because I know I've got other stuff.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_27]: So... Wow, you own a lot.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's like 40-something, I think.
[SPEAKER_27]: Disgusting!
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh well.
[SPEAKER_27]: But fun.
[SPEAKER_27]: Your house is a video game museum, it really is.
[SPEAKER_19]: And don't forget the Transformers and Valkyries that are littering my house.
[SPEAKER_26]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_26]: I'm afraid because the movie pile that I have in my house is starting to creep towards my bed, and I think it's coming after me.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yikes.
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay, we've got to wrap this show.
[SPEAKER_27]: We're already running like five minutes late.
[SPEAKER_27]: Any final thoughts from you folks?
[SPEAKER_19]: I want Boba.
[SPEAKER_27]: Jamie wants Boba.
[SPEAKER_27]: You know what, though?
[SPEAKER_27]: I've got to get back here, like, fast, so if we go get Bubba, we just have to go get Bubba and go.
[SPEAKER_27]: We can't really stay.
[SPEAKER_26]: I need to finish my website.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah, that's why I've got to work on another website for somebody else.
[SPEAKER_27]: Zero, any final thoughts?
[SPEAKER_27]: Thanks for being here tonight.
[SPEAKER_23]: No problem.
[SPEAKER_23]: I'd come back whenever you wanted.
[SPEAKER_23]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_23]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_23]: I would say if I was Willy Wonka, I would be really rich.
[SPEAKER_23]: And for the simple knowledge bands that don't know what I mean by get the fat kid out of my chocolate milk, and that's it.
[SPEAKER_26]: Rock, Jonas, any final thoughts?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, not much.
[SPEAKER_05]: I haven't spoken as usual as much.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, um, I'll be back next week again.
[SPEAKER_05]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: This time probably on time.
[SPEAKER_27]: You can play match game next week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, be ready at 5 o'clock or so, maybe.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah, they can't hear you.
[SPEAKER_23]: That was just dead air.
[SPEAKER_23]: I'm going to come back with them because I'll be ready at 5 o'clock.
[SPEAKER_23]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_27]: I don't really have a final thought.
[SPEAKER_27]: Life sucks.
[SPEAKER_27]: Go kill yourself.
[SPEAKER_27]: Hey!
[SPEAKER_27]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_27]: I didn't mean to look at you when I said that, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_27]: You don't need to kill yourself.
[SPEAKER_27]: You're fine.
[SPEAKER_19]: All right.
[SPEAKER_19]: Life sucks when you grow up.
[SPEAKER_27]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_27]: All right.
[SPEAKER_27]: Later, Jonas.
[SPEAKER_27]: Thanks for being here.
[SPEAKER_27]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_27]: That's the end of the show.
[SPEAKER_27]: Tune in next week.
[SPEAKER_19]: Thank you for the balls.
[SPEAKER_27]: Tune in to our Bomani Music and More program always.
[SPEAKER_19]: The blue balls were tasty.
[SPEAKER_27]: Pour up our listening hours.
[SPEAKER_27]: We fucking need it.
[SPEAKER_27]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_01]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_01]: Orange Lounge Radio is hosted by DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_01]: If you'd like to leave us a comment, send us an email at orangeloungeradio at yahoo.com And now, here's your fortune cookie message of the day.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sit on my face and tell me that you love me I'll sit on your face and tell you I love you too I love to hear you quarrel eyes When I'm between your thighs, you blow me away Sit on my face and let my lips embrace you I'll sit on your face and never love you truly Life can be fine if we're both 69 If we sit on our faces and walk up to bed in a place Halloween
[SPEAKER_01]: Thank you very much for listening, and we'll see you next week.