[SPEAKER_03]: and I November 7th, 2010.
[SPEAKER_03]: The new Xbox Kinect dashboard is designed to thwart pirates, Capcom brings retro arcade to the i-family, and as Microsoft swept indie games under the rug,
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Knights of the Old Sorority, I was telling you, or whatever this is.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Knights of the Crystals on Facebook, but it's just sorority life with Final Fantasy characters.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I'm going to stop playing this now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, you're no fun at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll play it after the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm being responsible.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, you should concentrate on the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: What do I save?
[SPEAKER_05]: There'll be plenty of time.
[SPEAKER_05]: You just close it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It saves as you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: The internet is a modern miracle.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also joining us, say hello to Tech Master Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_05]: How are you doing, Loki?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm doing fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you have a good week off, everybody?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, that's fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't have a week off.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why, what'd you do?
[SPEAKER_02]: Recorded another podcast.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh yeah, you had the other show.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, hey, I started a new show too, so you're not the only one that gets to plug a show now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ha!
[SPEAKER_02]: Guess what?
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: We still have a thing to do.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, we only taped a pilot, so we're not really a show yet, because I don't have a place to host it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is it a pilot light?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it just means, is the show going to work or not?
[SPEAKER_02]: Over the Frankenstein place.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, I'll get into that in a minute.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll talk about other side projects in a moment.
[SPEAKER_05]: I do want to introduce, of course, as always, our fourth guest, always here with us, the chat room, chat.orangeloungeradio.com, live on this Sunday evening as we tape at All Games Radio, www.allgames.com, 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern.
[SPEAKER_05]: Every Sunday night is when we tape Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, right after the Bobby Blackwell show, of course, I've got to plug Bobby because he's always been there.
[SPEAKER_05]: He calls himself the opening act, but I don't see it as a lesser billing.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's a smart guy, knows a lot about gaming, so tune into his show sometime if you haven't already.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, we're going to get into How Was Your Gaming Week.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's always how they start the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: We are back from a week off.
[SPEAKER_05]: One week ago was Halloween, so we just decided, you know what, let's just take a weekend off.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a lot going on in the real world.
[SPEAKER_05]: I had a bunch of stuff to do for one of my other hobbies, so we didn't even tape a show.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, Loki's got the baby.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura's got, I guess, other podcasts now that are bigger than this little shit show.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I have a big, fat, hairy cat.
[SPEAKER_05]: You do?
[SPEAKER_02]: Who has Twitter?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, Shermie has Twitter.
[SPEAKER_05]: When did Shermie get a Twitter?
[SPEAKER_02]: A few days ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who signed her up for Twitter?
[SPEAKER_05]: Was that you or was that a fan?
[SPEAKER_02]: That was me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: But she does all the typing, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what I have to deal with sitting in that chair.
[SPEAKER_02]: She doesn't do it to you.
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's because Rob's feet smell.
[SPEAKER_05]: My feet are smelly.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's quickly plug the side projects.
[SPEAKER_05]: Usually we'll save this for the end of the show because this was brought up a minute ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, you have a side project called?
[SPEAKER_02]: Comic Insanity.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's insanity without an I in the front of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So there's only one I and not two.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's at Infamous.net and F-A-M-O-U-S.net.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we go live on Tuesdays.
[SPEAKER_05]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just comic books, although today we were without a Maren Marvel.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, because she has a new house or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hard, hard, hard.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's me and Tiara, Maren Marvel, and Dan Shadow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who plays WoW with me now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who plays WoW with you now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, good times.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I don't play WoW with you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nope, both Marvel and Dan Shadow play WoW with me, but not you.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not a sheep.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's fine, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Speaking of WoW... I play Star Trek.
[SPEAKER_05]: Speaking of WoW, that's my new side project.
[SPEAKER_05]: Extifer and I have reunited.
[SPEAKER_05]: For those that listened to OLR back when it was a station, before the whole merger with All Games some time ago, we were doing a show called Guys on a Show, which is more like a pop culture thing, but now we do a Warcraft show.
[SPEAKER_05]: We just did a pilot...
[SPEAKER_05]: The Best Little Horde House in Azeroth
[SPEAKER_02]: I love the name Is it Disneyland right now?
[SPEAKER_05]: Actdeft says guys on an MMO
[SPEAKER_02]: I did play some Star Trek online and finally now that I have a shiny new headset I've been able to play on TeamSpeak with my Scottish guildmates or fleetmates I should say and I love listening to Scottish accents a whole lot actually one of the other guys I think in Holland and one of the other guys was in New York when we're playing we have another guy in Hawaii there's I think like three or four of us who live in the United States the rest all live in the UK and other places in Europe
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: I only get to see them when it's like before four here because then it's, you know, close to midnight there.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then I... Okay, Rob, don't hate.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't judge me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Judging.
[SPEAKER_05]: Getting ready to judge.
[SPEAKER_05]: Gavel raised.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got Second Life.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that I could see what the stupid Na'vi universe looks like.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, it's because I... You are guilty of nerddom!
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I wanted to see... I said, you know, before I actually judged Second Life, I was going to see what it's like.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's fair.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess you should try something... And I figured I would go to... Even if it's dressing up as a big smurf and running around...
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I said instead of doing, you know, I would try to do something that I couldn't really do in another game online.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I kind of, I thought it would be a great idea for them to do like an Avatar MMO.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess that thing would be lose all self-respect.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I've only been on it like four times just running around and going, oh, this is pretty, oh, this is pretty.
[SPEAKER_02]: Second Life controls like shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just letting you all know.
[SPEAKER_02]: The chat on there sucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: It controls like it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: And... I... It was free, okay?
[SPEAKER_05]: In our chatroom, salaciouspop at chat.orangelondradio.com says, I am jumping in front of Jamie in slow motion going, No!
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a terrorist bomb counts down to zero.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, get some self-respect.
[SPEAKER_05]: Play a Harry Potter universe if you have to.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just... I'm messing with you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, at any rate, it's not horrible.
[SPEAKER_02]: But after seeing some of the other stuff on there, I was like, yeah, I don't really have to play this that much.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've actually got a good game to play.
[SPEAKER_02]: We got Rock Band 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we played a lot of Rock Band 3 since a few days ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: We actually got it on Halloween.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we've been playing it since then.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm trying to think what else because I've played a lot of games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you guys get the keyboard?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, we did.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have you tried it?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't like it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It hurts my hand after a while because I want to hold the right keyboard position and it makes my hand hurt.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dan has beaten Fable 3 within a few days of getting the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: My pro tip to everybody...
[SPEAKER_02]: Make sure you have six million gold by the time you actually beat that part of the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: By the time you're the king or queen or whatever you're going to be.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love all the voices in that game because seriously, Jonathan Ross is in it doing announcement when you're beating up monsters and I love it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love Jonathan Ross.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's the one with the slight speech impediment.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, he speaks with the ahs and not the ahs.
[SPEAKER_05]: How's Fable 3 similar or different?
[SPEAKER_02]: Simon Pegg does voices in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love him.
[SPEAKER_05]: By the way, somebody came to Rocky, which was the thing I was doing last week and not here at the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: We had a costume contest.
[SPEAKER_05]: The winner was dressed up as Sean from Shaun of the Dead.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it was like A+.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was perfect.
[SPEAKER_05]: The guy looked the part and everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: A+.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would have to glomp on him.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you were saying how does it play?
[SPEAKER_05]: I was going to say, how's Fable 3 compared to the last one, Fable 2?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's got lots of good and lots of bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: The quest thing, instead of being able to just change your quests and things, you don't even have a menu anymore.
[SPEAKER_02]: You go back to this sanctuary, and then if you're trying to find a person to start a particular quest, it doesn't always teleport you right to them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, Rob's going to give us diseases.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have stuff going on.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have to do eye drops every three hours.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob's a zombie.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I'm a zombie.
[SPEAKER_05]: Brains.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: Navi.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, it's not bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, there's definitely a lot of glitchiness in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you know what really sucks is that when you have to take people places, you can't just tell them to follow you.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have to hold their hand and take them with you.
[SPEAKER_02]: and that's really irritating.
[SPEAKER_02]: And also I can see the seam on the dog and the textures and it's kind of meh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dogs do have seams though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but not like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not from the top of their head to the base of their tail.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sure they do.
[SPEAKER_02]: You'd expect you to see stitches or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, and then there's, like, a bunch of annoying people.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love one of the, quote, bad guys in the game, Reaver.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's just so ostentatious.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love him.
[SPEAKER_02]: And he's so evil and such a bastard.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love him to death.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: And then I played Robot Unicorn Attack in the middle of Starbucks at 11 o'clock last night.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, we had one of mine and Dan's friends over beat Little Nemo, the Dream Master, on Nintendo in our vault last night.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow, random.
[SPEAKER_02]: That game's actually kind of hard, you know?
[SPEAKER_02]: I played a bunch of other stuff too.
[SPEAKER_02]: I beat Peggle Knights.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's actually kind of hard.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's harder than the first Peggle.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lots of plants versus zombies.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm almost done growing my tree of life.
[SPEAKER_02]: or whatever, the Tree of Knowledge or whatever the crap the tree is.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the Tree of Worthless Advice is what it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, then.
[SPEAKER_02]: Stuff I've already figured out, but you get an achievement for it, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, and for anyone who has beaten mustache mode, all you have to do is just type mustache while you're playing and all the zombies will get mustaches and you'll be in mustache mode.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, it's completely retarded.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love how stupid that game is.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know I've played a bunch of stuff this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yeah, and I played Dance Masters tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I did Pala Pala dancing.
[SPEAKER_05]: What did you think of Dance Masters on the Xbox Kinect?
[SPEAKER_02]: The other dance game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I liked Para Para.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: They were playing Dance Central and there's this little solo freestyle part in it and Rob was going in and shaking his butt and jumping up and down.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then it plays back in high speed.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob peeking out, Rob peeking out, Rob's butt.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you just see Loki kind of flailing.
[SPEAKER_02]: He was actually doing stuff but when it speeds it up it looks like he's flailing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kind of what the Kinect is.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the Microsoft flail.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, the Microsoft flail.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what I'm going to call it from now on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anything else you want to share about your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_02]: Bam!
[SPEAKER_02]: Which is what I'm going to take a picture of.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, you do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dan and I found a bunch of our video game soundtracks so we've been ripping them and I found a VCD of Parapara Panic Volume 2 and 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_02]: I also found a Parapara DVD that belongs to Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: Random.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Parapara Master.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's like, that ain't mine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Parapara Master?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, you loaned it to me like five years ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't even remember that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, everybody else.
[SPEAKER_05]: Going to the chat room real quick.
[SPEAKER_05]: Spazinator in our chat room says, if someone were to put ABBA, Rocky Horror Picture Show, Dance Central, and SingStar into a blender and then puked out the resulting game, Sky would probably squeal.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, probably.
[SPEAKER_05]: It stinks!
[SPEAKER_05]: It was okay, I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like the message at the end, but otherwise it was censored and dopey.
[SPEAKER_05]: What is this?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Kidz Bop.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, you want to talk about digging through old treasures?
[SPEAKER_04]: It must have been something I got for free when I was ordering VCDs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Get VCDs.com, special price.
[SPEAKER_04]: Must have been free.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're Gaming Week, yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: I started off playing some of the demos for Joyride and Dance Central.
[SPEAKER_04]: And really the demo for Dance Central, which is on the disc, so if they put it on Xbox Live Marketplace, you don't really need to download it because it's already on the disc.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's only got two songs on the demo, which were Poker Face by Lady Gaga and Poison.
[SPEAKER_04]: Poison is a lot more difficult than Poker Face, that's for sure, because...
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm like, okay, Poker Face, that was really easy.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to go in the poison.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like, okay, break it down.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do this.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm like, I can't do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some 90s dance moves and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I think actually if you play through Dance Central, through the songs in the actual order that they're in there, from easiest to hardest, I think it would be a lot easier to pick up some of the stuff because some of the moves are just...
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a little tough for me to wrap my brain around it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yeah, it's a fun game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I played Dance Masters a little bit, or I should say I watched Dance Masters a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: The thing that's really frustrating about that game, although I have to say I didn't try the lesson modes, so maybe that breaks it down a little bit more, but...
[SPEAKER_04]: It basically says, okay, go.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then it starts doing stuff and you start messing up because you don't know what the hell you're supposed to be doing.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you just act confused.
[SPEAKER_04]: Unless, of course, you've played lots of Parapar and you know some of the Parapar dances, in which case there's at least four songs you'll be able to do just fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the rest of them are just very confusing.
[SPEAKER_04]: A lot of songs from DDR.
[SPEAKER_04]: A ton of songs from DDR.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everything from the Parapar songs to Sakura, Exotic Ethnic, Let the Beat Hit Em, Keep on Movin', Higher...
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm trying to think of some of the other songs that were in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yeah, a lot of DDR stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: And honestly, as Rob was saying when he was actually looking at the game, the game looks a lot better than Dance Central.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I was surprised.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dance Masters is actually a better looking game than Dance Central.
[SPEAKER_05]: The way...
[SPEAKER_05]: is a lot cooler than those little flashcards going up the side.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think the flashcards going up the side makes the dance, in practicality, like you said, it's easier to learn that way, whereas it's just kind of like throw it in and do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: But if you're just kind of trying to show off the poses and stuff, I think with the silhouettes collapsing in and the rings that show up, I think the game looks awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I think if you were to pull it off the way you're supposed to, which I know some folks might be surprised.
[SPEAKER_05]: They were expecting me to come on here and say Dance Masters is full of fail.
[SPEAKER_05]: But there's...
[SPEAKER_05]: Some interesting parts in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think the interface itself is pretty sleek when you're playing the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like the look a lot.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's interesting as far as some of the songs that are in there and stuff, because I think it'd be fun to see what the routines are for them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Obviously, and this goes for both games, there are some songs like, for example...
[SPEAKER_04]: Poker Face and stuff that I would feel like an idiot doing, you know, in real life versus, you know, some of the songs, you know, like Poison and stuff that have really good dance steps to them.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, obviously they have to simple, you know, have some simple songs in there so you can learn it because, you know, a lot of it's like, oh, I could do that, but it's actually really hard sometimes to figure out what they want you to do and you have to kind of do it a few times, Bill, to understand what you need to do in the game, but...
[SPEAKER_04]: Dance Masters.
[SPEAKER_04]: The other thing I don't like about Dance Masters is the actual menus.
[SPEAKER_04]: The way they have you navigate it is not very intuitive, and a lot of times they end up selecting things they didn't want to select.
[SPEAKER_04]: Was that Dance Central?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, Dance Masters.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have problems with Dance Central.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if that's just the Kinect device itself, but trying to select a song is a pain in the ass sometimes on Dance Central.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the thing with Dance Central, though, is you can actually use the controller to select stuff if you want to.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, didn't even try it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Derp, derp.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then other things... Can I say this real quick, though, about Dance Central?
[SPEAKER_05]: Some of those moves are kind of embarrassing, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is Dance Central.
[SPEAKER_05]: Again, we keep kind of going back and forth between the dance moves.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, they are.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's the easiest way to remember.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dance Central has real songs.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dance Masters has DDR songs.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, which...
[SPEAKER_05]: I realize some people consider them real songs.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't mean to spit in the eye of what we grew up on, but it's not music you're going to hear out in the real world.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you're a fan of DDR and you buy Dance Masters, you probably think, oh, originally, you're like, okay, well, I know para stuff is going to be in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: You think, oh, it's just all para-para dancing.
[SPEAKER_05]: well they have like a lot of songs from DDR and it was kind of cool to see a lot of that stuff on there but there's really only a couple songs that weren't in DDR or at least I didn't recognize in DDR I think though those of you guys that like grew up on DDR and have been playing for years and years ever logged into if you had an account on DDR Freak at any point in time go buy Dance Masters the rest of you get Dance Central that's that's really how it kind of breaks down
[SPEAKER_04]: Dance Central I like because a long time ago I actually took a dance class and the way they teach you how to do the different routines is the way you would learn it in a dance class, which is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I enjoy that game a lot more because you get an idea of what you're supposed to do, even though they do have the flashcards.
[SPEAKER_04]: If that's not for you, if you know the routine and you just want to do it, you can turn those flashcards off.
[SPEAKER_05]: anybody who's ever loved Para Para Paradise or even liked it you need to get Dance Masters because it basically is Para Para Paradise under a different name and just a different gameplay mechanic but like the Night of Fire dance is the same dance yes it is it's something remember like way back in the day I was like hey you know what would be kind of cool is if they had a para game with like different genres of music in there not just para para that's Dance Masters it's basically funny
[SPEAKER_05]: Let me go back to Dance Central for a minute, because Loki was talking about some of the embarrassing dance moves that happened in that game, and I'll tell you, I don't know if you've tried, have you played, you haven't really played the demo, or outside the demo, huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, not too much, no.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, I was playing the full version I was playing, there's a song by M.I.A.
[SPEAKER_05]: called Galang, and I don't know if you've ever heard this song, but let me play a little bit of it for the listeners here in, uh, listening to the song.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which, this is an awesome song, yeah, I really like this song, but like, the way you dance to this song, it's like you like...
[SPEAKER_05]: Dance Central?
[SPEAKER_05]: Dance Masters.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't tell them apart!
[SPEAKER_04]: Dance Central, I'm surprised that they didn't have that because they have all the moves broken down.
[SPEAKER_04]: You should be able to just order them in a way to create a routine and it wouldn't be that difficult for the actual on-screen dancers to follow it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dance Central...
[SPEAKER_05]: is very much a first game, as is Dance Masters.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, you have to go, okay, Dance Central is like the first Guitar Hero game, which led to Guitar Hero 2, which led to Rock Band and Guitar Hero 3, which led to where we're at now with Rock Band 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: So the potential is there for something really cool, but this first game is definitely like a bare-bones thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it'll be a hit at parties.
[SPEAKER_05]: Either one will be, really.
[SPEAKER_04]: It'll be pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: A couple reasons why I bought it.
[SPEAKER_04]: One, because it looked fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: And two, it was one of the games I was able to get early.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then also Kinect Sports, which I actually haven't touched yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I can't really give any impressions on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do still want to get possibly your self-fitness or your shape fitness or whatever the hell it's called.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just to try that out because right now I can't get out to the gym even if I wanted to.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's just no time of the day.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think it would be nice to have some sort of exercise program.
[SPEAKER_04]: And honestly, I would prefer getting the EA Sports Active 2.01 because it looks like it's a lot more structured.
[SPEAKER_04]: They actually have a nine-week program you can go through and a bunch of neat features for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Problem is, it's $100.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I really don't want to spend $100 on a game, even if it does work out pretty well.
[SPEAKER_04]: But...
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It'd be neat to just try that stuff because it looks like that might work pretty well.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yeah, I'm looking forward to more stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hopefully they actually start having indie games and Xbox Live Arcade games that support Kinect stuff and hopefully we get into some more different types of games other than stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I'm really looking forward to seeing the different genres.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because all the games that are launched are like dance, fitness...
[SPEAKER_05]: Interpretations of Wii games from their launch party.
[SPEAKER_05]: But we have yet to see how is Kinect going to affect Gears of War, if at all.
[SPEAKER_05]: Please hear me out.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not saying every game needs to have Kinect shoved in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: In fact, that would make me very disappointed.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I'm saying a Gears of War-esque...
[SPEAKER_04]: And now you think you need to go too crazy with some of that stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it would be neat to have a game where you play it on the couch, it just supports Kinect, but you're still using the controller.
[SPEAKER_04]: Say, for example, you're peeking around a corner or something, you just lean with your controller in hand, you lean to the side and your character peeks around the corner instead of you having to hit a button or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just really subtle stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think you need to actually flail around or something, but I think adding a little bit of extra stuff or maybe voice commands to different things might be kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just do it tastefully.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't have Halo Connect.
[SPEAKER_05]: And something you touched on a little bit there that I wanted to definitely mention and expand on a little bit is the more minority report style stuff that's in the Xbox Kinect, meaning that it will identify your face and sign you in.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have to calibrate.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have to go through this somewhat extensive calibration in Kinect ID.
[SPEAKER_05]: And for it to work really well, you have to do it in the daytime, in the nighttime, with all your lights on, with some of your lights on.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have to do it a few times.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, Rob, but...
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey girl, what it do?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, it's not going to do that, okay?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just like... But I will not have to pick up a controller at all.
[SPEAKER_05]: In fact, I have gone so far as to eject the game, put in the new game, walk away, and then I'll go Xbox, connect, close tray.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it knows who I am, starts and closes the tray.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, it's...
[SPEAKER_05]: Kind of scary in some regards, but neat.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to see that expanded on, though, because it's very limited right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's only very certain commands.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can't be like, Xbox, paint my house.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not going to know how to do anything but close the tray and go to your friends list.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then also, the fact that actually those voice commands work with pretty much anybody.
[SPEAKER_04]: My wife is yelling stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's like, I can hear a fear through stuff without...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: The nice little calibration cards that come with a lot of the games that are high contrast, black and white.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do they do?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's for calibrating the system.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have yet to use them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you can use it to calibrate the system.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a little smiley face, and it's placed so that the glasses are on the smiley face, and so you move it back and forth, and it calibrates the sensor to get distance or whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Where is that?
[SPEAKER_05]: In the dashboard?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: and then the little Kinect dashboard thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've done it once.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways, but that's not the point.
[SPEAKER_04]: The point is my son loves staring at that thing and just like plays with it and just like and smiling is so happy.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's literally his favorite toy now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, I'm just saying you could go get like a little piece of cardboard at Target for like 10 cents and a Sharpie marker.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can make a million of those.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I know that, but I'm just saying it's an added bonus.
[SPEAKER_04]: because they come with a bunch of them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I got it with it and it says, do not throw this away.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm like, what the hell is this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Do I have to hold this in front of the camera or something?
[SPEAKER_05]: And Bobby Blackwolf in our chat room is echoing you.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's in the Connect Tuner on the Connect Hub.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought I went through that setup.
[SPEAKER_05]: So there's a whole nother calibration I didn't even do?
[SPEAKER_04]: There's another calibration setup.
[SPEAKER_05]: God.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a lot of calibrating to do with this.
[SPEAKER_04]: But see, that's the other thing too.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's been working fine without all that fine calibration except the fact that I live in a tiny apartment and don't have a lot of space.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that only means that you can't play Connected Adventures two-player because it requires eight feet or whatever in order to play two players on that.
[SPEAKER_04]: A lot of the other games don't really give a crap.
[SPEAKER_04]: In fact, I'd say Jamie's living room here, that was maybe like six feet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it worked.
[SPEAKER_02]: It worked just fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had no problem with that little par-par-a.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it's just Connect Adventures, I think, is really... I don't even know if it necessarily needs that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just that they don't want you smacking into each other.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have you done the video chat at all?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's really creepy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Try it, because the Connect will follow you around.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, I was sitting in the chair.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, I wasn't actually chatting with anyone, but you can see your window.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then, like, if I stand up, like, the Connect follows me.
[SPEAKER_05]: And if I kind of move... Like, it follows you around, which is kind of creepy.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can only move up and down, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Marissa Congusto I do not want a system that hits on me or notices if I have gained weight
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, that would be a terrible one, wouldn't it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Xbox, connect.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, you might want to stop eating donuts.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought they were having a feature or there was something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe it was in one of those, like, you know, here's what it possibly can do.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, where I'm scanning my skateboard and that bull crap.
[SPEAKER_04]: Where, like, it could scan your image and it makes an avatar character out of that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, what's also going to be interesting is what future firmware updates will do because the technology is there now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now it's about really kind of squeezing out the potential of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm kind of curious to see what next year's update will bring because it's probably more of this stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Probably more like browsing.
[SPEAKER_04]: It won't probably be just like you'll be able to browse the marketplace or something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dance Masters fact sheet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently there is a lesson mode.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that would be nice because stepping right into the dance mode is like, huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anything else for your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, other than Xbox and Kinect stuff, well, actually, I played Rock Band 3 briefly.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just got around to it.
[SPEAKER_04]: One of my systems actually died on me, and I had it fixed, so that was nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I played, well, I spent a lot of the time just recreating my band, the, what was it, Unfit Barf Bags, because that was the random band name it gave me in Rock Band 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: And so I just stuck with it, and it was funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had to try that out, it was awesome I thought it was relatively easy for keyboard though
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, and of course, I didn't bother doing keyboards in normal mode because that's just retarded with the five keys.
[SPEAKER_04]: I stuck with the pro mode and just stick with easy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, if you actually want to be able to play things like Bohemian Rhapsody, you got to do five key.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, why can't you just play it on easy?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, okay, yeah, you can do it on easy.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, you can do easy in promo.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that's the way to do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've done a little bit of both.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, I can actually beat Just Like Heaven and Imagine on, like, expert pro keys, but it took a little while to kind of get there.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's cool that I can do it after practicing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had problems with, you know...
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: I had my hands too far to the left
[SPEAKER_04]: tried that tried a little bit of Sonic 4 Episode 1 on the iPod and it's terrible as I figured it would be thankfully I didn't buy it and what else oh yeah a little bit of Space Invaders Infinity Gene which I love that game it's pretty awesome that's pretty much it
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: Dance Central, which is fine, but the interface bugs me and doesn't control very well.
[SPEAKER_05]: But now that I know about this extra calibration stuff, maybe I need to try that.
[SPEAKER_05]: So now that I know, and knowing's half the battle, I'll try that a little more.
[SPEAKER_05]: But otherwise, the dances are kind of fun, and it's a pretty good workout.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that's the best thing about Connect, is that it's a good workout.
[SPEAKER_04]: They do have a calorie counter for the Dance Central.
[SPEAKER_05]: I noticed.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, oh yeah, I turned it on.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's good.
[SPEAKER_05]: The photo mode's a little creepy.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think I might need to turn that off.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't like being required to wear pants to play Xbox in my own house.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, with the Connect Adventures stuff, there's that ConnectShare.com website.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm afraid that one day I'm going to be sitting there playing with no pants on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Look, it's the privacy of my own house.
[SPEAKER_05]: Come on, guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know pants are restrictive.
[SPEAKER_05]: So sometimes you like to play with no pants.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was playing in my pajamas.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, that's what I'll do now because I am like deathly afraid that the machine is going to take a picture of me and like upload it to my Facebook without me knowing.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I realize this is a totally irrational fear and like, yes, these modes can be turned off.
[SPEAKER_05]: But come on, like it's like this part of technology kind of freaks me out or it's like suddenly, you know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Everybody's going to know if it's boxers or briefs.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's certain things that my Facebook friends do not need to know about.
[SPEAKER_05]: And what color I'm wearing today is one of them.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jumble, jumble, jumble
[SPEAKER_05]: Look, look, I swear I didn't even look at you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jessica Harper's in our chat tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hell, I'd play braless.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did I call it or did I call it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, the first thing that I did after Loki was setting up the connectors, I went in and put on a sports bra.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I didn't want to kill myself.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you, Jess.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jessica's backing me up here.
[SPEAKER_05]: My house is a bra-free zone, 100%.
[SPEAKER_05]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kitsune says, I don't want people to see me in my undies, so I got to make sure I wear pants.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the same completely irrational fear that I have.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, with this technology, the way it is, like, I need something in the intro to the game to assure me, hi, Rob, I promise I won't take pictures of you with no pants on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Then we'll be fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, as long as the Connect and I have that mutual understanding that we're not taking pictures, I'll be fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rob, now remember now, here's something to be afraid of, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, in fact, actually, I guess it doesn't really shine too much of a spot.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember those, I think they were Sony cameras, actually, that had an infrared filter mode or something like that, and people were using them to see through people's clothes?
[SPEAKER_04]: It might not matter with the Kinect camera.
[SPEAKER_04]: It will be undressing you with its lenses.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bobby Blackwolf says, to be fair, ConnectShare.com only shows your own photos or videos that you upload from the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can't find anyone else's stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's hackers out there, Bobby.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're hacking everyone on out here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hide your pants, hide your bras.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what I want, though, with the Kinect?
[SPEAKER_04]: The fact that it shoots infrared lights in a really neat pattern across the room.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want a laser light show, damn it, because it's already doing that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want it so that I can see it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, the Michael Jackson game that's coming out should do Michael Jackson laser shows, like the one I saw in Seattle last year.
[SPEAKER_05]: Am I the only one that feels like I should not look directly into the Kinect because there's that little red light that looks like a laser, which I'm sure is the infrared thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is a laser.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh my god, have you ever caught yourself staring right into it going, this isn't a good idea?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the mind control device.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Skynet.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like, wait a second, I recognize that red lint in your eye.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're Terminator.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sent back from the future to kill me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh oh, look what I started in chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Chat.orange.com Satellite minded.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're climbing in your windows.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're snatching your pictures up.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's exactly what I'm talking about.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh yes, other things I played this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: I also played Rock Band 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know I loves me some keyboards.
[SPEAKER_05]: My least favorite thing about Rock Band 3 is that there's not enough songs to play with the keyboards because I have like 300 songs in my library now thanks to Rock Band 1, Rock Band 2, all the download stuff which is a really obscene amount.
[SPEAKER_05]: I really hope they go back soon and add the key support.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, I know it's supposed to be coming, so I'll stop bitching.
[SPEAKER_05]: But that's the only thing that bugs me about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Otherwise, I think it's a fantastic upgrade.
[SPEAKER_05]: And if you own Rock Band 2 or Rock Band 1, drop the extra money.
[SPEAKER_05]: Drop the 50, 60 bucks and get this.
[SPEAKER_05]: The whole dropping in and out will be great for parties.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think the song select mode and being able to filter stuff is so much more intuitive.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think they really have learned.
[SPEAKER_05]: They have just created an incredible music game.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it really makes me go...
[SPEAKER_05]: What the hell are we going to get in Rock Band 4?
[SPEAKER_04]: And the sorting is awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is already blowing my mind.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, the sorting is outstanding.
[SPEAKER_04]: Outstanding.
[SPEAKER_04]: Real quick, just because it does kind of tie into the whole Kinect thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you think of the new dashboard?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's purpley.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not that different from the old one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Although, how much have they tried to kind of emulate the Wii?
[SPEAKER_05]: Right on down to the whole little...
[SPEAKER_05]: Little background noises that you hear when you're in the... Kind of what it sounds like when you're in the menus.
[SPEAKER_05]: And all the cuteness.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't like how white it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's been inspired from Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_05]: You got a problem with white things?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I do.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry to hear that.
[SPEAKER_05]: BlackWolf says they are adding Bon Jovi keyboard support this week, so they're going through the back catalog.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just impatient.
[SPEAKER_05]: So what if I have 63 songs to play right now?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not enough.
[SPEAKER_05]: Plus, some of the keyboard parts are really dopey.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, um...
[SPEAKER_05]: Is it Everybody Wants to Rule?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, that one, it's the other one.
[SPEAKER_05]: One of those songs, I always get the bands mixed up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tears for Fears is Everyone Wants to Rule the World, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: In Excess.
[SPEAKER_05]: Need You Tonight is the song.
[SPEAKER_05]: Has the dumbest keyboard part ever.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just 27 notes, even on expert.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's just do, do, do, boo.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that's the keyboard part.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do, do, do, wah.
[SPEAKER_05]: and so you're playing the wow like 27 times in the song it's ridiculous like you could beat it on expert and your score will be like 4700 tops this is funny
[SPEAKER_05]: but anyhow uh yeah um the game's fun and and the keyboard stuff will get better with the download packs and everything you know i'm actually like tempted to go find like a ten dollar copy of lego rock band just to import those songs into my massive collection i did i because i bet you can find them really cheap used now or not used uh with the code uh new new dude they still make it right
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I can probably find it on Amazon or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think it's dropped in price too much.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, I want to talk about a game no one's talked about yet, and then we'll get into gaming news.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know we've been doing this for a very long time.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's been a lot of games this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Pinball FX 2 came out on the Xbox Live Marketplace.
[SPEAKER_00]: Got it, by the way.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's free, which is awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: And if you owned Pinball FX 1, the game will go, oh, hey, since you were a loyal Pinball FX 1 user, I'm going to just import those tables right on into Pinball FX 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: and just all the different features that are in it now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Supposedly it does stuff with the Xbox Live vision camera, which made me laugh because now that everything's pushing Kinect, it's kind of funny that the vision camera's in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if it uses either or.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not interested in playing pinball with a camera, but apparently it will take video of you when you're playing on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_04]: I should try selling back my vision camera too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like five bucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here you can play Totem Ball.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Give you a nickel.
[SPEAKER_05]: But yeah, I was just very happy that all the tables re-imported and they have a more robust demo system.
[SPEAKER_05]: And yeah, just you can sense that the physics have been upgraded and the interface has been upgraded and everything has gotten a little tweak.
[SPEAKER_05]: We've been talking about Rock Band, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Same type of thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Pimbal FX Pimbal FX
[SPEAKER_05]: I look at a game like this and I go, with Game Room being in the state that it's in right now, I want Zen Studios to get Game Room.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want Microsoft to give that to Zen Studios because they seem to know how to do this whole microtransaction game within a game thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know what Microsoft has planned for Game Room long term now.
[SPEAKER_05]: If anything, they might just sweep it under the rug like they've been doing a lot of stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: But if they plan on keeping that going, I would love to see it go over there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Even though I think that studio probably has no interest in anything but pinball, but you never know.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's really it.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was it for my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't really have anything else to say on that, so let's get into housekeeping tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Join our Facebook, Facebook.com slash Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're also on Twitter at Twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think we have a MySpace, but really, who uses MySpace anymore?
[SPEAKER_05]: Is anyone on MySpace?
[SPEAKER_05]: Any MySpace fans?
[SPEAKER_05]: Didn't think so.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's get into some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll start off tonight with Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're only, what, 50 minutes into the show, finally getting to gaming news?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm totally on MySpace.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just kidding, I'm not on MySpace, because no one uses it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think anyone who's on Myspace just never deleted their profile two years ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, actually some pretty interesting stuff going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gran Turismo 5.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it's supposed to be out this week, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Right?
[SPEAKER_04]: No?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes?
[SPEAKER_04]: It didn't end up coming out this week, and it's been delayed again.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, they haven't really said when it's supposed to be coming out, other than just a few different comments based off of the producers of the game and what retailers are saying.
[SPEAKER_04]: For example, the creator, Yamauchi,
[SPEAKER_04]: Basically, it was telling the website, Japolik, that the discs were being stamped as we speak.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which I can tell you right now is bullshit, that the game has not gone gold, and I don't believe it's being stamped right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, apparently retailers are listing that the game is going to have a past Christmas release date.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some of them are showing a 1-1 release date or December 31st, which I can tell you right now is just a temporary date.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Just gotta wait longer.
[SPEAKER_05]: The more this is going on, the more I'm kind of like forgetting about this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's kind of sad because Gran Turismo is like a huge franchise and everything.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the more this is going on, I'm just kind of like, oh, there's all this other stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember when Gran Turismo 5 Prologue came out and it was supposed to be a taste of what the game was like?
[SPEAKER_04]: And now it's not even close to what the game is like?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember when they had, was it Gran Turismo 5, like, what was it?
[SPEAKER_04]: It was like Concept or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was the free download that was on the PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_05]: SatelliteMinded says in our chatroom at chat.ownershuntradio.com, do Gran Theft, or sorry, I was going to say Gran Theft, Gran Turismo 5 delays count as news anymore?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think in this case, yes, because they're missing the holiday season, if this is all true, which is pretty damaging.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, it is and it isn't.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think we've shown through this last year that games can do very well, even if released after the holidays.
[SPEAKER_05]: Case in point, Mass Effect 2 came out, what, like a week after the holidays?
[SPEAKER_05]: And it did fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: But still, to miss that holiday season, especially with such an epic, epic game, I think is newsworthy.
[SPEAKER_05]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Blowing my mind.
[SPEAKER_04]: I may have to take a day off work for that one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really?
[SPEAKER_05]: That big a deal?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm excited.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't even think I'm taking a day off for Cataclysm.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, going to other Sony news.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you know that the Tester 2 started this week?
[SPEAKER_05]: I did, and don't care The Tester 2, of course, you know, this is the sequel to The Tester 1 Which is Sony's original programming for PlayStation Network And, you know, it's been getting its share of crap And, you know, even though I myself am hazing The Tester 2 here on the show It's not as terrible as everyone makes it out to be It's just no better than, like, an average Bravo reality television show
[SPEAKER_05]: But is that as far as Sony wants to go?
[SPEAKER_05]: Possibly not, if you were to believe PlayStation Network director Susan Panico They want to go all the way That's right, she wants to go all the way Saying, quote, I hope five years from now we'll be winning Emmys for quality shows No, I'm sorry No one wins Emmys for reality shows It starts with a dream It starts with a dream, Loki
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: I will give them props to the fact that they are also a movie production house.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have the resources, I just don't see the tester as a good example of what can be done with those resources.
[SPEAKER_05]: It all starts with a dream.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Spastinator PSN in our chatroom says, there's only one good thing about the tester too, Adrian Curry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Need I say more?
[SPEAKER_05]: Really?
[SPEAKER_05]: She's in that?
[SPEAKER_05]: She is a hot mess.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, that might make it actually worth watching.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think she's a judge.
[SPEAKER_05]: That bitch is a mess.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, they don't have Hal Sparks this year or something?
[SPEAKER_05]: They have her instead?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because that, oh man, she is, let's just say she was very pro Prop 19.
[SPEAKER_05]: She was very sad, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: That didn't pass.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_05]: Satellite Minded says Sony will win an Emmy for PSN shows when GT5 comes out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, because I'm sure now she won't be able to do pot.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that was the only thing stopping her.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: That no vote really stopped everyone, I'm sure, California.
[SPEAKER_05]: Way to go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, you're right, though, that Sony has the studio behind it to make this work if they want to.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just that this I don't really see as the real motivator to get things going.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, you know, we'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_05]: What Sony should do is take some of the pilots that maybe don't work out very well or better yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's a great idea, Sony.
[SPEAKER_05]: Take shows that get cancelled before their prime.
[SPEAKER_05]: And if you want an example of this, just go to Fox.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because Fox always loves to cancel things before their prime.
[SPEAKER_05]: And get the rest of the episodes and put them up on PSN.
[SPEAKER_05]: Especially, like, can you imagine if something like PlayStation Store had been around when Firefly was on TV?
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, hear me out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, I know there's Whedon nerds that listen to this show.
[SPEAKER_05]: so imagine like Fox cancels Firefly but Sony is smart enough to know oh there was actually this really strong cult audience for the show somebody's already paid to make this show let's just buy the rights to put them on PlayStation Network and have it be ad supported and then that would just draw you know and then maybe it finally finds its audience in this on-demand network like that could be huge now I don't think Firefly was a Sony studio show I think I don't know Universal or yeah but
[SPEAKER_04]: but anyway just take that idea and apply it to maybe a really good show that Sony might have had or here's an idea since you've got you know you like doing television programming and stuff like that make your own IPTV channels you know actually have some different channels of content on there that are exclusive to the PlayStation Network and say maybe you have to pay a $5 a month fee to access this stuff that would be kind of neat you know oh so Hulu
[SPEAKER_04]: No, not necessarily.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's an on-demand type thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm talking about actual content that's like a live network where you can tune in at a certain time and watch something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not, oh hey, I want to watch old episodes of this and go.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, well, we'll see what happens with Sony programming later on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe they'll announce an expansion at E3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_05]: But I would expect that Xbox is going to announce a success for the 1 versus 100 first.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, wait, they did.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I don't think it came up anywhere on our show roll tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you hear about this?
[SPEAKER_05]: Just quickly, I've got to throw this out there.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a new game coming out for Xbox that is that whole 1 versus 100-esque type of thing, the massively multiplayer game.
[SPEAKER_05]: it's a poker game which I'm kind of like sick of poker games too many of them does he really?
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean there's an audience for it it's an easy game to learn it'll have an audience I'll try it once not interested unless it's strip poker and even then I probably wouldn't be interested and now with Kinect that's possible Kinect poker now you can Kinect in a whole new way DarkSakura what do you have for us?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we have something regarding Apple.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have filed a patent that looks like it's going to be an augmented reality game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It has something on there for targeting and using a real-world interactive game environment.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, yeah, from what it looks like on here, it's going to be so you can shoot people.
[SPEAKER_04]: In the face.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it even has a mention of a gun attachment for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I really don't know what they're doing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it could be maybe laser tag, or it could be that they're just filing it so that no one else does it, or it could be, you know, a money shot game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, I just can't help but think of that thing we played on the show a couple weeks ago from The Onion that was just the shoot people in the face over and over game and then it was like cute furry animals too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, this won't be controversial at all if you can shoot your friends in the face.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe it can be like Ink Blaster.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right, right, red ink.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, red ink.
[SPEAKER_02]: You got red on you.
[SPEAKER_05]: They could also just be patenting this so no one else can.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what my thought was.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, that's all I got to say on that.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, other interesting things.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently, with the new dashboard, and this is totally not unexpected, they are actually going to be implementing new features to try to stop piracy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Unhackable.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let me guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some mucky muck up there came out and said that you can't pirate on this thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have made this hack-proof.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think anyone said anything about it, but basically they have a new series of checks that they do for disks, which I guess hackers are referring to as AP 2.5.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess that work in conjunction with security sectors embedded in the disk.
[SPEAKER_04]: If the checks come back negative, the player receives a dirty disk error, and his or her console is flagged for permaban.
[SPEAKER_04]: It says pirates, though, can hypothetically avoid these checks by not updating to the new firmware, and though this will prevent them from playing on Xbox Live, which kind of defeats the purpose of avoiding the permaban, it
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, apparently, one, if you're burning a copy of the game anyways, you could just delete the update on it, so that would bypass that, because not all games that have the new firmware attached with them actually require that firmware to run.
[SPEAKER_04]: And also, if you have a JTAG console, you can just plain delete the update anyways, and that way you can avoid actually...
[SPEAKER_04]: you know having to update your system of course well if you have a JTAG you can't update it anyways
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, look, Microsoft has a right to protect their assets, and I get that and everything, but are they bragging about it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Did they come out and say?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: Digital Foundry did.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, then, you know, it's to be expected in this case.
[SPEAKER_05]: The only thing that gets me is when they come out and say, oh, well, this system, we put measures in this to make this unhackable, and it's going to do this and this.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's just an open invitation for people to say, please hack me.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: and then they can get past all those checks.
[SPEAKER_04]: And replacement drives are only about $20.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but that's a lot of work.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's not a lot of work for someone that's really determined.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, yeah, but how many people are that determined?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've spoofed a drive before because I've messed up flashing a firmware on there.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's really simple to do.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yeah, I mean, you'd really have to want to play burn games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you know, I'm sure we're going to continue to hear news like this as more of these firmware updates come out.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's really no surprise that half the time new firmware updates are too dressed.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's always a back and forth.
[SPEAKER_04]: They'll figure out a way around it and they'll come out with something new and they'll figure out a way around that and so on and so forth.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, well, let's move on to something a little different, and this has to do with the iPhone slash iTouch slash iPad, the iOS family of games.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a brand new service from Capcom out there.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a free-to-play iPhone arcade app.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's called Capcom Arcade.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is free, and you can play Street Fighter II, Commando, Ghouls N' Ghosts in 1942.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ooh, ah, but here's the catch.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just like Game Room in the sense where you can get tokens to play games for 99 cents or you can pay three bucks for unlimited access.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or, here's the best part, you get three free plays per day.
[SPEAKER_05]: So if you just want to download and play three times a day, free!
[SPEAKER_05]: Yay, go get it.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's the subbie from just changing the date on your phone?
[SPEAKER_05]: I have no idea.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not that desperate to play more Street Fighter 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I played that game until my fingers were bleeding back when I was like 12.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll play it once and I'll go, hee hee, this sure controls like ass on my iPhone, but it was fun to try.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's really what it's going to be.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because let's not forget, they make terrible controllers.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the one thing that's really stopping iOS from moving on is the lack of something tangible right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: But hey, I'm all about free, even if it's just three times a day.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll get as much of that out as I can.
[SPEAKER_05]: But where's Quiz and Dragons?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what I'm waiting for.
[SPEAKER_04]: Keep room for updates.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, what do you have for us?
[SPEAKER_05]: We have release dates coming up right after this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Classic Game of the Week, not that far away.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, this sounds really cool and something I'm actually thinking about participating in is that Capcom's forum has these contest rules.
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically, until November 22nd, you can do your own artwork for Marvel vs. Capcom 3 and if it basically wins...
[SPEAKER_02]: Then you get an Xbox 360 and a couple of Marvel vs. Capcom 3 and a framed print of your own work.
[SPEAKER_02]: Make sure it's not dirty.
[SPEAKER_02]: And your work gets to actually be in the Marvel vs. Capcom 3 art book.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I don't think that my stuff is all that fantastic, but it'd still be fun to participate.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess if you have artistic talent, which won't be me.
[SPEAKER_05]: When they do the voice actor thing, then I'll try, but for now...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Playstation 3, Xbox 360, and PC
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a version for the Wii, but really isn't anyone going to play it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I'm sure DS sells a lot of Call of Duty Black Ops.
[SPEAKER_04]: Other fun things coming out this week, of course.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know there's more Kinect games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yay, more?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, more.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, actually...
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll see here.
[SPEAKER_04]: God, I hate the new site that they have here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you know, you could always prep these things in advance.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course not.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's talk about other things that are not necessarily Kinect games, because there's a lot of those, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've got to mention all of them, because everybody wants to know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um...
[SPEAKER_04]: Chuck E. Cheese's Playhouse, a crappy game for kids, and that's on Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: Noah's Ark, also on the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: Chuck E. Cheese's Game Room on Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nickelodeon Fit on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's really for little kids.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rudolph the Red-Nosed Reindeer, that's right, the one that's claymation that they have each year.
[SPEAKER_04]: They based the game off that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's on the Wii and DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: Family Feud, decades coming out on the Nintendo Wii.
[SPEAKER_05]: What the hell is Family Feud Decades?
[SPEAKER_05]: Is that like where you get Richard Dawson from the 70s?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ray Combs from the 80s?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's much simpler than that.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have families dressed up like different cliches of decades.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is the cheapest cash-in I have ever heard in my life.
[SPEAKER_04]: Monster Jam Path of Destruction on the Wii DS, Playstation 3, Xbox 360 and they actually do have bundles that include a steering wheel even one for the Playstation 3 but not for the move you'd be surprised to find out it's actually for the stupid DualShock 3 because I guess the game uses 6 axis steering
[SPEAKER_04]: Just Dance Kids.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is also another game for little kids.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Just Dance with the wheels on the bus go round and round and other things like music from the Wiggles and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_04]: Definitely not something that our age demographic of listeners would be interested in.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, Karaoke Revolution Glee.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have a bundle coming out on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: This game gives me nightmares.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Honda Fever.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's basically just a repackage of another game that came out that sucked.
[SPEAKER_04]: Beyblade Metal Fusion.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess this is actually a series that's still on TV, but they have that game coming out on the Nintendo DS and the Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, and I guess Monster Jam Path of Destruction came out on PSP as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: This has got to be the worst game I've ever seen.
[SPEAKER_04]: Reload Target Down for the Nintendo Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is a game where you test fire guns.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a game.
[SPEAKER_04]: You don't shoot people.
[SPEAKER_04]: You target shoot with guns.
[SPEAKER_04]: Style Lab Fashion Design Hasbro Family Game Night Challenge Me Brain Puzzles 2 Nintendo DS
[SPEAKER_04]: Remington Super Slam Hunting North America on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, let's see here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remington Super Slam Hunting Africa on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: My Sims Collection with both My Sims Racing and I believe just My Sims.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tom Clancy's Hawks 2 on the Wii finally coming out now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rune Factory 3 of A Fantasy Harvest Moon on the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently they're doing an ESA game pack.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is something that they do every year.
[SPEAKER_04]: Usually a certain game manufacturer will actually put out a collection of stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: This one comes with Uncharted, Drake's Fortune, Tomb Raider, and Mercenaries 2 for $29.99 and all the proceeds I believe go to charity for that to the ESA if you want to support that and some really old ass games.
[SPEAKER_04]: SingStar Dance, a very terrible add-on to the SingStar series.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is on the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Fight lights out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Seriously, do not buy this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was terrible.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's got horrible reviews.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really do not need this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Sly Collection, that's coming out on PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a recreation of, or I guess, HD versions of the old Sly Cooper games, and the third one's actually in 3D as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ah, yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Man, there's a ton of crap coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Digging for Dinosaur on Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: Zuzu Pets has some more games coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Kungzoo on Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just going to skip past a bunch of this crap.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess Harvest Moon is being re-released on Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, same with... They're doing a lot of re-releases on stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rune Factory 2 is coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're re-releasing that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think there's probably a price drop.
[SPEAKER_04]: Same with the first one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Releasing all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: The new Xbox controller with that wonderful fixed D-pad is now coming out this week for $65 if you really want to buy that.
[SPEAKER_04]: and then a few things one week from today Mario vs. Donkey Kong Miniland Mayhem coming out on Nintendo DS and then also one week from today will be the potential for a new Mario Paint U-Draw tablet with U-Draw Studios will be coming out and then of course the two games that go along with that Dude's Big Adventure and Pictionary and of course that's that tablet thing that looked like the Mario Paint type pen tablet thing
[SPEAKER_04]: and then of course Pictionary is also on Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Finally, jeez.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, there's a lot of crap going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, no, I know it's holidays.
[SPEAKER_04]: And emphasis on crap.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's go to Japan and see what's coming out over there.
[SPEAKER_05]: On the Xbox 360, Forza Motorsport 3 on November 11th.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is the Ultimate Edition, by the way.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mushihima-sama Futari Version 1.5 is the Platinum Collection.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why do you want this so bad?
[SPEAKER_05]: This is a shooter game, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_01]: It is, and it's a really cool shooter.
[SPEAKER_01]: And there's also the iPhone version adventure game coming out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, Dragon Ball Raging Blast 2, Mafia 2, and Scared 2 Fallen Angel.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also getting a price reduction.
[SPEAKER_05]: Those are all on the Xbox 360 this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: What did I say?
[SPEAKER_05]: Scared.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, my bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, Sacred 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like a game called Scared 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Scared 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: PlayStation 3 has Biohazard 5 Alternative Edition.
[SPEAKER_05]: That would be Resident Evil 5 with the move.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dragon Ball Raging Blast 2, Mafia 2, Scared 2, Fallen Angel, Shinsengoku Musou Online, Soten Ranbu comes out this week as well on the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is the online version of the one where you kill everything and smash the button.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's like seven of those games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dynasty Warriors, is that it?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's that, but online.
[SPEAKER_05]: What was the one?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, Dice Wars Online.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it's that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Moving on to other systems.
[SPEAKER_05]: On the Nintendo Wii in Japan this week on the 11th.
[SPEAKER_05]: The 25th anniversary Mario game comes out over there, as well as the Nintendo Wii in some different colors.
[SPEAKER_05]: Something called the Party Game Box 100.
[SPEAKER_05]: Use your imagination.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wii Remote Plus controls in all sorts of different colors.
[SPEAKER_05]: Black, blue, pink, red, white, Wii!
[SPEAKER_05]: Puyo Puyo 7 gets a price reduction.
[SPEAKER_05]: No one care.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jinsei Game, Happy Family gets a release as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: Speaking of things that we don't care about.
[SPEAKER_05]: PlayStation 2 gets one game this week called Shinkyoku Sokai Polyphonica After School.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can only guess what this game is going to be about.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll give you a hint.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a girl in a school outfit on the cover.
[SPEAKER_05]: Porn?
[SPEAKER_05]: Puyo Puyo 7 Tamagotchi
[SPEAKER_05]: Caru Batake de Tsukamete Portable Caru Batake de Tsukamete Portable
[SPEAKER_05]: and it actually is not that although it looks like this game stars plenty of bukkake people that you'd probably want to see in a bukkake porn I'm just kidding they're kids that's gross alright what's wrong with you what's wrong with you how about it
[SPEAKER_02]: Call of Duty Black Ops Dance Central, Dance Paradise, Dance Evolution, Dance Masters, Fighters Uncaged, Game Party In Motion, The Connect, Connect Adventures, Connect Joyride, Connect Sports, Connectimals, Motion Sports, Connect Adventures, Your Shape Fitness Evolved,
[SPEAKER_02]: and also Raving Ravage, Travel in Time and Sonic Colors, Tom Clancy's Hawks 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's all I'm going to say anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: See, I like how you filter the crap out.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry, I don't understand what you're talking about.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just messing with you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_05]: A couple more stories in the Classic Game of the Week.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to filter all the crap out.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll just mention one game the next time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stop.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, this week only comes out when we're going to filter all the crap.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is Chuck E. Cheese.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is the only game coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, Xbox Live Indie Games has disappeared off the main marketplace menu and you actually have to dig for it now.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's in specialty shops.
[SPEAKER_04]: By the way, it's not that hard to find, you guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is a couple menus deep, but it's not impossible to find.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I understand why people are pissed.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, I'll shut up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, so it is now under Specialty Shops.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, Avatar Marketplace being the first spot on there.
[SPEAKER_04]: But Indie Games is a close second.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, of course, Xbox Live Indie Game Creators are bummed over the fact that the menu has been slightly hidden, if you will.
[SPEAKER_04]: and I don't know it's just they kind of feel like they're being brushed off I guess I don't think it's that big a deal to be honest
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_05]: Imagine if they had something like Windows Media Player with a store in it where it wasn't just the music and movies, but things that you could download to your Xbox.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or maybe like when you download a movie, it would download to your PC and your Xbox.
[SPEAKER_05]: But within that, they could do like this whole indie games thing, kind of like iTunes does.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I could kind of see that being kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: at the same time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe it's too much work.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe they're trying to sell this whole Kinect thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they haven't opened up Kinect to indie developers yet, have they?
[SPEAKER_05]: Probably won't for a long time.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't remember if they have or not.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think maybe Xbox Live Arcade, but not, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ross Steel UT is in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is it really?
[SPEAKER_05]: Ross Steel UT, I haven't seen him in like two years.
[SPEAKER_05]: The indie games aren't any less easy to find than they were before.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're just butthurt.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well...
[SPEAKER_05]: yeah I mean I didn't find them particularly hard to find and I think again if you sell yourself on the web you'll be fine I can understand though where the developers are feeling a little bit unloved but keep in mind there's a lot of things at Microsoft right now being unloved Game Room's another one everything's all about the Kinect Kinect Kinect Kinect Kinect Kinect maybe after the holidays they can focus on that other stuff again but we'll see although I somehow wouldn't be holding my breath
[SPEAKER_05]: Something you know is inevitable, though, and is going to happen is a Bejeweled 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right, Bejeweled 1 and Bejeweled 2 are some of the biggest freaking games ever made.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bejeweled 3 is coming out on December 7th.
[SPEAKER_05]: And my wife didn't care.
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought Bejeweled was the only game she plays.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's like, what are they going to add to it?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm like, well, they have this new poker mode thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's like, that's dumb.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, wait until she tries.
[SPEAKER_05]: There are also, just so you know, new Quest and Zen modes are coming to the game, unlockable secret game variants, and there's also supposed to be smoother gameplay and new music and sound.
[SPEAKER_05]: $20 if you want to get it through PopCap.com, but I bet you'll have to wait not even six months and it'll be out on iPhone and Xbox Live and PlayStation Network and pretty much anything with a controller or touchscreen.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll have Bejeweled 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: by the way, Zuma Blitz is supposed to be coming out very soon as well too I think that's in beta right now so lots of new games coming out of Pop Crack what about Plants vs. Zombie Blitz?
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess I shouldn't hold my breath on that one hey, it's the time of the show where we take a stroll down memory lane and allow Dark Sakura to take the reins for a little bit oh, we must be crazy
[SPEAKER_05]: Dark Sakura, what is the classic game of the week?
[SPEAKER_02]: The classic game of the week is Marvel vs. Capcom Clash of Superheroes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ooh, ah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I got a big excited girl boner for Marvel vs. Capcom 3 today.
[SPEAKER_05]: A bit of Ladywood.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we have to start off with the characters that came out of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is my favorite music in the game, for the record.
[SPEAKER_02]: So yes, the game is the fifth of the Marvel Comics licensed fighting games.
[SPEAKER_02]: This one actually, instead of being just an X-Men vs. or Marvel Super Heroes vs. Street Fighter, this goes all over the place.
[SPEAKER_02]: and you have to basically get all of these people against Onslaught who I thought was actually kind of a retarded character in the comics but that's just me.
[SPEAKER_02]: So moving forward we have this one is where you actually have a random assist character that you start off with bringing one of your teammates in which I think they've gotten rid of for Marvel vs. Capcom 3 and
[SPEAKER_02]: Then, you know, there were also ways that you could select who your little bonus person was.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then you also had duo team attacks.
[SPEAKER_02]: This music is awesome, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the theme of Strider 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's not in Marvel vs. Capcom 3 so far.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: So far.
[SPEAKER_02]: I said so far.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought he was.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was like, why not?
[SPEAKER_02]: But no, not yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: So anyway, the different characters in this one is you had Spider-Man, Captain America, Hulk, Wolverine, Venom, Gambit, War Machine, Gold War Machine, Red Venom, Orange Hulk, and Onslaught on the Marvel side.
[SPEAKER_02]: and on Capcom you had Ryu Chun-Li, Zangief, Mega Man, Jin, Morrigan, Strider Hero, Captain Commando, Roll.
[SPEAKER_02]: You should play Roll's music now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lilith or Shadow Lady.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love Roll had singy-songy music.
[SPEAKER_02]: As in his...
[SPEAKER_02]: As far as your special partners, you've got Unknown Soldier, Lu and Siva, Saki Omokane, Pure and Fur, Psylocke, Michelle Hart, Iceman, Arthur, Tonpoo, Juggernaut, Devilot, Thor, Magneto, US Agent, Cyclops, Storm, Colossus, Anita, Jubilee, Rogue, Shadow, and Sentinel.
[SPEAKER_02]: At least gave the nods over.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dude, Tonpoo, that was just cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I laughed.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, at any rate, there is a perfect version that came out on Dreamcast in 1999, and it had cross-fever mode, so you could have four players play simultaneously.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, there was a version that came out on the PlayStation, which is the EX edition in Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: but it didn't have the tag team gameplay and it didn't have the secondary characters except just for assists but it did have the crossover you could play a tag team with identical teams which was kind of stupid but it did allow you to play as Onslaught and if you beat the game with well that's I think if you beat the game with Mega Man or something
[SPEAKER_02]: And yeah, the soundtrack came out, which I've got the soundtrack, and it is amazing.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it was great, and it opened the door for all this other funness.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course, Dan got me hooked on playing with Strider New Year.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is other good music.
[SPEAKER_05]: Everyone should recognize that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yep, the theme of Mega Man.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a great game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Definitely one worth having on the Dreamcast because it was perfect.
[SPEAKER_02]: Marvel vs. Capcom 2 is really good.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm looking forward to Marvel vs. Capcom 3, but I had to start it with somewhere and I think this is a good place to do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's as good of a place as any.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yep, so that's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's your classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, there it is, your classic game of the week, Marvel vs. Capcom 1.
[SPEAKER_05]: Back before, there was all these other sequels, and now this new fancy one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Although, I gotta say, the videos I was looking at online for the new one, and even seeing it at E3, although it looks like it's come a long way, just even in the videos I've been seeing online, pretty awesome, gotta say.
[SPEAKER_05]: Looking forward to it.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, we're going to take a break.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll be right back, though, guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: Stay tuned.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have plenty more show to come.
[SPEAKER_05]: We got our rapid-fire news, of which there's a lot, since we have to make up for last week.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're also going to talk a little more about that whole Kinect hacking stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have another story on that coming up in a minute.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to talk about Fable 3 and Saints Row as well on the Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_05]: So don't go anywhere, guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: We will be right back with more of Orange Lounge Radio right after this.
[SPEAKER_05]: And welcome back everybody to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: We are taping the 388th episode of our show live on this November the 7th of 2010.
[SPEAKER_05]: We've been talking a little bit in Part A tonight about the new Kinect obviously is out and we've all had a chance to get our hands on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which is weird because I still have yet to really play PlayStation Move outside of E3.
[SPEAKER_05]: But Loki, you've gotten a chance to get your hands on both at this point now.
[SPEAKER_05]: What do you think...
[SPEAKER_05]: Both are going to offer us in a year's time.
[SPEAKER_04]: The move, I think, is going to pretty much be what you see right now with the Nintendo Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: The only difference being that since they do have the camera in there, they can do some of the augmented reality stuff, which is actually pretty cool with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: um I don't think it's really that different and they do um I don't know they have more of a setup now where they're going to kind of use it with more of their hardcore games I guess because like Killzone 3 is already going to have that SOCOM 4 they've got support for it so it'll be interesting to see how they implement that stuff or if you know it's even going to be necessary or you know you're going to be able to play as well with it
[SPEAKER_04]: and then of course the Kinect it's hard to say how that's going to really I think there's a lot more potential with the Kinect because they can pretty much do whatever they want with no controller gaming but then they can also if they wanted to and they've said it before they're like
[SPEAKER_04]: You know we can have this so that it works with you playing, not using the controller, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, the complaints, oh, there's no buttons and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like, well, who says that we can't do that or put out another controller later or, you know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, so there, it's, I think there's a lot more creative freedom with the Kinect than there is with the Move.
[SPEAKER_05]: What do you think this says or is going to do anyway about the possible Xbox 720, the PlayStation 4, the Wii 2, and obviously all these names are hypothetical.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, but if you notice, and I'm not sure if this is necessarily because Microsoft's spending more money on advertising.
[SPEAKER_04]: because they are spending a lot of money on advertising.
[SPEAKER_04]: But have you noticed, like, with the whole Kinect stuff, there's been a lot bigger of a splash with the Kinect stuff as far as, like, all the, you know, talk shows and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, absolutely.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then there was the movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: The movie just, like, came out and, like,
[SPEAKER_04]: It's here, guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: They had commercials.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's mostly of what you've seen for the move and targeted commercials during things like South Park.
[SPEAKER_05]: You'd always see a commercial for the move.
[SPEAKER_05]: Things of that sort.
[SPEAKER_05]: But yeah, definitely the Kinect is definitely trying to go that Nintendo route of being on Ellen, being on the news, doing the whole Times Square thing that they did.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to be very interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course, Nintendo gets to go through this whole hub-a-loo again with a 3DS because that's going to be another big thing that, you know, they'll parade that out on the Ellen show too and she'll go like, wow, it's like I could really see 3D guys, you know, and the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some corny joke.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ooh, let's dance.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: That'll be what happens.
[SPEAKER_05]: So.
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh, go to our chat room at chat.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actdeft says, I think the next Wii will be a Super Wii.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's certainly a possibility.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, that might be a silly idea, but, you know, the Wii has that recognition, just like Nintendo had back in the day as a system.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then there was the Super NES.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, that whole Wii HD, everyone likes to theorize about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh, and Frisbee follows that up with, and then the Wii 64.
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh, Ross Steel UT says, the Kinect is more novel than the Move.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's be real.
[SPEAKER_05]: You agree?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the other thing, like I've said... Sorry, I don't mean to cut you off, but I think it's more something we haven't seen before.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, it is and it isn't.
[SPEAKER_05]: It feels like more of an evolution than the move does.
[SPEAKER_05]: Although, the technology behind the move sounds pretty cool compared to what we've seen on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_05]: We just don't see a lot of that in motion yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: But this whole augmented reality and all the stuff you talk about makes me very excited.
[SPEAKER_05]: The potential.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's the other thing too.
[SPEAKER_04]: The augmented reality stuff...
[SPEAKER_04]: is possible with the Kinect.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, who's to say?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because it can track your body.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's to say you can't, I don't know, even just have a game come out and have something as simple as you hold up a piece of cardboard and there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it just has to have something like a target for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it basically uses the sensors that are in the
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, move controller and the orb to track that.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, you... There's potential they could do all the same stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, you know, it has a good, you know... It can track you really well, as we saw with, you know, Dance Masters, where it can do a literal... Almost like a green screen of myself while I'm playing the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not that I really want to see that, because that's very... I feel like an idiot already, and looking at myself playing the game, it's just like...
[SPEAKER_05]: Why are you doing this?
[SPEAKER_05]: Let me ask Jamie here for a minute.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't mean to take you away from our lovely chatters.
[SPEAKER_05]: The chatroom at chat.orange.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I know you don't get as into the new stuff, I think, as you have the classics.
[SPEAKER_05]: You definitely, the most room in your heart is for the classic games.
[SPEAKER_05]: What do you think about this new, I mean, certainly this is technology we never really saw before in the classic gaming world.
[SPEAKER_05]: What do you think about the Kinect and the Move and all this and its potential impact on gaming?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think the move looks like a sex toy, so I'm completely not interested.
[SPEAKER_02]: Connect, I like.
[SPEAKER_02]: I really do.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that it combines everything that they were trying to do with the move and with the eye toy, except it doesn't write.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it definitely gives you more of that virtual environment feel to your games.
[SPEAKER_02]: That, I think, is great.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that...
[SPEAKER_02]: I can see it going two ways.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can think we're going to get more and more and more like that and it'll be great or it will wear off after a while.
[SPEAKER_02]: The novelty will wear off and people want to sit back on their couches with their controllers in their hands.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like half agree with DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_05]: I kind of...
[SPEAKER_05]: The Kinect, there's some things about it that strike me as gimmicky too.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, and I think it's that we haven't really seen its full potential yet, whereas at least Sony's kind of like throwing these things out there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, I don't write off the move quite as fast, but I will say right now, there's nothing I really want on the move.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's nothing the move is doing for me and the type of games I like right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a lot of possibilities for things they can do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember the whole head tracking demo that we saw with the Wii where they have the guy wearing the Wii remote?
[SPEAKER_04]: You can do that with the Kinect because it tracks your head.
[SPEAKER_04]: They can do that kind of stuff for first-person shooters.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's why I was saying that it's not necessarily...
[SPEAKER_04]: you don't have to have a game where you're just moving around like crazy they could just have it where they track your head you're doing all your movements and stuff on the controller and you can still be slightly more immersed in the game and it can be an optional feature which is kind of cool you can bring the mocap games home yeah
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm really interested to see what next year's E3 is going to be because at next year's E3, all of this is going to be the norm.
[SPEAKER_05]: The 3DS is going to be out by next E3 and all the rumors about the March release date or what have you, but it'll be out before June.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a given.
[SPEAKER_05]: All of this stuff is now going to be the norm at NextE3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Move is now out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Connect is now out.
[SPEAKER_05]: 3DS is now out.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's going to be really interesting because the NextE3 is now going to be all about, okay, now what are you going to do with this?
[SPEAKER_05]: Now that it's out, what have you come up with in the past year for how to use this technology?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to be a very interesting show.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm really excited about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Even though it's like, what, nine months away?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to go this year.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hopefully we can make it all work for us.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know, I was just thinking, I still, if you put both in front of me and said pick which one you want for free, I'd grab the Kinect.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think me too, but only because it goes back to the rule of the system is only as good as the games that are on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I wouldn't write the move off yet, because a year from now, we might be looking at the opposite.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's just kind of what I see.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not sure I really see where Kinect is going, but maybe I'll be proven wrong at the next E3.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think, if anything, if the whole point of releasing these new motion systems were to capture...
[SPEAKER_04]: The new audience that they're looking for, the more casual audience, I think that Kinect has done a better job of that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or at least it seems like it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because the move, I don't think a lot of people care.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's too bad, because it's not a bad piece of hardware, it's just not...
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just slightly better, and yeah, granted the hardware is better, so you can do better looking games, but it's not completely different.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whereas I would say the Kinect is completely different than what they're doing with the Wii and the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is separate.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I think one thing to consider as far as new hardware goes, I don't think it came up anywhere else in our show role, but something that's been coming up.
[SPEAKER_05]: This was a lot the week we were out, but were those rumors of the PSP phone and some of the screenshots that showed up and all that.
[SPEAKER_05]: So if this new PSP evolution is going to be shown at E3, it could be interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I don't think it's going to be anything outside of this whole motion gaming stuff and what we're talking about here.
[SPEAKER_05]: But we'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, let's move on into some rapid fire news and some of the quick stories we have for you now.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have a lot since we had a week off.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, Loki, we're going to start with you with a quick news.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Twitter topics.
[SPEAKER_05]: Get them in quick.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have about two more minutes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: So anyways, some interesting stuff going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, we were talking a little bit about Dance Central and Harmonix being the ones that like to support download content.
[SPEAKER_04]: They had some download content day one, whether you like that or not.
[SPEAKER_04]: New songs that are coming out for Dance Central are going to run you $299 or $240 Microsoft points each.
[SPEAKER_04]: and Sean Paul's Temperature.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I guess those are all available now and hopefully we'll see some more download content next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_04]: It didn't really say if the same moves are in there or if they're recycled or whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I think it's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_04]: I really wish that the game had kind of a routine editor because they could easily do that with the flashcards and stuff they have on there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can anyone say the sequel?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, Black Friday is not too far away.
[SPEAKER_04]: And with Black Friday, of course, the ads will leak out.
[SPEAKER_04]: The first one to leak out with gaming-related information, of course, would be from Sears.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they had some new bundles and stuff for the holidays and some new interesting colors for different things.
[SPEAKER_04]: For example, the limited edition red and green DSi bundles for $150, which include Mario Party DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: They've got a 160 gigabyte PlayStation 3 bundle for $300, which includes Uncharted 2 and a Blu-ray of the new movie Karate Kid.
[SPEAKER_04]: PSP... What a deal.
[SPEAKER_04]: The PSP 3000, well, I think those two games are free.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, just the whole Karate Kid Blu-ray.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not a bad movie, I liked it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just refuse to see it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm being stuck up for no reason.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was good, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: The PSP 3000 bundle for $130, which includes LittleBigPlanet and UMD of the Karate Kid.
[SPEAKER_04]: 4GB Xbox 360 bundle for $200, which includes Halo Reach.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's not bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, they had $10 off of a standard, I guess, Wii bundle.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then, um, also they're going to be doing, um, discounts on different games like, uh, Medal of Honor, Fable 3, Halo Reach, all will be available for $40.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um...
[SPEAKER_04]: which is pretty awesome and actually this is kind of cool one of the games that's being marked down to $40 which will be just coming out about around that time Need for Speed Hot Pursuit so if you're interested in that game which you should be because it's by Criterion and they do really awesome racing games you should definitely check it out
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just saying, Loki, that of the Smith kids, I think Willow is more talented because she whips her hair back and forth.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: The movie was not bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: I liked it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whatever you say.
[SPEAKER_04]: I enjoyed the movie a lot.
[SPEAKER_05]: Isn't it the Kung Fu Kid?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is the Kung Fu Kid.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_04]: They think we're dumb, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, and then of course, with that, there's some new Xbox demos that came out on the Marketplace this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rock Band 3, which is pretty awesome, so you can check out a few songs from that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apache Air Assault, which is a helicopter attack game that's coming out on the 360 and PS3 in, I believe, next week or so.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then, the most retarded addition to that would be Joyride, which...
[SPEAKER_04]: If you have the Kinect, you'll realize that there is already a demo for Joyride on the disc of Kinect Adventures.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why you would need to download an additional demo is beyond me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have at it, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yeah, definitely check out those demos if you haven't yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dance Central, Joyride, Your Shape Fitness, and yeah, I believe that was it on there.
[SPEAKER_04]: But hey, three games you can check out for free.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I didn't notice that right away, and it said other games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm like, other Kinect games?
[SPEAKER_04]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm like, oh, there's demos on here?
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome!
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my gosh!
[SPEAKER_04]: so yeah check that out and then finally I don't know this is kind of ridiculous but apparently with the Wii version of the Michael Jackson the experience game you're going to get the jewel studded white glove to play the game with I guess so that you can feel more like Michael Jackson is it possible to think something is lame and yet totally awesome at the same time like this is totally awesomely lame
[SPEAKER_05]: It's so bad, it's good.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's bad, it's bad, it's really, really bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, what I would pay to see Loki modeling one of these Michael Jackson gloves.
[SPEAKER_04]: I may have to get the game when it comes out for the Connect.
[SPEAKER_05]: I gotta say, it actually looks kind of awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's face it, Michael Jackson had some badass songs, and you know there's gonna be good dances.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just...
[SPEAKER_04]: Just Dance with Michael Jackson songs and with optional karaoke.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't give a shit about the optional karaoke, but I think that would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: I fucking love Michael Jackson's stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't care what people say that he did or did not do.
[SPEAKER_04]: He was an awesome music artist.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm with you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just ignore all the other stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: He has some new songs coming out, apparently.
[SPEAKER_05]: their rumors are saying that there's a sound like doing some of them but who gives a fuck everything that's been going on with like Tupac and Biggie when they were you know gone before their time and yet it seems like Tupac is still releasing a new album every other year from some shit they dig up expect it to be even worse with Michael Jackson like there will be a new album every year for as long as you're alive and then there will soon be the rumors about he never really died they fake the death and the body that came out of the house wasn't really him and
[SPEAKER_04]: and all this stuff he did it to escape his personal problems even though his kids were up there on stage crying and two more songs apparently have been announced for the game one of which is my wife's absolute favorite Michael Jackson song one I kind of like, Speed Demon and Dirty Diana Dirty Diana her absolute favorite song that's one of my favorites too you know what, my favorite actually isn't one of his dancey ones Man in the Mirror
[SPEAKER_02]: She's out of my life.
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, we need to have a whole Michael Jackson The Game launch party.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I just don't think everyone else would be as into it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just don't want to get in on the weed.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think the generation after us, too, which makes up a lot of our listeners.
[SPEAKER_05]: They have terrible taste in music, okay?
[SPEAKER_05]: They weren't around when it was about Michael Jackson on MTV.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, we literally grew up with him.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know?
[SPEAKER_05]: This is different.
[SPEAKER_05]: I remember when Thriller was on every hour.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, he and my mom were the same age.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, you know, I went through all of her old stuff and I grew up with the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, anyhow, let's move on and talk about other gaming news.
[SPEAKER_05]: You Don't Know Jack.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh god, I love this game and I'm so excited it's making a comeback.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because they did kind of burn that series into the ground.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like there was all these You Don't Know Jack games back in the day.
[SPEAKER_05]: You Don't Know Jack, The Ride, and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Those are actually kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: But