Orange Lounge Radio
Who's the host?
Dark Sakura
Sky and Loki
Tonight, November 21st, 2010
Layoffs and downsizing hit four game studios
Developers pay a premium to create the 3DS
And did Nintendo give away a prototype version of a classic game?
Orange Lounge Radio
Hello my friends out there on the internet
And welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio
The video game podcast where every gamer has a voice
We do tape live and for all the information to listen to us live
Visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com
We are live here on this lovely Sunday evening
6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern
My name is Rob Roberts
I'll be working with you over the next few hours with my co-host
The one and only Dark Sakura
Hi
Hi, how are you? Dark Sakura?
Jamie Summers
I'm alright
Happiest bunny on the farm?
You seem like a little bit of a sad bunny tonight
I am a little bit of a sad bunny but it's alright
Do you want a hug? I'll come give you a hug
I prefer the chocolate ones, thank you
You need candy
Alright, well I hope some discussion on video games will help brighten your spirits
You know, I had a terra-bad week this week
I mean, it was really awful
Was it bigger than a giga-bad?
It was a terra-bad, actually
That's what I was saying
It was
Yeah, but I did the other show
Because now I'm juggling two shows just like you
And that actually put me in a lot better mood
So podcasting hopefully will brighten your spirits
We'll see
Cool, I was watching V before you came over
New V or old V?
New V
I stopped about halfway on new V
Not because I hated it
It was hard for me to watch TV every week
I caught up on Supernatural so I was just sitting
Marathon-ing stuff because I didn't feel like doing anything
I heard a lot of people that kind of like watch TV while they play games
A friend of mine on the WoW guild was telling me about how he was leveling to 80
While watching Arrested Development on Netflix
Fun
So, yeah, good times
Alright, say hello as well to somebody who will hopefully make us laugh tonight
If not, he's fired
No, just kidding
Say hello to Techmaster Loki
Hello
How are you, Loki?
I'm fine
Alright, what's new in your world?
Anything new, fun going on?
Not much, just eating bad for me pizza
Alright, is your mic even on?
We are having a real hard time hearing you tonight
Did you plug me in the wrong hole again?
No, you're good
I just, we just had to get you angry in order to hear you, I think
No?
I don't, it's very quiet
It's very, very quiet
Live radio, some of the perks
We'll try and fix his stuff all in one
Fix me now!
No, you're definitely fixed now, alright
Everybody's just all quiet and somber tonight
Must be the weather
The weather changing is
I call it complete and utter apathy
Last night was, was it thunder, I was in the bay
But it was thunderstorming, like crazy
It was fantastic
It was a light the candles type of day
I love rain, I love rain a lot
But the whole problem with rain is that it makes me intensely homesick
And also nobody can drive in the rain
Is the other big problem
Nobody from here
No, yeah, big problem with the rain
Alright, if you've never listened to Orange Launch Radio before
I haven't given this spiel in a while, so I'll just say hello
If you've never listened to our show before, we do tape live
And the three of us here, Dark Soccer, myself and Loki
We all met playing video games at the local arcade
It was Dance Dance Revolution, ironically enough
Was the game that brought us together
So for a long time we did a show about music games
And, well, things evolve, things change
And now we're podcasting about all the video games that are out there
From the classics, Atari 2600, NES, Sega
All the way to the new stuff on the PS3 and 360
We like to talk about the news and talk about it with you guys
Cause, you know, we, we know you guys are smart
You go on game blogs, if you subscribe to this show
You probably read the big game blogs
You already know a lot of the news
But we like to talk about it and discuss it
And get your perspective
And to do that we always have the present fourth guest on our show
The chat room, chat.orangelaungeradio.com
But of course we're also gonna take calls later in the show
There's our Twitter, our Facebook, and all that fun stuff
But we do always start off the show with a little bit of
How was your gaming week where we talk about the video games
You've been playing this week
Dark Soccer, how was your gaming week?
Um, kind of, not much of anything
I played Star Trek Online for like an hour this week
And, yeah, oh, Angry Birds
The game is retarded and fun
Why do you think so many people are into Angry Birds on the iPhone?
Like, I have to admit, it's not a game that's ever really interested me
But it seems like everybody is playing this game
Because pigs aren't kosher
Okay
You just, you fight evil pigs
Oh, I see, I see
And they're not kosher
So I kill them
By toppling bricks on top of them
Until they poof and die
And they get all beat up and bruised beforehand
So it's really great
And you've got chickens that explode
Poor piggies that can't defend themselves
Aw
Um, well they're idiot pigs anyway
Um
Maybe that'll be the sequel to Angry Birds, idiot pigs
I found my Digimon
It's way dead, but I found my old school Digimon
Was that, did they actually
The brick looking ones
Like, that were like the Tamagotchis?
Yeah, but they could connect
I never knew they had those
I always thought Digimon was just like a Gameboy game
Well, and an anime
Yeah, but they were actually made from
I think the same company that did the Tamagotchi
Or something like that
But anyway, you could connect the two end to end
And they would battle
And uh
It finally is dead, we finally just got rid of it
We cleaned out a lot of stuff in the house
I was gonna say, the battery must have given out after all this time
You leave a battery in something way too long
Then it just goes bad
Um
We've got rid of a lot of stuff
But we're also sitting aside, I guess, some swag for people
I guess
And
Yeah, that's about it
Oh, we picked a Brad Racer
Did I say that already last week?
I don't remember
Did you get some Elite 3D glasses to go with it?
No
And uh
Yeah, that's about it
That's really about it
Alright
Loki, how was your gaming week? What have you been playing this week?
Um
Not as much as I was going to
But I played basically Grand Theft Auto
And some of the Kinect stuff
Like I was demonstrating the Kinect things for a few of my
Fellow employees
So a little bit of Kinect Adventures
Which is
You know, not surprisingly
Very boring, you know
So many times I can play the River Rafting game
Or even the other games in there without going
Eh, whatever
I've been playing more Dance Central
Which is pretty fun
Playing some of the more difficult songs
Which aren't that difficult
But it's just different
So I was playing Jungle Boogie a little bit
And um
Yeah, more Grand Theft Auto
That's pretty much it
I've played some of the iPhones
You know, iPod stuff
But uh
Not really anything worth mentioning
Just like, you know, I've played a few games of
You know, the Stick Wars stuff
Um
I haven't got a chance to play Rage yet
Um, because I went
Downloaded it
Synced it with my iTunes
And somehow it deleted the game
Off my iPod
And in iTunes I'm like
And I also have Lego Harry Potter
Where I haven't played that yet either
Is that the one that's supposed to use Kinect?
Like, I knew there was a Harry Potter game that uses Kinect in some fashion
No, Lego Harry Potter, it's the one on
The iOS stuff
Oh, I'm sorry, you're still on iOS
No, no, no
There's a Harry Potter in Deathly Hallows Part 1
Okay, that's what I was thinking
And it has like a little on rail shooter portion
That you can use Kinect for
But apparently it's really dumb
Well, it's early
Tech demos turned into games
It's still tacked on
Hey, you know what, it's better than nothing
You know, they could have just done nothing
Do you find yourself
Yourself still playing
Kinect a couple weeks later?
Because I kind of stopped
Um, yeah, Dance Central
I've actually been playing Dance Central
It's pretty fun actually
And funny enough, I got some of my other employees into it
They were like really
It was surprising
I didn't think they would try Dance Central
I had one of my co-workers playing Just Dance
This guy, you know
Purple Belt and Tae Kwon Do
And stuff
Just not
The person that would be playing
That song
You know what, there's no shame in having fun
No, not at all
Even if the song's a little fruity, it's fun
He thought it was hilarious, so
Yeah, it's fun
The problem really is
I don't have room to play it
So I play it at work
We have our game room
I guess, it's in a conference room
So I take the conference room table that's split in two
And I push one to one end of the wall
One to the other end of the wall
And it gives me a good ten feet
By ten feet space that I can actually play in
You don't know how lucky you are to be able to turn
In your conference room at work into like
A gaming hotspot, it's amazing
To me
Yeah, I guess
That's part of the deal
I guess, so
Anything else?
Yeah, that's pretty much it
I had a pretty dramatic week
In World of Warcraft
I won't get into all the details
The good news is I don't have to subject you guys
Now that I have the spin-off show, I don't have to subject you guys to all the talk anymore
But I'll say it was a very traumatic week
Because my authenticator reset itself
Yeah, I don't know how it happened either
But I had to make a phone call to Blizzard and all that
At least you didn't swallow yours
No, what happened?
Some person swallowed their authenticator
No, mine's on my iPhone
And somehow it just reset
And I couldn't restore it from backup
None of it would work
It would just give me the new serial number
And you can't input your own serial number
So, it was weird
And then Wednesday, my guild got the first
Kill of the Lich King ever
But I wasn't there because I had to drop out of the raid
Because Comcast kept cutting out on me
And so, yep, wasn't there
So anyway, I won't get into all the details about it
It's on the other show, Horde House now
That's kind of odd
Now I don't get to go on these long Warcraft tangents on the show anymore
You can still go on the tangents
Now I feel like I'm spent, I already went on that tangent
I don't want to do it again
So yeah, it was an interesting week in Warcraft
But let me talk about other games, because there were other games I was playing as well
Maybe I wasn't playing the Kinect games so much
But I did kind of go on this demo downloading
Binge of stuff I've just kind of missed on
One of those games I checked out was
Super Meat Boy
Which, actually was kind of cool
Like, the demo is very robust for that game
I get the sense it's a flash game that's been converted somehow
But there's a lot, well it's Newgrounds
So that was kind of a sign right there
But it had a surprising amount of depth to it
One of the mechanics I really liked is that
You know, you're on this Mario style map
Doing all the little challenges
But when you get an A plus on a level
Meaning you beat the level within the par time
You can hit a button to go to the dark side
And you can hit a button to go to the dark side
You can hit a button to go to the dark world
Where you play the stage again
And it's like the exact same map
Only harder
Like maybe there will be more saw blades out now
Or more enemies
So I thought that was kind of a neat mechanic
And one of the things I really like
Is that the game plays very fast
Every stage is meant to be beat in like under a minute
And some of them are literally like 10 seconds long
So it's almost like micro games
But you might have to play the round
Like, not even kidding
50 times
To get the rhythm just right
To time that jump just right
So you can kind of get through the gap
And do like a jump around
You know what I mean when you jump to the right
And then push control over the left to get around an obstacle
You know, you kind of do all these weird sorts of things
But what I like is that when you finally beat the level
You get to see an instant replay
But the instant replay isn't just
The replay of you beating it
It's the replay of every single attempt you made
At the level all at once
And you'll see like 50 little meat guys
All jumping and you see them all dying
It's actually really clever
And a really neat game mechanic
And I'm sure I've got to have seen this somewhere before
But I can't think of anything
So I was very surprised at what a robust demo it was
And I was very pleased with it
And I do plan on buying the full game
I would have never guessed this was a game that interests me
Because I'm going to be honest
And this is going to sound really weird
And I should be made fun of for this
And I'm okay with that
But the gameplay and the artwork
Of like that red case with the weird
Funny green toothy thing
Made me, honestly
I kind of looked at it and went, what's this super meat
That sounds stupid
That game sounds stupid, that looks stupid
It's kind of amazing how much judgement
I passed on this game, really not knowing dick about it
And I was wrong
I can admit that
But at the same time
I was a little kind of turned off by
Why didn't you try to like
I don't know, put a little more
Into the retro
Jokes like on the box art
Or something, like that whole like red gritting
Face just was a little silly to me
I don't know, I'm sure
I'm not even looking at chat because I'm sure I'm being
Taunted for being irrational right now
But it did kind of make me step back and go
Wow, you do kind of put a lot of thought
Into even like what's on the front
Of a box
As to whether I'll pull it off the shelf
And I realize this is all happening virtually
I'll pull it off the shelf and read the back of the box
So, kind of interesting
So again if you want to go
Chat.orangelaunchradio.com you can join us
Okay now I'm being brave and reading it there
Um
Let's see, uh
Sorry I'm reading this live here
Dark Tetsuya says
Don't forget Alien Hominid was a Newgrounds
Game too, that's true, that was kind of a cool game
The Castle Crashers, was that a Newgrounds?
It was the very same style
Very similar style
Only Hemeth did that and they had done
Alien Hominid, I think that's the deal
They've done Alien Hominid, yeah
So
So I played that and I definitely want to pick up the full
Version of that, I also played Pac-Man Championship
Edition DX
Which I thought was kind of a worthy
Upgrade based on the demo I played
You know, more maps
Different skins looking thing
But they also made a couple big changes to the mechanic
That make it worthy of an upgrade, one of them is
Bombs, which I know sounds very weird for a Pac-Man
Game, but how often
In Pac-Man do you get trapped in a corner
Where there's a ghost coming one way and there's
A ghost coming the other way and you're like, oh shit
I'm fucked, now I realize that's the whole point
Of Pac-Man, but this being a sequel
You get to try new things, so now you have
A bomb and you can hit this bomb and it
Blows the ghost out of your way
So you can get through, it's
A simple thing that kind of adds
A whole new level to it, I don't want to say it makes it easier
But now you can
Get yourself in different situations
Than you were able to before, if that makes sense
The other thing that's kind of cool
About the game is that you have these like
Sleeping ghosts, we'll say
These ghosts that just stand in place and don't do anything
Until you go right next to them
And once you go right next to them
They'll wake up and start to chase you
But they chase you in a very
Logical pattern, like they just keep following you
And if you do this right
You'll get like 30 ghosts
All in a row, and then pick up a power pellet
And you'll just go chomp chomp chomp chomp chomp chomp chomp
And you'll just rack up a high score there
So I thought that was kind of a neat new
Mechanic, so just a couple new little twists
Kind of breeze fresh life
Into a game and I thought it was pretty awesome
And the music was really cool
So yeah, I gotta say
I haven't read on the net
What the reception is to this game, I don't know if people
Are saying unnecessary copy or whatever
But I gotta admit, I find the
Few little twists
To really kind of bring new life
Into what was otherwise a game that you know
Was, you know, it's been on the iPhone
And the Xbox
You know, we've kind of seen it
Several times over the past few years, so
I thought that was cool, so
Go to our chatroom at chat.orangelandsreader.com
Salacious Pop says, it's amazing
The music alone, if you use a bomb
On a chain of 40 plus ghosts and they all fly back
Into the base, it's a very epic satisfying
Feeling, that's very true
I agree with that
Black Wolf is clarifying an earlier comment I was saying
Castle Crashers used Newgrounds for the music
At least, that makes sense
There was, definitely
A lot of those games have the same look
And feel and so forth
Another game I checked out on Xbox Live
Again, these are all demos and I always feel weird
About reviewing demos, but a lot of these were very
Robust, and I think
Still
When you're gonna put a demo of your game
Out there, you're kind of putting
It out there to be, to have
Your entire game judged, should I drop
$10 on this, yes or no
I feel somewhat justified in that
Salacious Pop is reminding me
I also played Guang
Guangi?
I don't even know how to pronounce this game, but I did play that
On Xbox Live, and
I know we have a really diehard
Shmup fan in the chatroom that's gonna really hate me
For this, but I didn't get it, I didn't get it at all
I liked that it was
Different, but I didn't understand
What the hell I was doing, it was just bullets everywhere
Ahh!
Apparently there's reskinned modes, but they're not really in the demo
It was just the first level of the arcade game that was in the demo
I had no idea what the eff I was doing
You know, not being the big
It seems like a lot of the
Cave shooters that they're bringing over
No offense, it's like
You could like
Randomly show me different, you know
Video from a bunch of different ones
They all look the same
Well, but to be fair, Loki, this game wasn't
The same, and that was kind of what
I will say I liked about it, because
What was cool about it is that
For one, this character I was playing
You didn't just fire bullets, but you had a
Wolf that you moved around the screen
And bombs would fire from
The wolf or something, I don't know
But it was a different mechanic
So it didn't make it feel like every other shoot-em-up
So I don't think you can say every shoot-em-up
Is the same, it's just that
Because maybe I was
Expecting to understand it
Because I played a lot of other shoot-em-ups
It was really confusing to me
At first, but I don't know
I don't know
Um
Anyhow, that was
That was the game
If I spent more time with it, I'd probably enjoy it
Or if I was more of a fan of the
Shoot-em-up games, and really understood
What was so different
I should have spent more time with it, really
But again, demos were supposed to sell me on the full games
And after playing the demos I did
This week, I'm like, I'm more interested in going back
And playing more Super Meat Boy, which I never thought
I'd say a couple weeks ago
They have that
To internets on there and stuff
That they unlock new levels
Every now and
Every once in a while without sort of
Updates, I guess
Did you say Super Meat Boy? Oh, no
I wasn't aware of that, that's cool
It seemed like there was a lot of
People
Ray in our chat room is a little irritated
At what Loki just said
I could say the same of any genre
All MMOs are the same
All genre are the same
Yeah, but I'm saying that the actual artwork
Looks very similar game to game
I'm not saying all shooters are the same
That doesn't make any sense
I'm saying that these games play very much alike
Like, I played a bunch of different cave shooters
And they play very similar
I'm telling you, this doesn't play like the other ones
Oh, big deal
It's a different thing that they added in there
It was different
Because you could kind of
Fire at the bullets and stuff
I don't think
People should pass judgment so quickly
It's still fun, I'm just saying
At least try it out
They're not like night and day
It's not like comparing
A Gradius game with
Ikaruga or something like that
Two games that have very different
Looks to them
Maybe similar
Types of gameplay, obviously
Ikaruga would be a lot harder
I don't know
Maybe it's just because they're all done with spray
Animation and stuff like that
It just seems very
Similar
You could show me one of those games and be like
Oh man, that was a cave shooter
I don't know
I don't get it
Why even bother having any storylines in it?
There's no point, really
And the last demo I played was for
King of Fighters 2002
Which, um
I didn't get it
I actually played the Neo Geo fighting franchises
Past Fatal Fury Special
I think was about the last one
With the exception of Capcom vs SNK
Which is still amazing
The problem is the demo only limits you to
A handful of characters
None of which I recognized
And all I did was I button masked
The chick with the whip
And I think her name was actually Whip
Yes, her name is Whip
And she's on Team Ikari
Very creative
No, she's actually a really cool character
And if you're good with her, she's really effective
But I always use Leona
But who you can't pick in the demo, I don't think
I would have recognized her, so I don't know
I didn't get a good feel for that one from the demo
She was on the same team with Leona, Clark, Ralph
Haytern
She's, I guess, Ikari themed
In the one I played, you were picking teams
You were picking individuals
But I'm saying that her story
Her character comes from the whole Ikari team
Alright
That's awesome
They did a Marvel vs. Capcom game
But Capcom vs. SNK
Do it in that style again
Now I know that they've had Capcom vs. SNK
1 and 2 and stuff
But the crazy over the top style
That is Marvel vs. Capcom
Would be awesome
Because I'm sorry
Just plain as the Metal Slug characters
I know they have
An SNK game that came out
I think it's already out
In Xbox Live Arcade
That's a port of an arcade game
It's like Neo Geo
Battle Colosseum
That has a bunch of those different characters
But it's just not
It's not as cool as
Or fast as
Marvel vs. Capcom or something
So that's pretty much all the games
I played this week that are worth mentioning
Although I did play Knights of the Clicky
Clicky Vampire Sorority Life
Farm Town Wars
That too
It's so sad
Facebook games really are the future
And there's really no depth to this game
But aren't the boss fights really cool?
They do these little cut scenes and stuff
That makes the whole game worth it to me
They're alright, you're in my party
You're shaking your head disapprovingly Loki
You don't like Knights of the Clicky Vampire
I haven't played it
And I'm not going to play it
I support you in that, it's fine
I really should not play that
Because if people support games like that
They're just going to keep making games like that
Well I don't give them money, and I will not give them money
And Alan always teases me
Like, you know you want to buy Squeenix coins
Just to get yourself this stupid armor
No! No no no no
And he knows how I feel
No, I'm not spending money
Rob, I have to go do something
Orange lunch foodie-o related
Make some orange soup
My soup is orange
And what's the soup of the day?
Actually it's soup that I made
It's soup that I made
Butternut squash sweet potato pumpkin soup
With curry and ginger spices
With shaved onion zucchini and squash in it
And I made it, it's delicious
Thanksgiving is definitely right around the corner
It is, and we have to roast a turkey
We haven't done turkey before
Are you doing the dinner this year?
No, but we have to contribute another turkey
So I'm making the stuffing for it
And I have a total recipe in my head
For cranberry apple stuffing
Cornbread stuffing
Because cornbread stuffing is the best
I'm officially sick of bacon pizza by the way
I noticed you did not bring bacon pizza
To the show tonight, it was like mushroomy pizza
Or was it actually bacon?
No, that is bacon pizza
They burnt the crap out of it
Yeah, thank you
That does not look appetizing
And I actually asked for quadruple bacon pizza
But she's like, triple bacon?
I don't think they understand more than three
If anyone wants that, I'm not worrying that for you
Um, no, it's
It's a little much, it's very heavy
I believe Loki is finally admitting
There is such a thing as too much bacon
No, it's just because
I didn't have the correct dipping sauce
I wanted a side of ranch
Well, ranch in round table speak
Is the creamy garlic sauce
The white sauce that they put on pizzas
But some round tables decide
Hey, you know what, we're gonna get some shitty ranch
We're also gonna call that ranch
Or creamy garlic sauce as well
And it's just not as good
Now if I had that, it would be so much better
What you should tell them is that next time
That they make it, is to put your bacon on first
And then put the cheese on top of it
So that the bacon won't burn
Because the oil from the cheese will saturate the bacon
And prevent it from burning
It's like our own little Paula Deen right here in the studio
It's not so bad even with the burnt bacon
It's just, it's too much
I cook
Don't look at me like that, cause I love Paula Deen
She's a frightening looking lady
Because she totally looks
Both botoxed and surgicaled
And still looks
Really scary old with those
Overly
Terrified looking eyes
Paula Deen is like the Cher
And you're like the Christina Aguilera
It's because she's preserved her body
With all that fat that she
Takes in
I mean, my god, she's like
I need to put a stick of butter in this one
Put a stick of butter in there
I seem to recall this was a video game podcast
I don't really remember
This is getting back to video games
I'm just going to make my dinner
I'm just saying that I'm probably going to stick to like
Cheese pizza or the twist
The twists are damn good
You know, have you thought about maybe like a salad?
I don't like salad
I've tried salad on multiple occasions
The only salad that I can tolerate
Is like a Caesar salad
And even then, I know that's way not good for me
I just do not like the taste of
Plants, okay
It's just, it feels very unnatural
It's like a cow trying to tap dance
It just, it doesn't feel natural
Eating plants, what do you think our ancestors
Had to do back in the day?
Well, we've evolved past that now, okay
Why do I have to eat the damn plants?
The animals that I'm eating right now
Have eaten those plants
Alright, look, we gotta get into
And since the pigs, they probably ate garbage too
But you know what?
I'm not going to eat garbage
Alright
Housekeeping, before we get into news
We will still have a show next week
I know the holidays are canceling some of your favorite
Podcasts, but thankfully, Sunday
Is kind of a nice day to be on
So we will still be bringing you new shows
Tonight, obviously, and next week
We're not going to have any time off for the holidays
We're working hard for you guys
Because we love you
Also, if you want to love us on Facebook
Facebook.com slash Orange Lounge Radio
Please consider joining our little club there
On Facebook
And everybody likes to like things, so
Yes, so you should like us on Facebook
Which I think is actually what you do
You don't actually join, you just like
Because if people can like things like Chase Bank
Or, you know, Miracle Whip
Then they can like our damn show
Or RuPaul to host
Saturday Night Live and all that stuff
Although that really should happen
No, it shouldn't
I'm sorry, he's not, she's not funny
What?
Stop the show, stop the show
She's not funny
RuPaul is amazing
And you need to, have you ever watched
Drag Race, have you ever watched Drag Race
I've seen an episode
Then sit down and shut up, because you're saying no
In a creative way, you're saying no
I'm sorry, it would just be weird
It's funny, it is
Funny, drag queens are
Funny
Alright, fine, then if you bring RuPaul on there
You need to have at least more than one
Drag queen on there, because
Just a show about
Nothing but drag queens competing to
Be the biggest
Cunt of them all
Well that's not Saturday Night Live, that's why I'm saying
You need more drag queens on there if you're gonna bring her on there
Those guys dress up as chicks all the time
On Saturday Night Live
This is the only video gaming podcast
Where you will hear
A very straight guy arguing
With a very gay guy about drag queens
I'm just saying
RuPaul needs a video game
You know you want it
I'm just telling you
If they made a game for Connect called
You better work
Okay, I get it
See?
And you know you want RuPaul being all
Alright, let's see that dance again
And don't fuck it up
But Rob, alternate costume has to be the suit
From Drag U
And we could
It could film you on the Connect device
But then like as you do better
It just starts to put like
Costume parts on you, it'd be really funny
And then we make Loki play it
And take pictures and upload them to the interwebs
Hilarity
That's up there with Tingle
Alright, anyhow
Loomis
Just join chat
Just to tell Loki to get a sense of humor
Hahaha
Oh, Loki
Alright, also Twitter
Twitter.com slash O-L-R
Not Twitter.com slash RuPaul
Just saying
Alright, let's actually get into some video game news
Which I'm only trying to make you laugh
Because the news we have is very depressing
I think it's funny
Not me
You are rude
That's hilarious, Bizarre Creations
Is terrible
It's like, hey, you know what
We decided to have a really terrible idea
And release a Bond game
That's based off of no movie whatsoever
And we're gonna pimp out Daniel Craig
In it again because we apparently
Own the likeness of Daniel Craig
For a long time now, that's why he's also
In Goldeneye
But yes, Bizarre Creations
They've done some pretty awesome things
And some pretty terrible things
Awesome being their racing games
Project Gotham Racing Series
Cooler, terrible being
And Geometry Wars
Yes, Geometry Wars, the awesome
Racing game
What the hell, you need to listen
No, Geometry Wars is an amazing game
Stop interrupting me
No!
Yes, you shut up
Other things that were awesome
Non-racing
Geometry Wars
Terrible things that they've released
The Club
Yes, they're
No, The Club, their shooter that wasn't
Quite good
And of course, James Bond
Bloodstone, which
Not very good, but it also has some driving in there
But driving apparently is better than the Bond game
Anyhow
So they're getting closed down
Because apparently
They aren't making enough money for their pimps
At Activision
And
Apparently they're giving them a 90 day period
Which I guess
Is serving as notice to the
Employees that their company is likely to be
Closed, sold, downsized, etc.
And apparently
Activision says over the past three years since
Our purchase of Bizarre Creations
The fundamentals of racing genres
Have significantly changed
Although we
Made a substantial investment
In creating a new IP
Blur
It did not find a
Commercial audience
Mind you, that they're
Still keeping the Tony Hawk
Ride franchise around
Even though that's
Incredibly terrible
But, you know, Blur
A racing game that probably had a decent
Following, just not exactly, you know
Tony Hawk
Ride numbers, maybe
Which I do know that they sold more than Tony Hawk
Ride, by the way
And then of course
Other developers and whatever
And there is a chance though
That they may be purchased by somebody else
Obviously
Because Project Gotham Racer is an awesome
Series
It's funny how they sucked when they were bought
By Activision, but they were still pretty awesome
When they were with Microsoft
Could it happen to be maybe
Activision is to blame?
Hey Jamie, knock knock
Who's there? Interrupting cow
Boo!
That's all I know how to do is interrupt people
Well you weren't
Listening, obviously, because you're like
Hey, guess what
Geometry Wars was awesome
Hey, listen
I just feel, you know, that's
Right, it was an awesome game
But it wasn't an awesome racing game
Which is what I was talking about
Well maybe it should have been
Maybe they should have had Geometry Wars racing
Blur was actually kind of like that
A little bit
Shoot him up and the whole little like
Art thing going on with it
Honestly, when I saw Blur
I couldn't get
It wasn't very interesting to me
SplitSecond was more interesting to me
And, well, part of the problem with Blur
Is that it came out like the same week
As SplitSecond
ModNation Racers
And, you know, while Mario Kart is still selling big
You know, and
It's just kind of unfortunate, but
I don't know
Does our creations really deserve to bite the bullet
I think you hit the nail on the head
They were doing fine until Activision bought them
Well, Activision, they're like
Hey, you know, we need you to make some better stuff
So we're going to have you do a James Bond game
Honestly
I can't think of a James Bond game
Since Goldeneye that has sold well
And those are the ones
Normally based off movies
This was based off of nothing
So, their excuse was
Well, you know, since there's a lawsuit
Going on right now with the James Bond
Licensing and stuff
So, hey, this is the closest thing
You're going to get to a new movie
Well, that's great and all
Except no one cares
And
I don't know
It was just a terrible idea
Another company
Also taking some cuts
Thanks to Activision is Budcat
And Budcat
Of course, they were
One of the developers that was acquired
To work on a Guitar Hero franchise
And of course, it says
Approximately 88 positions
Or approximately 1%
Of our global workforce has been
Affected by the layoffs
So that's
1% is not bad, I guess
It says Budcat though
Is comprised of roughly 60 people
So
I don't know
It's interesting, I guess they were saying
They're doing
They're targeting
Reduction in jobs
For its QA department
I guess that makes sense
Because, I mean, they hire
And fire people for QA all the time
Based on
You know, the games that are coming out
Although
Some of those games
Probably should keep the QA department
Around a little bit longer
Not necessarily just with Activision
But companies like Bethesda
Might learn too
By keeping more QA around
You won't release buggy ass games
Like Fallout New Vegas
And Activision, they're saying
We continue to streamline our music
Development resources to ensure that
They are aligned against our slate
And strategic goals
As a result, we are implementing
A targeted reduction in jobs
In our QA team in California
And closing our Budcat studio
In Iowa
Budcat has a great partner to Activision
And has created a lasting impact
On the Guitar Hero franchise
Honestly, I think what this is coming around to
Is that before they had
One team developing stuff
For Guitar Hero
And then they acquired a few more studios
To do stuff for Guitar Hero
And now that they're reducing the amount of games
They're releasing each year
From Metallica's, Van Halen's
And whatnot
They don't need that many development teams anymore
Because they're going to be releasing
One Guitar Hero game a year
Approximately
I hate to say it because it's never happy news
To report on game studios closing
But unlike the last one, this one makes a little more sense
We know there's been too much saturation
Of the Guitar Hero games
So to hear that one of the studios that's been making
All these unnecessary ports
Sorry, that's how I feel
That shutting down makes more sense
Than the last one you reported on
Especially with the story we're going to get into here in a minute
Which you know is not inevitable
About the music games kind of
Slowing down as it is
I don't know if they are slowing down
I think
People have their expectations
Wrong on some of these games
But we'll get into that
A little bit later
I just don't agree with
What they're saying
LucasArts, another company that's not Activision
Is also confirming layoffs
And they're saying that they're
Committing
To their internal development
And they're saying that recently
They've made minor adjustments in staffing
And that
It will help them better address
The needs of the business
And they're remaining
They remain committed to
Their internal studio
And fostering relationships with trusted
internal partners in order to develop blah blah blah
In other words
They just let some people go
Outsource
And of course
They had let go
Some of their staff
Earlier
This year as well
Back in September
I guess
This is
I don't know if it's necessarily
To do with poor sales in different games
Or whatnot but honestly
LucasArts doesn't have
A lot of games coming out each year
It's maybe one or two titles a year so
I don't know
It's kind of to be expected I guess
Since they just finished a big title
Yeah I guess
Still kind of sucks but
Okay
What's going to happen when they run out of Star Wars games to make?
I don't think they ever will
They never will
Besides they have the huge MMO coming out
Of Bioware but whatever
And then finally
745 Studios
The company behind the
Well the game
PowerGig
They also said that they are
Linging off people
Apparently
Approximately 20 to 30 people were let go
Most of which were in the QA team
And a bunch of full time staff
And of course
They're saying that
With the gig already on the store shelves
Last week's 745 Studios restructured
The company is both a part of the
Natural cycle in game development and the focus
On the development needs of its upcoming game projects
Also the fact that
Their games scored really poor
Or really poorly
As far as reviews go
Was not a good game unfortunately
And this is the studio
Thanks to everyone who contributed to their first game
PowerGig Rise of the Sixth Stream
And we wish the individuals impacted by the reorganization
All the best
So yeah lots of people getting let going
Right before the holidays
I feel like this is like an echo of what happened last year
This is sad but I mean it's kind of a
I guess it's to be expected
But it doesn't
These are the folks that bring our games
Well I think it makes sense because if you think about it
Maybe these games
For some of these smaller companies
Not necessarily Activision and Bazaar
And stuff like that
It's like 745 I would think
That they're developing the game and stuff
They don't really need a large QA team until they're getting
The product all fleshed out
And then they're gonna hire people in
And unfortunately QA
A lot of the testers and stuff
It's not as glamorous
As the tester would like you
To think
It's really just like
Minimum wage
Shit job that you take
And you get hired and fired
Pretty regularly
So it's not a big shock
Yeah I mean I hate to say it
But especially when you consider
That Power Gig has come out now
And it's kind of landed with this big
Unfortunately
It makes this news
A lot less surprising
But again
It is better than Rock Revolution
Yeah but a studio like Konami
Can kind of take the blunt
Of some of that
Studio Closure's economy too
I mean they closed one of their big offices
I think two actually
Well Hawaii had closed at one point
And then they had the Bay Area one closed
So I mean it's not like even the big companies are immune
To this sort of thing
But you know I don't like to report on people losing their jobs
As happy happy
But I think that the silver lining to this
Is that you know
For I hate to sound like such a dork
But you know for every door that closes another opens
But especially in the gaming world
They will be on their way out
Well I don't think, well we're going to get into that in a minute
But they're not what they were before
Something new will come to take its place
You know we're not looking at another
Huge video game crash
Or there's going to be no jobs in gaming whatsoever
I think there will be other opportunities
That just might not be the same type of game
Or the same studio as before
So hopefully these guys land on their feet somewhere else
You know what I mean
Like there wouldn't have been a Power Gig in the first place
If Guitar Hero and Rock Band hadn't done so well, right?
Yeah, so
Anyhow, I guess I've referenced this enough
But you might have been reading some stories this week
It is being reported that music game sales
Are continuing a downward trend
It's an analysis that was originally published by Gamasutra
They were looking at the period of January through October
For the past three years
Looking at music game revenues
Apparently it was $1.6 billion in 2008
And where they are today, under $250 million for the year so far
And they say short of a Christmas miracle
Music games won't break $400 million for all of 2010
So that would be what, a quarter of where they were in 2008?
So
While that is kind of sad
I also kind of go back and say
Okay, well wait a minute
2007 was the first year that Rock Band and Guitar Hero 3 came out?
So
To go January-October of 2008
That was the period when everybody was playing it over at their friends' houses
And all that
Yeah, and
I don't know, I mean
With Rock Band at least, they didn't have to sell software
They were selling download content
Now I'm not really sure if that counts download content
As part of that revenue
But that's where all their money's been made lately
It's not been with new games
I mean, yeah, they just released a new game
But it's been out for maybe
Not even a month yet
Well, actually just slightly over a month
But
I don't know, it's hard to say that
It's dying
I think a lot of people are like
Maybe they don't need the keyboard peripheral
Maybe they're happy with the hundreds of songs
That they have in Rock Band 2
Here's my thought though
And I'm gonna bring this full circle
Watch
To say that music games are declining
And on their way out the door
Is an extremely ignorant statement to me
Because it's no different than
Remember earlier in the show when you were speaking about
Guwang
And you were saying it was like every other cave shooter
And somebody took issue with that
For me, it's very similar to what's happening here with music games
I don't think the period of music games
Means the period of plastic guitars
And plastic drums
Is satiating
There's not anything else you can really do
With this
I mean, Rock Band 3 is trying with the keyboards
And so forth, but it's unfortunately
Not really gonna be enough
That doesn't mean music games are dead
Look at Dance Central
I can say pretty confidently
It's the best selling Kinect game right now
That isn't the one that's packaged in
With the Kinect
Probably the two big ones
Still though, to be doing that well
Kinda shows that maybe there's a future there
And maybe other types of music games
That haven't quite been thought of yet
Believe me guys, we've been following music games
For a very long time here on OLR
Here's a perfect example
Ten years ago it was DDR
Before that, even Parappa the Rappa
Busta
Just all these other games
Perfect example, what do you think the top Wii title was for October?
For October, the top Wii title?
Probably, it's still Wii Play
No
And you would think, maybe it might be Kirby's
You know, the
Epic Yarn or whatever
It's gonna be something a lot more
Like every
Adult picks it up for the family
It's gonna be something family
It's a Wii Party
Just Dance 2
Okay
Not too surprised, okay
And not even close for second place
Just Dance 2
For the month of October
And this is since it was released
Cause I believe it came out the second or third week
Of October
It sold 285,556 units
Compare that with second place
Which would've been
Wii Fit Plus
With Balance Board
Cause you know those games
You know, Ten to Sell
And Wii Party of course
Wii Fit Plus 89,000
So it
Oversold it by more than double
And same with
Wii Party
It was 92,000
So
You know
You can't really see that the music genre is dead
Because these games are just doing
Crazy well
Just Dance, the first one
Number 8 for October
And it sold actually
I just wanna say real quick
To be fair in the Gamasutra
And I'm not interrupting you, I promise
To be fair in the original Gamasutra report
They are acknowledging that Dance Central
Could be a new opportunity for where this is going
But nowhere in this report does it mention
Just Dance
It should, and here's another cool fact
You know
Games like Wii Fit
And stuff like that
Sold a lot
Four million copies
From launch to date
Some other stuff
Real quick, I'm trying to find another game that would have been
Like a real big one here
Let's see here
Okay, here we go
Metroid Other M
You know, I guess that's kind of a poor comparison
Because it didn't do well all the way
Well yeah, Reggie acknowledged it's not
187,000 life
From launch
Okay, here we go, here we go
How about like a Mario Party 8
See that did 3.2 million
Launch to date
And you know
The
Just Dance series, the first one
Did actually
Pretty well, I mean within a year
It has sold almost 2 million units
1.8 million units
In closing, and here's kind of my closing thought
With this, this whole report here
Does not really sound like
A referendum on music games
So much as it is a referendum on
Harmonics, and maybe trying to make sense
Of why Viacom suddenly wants to
Unload them, because
Even though it's talking about Guitar Hero and Rock Band
I'm sorry, Guitar Hero was still a
Harmonics franchise
Yes, it's been turned over to somebody else since then
But Harmonics made that first game
That everything else has been modeled after
Everything that's happened
In the Guitar Hero franchise has been a rip-off
Of something Harmonics has done
Since Harmonics left the building, right?
Is that really an unfair thing to say?
No
So this is more speaking to, in my opinion
Harmonics
Than it is music games
Because nowhere in here are we talking about
The Just Dances of the World or the
You know, Konami, DDR
Which I'm sure is really nothing to scream about
But it's still out there cooking
And it's poking along
Unfortunately, that is the future of Rock Band
It's going to be like the
DDR releases
It's going to have its loyal following forever and ever
And it will still get its yearly releases
But they're going to, unfortunately, probably
Be a little more and more meh
But here's the thing, I think Harmonics
Is a studio that knows better
And will continue to innovate and such
Like they're trying to do with Dance Central
Which, you know, it seems to be working out
Well for them, and who knows whatever else
They're going to bring out in the future
Maybe something else connect, maybe that whole
Rumored revival of the amplitude frequency
Style game, who knows
Anyhow
Maybe I've spoken too long on this, I don't know
But if you want to join us in our chatroom
chat.orangeloungeradio.com
Some folks talking about Dance Masters
And maybe arcade games
Let's see, Dark Tetsuya
Saying, so if Konami could get with them
To put out Dance Masters, they could put it in arcades
Oh, Izzam says
Music games aren't out the door
They're just not the cash cow everyone wanted them to be
They were for a while
You know, I could see, see that's
One thing that's kind of cool about the Kinect
And the way it's set up, is
An arcade release wouldn't be that
Difficult for them
I mean seriously, since there's no controller involved
You just use the same damn technology
And away you go
Nothing like this lasts forever
Any type of fad in gaming
Or really anything it is
Movies even, nothing like this lasts forever
Like, remember teen comedies
When American Pie came out
We had every teen
Comedy in the world came out
Over the next couple years
And then suddenly, they didn't all start doing well
It doesn't mean teen comedies are gone forever
But it's just you don't see as many of them
Right? Or if they did come out
They're not the gross out
Stuff like American Pie was
People, they try to
You know, they try to figure out what the trends are
There's certain companies that will
Create those trends
And then there's other companies that will try to mimic
Those trends
And try to capitalize on them
And some of them do a good job of it
Like for example, when Activision
When Guitar Hero first came out
That was a good franchise
And then you had EA come out with
Rockband, of course both developed by the same company
But it kind of
You know, was taking
Some of the thunder from
Guitar Hero, but then improved upon it
It's hard though right now
Because it's hard to improve upon
What they've already got
With what's out there as far as
The peripherals go
And really, how much more can you do
Other than adding new instruments
To make these games any more
Unique or exciting or whatever
I mean, other than the song list
I guess in peripherals, it would just be
There's not much you can do with it
It hasn't been thought of yet
Who knew three years ago
We would be looking at a game like Dance Central
I don't think any of us could have predicted that
Um
Especially with the iToy stuff
It just didn't work well
It just didn't work well before
And I think a lot of us wrote it off then
As the trend that was going to go away
You know what I mean?
Oh, we saw this done on the iToy
And it was kind of ridiculous at best
So, bye
So who knew that the technology would be there later on
You know, perfect example of people trying to capitalize on this stuff
They have
It's funny
They actually have another dance game
For the Kinect that we haven't really heard of
Because it's only in the European markets
Dance Paradise
Yeah, I remember a story on this one had come up briefly
Didn't look very good
Kind of similar to
It reminds me a little bit of Dance Masters
But like, really dumbed down
Because it has all your
Avatar characters dancing around
Well, and you, me, and her can't exactly run over to Target
And get a copy of that
Exactly
And then the other thing too
Is the star plus dance
Something else that they're trying to capitalize on
The whole Just Dance and Dance Central stuff
But it's just not done well
And the problem is you're going to get a lot of these companies
Especially if Dance Central does really, really well
They're going to release their dance games
They're just going to be
Probably terrible
I bet you anything
Dance Central does really well
Well, we've already got the trademark for Dance Hero
How much you want to bet?
Alright, I want to say this real quick comment
From our good pal Bobby Blackwolf
Is in the chat
I want the inevitable Glee ripoff
Based on a marching band
Someone make this trend happen
That is one trend I'm not looking forward to
Is all the Glee ripoffs coming next season
By the way, because you know
The Glee game, Karaoke Revolution
I mentioned that there was a sequel on the way
V2
Road to, what was it?
Road to Regionals is the
The name
Will it have Teenage Dream in it?
Can't wait
Yay, now I know what to buy Dark Sakura
For Christmas, except she'll throw it at me
Or Hanukkah, excuse me
Chrismica
If I bought you Glee the video game on Wii
How quick would I be wearing the box?
I don't know
I'd have to actually get Becky over here to play it
I wouldn't play it
But she loves Glee, so I would let her play it
And then I would go
Trade it in and get a good game
But see, that's what Karaoke Revolution
Has become to
Konami
I don't think they take it seriously anymore
Well, I'm gonna get more attention to this
I know, let's attach
Glee to it
I know, let's attach American Idol
To it
How long
I can tell you how long
It's because once that show actually launches
How long are we gonna have Karaoke Revolution
X Factor edition
I mean, seriously
That's gonna be the next thing they have
Alright
Let's move on, we gotta talk about something
Not music games, so hopefully Dark Sakura
Can help us out, do you have a non-music game story for us?
Remember that thing that we
Were wondering if ever would come out
And it looks like it finally is, and maybe people
Care? Duke Nukem Forever?
Gran Turismo 5
Well, actually
It's gonna have a feature where you don't
Have to load the whole thing onto your
Hard drive, which is actually supposed to take
About 40 minutes to do
Wow
Yeah, it needs 6.4 gigabytes
Of hard drive space
Um
But what you can do is you can actually just
Opt not to and let stuff
Load as it will, but what it does
As it loads is that it loads
What you're playing
Onto your hard drive, so you're
Installing it in fragments
So it's
Copying over what you need
For that particular race
Exactly, and of course
You know, say that you do new content
Well, you've got
That going on, and then say you go back
To an old race, well it's already there, you don't have to worry about waiting
For it to really load
Because it'll be going off hard drive
Interesting, and I wonder if it, does it use any
Idle times? I don't know if this is even out there
Or not, like while you're on menus and stuff
Maybe to be doing some of the loading as well?
Um, sure it will be
Interesting
But the number of cars is listed on here
As 1031 cars
And that's pretty crazy
That's a lot of cars
Yeah
It's actually the largest install
That's gonna be on PS3
I mean, other big ones were
Devil May Cry
And Endwar
And Bioshock 2 and Lost Planet
They were around the five gig
Four and a half, five gig range
And this is 6.4
So it's big
And for our European listeners it will be out
On November 24th
That's an eventual
That's also for us, yeah
The worldwide launch thing
I was confirming
Men
Are you gonna pick it up?
Is it a game that interests you?
Probably, though I won't, Dan will get it
Okay
He's the one who sits here and waits for
All the new episodes of Top Gear to come out so he can
Watch them on the internet
So, oh give me that
I'm trying to open this new little
Toy I bought, sorry
Dark Soccer is using her nails
Maybe, maybe scissors?
I don't know, alright, anyhow, let's move on
More news, nobody wants to hear about my package
Opening drama, except for the fact, why do they
Make packages so difficult to open?
So people can't steal. Loss prevention
Still
And because they're so fragile
Just have the cameras and the beepers
Yeah, of course that never works either, the beepers
Always go off even when I legitimately
Bought them
Just to let everyone know I'm using the scissors
I stole from work
From the place of which I am officially
No longer employed
Way to stick it to them
Oh yeah, I'll take some scissors
Sure
So we were talking a little bit about the
Connect and Dance Central and stuff
Well Connect has actually sold pretty well
It's already moved a million units in the first ten days
And they're saying it's on track to hit their goal
Of five million this year
I have a little problem with that
Because
GameStop and
Me personally
Based off of what I've seen coming from Microsoft
They're saying there's shortages
Of this
You know, Connect hardware
So I'd be surprised
If they hit five million by the end of this year
Because what we see coming
Is definitely not
You know, a lot
Is it really shortage time?
Because when I was at Best Buy the other day, they had plenty
Well that's what GameStop's saying
They're saying it's hard to get
And I think that you're gonna see
It may be hard to find right now
Because they're holding them back for Black Friday
I don't know
I just know that there's a lot of them
On eBay going over retail
But people are crazy
And of course they're gonna say
Oh yeah, it's hard to get
But you know
It's gonna be one of the must have things
Definitely this holiday
So
You know, if you're interested in buying one
And especially if you're looking
To put it under the Christmas tree
Or in a stocking
Or whether festive
Kind of a big thing to put in a stocking
That's a really big sock
Really big stockings
If it's something
You're looking to purchase
For Christmas or a holiday or whatever
Give as a gift
You probably want to start looking now
Don't wait till the last minute
Alright
Well if they don't meet their numbers because of shortages
Then that's their own damn fault
How can you predict that you're gonna sell five million
Yet know at the same time you're not gonna make that many
They said three to five was their original expense
Now we're downplaying it a little bit
Alright
We'll see
I don't think they're going to
Here's the real message on everyone's mind
How's this doing compared to the move?
I don't know
I know Sony put out something and said
Oh yeah the move's done well
Fortunately the NPD and stuff
They don't really track
Accessory sales
Which is what this would be kind of considered
I guess
So I don't know
Maybe we'll find out in a future episode
Alright well moving on to some news
About Marvel vs. Capcom 3
We have a release date for the game
So I know this is something
Dark Sakura's gonna pick up
Or make Dan get for her
What a perfect opportunity
Dark Sakura just in time for Valentine's Day
Actually a little bit late
February 15th, 2011
So if you're willing to put Valentine's Day on hold
By one day you can make it of
Marvel meets Capcom and falls in love day
You know what?
We typically play games on Valentine's Day
So he can get me that
Instead of a bunch of roses
I don't care
At least he won't bitch about how much this costs
Instead of the roses
Just dip the box in chocolate
Yes to be fair this game would probably be cheaper than the roses
You know I always tell him that I want one
And he buys me a dozen
And I'm like, dude I want one
Maybe he thinks you mean one dozen
Maybe one doesn't
Alright the game is coming out
It's gonna be out on February 15th, 2011
On the 360 and the Playstation 3
Europe you have to wait just a few more days
So you might have to make it Valentine's week
February 18th is the day for you guys
There is a regular and special edition
And the special edition will cost you
70 bucks
Now in the news of more characters
There are some more characters announced for the game
She-Hulk and Zero
Are going to be in Marvel vs. Capcom 3
I love She-Hulk, she's so awesome
She-Hulk is female Hulk
And Zero of course is from the Mega Man franchise
I wonder if she's also gonna
Break the fourth wall since they're letting Deadpool do it
Why not?
Well she does it in her own comic too
I don't see why they wouldn't
Be a good thing to do there
So those characters are coming out
I believe I was reading something about
They're the special edition characters too
So if you want all the characters
You gotta shout out the extra money
Oh no, I take that back
Jill Valentine is one of the special characters
And Shumagrath
I have to tell you
We always call Shumagrath Shumachan
Because apparently Shumagrath is supposed to be
Female but also a really bad tentacle rate monster
Seriously, Shumagrath
Is this giant eyeball with a bunch of tentacles
Alright
I was gonna say
Maybe a boss monster, but I guess it's not
Shumagrath was also in
Kinda like Medusa on crack
It was in
Marvel Superheroes vs Street Fighter
So there you go
In the special edition we'll also
Get you exclusive
Artwork, a steel book case
A one month
Subscription to Marvel's online digital
Comic service, that's kinda interesting
And a prologue comic that will be 12
Pages that will explain
Why there's a contest between these two
Universes, so they're gonna retcon this whole
Thing in which I'm sure will also be explained in the
Intro
But comics are different
So there you go
Remember, that comic will probably be
Scanned and put online immediately
I'm actually dying to know from Dark
Sakura since this is kinda part of the world she lives
In, how do you feel about the digital comic
Being a pack
In? I mean, do digital comics cut it
For you, or no thank you, I want
Books? Well
Given that I read a lot of my comics
Digitally anyway, it's just fine by me
Um, actually
Tiara and I share a
Subscription to Marvel digital comics
Oh, very cool
Yeah, so
It's mostly old comics
And a lot of them actually do have in print
But it's still pretty cool
And I've always
Did it say that
It was just a digital comic or one of the
Motion
Comics? It's the
Subscription to their digital comic service
But I mean, they say that they were
That they were gonna release another
Comic
I think the actual comic book that comes with it
The prologue comic is a physical comic book
Oh, see, that I want
Oh, nevermind, I misunderstood, I thought
Okay, so you have a digital comic and a
It's MODOK! Sorry
I was looking back at the video and I was like
Ah, MODOK
It's gonna be a fun fighting game, looking forward to it
I'm looking forward to it, and you know what, I love the little touches
Because I've been going back and watching movies
With characters, just to check
Authenticity
And there's been some pretty neat little touches in there
Now Marvel, I'm really happy for you
And I'm gonna let you finish
But Capcom vs. SNK
Was the best crossover fighting game of all time
So I'm looking forward to maybe that being next year
Just saying
More news stories
And then release dates coming up in just one moment
Dark Sakura
Well, in other news, we have
A bit of a cost
Issue with development on the 3DS
It's going
To be expensive
As in, probably three times
As expensive
As doing other
DS, as doing DS games
One times expensive for every dimension
Yeah
They're basically saying between
50 million and 150 million yen
Per
3DS title
So, um
That's a lot of money
It's going to
Pretty much, like, here's
An example
Gaming
Actually reported that
Japanese studios spend between 4.4 million
And 43.9 million on a DS title
And we're talking
50 million
To 150 million yen
Yikes
That's a lot of money
Yeah, and just to put that
Into perspective
At least for our UK listeners
They're spending roughly 33,000
To 333,000 pounds
And then
The estimated cost
Is going to be
A lot
Well, now, there's a part of me that wants to say, well, duh
You know, new system, new expenses
DS has been out a while
So, of course, it's cheap, and this is going to be new
But
There was a call
Especially when E3 was around
That they were saying, it's going to be easy to develop for
Because it's just like
Developing for other Nintendo platforms
Ease and cost are two different things
I guess that's true, but
They were saying, like, if your game at all
Is calculating a type of Z-axis
To render 3D in a 2D
TV, if you know what I mean
It's very easy to translate that into the 3DS
And remember, they were showing those demos
Of the 8-bit games
That, you know, were redone
And not just 8-bit, but they had the Zelda
All Green of Time was out there
And Star Fox was out there
I would imagine that they wouldn't be too difficult
To develop that kind of stuff because all they have to
Really do is create a second virtual camera
That's going to be, you know, one for each eye
And that's how you create your depth
For rendering purposes, but
I don't know
So I'm surprised to hear it's three
Times as much money
I mean, okay, a little bit more expensive
Perhaps that will
Stave off some of the
Shovelware that may appear on
That platform
That might be a nice side effect, but I sadly don't think
You're right
It's only a matter of time before those development
Costs come down, right?
So
Well, as technology
Catches up with it too, I think
But this is still
Mostly speculation, I think
You know, once they actually get practical
Costs out of it, once it's in motion
Then we'll be looking at something a little different
Alright, well, we'll see
We'll see if these, uh, spending
The money was worth the effort in just a few months
I can't believe I'm saying, a few months?
3DS is out for us all to
Consume. Alright, in the meantime, let's see
What's coming out a little more
Sooner for us to consume
That was the worst transition ever
Good one, you know we're going to have huge mungus
Lists
Anyhow, what's coming out of the
US? Black Friday is right around the corner
Can't wait to see what Steam is selling
On Black Friday. I was just telling Dan that earlier
Hey, apparently the whole
Game for Windows thing, 10 cents
For Age of Empires 3 today, and I'm sure
That's been everywhere, yeah
But, it's Age of Empires 3
I have 0 cents interest in that game
I mean, I think it's great that there's bargain basement
But the game's like 5 years old
No one cares anymore
Now that it's 10 cents, people do
Like, I could get a game for 10 cents
It's 5 years old
It wasn't selling any copies anyway
Anyhow
Today, actually, marked the release
Of Raving Rabbids Travel in Time
For the Nintendo Wii, as well as
Donkey Kong Country Returns, which I hear
Is pretty good
That is also on the Wii
This week, not a whole lot coming out, but some
Pretty cool stuff
Red Dead Redemption, the Undead Nightmare Collection
On Xbox 360 and Playstation 3
That is the Undead Nightmare expansion
Which brings a brand new single player
Campaign, as well as
All the multiplayer
Expansions
This can actually be played by itself
So you don't need the original Red Dead
So if you're looking to play some online Red Dead Redemption
And you want to do it cheaper
This is the way to go, because it's only 30 bucks
Hot Wheels
Track Attack on the Wii and DS
Actually kind of cool because you can
Build your own tracks with this one
And they have the 80's
Hot Wheel Orange Tracks
With it, so you gotta love that
This week also, the Rock Band 3 Pro Wireless Guitar
Is making its way out for 150 bucks
That's on Playstation 3 and
Silly Bands
A game based off of Robert Vance
Awesome
That's on Nintendo DS
Where all the shovelware lives
Challenge Me Brain Puzzles 2
On Nintendo DS
That looks terrible as well
Some re-releases
Looks like it's kind of capitalizing
Black Friday stuff
They're re-releasing Enemy Territory
Quake Wars and Soul Calibur 4
This is by a third party company
Which is why none of those are from the same
Publisher
That's for 30 bucks
I think there's some more coming out later this week as well
Splatterhouse
Coming out on Playstation 3 and Xbox 360
This week
Include the original Splatterhouse game as well
As kind of an unlockable bonus
CSI Unsolved on Nintendo DS
Majin
And the Forsaken Kingdom on
Playstation 3 and Xbox 360
Another re-release pack
Kalbella's
Outdoor Adventures and
Rapala Fishing
That's for 30 bucks as well
Monster Jam
Path of Destruction for Playstation 3
This is a bundle that comes with a stupid wheel
To your DualShock 3 controller
Great
Worms Battle Island for Nintendo Wii
Another re-release pack
Brutal Legends and Splinter Cell
Double Agent
Man, some of these games are dirt cheap
I'm not sure if you're getting a great deal on this
But that's on Xbox 360
Drawn to Life Collection
A re-release of those two games
That's on Nintendo DS
To tie in with the new Disney movie
Disney's Tangled
On DS and Wii
Pro Evolution Soccer 2011
On the Wii
And it looks like they're doing
A Sonic the Hedgehog
Re-release pack
Sega All-Stars Racing and Sonic Unleashed
That's for 35 bucks
And also Brutal Legends and
Timeshift, those are on Playstation 3
For 30 bucks
Eternal Sonata and Katamari Forever 2
Pack, that's 35 dollars
And some actual new stuff
Michael Jackson, The Experience
Special Edition, which is on
Nintendo Wii, that does include a
Jewel-encrusted white glove
Just to complete the experience
Which I really want
Loki to wear to an episode of the show
Caution, rhinestones
Cupid Zirconia
That's also available on DS
And PSP as well
360 and PS3 versions coming later
Football Manager 2011
On PC
Gran Turismo 5
Coming out this week, both
The standard and the limited edition
And that
Wraps up the week, of course it's kind of
Gonna be slowing down
Here quite a bit, so don't expect much
Coming soon
Alright, well we'll travel over to Japan and look at
What's coming out of there, on the 360
Dudampachi Resurrection
Comes out in regular and limited edition
This is from Cave, so you know
Where this is going, right Loki?
It's a shooter game, but this is a
You know, it's kind of like made for the 360
So it's very purdy
Kind of looking at the graphics here
So check that out, that is on the 360 this week
And that really is the big release in
Japan this week on the 360
There is Shaun White skateboarding
But no one curr
Alright, moving on to the PlayStation 3
This week, Gran Turismo 5
Not only coming out here, but in Japan as well
So check that out if you like that stuff
Also, Pachipata 16
Gengita Paradise 2
Comes out this week
From Irem
And yeah, it's just pretty much
Chicks on the beach playing pachinko games
That is literally what this game is
But they're all like 3D rendered and shit
Look at this 3D rendering of pachinko machines
It almost looks like a
Make your own pin
Type of mode, where you can put the pins wherever you want
I'm telling you, it's a big deal there
There also is a
PlayStation 3 bundle
With the console coming out
With the Gran Turismo bundled in
Because it's kind of a big deal in Japan
So look for that this week
Shaun White skateboarding as well, big deal
Trinity Zero comes out this week
That's also a PlayStation 3 game
That's coming from Koei
And this is like a swords and magic type of game
Kind of looks like you have a party of people
But it looks to be a little bit more of like a
Action-y type of
Roleplaying game
So that actually looks kind of rad
Is this coming out in the US as well?
Not this year, probably next year
That might be one that you want to import
For those of you that are big into importing
But just be careful
It's a lot of Japanese
So if you don't know Japanese
You might be screwed
Mario Sports Mix this week
On the Nintendo Wii in Japan
And we got that here
Or are getting it here
I remember playing this one at E3
Just the hockey and dodgeball
And all that stuff pretty soon
It's this week in Japan
On the Nintendo DS this week
There's quite a bit
Some of the standouts though
Super Robot Taisen L comes out this week
Rege Taisen
Getenka
Tenkaishi Battle Royale comes out this week
From SEGA
Konami brings us Power Pro-kun Pocket 13
And Penguin no Mondai
Cross Tenku
Seven Senshi
That's a price reduction though
And then Cooking Idol
Ai Mai Main Game Day Harimeki
Kinomeki Cooking
Also gets a price reduction
I don't think these are all
Games that you guys are going to be pre-ordering
But lots of price reductions this week
Lastly on the Sony PSP
Quite a few games this week
Also you have quite a few price reductions
Some of the new games though
Miyako comes out this week from Idea Factory
Ikitosen no Ken from Konami
And lastly from D3
Ishin Renka
Ryuma Gaiden comes out in
Regular and Limited Editions
Check that out
Or don't, see if I care
I'm not
Let's go to Europe
Well actually there are quite a number of games
Coming out next week
We have
Starting with
I'm starting with clearing my throat so I can breathe
On the 22nd Poker Night
At the Inventory
The 23rd Mafia 2
Joe's Adventures
On the 24th we have
Crazy Taxi
Gran Turismo 5
And Pac-Man Championship Edition DX
As we discussed earlier
Well that's the PlayStation 3 one
And actually there is a release on
The 25th
Of course it's not a holiday for them there I think
Plus Island Freedom
26th is Def Jam Rapstar
Yay
Disney Epic Mickey
Football Manager 2011
Michael Jackson The Experience
Pac-Man Parties, Sega Master Drive, Classic Collection
Volume number 3
Tron Evolution which I'm looking forward to
So getting that
And
There's a bunch more
There's also Venetica
And on the 30th
Super Meat Boy
Yeah Venetica is supposed to be coming over here in January
So that should be cool
You played the Daughter of the Devil
Yeah that actually looks pretty interesting
Because apparently
Death is real or not the Devil
Death
The Daughter of Death
Close enough
Both begin with D
That looks kind of interesting
Jimmy
Eh
It does kind of have a bit of a
Fable vibe to it just in looks
Yeah
Cool
That's it
APB
It's kind of funny because people were pissed off
That this game actually kind of went under
Within about 3 months of its launch
And now it's been acquired by
Gamers First and they're relaunching
As APB Reloaded
In the first half of 2011
And what's kind of cool about it though
Is the game will actually be
A free to play
Iteration of the game
So lots of microtransactions
As well but hey you know what
That's awesome because
I would love that game to be free to play
It was pretty fun to begin with
But I couldn't see myself paying for it
Thank God I was too lazy to pay for it
This was a game that you were excited about
But you were like too lazy to get
Right?
Exactly
Nice
Or as Rama says in our chat room
APB rise from your grave
Get it?
Anyhow one more story
For you guys and we're going to get to the classic game of the week
But this is about a different type of classic
On the Wii
It's this whole super special
25th anniversary edition here
You know the Wii has
The 25th anniversary Mario collection
That comes with like a Mario collection
And Wii Sports
And the red controllers and all that
Here's the interesting thing though
Is that in Europe they got the Wii
And it came with New Super Mario Brothers
And Donkey Kong original
Edition
It was preloaded onto the Wii
It was kind of like a virtual console game
Because you know how Donkey Kong was on the NES
Originally right?
Well here's the interesting thing
Donkey Kong original edition
On the Wii that's coming out in Europe
Has the cement factory level
And you might be going
Okay well who cares about that?
Well that's because the cement factory level
Wasn't in the NES version of
Donkey Kong
So it's kind of weird because
It's very obvious I guess you can tell
From the way this kind of looks when you're playing the game
That it's not a port of the arcade game
But it's actually like an NES ROM
But it actually has the
Cement factory level in it
Which by the way I used to call the pie level
Because I'm the Commodore 64
That for whatever reason
Are going into burning oil
Just roll with me here
So yeah kind of weird that
Nintendo either knowingly or unknowingly
Kind of dug out this prototype
Donkey Kong game
That honestly never saw the light of day
In either continent
I think that's kind of cool actually
I mean whereas a lot of people are going to look at this
And go eh big deal a missing level shows up
In a game that's like what 25 years old now
I kind of go wait a minute though
Nintendo has this kind of shit in the vaults
And they're capable of putting it on
A service like virtual console
Why aren't they?
Like yeah we got
Some of these what Japanese
Games that never came out here in America
Or Europe or whatever the case may be
And like Sin and Punishment right
That was a big thing they did a couple years ago or last year
How about some of these
Unreleased Nintendo games that never saw
The light of day
Or here's something kind of interesting
Seeing as you know
They have the 25th anniversary edition
And the Super Mario All-Stars
Limited edition stuff coming out
Which by the way
Is just a port of the Super Nintendo game
Why couldn't they have ported over
I don't know the Super Nintendo
Cartridge that had both Super Mario World
And Super Mario All-Stars
You know a little bit extra to go in there
Seeing as you have a whole fucking disc
That you could pack full of stuff
Why would they do that
When they could just put in an ad
To go onto the virtual console marketplace
And spend 800 Wii Points
On that game
Why would they give you something for free Loki
You just want something for nothing
You want grateful kids
What they had for the game
They had the pre-order discs
Remember that you could get the two
Nintendo 64 Zelda games
And the two 8-Bit Zelda games
I don't understand why they can't
Oh I know because like you said
They're selling them on the virtual console
That's right
Rama in our chat room says it could be an unlock lol
I doubt it
By the way there is this
25th anniversary Super Mario
Brothers thing that they did
All they did they like changed the copyright
Date and they just kind of
Edited the question mark blocks to say
Basically it's a ROM hack
It's on that same level as
Super Penis Brothers
Where somebody took all the pictures of Mario
And turned them into penises
Which is freely available on the internet
So that's the business Nintendo is in now
Speaking of ROM hacks
I don't think we talked about it last week
New Super Mario Brothers
Someone ROM hacked the
DS ROM and made it
New Super Mario Brothers
I remember that coming up last week
That's sweet
See that's what you do
Because Mario All Stars
That's great that you made everything 16 bit
And stuff why don't you just
Update it again
Make it all like New Super Mario Brothers
So you have all the original levels
With Mario Brothers, the lost levels
Mario 2 and stuff like that
Make it all brand new
And guess what you could have sold it for
$50 instead of $30
Here's the thing
Because basically you're buying a $30 ROM
Or if they were going to do a ROM hack
With this 25th anniversary
They could have done a good ROM hack
You know some of the ones out there
They took the graphics from Mario 3
When Mario looked a lot sharper
And the sprites were kind of better
And put it in Mario 1
They should have done something like that
Or maybe they went back and redone the sprites
I'm not just talking about that
I'm talking about a ROM hack out there
That takes the Mario 3 sprites
And puts them in the Mario 1 game
This is just a little extra thing
For itself
Oh it's an extra bonus for buying the actual console
It's this 25th anniversary edition
Of Mario Bros
Which by the way the ROM will probably be floating around out there
As if it really needs to be
Because it's just a simple ROM hack
But
I don't know
It's just
It's neat I guess
But it's not that unique
Alright well it's a bummer
It's probably never going to go anywhere past this
Wow that's kind of cool
I'm telling you somebody just grabbed the wrong damn file
Is probably what happened
With this whole prototype getting released
Somebody grabbed the wrong damn file
And didn't even know what they were doing
Alright anyhow let's get into
Speaking of classic stuff
I know we're talking about Donkey Kong
But I think Dark Soccer wants to take a trip down memory lane
And point out a different game
She says hey
Listen up kids
Grateful brats that don't know what a pie factory is
There's a game out there
That you should be checking out and playing
And showing a little love this week
Although I gotta say I think a lot of the kids
Know about this one but if they forgot
It's time they remember
I think that we should actually start this one off with the music
I think we should too so let me pull up the music
If they don't get it then
Yes the game of the week is
Bubble Bobble
Which I could have sworn I've done before
But I don't think I did so here it is
Bubble Bobble was put out by Taito
It came out in 1986
And came out on Damn Near Everything
There are bubble dragons named Bub and Bob
Or as they were in Japan
There was Babarune
And Babarune
So same diff
And basically they spit out bubbles
And push them around
And smack their enemies
And there's been many
Many many games in their series
So yeah basically
You blow the bubbles
You can trap the enemies in the bubbles
And you can push them to
Burst the bubbles
And make the enemies fall off
And the enemies
The bubbles with the enemies and it can float
So you can jump on them all
Use them to get to hard to reach places
Or pop many of them at a time
But if they're
If they're the last one left on the screen
They get angry
And change color
And then you have to bop them
And they're harder to get
Some of them have rocks, lasers, fireballs
For projectiles
But sometimes you have
Different things like water
And lightning
Little balls that you can smack them around with
As far
As ports there have been a
Bajillion like I said
And that's the technical term for it
There's been Commodore 64
Sinclair ZX Spectrum
Amiga Atari ST MSX
Armstrad CPC
Sharp X68000
PC there was a
DOS one in
1989 and in 1996
There was I think another one
Apple II
FM Towns Marty Sega Master System
Game Boy Game Boy Color Game Boy
Advanced Nintendo DS
PlayStation Sega Saturn
NES Famicom Disc
Game Gear Mobile Phone
TI 80 whatever calculators
And it came out
On the Ultra K Taito arcade classics
There's also one for the BBC
Micro that
Never actually got released
Taito said in
1996 that they lost the
Original source code
And um
Probe
Was actually
Sent that so that they
Could reproduce the mechanics
And that also meant that later on
Uh
There were re-releases of
Rainbow Islands for Saturn, PlayStation
And PC in 1996
The Game Boy
Game Boy Color versions have a water moon
Storyline and it's known as
Bubble Bobble in classic Bubble Bobble
And there's a
Like I said there was one for the TI-83
Graphing calculator that someone made which I
Think I had
At one time till my graphing calculator
Died um there was
Uh Xbox PS2
PC for the Taito Legends
Compilation um
It was on mobile phones in Europe and Japan
And then it came out
On the Virtual Console
There were also broken versions later on
Like uh ones that wouldn't let you get past
Level 30
Yes seriously
As far as other games that came
Out in the series
Let's move on to those we have
Rainbow Islands the Bubble
The story of Bubble Bobble 2
We have Rainbow Islands extra versions
Parasol Stars which originally came out
On the PC Engine and I know where you can get a copy
In town and they want 70 bucks for it
And I'm like no!
Which by the way if it feels like you've done this game before
It's because you did Parasol Stars
I did do Parasol Stars
Parasol Stars is a great game
And there's also Bubble Bobble Part 2
Bubble Bobble 2 slash Bubble Symphony
Um Bubble Memories the story of
Bubble Bobble 3
Rainbow Islands Putty's Party
Which was on the Wonderswan and I think
I have it I have to check
I've got some Wonderswan games I don't remember what I have
Rainbow Islands Towering Adventure
And Bubble Bobble Plus which is a WiiWare game
And also Bubble Bobble Neo
Is the same version that came out on
Xbox Live Arcade
And that is Bubble Bobble
Okay yeah there's
There are quite a number
And don't forget about the related
Ones in the series
There was Puzzle Bobble
Which was over here Bust a Move
Mhmm
Which is a really dumb name
For the game
There was Azumanga Puzzle Daioh
After the Azumanga Daioh
Which is also in the series
So
Puzzle de Pon, Fairyland Story
And Check and Pop
Similar
Your classic game of the week boys and girls
Bubble Bobble on like every system ever made
But is there
A certain system that you prefer above
All others
I would say original arcade
But that's
Yeah well I can tell you what
What my favorite in the
Series was and what system I played it on
Was Puzzle Bobble 2 on Saturn
I played a crap ton
Of Puzzle Bobble 2 on the Saturn
Seriously
I would just sit on the floor in front of Danzel TV
And just do nothing but play it
And there's so many clones of that game now
I know I have a free one on the iPhone
Crazy stuff
Alright guys that's it for this part 8 of our show
But don't go anywhere guys
We're going to be right back with plenty more show
And still more news to come tonight
News about a Yars Revenge remake
And it's really not what you think guys
Talking about an exciting new pinball table
I know will make Dark Sakura happy
And a new Dreamcast collection
And we want to talk a little bit about OnLive
Because there's been a lot of news about that this week
So don't go anywhere guys
We'll be right back
Music
And welcome back everybody
To Orange Lounge Radio
We are taping live here on Sunday November 21st
2010 at AllGames.com
And we tape live of course
Every Sunday 6 o'clock Pacific 9 o'clock Eastern
Right after the Bobby Black Wolf show
It is episode number 390
Of our show
And if you like what you hear here at
Orange Lounge Radio support some of our other
Podcast projects
Dark Sakura does a little show called
Comic Insanity
But that's N, Comic N-sanity
No I in insanity
But it's still insane
All the less
And it's awesome-tastic
And then a brand new World of Warcraft focused show
The best little Horde house in Azeroth
Is now available on iTunes
You can just sort for Horde house
And there it is
So some of our side projects, that's me and Xtaphir with Warcraft chat
On this week's episode we had Rice Princess
And yeah
It was definitely me, Xtaphir and Rice Princess
That's all I'm gonna say
Anyhow let's get back into some more gaming news
Here we got some rapid news
We're gonna get to and then Twitter topics
So if you haven't gotten your Twitter topics in
Send us a tweet
And we're gonna get to those in just about 10 minutes
But first some quick news stories
Starting with Loki
Rock of the Dead
The game that actually uses the guitar peripheral
For something other than playing guitar
Is now possibly coming to Facebook
Apparently Epicenter
On Conspiracies game
Is kind of a little bit like
Typing of the Dead
Except with the guitar type controller
And it is gonna be coming
Of course in a guitar less
Version sometime in 2011
And apparently development
Is started
Or is slated to start Q1
Of next year
And it's a few
They say it's a Facebook game
So what a couple weeks after that
So that's kind of neat I guess
It'd be something different to play
On Facebook
Rock band
This week has some pretty cool stuff
Coming out
Including John Lennon's Imagine album
So you can buy the whole album
For $15
Or the equivalent in points
Or each individual song
Which includes
Crippled Inside
Jealous Guy
It's So Hard
I Don't Wanna Be A Soldier's Mama
Gimme Some Truth
Oh My Love
How Do You Sleep
How
Oh Yoko
And of course the Pro Guitar
And Bass Expansions
Are available for
Looks like actually only one of the songs
In that pack How Do You Sleep
That has Pro Guitar and Bass
And then
Lastly
Looks like
Ark the Lad
And Ark Arena are coming
To the Playstation Network
Next week
So you can get your 8-Bit
Gaming on there
Looks like Ark the Lad 2
Will be available for $5.99
Well Ark Arena
I guess it was an offshoot of the series
Will be
Can be purchased with Ark the Lad 2
For $8.99
I don't know if the other
Ark Arena is gonna be available separately
But
That'll be coming Tuesday November 23rd
That's very soon to see now
Yes a couple days away
Some of the quick stories here
This one is about
Hold on I have to have an excuse to play this song
I've been doing this show for what almost 9 years now
And I don't know if I've ever had an excuse to play this song
Let's see here
Gotta pull it up real quick
And here we go
We played this once in Marching Band
That's right it's a Monty Python story
Yes we've managed to find a
Story about video games and Monty Python
Of course it might not be the
Type of video games you're really into
But it's a UK company called
Zatika
Which is trying to make a social
Game based out of the Monty
Python license
They also have games called
Buttscan
Yes that's right Buttscan
And Mr. Bean out of control
That's already being made for
The iOS stuff
So I don't know whatever
Here's a quote from the press release
Monty Python is one of the most iconic
Comedy licenses around but there has been no new
Material for over 20 years
By acquiring these rights we will be transporting
Monty Python into the 21st century
With a totally new experience for their unique
Comedy that will delight old and new
Fans alike. Forget Web 2.0
This is Python 2.1 and 3.25
Well you know what
They did something a while back called
Monty Python's Complete Waste of Time
I do remember that
And it had the desktop pythonizer that
Turned every other sound on your keyboard into farts
And a game called
Spam
Which filled your screen with a giant can of spam
And says try to locate the kind of spam
I love Monty Python
But this game will probably
Be about the parrot sketch or something
That's been just beaten into the ground
Speaking of things beaten into the ground
Are you suggesting that the parrot is dead?
This is an
Expedite
Anyhow
This might be an ex MMO pretty soon
Final Fantasy 14
Has extended their free trial
For yet another 30 days
This is the second time
They've done this and they have
Promised that there's a big update coming
On November 25th
So this 30 days is a
Thank you to the existing fan base
For sticking with it through all this crap
It'd be hilarious
Isn't November 25th like Thanksgiving?
Wouldn't it be hilarious if the
Update wasn't actually an update
The fix on the 22nd, Monday, 23rd, Tuesday
The 25th is Thanksgiving, they're putting in a patch
And I mean I realize it's probably
In Japan and they don't really have the same holidays
We do but it's still just kind of funny to me
But wouldn't it be funny though if the new update wasn't
Exactly one to fix all the bugs
It was just like the holiday event
Right, right. It's a big update
There's now snowmen
Yes, but no auction house
No auction house
Snowmen and fireworks
Santa costume
There's a whole thread
Actually now I'm curious, I gotta look at what is
Coming in the November update
There's also another update coming in December
Wow
The update's actually just a download
For Final Fantasy XI
That's right, they are making changes to
Events and battles
UI, they're changing
The macro functions, some new map features
You can now expand and
Collapse your map
That sounds useful
Also the map
The mouse will now scroll your map
That also sounds very useful
The left mouse button
Has been enabled for use
Good job Square
For making my mouse
Look, I realize the game was developed for a system
That has no mouse, but come on
The ability to turn left has been added to our
Make sure
No longer will you have to
Sprint, but the walking
Functionality will be enabled
I know there's a
Hardcore Final Fantasy XIV fan out there
Listening to this show going, you guys are assholes
You guys are just assholes, you don't understand
Out of the ability
To use your right leg
Rob, that little voice that you did
Just sounded like Dane Cook's
Impersonation of himself in the womb
Don't you ever compare me to
Dane Cook ever again
I can't help that is what you sounded like
Don't you ever
Moving on
Ziba in our chatroom says
I still don't think they have chocobos yet
Isn't it mandatory in Final Fantasy games
Like you have to have a chocobo somewhere
Even the fucking Facebook games have chocobos
No, no, no, they're not chocobos anymore
Now they're just giant turkeys
Remember, because it's all the same, but different
Just like, you know
That's right, they're now called
Chocobocos
Yeah
They're very, very buff
They're muscle bound and wearing spandex
Loki should design an MMO
He really should
My MMO would be awesome
What would your MMO be all about?
I don't know, it'd be very freeform
Now we don't want to necessarily rip off
Freeform like that
It's like second
Organized chaos, if you will
I don't know
I'd start off with a traditional MMO
And then I would take suggestions
I would take most of those suggestions
Alright, anyhow
I had my own
Random things
Now who's interrupting who?
You asked, I wasn't done talking
So technically you are interrupting me
Let me finish
I'm finished
Are you really finished?
God damn you
Amaze Satsuma says
I want a turducken made out of turkey bows
There you go
Chocobos have now been replaced with turduckens
And no, my MMO would not be like
Bonetown, Bonetown is lame
My MMO is not lame
Salacious pop
In our chat
I'm assuming this is about the Loki MMO
I'm a dual spec
Bacon baron and titty hound
Oh, so you're Loki's wife
Alright
Anyhow, moving on
Hey
More Blizzard news that isn't WoW
This is about Diablo
And apparently
There might be, there could possibly
Be the possibility
That Diablo might
Maybe happen on consoles
Here's
Here's the company's official response
To speculation
Funny, I know someone that
Would be very
Appropriate for that
It's a studio called Bizarre Creations
Unfortunately you just
Fired them, so
Yeah, it's a little awkward
Yeah, I'm sure
That Diablo would be perfect for consoles
Because it would make them lots of money
I mean, seriously, if they thought Bloodstone
Was a good idea
Then Diablo is gonna be a great idea
Now, please
Note that Blizzard made it very clear
On the job posting itself
Quote, please note this is
Not an announcement of a console title
We are first and foremost developing
Diablo 3 for Windows and Macs
PCs, and don't intend to allow
Any possibility of a console interpretation
To delay or affect the release of that game
Yes, we first and foremost are developing
That, and then we're gonna develop
The console version, which we just announced
Right now, Diablo Ghost coming
Soon everybody, Diablo Ghost
Soon on a console near you
Check it out
Or don't
DarkSakura, what do you got for us before we get to Twitter topics?
Stuff and nonsense
How about an arcade game called
Let's Connect
It, um, basically
It was at the
IAPPA
Man, that's gonna be kind of a tone twister
Trade show, and it uses
The Kinect to
Play things that are like
I guess the Nintendo's Play Choice 10
Cabinets, you know, you can pick your game
And, um
So, it's not actually official
Microsoft thing, but
The manufacturer Quasimodo Interactive
Um
Needed the license to play
The games publicly, so
I don't know how well that's
Gonna work, but it's a neat idea
And then, uh, Kingdom Hearts
3D will have
New Disney World
Ooh
They are, uh
It's gonna have, uh
It's gonna be, of course, on the 3DS
And it will have Sora and Riku
And, um
They're just gonna be different places
I would say that they have to
Pan out
But this is, but they're gonna
You know, still have the Traverse Town
And all the other places still be there
But, new places
They could do a zone on Princess and the Frog
And some of the new things that have come out, but
At Cauldron level
How about, uh, since there is a new Tron movie
I'm just saying, the Tron universe can be revisited
I know!
The Space Paranoids level needs to be updated
Seriously, Disney, if you want a really
Good primetime animated series
Boom! There it is
I'm surprised that hasn't happened, actually
It would be awesome
There's manga already
Yeah, that's pretty cool, but
I mean, seriously
You get their animation team behind it
And you could do something really
Awesome
Awesome while we were cleaning, Axel
Hot
Because, I mean, seriously, it's a great series
To get people at sea may not be
I have another story
Interested in the characters
Back, you know, into those characters
And in other news
Star Trek Online
Season 3! Yay!
Didn't season 2 just come out?
A couple months ago
But they've just finished up
Some of the new episodes
I actually just finished the Davidian
Missions, and it actually takes some kind of
Lame psychic energy
Stealing creatures from the next generation
And makes them actually pretty cool and
Badass in a very Silent Hill
Level sort of thing, it was really cool
Well, I guess that's kind of cool that they're supporting it
As well as they are
They put out the scary ones for around Halloween, it was really neat
Season 4 is going to be entirely in the holodeck
And it's going to be set in the Wild West
The server's called the holodeck
Our server's called the holodeck
Our test server's called Tribble
At any rate
Can I play on the Zachary Quinto server?
Actually, he does voices for a character
Right at the beginning of the game
The emergency medical hologram
I'll be playing that level with the lights off
Anyway
What is your emergency?
As I was saying
The third season
Starts on December 9th
And has a mission
Creation beta
So it's for the
Foundry is what it's called
There's also going to be unlockable Borg tech
Mission replay
Which is what I'm looking for
Shut up Rob
I'm laughing at what you said, not what you said
But I'm looking forward to the mission replay
Because there were some pretty fun missions
There's also going to be one thing that's not in this little piece
That I was reading up on
The Star Trek Online forums
They're going to have extra accolades
And different prizes you can get for
Your ship builder missions
And making changes to some of them
Based on your rank and that type of thing
So it's looking pretty good
They've also got
Some sort of online ship builder thing too
And don't forget about translating your tweets into Klingon
I'm sorry I'm not programmed to do that
Oh, you know what they just released
Which I thought was absolutely retarded
I mean, not even just retarded
But retarded
They released the Enterprise
Outfit packs
Vulcan chick
I'm like, dude, that series sucked
I did get the 7 of 9 outfit though
I will put pictures up
On our website soon
You can have 7 of 9
But I can't have Zulu
You can just have her outfit
Where everybody gets goatees
The evil pack
Tyra Crew gets goatees
I like that
Did anyone ever have a goatee in Star Trek except for him?
I don't remember
Everyone in Star Trek was fairly clean shaven
Except for Riker
The old school Klingons
They all had those weird sort of
Goatees
And now most of the Klingons have uberbeards
Alright, anyhow
Let's not turn this into a Star Trek show
As much as Star Trek would like that
Let's go to the Twitter
Every week you guys send us your tweets
Tweet, tweet, tweet, tweet
Twitter.com slash O-L-R
13forever
13crossforever
13xforever
Sends us some tweets
Wants to alert us to the whole Age of Empires 3 for 10 cents
As a lot of people have been doing today
Just gamers wanting to spread the word about next to free ship
But he also wanted to point out
Game for Windows Marketplace also has
Bioshock 2 for $9.99
And some cheap add-ons for it
So I guess the 10 cent deal
Is not the only deal out there
I think Bioshock 1 was available for $1.99
For a day somewhere
Probably on Steam
See, this is the one reason I support
This whole Game for Windows thing
Because competition, we're all gonna win
With these companies
Trying to undercut each other
It's gonna be awesome
Zebo wanted to alert us to the Final Fantasy 14
Free trial will be extended again
But I already covered that
Thanks for trying
Let's see, Retertainment for whatever reason
Just sent us a tweet that is a picture of Pito Bear
In the TSA logo
Saying the U.S. Department of Molestation
I don't know if I find that funny
Just kidding, it's funny
Pito Bear is always funny
My favorite though, nothing will ever top
The Pito Bear on the Trader Joe's price tag
It was like for honey
Or something
I'm sorry, it was funny
Let's see, TigerClaw sends us a couple of stories
On the tweeters
One of this is about a really cool hack
I'm surprised he didn't say anything about this yet
But apparently it's using the Open Connect drivers
I apologize if I'm mispronouncing that
Apparently used the Open Connect drivers
And image processing
To create a lightsaber effect
On his PC
Out of a wooden stick
And so the Kinect tracks the wooden stick
And replaces it with a lightsaber
That is awesome, sir
You win the internet
And yet, how long is it gonna take for the real lightsaber game
To come out, especially with all these layoffs
Later next year
By the way, there's a YouTube out there
So of course I'm gonna turn it on and watch this guy
Oh, this is way better than Star Wars, kid
Just saying
It's actually kinda awesome
It's kind of
The delay on that is not as terrible as you'd think
I mean, it's not totally fluid
But it's not horrible
Kinda neat, I like that
They're just early drivers, they'll get better
Again, our Twitter
Twitter.com slash O-L-R
O-L-R
Another tweet from Tiger Claw
Sending us this one about Pac-Man
It's another Pac-Man story, but it's not about Pac-Man Championship Edition DX
It is about the Rose Parade
Yeah, Namco Bandai
Has said that a 55 foot tall display
Featuring Pac-Man and
Blinky, Pinky, Inky, and Clyde
Is going to be one of the first
I'm sorry, the first video game focused
Float in the 122 year old
Tournament of Roses parade
It's because of Pac-Man's 30th anniversary
There's going to be a cake toting
Pac-Man surrounded by presents
And standing atop a bright and colorful
Cornucopia of floral arrangements
You have to remember, it's the Rose Parade
There's tons of floral arrangements on every float
So, that's kinda cool
And if you want to see that on TV
8 AM Pacific time on Saturday
New Year's Day
That's right, you have to get up at 8 AM
Or set your TiVo
Or just wait for the YouTube that will inevitably show up on all the gaming blogs
There you go
Anyway, Sonic the Hedgehog was the first
Video game character that ever had a balloon
But that was in the Macy's Thanksgiving Day parade
That's a whole other parade
Pikachu was also in that parade
But in 2001
And then escaped and killed everybody
Yes, it did
But no one wants to report on that
Let's see, Spazenator
PSN wants us to note
That there is a release that didn't get mentioned earlier
The Magic the Gathering game
That is on Xbox Live Arcade is being ported
To PSN this Tuesday
And he sends a follow-up tweet
Saying, I recommend the Magic the Gathering
PSN game for those who don't already have it
On Xbox Live Arcade or like
The Magic the Gathering card game
Yeah, it was a pretty faithful translation
It's kinda hard to translate an intricate
Card game like that when cards can be played
At a variety of times
To a console, but they did a pretty decent job
Even though I think
It plays a little faster in real life
But still kinda neat
And certainly a lot cheaper
Oh my god, trying to collect those cards?
Geez
So I think that's gonna close it for the Twitter
I'm doing one last refresh to make sure we don't get any last minute tweets
Nope, I don't see any
So I hope that's not a bug or whatever
But yeah, Twitter.com slash OLR if you want to send us some tweets in the future
In the meantime
Some more news stories for you guys
Then we're gonna be getting to the Skype line in a little bit
At 1-877-GAME-OLR
But first, Loki
Ah, yes
Um, I don't know what to think of this
I honestly didn't play the first game
But this doesn't sound
Very close to the original image
Of Yars' Revenge
Uh, Yars' Revenge is being made
Or remade into an anime-inspired rail shooter
Um
Honestly
It
It seems like
A stretch to me
I was making the joke earlier saying that
It really should have been about an angry pirate
But, um
YARRRR
YARRR I will have my revenge
But, uh, yeah
It's supposed to be like some sort of
You know, they're saying like
Like a Xeno saga
Or something like that
I don't know
It seems like a stretch to me
Um, it's kinda weird
Because Yars' Revenge was like
Probably one of the greatest Atari 2600 games
There ever was
That wasn't by Activision
Um, I've never played it
It's cool, but you know
You play it now
And you go like, there's not a lot to this
What is this? But you have to remember
Atari 2600 games were very straightforward
Back in the day, I mean
Games were four kilobytes
In size back then
You write essays now that are longer than that
You know what I mean? Like, they had to cram a lot
In those little cartridges, so most of the games were
Very straightforward
So fine, they're reinventing it or whatever
But this whole like, anime chick
And rail shooter, like, doesn't seem to be
At all similar
To what was there before
As long as there's like, some
Resemblance to the original game
I would approve
But I have a bad feeling I'm not gonna be seeing that
Yeah
I mean, I guess a good game's a good game
No matter what they do artistically
With it, but I just
I think y'all can see where we're all a little
Apprehensive
But we'll see, we have yet to really
See gameplay, the only trailer that's come
Out so far is this weird announcement video
Right? Yes. So
We'll see when gameplay comes out
That's true, Dungeon Busters
In our chatroom saying, there was more
Story in the manual than there was in the
Actual Yars Revenge game, very true
Very true point
Alright, moving on to another story
Talk about more old
Games making a comeback, but this time not quite
As old, it's the Dreamcast collection
Yay
The Dreamcast collection has been listed for the
Xbox 360 and the PS3
This was caught in a listing on GameStop
It's the Dreamcast collection
Supposed to cost $29.99
And the date that is tentative
Right now anyway for release is February 15th
You shouldn't really treat these
GameStop leaks as, you know
Word and Bond and all that because
It could change, and a lot of these are
Service holders to get people to pre-order them
But you what?
I haven't seen anything yet
Okay, here's the weird thing though
Is that Sonic Adventure and Crazy Taxi
Are the only announced
Dreamcast games right now
Now those games are going to cost $10
Well obviously Sonic Adventure already came out
Crazy Taxi I believe is this week
They cost only $10 a piece to download
So it would make no sense why you would drop
$30 on this game when these two games
Are $20
Some more XBLA and PSN ports
That have not yet been announced
Are coming
By the way there were a couple that had leaked
Previously including Sega Bass Fishing
And Space Channel 5
Part 2
So that could be
Where this is going is that maybe it will be
Four games in one
Although I could really do without Sega Bass Fishing
I'm sorry but I'm not really into the
Fishing games but whatever
But
Okay it was fun with the rod controller
And
But mostly because of the fact like haha
It's a rod controller now I'm over it
And then in the Japanese version it would say
FISH GET
We need the game that was formally named
Daytona
Do do do do do do
Have you seen the new one now?
They don't have the Daytona song in there
So it's like do do do do do do
Let's go
Cheat pack
It's pretty fun
Thank you. So ladies and gentlemen in our chat room
Needs to have Power Stone 1 and 2
Thanks. Agreed with those Capcom games
Ah yes they were
So probably not gonna happen
But you can dream
Remember Power Stone collection did come out on
PSP. Oh that's right. Good call
Anyhow Dark Sakura
What do you have for us?
I have stuff and nonsense again
Actually this is pretty cool
Pinball is coming to Xbox Live
Arcade and Playstation Network
In December
Put out by Zen Studios
Um
It actually was leaked out
Because of a ratings board
Deal
But it's going to be coming out
And it will have
Different tables that are
Themed after Marvel
Superheroes like one that I'm looking at
Right now is Iron Man Pinball
I don't know
If it's actually patterned after the stern Iron Man
Pinball. I don't think so
Because that table kinda sucked
The one based off of the movie
Not for the comic
And then they said initially
Four different tables will be available
There's Blade, Spiderman, Wolverine and as I said
Iron Man
Taking a look at some of them right now
And there's also supposed to be
New download content coming
Later on
Okay the Blade one looks stupid
Iron Man one looks okay
Spiderman one looks kinda fun
Um
The Wolverine one
It's Wolverine
Oh it's alright
I don't know it could be fun
I'm kinda picky on my Pinball
I'll check it out. I think Pinball FX2 is pretty awesome
Yeah we got it
Good times
It's free. Everybody should go get it if you don't already have it
I know right
It's the same. It automatically imports all the tables
I think I talked about this last week or the week before
You did? I did
Well it's not a big surprise
Rumors that the
PSP2 prototype
They have leaked images
Of it and
It's actually been confirmed by some
Developers
Saying that the photos are legitimate
But that it's
A dev kit and that the hardware
Will probably change
The way it looks by the time the system comes out
But some of the features that were
Noticed in the pictures
It's got a front facing camera
Microphone
Finally two analog
Sticks which is awesome
Also has a back facing camera
And the rumored
Trackpad which is on the back
Of the device
That seems awfully weird to me
Unless somehow the screen like
Flips over where you can use the trackpad on the front
But um
Neat
I guess
The prototype right now looks very similar
To like the PSP Go
But they're saying that it's possible that they may
Make either
They're gonna have like two different models
One that resembles like the PSP 3000
And one the PSP Go or it's gonna be just
The PSP Go
Also it will not have a UMD drive
Instead it will be using
Some sort of memory
Sticks
Interesting so they are
Saying there's gonna be a physical media
But it's just not gonna be these discs anymore
Uh yeah
Let me be the first to say that if it's gonna be memory
Sticks that this thing's gonna be using
This will be cracked so fast
It's not even funny
Because if it's on a physical device like that
Why even bother
I know that's kind of
A scary thought on their side
But not a lot of other
Like new things about what could be on this system
Besides the whole trackpad thing
I mean you know
The new DS is going
All 3D
And stuff
Well the top screen looks like it's supposed to be
An HD screen they're saying that the
Graphics are gonna be comparable to the
Xbox 360
Oh interesting
Alright well I'm sure we'll be hearing
Plenty more about that at E3
Because it really is hard to say
That this is not at least somewhat
True at this point
Anyhow we got about 6 months to go before E3
Something that's coming out a lot sooner
If you want to get a new console is the
OnLive micro console
It is coming out December 2nd and it costs
$99 this is the whole little
Console for you to use OnLive on your
TV and yeah
When they say micro console like this thing
It's small I mean it's basically a
Miniature PC that will just do all the
Connecting to the internet and the whole cloud
Gaming thing
Strange little thing
They've already got those internet TV devices
Like at Fry's so I imagine it's the same deal
It's you know all it is is really
It just serves the
Sole function of connecting to the online
Services and using whatever technology it does to
Deliver the video just quickly
To your TV so
Kinda cool
By the way they are saying that you will only be able to get
This though on the OnLive
Website until like next year
And it's only going to be in limited quantities
So if you think you might want one of these
You gotta act like really soon
There is some other news coming out of OnLive
They are getting rid
Of the whole monthly fee that is
Going out the door
There's now going to be a flat rate pricing
Plan that will provide access to
Back catalog and indie games
Kinda similar to what you see with Netflix
And all that it's
So they're thinking maybe no more than $10
A month but there's no longer going to be a fee just to
Access the service itself which is always
Kinda a dumb idea and nobody was really
Paying for it yet anyway because it was like
Sponsored right now but yeah
That is all going out the window which is good
More information on the full
Pricing and the lineup will be coming out in December
That's according to the CEO Steve
Prolem in December we'll announce
Pricing and the lineup of games it's literally
Just a matter of getting publishers to sign
This and that and the other thing so
Very cool they eliminated the monthly
Subscription fee after they kinda pulled the
User base and looked there
And saw what users really wanted
That's cool that they're listening to that
That's smart
Also there
Could be some new platforms that come to this
As well and possibly
Exclusive games
The company is trying to get some big name
Releases as well Duke Nukem Forever
Deus Ex Human Revolution
Assassin's Creed Brotherhood Red Faction Armageddon
Ghost Recon Future Soldier Fear 3
Driver and so on and so on and so on
All those types of games they're trying to get as well
What's also interesting
Is that they're looking at
iOS versions of the client
Software so on live
On your iPhone
That won't work very well I don't know how that would work
Without better controls
But I guess
You might
Might not be too far out of the realm
Of possibility I mean if Netflix and all that
Is on there somebody wants to put games on there
So I don't have to control with you
I know I get that I get that but who knows
Who knows what could happen
So there you go
By the way Apple TV they've also
Been toying with the idea of in Google TV
But they say Apple TV
May not work because it runs at 720p
And 30 frames a second you'll never get above
30 frames a second and you can't really
Get the 720p
So
Who knows
Anyhow let's move on and open up the old
Mailbag every week DarkSakura
Dives into the mailbag head first
Mailbag at
OrangeLoungeRadio.com and she pulls out some
Of her favorite emails and reads them for us
Live on air but
I don't know if there were a lot of pickins this week were there
No there weren't but I did get a reply
From the one who
Got the
Wrong name and because
They're so nice about it
He's our winner
Aww what a nice
Well Mike
Congratulations you've
Won a Castlevania Symphony of the
Night Xbox Live Arcade
Code
Enjoy
Free stuff is always good
So that's it
That was it for the emails really?
We didn't get any questions or nothing?
No
Dear OrangeLoungeRadio why is DarkSakura
So cool
I don't know listener
I think it's in her DNA
And that says such a bitch
Like I think you changed
Rob got pot hollered
At least it wasn't
Flaming hot pot holder
Well that was mailbag fail
Fail
Every one of you needs to send
An email and then we'll get Rob to read them
DarkSakura is going to have to read 50 emails next week
We'll get our special guest to read them next week
Do we have special guest next week?
You know who our special guest is?
Marissa
I am so excited
We need a pile of
emails bigger than her boobies
That's a lot of emails
That's impossible
Get starting
Marissa's rack is quite mighty
Well in the absence of emails
There's always time for FUs
Um FU to the sudden realization of my unemployment
I hated that place
A lot of the people I worked with
Actually a lot of them pissed me off too
But
It's sort of the uncertainty side of things
What am I going to do now?
I'm not having insurance
But I get to finish school
I can sleep in as much as I want to
And I'm getting my severance check
So it's not a big loss
But still kind of melancholy
You know what I mean?
It's a weird in between
place kind of be
And also um
I want frozen yogurt a lot so I feed me not having any even though I do have pumpkin ice cream
OMG I want pink berry so bad
Pink berry!
Let's go
That pumpkin pink berry right now
It's not good
It's not terrible though
But it's pumpkin
Hardly
Whatever
Loki
I guess FU to um
I don't know black asleep I guess
It's just uh
You don't have to get up early every day
It sucks
I hate waking up at 4 in the morning
And sleeping on the couch
Well
It'll only be for hopefully
A few more months
Or maybe another year or two or three
A few more years
Look forward to it
A few more years and then um
The random calling into bed and getting kicked in the head
That happens too
And then when he's like 15 or 16 he's gonna start fighting with you every day
And then your friends who don't have children have to hear about it
Or your entire internet radio audience that'll be fun
I'm also sending major hearts to Becky right now
My FU of the week
Uh goes to all the sand
That somehow lodged itself in my vagina earlier this week
Because dang there was a lot of it
No I had a really crap week
But things got better they always do
It gets better guys
It gets better
That's really it otherwise I'm just
Just looking forward to getting the week of
Lady you know
You know we're doing a show right
Yeah
But I want Dan to give an FU because Dan's FUs are amazing
Okay George can do one
An FU?
FU of the week duh
Aren't you mad at something that you want to say FU to?
Jamie loves to put people on the squad
I know I love doing it George
Which is kind of shocking because I'm normally mad at everything
What's that George? Hi George
Hello
I'm normally mad at everything but I'm not mad at anything this week
Well FU for being so happy
Damn you and your happiness
So I gave you one
That's awesome
Alright
Poor George
That's when people come over to my house they get to be on the show
You come over to my house you're going to be telling them my show
Get in here
Nobody gets off the stage unless they sing the blues
You know where that came from right
Adventures in babysitting
Just a couple more stories then we're going to get to the skype line
At 1877 game
O-L-R
Hey oh I don't know if I like this
Jamie get ready to rage
What? Jeremy Todd 1 in our chat room
FU to Jamie for fucking up the FUs of the week
You know what
Don't say that to somebody with ops
Because I will kick your ass
Literally
Alright
Oh no
Oh no he didn't
Alright
Oh he says FU to myself
I don't care
Alright lowkey come on let's move on
Portal 2 has been delayed again
Yeah man it wasn't going to come out
When they said anything
Wait wait wait wait you mean Valve delayed a game?
What?
And this is news?
That's alright though it's just putting extra polish on it
It's been delayed to April 20th 2011
The day after my birthday
People you know what to do
It's the day after your birthday
You're screwed
My birthday lasts all week
It was originally planned for holiday 2010
And delayed to February 9th
So now it's April
I kind of always thought it was going to be April anyways
I thought that's what it was
I didn't realize it was actually February
It was the release date for that but yeah whatever
It's April now so get over it
Alright just in time for Jamie's birthday
What about my birthday?
What are you going to get me for my birthday Valve?
I'll give you a dollar
You're not Valve
I'll give you a Valve
I'm sure we got a couple
Alright file this last story
Of our night under what
And huh
Yeah this is a
Comment from Bobby Kotick I don't know why
Whatever this guy says makes news but I don't know
You love to hate him or you hate to love him
I don't know very interesting comic
Though a comic
Freudian slip maybe I don't know
Very interesting comment from Mr. Kotick
Though it's about the online pass
Thing you know EA, THQ
$10 online play if you buy
The game used
Quote from Bobby Kotick
We can do some of these things
EA's and others have done
We actually don't think it's in the best interest
Of the gamer and so we've chosen not to
From a financial
Perspective you look at it and say
Okay well the retailer is not paying us
Anything for the privilege of doing it and you know
We invest all this capital in making a game
We're not getting any credit any return on their
Resale of the game but you know something
The best way to keep people engaged in your game
Experience is to keep giving them
More great content
I think you always need to be sensitive to that
Relationship and not crossing the line to a
Place where the customer feels like they
Have been taken advantage of
So that's why
They would rather put out $15
Map packs for their games
Than an online pass
You know what though
I'm actually kind of okay
With that
I mean
It would be better if it was cheaper but at least
It's like more content
But the only thing, here's what I don't like
Is that when that additional content
Is um
Stuff that like is
Necessary to the game and what I
Really hate is when that content is already
On the disc because that is not
Downloadable content, oh man I haven't gone on
Download to unlock, I haven't gone on this rant
In years, that is not downloadable
Content that is pay to unlock
Content and that's what we should be referring
To it as, when you're
Paying to unlock content on our young disc
Like beautiful
Katamari on the 360, had plenty of pay
To unlock content
There it is
Alright that's gonna do it for our
News stories tonight
We're gonna open up the Skype line now, I should probably take us
Off Do Not Disturb in order to do that
Orange Lounge Radio is our username on Skype
Or you can give us a call on the old telefono
877-GAME-OLR
Is our name on
I'm sorry 877-GAME-OLR
Is our phone number
And you can give that a call
In the meantime
I don't know if Loki has any
Last minute stories tonight but
You have anything last minute for us Loki?
Uh
Yeah apparently there's gonna be
A new cheat tool coming to the
PlayStation 3 from Code Freak
Um
Apparently the people
Behind the Code Freak
Um tool
CyberGadget have announced a new device coming
To the PS3 in Japan
Um it's a
Walkthrough tool as they call it
And it's gonna cost 7800 yen
And it'll come with cheats for 50 titles
And they say
More codes can be downloaded via
PC
So I don't know
It sounds like modified saves almost
Shall we go to the phones?
Yes let's
Hi you're on Orange Launch Radio who's this?
Hey this is X-Link
Hi X-Link
I just had to beat out Rama for one week
That's alright long time listener first time caller right?
As always
What's on your mind?
I have a question for you
How the hell can you dog Age of Empire 3
But yet you will play Civilization
Because I'm a hypocrite
I'm just kind of curious
I was like wait a minute you're sitting there saying
Age of Empire is not worth the 10 cents
But yet you would play
Powers on end Civilization 5
Because I have a very simple answer for you
It's just gonna blow your mind
My simple answer for all of this X-Link
It's amazing I can't solve world peace
You ready?
The reason why I don't want to pay 10 cents
For Age of Empires 3 is because
I have Civilization 5
I don't need anything else
Well that's true I kind of agree with you
Unfortunately I don't have Civilization 5
So I have to go with the next best thing for right now
But yes
In all seriousness
You know what 10 cents for a game is obviously a steal
But I'm just more making fun of the fact that like
The entirety of the internet is freaking out about like
OMG game for 10 cents
But it's kind of like well yeah
The game's 5 years old and who would give a shit about this anyway
It's like most of the Steam sales
You rarely see current games
Going on sale on Steam
Although to be fair
Steam does manage to get some of those really good deals
Like you know when they were putting Torchlight on sale
For like half its price
They've done some deals with Poker Night which isn't even out yet
So you know
Which I'm looking forward to that
Because that supposedly is going to be coming out Tuesday
So I'm definitely looking forward to that
I think it's actually tomorrow
Is it tomorrow? I think so
Maybe it's tomorrow
Jeremy Todd one in our chatroom says
But it's only 10 cents
I bought it 6 different times just so I can have more AOE 3 than you
Now that's showing your support
Wow
Yeah but yeah
You know again
Competition never a bad thing
I'm really excited for Black Friday
OMG we're going to get some steal games
But that's a really good deal though
10 cents you can't really
Don't really want to pass that up
For even a game I mean even if you don't get a gift
For somebody else you know 10 cents
We'll see we'll see
It sounds like almost like we're doing one of those info commercials for those children
I know right
It's just the price of a cup of coffee a day
Precisely
But you know I saw that I was amazed by that
I'm like a $40 game 10 cents
Well it was $40 back in 2005
But I guarantee you that game is in like $3 bargain bins
At Best Buys everywhere
Probably but according to their website it was still at $40
Well of course because it's a Microsoft game
They don't want to admit that it's you know
Yes they officially haven't dropped the price of it
Does not mean everybody else hasn't to try to clear out inventory
That's right
Speaking of Microsoft and things like that
I'm actually looking forward to this whole Dungeon Siege 3
Even though technically it's what Squeenix is doing it now
Microsoft has done the first couple games
I'm looking forward to that
Those should be very interesting
Hopefully they don't bastardize it like Final Fantasy XIV
Well it's not like an online MMO type of thing
And don't feel too bad
I was right with you with the whole raid thing
Remember because unfortunately my account
I was stupid and let it lapse
So I wasn't there during that whole time
Yeah we're not able to take phone calls during Horde House
So I know you couldn't really chime in on this
But yeah I know we both missed it
At least you don't have to feel all alone
Like I'm the only one who didn't get it
No I'm right there with you
All in due time my friend
Yeah I know we'll get it eventually
We just might be level 81 or 82
But hey it'll work out
We'll be geared for it
Cataclysm happening soon
The rumor on the street is that the world is coming to an end
On Tuesday in World of Warcraft
It's the end of the world as we know it
But I feel fine
They're doing a lot of odds and ends and disconnects
Going to be more Gloriant than ever
So yes
We all look forward to that
Now you started playing WoW with Wrath of the Lich King right?
So are you looking forward to your first
Proper expansion rolling out?
No because I don't have the money for it
Aww
Well you know what the good news is though
You won't be competing with everyone else
Trying to level in those zones and everything
Because it's going to be a shit show
I was going to do that anyways to be quite honest
My first goal when that was going to come out
Was going to be the archeology
To get that to 450
Gotcha
Well anyway the other hosts are going to start
Glaring at me if I fill up the show with the Warcraft chat
Nope
My eyes glosed over and my brain went foggy
Exactly
That's why they made me take it to a separate show
Have a good one
Thanks for calling
Bye
1877 Game OLR if you want to give us a call
Our username on Skype is OrangeLoungeRadio
Give us a call
Meanwhile do we have any last minute stories
Mr. Loki over there
Well good
Because we have other calls coming in so we might as well go to those calls
Hi you're on OrangeLoungeRadio who's this
Hey it's Ronman this time my Skype works
Long time listener first time caller right
Hi
What's on your mind buddy
Hey um
Now this is something I wanted to talk about
Unfortunately I wasn't able to last week but
This is the whole
Music game genre with
Rock band and guitar hero
Now let me ask you
Guys do you see it
Like really dying
Dead like DDR or
Something else
DDR hasn't exactly fallen
Over dead though like I get what you're saying
DDR is not what it was to
You and me ten years ago
But they did just release a game
Two weeks ago so I don't see any
Reason why they won't continue to release
Rock band style plastic guitar and drum
Games ten years from now
But it's not going to be what it was
In it's hey day when rock band and all
This stuff first came out
Okay cause the way I see it is this
Konami throws us DDR
Yay here's another one
Wait wait what is this
Yeah Konami we got to talk what is
This drop
Or as with rock band and guitar hero
Here you go yay
Here you go plus we threw her some
More stuff sweet
Here's another game this time
We'll give you more stuff sweet
That's the way I see it
And having an interesting
Discussion with a couple of people on Twitter about this
Who think that the whole
Gaming rhythm gaming is falling
Apart due to lack of sales
I honestly believe lack of sales
Come from the fact of it's too
Damn expensive because of the pricing
Of the bundles and all the other accessories
More or less right about now in this economy
Who has 180 bucks
And what I would tell your friends on
Twitter is again the sales
Of Dance Central sort of
Kind of counters that argument that music games
Are just dead in the water
Music games are just evolving
Plastic guitar and plastic drum games
Are on their way out
That is what these studies are showing
What has the music genre been focused on for the past few years
What has the media been focused on for the past few years
It's all about these plastic guitar games
Alright their time is coming to an end
Let's bring on the next big thing in music gaming
It's out there somewhere
Which is why I don't blame
EA for not bundling
Rock band 3
With a pro guitar
Or even a regular guitar
My roommate went to go buy the game like last Sunday
He comes back and he's like I didn't buy the game
It's because all the instruments are not made by EA anymore
So that's why they're not doing any of the bundles
Even the bundles with the keyboard were actually
Being published by Mad Cats
And they opted out on doing
Bundles with all that stuff because they need to have
80,000 bundles in the stores
And it would confuse people
Most retailers though are kind of smart
And they put the plastic guitars
Right next to the game, you know what I mean?
Exactly, and I explained that to him
But he still, it took me like 3 days
To explain to him, they're not bundling it
Because it's a different company making the accessories
If you want the pro guitar that badly
Just be like everybody else
Pre-order, go down there
And whoop somebody's ass to get one
Interesting, I wonder if
Just all this saturation is partially to blame
Well, as we went into a couple weeks ago
On the show, it kind of is
I think Guitar Hero
In some ways is to blame for rock bands
Tumble
But I don't know, you know what?
We still have All Christmas to get through
I think they'll still sell more copies of Rock Band 3
I tend to think so too
And you know
Not for nothing, I did pick up Rock Band
The Beatles' Rock Band, but I can understand why
The game didn't do so well
And the same thing with Green Day Rock Band
Because it's simple
Most of today's, to this generation
Probably had never heard of the Beatles
I guarantee you
I guess it's just me being biased
But if it was Rock Band, Bon Jovi
I think we would have done at least 2-3 times
Normal sales
Because everybody's heard of Bon Jovi
Hate me if you want
That's not really a game I'd be interested in
That's the problem with these games
No matter what, no matter who the band is
That they pick, because I'll sit here and go
But give me Rock Band Journey and oh my god
You know, but I realize it's still not going to sell
Any better, you know, I think
You take the Beatles
They are the biggest selling band of all time
Whether they are anymore or whatever
It's just one of those, you know what?
A game so focused on one band
Is never going to appeal to a mass market
But Rob, if they gave you the choice
If they said, okay, hey, we're going to release
Rock Band Journey as a standalone game
Or you can download all the songs
You probably download all the songs
I would like it better if I could download all the songs
And like a Journey themed background or something
Fair enough
You know what I mean? Like something to kind of add into the Rock Band experience
Which I'm kind of surprised they haven't done
Like, you know, you have all these track packs
Or whatever, why not have like a
You know, no doubt themed arena
To go with the CD or something like that, you know?
I'm glad you asked that question, and the reason why
Is because they have each song
They have programmed in
Different camera cuts and stuff
Depending on which stage they're in
And if they add another stage, they go back and edit
Every single song to add that stage into it
Interesting
I always thought it was just more generic than that
Like, you know, cut here, cut here, or whatever
No. Interesting
Rob, you're right about that
You wouldn't buy the game, but
What I see is this
If it was out of like ten people
Maybe eight people would buy
The Bon Jovi game compared to maybe like
Six would buy the Journey themed game
You see what I'm saying?
Go with a band that more people would probably buy
Because it's a given
100% is not going to buy
A band themed game
Because not everybody is behind them, you know?
Here's the thing though
I think there are very, very, very few
And I know I've gotten into this on the show before
So you've probably heard this feel before
There are very, very few bands
And artists that
Can justify an entire release
For their brand
And the Beatles were
Certainly one of them
Michael Jackson is another
And there's probably nobody else
In that top tier, to be honest
I don't think there is any other band or musical
Act that fits into that same caliber
As Michael Jackson and the Beatles. None
Now you go down to the next tier
And that's where you get your
Bon Jovis and your
Van Halen's and your
Aerosmith and Metallica
But I don't even think
Green Day fits into that tier
Honestly, I was too fond of
Green Day being in that tier
In that tier above. I don't even think
Aerosmith was more deserving than Metallica
If you'll ask me, but that's just my opinion
Right, and then it just
Starts to get into opinions
But you just have to look at history, record sales
How many t-shirts of the band's name have been sold
I think Metallica
And Aerosmith are about even, it's just different
Crowds. Pretty much
So, but I think
That very very top tier
There's nobody in it but the Beatles and Michael Jackson
Nobody has that same kind of
Pull. And now we see
What we're getting, I mean Michael Jackson
Just never really worked right for a rock band
Kind of set up, so now we see
What we're getting instead, which I don't know if
It's the best idea, but I won't see
For real until I get to play the game
I'm interested, I gotta say
I find the idea of a Michael Jackson
Dance-y type just dance game
More appealing than some of the other dance
Games I've seen
Well, I mean, I've seen people
Play, I think it's pretty fun. Me personally, if I'm gonna
Sit there and play it, I'm gonna get the official
Loafers and the glove and the jacket
And just rock out with my cock out, you know
Hey, hold on there, Michael Jackson got in trouble
For that. Alright. Yeah, but I'm an
Adult, so it's okay. Alright
Alright, we gotta let you go buddy
But I appreciate the discussion, it was good
Come on buddy. You too, later
Later
1877 game OLR, username on
Skype is OrangeLawnsRadio
GioVidea says, I want Billy Joel for rock band
Hey, good news GioVidea, they're gonna do like
This huge Billy Joel track pack
Keyboards and all
I believe December-ish
Early December-ish
Is when it's coming, and I'm talking like
It's like ten songs, so
That should be very exciting, correct?
I don't know
Should we go to more calls, or
Last minute stories, or what are we gonna do here?
1877 game OLR, username on
Skype is OrangeLawnsRadio
You wanna throw out a last minute story real quick, Logan?
Yeah, sure, let's do that
Okay, I'm trying to think
Oh, this is kinda cool
I saw this actually
You know that game, Super Mario crossover
Well of course they're doing another update
For it, and they're adding the blaster master
Vehicle as
One of the characters you can play as
Yeah, I saw that on the Twitter, somebody tweeted that
To us this week, I saw that, that's cool
Yes, very very cool, so
That update is not yet live
But it will be coming soon though
I actually played a little bit of that game before
The show with the last update
Ryu from Ninja Gaiden
So
Very cool
Alright, hold on, our phones are lighting up like all at once now
Let me go take some calls, hi you're on OrangeLawnsRadio
Who's this?
Hi, this is Pazinator
Hi everybody
Yeah, a couple of things that I
Didn't get around to tweeting to you
For
They're all kinda interrelated
First off
Right off the top of my list
For those of us
That have access to a PlayStation 3
And the PlayStation Network
There's another
Free anime
Episode currently on the store
It's called
Saigon the Complete Series Episode 1
The 60 Billion
Double Dollar Man
Hey, let me ask you this
How do you keep tabs on
All this free stuff that's coming out
Is this you just checking the store kinda every Wednesday
When they do the updates, or is there like a blog
That kinda tracks all the free shit on
PSN
There's no blog that I'm aware of
That tracks all the free stuff
It's just that
I was like self-censoring, did you hear that?
Yeah
I just hate to say it
But I got no life
And I'm constantly
Checking things on the store
You know what, it's okay
When Game Room was still new and fresh
And the games were really notable
Every Wednesday, I would plop on the couch
And run over and see what came out
And Virtual Console, it was new too
No worries, dude
Yeah, I really won't
Get into my opinion of
The free show cause
Why I think of the show may differ from
What you or Jeannie or Loki
Would think of the show
My own opinion
Would probably be irrelevant
Sum it up into one sentence
Basically
It's a free show
Even if you download it
And hate the show
It's free
That was a perfect sentence, Spaznator
It's a free show
Perfect, perfect
Alright
On a relaying note, for those of us
In our age group
That grew up with it
They just
Start putting, of all things
He-Man and Masters of the Universe
On the PlayStation Network
Dude, really? Is She-Ra up yet?
Not yet
But at this rate, I'm wondering if it
Goes up there soon
They don't have all the episodes
Up yet, just 33
But damn, damn it all
I, I grew up
You know, watching that show
Religiously, I mean, you know
Dad and Voltron and Transformers
I mean, you know, I practically
Had a orgasm once I realized
They went up on the store and
Granted, you know, the first
One on the store was, you know, they had
A fail at the same time, 99 cents
Each, you know, I grabbed
What I could afford and
I was blessed, sorry
Only two episodes
But as soon as I came
I'm gonna snatch up the rest
And, you know, if only
They put up like Gia, Joe
And the rest of the
Episodes of Transformers
You know, season two and onward
You know, I'd be a
Happy camper, you know?
Hey, Gia Videa is saving the day for me and pointing out
That She-Ra is at least on Netflix
So you can get it on your PS3
You know, when they switch to digital
TV and stuff right here and we started getting all those weird
.2 channels
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah
There is actually a channel, I don't remember what it's called now
But in the Sacramento area that plays
Old cartoons like that
They even play the original Ghostbusters cartoon
Not the 80s cartoon
But the one that actually predated the movies
You know, like from the 70s
Uh, what, who's station
Is that Fox's number two?
I don't remember
It's not the more or
It, it
My friend actually watches
A lot of that stuff
Voltron and stuff
One of them, the Fox affiliate here had a
Second channel that was nothing
But music videos
It was like what MTV should have been
But that went away, it only lasted like four years
If you haven't checked it out
Because not all cable companies pick them up
Get your HDTV to search for signals in the area
Because that's kind of part of the cool thing about HDTV
Now your NBC station
Only ever had one channel
But now they have like three or four
Some of them
And some of them are weird, like we have this one, it's like
More TV Sacramento where they play these random movies
Like these strangest movies out there
Some of them are gonna be like Gospel
And some of them are nothing but the Weather Channel
But local, but there's some
You'll find some weird shit out there
Sorry
Yeah, yeah, yeah
I can't really knock
Because I never used it
So I can't really say anything positive or negative
About it until I use it
You know
The thing is with me
In order to use it I would have to get a credit card
I don't have one currently
So I'm basically stuck
Buying things off of
Either Xbox Live
Zoom Marketplace
Or TSN
And in a way
It kind of works out
In a way
It may be
Kind of expensive
Depending on how you look at
Compared to other
Ways of getting stuff
But at the same time
It's also cheaper
At least in the sense that
You can buy the stuff piecemeal
Low over time
Over an extended period of time
And not only that
But at least
Compared to getting
Stuff on BluRay
Or DVD or whatever
Where you're basically stuck
Every episode of
One particular season
Where you really only want
Let's say an episode of
Five of whatever series
Well it's nice if nothing else
At least there's different options
Out there
Yeah
Granted
TSN's not perfect
I've been on board
On the show multiple times complaining
About here and there
But at least
It's out there
It's something you can do at least
Alright Spaznator we're going to let you go so we wrap up
The show but thanks so much for your call
Really appreciate it
Have a good one buddy
Alright that's going to do it for the skype line tonight
Sorry to those that didn't get through
And if you're sitting there going why is it always the same people
Every week to get through on skype
Because you're not calling us
So if you're mad at hearing the same people
Every week you've got to give us a call
1-877-GAME-OL-R or remember there are
Other ways you can interact with the show
If you're like shy and you're like I don't want any people
To hear my voice hehe
Or you don't want your parents knowing that you're calling that's fine
Give us an email mailbag at orange lounge radio
Dot com we don't want you to get in trouble
You can also send us tweets
This is the show where every gamer has a voice
We want to make sure you are heard
Anyhow any more last minute stories
We want to get to tonight Loki before we wrap things up
Yeah one
One other thing here
Halo Wars they're turning off the servers
December 15th I heard about that
So that sucks and the game's not that old
Either and
Apparently yeah
Barely two years old Microsoft
Is pulling the plug on Halo Wars
Getting rid of the leaderboard and stat
Tracking as well as the forums
They're just
Throwing it all away aren't they
They are forums that expensive to maintain
Really
It says community was informed that on Tuesday
They were also told that they were transitioning
To the Halo Waypoint forums
Which is a nice way of saying
That halowars.com
Is going away
So it says
More importantly the forums will disappear
And so will online stat tracking
And it says
I know this will be rough on a lot of you guys
This is from one of the forum mods
And here's some of the comments
Game is dead. Fuck you. No stat tracking
You just killed this game. Fuck you
They are cheap bastards
I'm buying this domain when they let it go lol
And it says possibly the most
Close knit video game
Forum community is going to be tossed
With a bunch of reach junkies
Doh
So sad
So TigerClaw sent me this link he wanted me to play
For you Loki
You might recognize this
Wow this is old
I was thinking about the ghostbusters
And the real ghostbusters but I didn't even
Know there was this really old one
We used to watch this all the time
My little brothers loved it
And when we were really really little
We had this
It was a garage that had been converted to a
Playroom and they'd take
This big chair and put a driving wheel in front
Of it and try to beat the car
Nice
JeremyTaw1 in our chat room is kind of pissed about
This story that Loki just reported on
I'm sorry but this whole server pulling thing
Is bullshit. Someone pays 60 bucks
For a game should be able to play it online
For at least a few years without them
Turning it off. Now here's the thing though
I don't think it says that they're taking down the online
They're taking down the leaderboards and stat tracking
All the frills that come on the website
I still think you can play online
Because it's Microsoft's live servers
I can't imagine they'd take those down
What else do you pay for gold for?
The other quick thing I wanted to throw out here
That Tigerclaw had sent us
Was about the video game awards on
Spike TV. I guess the nominees have been announced
But I'm kind of like
Are these really relevant?
The only reason why the video game awards
Are really relevant at all
Is that they show commercials for new games
And get new game announcements during the show
And I guess, I don't know
It kind of tries to bring this like
Legitimacy quote unquote
To the video game scene but I'm just kind of like
Eh, I don't need it
But for the record if you're curious what they nominated
Game of the Year, Call of Duty Black Ops
God of War 3, Halo Reach, Mass Effect 2
Red Dead Redemption
Those are the nominees for Game of the Year
Okay, no surprises there
Any other last minute stories, Loki?
I think that's
About it
Fan made Thief 2
Multiplayer beta has been released
So if you're a fan of Thief 2
And wish that you could have played it with more than one person
Then you might want to check it out
Alright
Well it's time for us to wrap up the show
And get on out of here for the night
And you know, so forth
So Dark Soccer, do you have any final thoughts
For our listeners tonight?
Money, I can have some?
Pinkberry!
Aw man, you just took mine, I was gonna say
My final thought is Pinkberry, can I have some?
But I'll just say
Four day vacation, can I has it?
Loki, your final thought tonight
My final thought
Is
I get to make turkey
Turducken?
No, it's just turkey
Turducken's just too, I don't think that'd be too much
What are you doing, are you
Since both you and the missus
Have parents locally, you kind of have to do like
Two thanksgivings at once, right?
Not necessarily, we're just having our way over to our house
Oh, smart
Smart, alright, good luck with that this year
Alright, that's it guys, we're
Out of here, have a wonderful night
And we'll see you next week, hey if you enjoyed
The show tonight, all we ask guys
Tell a couple people about the show
Tell folks that you enjoyed Orange Lounge Radio
And help us spread the word, because you know guys
We don't have a huge website, we're not part
Of a gaming magazine or anything like that
We rely on word of mouth, so
Tell a couple people about the show, and if you think you've told
Everyone you can already, then please
Consider leaving us a nice review on iTunes
A five star review goes a long way in helping us
Get the word out and more exposure on the network
Really appreciate it guys
Have a wonderful night and we'll see you next time
Next week here at Orange Lounge Radio
Have a wonderful Thanksgiving to those of you in the
US that celebrate it, to everyone else
Well have a great week and we'll see you on Sunday
You've been listening to
Orange Lounge Radio
Orange Lounge Radio is an
Orange Lounge production
To join us for a live show
Visit www.allgames.com
Sunday nights at 6pm Pacific time
The views and opinions expressed
On Orange Lounge Radio
Do not necessarily reflect those
Of the entire staff of Orange Lounge Radio
Or allgames.com
But we're probably right anyway
See you next week!