[SPEAKER_06]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and released to our podcast stream twice weekly.
[SPEAKER_06]: To listen to the first half of this episode, visit www.orangeloungeradio.com for links to websites with listings of past episodes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now the conclusion of this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: And we are back here on Orange Lounge Radio on this Sunday, October the 28th, 2007 for this Part B of our program.
[SPEAKER_08]: And since we already talked about our gaming weeks and all that stuff in Part A, you can hear about my injury and all that fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: You've got to go back in the archives, though, and grab Part A because we're already in the second half.
[SPEAKER_08]: And in the second half, we started off with gaming news.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, what do you got for us?
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, what I got for you is a...
[SPEAKER_07]: Brand new thing they're adding to the Wii Virtual Console.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's the ability to give games as gifts, apparently.
[SPEAKER_07]: So you can purchase a Virtual Console game and then put one of your friend's names on there and it will automatically send them a message allowing them to download the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's kind of cool, except it doesn't address the fact that what if the person already has the game?
[SPEAKER_07]: That's exactly what I want to know.
[SPEAKER_07]: What if somebody tries to send me a game which I already have?
[SPEAKER_07]: Too bad, I guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think that they should have the option where you can send, and this should be in all, I think, the online things, at least Microsoft, they should have an option where you can send people points.
[SPEAKER_07]: Without having to go buy one of those cards that's taxed?
[SPEAKER_07]: Example.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have my account on Live, and then I have those four other Xbox 360s.
[SPEAKER_07]: Say I want to
[SPEAKER_07]: Download a map or something on all of them.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't want to fucking have to put in billing information for five different 360s.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'd rather just send the 200 points it costs to buy this map to each one.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know why you can't do that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Can't you just tie it to your live name and then go on each?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, because you have to have a different name for each one.
[SPEAKER_07]: You have to be tied to that account.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's stupid.
[SPEAKER_07]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: But yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: So this basically sounds like it's something that's in the very early stages that they haven't really mapped out how you're going to give the gifts or any of that yet, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wasn't there supposed to be some massive Wii update last month that didn't actually end up happening?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you think it'll be here in time for the holiday season, which is just around the corner?
[SPEAKER_07]: I hope so.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hope they have that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm kind of curious what they're plotting, because you know how Nintendo likes to slowly pull off the wrapping on things, you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_08]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, anyhow, one thing that's getting the wrapping pulled off of it this week is Virtual Console in Japan.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the Virtual Console releases come out in Japan on Tuesdays.
[SPEAKER_08]: And this week in Japan, they got a little game called Downtown Nekitsu Koshinyoku Soriyuki Dayo Kodai.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know what that is.
[SPEAKER_08]: And what would you call that?
[SPEAKER_03]: River City Ransom
[SPEAKER_08]: I believe it might have been.
[SPEAKER_08]: So kind of interesting there that... Wait a minute, Sega Channel?
[SPEAKER_08]: Hmm, what kind of thing does this open up the Virtual Console to?
[SPEAKER_08]: How about some Nintendo Channel releases?
[SPEAKER_08]: Or what do they call that?
[SPEAKER_08]: The... Was it the BS or something?
[SPEAKER_03]: Just the Teleview.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it's Teleview, that's it.
[SPEAKER_08]: BS is what it was for short.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, um... That would be cool if we got like the Zelda remake over here and that kind of stuff, but... I've played a ROM of it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe I'm just dreaming a little bit, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, for our friends in the UK, they get some cool stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: The coolest being Yoshi's Story that was on the Nintendo 64 for 1,000 Wii Points.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yoshi's Story was a very, very cute game.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's all I have to say.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, as I mentioned in Part A, Super Air Zonk!
[SPEAKER_03]: Rockabilly Paradise, which was a Turbo CD shooter.
[SPEAKER_03]: They've removed a few of the graphical features to it.
[SPEAKER_03]: and they have uh instead uh basically just beefed up the soundtrack a bit so super Arizona and also magician lord 900 points it's a neo geo game i have yet to download a neo geo game onto my wii i just i don't know i get magician lord i kind of want it but i don't know like
[SPEAKER_07]: Magician Lord is one of those games that are like, ooh, it was so awesome, and then I downloaded it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ten years ago.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wow, this wasn't that good.
[SPEAKER_07]: What the hell was I thinking on that?
[SPEAKER_07]: I remember it being very hard.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's like how Virtual Console does all of its business, is off of reactions like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, oh, remember this game?
[SPEAKER_08]: This game was awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then you download it, and you're like, wait, no it wasn't.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's why they don't have demos.
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess, probably.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, we still need to do Super Metroid, Rob.
[SPEAKER_08]: We do.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's make it happen.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can't do a lot of physical stuff this week thanks to my injury, so maybe we'll have to do it this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dude, no, no, no, GS68 said it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Blazing Star on Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like one of my favorite ever Neo Geo games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Polestar was a good game, but Blazing Star was freaking awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Someday.
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently there's a rumor going around that Nintendo is planning on adding flash card support to the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, I'm sure that many people know that there is flash card support for the DS online,
[SPEAKER_07]: in a not-so-official, not-entirely-legal way.
[SPEAKER_07]: But the rumor is that they're going to be offering this as part of a download service that will allow you to put Game Boy and Game Boy Color games onto your DS, say, maybe via, I don't know, Virtual Console or something like that, where you can download your games using the little SD memory card, pop it out of your Wii, plug it into your DS, and take it on the go.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_07]: but who knows, maybe Jamie will be able to get Kid Dracula through the service that might be kind of cool for her actually I'd want to play it too here's a problem though I see with this and I don't know how it would work is how would you be able to say if I put a copy of Super Mario Land or something like that on my memory stick or whatever and Super Mario Land will be one of those games and I'm sure it was better when I was a kid let's say I put it on my SD memory card
[SPEAKER_07]: How's that card going to know which DS is going into?
[SPEAKER_07]: For example, basically that would allow you to rip the ROMs and just distribute them freely.
[SPEAKER_07]: It would be hard for them to be able to lock that down to one DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why can't it just beam the game over the Wi-Fi?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because the DS has no internal memory to store the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then once it's beamed over the Wi-Fi, you save it to the...
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe you link it up with a unique ID, like a friend code type thing?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you save it to, like... Maybe the friend code thing could work, I guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: It would still be very hard.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, coming out on the Nintendo Wii is a sequel to a very obscure game.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know if a lot of folks know about this...
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: And I know it's a joke on that show because they have that sound effect, the, oh no, whenever you fall off the building, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, get this.
[SPEAKER_08]: Crazy Climber is being remade for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_08]: And this just struck me as very odd when I read about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm like, really?
[SPEAKER_08]: Really?
[SPEAKER_08]: Out of all the games they could pick, they're remaking Crazy Climber.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who's publishing that?
[SPEAKER_08]: Crazy Climber is being made by Nihon Busan is doing the publisher there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Crazy Climber Wii is coming out.
[SPEAKER_08]: It kind of looks interesting from the screenshots, but you actually use the Wii remote and the nunchuck to climb up the building, which is kind of an interesting concept, you have to say.
[SPEAKER_07]: The only thing that scares me about this, though, is the fact that they have a game like Impossible Mission and they also had Spy Game
[SPEAKER_07]: What was that?
[SPEAKER_07]: Elevator Mission or some shit like that?
[SPEAKER_07]: That was really crappy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, you can pick different characters from the game to play as.
[SPEAKER_08]: And there's this one character called Fox who looks to be a foxy little girl.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or actually, big girl.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, you know, kind of a little spin on the 80s thing where the 80s thing only had the one guy.
[SPEAKER_08]: And somebody actually in chat has posted the link to the clip.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, no!
[SPEAKER_08]: Crazy Climber
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I'm thinking about modding my Wii, and this comes out in Japan on December 20th, so, you know, I'll be able to play Region 3 soon.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you don't get locked out with some future dashboard update, be careful, or whatever they call it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry, that was 360, but whatever, the interface update.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, that's enough Crazy Climber.
[SPEAKER_03]: So crazy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank God.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's rumor floating around, this is all purely speculation, honestly, I don't think there's much...
[SPEAKER_03]: Actual fact in this, that Animal Crossing will be going the way of the MMO.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think it will happen anytime soon.
[SPEAKER_03]: If it does, and it's really all based off of Eguchi saying that they wanted to expand the connectivity to mobile phones and computers.
[SPEAKER_07]: All Chinese fruit sellers, you know, shaking my tree, stealing my fruit.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, that's so...
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't even see how you can grasp that straw.
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: If it's going to happen, it'll be much further down.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, I could kind of see something like this happening for some reason.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know, it just seems like a very logical, and maybe that's why this is grabbing all this steam around the internet and is catching a lot of, you know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: They've been saying it for years, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: and it would make sense.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, God, it would totally change the game too because on the DS it kind of felt like a little bit like we've all played before.
[SPEAKER_08]: It felt forced.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, to be honest, I don't think they're going to do this because that would mean that Nintendo's actually getting with it and we know that's not the case.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're going to be opening themselves up to a lot of trouble and you know that Nintendo plays it safe.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nintendo will decide, hey, you know what, let's run an Animal Crossing BBS and then they'll go from there and then eventually you'll have like your
[SPEAKER_07]: Animal Crossing chat room and your Animal Crossing game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: My gut tells me something like this is definitely possible.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think this could happen.
[SPEAKER_08]: But we'll see.
[SPEAKER_07]: It'll happen, all right.
[SPEAKER_07]: In 2010.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or never.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm kind of afraid of it happening.
[SPEAKER_08]: If it is an MMO, I'm going to come to Jamie's Village all the time and shake her trees.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who says I'll play it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, snap.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think I... You know, if it went the route of MMO, I don't think I'd play it.
[SPEAKER_08]: What if it was free?
[SPEAKER_08]: Like a Guild Wars-style thing, where once you buy the game, you can play it however much you want.
[SPEAKER_03]: If somebody gives me the game, sure.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're not the Animal Crossing addict you used to be.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, not really.
[SPEAKER_03]: It just got really boring for me, and I'm already playing a good MMO right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ooh, we'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, interesting rumor that got leaked out this week is that there was a new character...
[SPEAKER_07]: Coming to Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_07]: Crystal, the girl fox who's also in scantily clad blue... Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Of course, you know, if you told me last week that King Dedede was going to be a character in the game, I would have said, yeah, right.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then look what happened.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: By the way, that's too much Kirby in one game, I think.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, I know Kirby's great and all, but seriously, three characters, two of them a bit obscure, King Dedede and Meta Knight...
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: King Dedede's not obscure.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know, he's not obscure, but... Mr. Play and Watch, I mean... What about Kirby?
[SPEAKER_08]: What about that?
[SPEAKER_08]: Mr. Play and Watch was great.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or Game and Watch, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mr. Game and Watch was great.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was a good unlocked character.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was kind of a throwback to Nintendo's history.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I just don't... I honestly think if they... I think King Dedede's a good addition and all, but I think they should have just done away with Meta Knight in that case.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, who's a Meta Knight fan?
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe when the game comes out.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's a lot of people now, but I don't know who the fucking King Dedede is.
[SPEAKER_07]: All that reminds me of is fucking Carlos Mencia.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: TigerClaw has a really good point in our chatroom.
[SPEAKER_08]: Chat.OrangeLandsRadio.com Keep in mind the creator of Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_08]: Brawl also created Kirby.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, damn good point.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, he's also created... You need to have Lolo and Lala.
[SPEAKER_08]: I wish.
[SPEAKER_08]: That would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: He's also created this, which for the Nintendo Wii is something a little bit unheard of, which is getting people very excited.
[SPEAKER_08]: and, of course, there's another Target Smash mode yet again.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, we see this often in the Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_08]: game.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's going to be a new Target Smash mode in the game, but what's very cool about it is that you can actually send your replays through Target Smash mode to other people on your Wii console friends list.
[SPEAKER_08]: They even show pictures of it happening.
[SPEAKER_08]: So a lot of us are like, oh my gosh, we don't see a whole lot of this Wii Connect 24 thing going on right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, you have that one random Elebits thing and a couple other, but you don't see a whole lot of this, like, send game stuff
[SPEAKER_08]: Two Friends.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, very cool that this looks like it's going to be happening.
[SPEAKER_08]: A real quick quote from the article, quote, this time you can view replays.
[SPEAKER_08]: What this means is the game records what you did in Brawls or in Target Smash and lets you review it.
[SPEAKER_08]: And you can record up to three minutes of data.
[SPEAKER_08]: So not just in the Target mode, it looks like you can actually do this in the actual Brawls.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's going to be fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now the next thing is we need to be able to post them to the internet.
[SPEAKER_08]: Download them there, kind of like Halo 3.
[SPEAKER_08]: Imagine some of the brawl matches we'd see on the site ready to download.
[SPEAKER_08]: That might be kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I'll tell you what is very happy for me is a zombie game on the DS.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love zombies.
[SPEAKER_08]: Zombies are pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ignition is releasing a game called Teenage Zombies Invasion of the Alien Brain Thingies, which is the best name ever.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was a teenage zombie.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, Invasion of the Alien Brain Thingies.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's basically the world is taken over by aliens called, or alien or something called the Big Brain and the Army of Brain Thingies.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so these zombies rise from their grave.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rise from your grave.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're immune to the Brain Thingy Ray and start eating people.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_08]: What exactly do you do in the game?
[SPEAKER_03]: It has a bunch of stylus minigames and boss battles and puzzles.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yay, minigames and puzzles, just what the DS needed.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's zombies, and it's supposed to play out sort of comic book style.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, that might be kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it has the word thingy in it, and that's great.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe instead of Mario Party, we need Zombie Party.
[SPEAKER_08]: That might be kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or Zombie Mario Party.
[SPEAKER_03]: We need Romero Party.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, I'm going to stop you right there with the whole zombie teenager thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ignition, what games have they put out?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, that's what I thought.
[SPEAKER_07]: What, you mean they can't judge a game based on its title alone?
[SPEAKER_07]: What does this world come to?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, remember that other game, Monster Madness, how awesome that was?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh wait, I'm sorry, it was not awesome, it was crap.
[SPEAKER_03]: We had zombies, you know what, we need a remake of Zombies Ate My Neighbors.
[SPEAKER_08]: I knew somehow we could not get through a zombie stories without that game coming up.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was great.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what Monster Madness was sort of trying to be, but it sure as hell was not.
[SPEAKER_03]: It failed with a PH.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, so moving on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Some interesting stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Of course, not a huge surprise, but, you know, there's going to be yet another Castlevania game on the DS.
[SPEAKER_06]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_07]: Big surprise there.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, of course, producer Koji...
[SPEAKER_07]: Igarashi said, the first thing we're doing is another DS version.
[SPEAKER_07]: There hasn't been an official announcement, but we're doing it.
[SPEAKER_07]: That would be the official announcement.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was in an interview with Game Life.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're going to be doing a new DS version.
[SPEAKER_08]: More Castlevania?
[SPEAKER_08]: Or what do they call that?
[SPEAKER_08]: Metroidvania?
[SPEAKER_08]: Metroidvania.
[SPEAKER_07]: Metroidvania
[SPEAKER_08]: But, you know, it might be interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Can you imagine Castlevania and the Metroid Prime 3 engine?
[SPEAKER_08]: Could be interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would be fairly cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know yet.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's iffy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Obviously, it's a very iffy thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a very iffy thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, last segment we were talking about Spore, and of course a lot of folks are very excited about Spore and Will Wright.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, he's the man.
[SPEAKER_08]: But Will Wright made a pretty bold statement this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: He said that the Wii is the only next-gen console.
[SPEAKER_08]: He said in an interview, quote, Somebody asked me what I thought next-generation meant, and what about the PlayStation 3 was next-generation.
[SPEAKER_08]: The only next-gen system I've seen is the Wii.
[SPEAKER_08]: The PlayStation 3 and the Xbox 360 feel like better versions of the last, but pretty much the same game with incremental improvement.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was in an interview with Guardian Unlimited.
[SPEAKER_08]: uh goes on to say quote not that the graphics are more powerful but that it hits a completely different demographic in regards to how the Wii feels like a major jump so coming from one of the you know a major you know gaming mind pretty bold statement there and just kind of goes yeah it's kind of interesting because a lot of people call Wii and you know Nintendo themselves call this the new generation like the Wii's going off over here in this direction whereas Xbox 360 and PlayStation 3 are kind of doing a little bit more of the same but prettier
[SPEAKER_08]: Shut up, you people don't know anything.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what I have to say about that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Make your damn games and be quiet.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is next generation.
[SPEAKER_07]: Listen, they're all fucking new consoles.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're all next generation.
[SPEAKER_07]: Shut the hell up.
[SPEAKER_07]: If I made a new 16-bit console, that would still be another generation console because it has come out in this generation of consoles.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: There is no next-gen.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's only current.
[SPEAKER_03]: Next-gen is stuff that doesn't exist yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just like that you just told Will Wright to shut up.
[SPEAKER_07]: 7th Generation of Consoles
[SPEAKER_08]: No, Wikipedia puts the Atari 2600 in the second generation of games with, I believe, like Coleco and some of the ones before it in the first generation.
[SPEAKER_03]: So then the first generation would then be like the Odyssey and the Fairchild Channel 11?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh boy, here we go.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hold on, here we go.
[SPEAKER_08]: I will pull up the article right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, no, I just think that this whole classification is pretty retarded.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm just tired of people commenting on what systems they think are next-gen and which systems are not.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're all fucking... whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_07]: Your comment makes...
[SPEAKER_07]: So you don't own a PS3, so you don't use your 360, I don't care.
[SPEAKER_07]: Make your damn game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Stop chit-chatting.
[SPEAKER_07]: More workie on Spore.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm actually bringing this up right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: They split this out into the different generations here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see if I can grab the wrap-up here real quick.
[SPEAKER_08]: with the generations.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's talk more rock.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, yeah, the first generation of games would be from 72 to 77 and includes the Magnavox Odyssey, Pong, and the Coleco Telstar are the games in the first generation.
[SPEAKER_08]: Then the second generation moves on to...
[SPEAKER_08]: The Fairchild Channel F, RCA Studio 2, Atari 2600, Valley Astrocade, The Odyssey, The APF Imagination Machine, The Intellivision, The Atari 5200, Milton Bradley Vectrex, The Immersion Arcadia 2001, ColecoVision, and the Sega SG-1000 are all considered in the second generation.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Fairchild Channel F was ass.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then the video game crash of 1983 separates to the third generation, which is the Nintendo Entertainment System, the Sega Master System, and the Atari 7800.
[SPEAKER_08]: Then we get into the fourth generation of console games.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the fourth generation of console games includes TurboGrafx-16, the Sega Genesis, the Neo Geo, and the Super Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_08]: Speculate!
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, hey, how about some other stuff?
[SPEAKER_03]: Sure!
[SPEAKER_03]: Poppin' Music B-Mouse!
[SPEAKER_03]: The new Poppin' Music to be coming out.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's themed after computer mice, so it's B-Mouse.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, it's a computer mouse.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wait, and it is an actual mouse?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, it is an actual mouse.
[SPEAKER_07]: Take a look at the picture.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: It basically folds open and there's buttons underneath it.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's bizarre.
[SPEAKER_07]: You really need to check it out.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can open up the mouse for nine buttons and play a pop-up music simulator with a CD.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's very interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: They've got the list of songs.
[SPEAKER_07]: They have a really cool picture of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's on Konami Style.
[SPEAKER_07]: Definitely worth checking out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anything worth noting?
[SPEAKER_07]: On the song list, I mean.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's actually some pretty cool stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's Mr. T, Gradius Full Speed is on there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Daikinkai by Desiro Gumi.
[SPEAKER_03]: Another Lament theme song.
[SPEAKER_03]: Shizuku Bayasaki, we have Megane Rock, Pop Music Wan, Gira Gira Megane Dan, Showa Kayo, Ringo, I can't see the text, it's so small, Hachimitsu, Anettai Majisuka, Orchestra Featuring Maki, yeah, that's what it says.
[SPEAKER_03]: Lots of stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's Shining by Ryo and Noria.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I think
[SPEAKER_07]: And I think this actually is a mouse.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can actually use it on your computer.
[SPEAKER_07]: But if you take a look at this wonderful picture here, Rob, this is what it looks like.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, good, because I was actually bringing it up right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, that is weird.
[SPEAKER_07]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's kind of cool, though, I guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: So gaming, it's a mouse, and then when you're, you know, ready to game, you can do it.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's totally...
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm putting the link in the chat room so they can see what it looks like.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think the 2DX mouse.
[SPEAKER_03]: 2DX mouse would not work.
[SPEAKER_03]: Especially for, you know, people like me who are right side players.
[SPEAKER_07]: But you could do it though.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, if you think about it, you could have like a scroll wheel on the side of the mouse that would be the scratch.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you know what they did for the... Or hell, just play 2DX with this.
[SPEAKER_03]: For the WonderSwan?
[SPEAKER_03]: For Beat Mania on WonderSwan?
[SPEAKER_03]: They had an add-on to it that you could attach a scratch pad onto the controller.
[SPEAKER_07]: We should get 2DXDS.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would work.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that that would work.
[SPEAKER_07]: I stand by what I said in Part A about what they really need to do to innovate.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, so other fun stuff, of course.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's more firmware coming out now for the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you happen to purchase a copy of Ratchet & Clank Future, Tools of Destruction, you got version 1.94, which didn't really do much.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it added some support for the DualShock 3 for that game, and then maybe some other shit.
[SPEAKER_07]: But that doesn't matter, because apparently firmware 2.0 is supposed to be released on October 30th, and will feature some wonderful stuff, including...
[SPEAKER_07]: The ability to turn on and off your PS3 using the PSP Remote Play.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't see the purpose of that.
[SPEAKER_07]: A new PlayStation Network category.
[SPEAKER_07]: A TV category for those of you who are in Europe who are installing the Play TV onto your hard drive.
[SPEAKER_07]: A new playlist for music and photo.
[SPEAKER_07]: A content group for video and game.
[SPEAKER_07]: and apparently there's the cross media bar customization including themes and background color settings sort of like what they have with the PSP right now and then the Trend Micro Web Security for PS3 Internet Browser which is a parental lock for website viewing that will be free for a while and then eventually they'll charge you for it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well Ratchet and Clank also has something else very interesting in it not just a surprise upgrade
[SPEAKER_08]: in anticipation of 2.0.
[SPEAKER_08]: But Ratchet & Clank Future Tools of Destruction apparently will actually tie up to the upcoming PSP game Secret Agent Clank.
[SPEAKER_08]: And this was from a one-up interview with Insomniac's creative director, Brian Alagier.
[SPEAKER_08]: And apparently he says that the PS3 game and the new PSP game will actually work and connect to each other in, quote, some secret, undisclosed way.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that's all we know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you unlock some old Ratchet & Clank game with it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Like a Metroid hookup type thing?
[SPEAKER_08]: Unfortunately, we don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: But we do know that the game will not connect up with other services.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tools of Destruction will not connect to Home or any other PlayStation game or PSP game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just the other Ratchet & Clank game that is coming out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Secret Agent Clank.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, look for it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'd be curious to know what that connectivity is.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hope it's something new and exciting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not something we've kind of seen before.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, for anyone who is playing Motorstorm, there is a, looks like a patch to the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_03]: that will actually add vibration support for the DualShock 3 controller.
[SPEAKER_03]: Grid order randomized for the first race in any online lobby.
[SPEAKER_03]: Finishing positions for your last race to determine your starting grid position in the next race within the same online lobby.
[SPEAKER_03]: Screen indicators added to show whether voice comms are issuing from TV or headset.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sensitivity for 6-axis motion sensor
[SPEAKER_03]: Gloating Index, that's kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_03]: It gives you an idea of how well another racer has performed.
[SPEAKER_08]: I do like how it seems like quite a few Sony games are doing this.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like how these games kind of keep patching themselves to get a little better.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: It feels like I'm seeing that happen more on the Sony games than on 360 games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Usually the 360 games get patched to fix something that broke, not often to add completely new stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that makes it feel a little more like, well, let's say World of Warcraft constantly patches itself, and a lot of MMOs do this, patch itself with brand new stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it kind of sucked when everybody was hitting it at once.
[SPEAKER_08]: But World of Warcraft does it kind of smart now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Right before a major patch will come out, a couple days or maybe even a week before, they'll actually put a thing similar to BitTorrent that will automatically run when you launch WoW.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it slowly downloads the patch as you're playing.
[SPEAKER_08]: And so that way when it's time for the patch to go live, then it'll send a pulse that says, okay, time to update the game with the patch.
[SPEAKER_08]: And so everybody already has it downloaded.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's pretty smart.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like the way they do it on WoW.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I want 2.3 already, because I want my Arena Season 1 gear without having to work for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Although I still kind of like how they do it in Ragnarok, where they do small patches every time.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so it makes sure that your patches are all up to date right when you start the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's kind of how Guild Wars worked too, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think so, it's just little bits at a time.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, let's see here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Interesting news.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I wouldn't exactly call this news because I've been talking about how stupid easy it's going to be to copy the damn cards for Eye of Judgment.
[SPEAKER_07]: But apparently it's even easier than you may have thought.
[SPEAKER_07]: The game has absolutely no copy protection whatsoever.
[SPEAKER_07]: In fact, you can pretty much draw symbols on a piece of paper using a felt tip marker and it will work.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's really sad.
[SPEAKER_07]: But yeah, it's very easy to copy them.
[SPEAKER_07]: The game has no problem reading, you know, printed out copies of the cards, or just if you happen to scribble in the symbols that they have on the cards, it will work as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: So basically with a box of Crayolas, I could recreate the cards.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, you could.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's kind of sad.
[SPEAKER_08]: It is sad.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't...
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm just curious what the chat room has to say for this.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I will remind... I'm having live stream problems.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dark Tetsuya is giving a big XD to Crayola.
[SPEAKER_07]: I will remind you, though, that in case you don't want to copy the cards, the theme packs are available for $15 each or $4 per booster pack.
[SPEAKER_08]: I swear I didn't use a crayon reference on purpose.
[SPEAKER_08]: I swear.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyhow, what's that?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, the fake cards?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyhow, you know, this means we got lied to about the whole copy protection thing, and I don't like getting lied to.
[SPEAKER_08]: We all knew this was coming, we all knew this was going to happen, and this makes us very angsty.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you know we have to bring on the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_08]: And back by popular demand, folks.
[SPEAKER_03]: FU to this music, I'm fucking sick of it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry, we got emails.
[SPEAKER_08]: They missed it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't care.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_07]: F you the women for not being able to make up their mind on certain things.
[SPEAKER_07]: For example, say you're asking your wife what they want to eat for dinner.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they're like, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: So you start suggesting things.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they're like, no, I don't want to do that.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I don't want to do that.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll fucking suggest something then if you're just going to deny every one of my suggestions and fucking come up with your own.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hate it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not about everything.
[SPEAKER_07]: Women do this about all sorts of categories.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to give you a hint.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just do whatever you want.
[SPEAKER_07]: I do, and they complain.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, there's no winning that argument.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, my FU of the week goes to my injury.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because it sucks.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I don't like having a sore thigh thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: It makes it hard to sit down.
[SPEAKER_08]: People go, ha ha ha, you can't sit down.
[SPEAKER_08]: Being injured sucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: I had a real FU, actually.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, yes, what is that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Stupid music pushed it out of my head.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't even know if I have the other music queued up.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see if we can do... Shuffling, shuffling, shuffling.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is Wonderful Radio as I dig through the computer.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't worry about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hold on, hold on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nope, nope, nope, nope, nope.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm in the right folder.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just need the right file name.
[SPEAKER_08]: And here we go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Much better.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: My actual F.U.
[SPEAKER_03]: goes towards... I don't really want to say towards my husband.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I really, really, really do love my husband.
[SPEAKER_03]: But he can be freaking infuriating sometimes.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I know that he has good intentions.
[SPEAKER_03]: But don't try to...
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't try to have a logical discussion with me when I haven't eaten anything in like 12 hours.
[SPEAKER_03]: It doesn't work.
[SPEAKER_03]: And don't be pushy about it either.
[SPEAKER_03]: The end.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry, I was putting away the webcam because our Op 11 time ran up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why are people pushy?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: You shouldn't be pushy, you should be pully.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, let's get back into some gaming news, because then we'll be pushing the listeners to call in on our Skype line.
[SPEAKER_08]: 1-877-GAME-OLR, our username on Skype, Orange Lingerie.
[SPEAKER_08]: We have a few more stories, a handful of stories for you guys before we get there.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the first one has to do with GameStop.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, GameStop, they have EB, and it seems like they're taking over the world when it comes to mall video game stores.
[SPEAKER_08]: And they just might be, because they just opened up.
[SPEAKER_08]: This place isn't that far from us, actually.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jackson, California.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's not that far from here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just probably...
[SPEAKER_08]: They opened up their 5,000th store, GameStop did.
[SPEAKER_08]: The 5,000th GameStop store.
[SPEAKER_08]: What GameStop?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, to put that in perspective, and a lot of people feel that way, which is why this news may be good news for some and bad news for others.
[SPEAKER_08]: To put it in perspective, Starbucks has 12,000 plus locations, but I wonder if that counts like the ones in the grocery store.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: and McDonald's, get this, has 31,000 restaurants.
[SPEAKER_08]: But still, to think that for every six McDonald's there's one GameStop, I mean, there's a lot of frickin' McDonald's, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, every exit on the freeway has a McDonald's, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: So, kind of interesting that for every six of those there's still one GameStop.
[SPEAKER_08]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you know what else is interesting is that people are still making Dreamcast games.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the rest of the world goes, why?
[SPEAKER_03]: Dreamcast was so awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, it's a little bit of fun here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I don't know if this is fun, but the place where the internet goes to die is now going to be the place where games go to die.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because MySpace is launching their Casual Games channel in 2008.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you'll be able to put crappy Flash games into your webpage.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I can destroy my profile with all those buildings.
[SPEAKER_08]: Some people do that already.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think people on MySpace have seen it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Some coworker of mine has Pac-Man on their profile.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like a little mini Pac-Man game.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not real Pac-Man.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's some cheap knockoff, but oh boy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Could that be interesting though if they had leaderboards all tied together and you could see how you compare on these casual games to your friends?
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, a little silly fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: I had somebody make mine.
[SPEAKER_08]: But mine was pretty.
[SPEAKER_08]: You still had the final approval and you looked at it and you go, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: I helped design the graphics on it too.
[SPEAKER_08]: I look at some of my friends' MySpaces and I go, do you even look at your own page?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's hideous.
[SPEAKER_08]: You have to scroll down forever to see anything.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who's actually going to look at this?
[SPEAKER_08]: I actually scaled my MySpace page back a little while ago.
[SPEAKER_08]: A, so I can make it public, and B, because it's public again, and B, so I could just not have to scroll so much because of all the stupid pictures I had on it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Black Lab in our chatroom says, MySpace is garbage, but don't you have a MySpace?
[SPEAKER_08]: GS68 says, you do not say the MS word.
[SPEAKER_08]: Microsoft?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, MySpace.
[SPEAKER_03]: Someone left a comment.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was just checking my MySpace now to see what was on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Neki left the best joke ever.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Where do mentally ill people go that's bigger on the inside than the out?
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's their retardus.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's awful.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, a tardus.
[SPEAKER_08]: I get it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bad Doctor Who joke.
[SPEAKER_08]: That is a very bad joke in many different forms.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it made me laugh.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyhow, maybe our listeners want to tell some jokes tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to take some calls right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: www.orangelounge.com Click on Interact With Us for all the details.
[SPEAKER_08]: 1-877-GAME-OLR is the number if you want to pick up the phone and call.
[SPEAKER_08]: Have your mom or your daddy's permission because it's only toll free in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_08]: and Canada.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or you can call us on Skype.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's free for everyone.
[SPEAKER_08]: Our username is OrangeloungeRadio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Looking at some other quick comments on chat while we wait for some calls because of the delay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Escapist in our chatroom says, In regards to Facebook...
[SPEAKER_08]: Here we go again with the MySpace versus Facebook thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just try to lick me in real life, I dare you.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sure that's from one of those, you just got a lick, or you just got poked by so-and-so.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't want to go back to my annoyance with Facebook.
[SPEAKER_08]: I actually tried to, I went back and added some friends, because some OLR people added me on Facebook.
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess amongst all my rants on the show recently, folks figured out I had an account, so.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, let's head on over to the phones and we'll take a call.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_08]: That's Legend of Zaku.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello, Legend of Zaku.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_01]: Nah, just going through the usual Sunday 15.
[SPEAKER_01]: Just, you know, getting prices and stuff like that.
Demo.
[SPEAKER_08]: Listening to our show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Are you doing both at the same time?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, if I could, now that I have a new PC to do it on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_01]: So what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_08]: What do you want to tell us about?
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: The fact that Crysis is just, you know, it's not for the faint of heart, graphics-wise and, you know, system-wise.
[SPEAKER_01]: Obviously, you're going to need a really beefy PC to get through it.
[SPEAKER_01]: But is it a good game?
[SPEAKER_01]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_01]: Is it a good game?
[SPEAKER_01]: So far, it is.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, it's kind of like Half-Life and Far... Half-Life 2 and Far Cry had a love child.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright, I mean, yeah, so far it's running pretty good for a new system that I built so far.
[SPEAKER_01]: But, you know, hopefully when it launches it'll probably be optimized and ready for use.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was a little laggy from what I hear from other folks with other more powerful systems than mine.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, very cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, anything else you've been playing lately besides Crysis?
[SPEAKER_01]: Um, just...
[SPEAKER_01]: Quake Wars, another game that came with my video card.
[SPEAKER_01]: Enemy Territory, Quake Wars.
[SPEAKER_08]: And how's that?
[SPEAKER_01]: It's alright, I mean, it's kind of like Battlefield in the Quake Wars world.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, the Quake world.
[SPEAKER_08]: Quake, you know, Quake needs, you know, because Quake 4 wasn't all that great, so Quake needs some good games that make me remember how much the first game was awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: We need Duke, Enemy Territory, Duke Nukem.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what we need.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe after Duke Nukem Forever.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wasn't that supposed to come out at the end of the year?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, fucking hell.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wasn't one of those, hey, it finally got a release date, and it's like... No, it never got a release date.
[SPEAKER_07]: That'd be all over the internet, man.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, that's true.
[SPEAKER_01]: And also, I think I heard of another Xbox Live horror story where this one guy, he sent his console to get it repaired, and then when he got the new one back, he couldn't even transfer $320 worth of Microsoft points.
[SPEAKER_01]: because they're not transferable.
[SPEAKER_08]: Right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Can't you call Microsoft and get that fixed?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, that's apparently, unfortunately, that's a policy that they have.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: You don't need to transfer the points because your live account is on their server.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not on the 360.
[SPEAKER_01]: All you've got to do is re... What they told him was that the points were actually tied to the console.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, they're not.
[SPEAKER_08]: From what I recall, it's a little bit of both.
[SPEAKER_08]: You download the game, and that's tied to your account, but here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's say me and you, let's say we're roommates again, Loki, back in the day, and we have one 360 in the house.
[SPEAKER_08]: If I paid for the game and I downloaded it, you get to play the full version on the console.
[SPEAKER_08]: But here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: If we get a new console or whatever, and I sign in and download the game, you can't play it.
[SPEAKER_08]: You still get the trial version.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, that's still, that doesn't matter, that's the thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is that his games that he purchased should be able to be transferred over because he can just re-download them again and he still has the full rights to them because it has, you know, on record that he's paid for it.
[SPEAKER_07]: and also if he has any Microsoft points because you can purchase those points through like independent websites and stuff and add them on there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like for example, if you're buying stuff for your Zoom, your Microsoft account or whatever, still tied to all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: So you can port it over even if you buy a new 360.
[SPEAKER_07]: They have the ability to do that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've done that.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know the story right now.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know where.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know I saw it on... Well, that's the story and you stick into it.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, Zach, we got to let you go to get some more calls.
[SPEAKER_08]: Real quick, last final thought for everybody.
[SPEAKER_01]: Um, just, I don't know, just, you know, just get a better computer.
[SPEAKER_01]: Somebody might need one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Everybody, get a better computer.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, thanks, Saku.
[SPEAKER_08]: Have a good one, buddy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did you hear that, everybody?
[SPEAKER_08]: You need to get a better computer.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, get a better computer.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, get a better computer.
[SPEAKER_07]: I do need a better computer.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I need a computer.
[SPEAKER_07]: My computer, the hard drive, or something's crapping out on it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I actually want to...
[SPEAKER_08]: Shutting off.
[SPEAKER_08]: This fucking fan on this thing is so... I wonder if I could, like, hold the microphone.
[SPEAKER_08]: You could hear it.
[SPEAKER_08]: The fan on this thing is so loud.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can hear it throughout the whole house.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's crazy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_09]: This would be the Dark Knight himself.
[SPEAKER_08]: There you are, sir.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're a little bit quiet, but that's all right.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll fix that.
[SPEAKER_08]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_08]: How you doing, Dark Knight?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, how you doing?
[SPEAKER_08]: Good, how are you?
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, a little bit happier now that I have my 360.
[SPEAKER_08]: I actually, I noticed that you've actually been signing into live.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was playing Guitar Hero 3 earlier today, and I saw you sign on, and I was kind of like, wait a minute, I thought he only had an Xbox.com account, but not a live.
[SPEAKER_08]: So now you're actually on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_08]: And all that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: So what kind of games have you been playing?
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, Forza 2 and, um,
[SPEAKER_09]: Man of 97, Man of 07, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: But yeah, if you were playing Man of 97 on Xbox, that would be something though.
[SPEAKER_08]: That means you had to crash the cartridge into some slot.
[SPEAKER_09]: Xbox Live Arcade or something like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, what's it like being all brand new to the Xbox now?
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, does it seem like there's like a lot out there the Xbox has to offer?
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess let me back up and rephrase it this way.
[SPEAKER_08]: What made you finally decide to take the plunge after all this time and jump in and get a 360?
[SPEAKER_09]: Part of it because I
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: Not everybody can just afford to run out and go buy an HD TV.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're still kind of pricey.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you think, amongst your gaming experience, does Microsoft do a pretty good job of still keeping the love for the folks that are stuck with standard definition for now?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I mean, it's not really that bad at all.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like I said, I'm playing Mando 7, and it looks just as good on HD.
[SPEAKER_09]: The only difference is I don't have that total clearness, and I...
[SPEAKER_09]: HD would have them, but it does do it justice.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do most of the standard definitions of games letterbox?
[SPEAKER_09]: Do you get the bars?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, because basically it picks up as a 480p TV.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Some games letterbox themselves though, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Didn't Final Fantasy XI automatically letterbox even if you were on a standard TV?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, it depends on the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, because you have to set your console to just, you can set it so that your TV is a 4x3 aspect ratio and then
[SPEAKER_07]: If the game wants to letterbox it will, otherwise it may just do full screen.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like I said.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, Dark Knight, what would you say you're looking forward to most on the 360 now that you're an owner?
[SPEAKER_09]: Just messing around with it right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just getting used to it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, so far I downloaded some, like...
[SPEAKER_09]: Xbox Live games and whatnot, like I downloaded Final Fantasy Special and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_09]: I can't get my words out tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, that's all right.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, wow, if you think about it, they're almost up to like 100 of those games pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_08]: So being a new, I mean, for those of us who have been on Xbox Live a while, it seems like, all right, you know, we just kind of wait for each week to see what they're going to release and see if it's worth buying.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, man, to be jumping in on that now and then you dip into the archive, like,
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, Dark Knight, we have to let you go so we can get to some more calls.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you very much, and enjoy the Xbox.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I hope your Xbox experience is Red Rings of Death free.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, lo and behold, my system is like a link to it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think it was dated July 22nd of 07, so it's recent.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Then I hope it's red rings free.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll be pulling for you, buddy.
[SPEAKER_08]: You have a good one.
[SPEAKER_08]: See you.
[SPEAKER_08]: You too.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you'd like to give us a call, 1-877-GAME-OLR or username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see if we can squeeze in some  oh, we're already getting a call.
[SPEAKER_08]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yo, it's Xenacore.
[SPEAKER_05]: How y'all doing?
[SPEAKER_08]: Good.
[SPEAKER_08]: How are you, Xenacore?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I'm living, I'm living.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know how things go.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_08]: So are we.
[SPEAKER_08]: Even with minor injuries and whatever else is going on in our personal lives, we're making it to another week.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_05]: Not too much.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just heard you guys referencing some of the old school stuff and thought I'd call in.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura was talking about Ragnarok 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: I touched something that looks like it was made in the same engine called, was it
[SPEAKER_05]: Pirate King Online
[SPEAKER_05]: I got that feeling, but I'm going to farm that off on the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: I couldn't review it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Xenocore, what is a weird echoing with you?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know what that is.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just want to let those people who are listening on their iPods and stuff know, if you're hearing him repeat things, that's not you guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's something weird with the call.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, it is you guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: You just can't hear correctly.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know what that is.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's an error I've not seen before.
[SPEAKER_08]: But anyway, so Pirate King was okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ragnarok was a ton more fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, all right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: that one and all different odds and ends here and there managed to get some more points on ER Kung Fu and Xbox Live but that's pretty much the only noteworthy thing I've been doing lately so
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, Yara Kung Fu is a pretty fun little game.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's often overlooked.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, you know, because fighting games have evolved so damn much since then.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, you know, you've got to respect the elders, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know you play a lot of RPGs.
[SPEAKER_08]: What other kind of obscure MMOs, because everybody always talks about Warcraft, Warcraft, Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_08]: What other types of MMOs and just maybe other role-playing games in general should we be looking out for that maybe the mainstream media doesn't pay enough attention to?
[SPEAKER_05]: Bounty Bay Online Bounty Bay Online
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a pirate simulator.
[SPEAKER_05]: It plays like pirates does, but it's an MMO environment, so it was pretty neat.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow, we really do have a lot of pirates MMOs, because then Disney put out an official one.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm thinking, well, of course, there's puzzle pirates too, and it's kind of all probably thanks to Johnny Depp, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: You'd like to think probably he has something to do with that.
[SPEAKER_08]: But where are my ninja MMOs?
[SPEAKER_08]: That's the ultimate question.
[SPEAKER_08]: We have all these pirate MMOs.
[SPEAKER_08]: Where is my ninja MMO, whether it be Ninja Gaiden or Last Ninja?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know, just a ninja MMO.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
[SPEAKER_05]: Damn Skippy, man.
[SPEAKER_08]: We need to take our idea and patent it.
[SPEAKER_08]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: I now own the patents and trademarks on the Ninja MMO.
[SPEAKER_08]: Watch me get sued.
[SPEAKER_08]: Somebody probably made one.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just don't know of it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anything else you want to share with our listeners?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm still waiting for Rock Band and Guitar Hero 3 to come out.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see how they do upon release.
[SPEAKER_05]: Guitar Hero 3 was out yesterday.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh yeah, that's true, that's true.
[SPEAKER_05]: But Rock Band's the one I'm looking for, but I'm waiting for the peripherals to start coming by themselves.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't have that many homies around me to buy the whole set.
[SPEAKER_08]: Exactly, that's too much money for the whole set.
[SPEAKER_08]: And unfortunately, the peripherals by themselves are going to be going into 08.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I'm probably going to pick up the game because I have the Guitar Hero 2 controller, which will work with Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_08]: So at least I'll have guitar, and if my microphone works for Xbox Live, then I'll have a microphone.
[SPEAKER_08]: If it doesn't, then it doesn't.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nobody on Xbox Live needs to hear me sing anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm buying it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't need to hear me sing.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm buying.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're going to buy the whole bundle?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sucker.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know, because I hate playing guitar here, and I don't know why the fuck I keep buying this shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm getting the bundle.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because I can.
[SPEAKER_07]: You guys are made of money.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not made of money.
[SPEAKER_05]: The bundle's worth it if you're going to get anything, everything, anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you're not going to, then you better.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, Rob.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've cut down on my buying of 360 games, so I don't have to really worry about, you know, I'm saving up.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not your mommy.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can buy.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can spend your money however you want.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm just saying.
$170.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's a lot of money.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not really, because I mean, if I don't, you know, go out for lunch during my work week, then after, you know, a few weeks, that's enough to pay for the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then again, next month is going to be slim for me anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, Xenocor, we've got to let you go so we can get some more calls, but any other quick last comments?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, that's pretty much it, guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll talk to you guys later.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, take care, Xenocor.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think this is the first time he's been on the program, actually.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't remember him calling in before.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe he did once.
[SPEAKER_08]: But appreciate always hearing from the people we don't often hear from.
[SPEAKER_08]: But we also appreciate hearing from the people we do often hear from, which I believe is our next call.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, it's Ranma.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's up, everyone?
[SPEAKER_08]: What'd I tell you?
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, everyone.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ranma, how you doing?
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I just said because the last caller was someone we don't hear from a lot, but now we're hearing from someone we do hear from a lot, but that's all right.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_04]: Not much, not much.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, and Sky, I know you're pro-Ninja.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to try to send you a Ninjas vs. Pirates shirt where Ninjas win 4-3.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, definitely.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I don't hate Pirates.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, usually, you know, in the Ninja vs. Pirate war, you have to love one and hate the others.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't hate Pirates.
[SPEAKER_08]: I respect Pirates.
[SPEAKER_08]: But they're just, you know, they're just inferior to Ninjas.
[SPEAKER_04]: Plus, Ninjas are cooler.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: What did you want to call us to talk about tonight?
[SPEAKER_08]: Surely it wasn't Pirates vs. Ninjas.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh no, I got a couple of game reviews for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Woohoo, what games?
[SPEAKER_04]: Puzzle Quest for the DS and The Legend of Zelda Phantom Hourglass.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, let's start with Puzzle Quest for the DS because it's the older game.
[SPEAKER_08]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_04]: Honestly, I should have waited until the game dropped in 1999.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh snap, not a big fan, huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I am a big fan of Bejeweled and a friend of mine bought it and I really didn't know too much about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: She said, it's just like Bejeweled.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm like, really?
[SPEAKER_04]: Went out like a couple of weeks later and I bought it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like the puzzle aspect, the puzzle RPG element of it, but it's just that when you're looking at the game, it's like you're not sure where to begin.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you want to build up your gold?
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you want to start fighting the creature, build up your experience?
[SPEAKER_04]: And you just got to be very careful in the patterns that you move because you make the wrong move, your opponent's going to hit like a 5-6 chain combo, then you're like really screwed.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, my wife's not having trouble beating the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, your wife has a super brain or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I don't know, it's just a different way of thinking about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've got a few words for you, Loki, okay?
[SPEAKER_08]: There's a lot of people I know that have beat the game, but it's a different way of thinking about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can't play it like you're playing Bejeweled, because you'll be screwed.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's all about the skulls.
[SPEAKER_08]: You have to look at the screen and make sure there's no skulls that you can line up first, because if you don't get it, I swear to God, the computer will every time.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're ruthless, but that's a challenge.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love unlocking stuff in the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, if I could just sit there and do those puzzles all day, it just kills my entire time on the train going to work.
[SPEAKER_08]: So maybe this game's worth a little more than giving it credit for.
[SPEAKER_08]: So what don't you like about the game?
[SPEAKER_04]: One thing that really gets on me is the music.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, yes, it's supposed to be a medieval style, but the music can be so low that I find myself almost passing out and going to sleep.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll give you that.
[SPEAKER_08]: The music's a little generic in the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's nothing too special.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, well, tell us a little more about the other game you're going to review.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is it Phantom Hourglass?
[SPEAKER_04]: Phantom Hourglass.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is so good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I mean, I'm playing it, I'm like, this is so much like a Link to the Past to me, the way they have it set up.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is what it reminds me so much of.
[SPEAKER_04]: Honestly, I didn't even know you controlled Link with the stylus, I bought the game, and I'm like, I don't know if I'm going to like this, but ten minutes in, I'm like, okay, I could definitely rock this.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is it, this is fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: I see, I'm still not sure how I feel about it, but I'm going to try and borrow it from my friend.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm starting to get poor from all these games I'm buying, so I definitely want to try and borrow it from somewhere, but that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, I mean, how does it compare to other handheld Zelda games?
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, does the whole stylus element just really change things for the better, for the worse, or just the new gen, or whatever you want to call it?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it makes things for the better, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, because the last bunch of portable Zelda games, what do we have, like Oracle of Ages, Oracle of Seasons, A Link to the Past, the port of that, you know?
[SPEAKER_08]: None of those were bad games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: But they were just kind of the Super Nintendo games in handheld form.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, definitely.
[SPEAKER_04]: Could you hold up one second?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did we just get put on hold?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: My roommate's playing Guitar Hero 3, and I think he's on the very last song.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, my gosh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: How funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's pretty hardcore.
[SPEAKER_08]: You've got to be playing that game a lot to get that far.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, Ranma, any other quick thoughts?
[SPEAKER_08]: We've got to let you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: Try to take one more call before we sign off.
[SPEAKER_04]: About Loki's tingle costume, teal green or bright green?
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you going to make him a costume?
[SPEAKER_08]: I know people that will do it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't put the cart before the horse.
[SPEAKER_08]: The game has to sell a million copies first.
[SPEAKER_08]: I ain't going to sell a million copies.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's okay because I can get the fabric for cheap either way.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a win-win situation.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm pretty sure it's a darker green, very similar to what Link wears.
[SPEAKER_08]: But when the game sells you a million copies, we'll send you Loki's measurements.
[SPEAKER_07]: is not going to sell a million copies.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's totally not.
[SPEAKER_07]: That would be extremely, extremely unlikely.
[SPEAKER_08]: But you have to admit, what a hilarious Christmas gift that would be.
[SPEAKER_10]: The ultimate gag gift.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, it wouldn't be Christmas since it's six months from now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, Ranma, we've got to let you go, but thanks so much for calling in, alright?
[SPEAKER_07]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_07]: It would be a fun six-year anniversary gift.
[SPEAKER_07]: For the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, because that
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura and I might have to go to Hancock Fabrics or whatever fabric stores are out there and go get some fabric.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's go to LA.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or just go to New York and meet up with Ranma's friends.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think this is going to be the last call tonight, folks.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's Puppy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Puppy!
[SPEAKER_08]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_08]: Why aren't you in studio tonight?
[SPEAKER_08]: We have a fourth mic now.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, you do?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I have a guitar here with me and that's what I've been busy with today.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fair enough, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, how was the game?
[SPEAKER_08]: How are you enjoying it?
[SPEAKER_10]: I like it a lot.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm a little bit teed off at the amount of selling out that Activision did with the game because by the time I got to the third set of songs, I had already seen like four new companies advertising in the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Really?
[SPEAKER_08]: How did they advertise the companies in the game?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because maybe I'm just oblivious.
[SPEAKER_08]: I totally missed it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, other than the Guitar Center stuff from the store... That I did notice.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've seen...
[SPEAKER_10]: I saw there was Axe doing some stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: They have Axe guitar patterns and these Axe girls that come out and dance during some of the encore stages.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then Pontiac came out and there's one whole stage where it's just like the Pontiac garage like from Jimmy Kimmel Live or whatever it is because it's supposed to be some sort of fancy music video set.
[SPEAKER_08]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: and a Pontiac car comes and runs you over.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's hilarious.
[SPEAKER_08]: But at the same time, I look at this and go, okay, would I rather we have the Pontiac stage of Guitar Hero or the Yaris game?
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, here's one thing that they forgot to mention about Guitar Hero that's really fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: The intro and the fucking cut scenes that are in this game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, the cartoons.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why don't they just do a Guitar Hero cartoon series?
[SPEAKER_07]: That'd be fucking cooler than the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki feels very strongly about his dislike of Guitar Hero over here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, hey, they've already done that before.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was called Legend of Black Heaven, and it was an anime thing about this middle-aged guy who becomes a rocker again and fights aliens, and it's awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: The cartoons, the cutscenes made me think of, what the hell's Metalocalypse?
[SPEAKER_08]: What's that show on Cartoon Network?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's Metalocalypse.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's what the cartoon things made me think of.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't watch that show a whole lot, but anyway, I'm sorry, Bubby.
[SPEAKER_08]: That would be funny.
[SPEAKER_10]: That would be funny enough.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, so what did you, we made you talk about Guitar Hero, what did you actually want to call in and talk about tonight?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, other than Guitar Hero, yeah, that's what I've been spending most of my time on, but I just was wondering also, you know, you were mentioning earlier about the Halo 3 downloading videos and game views and stuff like that, and I was wondering if you had actually seen a bunch of the stuff that had been coming out recently with all the
[SPEAKER_10]: All the funny little clips of people getting killed by cones and shooting themselves in the head with sniper rifles.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, but you need to send me some of the best ones, and I will.
[SPEAKER_08]: Simply because I've been playing so many other games since Halo.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because now we're getting into that gaming barrage where it seems like every week I'm playing a new game I want to play.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then next year I'm going to go back and catch up on everything.
[SPEAKER_08]: So at some point I will have to go get that.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I love taking the pictures and putting them online.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, forget looking at other people's stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like playing with my own stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Stuff that I create is fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: But to be honest, I haven't touched Halo 3 in about a week at least.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I need to look up some of this funny stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: So please send me some funny ones.
[SPEAKER_10]: A bunch of this stuff is actually on YouTube, some of the more popular stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it's all free advertising for Halo 3.
[SPEAKER_08]: All free advertising.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh yeah, definitely.
[SPEAKER_10]: Bungie's loving it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, in all honesty, all that money probably went to the celebrities that they had in the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, they got Slash and...
[SPEAKER_10]: Tom Morello, and I think a lot of original versions of songs too.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, and like the lead singer from Poison, I forgot what his name was, Brett Michaels, he did all the motion capture for the singers in the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did you, what did you think of the new version of Anarchy in the UK?
[SPEAKER_10]: I haven't gotten that one.
[SPEAKER_10]: I never had heard that song before, so I honestly don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's the first time I think the Sex Pistols have been together since the 70s.
[SPEAKER_03]: to record anything.
[SPEAKER_08]: I saw that that was an unlockable video that you could get, so I might have to check that out.
[SPEAKER_08]: I remember the old song, and I know the bad, bad guitar freaks cover, but I'm curious about what this is.
[SPEAKER_08]: Man, they must have been hard up for money then.
[SPEAKER_08]: You never know.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, well, Puppy, we've got to let you go because we're going to go wrap up the show, but thanks so much for calling, all right?
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, and come back to the show in the future.
[SPEAKER_08]: You don't live that far away.
[SPEAKER_08]: I will.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, you better.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll try to.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, take care.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you.
Bye.
[SPEAKER_08]: Escapist in our chatroom says, Brett Michaels should have paid to be in Guitar Hero 3 instead of being paid.
[SPEAKER_08]: I kind of agree.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's great exposure for these folks.
[SPEAKER_08]: And in some extent, I mean, I don't know, God, maybe I'll say something controversial here, but some of these people are kind of washed up.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like Brett Michaels, I mean, well, he has that show on VH1, but, you know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, that doesn't make him washed up at all.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess that's true.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's on VH1.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's usually a sign of being a washed up celebrity.
[SPEAKER_08]: True, true.
[SPEAKER_08]: And you know, I don't know, Slash is a great guitarist, but the mainstream doesn't talk about Slash, but now they might.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you're right, these guys maybe ought to be paying them to be in the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyhow, we've been going at this a long time, so I think it's finally time to wrap this up and call it a night.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we're going to go around and get everybody's final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, we didn't get last minute stories.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did we have more last minute stories?
[SPEAKER_07]: We didn't get any last minute stories.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sorry, then let's get last minute stories real quick.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, so a few things.
[SPEAKER_07]: First off, let's see, GameStop's dropped their Xbox 360 product replacement plans.
[SPEAKER_07]: So apparently now they're no longer fixing those.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess Microsoft will have to do more of that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_07]: GripShift has been rated for the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you might remember, that was a crappy-ass game.
[SPEAKER_07]: They came out on the PlayStation Network and also on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_07]: I highly recommend it.
[SPEAKER_07]: If it does come out on Live Arcade, do not fucking buy it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's horrible, horrible, horrible.
[SPEAKER_07]: That crappy Xbox Live Arcade game stick is now 50% cheaper in the UK.
[SPEAKER_07]: Still shouldn't buy it, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: There is a wonderful application made by Microsoft, I guess, employee Adam Keener, or Kenny?
[SPEAKER_07]: Keeney?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: XBOX Live Friend Tracker TV Program Schedule Channel
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know about you but I'm pretty sure on most cable networks especially if it's satellite or digital cable there's a guide button on your remote to see what's on TV.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do we really need this on here?
[SPEAKER_07]: People are speculating, oh it's going to lead to an IPTV channel.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, where the fuck are you going to store that shit on the Wii?
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what I'd like to know.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you're ordering Super Mario Galaxy you ain't getting your pre-order coin until the fucking game comes out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not that you really should order the game because of that coin.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, might remind you that that game is going to be fucking hard to find around the holidays.
[SPEAKER_07]: So if you haven't pre-ordered it yet, it's time to do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because it's going to be like the Legend of Zelda Twilight Princess where it's near impossible to find.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then finally, Gran Turismo 5.
[SPEAKER_07]: They've had some of the features announced for it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Including there's going to be an online garage course, online head-to-head racing, time trials.
[SPEAKER_07]: Track of the Day, B-Spec Race, License Test, Drift Contest, Tuning and Setting Features, Friends List, Lobby, Voice Chat, Bulletin Board, Spectator Mode, Team Building, Club Building, Color and other editors and looks like some other fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: So photo albums also.
[SPEAKER_07]: Lots of wonderful features for a game that's not going to come out until Christmas of next year.
[SPEAKER_07]: If that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, and by the way, there's also something fun in the little Sears ad that was on gonintendo.com, and I tell you, this also tickles me rose and gold as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_07]: In other words, it also, they basically have the two DS Lite bundles, one with Triforces on it, one with a paw print, the one with the Triforces gold comes with Zelda, the one with the paw print comes with a special edition of Nintendogs.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry that I forgot to bring you the lotion I was going to bring you.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I can give it to you tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or if you want to come by.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know about tomorrow because tomorrow is the boyfriend's birthday.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we're pretty busy, but maybe... Go look for anything with Arnica in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is my natural remedies session.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now I need something for my toothache.
[SPEAKER_08]: Clove oil.
[SPEAKER_08]: I really don't want to go to the dentist because I hate going to the dentist.
[SPEAKER_03]: Clove oil.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm a used car salesman.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Clove oil.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not on the gum, but on the tooth.
[SPEAKER_08]: On the tooth.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what they used to use in dentist's office back in the day.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, yeah, I'm going to be very strict for the next three weeks until Thanksgiving because when I go to Alabama, I am going to eat fried chicken and grits and fried chicken liver.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't talk about food.
[SPEAKER_08]: That sounds yummy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fried chicken sounds good right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love fried chicken liver.
[SPEAKER_03]: With country gravy, I'm going to have fried catfish.
[SPEAKER_03]: and I'm not going to do anything.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a vacation from everything.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Sauce is coming with me.
[SPEAKER_03]: And all we're going to do is sit and watch movies and eat.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sounds like fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sounds beautiful.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I have to be extra, you know, constant vigilance for the next three weeks.
[SPEAKER_08]: Speaking of food, I just want to say this real quick since we love to talk about, like when we're not talking about games, we're talking about food, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: I had dim summer today.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, I love dim summer.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, so good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because like we went to one of those like authentic Chinese places that have like the duck feet and everything.
[SPEAKER_08]: or not duck feet, chicken feet.
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't have any of that because I just don't like chicken feet, but there was some real good food today.
[SPEAKER_08]: That shrimp wrapped up in pasta was so good.
[SPEAKER_03]: The actual spring rolls.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, they had those too.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to go to In-N-Out.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to have a chocolate strawberry shake and animal style fries for dinner.
[SPEAKER_08]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tomorrow I'm having vegetables.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: All the food talk.
[SPEAKER_08]: Your final thought, Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have a lot of games to play this week and not a lot of time.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well said.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that's going to bring our show to a close.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're done tonight, folks.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you for listening to Orange Lounge Radio and thank you for downloading our show if you chose to.
[SPEAKER_08]: And remember, spread the word because that's how our show grows.
[SPEAKER_08]: We are independent after all.
[SPEAKER_08]: We don't really profit from doing this.
[SPEAKER_08]: We spend our time to bring this to you for the past five and a half years because we love you and our live listeners and you guys that stick with us.
[SPEAKER_08]: So tell a friend.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's all we ask.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or post a positive review of us on iTunes or Twitter
[SPEAKER_08]: Any podcasting site you can think of to help spread the word.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, until next week, I'm Rob, that's DarkSakura, and that's Loki from Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll see you next week.
[SPEAKER_00]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_00]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_00]: For more information on our live and podcast programs, visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com See you next week!