[SPEAKER_02]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and released to our podcast stream twice weekly.
[SPEAKER_02]: To listen to the first half of this episode, visit www.orangeloungeradio.com for links to websites with listings of past episodes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now the conclusion of this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: And welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: We are live here on this Sunday evening, October the 7th, 2007, for part B of our 250th weekly episode.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's 250 weeks in a row, give or take a few.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's applaud.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're testing out our new applause light tonight, everybody.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_17]: It just means that we've had nothing to do on a Sunday night now for how long?
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think we've gotten emails about this before.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, how do you guys manage to motivate yourselves to do it every week?
[SPEAKER_04]: And we just kind of go, well, we just do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's our club.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some people go to knitting clubs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some people go to church.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do or do not.
[SPEAKER_17]: There is no try.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some people go to poker.
[SPEAKER_04]: We do a radio show on the internet.
[SPEAKER_17]: Some people go to bingo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_17]: Some people go to a bar and get pissed, by the way.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, back to the news.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bungie, Bungie, Bungie, Bungie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some people play Halo religiously every Sunday night.
[SPEAKER_17]: I like the word Bungie, and I like saying it repeatedly.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's like balls.
[SPEAKER_17]: Just one of those words that makes you laugh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well.
[SPEAKER_17]: Anyway, Bungie has decided to be independent once again.
[SPEAKER_17]: You know what this means?
[SPEAKER_17]: This means we could very well get Bungie games on a system that isn't an Xbox.
[SPEAKER_05]: They could go back to Mac games.
[SPEAKER_17]: Halo for the iMac.
[SPEAKER_17]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: It would look better.
[SPEAKER_17]: It would probably look better.
[SPEAKER_17]: Because what does graphics better, Mac or PC?
[SPEAKER_17]: The Mac.
[SPEAKER_17]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: That should be determined, actually.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, this battle is not happening tonight.
[SPEAKER_17]: Microsoft
[SPEAKER_17]: is going to continue keeping up with the Halo franchise and continue to partner with Bungie on games however we could have another Rare on our hands
[SPEAKER_04]: Killer Instinct 3 by Bungie
[SPEAKER_04]: But she's still got to turn tricks for me whenever I want, basically, is what it is.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's like the pimp in his hoe.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kind of, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what I'm saying.
[SPEAKER_04]: So the hoe's still got to put out when I need it, right?
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, I mean, then that makes me think, what in their right mind is Microsoft going to pass on?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because Bungie makes a lot, a lot of hits.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I think the only way they're going to pass is if Bungie says, hey, we want to make a game starring Mario, or we want to make a game starring...
[SPEAKER_04]: What's the Sony franchise?
[SPEAKER_04]: Ratchet and Clank?
Spyro?
[SPEAKER_04]: We want to make one of these games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Spyro, yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: We want to make a Spyro game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, that's not a Sony franchise anymore.
[SPEAKER_17]: Banjo-Kazooie?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_17]: No, that was Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_17]: That was Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_17]: Crash Bandicoot.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sweet Tooth.
[SPEAKER_03]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dark Knight in chat, chat.orangelauncher.com says, Marathon, Kthanks, and GS191 says, I think it's time to revisit the Marathon series.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ranma says, and Halo was originally developed for the PC before Microsoft bought them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, your comments in chat, chat.orangeontrade.com when we tape live every Sunday night.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, so as we've been talking for the past few weeks now, there's this new SKU that people keep talking about, the Xbox 360 Arcade console.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it's been listed on a few retail sites now, Toys R Us being one of them, another one being Amazon.com, both having it showing as being released on the 23rd.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: All for the same price as the current core system, which is $279.99 in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, you will not be surprised to see this come out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, this story just goes to prove that rumors about Microsoft are always true.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because this rumor about the arcade thing has been going around forever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Forever, and they have screenshots taken from the website.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pardon the man behind the curtain there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pay no attention to him.
[SPEAKER_04]: Going back to Halo 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Halo 3 is in the news, and we love Halo 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's the hatred for Halo 3 over here, Casper?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't hate Halo 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just a boring, generic space fighter game that I'm just indifferent about.
[SPEAKER_04]: Says Metroid.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but have you played the multiplayer game?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_03]: Are we going to get into the Halo game?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, that's where 73% of people go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I just want to say this.
[SPEAKER_04]: On the Japanese software charts this week, Halo 3 actually managed to top the charts in Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, keep in mind, though, that's if you separate two of the Pokemon games, of these Pokemon games, if you separate the two Pokemon games, then Halo 3 was number one.
[SPEAKER_04]: But this is just kind of a for people who said that Halo would not do well in Japan and the Japanese hate Halo and blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would like to actually say I got, because I really suck at Halo, I got my ass kicked by a Japanese player the other day on Halo and it made me feel
[SPEAKER_04]: Halo 3 moved 59,000 copies, but it should be said Pokemon's Mysterious Dungeon Toki moved 55,000 copies, but there's another version called Yami which moved 46,000 copies, but they're counted separately.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gears of War PC
[SPEAKER_17]: which we all know was an Xbox 360 title.
[SPEAKER_17]: There are five new single-player parts of the game, new campaigns.
[SPEAKER_17]: Or, I'm sorry, there are new places to explore in the main campaign.
[SPEAKER_17]: And there's also an encounter with the, what's it called, Bromak?
[SPEAKER_17]: That's from the end of Act 1 in the 360 version.
[SPEAKER_17]: I guess it's this big dinosaur.
[SPEAKER_17]: I've never played it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a big creature thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: They had it in the trailers and stuff.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, they've also, of course, expanded the multiplayer options.
[SPEAKER_17]: They have a bunch of new maps.
[SPEAKER_17]: They've improved graphic quality and resolution so that if your machine is beefy enough, it'll make it look sweet.
[SPEAKER_17]: They don't have, though, the four-player co-op.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gears of War was really fucking hard, especially if you don't play first person shooters.
[SPEAKER_03]: A lot.
[SPEAKER_03]: You probably wouldn't like the multiplayer in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the multiplayer is kind of... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't like the multiplayer for Gears of War.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't play it that much either, though, so I can't really judge it too much.
[SPEAKER_03]: Halo's fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, if you're going to compare just straight graphics, then Gears of War fucking kicks the crap out of Halo 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: And also, too, you know, a bit of semantics here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Gears of War came out last year.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, did it?
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought it was like... No, in November.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, damn it.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, then never mind.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, then wait, but they're still out within a year of each other, so the question still works.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, how about this?
[SPEAKER_17]: If you were a completely new player sitting down and you played through Gears of War and you played through Halo, what would be your opinion?
[SPEAKER_17]: How's that?
[SPEAKER_04]: My thing is I love co-op mode in both of the games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think they both have a stellar co-op mode, and more games should have co-op mode in them because it makes the game fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Quit falling asleep over there, Eddie.
[SPEAKER_04]: But as far as I just didn't like the cover system in Gears of War, so Halo 3 is more the game for me.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't like the cover thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Say what you will.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, I'm sorry, we're putting the Nintendo fanboy to sleep, so we better move on with some news.
[SPEAKER_04]: So sorry to inconvenience you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe we'll just get some completely random news, Loki, to wake Eddie up over there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, something very inconceivable has happened, and they have...
[SPEAKER_03]: they have decided to make a Princess Bride game which is going to be they're going to be releasing I guess sort of a demo version of it to coincide with the 20th anniversary DVD of it and it will be I guess the True Love and High Adventure the official Princess Bride game only one little problem though is that it is going to be a casual game so at least by the sounds of it so far
[SPEAKER_04]: Wuv, Twiwuv
[SPEAKER_03]: I've never heard of them.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're not going to go there.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, honestly, I've never heard of Worldwide Biggies, which can be found at www.biggies.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not familiar with any of their games, so I can't say if it's going to be good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well...
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, sleep all you want through the Halo and the Gears of War news, Eddie.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you've got to admit, this is good.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is Halo being used for a good cause.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is a group called the Cave Girls who put this together.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, seriously, it's like a gaming group called the Cave Girls put this together.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a tournament called the Fight Like a Girl Halo Tournament.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's being held this year on October 20th.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_04]: It has a $10 entry fee.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anybody can sign up and it takes place.
[SPEAKER_04]: All the proceeds go towards the fight against breast cancer.
[SPEAKER_04]: So the tournament is being used to raise money.
[SPEAKER_04]: for breast cancer awareness, which is pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's two different tournaments they're having.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a single elimination and double team, two versus two.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if you want to check out their forums at cavegirlforums.com, they really go down the list of everything that it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you can actually donate your entry fee there online.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pretty neat there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good, very creative idea for a good cause.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would hope that maybe Microsoft, this will get on their radar.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe it'll be a blip on their radar.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe they'll
[SPEAKER_04]: Advertise it on the site or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is it Cave Girls?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it's just like a cave, G-I-R-L, like a no riot girl, G-R-R thing going on there or whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there you have it.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, the resident OLR cave girl is going to open up the mailbag right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you notice how she responded with a very cave girl.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey!
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't make me get out of this club and beat you.
[SPEAKER_17]: We have an email from Picaruno.
[SPEAKER_17]: Is that how it's pronounced?
[SPEAKER_04]: I believe so.
[SPEAKER_17]: Hi, all.
[SPEAKER_17]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm writing in to tell you about something I verified this week.
[SPEAKER_17]: So you know that Sony opened the PC version of the PlayStation Store in Japan only for now, right?
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, there's something to slightly dodge you about how they check to see if you're allowed to access it.
[SPEAKER_17]: When I tried to access the store, I managed to see the front page and usage FAQs, but since I tried to click on a game, I got an English message saying PlayStation Store is not available in the selected country or region.
[SPEAKER_17]: This is rather odd seeing as, you know, I live in Japan.
[SPEAKER_17]: So I took a screenshot showing the error message along with an IP geolocation result.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's on Flickr, but...
[SPEAKER_17]: Now, you might be thinking that since I was using a Mac, the error message was a badly worded way of saying, Use Windows, fool!
[SPEAKER_17]: But no, even on Windows, I get the exact same error.
[SPEAKER_17]: Then Sakurina suggested I try changing my system's language settings to Japanese.
[SPEAKER_17]: Lo and behold, it now works.
[SPEAKER_17]: There are several reasons why this is retarded.
[SPEAKER_17]: First, regional settings on the machine should make no difference to a website.
[SPEAKER_17]: And also to point out something, when the Sarah Jane Adventures was first coming out and they had all the clips of everything on the BBC's website, they actually had it bought by IP, not by your language.
[SPEAKER_17]: This is what Sony should have done so that you couldn't see the website outside of the UK.
[SPEAKER_17]: But anyway...
[SPEAKER_17]: Second is borderline racist as it implies anyone who doesn't have their computer set to Japanese, i.e.
[SPEAKER_17]: native Japanese people, shouldn't have access to the site.
[SPEAKER_17]: Seriously, I'm a registered resident of Japan and I have a legal right to access the store.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's ridiculous that I'm barred because I have my computer set in a language I'm more comfortable with.
[SPEAKER_17]: Does this mean that any native Japanese person can access the Japan store from wherever they are in the world just because of their computer's language settings?
[SPEAKER_17]: How dare you, Sony?
[SPEAKER_17]: You know what I would love for you to do is...
[SPEAKER_17]: Change your settings to Japanese, and I don't think that you'd be able to do this given where you live, but I would love to have somebody else anywhere else in the world set their language settings to Japanese and try to order to ship outside of Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was going to ask, if that's all you have to do, then me living in the U.S., could I just change my language to Japanese and do it?
[SPEAKER_17]: The only other thing I think of, and this is because I've ordered stuff through Japanese websites, is that they actually, the way that the postal system works there, it has it all set by your postal code.
[SPEAKER_17]: And it's set by your postal code, what city you live in, and what section of the city you live in.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's really, really difficult because it's set so completely different than the U.S.
[SPEAKER_17]: system that you're not going to really be able to... If the fields are preloaded that way, then you're not going to be able to do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, good luck on your quest, Picoruno.
[SPEAKER_16]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_17]: So, next email up is... You mentioned the orange box in the last episode, and it just occurred to me that I should send you guys my anti-orange box rant from a couple weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_17]: The Rant, Valve and the Orange Box.
[SPEAKER_17]: Valve, you suck.
[SPEAKER_17]: That shall be the thesis of this rant.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_17]: TF2 and Portal.
[SPEAKER_17]: They added two games I already own and love into the package, cranked the price up to $50 and forced me to buy them.
[SPEAKER_17]: Again.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm not pleased by this.
[SPEAKER_17]: Now, I wouldn't mind this normally, but this is the one way Valve has announced they're selling Half-Life 2 Episode 2.
[SPEAKER_17]: Why is that?
[SPEAKER_17]: This is the point where some of you might say that they did this with Half-Life 2's release.
[SPEAKER_17]: Now, I know I have a special edition DVD.
[SPEAKER_17]: The difference is Half-Life 2 completely upgraded the graphics system for its packaged older games.
[SPEAKER_17]: Half-Life and Counter-Strike, now known as Counter-Strike Source and Half-Life Source.
[SPEAKER_17]: Now, some of the smart people may be like, wow, a company like Valve couldn't have screwed up the release this much.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, they think they didn't, but they have a solution.
[SPEAKER_17]: Gifting!
[SPEAKER_17]: Turns out that if I buy the orange box, I can give away Half-Life 2 and Half-Life 2 Episode 1 to people.
[SPEAKER_17]: What happens to them if they want to buy Half-Life 2 Episode 2?
[SPEAKER_17]: Are they going to release it so that you can buy it...
[SPEAKER_17]: Episode 2 alone, or are they going to do it launch day, or are they going to make us wait?
[SPEAKER_17]: At one point, they were going to have the black box, which didn't have Half-Life 2 and Episode 1, but that was axed.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'll probably break down and dish out the extra cash, because I absolutely adore the series, and let's know what happens next.
[SPEAKER_17]: So if anyone wants a free copy of Half-Life 2 and Episode 1, I'll probably post a follow-up regarding if I break down or not.
[SPEAKER_17]: Either way, Valve has gone out of their way to piss off the core audience in hopes of increasing their gamership.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well done, Valve.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well done.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that is from... There's still tons of people excited about this coming out, though.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's from Super Al.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that is, you know, nobody ever enjoys those type of, like, bait-and-switch things where it's like, you know, hey, you can get it for this low price, but oh, never mind, we don't want to do that anymore because we thought of a way to make more money out of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's just capitalism at its finest.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, hell yeah.
[SPEAKER_17]: So, the last email, because we didn't get very many.
[SPEAKER_17]: Greetings, OLR Peoples.
[SPEAKER_17]: Greetings.
[SPEAKER_17]: Ow, my neck hurts.
[SPEAKER_17]: This is from Poo Face, by the way.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love that name.
[SPEAKER_17]: Hi, Poo Face.
[SPEAKER_17]: Last week's show you were talking about the Asshole Mario levels on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, there is a download of a file you can use to patch Super Mario World ROM and turn it into the Kaizo Mario World Game, a.k.a.
[SPEAKER_17]: Asshole Mario.
[SPEAKER_17]: I downloaded it and played it.
[SPEAKER_17]: I was trying for nearly an hour on just the first part where you have to jump the bullet bills across the enormous jump.
[SPEAKER_17]: I still haven't gotten it, and I have no clue how many vulgarities I yelled out while trying to attempt this mass torture device.
[SPEAKER_17]: Download it and give it a try if you're feeling brave.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: But the sad part is... I'm not dumb.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't say that.
[SPEAKER_04]: You hurt my feelings.
[SPEAKER_17]: We got another email in.
[SPEAKER_17]: However, I'm not going to read it because it was fairly rude.
[SPEAKER_04]: Save it for next week.
[SPEAKER_17]: About one of our listeners, though.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm not going to read it at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, real quick, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to say that the sad part about it is I remember playing this game back when it was a part of Mario All-Stars on the Super Nintendo, and I totally beat it.
[SPEAKER_04]: No problem.
[SPEAKER_04]: It took me like a day to beat it.
[SPEAKER_04]: and now it's like my video game skills have deteriorated with age.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay, you're getting old, Rob.
[SPEAKER_17]: So which is harder, Rob?
[SPEAKER_17]: Who gives you some aspirin to combat the arthritis?
[SPEAKER_04]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_14]: Which is harder, that or the first level of Kid Icarus?
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, seeing as I got to World 2 and Kid Icarus eventually, it's probably that.
[SPEAKER_14]: Terror, danger, horror.
[SPEAKER_14]: I didn't even know there was a second level to Kid Icarus.
[SPEAKER_14]: I only know the first level song and it's like, wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_14]: Did you beat the game?
[SPEAKER_04]: What about you, smartass?
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you ever get to World 2?
[SPEAKER_14]: I never played Kid Icarus.
[SPEAKER_14]: You suck!
[SPEAKER_14]: So no, I didn't.
[SPEAKER_14]: I've beaten Kid Icarus.
[SPEAKER_04]: Me too, when I was 7.
[SPEAKER_14]: I beat Rygar.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or no, I have to have been older than that.
[SPEAKER_14]: Rygar is a great game.
[SPEAKER_14]: Rygar is great, except for the ending.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, if you beat Rygar, that's hardcore, because you could not save or password that game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, that shit was hard.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have to leave the Nintendo One overnight.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, we did, too.
[SPEAKER_17]: And you know what else they would buy on at Commando with Hitler's brain blowing up?
[SPEAKER_17]: I never beat that game.
[SPEAKER_17]: That game was so frickin' hard.
[SPEAKER_17]: You know what game was frickin' hard?
[SPEAKER_17]: It was Strider on the NES.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was based off of the Japanese comics.
[SPEAKER_04]: We need to pay tribute to video game endings at some point.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, we do.
[SPEAKER_14]: Good ones.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not ones that are like... There actually was a funny YouTube clip, I want to say it showed up on Dig this week, about really bad video game endings.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it just was a bunch of bad video game endings back to back.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hate the ones where it's like you can only get the good ending if you play it in hard mode.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, I'm thinking, ahhh!
[SPEAKER_04]: Wimp.
[SPEAKER_14]: Wimp.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well if you would like DarkSakura to read your emails on air, send your emails to mailbag at orangelawnradio.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just keep it clean and don't make them mean.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't like mean emails.
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't want emails bad-mouthing other listeners, so just drop it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Unless you want to bad-mouth Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, you can... Or Rice Princess.
[SPEAKER_04]: We need some good Rice Princess bashing emails.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hey, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Eddie bashing emails.
[SPEAKER_14]: Eddie's fine, but not me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's move on with some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, it started out as an April Fool's joke from ThinkGeek, but now, due to popular demand, they have gone ahead and made it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is the 8-bit tie.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a tie that looks like it's made out of pixels, and you can buy it for yourself for the low, low price of $19.99.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's available on their online store, and I guess it's a way to get you some extra nerd cred.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's a clip-on, by the way.
[SPEAKER_03]: 8-bit tie.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's kind of nifty.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it looks kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I tried.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it would be funny to wear it to work one day, just randomly, and have people stare at me going, what is wrong with you?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because they don't already do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, would you guys see it in the studio there?
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_04]: Would you wear that out in public?
[SPEAKER_04]: Would you wear that to the bank?
[SPEAKER_07]: Not to the bank, but yeah, I would actually probably wear that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because you're a nerd.
Yep.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, something else that is not to be seen in public is new levels from the new Simpsons game.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is, if you're Rockstar.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because Rockstar has their panties in a bunch because they're upset that the Simpsons game dares to make fun of Grand Theft Auto with its own little Grand Theft scratchy game thing going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently, some of the game's content had to be pulled because Rockstar was not happy with the way the license was being used.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, to be fair, Rockstar's not the only one, apparently, but Rockstar's the only one that's being...
[SPEAKER_04]: called out by name.
[SPEAKER_04]: So apparently at Leipzig, there was actually a poster at the Games Convention in Germany, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: There was a poster with Grand Theft Scratchy that caught Rockstar's eye, and they asked for it to be removed.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, on the other hand, Harmonix, they thought Sitar Hero was funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that is... That's great.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is being left in the game, apparently, so... So apparently some companies don't... Some people have a sense of humor, some do not.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: I, I, yeah, probably it's with Apu.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have no idea.
[SPEAKER_17]: I know somebody who has an electric sitar.
[SPEAKER_04]: But here's the thing is that I, I, I have this feeling, to Rockstar's credit, credit?
[SPEAKER_04]: To Rockstar's credit, I have this feeling that it's just one suit who has their feathers ruffled over this.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's just one person whose words have been misconstrued to person versus person.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I bet most people at Rockstar have a sense of humor.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's sad that one person...
[SPEAKER_04]: probably has made this whole thing get blown out of proportion, but that's what happens when you're an executive and you say something silly.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, the thing, I think that their thing behind it is that it's kind of, I mean, they're making it so that it's very obvious that it's a parody of Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, Grand Theft Scratchy, they're not doing it like, you know, was it the game that was in the actual Simpsons show, which I don't remember, was like Grand Theft Auto or something, you know,
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't remember what they called it, like Death Hunter or something, whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: But either way, the fact that it's so similar is why they're probably pissed off.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, if it was a game that you knew was kind of like Grand Theft Auto but didn't actually sound like Grand Theft Auto, they might not be so mad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but is it really going to cut into their profits?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, it's not.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're just whining little pussies.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, thank you for translating.
[SPEAKER_03]: I appreciate that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: One more story before we get into tonight's episode of Match Game, which we promised for this part of RP.
[SPEAKER_04]: One more story.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hold your applause.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're not into Match Game just yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have one more story.
[SPEAKER_13]: We do, don't we?
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, more joy for our European buddies.
[SPEAKER_17]: Call of Duty 4 is going to have a special edition.
[SPEAKER_17]: There was the beta test and all that went on.
[SPEAKER_17]: So what's going to come with the special edition is two and a half hours of SAS footage with the elite soldiers' history and their formation in the Second World War up to modern day conflicts, a making of documentary, a level walkthrough by Infinity Ward, and a hardcover art book with lots of the concept pictures.
[SPEAKER_17]: Anyone playing on the PC has to download their strategy guide.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that will also be available in the United States.
[SPEAKER_03]: Cool!
[SPEAKER_03]: Worldwide loving for Call of Duty fans.
[SPEAKER_03]: But only on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, since it is episode number 250, we're going to play one of our very favorite games, the match game.
[SPEAKER_04]: But in order to play the match game, we need to get some contestants.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we're going to take, if you would like to play the match game, if you're in our chat room, just type me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Only once.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you type me more than once, you're not going to get picked.
[SPEAKER_04]: But if you type me once, then we're going to let Puppy pick our contestant from chat today because he hasn't really talked a lot tonight's episode.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's not enough microphones.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sadly, our fourth microphone died, so we only have three microphones we're sharing.
[SPEAKER_04]: So Puppy will pick the chat contestant soon, but we also want to get somebody on the telephone.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you would like to give us a call and be our person on the phone to play, give us a call right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio or our telephone number, 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_04]: 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to wait for somebody to call.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a little bit of a delay between when we say something and when people hear it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just now seeing all the me's jumping up on the screen.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, meanwhile, okay, so Puppy sees all the me's.
[SPEAKER_04]: So why don't you pick somebody who said me only once that gets to play Match Game tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to...
[SPEAKER_04]: You're going to roll a D20?
[SPEAKER_05]: I did, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my lord.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait, hold on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're getting a chatter.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello, you're on... Hi, FootyMonster.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, FootyMonster.
[SPEAKER_04]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_04]: Is there a bad delay tonight?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, it's probably... I'm having fun.
[SPEAKER_18]: How are you guys doing?
[SPEAKER_04]: Good.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's probably the Operator 11 webcam causing us a little bit of a delay tonight, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a feeling we might have to kill Op 11 in order to have a little lag.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry, Operator 11.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to have to say bye-bye to you guys to kill the lag.
[SPEAKER_04]: But we'll see you next week here on Operator 11 with more Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, that's okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm pretty sure it's the lag is being caused from Operator 11, so we're just going to end the feed there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why are you staring at that?
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hopefully that will help a little better.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can you hear us now, Footy Monster?
[SPEAKER_18]: I can hear you, I don't know if I'll do it.
[SPEAKER_18]: Well, if so, you say something in blank and have to figure out what that's supposed to be, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, we're going to say something with a blank and you have to figure out what that something is.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I just want to make sure you can hear us okay, right?
[SPEAKER_19]: I can hear you okay.
[SPEAKER_19]: I think this is a bit late, but I can hear you okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, well, that's all right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now I see Escapist has left chat, so I hope that's not a bad sign.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to make sure he's still there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you going to play?
[SPEAKER_04]: You left chat.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's never happened before.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have a player just leave.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh shit, I got picked.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm bailing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I scared him off.
[SPEAKER_04]: Leaving.
[SPEAKER_04]: See ya.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh wait, I got a private message back.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whoops, yep, I'll still be there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, what's over here?
[SPEAKER_04]: This is tonight, Footy Monster vs. Escapist.
[SPEAKER_04]: But before we get to it, we need to get some theme music and introduce our celebrities tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, celebrity number one tonight is the queen of the show who does not put up with shit from anybody.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Celebrity number two tonight is the king of the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's me.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki is here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Say hello to Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm here.
[SPEAKER_04]: And celebrity number three is...
[SPEAKER_04]: Rob, it's me, hi, hello, how you doing?
[SPEAKER_04]: Also joining us tonight, say hello to Puppy!
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, and Puppy, are you here to plug anything, Puppy?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because celebrities on game shows are usually here to plug something.
[SPEAKER_05]: Normally I would plug Baskin Robbins, but I don't work for them anymore, so I don't give a shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: So go eat some Ben & Jerry's this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good idea.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go, go get your cakes from Cold Stone.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on, celebrity number five is Rice Princess.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hello there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_04]: And what are you here plugging tonight?
[SPEAKER_14]: My friends.
[SPEAKER_04]: You were about to say.
[SPEAKER_14]: La, la, la, la, la.
[SPEAKER_14]: I thought you were going to say something else.
[SPEAKER_04]: She sounded like she was going to say her butt.
[SPEAKER_14]: I didn't say butt.
[SPEAKER_14]: I said my friends.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, and as Carizzle in chat says, the drag queen of the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: That might have been about somebody else.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then also joining us, celebrity number six.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_04]: Casper the Gay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_04]: Pretty good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Excellent.
[SPEAKER_04]: And what are you here to plug tonight?
[SPEAKER_04]: I will be plugging your butt.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_17]: Remember, it's only porn if you tape it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Footy Monster, do you have anything to plug tonight?
[SPEAKER_04]: I do.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: You don't get to plug unless you win.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, there you go.
[SPEAKER_11]: Do I have to exit the chat or anything?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, you don't have to.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can use them for ideas.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not cheating.
[SPEAKER_04]: But remember, escapists can see their answers too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Question number one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie was very excited to hear that Brewfest was going to be celebrated in World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_04]: However, when she remembered that she cancelled her account, she was sad.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that's okay, she thought to herself.
[SPEAKER_04]: If I want to celebrate with the Warcraft players, I can blank.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie was very excited to hear that Brewfest was going to be celebrated in World of Warcraft, but she remembered she canceled her account.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: If I want to celebrate with the Warcraft players, I can blank.
[SPEAKER_04]: Our celebrities will need to ding when they think of their answer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ding.
[SPEAKER_13]: Ding, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bang.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, Puppy?
[SPEAKER_04]: Ding.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, Puppy's going to... All right, here we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: And do you have...
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you have an answer, FootyMonster?
[SPEAKER_04]: Have you thought of one?
[SPEAKER_04]: We're having very bad connections to Argentina tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have you thought of an answer, FootyMonster?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I can hear you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, here it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: FootyMonster, fill in the blank.
[SPEAKER_04]: If I want to celebrate with the Warcraft players, I can...
[SPEAKER_04]: Dance nude with no armor in the middle of Ironforge Dance nude with no armor in the middle of Ironforge Very good answer And Escapist said Gain 50 points and breathe through my mouth I'm sorry I guess I missed something I don't know DarkSakura, what did you answer this?
[SPEAKER_16]: Let's see if there's a match Not play World of Warcraft
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not a match, though.
[SPEAKER_14]: Can I go next?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sure, Rice Princess.
[SPEAKER_14]: Now, I can celebrate by... Logging on to my Final Fantasy XI account.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not a match, either.
[SPEAKER_04]: Casper the Gay, what did you pick?
[SPEAKER_07]: Go to the strip club, The Full Murloc.
[SPEAKER_14]: You are an idiot!
[SPEAKER_14]: That's terrible, Ross!
[SPEAKER_04]: The Full Murloc!
[SPEAKER_04]: That was the best part.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki...
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, I can celebrate by... Just drinking at home.
[SPEAKER_17]: How is that any different from any other night?
[SPEAKER_03]: Good answer, but not a hat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because you would have a celebratory hat.
[SPEAKER_17]: Party hats, ooh!
[SPEAKER_17]: That makes drinking more fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Puppy, I'm going to celebrate by...
[SPEAKER_04]: Drinking by myself.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good answer, but not a match.
[SPEAKER_04]: And lastly, my answer, she's going to participate by cosplaying in nothing but her lederhosen, which also was not a match.
[SPEAKER_18]: Isn't that almost like a match with me?
[SPEAKER_18]: Dancing dude kind of thing?
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yours didn't involve lederhosen.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, Escapist admits to being a shitty answer, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: Escapist meant to say, gain 50 pounds and breathe through my mouth, because that would make her a better Warcraft player, get it?
[SPEAKER_17]: To be... Yeah, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, I have a life.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey now, wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_04]: I play Ragnarok.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm level 68.
[SPEAKER_04]: at least you don't roleplay that's right, still would not have been a match but I did play on a roleplay server, however I never partied with anyone we were wondering what the fuck Escapist was smoking glad to know everything's okay ready for question number two, everybody are you ready for question number two, FoodieMonster?
[SPEAKER_04]: definitely bring on the pain, here we go question number two Loki immediately went and bought the 8-bit tie upon hearing of its release
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a game, people.
[SPEAKER_04]: The wife apparently didn't feel so great about the tie.
[SPEAKER_04]: When Loki came home from work one day wearing the tie, the wife exclaimed, What is that around your neck?
[SPEAKER_04]: It looks like a blank.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki immediately went and bought the 8-bit tie upon hearing of its release.
[SPEAKER_04]: The wife apparently didn't feel so great about the tie.
[SPEAKER_04]: When Loki came home from work one day wearing the tie, the wife exclaimed, What is that around your neck?
[SPEAKER_04]: It looks like a blank.
[SPEAKER_04]: NilssonSky, everybody think in here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, puppies think in here.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Footie Monster said ding.
[SPEAKER_17]: Ding.
[SPEAKER_17]: Dingly ding.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a ding.
[SPEAKER_13]: You sure do.
[SPEAKER_13]: We don't need to know about your ding on the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rice Princess.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you ding?
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you have a ding?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, I do, but do you have a ding?
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, here we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, wait, I'm actually waiting on Escapist still.
[SPEAKER_04]: Escapist does not send me a private message with his answer.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll just let the music play while we wait for that answer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Folks in chat are trying to help, giving answers there.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, I just saw the answer.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, here we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Finally, Escapist gives an answer.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, FootyMonster, you ready?
[SPEAKER_04]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki immediately went and bought the 8-bit tie upon hearing of its release.
[SPEAKER_04]: The wife apparently didn't feel so great about the tie.
[SPEAKER_04]: When Loki came home from work one day wearing the tie, the wife exclaimed, What is that around your neck?
[SPEAKER_04]: It looks like a... Piece of shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Piece of shit, says FootyMonster.
[SPEAKER_04]: Keeps it very simple.
[SPEAKER_04]: Piece of shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's go around and see what the folks in the studio got.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whoops.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have to say Escapist's answer.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm so sorry.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, say it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Escapist said it looks like a ding-a-ling ding-dong.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's going to be a tough one to match.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: You never know with this group.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, did you put ding-a-ling and ding-dong?
[SPEAKER_17]: Something close.
[SPEAKER_17]: I said big, blue, stripy, pixelated-looking dildo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Big, blue, stripy, pixelated-looking dildo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good answer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not a match.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rice Princess, did you ever think of an answer?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, I said clubbed foot.
[SPEAKER_04]: Clubbed foot.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good answer, I think, but not a match.
[SPEAKER_04]: Casper the Gay.
[SPEAKER_04]: It looks like a... Stripe of Rice Princess's titty juice.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: What the fuck?
[SPEAKER_03]: That doesn't make any sense.
[SPEAKER_04]: What is wrong with you?
[SPEAKER_04]: For real?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't want to ask my boyfriend.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, for the love of God, I have a decent answer here.
[SPEAKER_04]: It looks like a?
[SPEAKER_04]: Piece of shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Piece of shit!
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, and Footy Monster gets a point.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ding, ding, ding.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hooray.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Puppy, it looks like a?
[SPEAKER_05]: Dildo by Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dildo by Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dildo would have been a good answer.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good answer, but not a match.
[SPEAKER_04]: And my answer says it looks like a fucking waste of our hard-earned money.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Way to be realistic.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that's what she would really say.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, honestly.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: So here we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: You are so stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you ready for question number three?
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you going to keep up your lead, footy monster?
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm going to try.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: And blow Escapist out of the water tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: But Escapist, you know, try to catch up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have to compliment everybody.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, here we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Question number three.
[SPEAKER_04]: And our last question tonight, which thankfully has nothing to do with titty juice.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, question number three.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rob was happy to make amends with Nintendo when he called that poor rep back on Monday.
[SPEAKER_04]: They worked out their differences, and the Nintendo rep said she would send out the Wii cases right away.
[SPEAKER_04]: However, Rob was very surprised and shocked when inside the box from Nintendo, there wasn't any Wii cases, but instead the reps sent him some blanks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ding.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ding of the century.
[SPEAKER_04]: Steaming piles of crap?
[SPEAKER_04]: Dried Yoshi crap.
[SPEAKER_04]: What the hell is wrong with our country tonight?
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Argentina.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, we'll start with you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Instead of the Wii cases, the rep sent him some... Tube of Lube.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tube of Lube.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good answer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not a match.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rice Princess.
[SPEAKER_04]: Instead of the cases, the rep sent him some... Tact.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tact.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not a match.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Eddie, the rep sent him some...
[SPEAKER_04]: Titty Juice.
[SPEAKER_04]: How did I know that was coming?
[SPEAKER_04]: It was funny the first time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, and Escapist will like to remind us he's Canadian.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's wrong with three different countries tonight, apparently?
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: Doody!
[SPEAKER_04]: Doody, that's a match with Footy Monster.
[SPEAKER_04]: Footy Monster gets another point.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good job, Footy Monster.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Puppy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nintendo rep sent him some.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ribbed condoms.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not a match.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good answer, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: And lastly, my answer, the rep sent him a bowel movement.
[SPEAKER_04]: Someone had the nerve to send me a bowel movement, and they shall pay for this crime.
[SPEAKER_04]: Watch Pink Flamingo sometime.
[SPEAKER_04]: The couch has rejected me.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Another match for Footy Monster.
[SPEAKER_04]: Footy Monster.
[SPEAKER_04]: Argentina beats Canada 3-0 tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cool!
[SPEAKER_04]: That's okay, Escapist.
[SPEAKER_04]: We still love you.
[SPEAKER_04]: We love Canada.
[SPEAKER_04]: But unfortunately, you did not win tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Enjoy our lovely partying gift.
[SPEAKER_04]: Our lovely partying gift tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some of Rice Princess's...
[SPEAKER_04]: Love and affection.
[SPEAKER_04]: What did you think I was going to say, perverts?
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Foodie Monster, you win.
[SPEAKER_04]: You get to plug something.
[SPEAKER_04]: What did you want to plug?
[SPEAKER_19]: I just wanted to plug the Ultimate Quest, the RPG podcast that's also on ultimatequest.net and allgames.com.
[SPEAKER_19]: And you can listen to it on Wednesdays at noon Pacific or 3 p.m.
[SPEAKER_19]: Eastern time.
[SPEAKER_19]: And, yeah, check it out if you haven't yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, the Ultimate Quest, the ultimate podcast about role-playing games.
[SPEAKER_04]: They certainly are more educated on role-playing games than we could ever be.
[SPEAKER_04]: So check that out on all games on Wednesdays or their site, ultimatequest.net.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Congratulations, Footy Monster.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for having me on.
[SPEAKER_04]: No problem.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now we're going to let you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye, Footy Monster.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was a fun match game tonight, even if it was a little bit random.
[SPEAKER_04]: Spy Game Elevator Mission
[SPEAKER_03]: And now it's a crappy looking gun game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hooray!
[SPEAKER_03]: And they had some screenshots on this ds-x2.com site.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my god, does it look like shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, uh, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I only hope that that's just the DS screenshots, although I think it's only for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, those are Wii screenshots, so.
[SPEAKER_03]: One of those games I don't recommend buying.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know it's coming out at the end of October for like $29.99.
[SPEAKER_03]: Probably not worth $29.99, but hey, find it used.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rent it if you really want to.
[SPEAKER_04]: It might not be that bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then again, it might be that bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, it looks really bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll post some screens in the chat.
[SPEAKER_07]: They should have made it a sequel to Leisure Larry, like Elevator Mission.
[SPEAKER_07]: You mean Leisure Suit Larry?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: However, community leader Brian Gerrard has revealed that Bungie is at work on another Halo game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is based on the Halo universe and is a collaboration between Bungie and Peter Jackson.
[SPEAKER_04]: Isn't that Halo Wars?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, but that announcement's been out for a while now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that announcement was out there for a while, but it's not Halo 4.
[SPEAKER_05]: and some other Halo Universe projects.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought that announcement was already out there.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought it was supposed to be like a movie or a game based on the supposed movie that they were going to do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_04]: And, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: And apparently, though, if they do want to make a Pimps at Sea game, though, they do still have the ability to make that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, the codename for Halo when it was being developed was Pimps at Sea, which actually is a game I would want to play.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_17]: So, for anyone who wanted the Halo movie, sucks to be you.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's dead.
[SPEAKER_17]: It ain't happening.
[SPEAKER_17]: You've been shafted.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_17]: For the bits that were on TV, they had nothing to do with the supposed movie.
[SPEAKER_17]: And, in fact, the powers that be are quoted saying,
[SPEAKER_17]: The film is entirely dead.
[SPEAKER_17]: And the configuration it was in, whatever happens with that movie, assuming the movie gets made, will be a totally different configuration.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's not so much me as the entire vessel sank.
[SPEAKER_17]: Basically, it was a combination of, and there were two studios involved that weren't getting along in the process of making it, Universal and Fox.
[SPEAKER_17]: So guess what sucks?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, if they're not going to make it, I'll buy that Warthog that they made for the...
[SPEAKER_04]: I'd rather they cancel the movie than make one that bastardizes the entire series, to be honest.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think we can all agree on that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's probably for the best that they cancel the movie as opposed to making one that will completely give the series a bad name.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which I'm wondering, if the World of Warcraft movie is really based on the Alliance, maybe it should be Mercy Killed 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pimps at Sea was a fake joke project that Bungie announced, but I thought at one point during the alpha process people were seeing on Xbox Live playing Pimps at Sea, so I think it was a little more than just a fake project.
[SPEAKER_05]: So...
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it started off, it was basically, they were seeing, playing Pimps at Sea, which was, you know, the codename for Halo, and then for April Fool's Day, they created a poster or box art or teaser for Pimps at Sea, which featured a parrot with a pirate hook head, which is pretty funny, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, I would go back to playing Puzzle Pirates if it had that theme going on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, actually I'm considering going back to it after not having played it for years.
[SPEAKER_04]: You played Puzzle Pirates about as long as I played Final Fantasy XI, huh?
[SPEAKER_05]: I played it for about at least two years.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's hardcore.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's still going, huh?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it's still going.
[SPEAKER_05]: They just, like in the last month and a half or so, released a couple of new big features that actually have made the game even more successful.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Three Rings is rolling in dough.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they have the coolest fucking office ever.
[SPEAKER_04]: SSJ100 Matt says if he could cast the Halo movie he might cast Horatio Sanz as Master Chief I think that might be a sure recipe for disaster I think that's no I think that's more maybe why the movie got cancelled who knows ShadowNextGen says with the success of Halo 3 I find it hard to believe there won't be a Halo movie there's too much money to be made yeah but they can make even more by just making Halo 4 yeah but you know it would be nice if they made a movie to fill in all the plot holes between the games yeah
[SPEAKER_05]: It's more like a plot dashed line.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Cortana can just randomly interrupt the movie going like, Save me, Master Chief.
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't people play it for the multi-mode?
[SPEAKER_07]: Is it really about the actual game?
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, look at all the advertisements that they did.
[SPEAKER_05]: They went through that whole process of like, Oh, humanity's last hope is Master Chief.
[SPEAKER_05]: Believe!
[SPEAKER_05]: And those commercials had nothing to do with the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Y'all know that if the Halo movie gets cast, I am bidding for the role of Donut.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, that's all I have to say.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have to watch Red vs. Blue.
[SPEAKER_04]: Never mind.
[SPEAKER_04]: Forget it.
[SPEAKER_16]: I love Donut.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love Donuts, too.
[SPEAKER_16]: Just go on YouTube and look up Red vs. Blue and Donut.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or just go to RoosterTeeth.com
[SPEAKER_03]: and view them all there.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's not pink, it's lightish red.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or you can watch all the episodes on Xbox Live Video Marketplace or... Escapist says, I think there's a comic series coming out that fills in the hole between Halo 2 and 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck that, I ain't reading for shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why did they make me read?
[SPEAKER_04]: And GS68 is basically saying that I can play Tingle but only, quote, as long as Loki is a Covenant alien in a Tingle costume.
[SPEAKER_07]: Tingle from Zelda.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then set the Eye of Judgment on fire.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why has this not happened yet?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because the Eye of Judgment has to sell a million units first.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ah, we should still do it anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: It did, it did.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, we need to convince Joystick or Kotaku or something to run the story as a lie, just so we can say, look, it happened.
[SPEAKER_07]: Where do you even find a Tingle costume, I mean?
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, get a green leotard and a pair of red Tingle loose?
[SPEAKER_04]: Rice Princess will have to get out her sewing kit.
[SPEAKER_03]: First off, Rob...
[SPEAKER_03]: Just so you know, I do get monthly sales numbers, you know, of each title individually.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we can tell if they've sold a million units or not.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you, Debbie Downer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or he can just, you know, change the numbers if it actually does sell over a million.
[SPEAKER_05]: He can say he has proof.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, well, okay, moving on.
[SPEAKER_03]: First off, it'll never sell a million units.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, so there's a lot of Command & Conquer going around apparently.
[SPEAKER_03]: Electronic Arts announced this week that they'll release a Command & Conquer Saga, which is a compilation of 13 games in the series.
[SPEAKER_03]: Included in it will be the original Command & Conquer, Command & Conquer The Covert Operations, Command & Conquer Red Alert, Command & Conquer Red Alert Counter-Strike, Command & Conquer Red Alert The Aftermath,
[SPEAKER_03]: Command & Conquer Tyberian Sun, Command & Conquer Tyberian Sun Firestorm, Command & Conquer Red Alert 2, Command & Conquer Red Alert 2 Yuri's Revenge, Command & Conquer Renegade, Command & Conquer Generals, Command & Conquer Generals Zero Hour, and finally Command & Conquer 3, The Tyberian Wars.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, where do you have time to play all that?
[SPEAKER_03]: And that will be coming out later this month for $50.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, for...
[SPEAKER_04]: Rice Princess, do not say things unless you're going to say them in a microphone because that joke is lost forever.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Boo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, really quickly, I want to mention this MMO, which is something I'm looking forward to.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a sci-fi-based MMO, and it's by Richard Garriott, who, of course, was the guy behind Ultima.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ultima.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: So apparently there was a post on the game's official website.
[SPEAKER_04]: The game is having some stability and balance issues, so it's going to be in beta for just two more weeks.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a sci-fi based MMO that looks like it could be kind of fun, so I'm going to check it out.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the main character is Tank Girl?
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_17]: Dude, Tank Girl is awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kinda.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you can customize your character.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can show you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know how to describe how the game looks.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was looking at a trailer earlier today, and it looks like, I don't know, like Phantasy Star Online meets Mech Warriors or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of crazy.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it looks like fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm going to check.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to try a good sci-fi MMO.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you said they're working on balance issues?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: You mean there's actually MMO companies that care about that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Lord knows there haven't been enough class changes in WoW.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you know, the good thing about MMOs is that they can keep changing it if it ain't broke.
[SPEAKER_04]: or if it is broke.
[SPEAKER_04]: Blizzard likes to break things a lot anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently I'm broken and I need to be changed.
[SPEAKER_17]: If it's broke, break it more.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the way you do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's finish up the gaming news so we can get calls and end the show already.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, Nintendo is giving us a little love.
[SPEAKER_17]: They're offering a Zelda feather stylus.
[SPEAKER_17]: What?
[SPEAKER_17]: See?
[SPEAKER_09]: A feather?
[SPEAKER_17]: It's this transparent feather-shaped plastic thing.
[SPEAKER_17]: And that puts the nail in the coffin on those stories All right
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, we're going to be getting to the Skype line very soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: But one more story for you guys before we get to the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you want to give us a call, 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we look forward to hearing your calls very soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: But first, one more story.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, unfortunately, I guess Rockstar is going to be giving out a Manhunt 2 themed Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's disappointing about the whole thing is the whole artwork is...
[SPEAKER_03]: Airbrush Airbrush
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you think they'll just have a lady on her period sit on it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my god!
[SPEAKER_17]: It's like having Extifer on the show again.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, totally.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, Skyblind is open.
[SPEAKER_04]: Give us a call.
[SPEAKER_04]: 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_04]: The calls are already coming in.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_12]: Hey, it's Ranma.
[SPEAKER_12]: What's up, everyone?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_04]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm doing good.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm recovering from yet another convention I went to this weekend.
[SPEAKER_04]: What convention did you go to this weekend?
[SPEAKER_12]: It's Manga Next, a smaller, low-key convention geared towards Japanese comics and panels and cool stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: And really quickly, sum us up for the con.
[SPEAKER_04]: What was the highlights?
[SPEAKER_12]: The 18-plus stuff, like 18-plus Yaoi, Yuri, dating game, the 18-plus match game that I ran, and cosplay chess.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: You asked us if you could steal the match game from us to play at the con, huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: I remember that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was like, dude, it's a Mark Goodson production.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not really our idea, so you'd rip it off just like we would.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: We recorded the whole thing, so I'm going to try to dump it to DVD, so I'll send you guys a copy of it and see how lewd and raunchy we got.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_04]: So what else is going on in your gaming world?
[SPEAKER_12]: Not too much.
[SPEAKER_12]: From listening from last week, I figured I would call in and get a much better review of Digital Life.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, I swear to God, if we get into the DDR contest, this is going to be a short call.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, I wasn't even there for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, thank God.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, so then what was your review of Digital Life?
[SPEAKER_12]: The rate between a scale from 1 to 10, I'd have to give it a 6.5.
[SPEAKER_12]: I've gone to 3 out of 4 past Digital Life.
[SPEAKER_12]: Last year, it was bad.
[SPEAKER_12]: in terms of there's more vendors, there's more companies, more distributors showing off newer products and selling cool stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: This year, it was like as if they really couldn't get too much of anything.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, last year, GameCap was having a Street Fighter 3 tournament giving out a lot of cool stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: You had Guitar Hero 2, Justice League Heroes, a bunch of other cool games.
[SPEAKER_12]: And you had like two different sets of pro gaming tournaments going on.
[SPEAKER_12]: This year, the big things were the Namco display, even though it was the same one from last year.
[SPEAKER_12]: They were there, you know, it was just a little bit bigger.
[SPEAKER_12]: Best Buy and Geek Squad were there.
[SPEAKER_12]: Intel showed up, they had, I think it was Global Gaming League out there this year with Dell.
[SPEAKER_12]: And if you know any famous people that are handing out autographs, they have like a gamers lounge with the PMS clan.
[SPEAKER_12]: and then like a little kid section for the kids to play games and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why do you think things got downgraded this year?
[SPEAKER_12]: That I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: It didn't make any sense because when I got there, I got there Friday after work for about an hour or some change.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm expected to be packed full of people, full of vendors and exhibits and I didn't see it, you know?
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you think there's any correlation to the downsizing of E3 causing this?
[SPEAKER_12]: I have no idea because honestly what Digital Life is is more of an expo on the latest digital innovations and technologies and some cool games that are coming out this year.
[SPEAKER_12]: Maybe what I think it was so many people went last year thinking it was going to be all of this and they figured it wasn't going to be so.
[SPEAKER_12]: But the thing was
[SPEAKER_12]: Almost everybody there got in for free because if you knew the proper code, which almost everybody knew, you'd save yourself about $7 for entrance for four straight days.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, so if you could give, just to kind of wrap things up here so we can get some more calls, if you had any piece of advice to give the digital life planners for next year's show, what would you say?
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: Keep the same people you got here.
[SPEAKER_12]: Get some newer people.
[SPEAKER_12]: If you really want to expand more into the game, get more companies in there.
[SPEAKER_12]: More free swag, definitely.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, more free swag.
[SPEAKER_04]: Free is always a good thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Free stuff is always a good thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, definitely.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, Ranma, thanks so much for the call.
[SPEAKER_04]: Any last-minute words you want to give our folks here?
[SPEAKER_04]: I love you, Irene.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, I love you too, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_04]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_14]: Come back out here and see us.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will, I promise.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, you better.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Give us a call.
[SPEAKER_04]: 1-877-GAME-OLR Our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's go to the phones.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hola, como estas?
[SPEAKER_14]: Hi, Extifer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, Extifer.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_14]: We were just talking about you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, your ears must have been burning.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I didn't hear.
[SPEAKER_09]: I haven't been listening.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've been watching...
[SPEAKER_04]: How did you know to call us?
[SPEAKER_09]: Because I got a text from Myrene saying you guys are taking calls.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, is there anything you would like to share that's gaming-oriented with your week?
[SPEAKER_09]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_09]: I love Puzzle Quest and WoW still.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, Christopher, guess what?
[SPEAKER_14]: Did Annie tell you that I'm moving my orc from Elder Thalys, my 38, to Ravencrest?
[SPEAKER_09]: Really?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh my goodness.
[SPEAKER_14]: So I'm actually going to play on that server now.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's awesome news.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey Christopher, it's Eddie the Gay.
[SPEAKER_07]: How's your iPhone doing?
[SPEAKER_09]: My iPhone is doing absolutely wonderful.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you for asking.
[SPEAKER_07]: I miss it a lot.
[SPEAKER_09]: You do?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, I'm Eddie and I do.
[SPEAKER_17]: This hasn't raked yet like everybody else's.
[SPEAKER_04]: What the hell happened to this show?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it's like our 250th fucking episode, for God's sake.
[SPEAKER_04]: I always derail the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's my power.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's your mutant power.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, XFR, say titty juice.
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_17]: Titty juice?
[SPEAKER_17]: What?
[SPEAKER_17]: At least he didn't talk about bleached assholes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you hear that Puzzle Quest is supposed to be the next week's release on Xbox Live Arcade?
[SPEAKER_09]: That's nice.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm still playing it on my DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: Will you give Puzzle Quest on Xbox Live a try?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I'm not.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm Christopher and I will not.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because it's stupid.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't have an Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_09]: Silly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, what if you had one?
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's imagine you had one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Would you pay the $15 to download it?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, my hands would fall off.
[SPEAKER_09]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: What is your problem, Rice Princess?
[SPEAKER_03]: This is Xtofer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, Xtofer.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's your problem?
[SPEAKER_04]: Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wait, so what were you guys saying about me before I called?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's something about how you derail the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: And look!
[SPEAKER_04]: Look what happened.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know, look at me.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just want to take a moment and let everybody know that you guys need to think about me in the next two hours, because I might find out if I get a promotion at work.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know that has nothing to do with video games, but think of me while you're playing your video games.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, it does, because you're going to level up at work.
[SPEAKER_07]: Grats.
[SPEAKER_09]: I will.
[SPEAKER_09]: I will level up at work.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll be part of
[SPEAKER_09]: Infinity to Pwnage, man.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, man.
[SPEAKER_04]: No matter what win or lose on the job thing, we're still going to go to Disneyland in a couple weeks and celebrate, right?
[SPEAKER_14]: What does it have to do with video games, Rob?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because, because, this is what it has to do with video games, because we're going to Disneyland and we're going to be in L.A.
[SPEAKER_04]: at the same time E for All is going on, but we're not going to E for All.
[SPEAKER_17]: By the way, by the way, a moment of silence from my premium annual pass, which expired today.
[SPEAKER_14]: Did you know that you could play WoW at Disneyland for $6 an hour?
[SPEAKER_04]: Why would I do that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Why?
[SPEAKER_14]: I didn't say you were going to, but you have the ability to.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: Where is that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because that's kind of a novelty thing.
[SPEAKER_14]: Why would you want to know?
[SPEAKER_14]: You wouldn't do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just curious.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to take pictures of people who do.
[SPEAKER_14]: Fuck if I know anything I've ever been to Disneyland.
[SPEAKER_14]: Jeez.
[SPEAKER_14]: Someone just told me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gosh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Look it up, noob.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stop being so poor.
[SPEAKER_14]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: I want to be poor.
[SPEAKER_04]: Any last words for our listeners, Extifer?
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, die.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_09]: Live, people, live.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rude.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, live.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just live.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're beautiful.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye, Christopher.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, let's get some more calls.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you want to give us a call, 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Waiting for some calls.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just waiting for some calls.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_00]: It's GS68.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello, GS68.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm still playing Maximum Tune 3.
[SPEAKER_00]: I finally got the soundtrack this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Damn it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I saw somebody linked me.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if it was you or somebody linked me to where I could obtain the soundtrack for a low, low, low cost.
[SPEAKER_04]: Zero.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it was just a very low cost.
[SPEAKER_04]: What soundtrack?
[SPEAKER_04]: Midnight Maximum Tune 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, that just really sucks that you don't have that yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you have that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, maybe you could play it for me.
[SPEAKER_14]: Over and over.
[SPEAKER_04]: On my iPod.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, okay, so tell me a little bit about Maximum Tune 3.
[SPEAKER_14]: I would also like to hear it.
[SPEAKER_00]: The soundtrack?
[SPEAKER_00]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, it's very good so far.
[SPEAKER_00]: Like, especially, like, the songs.
[SPEAKER_00]: Like, especially, like, one song that sticks out is, like, Black Pressure.
[SPEAKER_00]: Like, it's not like the original...
[SPEAKER_00]: Max and Toon Soundtrack, like, there's a song called Destination Black that's, like, the Blackbirds theme.
[SPEAKER_00]: Why's it always gotta be about the black songs?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, well, this song, like, starts off with some choir chanting, and that's what, like, made it stand out from the other songs.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like... But it's still Eurobeat, right?
[SPEAKER_00]: Uh, no, mostly... Still... Uh, wait, Eurobeat?
[SPEAKER_04]: This is my heart... No, you're thinking of Initial D, silly.
[SPEAKER_04]: You think of initial D as the Eurobeat music?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it still kind of is.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's more of a Euro rave or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know how to explain it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I'm glad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is number three as good of a soundtrack as number two, if not better?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I'm liking it better.
[SPEAKER_00]: It has more... I'm worried about all the songs in my car.
[SPEAKER_00]: Is it good driving music?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, it's pretty good, but only when you're driving...
[SPEAKER_04]: Just make sure to obey those speed laws, son.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's not very good music to listen to in traffic jams.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's probably not, because then you want to run over the cars like it's burnout.
[SPEAKER_00]: I just pause the music and rewind it back, because I don't want to be listening to that kind of music when I'm stopped, because it wouldn't feel right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well, appreciate the review of the soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_04]: Any other thoughts for our listeners tonight?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, Jamie Moss' speed car is horrible.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's an okay song, but it's
[SPEAKER_00]: The cheesiest song I've ever heard.
[SPEAKER_00]: Which song was this?
[SPEAKER_00]: Speed Car, the one I was singing last week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cheesy.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, well, thank you, GS68, for the phone call.
[SPEAKER_04]: Appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_04]: No problem.
[SPEAKER_04]: Take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll do one more call.
[SPEAKER_04]: 1-877-GAME-OLR, username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Give us a call.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll talk.
[SPEAKER_04]: Our number is 555-4444.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, just kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're waiting for that call.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, here we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_04]: This is Pooh Face.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pooh Face.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_08]: I was just going to say how I'm really looking forward to Half-Life 2, the orange box.
[SPEAKER_04]: What is it about the orange box that has you so excited?
[SPEAKER_08]: I've just been really... I really got into Half-Life 2 and Portal looks really sweet.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, I played the...
[SPEAKER_08]: Project thing, the Narbacular Drop game, that was pretty cool, but it was really short, and Portal looks like it's going to make it a lot better, and of course there's Half-Life 2 Episode 2, which continues the story of Half-Life 2, and Team Fortress 2, I've been playing the beta for a couple weeks, that's pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_03]: All I'm hoping is that later on as a downloadable piece that they have Gary's mod, because that would be so awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's my crappiezy at home, can't write Half-Life 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, Portal is, it looks kind of interesting, but I can't help but think, didn't Prey have something similar, where, like, you had little portals, but... No one played Prey!
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, that's just, I played Prey!
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, the one first-person shooter I did play was Prey.
[SPEAKER_04]: I beat Prey.
[SPEAKER_08]: I played Prey.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I beat Prey.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was pretty cool, and that was what got me looking at Portal, because I thought the Portals and Prey were pretty cool, but... I think they just switched the graphics and made it the same game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, um...
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the first month.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the first month, hang on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even if you don't like first person shooters, it's not even necessarily a first person shooter.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's more of a first person puzzle game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's really original and
[SPEAKER_08]: It just looks like a lot of fun, and especially for the PC version, because people are going to be coming out with mods, like for multiplayer probably, and custom maps.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, that's fair, because I liked Metroid for that reason, just because it's not a shooter really, it's like an adventure, first person adventure game, so, good stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: That, you're a total Nintendo fanboy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, but I don't like first person shooters on any system, even PC, so.
[SPEAKER_13]: I get uber motion sick.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, anyhow, sorry Poohface, you had another thought I cut you off from.
[SPEAKER_13]: Uh...
[SPEAKER_08]: But yeah, I've also been looking forward to Guitar Hero 3, obviously.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm totally looking forward to Guitar Hero 3.
[SPEAKER_11]: Me too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I actually have a guitar.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's like I only have to buy the game and no fucking peripheral this time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Unlike Rock Band where I'm going to have to buy the Uber box where nobody's going to want to come over and play with me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I'm actually getting Drum Mania instead of Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_08]: Are you importing the one from Japan?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's hardcore.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I don't have the money to get the arcade-style DTX drum set, so I'm just getting the Konami controller.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: That'll do, as long as it gets you through the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all that's important.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, well, it sounds like you have a very busy gaming next couple of months between Orange Box and Drum Mania.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're going to be very busy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Any other last-minute thoughts for our listeners?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, Pooface, thank you very much for the call.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have a wonderful week.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hope to hear from you again.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: PooFace hasn't been listening for a little while.
[SPEAKER_04]: He just returned tonight for our 250th episode, so happy to hear from him.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'd like to remind everybody that I had the orange box last year.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hmm?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I had the orange box last year.
[SPEAKER_03]: In fact, I still have it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't really use it too much, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: Isn't that what you called something of yours?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello, Young Orange Songs Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's Raven Stolfen.
[SPEAKER_06]: I missed you, Bucket.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_10]: We just want to wish you a happy 250th episode from the Techie Game Podcast
[SPEAKER_10]: and now we're number 14.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're slightly getting back up there.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're number 69, which is an okay place to be, honestly.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's hilarious.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's my producer, Toki.
[SPEAKER_10]: She produces the show.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow, there's a lot of you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, it's a girl.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's my co-host.
[SPEAKER_04]: God, what was I going to ask?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is she hot?
[SPEAKER_04]: Rice Princess wants to know if she's hot.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why are you... I think so.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, Raven and her, you know, they've been together for like six months now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is there a little showmance going on?
[SPEAKER_04]: Is there a showmance going on on Tekken games?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not at all, Scott.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, it's all a publicity stunt.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can hear her in the background going, What's your publicity stunt here?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm not your publicity stunt!
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, Rook tried to fake it like you guys had a child or something that was illegitimate.
[SPEAKER_10]: He never did.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry, we did call in for something, Sky.
[SPEAKER_10]: We want to talk about the Orange Box.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ah, it's all the rage this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: It would make sense that people think the Orange Lounge show is about the Orange Box, so we forgive the confusion.
[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Box Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tell us about the Orange Box.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you see the commercial?
[SPEAKER_04]: We should call our show next week Orange Box Radio, just to fuck with people.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, what do you want to say about Orange Box?
[SPEAKER_10]: Did you see the commercial for the Orange Box?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was during the Sarah Silverman program.
[SPEAKER_04]: I saw the commercial for the Orange Box.
[SPEAKER_10]: Did you hear what they said about Half-Life?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh God, you were watching that.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, what did, or what, like Game of the Year or something?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, greatest game ever.
[SPEAKER_10]: Greater than Zelda, greater than anything.
[SPEAKER_10]: Greatest game ever.
[SPEAKER_04]: I loved it that they said, this is the game of the year in 2002.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's, well, I mean, like, come on, when they sell movies, like when they do, when they do like DVDs.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, our podcast is award winning.
[SPEAKER_06]: We've won awards.
[SPEAKER_06]: We got like two thumbs up from some guy.
[SPEAKER_04]: We go like, hey, we're a four-time nominee for Best of Life 365 in 2003.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, look at the iTunes store.
[SPEAKER_06]: We got some good reviews, man.
[SPEAKER_06]: None of that pew-pew-pew shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: We got some good reviews.
[SPEAKER_06]: We don't get some mew-mew-mews.
[SPEAKER_06]: We got some good stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: People saying we're the greatest.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, you should get on here so people can hear you.
[SPEAKER_06]: You got awards.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, guys, we've got to let you go because we've got to wrap up the show because, damn, we've been going a long time.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for letting us get on.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have a good one, you guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: You too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye, producer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: They hung up on us.
[SPEAKER_14]: See you later.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to close up the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you guys very much for calling in tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: But now we need to wrap up the show because we've been going a long time tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: First, any last-minute stories?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, a couple just real small here.
[SPEAKER_03]: The simple series, one of my favorite things to talk about from D3, is coming to the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I have the first few titles.
[SPEAKER_03]: These are all, of course, coming to Japan.
[SPEAKER_03]: The first one is the Mina de Kart Race.
[SPEAKER_14]: Mina.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Mina de Kart Race.
[SPEAKER_14]: Everybody Kart Race.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, Everybody Kart Race.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's slated for October 25th.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then they also have Mina de...
[SPEAKER_03]: Bassuri Taikai, or the Everybody's Fishing Conference, also coming out on the 25th.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Party Casino coming in December.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Shooting Action coming in December.
[SPEAKER_03]: the Block Kuzushi, or the Block Destructions, coming out February next year, and the YY Combat, which I have no translation for, also coming in February.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I guess the Onichanbara R is supposed to be coming out to the Wii, and that's that one for those who don't remember.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's the sexy zombie killer game, which is basically the chick wearing just a...
[SPEAKER_03]: No, it's not the fishing conference game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to be busy playing that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nintendo's supposedly working on a game that's going to support the Wii balance board that's going to be a snowboarding title and rumors are that it's going to be the 1080 game coming back.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, maybe.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I'm assuming someday there'll be a snowboarding game that'll support that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then finally, one piece of Wii accessories that will not be coming out to the market will be
[SPEAKER_03]: The Nyko Wii Party Station.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you remember, that's that stupid thing that they had to hold controllers, chips and soda, and all sorts of stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Apparently, originally they were marketing it as $25, but it ended up having to come out for the price of $50.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so no one decided to buy it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, and by the way, it also had LED scoreboards for your Wii tournaments.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that is going to bring our 250th episode to a close.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that deserves applause.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank God it's over.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: But first we have to get everybody's final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we'll start off with DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: Your final thought tonight.
[SPEAKER_15]: I like beer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you now?
[SPEAKER_04]: Is there any particular type of beer?
[SPEAKER_15]: I like Newcastle.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll go around in a circle here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Casper the Gay, your final thought tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for being here, by the way.
[SPEAKER_07]: When you play video games, children's do learn.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: Alrighty.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rice Princess, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_03]: And just when you thought Sony was done with releasing new SKUs, there is another rumor coming out of Japan.
[SPEAKER_03]: About a 160 gigabyte PS3 system.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh yes, this will come with 160 gigabytes of memory on your hard drive there.
[SPEAKER_03]: It will also feature six USB ports, two HDMI outs, and the three Ethernet ports.
[SPEAKER_03]: Much like the original design they showed.
[SPEAKER_03]: And this, actually, they have a brand new SKU that's been logged in.
[SPEAKER_04]: and it will do your dishes and suck your dick.
[SPEAKER_04]: In related news, Japanese men everywhere are marrying their PlayStations.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why the fuck does it need three fucking Ethernet ports is what I want to know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Seriously, what the fuck do you need that many Ethernet ports for?
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that it, Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'm sure, as with all other Sony rumors, it will probably become true soon enough.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Puppy, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for being here tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: My final thought?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Believe.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: My final thought.
[SPEAKER_13]: Master Chief will save us.
[SPEAKER_04]: My final thought is 250 episodes later, and you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: George Takei is still awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: He is still fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, my.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, that's going to do it for another week of Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you guys so much for tuning into and supporting independent podcasting.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you like what you hear, remember we do this shit for free.
[SPEAKER_04]: All we ask is for a little word of mouth.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just go advertise.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tell two people about our show.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you have no friends, or even if you do have friends, leave a comment on the iTunes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Am I Ron Popeil now?
[SPEAKER_04]: Am I Ron Popeil?
[SPEAKER_04]: For only three low payments of $39.99.
[SPEAKER_04]: No!
[SPEAKER_04]: Three low payments of $14.95.
[SPEAKER_04]: Forget it.
[SPEAKER_17]: What was it that Mitch Hedberg said?
[SPEAKER_17]: Three easy payments and one difficult payment?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that was actually the other guy.
[SPEAKER_16]: That was Mitch Hedberg.
[SPEAKER_16]: I just listened to this on Friday at work.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, I thought you said Dane Cook for some reason.
[SPEAKER_17]: No, Dane Cook would have just made obnoxious noises and then talked about his penis.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, the thing was I somehow got my list of comedians who died mixed with comedians I wish would die.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't wish death on anyone.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's really mean.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love Dane Cook.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I don't.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, can we end the show now, please?
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_01]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_01]: For more information on our live and podcast programs, visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_01]: See you next week.