[SPEAKER_00]: Tonight, October 28, 2007, a 360 Fall Update feature may have been leaked, Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_00]: lets you share instant replays, and could Myspace be the next great gaming outlet?
[SPEAKER_03]: Hello everybody out there on the internet and welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: We are that podcast dedicated to video games, gaming culture, and the gamer lifestyle.
[SPEAKER_03]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_03]: Joining me as always, say hello to DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yo.
[SPEAKER_03]: How you doing, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_03]: Been better.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, sorry to hear.
[SPEAKER_03]: But you know, we have good days and not so good days.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm having a not so good day as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll tell you about that in a moment.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have a beer now and that makes everything better.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have Fiji water and that makes things okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let me – I said now I dropped the cap.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now everything sucks again.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hate my life.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't cry, Emo Rob.
[SPEAKER_03]: Say hello to Tech Master Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_03]: How are you doing, Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: Doing fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Doing better than myself and DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_03]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, here's what happened is that I kind of stage dived last night but not on purpose.
[SPEAKER_03]: Those of you guys have been listening – Oh, that's all right.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll live.
[SPEAKER_03]: Those of you guys who have been listening to the show for a long time know that I'm involved with theatrical production of the Rocky Horror Picture Show, which is so different from what we do here on Orange Launch Radio, but we all have a variety of different likes and stuff, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Last night was the big Halloween show, and I was performing the criminologist role, which is what I usually do for them now when I'm not emceeing the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: And right at the end, I was dressed up in my Halloween garb, and my costume this year is Jack Skellington.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll have to go get my mask for the operator 11 people a little later so they can see, because it's actually a pretty rad costume.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I was dressed up as Jack Skellington, but the problem was I had that mask on.
[SPEAKER_03]: So as I was starting to exit the stage, I was walking down the steps, which have no handrail, mind you.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's about six steps to get from the top to the bottom.
[SPEAKER_03]: The MC for the night was running up the steps the other way.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, so I started to walk down.
[SPEAKER_03]: I put my right foot on the first step.
[SPEAKER_03]: I put my left foot down where there was no step.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I tumbled and fell, and it was really bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: Luckily, I didn't break a bone, so it could have been worse.
[SPEAKER_03]: But basically, I landed in kind of like this pretzel shape, and I basically kicked my shoe dug in to the upper part of my thigh.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I would show you on the webcam, except that might be indecent because it's right next to my booty.
[SPEAKER_03]: No webcam scars on that one.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I also didn't... I skinned my knee, too, which kind of... This does not deserve happy music.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why is happy music playing?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's trying to cheer you up.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not a happy event.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's saying, don't cry, Rob.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's saying, Rob... Bad news over happy music.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's saying, Rob, next time remember to hit the stop button when the intro's done.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, so that's why I'm a little bit in a foul mood tonight, because I'm in pain.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ooh, do you have...
[SPEAKER_03]: Drugs for me?
[SPEAKER_05]: I do.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to give you three of them.
[SPEAKER_03]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, let's talk about... You want some Vicodin too?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I don't want Vicodin.
[SPEAKER_03]: Vicodin will make me very sleepy.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: and I played a little Guitar Hero 3 today and my dumb butt husband, I love my husband to death but man, I'm mad at him.
[SPEAKER_05]: He was supposed to bring me Super Mario Galaxy on Thursday.
[SPEAKER_05]: He didn't.
[SPEAKER_05]: I cried because the game's not out for a little while and usually when the demos from Nintendo come, they're full versions.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was going to say, that's what I heard, is that the demo at GameStop and GameCrazy right now is the full version.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, and he was supposed to bring it home so that I could play it for great justice.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's only a couple weeks away.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_05]: Want.
[SPEAKER_01]: Do want.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm impatient.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's my right as a woman.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm thinking of modding my Wii to have a mod chip on it.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, for just modding stuff, not for piracy or anything.
[SPEAKER_05]: You should put a spoiler on it and lower it
[SPEAKER_01]: It can't get much lower.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, it's like the width of three DVDs.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, cases at least, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Eh, whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, no Super Mario Galaxy for DarkSakura this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry to hear it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sad face.
[SPEAKER_03]: How about Ragnarok?
[SPEAKER_03]: You still been active on the RagnarKrak?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yeah, and I have a new obsession in that game.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's that, pray tell?
[SPEAKER_05]: Buying old blue boxes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because you get something random every time, and sometimes you get something really great, and sometimes you get, like, crap, like, you know...
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't ask for heel, please
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, I don't play support classes, okay?
[SPEAKER_05]: The closest I come to support is when I'm playing a dancer.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that's just so, you know, she can walk around like a hoochie with a whip.
[SPEAKER_03]: For fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: For fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've got a gunslinger, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's wearing a pimp hat.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, yeah, that's about it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright, well, Loki, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_01]: My gaming week was okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: It didn't play as much as I thought I would be, but I bought a copy of...
[SPEAKER_01]: since basically I was too lazy to cancel my pre-order for Ratchet & Clank Future Tools of Destruction so now I have a copy of it and I haven't played it yet because I took the shrink wrap off of it and I'm like, ooh, case!
[SPEAKER_01]: And put it down on the coffee table and went on my way doing other things.
[SPEAKER_01]: I watched Nelly play Excite Truck because she's like, hey, I want to play Excite Truck again, so...
[SPEAKER_01]: There's... She's back into that again.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's nice to see someone showing the Wii a little love once in a while.
[SPEAKER_01]: Dude, Excite Truck is awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it seriously is the best Wii game, I think.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I don't give a shit about Zelda.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't give a shit about Metroid.
[SPEAKER_01]: Excite Truck is where it's at.
[SPEAKER_01]: If not the best game on the console, it's definitely the best racing game.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, whatever.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyways, I did play some Halo 3 multiplayer last night.
[SPEAKER_01]: That was kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: We went to a Halloween party and so we did
[SPEAKER_01]: Split Screen, and Live Multiplayer, and that was fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then I played some Orange Box, played more Portal.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've been playing more Conan, and that's an okay game.
[SPEAKER_01]: It'll be fun to play through it, but then after that, I won't be playing anymore after that.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then on the PSP, I've been playing more of the Jackass game, so I can finish it and delete it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean,
[SPEAKER_01]: sell it back, and, um, then, what else, um, oh, Guitar Hero 3, I tried a little bit of that, and it's, you know, Guitar Hero, I mean, fuck, there's not really much I can say about it, it's not like innovative or anything, it's just, um, I broke my guitar, because, um, you know, a lot of people might not remember, um, our Op 11 show that we did last week, um,
[SPEAKER_01]: We showed that my guitar had the orange and blue buttons out of order on there for some reason, which is weird.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I tried to fix it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I fixed it fine.
[SPEAKER_01]: I took it apart just fine.
[SPEAKER_01]: Unfortunately, it's designed slightly different than, say, the retail Guitar Hero 3 guitars because in the retail ones you're able to take off the entire top of the guitar so you can change faceplates and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, the wired version of it
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_03]: Let me read some comments real quick to our Gaming Weeks and use this opportunity to introduce the chat room.
[SPEAKER_03]: We always tape live on Sunday night, and that allows us to interact with our listeners.
[SPEAKER_03]: Chat.orangelawntrader.com is the place to be Sunday at 6 p.m.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pacific when we tape.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we have JAP28 wants to know, why not just paint them, Loki, in regards to the switch buttons?
[SPEAKER_01]: Because it wasn't that hard to take them apart to switch out the buttons.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's just that it's not designed to be taken apart.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, the...
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: Faceplate on it, when I was putting it back together the first time, we wouldn't have this issue, it would be fine.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's just, you know, who cares?
[SPEAKER_01]: It's just, I've got another guitar already.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't play multiplayer at my house, and when I do, it's only going to be in Rock Band anyways, so, whatever.
[SPEAKER_01]: And yes, I do like to tinker with stuff, as Blaze says in the chatroom.
[SPEAKER_03]: Gerardimo comments in our chatroom, Well, Loki, Excite Truck is up against the other launch racing game, and that's really it.
[SPEAKER_01]: There was more than just the one launch game.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, there was Need for Speed Carbon, there was the crappy GT racing game, Monster 4x4 World Circuit.
[SPEAKER_01]: And were any of those games particularly memorable?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, I played all of them and they sucked.
[SPEAKER_01]: Especially the Monster 4x4 World Circuit and GT.
[SPEAKER_01]: Excite Truck was awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: The problem is the company that's making it doesn't really make anything else.
[SPEAKER_01]: All they do is make racing games and before that it was some NASCAR heat game or something like that, but
[SPEAKER_01]: Get on it!
[SPEAKER_01]: Make Excite Truck 2!
[SPEAKER_01]: Come on!
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, seriously, just more of the same.
[SPEAKER_01]: You don't need to fucking innovate it.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was fine the way it was.
[SPEAKER_01]: It just needed to be longer, have more tracks, maybe some downloadable stuff once Nintendo figures out this whole download service or whatever.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, that would be kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: But, um, until then, you know, I'm trying to play every other racing game on the platform to see if there's something sort of similar to, you know, Excite Truck.
[SPEAKER_01]: Then, of course, Mario Kart's gonna be awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: But that's a different type of game.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, that's...
[SPEAKER_01]: Nelly's not going to like that game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Going back to DarkSakura's Gaming Week in chat, Shadowslyer says, first thing I install after I get Windows, freaking Ragnarok, and it's all thanks to OLR.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's because it's crack.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ragnacrack.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see, my Gaming Week, if you're all finished, Loki.
[SPEAKER_01]: Think I'm done.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: and I don't know if that's because of a some type of like up ramping in the difficulty curve but I noticed that like the king this time in a lot of the stages the big trick is that the king wants you to grab all of a certain item for instance there's one level where he wants you to grab Japanese things so you have to roll up as much sushi and you know fireworks and flags as you can that are Japanese or there's one level where you're supposed to roll up nothing but hot things which was kind of a cool level there wasn't anything like that in the last game but um
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, there was something like that in the last game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, there was the big fireball, huh?
[SPEAKER_01]: The campfire.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_03]: So see, a lot of it kind of seems like we've sort of seen it before.
[SPEAKER_03]: But here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will collect all of that item, and then the king is like, well, your Katamari sucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Even though I got it the size you wanted, everything's like, wow, your Katamari sucks, and it needs more of this item.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you're kind of like,
[SPEAKER_03]: Dude, was this game bug tested?
[SPEAKER_01]: It needs more Cowbell.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do I really just suck this bad at Katamari?
[SPEAKER_01]: You just need to say when he asks you to do stuff, you're like, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, roll over stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's all I do, you know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Except for the fire thing, because you have to be real careful with that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Otherwise, you'll keep failing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, that's how I beat the stages now.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was trying to be careful in the beginning, but I do feel like the difficulty curve went up a little bit in this game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because if you think about it, each level that's themed after something like Japanese or whatever, they're going to have tons of that item everywhere.
[SPEAKER_01]: So all you have to do is just roll over everything.
[SPEAKER_01]: And the majority of it will be that item.
[SPEAKER_01]: And your Katamari OBV.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'm sorry, Katamari fans, but this one's the worst game in the series so far.
[SPEAKER_03]: Honestly, the only reason I would suggest... Yeah, I would play the PSP version.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: The only way I would suggest picking this game up is if you don't have a PlayStation 2, which I can't imagine there's that many people.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I know there's somebody.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're going to get an email from somebody.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I can't imagine there's that many people that only own a 360 that don't own a PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: And honestly, just go back and play the first and second games again because they're superior.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I know there's Xbox Live modes, but they're kind of shiny.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then there's this whole downloadable content, which takes me on another rant for a moment.
[SPEAKER_03]: And this is a call to all the other bloggers and podcasters and media types that might listen to this program.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know how the downloadable content on this game has been discovered to simply be another unlock key for items that are already on the disc.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's not like we haven't seen this before.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, Dance Dance Revolution Universe comes to mind.
[SPEAKER_03]: We had that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Can you think of any others, Loki?
[SPEAKER_01]: Need for Speed, like practically every EA game with the unlockable cheats and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: We need to no longer call this downloadable content because it's not.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_01]: Car Key, you know, this is a download key, whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: That makes sense to me to call it that.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, from here on out, on this show, when we discover things like this, we're no longer going to refer to it as downloadable content.
[SPEAKER_03]: When we talk about it, review it on the show, it will now be referred to as pay-to-unlock content, because that's what it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, downloadable content, actual downloadable content in my mind would be something like Elder Scrolls Oblivion.
[SPEAKER_05]: The characters in Marvel Ultimate Alliance.
[SPEAKER_03]: and you weren't just downloading a key for that?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that you were actually downloading the full characters.
[SPEAKER_05]: See, that's the hard thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because they had to release a new version that already had them in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's true, that's true.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's going to be the hard thing about this is that game companies are not up front with this information usually.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, they prefer it to be seamless to the customer.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're just this tiny little show in somebody's spare bedroom, independently run.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I'm putting a call out there to all the bigger folks who might happen to listen to this program.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think we need to start asking developers when they announce this content.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is this downloadable content or is this pay to unlock content?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not saying pay to unlock content is necessarily a bad thing, but let's call it what it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's not, you know, if you're going to do it this way, I think the consumers have a right to know what it is that they're buying.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: I still bought the pay-to-unlock content in the realm of DDR.
[SPEAKER_03]: I bought the song pack.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not going to stop me from buying it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not saying we have to boycott all pay-to-unlock content, but I think we should be fair and call it what it is, pay-to-unlock content.
[SPEAKER_03]: So there you have it.
[SPEAKER_01]: And that even gets to the whole thing of why the fuck is it locked in anyways and why –
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a little bit janky to me.
[SPEAKER_01]: I can understand if you're saying, you know, in those EA games or whatever, where you want to cheat and say, okay, I want to unlock the cheat codes or something like that, and I don't want to play through the game, I'm just going to buy them.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, well, that's fine if you want to do that, because that's your choice.
[SPEAKER_01]: But it's stuff that's in the game, which I think Katamaru was too short anyways, and the fact that there was more levels in there, that's kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that's why this one particularly stings and why we need to put our foot down with this one because I think a lot of people feel, even for considering it was a $40 game and not a $60 game, it was still a little too short.
[SPEAKER_03]: And to have those unlock codes come out not even a week after the game is out is a little bit of a punch to the gut.
[SPEAKER_01]: Right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, it's just like all the DDR unlock songs.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's stupid too.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I understand why they do that because the licensing stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yet, at the same time, I also think that they could probably, you know,
[SPEAKER_01]: Bundling the licensing cost into the game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because I don't think that five extra songs are really going to cost five extra dollars or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: OLArmyBlaze asks, is the $5 horse armor downloadable or unlock content?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's downloadable.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, granted, it's shitty downloadable content, but it is downloadable content.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not saying that downloadable content... There's a perfect example of where downloadable content may not actually be better than pay-to-unlock content.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I'm just saying, let the consumer know what it really is they're spending their money on.
[SPEAKER_01]: Here's the other thing that people also forget, and...
[SPEAKER_01]: It's pretty easy to forget it, but if you go to retail kiosks, a lot of this downloadable content that costs you money, like themes and stuff, is actually available for free.
[SPEAKER_01]: If you bring your memory unit, and you can download it straight off there.
[SPEAKER_01]: I remember when Saints Row came out, they had some downloadable clothes or something that you could get for it, and it was all free on there.
[SPEAKER_01]: It cost you money on live, but it was free from the retail kiosks.
[SPEAKER_01]: So that's another option, too.
[SPEAKER_01]: Get one of those memory units and check it every now and then.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's what they're trying to do, but they don't advertise that shit, which is annoying.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, from here on out, we'll start on this show, calling it what it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I beg of the OL Army and the listeners of this program, spread the word.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's get it out there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's put our foot down as gamers and demand the developers call their releases what they are.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that whole microtransactions thing, we'll save that for another day.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because then you're getting into a whole other ballgame.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyhow, that's really pretty much it for my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I did play some of the Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess I should say real quickly, I did play some of the Xbox Live Arcade games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Exit
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: with the GuitarHero.com site and how you can link your Xbox 360 or from what I understand Wii or PlayStation 2 or 3 whatever versions to the website and you can have like an online band and all this stuff and these online on the web leaderboards.
[SPEAKER_03]: I really like that kind of functionality.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is that that whole web 2.0 thing to an extent?
[SPEAKER_03]: Rob, what did you think of the changes in interface during gameplay?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was a little hesitant to hearing that Harmonix was not going to be behind it and it was going to be a Neversoft, but considering they built the whole thing from the ground up, it's not bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm hearing things about some frame rate issues that people are having.
[SPEAKER_03]: I haven't noticed it yet, but then again, keep in mind I've only really played like five songs so far.
[SPEAKER_05]: I really like how it looks a lot better now.
[SPEAKER_03]: The cool thing about them having built the thing from scratch is that they didn't just up-res something they had before, as in the case of Guitar Hero 3, it's from the ground up.
[SPEAKER_03]: and I love the cartoon stuff in between levels.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, that was great.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dan was saying today, he's like, I love the bassist.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, honestly, this is kind of like the step up that I think Guitar Hero 2 should have been in a way.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not that I'm saying Guitar Hero 2 is bad, but it's just kind of like there wasn't much there.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was kind of a rehash of the first game with new songs.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think this is generally a step in the right direction, but again, I need to spend a little more time with the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I haven't played it online at all, but I'm liking what I see so far.
[SPEAKER_03]: So if chat room, you guys have some comments, chat.orangeloungeradio.com and we'll be reading those.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just trying to see what's going on.
[SPEAKER_03]: A lot of folks were still commenting on the unlock, pay to unlock stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Kevin DDR says, pay to unlock is only fine, in my opinion, when you have low or no price for the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Kind of like Xbox Live Arcade maybe, but usually they don't really do much pay to unlock with Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or free to unlock.
[SPEAKER_03]: and the only thing you're paying is for the price of Xbox Live Gold or Silver.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, Silver is free.
[SPEAKER_03]: But like I'm talking about like the Dead Rising costumes were free, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: But you had to be connected to Live to download them.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think many people have a problem with that and that just kind of is an enhancement for those folks that happen to be on the internet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, Rob.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what's bullshit about Guitar Hero 3?
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: They took out Pandora.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did they?
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't even notice.
[SPEAKER_05]: They put in that stupid Midori.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like Midori.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hate her.
[SPEAKER_05]: She's so stupid.
[SPEAKER_03]: I unlocked her green hair.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: I so miss Pandora because she was like the total goth rocker.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pandora was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe she's unlocked later.
[SPEAKER_05]: She's not an unlockable.
[SPEAKER_05]: She's completely not in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: But we do have Slash now.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, let's get to some housekeeping tonight, and then we'll get into the gaming news.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not a lot to say for housekeeping tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: I do want to encourage, if you didn't check it out, I mean, now the game's kind of out there, so it might not be as exciting, but on Operator 11, we did do a Guitar Hero 3 retail unboxing after the show last week, and we hope to bring you more stuff like that later.
[SPEAKER_03]: The chat room was asking if maybe we'd play some Guitar Hero 3 after the show tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, because I'm kind of...
[SPEAKER_03]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: Guitar Hero 3 Guitar on Guitar Hero 3
[SPEAKER_01]: But the Guitar Hero 2 Explorer model, at least on the 360, does work with both.
[SPEAKER_01]: So that's where you need to go.
[SPEAKER_01]: Buy that one instead.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, of course, some speculation is, you know, why is it not working?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, it might be that, you know, Activision's only, in fact, it does say on the box, only official guitars will, you know, work with Guitar Hero 3.
[SPEAKER_01]: And they've been known to do this in the past.
[SPEAKER_01]: But Rock Band though, Harmonix has actually come out and said they welcome any third-party software or they support any third-party guitars or accessories, so
[SPEAKER_03]: You can't help but feel like, though, that there's a little bit of, like, jabs going on here with this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I don't know if it's just an unfortunate coincidence for these guys, but it does feel a little bit like you wonder if they're taking jabs at each other, which is shit for the consumer.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, you know, but I guess according to that quote or whatever I had heard, they were saying, you know, well, we base it off the standard Xbox Live, you know, blah, blah, blah, and if people make their controllers to the Xbox Live specifications, then everything ought to work.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: But for whatever reason, it doesn't seem to be working in this case, which sucks for us in the end.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not for me, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: I resisted buying the bundle because I already had the Guitar Hero 2 controller.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, there's a lot of third-party adapters that they have out there that require... Like, for example, the ones that hook up a keyboard and mouse via the USB.
[SPEAKER_01]: You have to have a wired controller plugged in because it reads that identifier off of the wired controller and thinks it's just a wired controller plugged in.
[SPEAKER_01]: Otherwise, it wouldn't work either because that platform is not open.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's just...
[SPEAKER_01]: The third-party companies have to license that stuff, so when the homebrew guys decide to make an adapter for it, they have to kind of trick it.
[SPEAKER_01]: And maybe, maybe, someone will come up with an adapter for, say, the Rock Band guitar, the hookup to the 360 that also has a wired controller plugged in that will allow you to do this, kind of bootleg it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or, in my opinion, the bigger company will hotfix their game to just make it work.
[SPEAKER_03]: They'll find the specifications of the other guitar and just make it work.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll see, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: This user named Torchy has started a thread.
[SPEAKER_03]: Warning to those buying Guitar Hero 3 at Walmart.
[SPEAKER_03]: Check your bundles packaging carefully before you purchase to ensure the correct guitar is enclosed.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they have included screenshots.
[SPEAKER_03]: And yes, there are some bundles of Guitar Hero 3 that come with the classic red SG guitar controller.
[SPEAKER_03]: And there's screenshots all over this thread to prove that it's true.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, who knows where this is coming from?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I would think, well, this box... I mean, I don't think Walmart could have cooked these boxes up themselves.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it seems to me like it's some type of agreement with the company in a way for Walmart to stay the low-priced leader or whatever.
[SPEAKER_01]: They have to take some things out.
[SPEAKER_01]: They can sell it probably cheaper than getting rid of some of those older guitars.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_01]: So...
[SPEAKER_05]: That's completely false advertising, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_01]: It says it right on the box.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't think it's false advertising.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I wouldn't say it's false advertising, except it's kind of misleading for those of us that have been following this game on the internet, because we never knew that Walmart was going to do ha-ha-ha, switcheroo.
[SPEAKER_03]: And unfortunately, some of these people who ran to the store at midnight, picked up the first copy of Guitar Hero 3 on the shelves, like, oh, I've got to get this.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they maybe didn't think to read the box first, because they were just so excited, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Who can fault them?
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey, but hey, here's one thing, though.
[SPEAKER_01]: You can always take it back to Walmart, because they'll take returns on almost anything.
[SPEAKER_03]: That is a very good point.
[SPEAKER_03]: Walmart also has a very liberal return policy, and quite frankly, you ought to tell them, this was not the game I was expecting to buy.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is not the controller that you're looking for.
[SPEAKER_01]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, there you have it.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, be careful.
[SPEAKER_03]: A word of warning to those who are going to be buying their game at Walmart.
[SPEAKER_03]: Although, maybe you ought to just go to Target, Best Buy, GameStop,
[SPEAKER_03]: Guitar Center, for God's sake, sells this game
[SPEAKER_05]: If anybody wants to know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would like to know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would like to know the highlights.
[SPEAKER_03]: Read the songs that jump out at you as awesome inclusions.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, Rolling Stones, Give Me Shelter, and The Who, Won't Get Fooled Again, Boston, Foreplay, Long Time, David Bowie, Suffragette City.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, this game has David Bowie in it, and I'm happy it wins.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a cover of Paranoid by Black Sabbath.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't Fear the Reaper, Blitzkrieg Pop by The Ramones, Detroit Rock City by Kiss, though that makes me happy.
[SPEAKER_05]: We've also got Rush's Tom Sawyer, which is one of my favorite songs.
[SPEAKER_05]: Faith No More Epic, Pixie's Wave of Mutilation.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is my favorite R.E.M.
[SPEAKER_05]: song, Orange Crush.
[SPEAKER_05]: And we've also got Learn to Fly by Foo Fighters, Inner Sandman, Metallica.
[SPEAKER_05]: We've got Weezer's Say It Ain't So, Radiohead Creep, and I love Radiohead.
[SPEAKER_05]: Beastie Boys Sabotage, Black Hole Sun, I Think I'm Paranoid, Celebrity Skin and then for the more current stuff we have OK Go, here it goes again, Nine Inch Nails, The Hand That Feeds Red Hot Chili Peppers, The Danny California, The Killers When You Were Young and then one of the unlockable tracks is Ben Camaro, With Pleasure
[SPEAKER_03]: Random ass thought here.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it's kind of interesting because two of those bands you named that are in the game, Radiohead and Nine Inch Nails, have been in the news a lot lately about, you know, kind of their defiance of traditional record releasing.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, obviously Radiohead put out their album in rainbows on the internet for people to pay whatever they want for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Nine Inch Nails basically declared their independence from record label recently.
[SPEAKER_03]: It kind of gets me thinking.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is this type of Guitar Hero Rock Band thing a possible delivery method, promotional tool of new songs by these artists in the future?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yep, they've already said they want to do that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Wow, that's pretty rad.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're going to be releasing whole albums, and they're going to be tying in stuff with MTV, and that is definitely something that's going to happen with Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_01]: You watch.
[SPEAKER_01]: Very interesting little tie-in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm pretty happy with the list, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: I do want to say this, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I thought you had your hand raised.
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, bad radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will say this, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: Unfortunately, Rock Band did not have Heart.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: That makes me sad.
[SPEAKER_03]: That does make me a little sad, because Guitar Hero 3 did have Barracuda, which was all kinds of awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because pre-'80s Heart was the best.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: When they were still that folk rock.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, some post-'80s, you know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: In the 80s, they had Gem Hair.
[SPEAKER_03]: They did have Alone, too, which was, like, the best song ever.
[SPEAKER_03]: They had Gem Hair.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, thank you for the report on Rock Band, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think it's awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: I wish they would have, like, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Prodigy or something in there.
[SPEAKER_01]: That'd be pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: Nine Inch Nails in there.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's really sweet.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what I'm saying.
[SPEAKER_03]: If like Rock Band does well, I really hope they put out something like something to appease those of us that didn't
[SPEAKER_03]: Get more Beatmania in the US.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I know that's kind of a bit, you know, a lot of the purists for Beatmania are probably going to go, What?
[SPEAKER_03]: But seriously, I would like to see some type of trance dance using the Beatmania concept but improving on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it would be a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: But using songs that we know a little more over here maybe.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not to say that songs in Beatmania were bad because they really weren't.
[SPEAKER_03]: Although I do feel the series has gotten a little stale now that we're on, what, 13th, 14th game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would like to see stuff like Prodigy and all these other...
[SPEAKER_01]: Put out a game with Above and Beyond in it, I swear to God I'm so there.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'll pay $80 for controller, hands down, I'm there.
[SPEAKER_01]: So some other interesting things, and this is kind of something we've talked about before with patents and stuff, and why the hell isn't Konami suing these people for using, obviously since Guitar Freaks, Drum Mania came out way long before Rock Band or Guitar Hero were even around.
[SPEAKER_01]: So what's up?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, apparently actually Harmonix, and they've been licensing the rights to use this stuff, including the patents for the guitars,
[SPEAKER_01]: are being licensed from Konami.
[SPEAKER_01]: However, for the drum stuff, they're not licensing it since that's actually being, they're using patents from Drumscape, if you remember that MTV arcade drum game that came out a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_01]: Vaguely.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think I like saw it once and thought it looked kind of dumb.
[SPEAKER_01]: I never played it.
[SPEAKER_01]: So that was pretty interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: And also, of course, Activision is also licensing the rights for guitars as well.
[SPEAKER_01]: So,
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, Konami doesn't need to necessarily bring out the game here because they're making money outside from the sales of these.
[SPEAKER_03]: Gotta go to chat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Chat.OrangeLaunchRadio.com Legend of Zaku says, Fuck you, Sky.
[SPEAKER_03]: Konami needs to do it, not Harmonix Red Octane in regards to Beatmania.
[SPEAKER_03]: If they want to do it, great.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I'm not going to sit around and wait.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, I would totally support Konami doing this.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wish they would.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think they could do an awesome job with it.
[SPEAKER_03]: But they're not.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, they're testing 2DX Gold in America, but that's not going to do it.
[SPEAKER_03]: For those of us that have been hardcore into Balmani for a long time, yeah, that's awesome news.
[SPEAKER_03]: But where did Guitar Hero succeed where Guitar Freaks did not?
[SPEAKER_03]: Guitar Hero brought songs everybody knew and everybody wanted to play and people wanted to rock out in their living room to well-known songs.
[SPEAKER_03]: Unless Konami is willing to invest a little money in a powerhouse song list, not going to happen.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's just – to me, that's fact.
[SPEAKER_03]: and that's based on the success of Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: But if Konami wants to step up their game on Beatmania, I totally support it and I think they could kick some major ass and beat these other guys to the punch and show us why Konami was first.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't think they should bring it over.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't think they will.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't think they should because to be honest, Konami, especially in their, you know, Bimani, you know, line, has not been innovative in the last like 10 years.
[SPEAKER_01]: Seriously, I mean, what have we seen come out of there?
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_01]: Extreme, and Supernova, and the Universe series, and hell, Hottest Party, that shit is not innovative at all.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's just fucking copying and pasting shit from other games.
[SPEAKER_03]: I agree and I don't, because I actually thought some of the single player modes in Ultramix, I love Ultramix too, that's my favorite freaking Ultramix ever.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm not talking about Ultramix.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_01]: Pay to unlock packs.
[SPEAKER_01]: My mistake.
[SPEAKER_01]: One.
[SPEAKER_01]: One is the only thing that they had for it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, later on they could have had different unlock packs and stuff, but no.
[SPEAKER_01]: Instead, they're going to just release another retail version of the game six months later because, you know what?
[SPEAKER_01]: You can make money off of it a lot more than you would those download packs.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, I mean, this is what they did with Karaoke Revolution.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hear you and I don't because I feel like Guitar Hero 2 kind of did the same thing with the first Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_03]: They did.
[SPEAKER_01]: They did.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, and they did it with the Rock the 80s thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, they were just trying to make more money on the side.
[SPEAKER_01]: And, yeah, they haven't innovated either, but that's the thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's why Guitar Hero 3 is very encouraging to me so far because I see, like, this online thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I see, like, okay, this really feels like a step up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe Konami needs to take a page out of what's going on here, hand it off to some other developers.
[SPEAKER_03]: But see, that's the thing, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like...
[SPEAKER_01]: I can get excited about their arcade releases because that's some cool stuff that they're doing there.
[SPEAKER_01]: But when their home releases come out, nowadays I don't give a shit.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's like, ooh, another DDR game.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's really cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: But who cares?
[SPEAKER_01]: It's not like something I'm running out to the store and going to buy.
[SPEAKER_01]: I used to because it was really exciting to see all these new songs and stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: But
[SPEAKER_01]: Now it's just so watered down, they just don't care anymore, it seems like.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's like, whatever, you know, it's DDR.
[SPEAKER_01]: People will buy it because you'll exercise to it and stuff, and that's the crowd that they're going after.
[SPEAKER_01]: They don't care about the people that like the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tonight's show is very interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is a throwback to our old days.
[SPEAKER_03]: For those that may not know, check us out the first time.
[SPEAKER_03]: The first three years of our show or so, we were all about strictly...
[SPEAKER_03]: Music-based games and talking about the DDR community and tournaments and then other things going on.
[SPEAKER_03]: So very interesting tonight that we have all this music gaming news.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's been a real throwback to our heyday.
[SPEAKER_03]: So if we sound really passionate about these issues, it's because we are.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, myself, DarkSakura, you know how we met?
[SPEAKER_03]: Golf Land, DDR.
[SPEAKER_03]: Road trips to Miggle in the Bay to play Beatmania 2DX.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is how we should.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like a throwback road tour.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to make it a regular thing again.
[SPEAKER_03]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the core part of any DDR game.
[SPEAKER_03]: If it has a shitty song list, you're not going to want to play it.
[SPEAKER_03]: So make what you will of this song list for DDR Universe 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not going to read the whole thing, but let me tell you some of the licenses.
[SPEAKER_03]: Take Me Out by Franz Ferdinand, The Way You Move by Outkast, Walk Like an Egyptian by The Bangles, Rocket by Herbie Hancock, Safety Dance with Men Without Hats, He's the Greatest Dancer by Sister Sledge.
[SPEAKER_03]: We've got a lot of throwback songs in this one.
[SPEAKER_03]: And let's see, Fire by Ferry Corsten,
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm trying to see what else is here on that list.
[SPEAKER_03]: We also have some pretty cool Konami remixes because we have a new Contra medley mix by Niko Jira.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's going to be in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: So pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, Jelly Kiss is going to be downloadable, it looks like.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have also announced some of the songs that are going to be in the first download pack, and I hope this isn't pay to unlock.
[SPEAKER_03]: We don't know yet.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, I bet you it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: I bet you it is, too, because that's why we already have the songs for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Mutant Storm Empire on Xbox 360, Tony Hawk's Proving Ground on the 31st, Need for Speed Pro Street for the mobile phone, Avatar the Burning Earth on Xbox 360,
[SPEAKER_05]: Bladestorm, The Hundred Years War, FIFA Manager 08, Hellgate London, Naruto, Rise of the Ninja, and Naruto Ultimate Ninja Heroes, NASCAR 2008, Chase for the Cup, NBA 2K8, Sonic Rivals 2, Syphon Filter, Dark Mirror, Tabula Rasa on PC,
[SPEAKER_05]: The Simpsons Game, Tony Hawk's Proving Ground, Warriors of the Lost Empire, Sam & Max Episode 201, Ice Station, Santa, oh wait, I'm getting ahead of myself because that's on the 8th.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Santa.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_01]: In the U.S., there's quite a bit of stuff coming out, including the ever-controversial Manhunt 2, finally making its way out on PlayStation 2, PSP, and the Wii.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm sure we'll see a lot of that in the news probably in the next few weeks.
[SPEAKER_01]: Of course, today Guitar Hero 3 came out, so go pick that up.
[SPEAKER_01]: Other platforms, Disgaea, Afternoon of Darkness on PSP.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's see, we've also got Ben 10.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's coming out on quite a few platforms.
[SPEAKER_01]: PlayStation 2, PSP, Wii, and I believe the DS.
[SPEAKER_01]: Also, there's Cars Mater National, which is a sequel to the Cars game that came out last year, which sucked, by the way.
[SPEAKER_01]: That was another one of those launch racing games that, God knows, blew for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyways, let's see here.
[SPEAKER_01]: Also on the Wii, Battalion Wars 2.
[SPEAKER_01]: That one actually looks pretty good.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_01]: And let's see, the Simpsons game.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's going to be out on almost everything.
[SPEAKER_01]: PlayStation 2, PlayStation 3, 360, the Wii, and DS.
[SPEAKER_01]: Also on the PlayStation 3 this week, the ever-delayed Stranglehold.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's going to be coming out as well as the collector's edition.
[SPEAKER_01]: And let's see, on PC, we have Hellgate London.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's going to be coming out as well as The Witcher.
[SPEAKER_01]: And let's see, on DS, Barbie Island Princess.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_01]: That's also coming out on the Wii, I believe, and PS2.
[SPEAKER_03]: What exactly does Barbie do in Island Princess?
[SPEAKER_01]: It's based off some DVD that came out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Does she vote off her friends off the island one at a time?
[SPEAKER_03]: And who is the prettiest supremacy?
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: What else is coming out?
[SPEAKER_01]: Assault Heroes.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's also coming out on PC.
[SPEAKER_01]: Remember that was an Xbox Live Arcade title as well.
[SPEAKER_01]: Same with that Battlestar Galactica game.
[SPEAKER_01]: PC, Naruto, Rise of a Ninja, Viva Piñata Party Animals
[SPEAKER_01]: on the Xbox 360 woohoo and then Virtua Fighter 5 that's also coming out oh and Time Shipped on Xbox 360 as well chat comments GS68 says it's a fucking Barbie game skip Frisbee says the tribe has spoken Ken pack your bags oh and Ratatouille Food Frenzy on DS which is a rip off of Cooking Mama that may not necessarily be a bad thing because now you're mixing Cooking Mama with Disney Pixar franchises that could be okay
[SPEAKER_05]: Pixar can do no wrong.
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: In the video game realm, they've licensed their stuff out questionably before.
[SPEAKER_05]: But Pixar didn't do it.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pixar themselves can do no wrong.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's THQ that released it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, THQ can do some wrong.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hopefully they won't.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll have faith.
[SPEAKER_03]: XBOX 360
[SPEAKER_03]: Going to some other platforms on the Nintendo Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: Opuna is coming out in Japan on the 1st of November as well as Super Mario Galaxy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Opuna looked weird.
[SPEAKER_01]: Wasn't that that one where you control the entire game with like the nunchuck?
[SPEAKER_03]: I believe that is the game, yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll pull up more information.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll come back to that in a moment.
[SPEAKER_03]: And read some other release dates, such as the PlayStation 3 is getting G.I.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jockey 4 2007.
[SPEAKER_03]: We know that here is winning post 7.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Railfan, Taiwan High Speed Rail.
[SPEAKER_03]: Go Train Sims.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess, yeah, there you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: High Speed Train Sims.
[SPEAKER_03]: Go to TurboSpeed.
[SPEAKER_03]: On the PlayStation 2, MotoGP07, another port of G.I.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jockey 4, and Super Robot Taisen Scramble Commander II.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just what we need, more Robot Taisen.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're making an anime series now, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: I played one of the Robot Taisen games that had the Eva...
[SPEAKER_05]: Units in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, I forgot to mention a couple also in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_01]: Disney's High School Musical, the game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's give that for Shane.
[SPEAKER_01]: High School Musical Sing It on PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what I bought Shane for his birthday?
[SPEAKER_01]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: Just going on a total tangent here.
[SPEAKER_03]: I bought him tickets to see High School Musical on ice here in Sacramento, and then he moved to Kansas.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll go with you.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: He has to send me the tickets because it's this weekend.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, dude, tell him this in the back.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I think he stole his tickets.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tell them to FedEx it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll go with you.
[SPEAKER_03]: FedEx me your birthday present because Jamie and I are going.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll go.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll totally go.
[SPEAKER_03]: You really want to go see a high school musical on ice?
[SPEAKER_05]: I just want to go do something.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just going to... I've never been to see anything on ice.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know this is going to sound really wrong, but it just sounds so gay.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to go.
[SPEAKER_01]: I petition that they have Manhunt 2 on ice because that would be something I would like to see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Blood bounces.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't even think I could get my boyfriend to go see a high school musical on ice with me.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's how gay it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: My mom used to be an amateur roller skater and did figure roller skating.
[SPEAKER_01]: Roller skating is fine.
[SPEAKER_01]: I still don't like the figure skating part.
[SPEAKER_01]: Roller derby is cool, though.
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, it's kind of lame.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have a roller derby team in Sacramento that they wanted me to audition for.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: I could punch people.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'd be good at it.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what, though?
[SPEAKER_05]: You totally reminded me of something I didn't mention in my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: We have Ace Combat 6 with a controller.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, how's that going?
[SPEAKER_05]: I get totally motion sick on it, but it's really cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: The controller's really nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know how they could get more people to go to E4ALL next year?
[SPEAKER_03]: Put it on ice.
[SPEAKER_03]: E4ALL on ice.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've never been ice skating, Rob.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've never been ice skating.
[SPEAKER_03]: Although I hear E4ALL might get put on ice anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: You've never been ice skating at all?
[SPEAKER_05]: Never.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're going to go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have to for this Christmas.
[SPEAKER_03]: When my leg gets better, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: We can't do it this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: But when my leg gets better, we'll go ice skating for sure.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just in time for the holidays.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I've been water skiing.
[SPEAKER_01]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_01]: Skating sucks.
[SPEAKER_01]: I hate it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've tried it.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: But it's lame.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm really good at roller skating though.
[SPEAKER_05]: I used to be able to do all kinds of stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Gerardimo says roller skating on ice.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Tigerclaw says DDR on ice.
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do not want.
[SPEAKER_03]: GS68 says Mario Kart on ice.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh wait.
[SPEAKER_03]: They actually have those stages.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: I've never been kart racing out here.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've got a membership there.
[SPEAKER_05]: The last time I did anything on a go-kart was Autopia at Disneyland, my first time going.
[SPEAKER_01]: Really?
[SPEAKER_05]: And I haven't done Autopia since.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: And before that, it was at the Miracle Strip in Panama City, Florida, which they tore down the Miracle Strip.
[SPEAKER_03]: I never go on Autopia.
[SPEAKER_03]: Isn't it on a track?
[SPEAKER_05]: Isn't it on a... Yeah, it is, but they had this thing that was called like...
[SPEAKER_05]: It was another car type thing, but you could actually drive these little cars.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you had a set path that they went on, but they weren't on a track.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you could actually run into people.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was great.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry, internets.
[SPEAKER_03]: We were talking about Japanese release dates, and suddenly we got into RPM motor racing and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's why they listened to us.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the chat room is still going into crap on ice.
[SPEAKER_03]: Great.
[SPEAKER_03]: Violent fight on ice.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ranma says Pokemon on ice.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dude, I think they have that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think they've done that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think they've done that, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did you see that picture on... I'm never going to get these dates on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did you see that picture on Dig this week?
[SPEAKER_03]: The whole thing with... It was the picture of Pikachu and it looked like he had a vagine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, somebody in the chat room, please dig up that picture, because Loki and DarkSakura are giving me blank stares right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: I need to show them the Pikachu picture that was on Dig earlier this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was so funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did he have, like, camel toe?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, but it was like a giant, like, blow-up Pikachu, like at an amusement park.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've seen that one.
[SPEAKER_03]: And all these kids were going in, but it looked like... They were going in his crotch.
[SPEAKER_03]: They were going in a big Pikagina.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was great.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I think you put that on your... Do not want...
[SPEAKER_05]: Trauma Center on Icewind.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: I need to finish the Japanese release dates.
[SPEAKER_03]: I apologize.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would help, Rob.
[SPEAKER_03]: On the Nintendo DS this week in Japan, Dragon Tamer, Sound Spirits.
[SPEAKER_03]: How in the hell am I supposed to pronounce this this week?
[SPEAKER_03]: Zaiden Hojen Nippon Kanji Noriyuku Kenti Kyokai Koshiki Soft 250 Manin no Kanken.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: Just movies.
[SPEAKER_03]: No games this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: But if you want to pick up Gremlins, it's out this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Gremlins is the best movie ever.
[SPEAKER_03]: I suggest you do.
[SPEAKER_01]: I forgot something I played this week.
[SPEAKER_01]: And this is worth mentioning.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sorry to derail the whole show here, but I downloaded a CDI emulator.
[SPEAKER_01]: What?
[SPEAKER_01]: And they have a ROM online for Super Mario Wacky Worlds.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was an unreleased game that is awful.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was so horrible.
[SPEAKER_01]: and I played it for about 5 minutes here's the picture Loki oh that's pretty bad oh my god oh my god it was so horrible basically they just ripped the sprites and music out of Super Mario World and just took a dump on it and that's basically what it was horrible SSJ100Matt asks worse than Hotel Mario?
[SPEAKER_03]: well maybe not GS68 says you're just pissing in an ocean of piss I know
[SPEAKER_03]: They did have all the Zelda games on there too, if you want to play them.
[SPEAKER_03]: I swear to God we'll move on with the show just after I say that Opuna does look to be that game I think you were thinking about.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, wait, no, it's a role-playing game.
[SPEAKER_01]: It is a role-playing game.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it looks cute.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hope they release that over here.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's by Koei, and there's the little box art.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what Koei gave us, Rob?
[SPEAKER_05]: They gave us that game with the girl riding a missile.
[SPEAKER_05]: KO Flying Squadron.
[SPEAKER_03]: I could say something about girls riding missiles, but I won't.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know, that was the best game ever.
[SPEAKER_03]: In light of moving on with our program.
[SPEAKER_05]: Forza 2 downloadable content has a price cut because people bitched about it enough.
[SPEAKER_05]: So the Twin Ring Motegi track is going to be decreased from 600 points to 400 points because you're paying too much.
[SPEAKER_01]: Funny, because when we complained about the Guitar Hero download content,
[SPEAKER_01]: They didn't seem to care.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like, we're selling plenty of it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_01]: So an interesting rumor has come out this week.
[SPEAKER_01]: Apparently someone who had gotten their 360 returned back from Microsoft after being repaired noticed that there was a few additional options in their dashboard, including stuff for the 360's IPTV feature that was announced earlier.
[SPEAKER_01]: I want to say Tokyo Game Sh... Not Tokyo Game Show, um...
[SPEAKER_01]: Consumer Electronics Show, I think, this year.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's either that or Game Developers Conference.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, one of those shows earlier this year.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was announced.
[SPEAKER_01]: Good reporting, Loki.
[SPEAKER_01]: Excellent reporting.
[SPEAKER_01]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, anyways.
[SPEAKER_01]: So apparently it's going to have different features, including being able to pause and record stuff being streamed off there.
[SPEAKER_01]: Of course, none of these features really worked on it, but it's interesting to see that that's actually...
[SPEAKER_01]: in his dashboard now, so most likely going to be included in the fall update.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, what I want to know is how the hell did that happen in the first place?
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, how did some guy get this random update?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, because I guess if he shipped his Xbox back, did they just send him a new Xbox that were meant to be held off until the update goes live or whatever?
[SPEAKER_01]: Maybe, because it doesn't look like it's the entire update.
[SPEAKER_01]: Maybe, like, they had an updated firmware or something like that that's
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know when exactly the fall update is rolling out.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's probably within the next few weeks.
[SPEAKER_01]: So they're just probably getting it ready to go.
[SPEAKER_03]: What I would be curious of is that in light of this news, I wonder if other people that are getting their consoles back from Microsoft are going to find the same thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: One of my LiveJournal friends just had to send back their Xbox for Red Rings of Death, so I wonder if his is going to come back with that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: I can't wait to have the IPTV stuff because...
[SPEAKER_01]: Shit, more shows to watch.
[SPEAKER_01]: Although I'm not too familiar with Microsoft's IPTV service, so... I haven't been able to stay on... I'm actually very unhappy that my place that I usually watch TV online is going away.
[SPEAKER_05]: Aww.
[SPEAKER_05]: TVlinks.co.uk They got shut down?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, they're on their way.
[SPEAKER_03]: They went the way of Oink, which was another big, huge news story this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_05]: How else am I going to watch bullshit?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: MiniNova or something?
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, going back to the Xbox Live Marketplace and other Xbox news, Blue Dragon, which is a game I need to go back and finish, has some new content.
[SPEAKER_03]: Apparently there is a new...
[SPEAKER_03]: 6 Treasure Pack for Blue Dragon.
[SPEAKER_03]: You have to pay 200 points for it, but you get some new items that will allow you to boost abilities.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it sounds like this is some pay to unlock content for me, because you're going to get a Whimsical Mind, which randomly enhances...
[SPEAKER_03]: The Way of Thieves The DV Phonograph
[SPEAKER_03]: The Nothing Glasses.
[SPEAKER_03]: It visualizes all those points, because you can search everywhere in this game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It will allow you to actually see the points that you can search with little star symbols, instead of just going around aimlessly.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Shuffled Helmet, that will adjust magical and speed parameters.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the Spring Wind Scarf, which will adjust HP and speed parameters by 20%.
[SPEAKER_03]: So basically, you're going to pay 200 points to make the game a lot easier, it sounds like to me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which is...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, I just want to mention real quick, Spider-Man 3 has a new unlock as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: You get to download New Goblin, and this is notable because it was a PlayStation 3 exclusive feature, but now for 240 Microsoft points, you can have it on 360.
[SPEAKER_01]: Which I heard, by the way, is lame.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wouldn't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I try to avoid games based off of movies unless they're really good, which I can't even think of any off the top of my head.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know why you would still have Spider-Man 3 anyways, because I think that game really sucked, and so...
[SPEAKER_01]: It's probably not worth anything right now anyways.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, for our friends in Japan, the Xbox 360 is getting a price cut.
[SPEAKER_05]: Finally.
[SPEAKER_05]: We knew it would eventually happen.
[SPEAKER_05]: The price cut is going to happen on November 1st, and it should be the equivalent of $243.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow, that's a big cut.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: And this would be also why all those games I read earlier are getting a cut as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sure this all ties in.
[SPEAKER_03]: Make the Xbox 360 a little more cheap and maybe it can get a little steam in Japan.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know there's a few 360 games that are going to be dropping in price.
[SPEAKER_01]: I can't remember which ones.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I also know that there's some being discontinued.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like Perfect Dark Zero is one of them.
[SPEAKER_01]: I remember.
[SPEAKER_01]: Good riddance, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_01]: Make way for Perfect Dark Zero 2 now.
[SPEAKER_01]: Please no.
[SPEAKER_01]: Where you still can't jump.
[SPEAKER_01]: I fucking hate that.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's the thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: Next-gen system, no jumping.
[SPEAKER_01]: But one game you can jump quite far in, actually, is Burnout Paradise, which is going to be coming to the U.S.
[SPEAKER_01]: in January, on the 22nd.
[SPEAKER_01]: And that is going to feature an open-world environment, which is going to be kind of interesting, because I know none of the other games have been like that.
[SPEAKER_01]: But you can basically drive around aimlessly, really fast, smash into stuff, jump through the air, explode, all the fun stuff that you would be looking for in a Burnout game.
[SPEAKER_01]: And...
[SPEAKER_01]: So it seems that publishers are starting to get a little smart in releasing stuff in these slow months like January and February and the entire summer instead of just March and November and October.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm liking this whole trend lately where it seems like game companies are learning there's 12 months in a year.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's kind of exciting.
[SPEAKER_01]: They need to seriously do that because...
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_03]: That caters to a crowd that's going to probably go out and pick up a game whenever they damn well feel like it.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I don't think they're going to take a loss by releasing this in January.
[SPEAKER_01]: But it's good, though, that it's coming out in January and not, like, say, you know, November when there's a ton of shit coming out.
[SPEAKER_01]: In, like, January, I mean, January's actually looking pretty good game-wise so far.
[SPEAKER_01]: They have NFL Tour, Devil May Cry 4, God knows what else, and then as well as, you know, this now.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, if they put in a month that there's really nothing coming out, people are going to buy that game instead of saying, well, I'm going to buy this one instead and save my money and then later on they may just decide not to pick it up.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, some other games that you might be able to play through the Christmas season.
[SPEAKER_03]: And speaking of games that are geared at little kids, although I bet some big kids would like this too.
[SPEAKER_03]: THQ has announced they are bringing four new games to Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_03]: And some of these are very notable because they tie into Nickelodeon licenses.
[SPEAKER_03]: SpongeBob SquarePants Underpants Slam is coming out on Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I have to admit...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: It does kind of open up Xbox Live Arcade to being, you know, a lot of times Microsoft takes some shit for not being very kid-friendly.
[SPEAKER_03]: And certainly, you know Microsoft's going to be pushing this, especially with their new Xbox 360 Arcade console, really pushing the family thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: When Scenic comes out and all that.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's part of their marketing.
[SPEAKER_01]: They have a whole family marketing plan that includes that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Scenic, DDR Universe, actually Guitar Hero 3, and then these titles as well, Viva Pinata Party, and then of course the Xbox Live Arcade stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: and I know they did some other announcements about cartoons and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: By the way, the other games that THQ is going to be releasing, a game called Screwjumper, Elements of Destruction, and Rocket Riot.
[SPEAKER_03]: Spongebob and Screwjumper, that's kind of an odd name, but they are both scheduled for release next month.
[SPEAKER_03]: So they'll be here in time for Christmas.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what the world needs less of?
[SPEAKER_05]: Spongebob.
[SPEAKER_01]: Elements of Destruction I know is coming out in the DS next year as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Screwjumper, if you want to know what the hell that is, it's a vertical action racing game.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's per an interview from the developers.
[SPEAKER_03]: You have to destroy alien mining equipment and architecture while plummeting downward in a continual rapid freefall descent.
[SPEAKER_03]: The objective of the game is to maximize score by crashing into and dynamiting as many alien structures as possible on the way down the mineshaft, then to initiate a detonation and race back to safety on the planet's surface.
[SPEAKER_03]: So honestly, this sounds like it might not be bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's got aliens, it's got explosions, it's fast, it's racing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Screwjumper might be pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll see, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: But sometimes games that seem awesome in theory really suck.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we have to hold out until the demo's out this November.
[SPEAKER_01]: Down with Pants
[SPEAKER_03]: I like watching real stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: I miss all the stuff from when I was a kid.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because they expected kids to have, you know, follow the story.
[SPEAKER_03]: Imagination?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, imagination.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what Muppet Babies was all about.
[SPEAKER_03]: Muppet Babies is great.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tell me that cartoon wasn't the shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what that was all about.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll tell you though, I've had a revival of lately.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki wants to make a joke.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did you see Drawn Together Babies?
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: God, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't.
[SPEAKER_03]: Drawn Together wasn't funny last season, so I haven't been watching it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've been having a revival of Count Duckula.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Danger Mouse.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I tried going back watching Banana Man, and my God, that was horrible.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't believe I liked Banana Man when I was 12.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you like Banana Man?
[SPEAKER_05]: I used to like Banana Man.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very, very weird little British tune.
[SPEAKER_05]: Next story, please.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, Xbox 360 crap.
[SPEAKER_05]: How about that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Toshiba is saying no comment, except they didn't actually say comment, they just said no.
[SPEAKER_05]: about the Xbox 360 HD DVD rumor.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, because... No, would you like to comment on the internal Xbox 360 HD DVD drive?
[SPEAKER_01]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: Toshiba said no to the new Xbox 360 DVD HD DVD rumor.
[SPEAKER_05]: But we pretty much all still think it's a rumor, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know why this is newsworthy?
[SPEAKER_03]: We don't believe them!
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, you know why this is newsworthy?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because you know what they say about Microsoft rumors.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_01]: One game I'm actually kind of excited to see coming to Xbox Live Arcade this week is going to be Mutant Storm Empire.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I love the Mutant Storm Reloaded game when it came out, still one of my favorite shooter games.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was a little bit overlooked because it was too similar to Geometry Wars, I think, and it's slower paced.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, this one though looks really cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: They have it set up a little bit different.
[SPEAKER_01]: Some of the changes you'll see from Reloaded is that the stages now, you actually kind of, it's one long stage.
[SPEAKER_01]: Doors open up and
[SPEAKER_01]: DeLilla, DeLilla That would have been more entertaining
[SPEAKER_01]: It's going to be coming out for 800 points.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's due out this Wednesday, October 31st.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's going to be awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, and online co-op it's going to have as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hope since it's Halloween we're going to get some cheesy Halloween tie-in on the Xbox Live Marketplace.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yaris 2!
[SPEAKER_02]: Because it's scary.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's pretty scary.
[SPEAKER_02]: This time, not only does it have tentacles, but it has mech destroyer legs that the car runs on.
[SPEAKER_01]: The game will just evolve into something that's not even Yaris.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's just like, whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think for the next year, we should make every effort to make a Yaris joke every week on the program.
[SPEAKER_01]: Didn't that game remind you of the programmers of that After Dark screensaver decided to make a game and this is what it was?
[SPEAKER_05]: Guess what Jamie never played?
[SPEAKER_01]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yaris.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, it's probably a good thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: Consider yourself one of the lucky ones.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's free.
[SPEAKER_01]: Download me!
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm free!
[SPEAKER_01]: I know it's tempting.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's a free game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey, if it sucks, whatever.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's free.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, it's not worth it.
[SPEAKER_05]: You pay in the time of your life that you spent.
[SPEAKER_05]: You will never get back.
[SPEAKER_01]: You lose part of your soul after playing that game.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't got much left.
[SPEAKER_03]: In fact, I would like to actually open up our mailbag.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would like to actually solicit... No, because I have to read that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, too bad.
Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: We've got to make you work a little harder.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I would like to solicit your best Yaris joke.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I want to hear some Yaris.
[SPEAKER_03]: It can be about the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hell, it can be about the car.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was going to get one.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want some Yaris jokes in the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not tonight because we haven't gotten to the mailbag segment.
[SPEAKER_03]: We will.
[SPEAKER_03]: But for next week's show, as you guys are listening to the podcast later, I want some Yaris jokes.
[SPEAKER_01]: Honestly, though, how is this good advertising for the Yaris?
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, now when you associate Yaris, you're going to think suck.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, that's not –
[SPEAKER_01]: I wouldn't think that's a good thing that, you know, Yaris, oh yeah, that's right, that's that, you know, car that had a crappy game made for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or when I go shopping, and I like to see all the features of the Yaris, and I'm like, oh yes, well it has the built-in air conditioning and the GPS unit and the, you know, the leather interior.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'd be like, yes, but where is the tentacle gun?
[SPEAKER_01]: Where's the giant death tentacle?
[SPEAKER_01]: That the commercials and...
[SPEAKER_01]: Where the fuck did that come out from?
[SPEAKER_01]: The stupid tentacle thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is weird.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: We need to move on with the news.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can we please?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, we may.
[SPEAKER_05]: Please, please, please, please.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, yes, yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: News about Spore, which I'm very excited about Spore.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, we've always heard these things.
[SPEAKER_03]: Spore is...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe late spring is when you're going to see this game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would say it's probably going to be out somewhere next year.
[SPEAKER_01]: If it came out in April, that would be perfect.
[SPEAKER_01]: April is the crappiest game for months, or game for the year.
[SPEAKER_01]: Basically the worst month for games.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's horrible.
[SPEAKER_03]: It would definitely be a highlight in a low month.
[SPEAKER_03]: Speaking of highlights, we love to read the emails from our listeners every week, don't we, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, we do.
[SPEAKER_03]: I had a gun to her head forcing her to say that.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's, um, six...
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow, well let's get started.
[SPEAKER_03]: Long segment tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: This one comes from AceSavior, I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's an X instead of an S for Savior.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey guys, first I will admit that I am pretty new to the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just found the show when I was looking for RSS feeds and podcasts on my PSP a couple days ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like the fact that you guys have a website made just for the PSP.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sorry that I haven't updated it in years.
[SPEAKER_01]: Too bad it never gets updated.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey!
[SPEAKER_01]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was going to do OLRE and I kind of, I did not re-register the... Our main website's all kind of broken too, so anyway, whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: I really appreciate it seeing as how my PSP is the closest thing I can get to a laptop at the moment.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, even after only a few podcasts, I can honestly say this is the best video game internet radio show ever and I'm looking forward to more podcasts to come.
[SPEAKER_05]: Keep on gaming, guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then he said I was hot.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just something that happens to women when they get married.
[SPEAKER_05]: They lose their heart.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, stop it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know DarkSakura's very shy, but you should see her outfit today.
[SPEAKER_03]: She's very nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm wearing my pirate shirt that I got at Walmart.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's cute.
[SPEAKER_03]: With the skirt.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like the skirt.
[SPEAKER_05]: They sell the same shirt at Disneyland, and it's a bright red.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they charge $30 for it at Disneyland, and I paid $12 at Walmart.
[SPEAKER_03]: But what you're wearing today is dark.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's renaissance-y without being over the top.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's renaissance-y but modern.
[SPEAKER_05]: I feel kind of like a rockabilly.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which actually ties into future news.
[SPEAKER_05]: Super Arizona.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ooh, next email.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, this one comes from Polinosis.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's kind of a cool name.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was reading this fascinating article the other day and I was wondering what you guys think of this man's opinion.
[SPEAKER_05]: And he also included a joke.
[SPEAKER_05]: It says, why is the bicycle lying on its side?
[SPEAKER_03]: Why?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because it was too tired?
[SPEAKER_05]: Why?
[SPEAKER_05]: Cricket, cricket, cricket, cricket.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, um... Did I accidentally invite jokes from the listeners last week?
[SPEAKER_03]: I must have.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good effort.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, um... You know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: This article is kind of long, so instead what I'm going to do is I'm going to link it in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's the topic?
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to know if I read it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's about how reviews are phrased, I do believe so.
[SPEAKER_03]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, um...
[SPEAKER_05]: saying, consider the following sentences.
[SPEAKER_05]: This book has good book read.
[SPEAKER_05]: This record has good record listen.
[SPEAKER_05]: This movie has good movie watch.
[SPEAKER_03]: This game has good gameplay, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: I do sort of understand that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like you could say, it plays well.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know.
[SPEAKER_05]: But... Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I kind of, in my...
[SPEAKER_05]: Attention to semantics, I guess that I do sort of agree with that.
[SPEAKER_03]: But we'll read it more and maybe respond to it next week.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're going to take that as a homework assignment.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm posting it in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll take a look at it real quick.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ooh, Pirate Bay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, moving forward.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have one from Mark F. Says, Hi, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_05]: And my name is spelled the other way, by the way, but that's okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: You've been playing a lot of Ragnarok Online.
[SPEAKER_05]: I haven't confirmed, but I think RO2 Beta is out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have you been playing that or the original RO?
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, since you're an MMO girl, have you played World of Warcraft or Guild Wars?
[SPEAKER_05]: Keep up the great work.
[SPEAKER_05]: You guys are very entertaining.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hope you bring back your extra guests from time to time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I know that the RO2 Beta was out in Korea, and I tried to sign up for it, but they needed me to sign up for a social security number or some shit, so I didn't do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: However, it has been brought to my attention that VR2 Beta is now out in the United States and if my laptop is up to the task, I will be downloading that like a mofo and playing it like crazy because I love Ragnarok.
[SPEAKER_05]: Especially since it's a beta, it'd have to be free.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_01]: Keep going.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, to answer your question, yes, I played World of Warcraft and I have stopped playing for World of Warcraft because number one, it's on my other computer and number two, honestly, I didn't think it was that fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: AllTrackValley
[SPEAKER_05]: Going through this whole thing with NC... The people at NCSoft are great.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're just really on the ball.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they've been able to replace my confirmation code, so I will be hopefully sometime in the next week getting back on Guild Wars.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have a character that looks like the Doctor.
[SPEAKER_05]: His name is John Smith.
[SPEAKER_05]: I also have another character that was supposed to be in my friend's guild, and she left the guild, so...
[SPEAKER_05]: I have no idea what the hell is happening, so.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll be on.
[SPEAKER_05]: You'll see me.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I also was thinking about getting into City of Heroes, but honestly, when do I have the time?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeehaw.
[SPEAKER_05]: I played Rose online too.
[SPEAKER_03]: One of my new friends who I met through William, I believe is going to come on our show next week.
[SPEAKER_03]: And he's really into City of Heroes.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the reason why I'm having him on next week is he was in the Tabula Rasa beta, which is a game I'm pretty excited about.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to know more about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: He was telling me about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It sounds really awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's going to show me the game this week to see if it's something I want to get into.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we'll have him on next week probably and talking about some of the PC games we sometimes overlook.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I have another email from the same person.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here are some of my comments for episode 252.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love the 3D Street Fighter games.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was different playing style that made the Street Fighter characters almost real because of the limitations.
[SPEAKER_05]: I got tired of them jumping 9 feet in the air and spinning around like tornadoes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, you're alone in that one, buddy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, at least he's not bringing up the...
[SPEAKER_05]: PC games are probably getting more love because of better laptop sales and external USB D-pads controllers.
[SPEAKER_05]: Keep up the great work.
[SPEAKER_05]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: I liked the later EX games, honestly.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was the first one that was kind of, well, bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, hey.
[SPEAKER_05]: This one is from Spamouflage.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just think that's a cool name.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bonsoir, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, that's French.
[SPEAKER_05]: So here's my statement of the week, and I'd love to get your opinion since I consider you as experts.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've heard that Nintendo is selling lots of Wii systems but no games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really?
[SPEAKER_05]: What if occasional gamers turn out to be cheap bastards who don't buy games?
[SPEAKER_05]: Three questions.
[SPEAKER_05]: One, is my statement true?
[SPEAKER_05]: Two, are Wii games not selling?
[SPEAKER_05]: Three, where do you go to get the latest game sale figures?
[SPEAKER_05]: I know I could just Google it, but I like hearing DarkSakura read my emails.
[SPEAKER_05]: Merci, spam a flash.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um... I... You know that you can find a lot of the sales types through Consumer Reports, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um...
[SPEAKER_05]: Some of the, a lot of the just new sites like Kotaku, what are the other ones?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, like Joystick and Destructoid are the big three probably.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, they'll list game sales figures quarterly when they do the quarterly reports.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then I also, for a lot of my UK news, I get from Eurogamer.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, where do you get your sales figures?
[SPEAKER_03]: Is that coming from a way of your internal sources at your day job or?
[SPEAKER_03]: MPD.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: When you talk about sales numbers on the show, is that numbers you're getting from your work?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, it's from MPD Group.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: Plenty of Wii games are selling, trust me.
[SPEAKER_01]: Maybe not all of the Wii games that they want.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like, I know Donkey Kong Barrel Blast didn't sell hotcakes, or maybe... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I imagine a lot of those Wii games, just based on what's out there, they're selling to kids and families.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're not necessarily selling to hardcore gaming audience, which is probably why...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_01]: Also, there's a lot of games that are crappy ports and stuff, or just crappy control and whatever, and a lot of people get jaded by that.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's like, well, shit, I don't know if I want to go spend $50 just to get a game that's going to suck, so maybe Wii buyers are a little more cautious.
[SPEAKER_03]: Unfortunately, all the A-list titles on the Wii right now, too, are coming from Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't think of a third-party A or AAA title on its way soon.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sure Chad will think of something, but I can't even think of anything.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, Manhunt 2, there's stuff from Capcom, Resident Evil, Umbrella Chronicles, Brothers in Arms.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, I'll give you Umbrella Chronicles.
[SPEAKER_01]: Medal of Honor Heroes 2, it's going to be big.
[SPEAKER_01]: Dragon Ball Z, Budokai Tenkaichi 3 from Atari.
[SPEAKER_01]: I personally am not really interested.
[SPEAKER_01]: Madden 08.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, there you go.
[SPEAKER_01]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, Nights, says Gerardimo.
[SPEAKER_01]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_01]: Nights.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, there you go.
[SPEAKER_01]: To be honest, though, you may like Nights, but Nights I don't think is going to be that big of a game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_05]: I am excited about Nights.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's going to be fantastically huge.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would totally believe though there's a lot of people just buying the Wii for Wii Sports and that's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a lot of families I bet are doing it and totally fine with Wii Sports.
[SPEAKER_01]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_01]: There are some companies that are getting smart about the games that are released and a lot of them are pretty budget games like this AMF Bowling Pinbusters from Bethesda I think.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think it's Bethesda.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm not sure.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's coming out for $19.
[SPEAKER_01]: And you know it's a
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: I love Christmas nights.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway... I love Christmas because I get presents.
[SPEAKER_05]: My favorite holiday, though, is coming up in three days.
[SPEAKER_03]: Halloween.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is Halloween.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a religious holiday for me.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's true.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a religious holiday.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, it's the end of the year.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, moving forward.
[SPEAKER_05]: This one comes from Robert M. Two stupid things here.
[SPEAKER_05]: This email... No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just teasing.
[SPEAKER_05]: First of all, I'd like to, although I have participated in the fun myself, suggest that we, after the whole Eye of Judgment bet is finished, drop the whole Loki is Tingle thing and try something fresh, such as Loki as Maria the Hippo from Sly Cooper.
[SPEAKER_05]: No idea why, just random.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't even know who the hell that is.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, I know of the game, I just don't know who that character is.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, I want to agree with this statement that maybe after the bet is lost, because we all know it will be, that thing ain't selling a million units, that maybe we ought to drop the whole Loki is Tingle thing, but I don't know, there's a part of me that says,
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just never going to go away.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like the whole Death Cake.
[SPEAKER_01]: Just because I did the voice one time, and I don't even remember how the voice was.
[SPEAKER_03]: Seriously, how many years ago did Loki play Karaoke Revolution live on air?
[SPEAKER_03]: It has scared him from doing karaoke permanently for the rest of his life.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, that's the effect this show has.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, it's just that we tried to duplicate the funny of it, and it's just you can't.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, second time's never as good as the first.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just like if Loki does actually have to dress up as Tingle for whatever reason, it will only happen once.
[SPEAKER_03]: Only then will we drop it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because we know now that if he does it again, it's just going to be some weirdo in a suit.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that it's more fun to speculate.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, what was that story written by... Oh God, now I can't think of the guy who wrote The Great Gatsby.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fitzgerald, was that his name?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: about the girl who said she was going to cut her hair.
[SPEAKER_05]: She's going to cut her hair.
[SPEAKER_05]: She's suddenly this popular and everyone loves her.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then when she does cut her hair, everyone's like, oh.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then she leaves.
[SPEAKER_03]: But seriously, he's going to set Eye of Judgment on fire.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's going to be awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: That'll be fantastic.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just made a classic literature reference.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will fucking dance around and set an Eye of Judgment on fire.
[SPEAKER_03]: I won't wear a suit.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: So to continue with this email.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Night of Tangents
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't care whether you don't like music games or whether you simply think a portable guitar game simply wouldn't work compared to having the actual instrument hardware.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can only think of two games right now that he could be talking about, and to suggest that Nintendo flat-out abandoned over 20 years of first-party development, that's arguably the only reason the company still has support.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because a different game developer on a completely different continent is publishing a game that he doesn't care for on their system seems dangerously ignorant and selfish to me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just venting, I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, you need to fire your friend.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that you should point this out to your friend and go, now how do you feel?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, here it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I don't think you should fire your friend.
[SPEAKER_03]: But your friend is misinformed on one huge thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: It sounds like your friend is assuming Nintendo makes all these decisions.
[SPEAKER_03]: They don't.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nintendo makes the system.
[SPEAKER_03]: Developers buy the kits to make games.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's up to them what games they want to make.
[SPEAKER_03]: So when they make all these Imagine Babies and whatever games they're making, that's not Nintendo going...
[SPEAKER_03]: Gosh, we really need someone to develop a baby sim for our system.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, they just kind of turn it loose out there, which in my mind is a good thing because a lot of great ideas come from these third-party developers.
[SPEAKER_03]: Unfortunately, a lot of shitty ideas and cheap knockoffs come from them as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the other problem is I would not call – I'm assuming the games he's referring to there are like Jam Sessions and the Hannah Montana game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would not call those knockoffs.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're different.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just because they all have music in common does not mean they're in common.
[SPEAKER_05]: Different is not necessarily bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, your friend, unfortunately, is a little bit misinformed.
[SPEAKER_05]: Your friend's a hater.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, I'm done.
[SPEAKER_03]: All done with emails?
[SPEAKER_03]: No more.
[SPEAKER_05]: I said there were six.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't count tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: How many have we done?
[SPEAKER_03]: Five?
[SPEAKER_03]: Six.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, we've done six?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then we're done.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mailbag at OrangeLaunchRadio.com
[SPEAKER_03]: The segment's pushing an hour 30, so let's wrap it up really quickly with a couple more stories.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyways, as most people in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_01]: know, there's a lot of fire going on in the L.A.
[SPEAKER_01]: area there.
[SPEAKER_01]: And now, of course, wildfires in the San Diego area have forced Midway to evacuate their San Diego office.
[SPEAKER_01]: But fear not, that will not delay Stranglehold any longer.
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, most of the development...
[SPEAKER_01]: It happens in other places.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think it's just their corporate office.
[SPEAKER_01]: Don't worry.
[SPEAKER_01]: Your strangleholds in Unreal Tournament won't be delayed any further.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, Unreal Tournament might, but strangleholds at least won't be.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's a real shame what happened there with those fires.
[SPEAKER_03]: Gosh, I hope none of our listeners... I imagine some of our listeners had to have been affected by it.
[SPEAKER_03]: They evacuated, what, like a million people?
[SPEAKER_03]: And...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: and Netflix is kind of trying to set their eyes on the future.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, Netflix has really kind of turned themselves into the current right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, hell, Ma and Pa Video Stores and even now Hollywood Video is really being impacted by, some would say, Netflix has been a huge part of this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, Netflix...
[SPEAKER_03]: has made an interesting comment.
[SPEAKER_03]: It came from the CEO, Reed Hastings.
[SPEAKER_03]: And he said he's interested in enabling Netflix through, quote, internet-connected game consoles.
[SPEAKER_03]: So very interesting that Netflix kind of wants to put their feelers out there on what they can do.
[SPEAKER_03]: The other thing that should be noted about this is that back in March, Hastings actually is now on the board of Microsoft, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: So you kind of go, hmm, could this mean that a Microsoft Netflix deal is in the cards?
[SPEAKER_03]: I hope so because I think the way the Xbox Live marketplace is set up now is not very friendly to movies and finding movies.
[SPEAKER_03]: However, Netflix on the other hand has an awesome system to find movies and has the whole friends thing and everything.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think Xbox Live is kind of clunky when it comes to their movie downloads.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I think a partnership could be a step up for them.
[SPEAKER_03]: But that's a little bit of fanboyism and dreaming there I think in a sense.
[SPEAKER_03]: That is a really big step because Microsoft kind of – they may think they don't need Netflix.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, I talk about this every week, and I probably sound like a broken record, but Sony's gonna have to step up really quick, or, you know, a few major announcements, and they're gonna be screwed.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, it's gonna, a lot of stuff is gonna happen too quick.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, Microsoft already has a pretty strong download service for movies and stuff, and if you add Netflix to that as well, where you can be able to pay a subscription per month and download as much shit as you want, um,
[SPEAKER_01]: That's kind of scary.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know Sony's talking about doing something as far as a download service, but they're kind of behind.
[SPEAKER_03]: But we don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just because it's on the board of Microsoft doesn't mean that maybe Netflix teams up with Sony.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that could be a huge boost for Sony, who seems to be finding the majority of their success right now as being a Blu-ray player.
[SPEAKER_03]: It would actually be really good for them.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll see if it happens.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's about time we bring this segment to a close because we've been here for a while now.
[SPEAKER_03]: But before we bring this segment to a close, we have to wrap up by paying a little respect to our elders.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we like to do that through DarkSakura's classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, DarkSakura, why don't you tell us what game you've picked for this week?
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'm actually curious because it's Halloween week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did you pick something a little Halloween themed for us?
[SPEAKER_05]: Sort of, but actually I was more paying tribute to the release of Dracula X Chronicles.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ah.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I was picking one of my favorite games in the Castlevania series, which would be Kid Dracula.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ah, okay, Kid Dracula.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was released in Japan as Akumajo Special Boku Dracula-kun, which translates to Demon Castle Special.
[SPEAKER_05]: Demon Castle Special, I'm Dracula-kun.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's playing as Alucard, pretty much, only he's Kid Dracula in the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's all super cute, and he has some of the powers that he had in...
[SPEAKER_05]: Symphony of the Night.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, the major bad guy in this game ended up being an enemy in Symphony of the Night.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, I love how they just tie in everything.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it was really great.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's a fun little, you know, little kid-type platformer.
[SPEAKER_05]: It came out on the Famicom in Japan.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also on the Game Boy.
[SPEAKER_05]: And over here we got it on the Game Boy.
[SPEAKER_05]: I actually own this game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm very happy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um...
[SPEAKER_05]: It has the first level music.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if you can hear it very well.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let me wait for it to get to the part.
[SPEAKER_03]: I missed this game when I was growing up.
[SPEAKER_03]: I never played this.
[SPEAKER_05]: We didn't get it in America.
[SPEAKER_05]: We got it on Game Boy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh yeah, I was going to say, I remember it on Game Boy.
[SPEAKER_03]: I remember seeing it somewhere.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, but this is a remix of Beginning from Castlevania III, if anyone recognizes it.
[SPEAKER_05]: The other cool thing about this game is that
[SPEAKER_05]: And I love how Konami does this, is that, um, Kid Dracula was also, um, a playable character, um, in, uh, Gokujo Parodius, which I thought was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: He was also a hidden selectable character in Jikyo Shiberi Parodius, which is actually my favorite of the Parodius series.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I also love chatting Parodius, too, but, um,
[SPEAKER_05]: So, uh, you know, I'll be covering the Proteus series somewhat later.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, look, it has, like, the clocks, like, just like Castlevania does.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, you go in the clock tower and everything.
[SPEAKER_05]: It has all of the, a lot of the classic levels that you expect in the old, um, uh, Castlevania games.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it was so cute.
[SPEAKER_05]: It actually was kind of hard.
[SPEAKER_05]: It got really difficult at times.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just like, uh, you know, you have the swinging pendulum and everything, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: A chatroom's joining in on this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Escapist says, Kid Dracula made using an umbrella as a weapon badass long before Kirby gave it a shot.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_03]: Son of Dad says, the music sounds very upbeat for a Castlevania game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, it was more of a parody-style game, but it was actually pretty good for how it played.
[SPEAKER_05]: I loved it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, we're talking about one of my top 20 games, I have to say.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Easy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: He has this toothy grin the entire time.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to paste a copy of the logo in the chatroom, just because it was adorable.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to post the one off of Wikipedia.
[SPEAKER_03]: Gerardimo says, Polka makes umbrella weapons best.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's a Turtle Sonata reference right there.
[SPEAKER_03]: What is he fighting here, a Klansman?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my god, it is!
[SPEAKER_03]: He has a swastika on his head!
[SPEAKER_03]: I swear to God, look at this boss he's fighting here at the end of stage one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Look at this.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's got a little swastika on his head.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's supposed to be like... I don't think this is supposed to be Shaft, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_03]: It looks like a Klansman.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's crazy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe this is a... Doing his part for racial equality.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess so.
[SPEAKER_03]: He made the Klansman cry and run away.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm hitting him too much.
[SPEAKER_03]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, so there you have it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Kid Dracula, your game of the week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_05]: and I'm probably one of these days going to cover Proteus.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I always say I'm going to.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't give it away.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't say when.
[SPEAKER_03]: I said eventually.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now you're here next week, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: You're still here next week?
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's two weeks that you leave for Alabama?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I leave actually taking a red eye on Thanksgiving.
[SPEAKER_03]: Gotcha.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's going to be a little later in the month.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just wanted to warn the listeners, be careful because when DarkSakura is out of town... I'm going to record my Game of the Week.
[SPEAKER_03]: All you're going to record it?
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought we got to pick in your absence.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sneaky.
[SPEAKER_05]: What would you pick?
[SPEAKER_03]: I would definitely go back to the Commodore 64 and dust something off from those archives.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't want to spoil it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I do have a game in mind right here.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you're going to go in that direction, then how could I deny anybody that?
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Heart.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki on the other hand, I have no idea what he'd pick.
[SPEAKER_01]: He'll pick Gals Panic or something.
[SPEAKER_01]: I would not pick Gals Panic.
[SPEAKER_01]: Or Miss World nude.
[SPEAKER_01]: I would not pick that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Everybody didn't move your body.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rob made the heart and I threw up the horns.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyhow, we really need to take a break here because we are pushing almost an hour 40 now.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we still have half the show to go.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkTesia points out Chill Einigi.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Please.
[SPEAKER_03]: We've got to take a break.
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have to pee.
[SPEAKER_05]: We are never covering Chill Einigi.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Break time.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll be back right after this with more Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Real quick break for those of you guys on the podcast.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll see you in a couple days.
[SPEAKER_03]: Orange Lounge Radio Orange Lounge Radio