[SPEAKER_00]: Tonight, October 14th, 2007, Nintendo unveils holiday news that includes a dreaded delay, Elder Scrolls Oblivion gets one last hurrah, and we're joined by members of Bizarre Creations to talk about Geometry Wars Galaxy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello everybody out there on the internet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: We are that podcast dedicated to video games, video gaming, gaming culture, and the gamer lifestyle.
[SPEAKER_04]: My name is Rob Roberts, and joining me as always, say hello to the one and only DarkSakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_04]: If we sound a little dead, it's because this is now our third time trying to record the show, and Jamie has been... Wait, wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_04]: This was empty a minute ago, and now it's full again.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is Mountain Dew Gamer Fuel that Chris brought for DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like cocaine.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's it taste like?
[SPEAKER_06]: The taste is sort of like orange cream soda, but the first taste of it is sort of like very orangey fruit punch, and the aftertaste of it is cream soda.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that's fairly accurate, wouldn't you say?
[SPEAKER_04]: It tastes like butt.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't like it so much.
[SPEAKER_06]: Kind of.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also joining us tonight, say hello to Techmaster Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello, since this mic cord does not reach.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it's fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can just speak into two microphones.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I don't need to speak into two microphones.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, the problem we're having tonight, folks, is that we're down to two microphones.
[SPEAKER_04]: The microphone that Loki usually uses died while we were trying to tape live here on this lovely Sunday evening.
[SPEAKER_04]: So Loki's mic is gone.
[SPEAKER_04]: So now we're having to share between the five people who are in studio tonight, two microphones.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we apologize if there's any audio delays or audio slowing or other audio issues, but this is what happens when you do live radio, folks.
[SPEAKER_04]: When things break, you don't have much time to fix it.
[SPEAKER_04]: So Loki's over there.
[SPEAKER_04]: So yes, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: My name is Black Lab.
[SPEAKER_04]: What is your quest?
[SPEAKER_04]: Ultimate power.
[SPEAKER_04]: What is the airspeed velocity of a swallow?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, forget it.
[SPEAKER_04]: God, you guys are crazy.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's what is the airspeed velocity of an unladen swallow?
[SPEAKER_06]: Is it African or European swallow?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, let's...
[SPEAKER_04]: Also say hello to a very special guest.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was surprised.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't even know she was coming tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Chris, everybody.
[SPEAKER_04]: Surprise, butt sex!
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: I got to keep my voice down because it's the acoustics in this room.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Chris is one of the official lesbians of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm actually surprised to see her back because I was thinking you were going to be flying to Wisconsin soon, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, well, I...
[SPEAKER_05]: I went to GeekCon last week, but that was only for a week.
[SPEAKER_05]: And in March, I am officially moving to Wisconsin for my school career.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jamie's helping me.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_06]: I am leaving.
[SPEAKER_06]: I am going in the U-Haul with Chris, and I'm leaving.
[SPEAKER_06]: She's coming back.
[SPEAKER_06]: I am not.
[SPEAKER_06]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was trying to be funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: I failed at it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I failed.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fail!
[SPEAKER_05]: You're not doing it right.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'm trying to hang out with you guys as much as possible, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: Ragnarokan
[SPEAKER_06]: It was lots of Ragnarok.
[SPEAKER_06]: I deleted a character and restart one, and I got two of them past job 50, and I played a lot.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I looked at your copy of Every Extend Extra and couldn't find the PSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: You accomplished a lot.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I bought a game, and I gave it to you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fantasy Zone.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then I don't have an old-school Nintendo to play it on, but I will do one.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I have three.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sweet.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I will lend you one.
Yay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe our top loader.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: So Halo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Lots of Halo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Halo and WoW.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's your kill ratio in Halo?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, more than one.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mine is less than .75.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think I'm like 1.6.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh wow, that's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not that good though.
[SPEAKER_03]: I still suck on occasion.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, well let's move on and Chris, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Megzi finally caved in thanks to peer pressure to get World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_05]: And she bought me an account for a month, so I've been kind of trying to use that up as much as possible to try to make it worth my while.
[SPEAKER_05]: And so I've been playing a lot of that and dying a lot, which is always a favorite pastime.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, honey, Mac... I'm working... So, Virtual PC.
[SPEAKER_06]: Virtual PC doesn't like... I don't have... Well, it works on Mac, I just don't have that much room.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that Ragnarok would run on a 486.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because it was probably created on one.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like my dancing blood elves.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dancing blood elves are fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: And good for you being Horde.
[SPEAKER_04]: For the Horde!
[SPEAKER_05]: For the Alliance!
[SPEAKER_05]: Diedrani.
[SPEAKER_04]: Boo Alliance.
[SPEAKER_04]: Draenei are okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can do Draenei.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because they speak like Russians.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_02]: It was good.
[SPEAKER_02]: I played Halo 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've gotten a little bit further in Legendary.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now I'm on the fifth chapter or whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Five out of ten.
[SPEAKER_02]: Halfway through the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's doing pretty good.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just have no idea how the hell I'm going to finish the last part of the game because that's where the difficulty really ramped up.
[SPEAKER_02]: and then, let's see, of course, more Saints Row multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's fun now because we've been playing in the Ultradome and we've been trying to jump cars to the top tier and actually been quite successful at that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So now it's who can get to the top tier the quickest and then try to survive without getting hit by rockets.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then, let's see, I've also been playing Half-Life 2 The Orange Box, mainly Portal on that, and that's...
[SPEAKER_04]: I was hoping someone on the show called Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, just kind of playing through that a little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then watching my wife play Puzzle Quest on the 360, which is just like Puzzle Quest on everything else.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then I played the Yaris game.
[SPEAKER_02]: God, what the fuck?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't even know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's free, but I feel like I'm being ripped off.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's, you know, seriously...
[SPEAKER_02]: Just because it's... I understand why it's free, because there's no way anyone would pay for that shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just... It reminded me of, like, was it Sonic the Hedgehog 2?
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, the bonus stages and that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Except really crappy and made no sense.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it was just stupid.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was horrible.
[SPEAKER_03]: I tried playing that, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: I downloaded it and played, like, about ten minutes of it and got confused.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because it's like, your car has, like, a tentacle that shoots lasers, and you have to shoot...
[SPEAKER_03]: Like flying box birds and toasters or something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: You said the best thing ever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tentacles that shoot lasers.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: You would think this would be the perfect game, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: A car with a tentacle that shoots laser beams at things.
[SPEAKER_04]: How fucking rad is that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yet somehow this game manages to fuck it up for free!
[SPEAKER_02]: By the way, I will not be buying a Yaris because of this game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just telling you that much.
[SPEAKER_02]: If I had thought about that... See, this is the thing now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Every time someone thinks about Yaris, they're going to think, man, that sucked.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have now associated suck with Yaris.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought they did that already.
[SPEAKER_02]: They've just driven that home now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, thumbs down on the Yaris game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not worth free.
[SPEAKER_02]: It definitely is not worth free.
[SPEAKER_02]: I still want a priest.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want my time back.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: My Gaming Week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Folks, today was a good day.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know why today was a good day?
[SPEAKER_04]: I now have a level 70 druid in Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_04]: I dinged 70 today.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hold on, everybody.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want my grats.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ding.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait, where's my grats?
[SPEAKER_04]: Grats.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: God, you guys need training.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you all call yourselves WoW players.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not a WoW player.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck that shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: These two are.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was forced into exile from my dead PC and my butthead husband who won't build me a new one.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm taking matters into my own hands, and I'm playing Guild Wars.
[SPEAKER_04]: Grats.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm level 20.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, that's not bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: 20 is partway to 70.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: So...
[SPEAKER_04]: So I did that, hooray, I'm officially an addict, and then I also played Puzzle Quest on Xbox Live with the tiniest text ever.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can definitely tell this game is a port from another system, namely the DS, and I don't know, for me, the mechanics of the game work a little well on the DS, but it is kind of fun to be able to play the game like humongous, the game itself, not the text, on the TV, just kind of kick back, you know, play on the TV, and it does have the Xbox Live element, which is kind of cool, but...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Use the stylus to swap the bricks.
[SPEAKER_04]: It works a lot easier.
[SPEAKER_04]: But otherwise, Puzzle Quest itself is a great game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it took Bejeweled and made it like 100 times better by adding this whole competitive element to it.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I was very happy with that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But one thing to the Xbox Live's credit, it costs about half as much as the DS version.
[SPEAKER_04]: And for an arcade title, for an Xbox Live arcade title, especially considering it came out the same week as Yaris...
[SPEAKER_04]: It's definitely one of the better things you can download on Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you don't have a DS and you like puzzlers at all, I definitely recommend you check out Puzzle Quest.
[SPEAKER_04]: But if you have a DS, maybe it's worth it to pay the extra 10, 15 bucks so you can have the game on the go and have the better controls.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's Puzzle Quest in a nutshell.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then I also played the Yaris game and I was like, WTF, LOL, BBQ.
[SPEAKER_04]: What else did you play, Chris?
[SPEAKER_05]: I play Dungeons and Dragons.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nerd.
[SPEAKER_05]: I am a nerd.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I converted nerds.
[SPEAKER_04]: I attack the darkness.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_05]: I went to GeekCon in Madison, Wisconsin last week, and they had a Dungeons & Dragons table in the RPG room.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it was set for beginners, and I'm an experienced player, so I just wanted to go in there for the gameplay and maybe help out.
[SPEAKER_05]: The guy looked at me, brought in my three core books, my 75 characters, and he looked so intimidated at me.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's like, oh, you play.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm like, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's play Let's rock it
[SPEAKER_04]: D&D is kind of the roots of video gaming in a way.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, modern RPGs.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, Meg Z's friends, I'm teaching them how to play, and they all have played all the RPGs, Final Fantasy, World of Warcraft, so they're really good at it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you're still a hardcore nerd for being into that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not that there's anything wrong with that.
Damn.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Going to our chat room.
[SPEAKER_05]: See that webcam?
[SPEAKER_05]: Damn right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Chat.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: Got dice right here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is where our chatters always are.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to start off tonight with NM64 says, Sky, if the text, speaking of Puzzle Quest, is a port of a DS version, how can the text be small?
[SPEAKER_04]: Wouldn't it be like five times bigger along with the rest of the screen?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what you'd think.
[SPEAKER_04]: But for whatever reason, they, you know, certainly they upscaled the graphics.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're not going to look at, like, pixelated stuff, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: It is HD graphics.
[SPEAKER_04]: The game looks very nice and has a good art style.
[SPEAKER_04]: But for whatever reason, they brought in text the size of the DS resolution.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have no idea.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would think that it would be a port of the PSP version since it's in a similar aspect ratio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Perhaps it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't played the PSP version, so it's hard for me to say.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that would make sense.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I hope the text in the PSP version isn't that small, because then you need a monocle to read it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, a magnifying glass is crazy.
[SPEAKER_04]: A fucking monocle.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right, you need a fucking monocle.
[SPEAKER_05]: The NDA 4.0 is going to suck.
[SPEAKER_04]: I heard they're making it like Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is, and you know what the problem is?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's worse.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because instead of them running around and doing stuff, it's little figures that you have on the mat, and they just move.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are Chinese people going to be farming for gold in D&D 4.0 as well?
[SPEAKER_02]: No idea.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Those little figurines were cool when they were on their own separate game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because they had those D&D figurines for a few years now.
[SPEAKER_03]: I used to collect them for my roommates.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that like Warhammer?
[SPEAKER_03]: I am a nerd.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are those like Warhammer things?
[SPEAKER_03]: Kind of.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you used the hex charts to move them around and all that crap?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it wasn't a hex chart.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was just the squares.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, you had little characters.
[SPEAKER_06]: The guy who runs our game actually uses... The guy who runs the game that I'm in actually uses a hex map and little figurines.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck that.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's, you know, fuck the hex maps.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's all about, if they survive the fall down the stairs, they win.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is, you just flick those little things off the stairs and they fly.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I have a suggestion.
[SPEAKER_06]: How about we move off of D&D?
[SPEAKER_04]: No disrespect, but we do want to move on with the show because thanks to all our audio problems that you didn't hear tonight if you weren't listening live, we're now 40 minutes into our program tonight and no news yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: So really quick, some housekeeping.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can view a live webcam of our show in progress or an archived webcam of our show over operator11.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can see our smiling faces all looking at you, waving hello and doing this program.
[SPEAKER_04]: Operator11.com Also join our LiveJournal and our MySpace and if you swing this way you can join our Facebook communities too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_04]: Brawl It's Delayed
[SPEAKER_02]: Haha, no Smash Brothers for Christmas, Timmy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways, it's going to be coming out now in February on the 10th.
[SPEAKER_02]: And other news, Sonic the Hedgehog's in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god, that's like such a surprise.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, who would have thought that Sonic the Hedgehog would be on a Wii game?
[SPEAKER_02]: Really?
[SPEAKER_02]: Who would have thought?
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, you know, it's not like that they have, I don't know, Mario and Sonic at the Olympics and shit like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sonic is in there, it's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: What more can I say?
[SPEAKER_02]: Although I am not surprised.
[SPEAKER_02]: In fact, this will be, I'm guessing, the first of many delays to come.
[SPEAKER_02]: In fact, we had heard, straight from Nintendo, Nintendo recently announced that there will be an additional 30 days added to most fourth quarter Wii releases due to production issues.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you'll probably see a lot of Wii titles slipping by 30 days or so.
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Where is this coming from?
[SPEAKER_04]: Nintendo?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mega Man
[SPEAKER_04]: Mega Man?
[SPEAKER_04]: Anybody?
[SPEAKER_04]: Anybody else think?
[SPEAKER_05]: Who's not in there?
[SPEAKER_05]: Or who's already in there?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: If they kept on the Sega route, I would actually put Knuckles in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would say to make, because now everybody's going like OMG Mario vs. Sonic, I would say to make the console wars of yesteryear complete, Bonk needs to be the third party character in the game, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: So they're like, okay, hooray, we're going to have Sonic in the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, and by the way, we're going to release this game next year on February 10th.
[SPEAKER_07]: They just ran out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Darth Vader, no, forget it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bad joke.
[SPEAKER_02]: Joke gone wrong.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was just going to say, they probably just ran out of days, you know, to tease characters, you know, in the Smash Dojo.
[SPEAKER_02]: So they're like, fuck, we need some more time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's just push the game back.
[SPEAKER_02]: How about that?
[SPEAKER_06]: I think I like Saikun's suggestion of Bomberman.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because that's more... Because Bomberman was also one of the NEC, you know, Hudson main people.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dark Tetsuya says Pyramid Head.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be awesome, but not going to happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you want to be cooler than all your friends and play Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_04]: Brawl first, you've got to go to E4ALL, which is being held in L.A.
[SPEAKER_04]: next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Starting on October 18th at the L.A.
[SPEAKER_04]: Convention Center.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, this is the little band-aid because there was no real E3.
[SPEAKER_04]: There was mini-E3 earlier this year.
[SPEAKER_04]: So this is their throw to try and fill that void.
[SPEAKER_04]: But of course, Sony and Microsoft are not going to be there.
[SPEAKER_04]: However, Nintendo is, Nintendo said, we're going to be there and we're showing off all of these games.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're showing off Super Mario Galaxy, Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_04]: Brawl, Donkey Kong Barrel Blast, Battalion Wars 2, Fire Emblem, Wii Zapper, Crossbow Training, Mario Song at the Olympics, Guitar Hero 3, Rayman Raving Rabbids 2, Resident Evil Umbrella, Ella, Ella, A, A, A, Chronicles, Medal of Honor Heroes 2, Ghost Squad, and on the DS, there's a lot of stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pokemon, Diamond and Pearl, wait, didn't that come out?
[SPEAKER_04]: Brain Age, wait, didn't that come out?
[SPEAKER_04]: Brain Age 2, wait, that came out too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Zelda Phantom Hourglass, actually that came out as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nintendogs, you know, that came out too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mario Kart, you know, a lot of these games they're showing actually have already come out, I'm noticing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Shh, they're new.
[SPEAKER_02]: If they're not new, they're new to you.
[SPEAKER_04]: But hey, if you want to play them like they're new again, head on over to E4ALL.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, Final Fantasy XII is going to be there, that little spin-off game on the DS, so there's some new stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: They may not be new, but you'll think they are.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're going to try to fool you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, what is not new, and actually this does not completely surprise me at all, is that the Wii is not lowering price at all.
[SPEAKER_06]: It will stay at $249.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's because the folks at Nintendo are saying that they're selling them as they make them.
[SPEAKER_06]: So they're having absolutely no trouble and see no point in lowering the price.
[SPEAKER_06]: On top of that, I mean, honestly, $249 is not bad for a system.
[SPEAKER_04]: So basically Nintendo's saying, you know, well, you guys are still buying them, so what do we need to do any different?
[SPEAKER_04]: In fact, we're going to increase the price!
[SPEAKER_04]: You know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sucka!
[SPEAKER_04]: They could.
[SPEAKER_06]: The direct quote, I think it's funny that this guy's name is George Harrison.
[SPEAKER_06]: But anyway, who is one of the Nintendo reps, said that we'll stay at $249 for the foreseeable future.
[SPEAKER_06]: We are still selling everything we can make.
[SPEAKER_06]: So hey, you're making money.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're still selling them.
[SPEAKER_06]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_04]: I know one thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought George Harrison was leaving Nintendo and going back to being a dead beetle.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: I heard... No, I seriously heard he was leaving Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_04]: So what's going on with that?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a bad... Okay, that's the bad joke.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was going to say that this didn't make the show roll, but there was conspiracy theories going around that there...
[SPEAKER_02]: One, that they're either lowering production so that there's still a shortage going through the holidays to increase demand on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or, because this is also kind of being shown in their marketing campaign, or that they're just making the best of a bad situation.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because, if you notice, their new set of commercials now, the very first thing that starts off is all, we got one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, it's a big thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, we got one.
[SPEAKER_02]: And now, no, you know...
[SPEAKER_02]: We stood up, we started playing, we had fun, we bonded, all this shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the whole thing is like, we got one!
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god, celebration!
[SPEAKER_02]: See, that's the fucking thing, that's what they're doing.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're trying to market off of this shortage thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: So whether it's intentional or not, they're using it to their advantage.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: They probably don't need to anyways, but it's probably a good marketing campaign.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because it's just going to increase hype, and really that's all that they care about.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although...
[SPEAKER_02]: There is a part in there that is a little disturbing with the mother and son.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're playing some game or something, and she's like holding his hand, and it's like, was it We Came Together?
[SPEAKER_02]: Or something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, oh!
[SPEAKER_07]: No!
[SPEAKER_05]: God, only you people could think that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is that the one that at the very end, the Japanese guys hand you the controller?
[SPEAKER_07]: We would like to play!
[SPEAKER_05]: It was really funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: When I was in Wisconsin, Megzi's mother was entertaining some Japanese guests, and she's got a Wii, and they were looking at it, and Megzi was like, oh, yeah, it's a Wii.
[SPEAKER_05]: And he's like, we've never seen one.
[SPEAKER_05]: They were from Chiba, so I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: We actually have the chatroom reaction to Loki's little comment on We Came Together.
We Came Together
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Way to have that clip queued up.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't realize there was going to be like 15 seconds into it.
No!
[SPEAKER_04]: That's why we don't have a soundboard on the program, folks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_02]: In other news, and more to get you up on your feet, Wii Fit's coming out to Japan on December 1st for 8,800 yen.
[SPEAKER_02]: And of course I'll feature the Wii balance board that's approximately $75 US And yeah, no idea when it's coming out in the US though So you'll have to wait your fat asses until it comes out Actually those boards supposedly only hold up to like 300 pounds So if you're like one of those people on the Maury Povich show You may not even get to play this game at all Get two boards One for each hoof Wait, no
[SPEAKER_04]: How many yen was that?
[SPEAKER_04]: It was 8,800.
[SPEAKER_04]: 8,800 yen.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now if you're having difficulty imagining how much money 8,800 yen is, imagine one yen 8,800 times.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not over 9,000 though, so that's good.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like 85 bucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: However, what's coming out right now is the 3.1 update for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to have USB keyboard support for everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because remember before, the Wii update only had the limited USB support.
[SPEAKER_02]: And how long did it take them to do this shit?
[SPEAKER_02]: Come on, seriously.
[SPEAKER_02]: This should have been in their...
[SPEAKER_04]: and also with the new Wii update a brand new enhanced Everybody Votes channel and did they make the Everybody Votes channel interesting again?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sadly no, they just added the USB keyboard support to the Everybody Votes channel so if you're actually still voting
[SPEAKER_04]: of which I can't imagine there's that many people still voting, but if you are, then, well, you get a new enhanced version and you can submit your questions now using the keyboard so you can annoy Nintendo even faster with your questions like, what's better, cake or pie?
[SPEAKER_04]: Cake or death?
[SPEAKER_04]: What's a better way to die?
[SPEAKER_04]: Fire, boat fire, you know?
[SPEAKER_04]: And I encourage people to send their dumb questions to Nintendo because it's funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's really funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: Funny!
[SPEAKER_06]: funny haha or funny oh fuck well for our friends in the UK we have a few updates to virtual console we have Super Metroid dun dun dun and it is 800 points uh 560 or 8 euro what Rob's giving me this look I'm like what so yeah go play Super Metroid all of you now
[SPEAKER_06]: And then you also get, that was on the NES, you get Protector Bot 2, Return of the Evil Forces.
[SPEAKER_06]: Known to us as Super Contra.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a retarded name that they... Protector Bot.
[SPEAKER_06]: Contra came out of there as Protector Bot.
[SPEAKER_02]: Protector Bot.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it had different sprites too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dude, Contra is just awesome, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: With blood.
[SPEAKER_04]: Going to the chatroom, I was giggling because Nintendo Maniacs64 says, The best Everybody Votes channel question, what's better, the Xbox 360 or PlayStation 3?
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see, SSJ100Matt thinks the Mii's will be the last unlockable character in Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_04]: Brawl.
[SPEAKER_04]: VXChaseXP says, The Everybody Votes channel rules!
[SPEAKER_04]: I vote every day, says our loyal webmaster, VXChaseXP.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I just made fun of the guy that hosts our website for nothing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good job, Rob.
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought Jason had more of a life than that.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: He's just very democratic.
[SPEAKER_04]: He wants his voice to be known.
[SPEAKER_04]: He wants people to know who he thinks should win American Idol.
[SPEAKER_04]: He wants people to know what color is better.
[SPEAKER_04]: What other kinds of dumbass things did they ask on there?
[SPEAKER_04]: He wants people to know that he prefers winter over summer and all that crap.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Jason Oches commented, gotta love this like, puppy should die in a boat fire.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: boat fire is okay at least there's water so finally it seems that Nintendo is going to be turning around this whole lack of stuff for Wii Online including of course they talked about the WiiWare service and they made some announcements of new titles that are going to be coming out for the WiiWare service including Pokemon Farm a Crystal Chronicles Yay!
[SPEAKER_02]: Pokemon Farm!
[SPEAKER_02]: Shut up!
Don't just poke
[SPEAKER_02]: Crystal Chronicles game called The Young King and the Promised Land where you build your own country and let's see here also Star Soldier R and Dr. Mario Wii that's also going to be coming out as well of course no dates yet as far as when we're going to see them in the US or pretty much anywhere on Earth imagine next year at some point
[SPEAKER_02]: Other games announced as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was Mina de Puzzle Loop, which came out over here as Magnetica.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a ripoff of Zuma.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then also, of course, there was a game called Marubo Shikaku.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's some weird thing that involves screens displaying different patterns, circle, line, and square based.
[SPEAKER_02]: And no idea what the fuck that is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways, and of course, those are only kind of a little sampling of what's going to be coming.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nintendo says that there's going to be over 100 WiiWare games that have been proposed to them.
[SPEAKER_02]: And who knows?
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see some good original content coming in 2008.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was going to say there was one other thing, too, that they showed off there real quick.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck yeah, it's about fucking time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I wish to understand that you have a mudkip.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would like to trade your mudkip for my pillup.
Hey, that pillup turns into a big buttfucker penguin.
[SPEAKER_05]: That pillup turns into a big buttfucker penguin, to quote my girlfriend.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, so WiiWare, lots of stuff coming out for the WiiWare.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, another game coming out, Wii Music.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, a lot of us saw this game at the very first time we saw the Wii at E3 2006.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember when, I think it was Miyamoto came out on stage, he's conducting the orchestra, da-da-da, what?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, that was Miyamoto on the thing, but I saw Koji Kondo playing, and got his autograph.
[SPEAKER_04]: www.DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: I want a band that has a zither, a harmonica, a melodica...
[SPEAKER_06]: an auto harp, and one snare drum.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would like Nintendo to know that if this game does not have a didgeridoo, it sucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Seriously, like, you better fucking have a didgeridoo in this game, because I want nothing to do with it if I cannot have my... A flugelhorn.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway...
[SPEAKER_05]: and a cowbell.
[SPEAKER_05]: It has to have a cowbell.
[SPEAKER_06]: It has to have a cowbell.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we need a band with a didgeridoo, a zither, a cowbell, a flugelhorn, a sitar and a harmonica.
[SPEAKER_02]: And this is why we don't let you guys make music.
[SPEAKER_05]: Son of Dad would like there to be a skin flute in the game that you can play.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like the sound of human screams.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that an instrument?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you need a game for that, then you need to do simple steps.
[SPEAKER_06]: Stand up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Go to your door.
[SPEAKER_06]: Open it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Walk out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Closing the door is optional.
[SPEAKER_06]: Go through the appropriate hallway to get to your front door.
[SPEAKER_06]: Open it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Step out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Leave.
[SPEAKER_06]: Experience nature.
[SPEAKER_06]: Real life.
[SPEAKER_06]: Get
[SPEAKER_05]: I highly recommend that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, this coming from the bitch who wants a sitar in Wii Music.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want an electric sitar, because sitars are sexy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's explicit on chat.
[SPEAKER_06]: We were explicit from the moment you said surprise butt sex.
[SPEAKER_05]: I make the explicit tag come up.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, shall I continue?
[SPEAKER_06]: For anyone who's looking forward to the new Mario Kart, you are going to be able to play up to 12 players online on Mario Kart Wii, which will officially make it the biggest Mario Kart ever.
[SPEAKER_06]: As long as you do it right.
[SPEAKER_04]: And as long as there's not two people on the car at the same time, because that's just going to be bad memories I don't want to revisit.
[SPEAKER_04]: and also there's bikes now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait, so now it's like Project Gotham 4?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, I tried playing the motorbikes in Project Gotham 4, not pretty.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm really bad at Project Gotham racing.
[SPEAKER_04]: And like, watching me race the motorbike in Project Gotham 4 was like watching me learn how to ride a bike for the first time.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was like, I'm going left, I'm going right, and then left, right, and then I fall off and collapse in a big heap and my bike falls on top of me to add insult to injury.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you, Project Gotham, for making me feel like a bad driver.
[SPEAKER_02]: but yeah, there will be bikes which, it's like why the fuck do you need bikes?
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, the game was fine as Mario Kart it's not Mario Kart and stuff I mean, seriously
[SPEAKER_02]: um anyways so Mario and Sonic at the Olympics they've already announced a bunch of really cool characters that you can play as but fuck that let's play as myself because you can play as your own me in the game because you know hey fuck all the time that you know it takes to actually put these wonderful characters in the game let's just have some dick put his own stupid me in there and play as himself hooray
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck that, I ain't buying the game anyways.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the fucking Olympics.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're gonna trick me this time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, I like this idea because now, like, we can find out who's better, me or Mario.
[SPEAKER_04]: Me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's faster, me or Sonic?
[SPEAKER_04]: I can now prove that I'm the best thing ever with my me, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's all about me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it's all about me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_04]: One game that I'm glad my me cannot be put into is Resident Evil Umbrella Chronicles because I would not want to die in this game or get shot or what have you or get my brains eaten by zombies.
[SPEAKER_04]: But what you can get with the Resident Evil Umbrella Chronicles is the Wii Zapper.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's actually going to be a Wii Zapper combo coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: And although right now it looks like it's only coming out in Japan, you never know.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you cross your fingers, hold your breath, it might come out over here on stateside.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not gonna happen!
[SPEAKER_02]: Why's that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because it's not gonna happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: Japan gets all the cool shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well they also get with this cool shit called the Expert Package, a 28-page book called Wesker's Extra Report.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they also get stickers.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stickers!
[SPEAKER_04]: Because who doesn't love stickers?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I love that it says zombie pew pew.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway...
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, one thing though about the special editions is that when we got, when Biohazard Code Veronica came out over here, well, we didn't get the big briefcase that had the Wesker's files and everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dan and I were tempted to order it.
[SPEAKER_06]: However, what they did after the fact was release the Wesker report as a special disc, like a free giveaway.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I got like a bunch of them.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, you know, I think that we're going to get the stuff
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just not going to be in the cool-ass bundle.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: Something that is happy yay face is... It's O-face.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you get Contra 4, you are getting Contra... Not just that, you're getting Contra Super C and the Protector Bot from the UK version.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rob, stop having Pikachu fuck!
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just entertaining our Op11 people before they get cut off, but I'm listening.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Op11 feed limits us to 40 minutes of recording, so... Anyway, so, um... So you get... Stop it!
[SPEAKER_06]: So you get Contra, Super C, and you get the Protector Bot.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, I bet you're happy.
[SPEAKER_02]: and art galleries and comics and all that fun shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know about the comics, but fun shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways, so other things that you're going to get, including this week, lots of fun games coming out, including one game that's kind of infamous with this show, a certain game on the Xbox 360 to which you roll around a ball, we'll call it, and you roll over objects and you're, let's call them
[SPEAKER_02]: The Prince, Mercury Meltdown Revolution
[SPEAKER_02]: 20 bucks.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's not bad for that game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Guilty Gear XX Accent Core.
[SPEAKER_02]: That should be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Victoria's Boxers.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if you're looking for an anime Mike Tyson's punch-out, maybe.
[SPEAKER_03]: That doesn't sound very interesting at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: It sounds like Victoria's secret is that she actually wears boxers.
[SPEAKER_04]: Victorious, not Victoria boxers.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought you said Victoria's.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it's Victorious.
[SPEAKER_02]: Never mind.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_02]: So other stuff coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tony Hawk's Proving Ground on almost everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: PlayStation 2, 360, Wii, PlayStation 3, DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: Avatar, The Burning Earth.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's coming out on almost everything as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Elder Scrolls Oblivion.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Shivering Owls expansion is coming out on a disc version for Xbox 360 as well as Oblivion, the Game of the Year edition is finally coming out for the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_02]: On PSP
[SPEAKER_02]: Spider-Man 3 is coming out, which, for those who don't remember, the game originally came out back in June on everything else.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or actually, I think May on everything else.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it sucked.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: SWAT Target Liberties coming out on PSP as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Crash of the Titans is finally getting its PSP version coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Backyard Football 2008.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't touch that game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's horrible.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then on PC, there's a whole bunch of crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then, let's see here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fury's coming out, so that's going to be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Flight Deck 5.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that looks like shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Zoo Tycoon 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because where would we be without a Tycoon game each week?
[SPEAKER_02]: Finally, let's see here.
[SPEAKER_02]: On the DS, Flash Focus Vision Training.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, another fucking training game that Nintendo's going to sucker you into buying because you're blind without it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Disney Princess Magical Jewels is going to be coming out on the DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do not want to see the princess's magical jewels because that sounds just really wrong.
[SPEAKER_02]: And this, I'm sure, will make a certain chatter happy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hannah Montana Music Jam on the DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck the chatters, I'm happy!
[SPEAKER_03]: Are you paying $2,000 for a concert ticket?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I'm not stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm happy, not stupid.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a wonderful game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like jam sessions, except, well, you can, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jamie was asking me what.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've seen it on CNN four times in the last month about how their concert tickets are getting sold by scalpers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Real quick, though, and one other thing on the PC, Heroes of Might and Magic 5, Tribes of the East, that expansion is finally coming out as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that is pretty much everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, then let's go to Japan and see what our friends overseas are getting this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: They are also getting a game you may have heard of on this program.
[SPEAKER_04]: Before we had to get rid of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Beautiful Katamari Damacy ships in Japan on October 18th on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: Another game coming out on the Xbox 360, Zoids Alternative.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not Zoinks, but Zoids Alternative.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it kind of looks like a cyborg type game, but what I find very interesting is that the box art totally has Final Fantasy font.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yet it has, like, it totally looks like a Final Fantasy game, but yet...
[SPEAKER_04]: Nothing to do with Final Fantasy.
[SPEAKER_06]: I noticed that it's a Takara game and Takara is responsible for Transformers over there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Zoids is like a, I don't know, I call it a ripoff of like fucking, I don't know, like Mighty Morphin Power Rangers or maybe even like... Which was a ripoff on the Japanese franchise.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly, and I'd say maybe even also a ripoff of Voltron a little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Power Rangers destroyed my childhood.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hitstun in our chatroom would like to remind us they've been making Zoids games since the NES.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would also like to point out with all the ripping off thing and Rob bringing up the Final Fantasy font that it was Yoshitaka Amano who was in part responsible for us having the whole transforming team whatever mecha genre to begin with.
[SPEAKER_06]: So he's responsible for the rape of my childhood.
[SPEAKER_06]: He did the character designs for Kagaki Ninja Tai Gatchaman.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't care what anyone says.
[SPEAKER_05]: Trini was hot.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also hot is Tobey Maguire starring in Spider-Man 3 coming out on the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: See how I took it right back on track?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's so cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like the Japanese.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, well, because it's the Japanese version.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's why the box says Japanese writing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go figure.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't see that every day.
[SPEAKER_04]: PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't panic.
[SPEAKER_04]: Seaman 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Notice that is a sea man, not the other thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dan and I sat around with our Dreamcast talking to our Seaman for how long?
[SPEAKER_04]: How often do you talk to Dan's Seaman?
[SPEAKER_06]: Dan was the one who talked to our Seaman.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then they turned into man-frogs and left.
[SPEAKER_04]: Make it stop!
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: That sound you hear is millions of listeners across America throwing up into their mouths.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's true, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you know you can import this into America?
[SPEAKER_04]: The bundle for Seaman 2 for the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: The full title, Seaman 2 Peking Engine Ikusi Kit is coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to cost you 90 bucks if you want to import that sucker.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that comes with a microphone so you can yell at your Seaman.
[SPEAKER_05]: What is it?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've never played that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Seaman, first of all, when it came out over here, it was narrated by Leonard Nimoy and that was really cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: You start off with these
[SPEAKER_06]: These eggs, and you grow them into tadpoles, and they eventually grow human faces.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you... Wait a minute, wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_04]: Isn't that kind of like the other kind of Seaman?
[SPEAKER_04]: Does that too?
[SPEAKER_06]: Allow me to continue.
[SPEAKER_04]: I grant thee permission.
[SPEAKER_06]: Someone take the mic away from Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: See, I like having two mics now, because I can tell Rob to STFU.
[SPEAKER_06]: Continue, I want... Anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: So they speak this own little nonsense language and you talk to them.
[SPEAKER_06]: And eventually they start talking back and they build their vocabulary as you talk to them.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then they start speaking in this distinguished sort of posh British accent.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then you have conversations with them and they ask you questions and then they remember the things that you've answered.
[SPEAKER_06]: and they ask you your birthday and you speak back and forth to them and you monitor their habitat, make sure that the water is right, feed them every day.
[SPEAKER_06]: But eventually they start eating each other.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know, it's fantastic.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or like one will die or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait, okay, so it's like Pokemon and the Sims combined.
[SPEAKER_06]: But you talk to them.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you're teaching them to say damn fucking shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: They have everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's programmed in, but it's very interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: How has this game not shown up on my radar in the years that we've been doing Orange Lounge Radio?
[SPEAKER_04]: Five and a half years and I've never heard of this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you want to borrow mine?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you have a working VMU?
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, I do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I still have my chow.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have the Dreamcast hooked up in the garage.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can play Seaman all night long.
[SPEAKER_06]: At any rate...
[SPEAKER_06]: As you progress through the game, you have another tank that's a terrarium.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you're actually growing another environment, and after a while, your seaman's going to start floundering around and start turning into a cocoon.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't stop laughing!
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm trying to take the mic from Rob!
[SPEAKER_06]: And then you eventually move the cocoon into the terrarium, and it hatches into a frogman.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then he leaves, and the game is over.
[SPEAKER_02]: See, and then in the sequel game, you actually, your guy turns into a caveman.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so, thus the cycle starts all over again.
[SPEAKER_02]: Think about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So he turns into a caveman, so he can do Geico commercials.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a series about that now.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they sold that from Unfrozen Caveman Lawyer on Saturday Night Live.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why'd y'all have to remind us about that show?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, just when I purged it from my memory.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, my turn, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Or do you have more stuff?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I have more stuff, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: We got sidetracked by Seaman.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the sequel to Seaman's coming out on the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, Galaxy Angel 2, Mugen Karunokagi is coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have no idea what the hell this game is, but you know it's cool because it's by a company called Broccoli.
[SPEAKER_06]: Broccoli did DigiCarrot.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ah, very cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, from the people who brought you DigiCarrot.
[SPEAKER_04]: so Sonic Rush Adventure is coming out on the Nintendo DS from Sega and also in Japan this week on the PSP Riviera Yasuko Nochi Special Edition is coming out and looks like another game based off an anime surprise surprise that's it my turn and coming out over in the UK on the 16th Warmonger Operation Downtown Destruction 17th Speedball 2 Brutal Deluxe everything else is coming out on the 19th
[SPEAKER_06]: Eternal Sonata for Xbox 360, Football Manager 2008, which, by the way, is real football and not the shit we have in America.
[SPEAKER_06]: Galactic Assault, Half-Life 2, Episode 2, King of Clubs, Lair, Life Science, Hospital Affairs, Luminous, Ark, Myst, Naruto, Ultimate Ninja, and Naruto Ultimate Ninja 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, they get the game and then they get the sequel the same day.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why?
[SPEAKER_06]: Portal on Xbox 360, Pursuit Force Extreme Justice, Rockstar Games Presents Table Tennis.
[SPEAKER_06]: Didn't that already come out?
[SPEAKER_06]: They're just getting Portal on Xbox 360?
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're just getting Portal.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would just buy Portal and skip Half-Life altogether.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also, Tabula Rasa on PC, Team Fortress 2, The Legend of Zelda Phantom Hourglass, The Orange Box on Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why did they get an option of getting Portal?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it might be a typo.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can buy it standalone here, but only on the PC.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can get it through Steam.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bastards.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thrillville Off the Rails, also coming out on damn near everything else.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yeah, I forgot Thrillville Off the Rails is also coming out in the US.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's fun, you get to make people hurl.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yee.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_02]: Something else that's coming out here pretty soon and unfortunately is the last in the long line of download content for Oblivion is the brand new Fighter Stronghold.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is the same price as a Yaris Xbox Live Arcade game, but way better.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it will be coming out, it's actually going to be free beginning on October 15th, but it's only free for a week.
[SPEAKER_02]: I need to remember that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Make sure you download it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the last bit of download content you're going to see for Oblivion, so what a way to close it off for free.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, here you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: This show actually will go to its podcast form on the 15th, which is the way most people listen to the program, so go check Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_04]: It should be up now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Friendly reminder from the folks here at OLR.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, the other thing, here's some of the cool features, though, that the Fighter Stronghold comes with.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can get your own, I guess, Venter to create your own wines for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have a combat trainer, a taxidermist to create trophies for your pad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: They also, I think there was some other stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically, you get this whole castle to run after you do a little quest to get.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would be so cool to just fill my castle with a bunch of dead bears.
[SPEAKER_04]: Seriously, how is Elder Scrolls V going to top Oblivion?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, like, Oblivion, I mean, this is literally saying, look, we're going to give you the kitchen sink in this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it's everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's amazing.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is amazing.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a video game, Chris.
[SPEAKER_04]: You don't actually have to have real pets on your wall.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know, but it's only fun to kill the simpets.
[SPEAKER_04]: Chris.
[SPEAKER_03]: But still.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're so difficult to please.
[SPEAKER_03]: But in The Sims, you can't throw fireballs at things.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, look, I'll tell you what, Chris.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's nothing funner in Oblivion than throwing fireballs at the sheep constantly.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then they start to attack you.
[SPEAKER_04]: They figure out you're a bad man.
[SPEAKER_04]: If they live long enough.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: When sheep attack.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's pretty bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, as was that joke.
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sierra Online, also Vivendi Games, is part of that.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have given us some more details about what is coming out on Xbox Live Arcade and PC through the rest of the year.
[SPEAKER_04]: There is a third-person retro arcade shooter called Aces of the Galaxy.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's another title called Boogie Bunnies.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is a game where players match rabbits in a match-three puzzle game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Those are both coming out on the PC and Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rabbit threesomes?
[SPEAKER_04]: X-Box Live Arcade Shooter Assault Heroes Arcadian Warriors
[SPEAKER_04]: and 33, Scar, Resurrection Ship, Exodus, and the one some people have been looking forward to or not looking forward to because it may bastardize what they know and love, Battlestar Galactica, where you can play as the humans or the Cylons, 16-player online gaming on the PC, 8 players on Xbox Live Arcade, even though the early reviews on that were mediocre at best, but, you know, they've had a long time since then.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure that was an early version, so you never know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, who knows?
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's be fair.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like time makes games better.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't feel so bad now!
[SPEAKER_04]: But I have Doctor Who.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, anyone who cares, Speedball 2 is going to be on Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_06]: I care, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I think this is funny that it was referred to like this on Joystick, that it's like Calvin Ball.
[SPEAKER_06]: For anyone who reads Calvin and Hobbes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Calvin Ball is the game where you make up your own rules.
[SPEAKER_06]: As you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: I demand euphoria.
[SPEAKER_02]: so yeah, Calvin Ball the game anyways let's see here for those who may not be into Calvin Ball there are some other tidbits on Xbox Live Marketplace that you might be interested in including a whole fucking ton of demos the Simpsons game is actually on there now definitely check it out I forgot I did play that this week awesome, awesome game if you're a Simpsons fan you're going to love it
[SPEAKER_02]: Conan, which of course is based off the movie and comic series.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's supposed to be very, very bloody.
[SPEAKER_02]: I haven't got a chance to play it yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: I will soon.
[SPEAKER_03]: I tried it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I could not understand the control system at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just hit, mash one button, swung my sword, and there was lots of blood, and I died a lot.
[SPEAKER_02]: But at least that's why they have demos, so you don't have to waste $60 to find that out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Project Gotham Racing 4 is up there now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I played that one.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's pretty, it's fun, but I really suck at it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, I cannot control the car for shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just have not figured out, like, the only racing game I can control worth a damn besides Mario Kart is Burnout.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, these other ones, I can't do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I keep crashing into walls.
[SPEAKER_02]: I highly recommend, Rob, I swear you're going to love this game, Flat Out Ultimate Destruction.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I played the demo for that, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: I did.
[SPEAKER_04]: Based on your recommendation, I downloaded the demo for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: A little clunkier than Burnout for me, but I like the fact that when you ran people off the road, it actually told you who you just killed.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they get pissed off at you, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that was good.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, Ultimate Destruction.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the majority of them were hot chicks that I was offing, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, babe.
[SPEAKER_02]: Woohoo.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, well, Microsoft is cracking down on naughty, naughty, naughty, very naughty mottos that people have in their gamer tag.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not so much the tag itself, but you know how everybody on Xbox 360 gets a motto, a little line that they can have under their name?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, for instance, mine is OrangeLaunchRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Trying to plug the site in very cheap ways.
[SPEAKER_04]: So when people kick my ass at Halo, they'll go, hey, let's check out this guy's crappy podcast that he does with his friends.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, yeah, that's there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know what you guys have for your mottos.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you have for your motto, Loki?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_04]: You don't remember?
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Does anybody... What's yours, puppy?
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you remember?
[SPEAKER_03]: I honestly... You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: I only made it a month ago and I don't remember it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because it's really not important.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think to be funny the first time, I think I had it so much fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then I think I just changed it to the website.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, one of our fellow independent podcasters found out the hard way that Microsoft is actually keeping an eye on those mottos.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cheapy D over at the CheapAssGamer, they're the guys that won the podcast award this year.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, good for them.
[SPEAKER_04]: But they got banned from Xbox Live for a day for saying, Konichiwa, bitches, in their motto.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently Microsoft does not appreciate the word bitch, because poor Cheapy D. Yeah, they're offended by the word Konichiwa.
[SPEAKER_04]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what's funny is that when I read that, I think of the Robins song, but maybe I'm just, I don't know, I'm crazy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, also, another user on the site, an unnamed user, but I think I actually know who this might be if you listen to All Games Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: There is a person whose motto was, called the shit poop.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's my thing is I want to know what exactly does Microsoft consider offensive?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm like, the bans are just for a day.
[SPEAKER_04]: So let's have a little fun with this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's push the limits.
[SPEAKER_04]: So tonight I'm going to change my motto to fisting fan.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I want to see if anybody catches that that could be actually a pornographic thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I meant like karate fisting.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm going to change my motto tonight to like I heart fisting or fisting fan or fan of fisting.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I want to see if that will get by the censors.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_06]: One of Dan's friends, his gamer tag
[SPEAKER_06]: is, um, uh, okay, I have to think of how he has it, um, DuckMySock.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, apparently, um, one of the listeners over at All Games, Flaming Bozo is reporting, uh, one of the other listeners at All Games, Buck Fush, is his nickname, Buck Fush got banned for a day because his motto said Bush Plan 9-11.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently, that was a no-no.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who cares?
Seriously, my girl?
[SPEAKER_05]: Seriously, Microsoft, who cares?
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, Loki, a seat now, good.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like this.
[SPEAKER_04]: The chatroom is coming up with things that are questionably offensive for us to put in our mottos.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, Loki, you're going to use this one from Takeo Rei, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: Dirty Sanchez is all around.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can you change your motto to that and see if you get banned for a day?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just a day.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just one day.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can go without Halo for a day.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can get banned for other reasons, but...
[SPEAKER_04]: Son of Dad's new motto says, Halo soaks cork.
[SPEAKER_05]: Frisbee says, buy a Wii.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't have an Xbox in my garage.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is on Xbox, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, it's 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, 360, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, Megsie's got one, but she doesn't have time to play because she's stuttering for finals.
[SPEAKER_05]: But can someone in chat, for me, or anyone who's listening, like, who wants to actually participate, add something to the lesbian?
[SPEAKER_05]: Or, like, I like dykes or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: Carpet muncher.
[SPEAKER_05]: How do you know?
[SPEAKER_05]: That could be my cat.
That's true.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's a special time, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: Color of Sakura is going to change his motto to save the rug doctor.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, God, yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we need to start a thread in the forums for questionable mottos that get caught by Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that would be funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: Somebody start that up, orangejohnsradio.com, forums.
[SPEAKER_06]: Plug, plug.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or, like, have one that says, like, I want a fag, or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but fag means cigarette, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you get banned for reels, like, permanently, though, you can't blame us, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: You're doing this at your own, because I don't want no, like, lawsuit, like, oh, those assholes on Oregon Radio told me to change my mind.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, you're doing it for yourself, okay?
[SPEAKER_05]: But we really appreciate it, so give it to pure pleasure.
[SPEAKER_04]: But only cool kids do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Segment.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ah, yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have a segment coming up now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because we're over an hour now, so it's time for Part A to finish up.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you know we like to close out Part A here at Orange Lounge Radio by respecting our elders and paying tribute to a classic video game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's DarkSakura's Classic Game of the Week.
[SPEAKER_04]: So DarkSakura, what game should all the kids be putting in their Gamefly queues right now?
[SPEAKER_06]: The Classic Game of the Week.
[SPEAKER_06]: For all of you awesome people who own a Saturn.
[SPEAKER_06]: Magical Night's Dream Cotton Boomerang, which is a fantastic game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Cotton Boomerang is actually...
[SPEAKER_06]: A Saturn port of Cotton 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: So actually, if you've got MAME, you can play the game on your emulator, and it'll run just fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it was basically going back to the original Cotton, the way that it worked, as being a side-scrolling shooter with extra fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I know I've talked about Panorama Cotton and Rainbow Cotton a lot.
[SPEAKER_06]: Those are sort of special in the series, in the fact that they are...
[SPEAKER_06]: Behind the Character View, and they're actually kind of hard to play.
[SPEAKER_06]: But Cotton Boomerang is completely side-scroller with lovely animation for the levels, but you also get pretty much unlimited magic, and you get all these different skill items that you can use in the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: My favorite item in this game is this big ball of fire.
[SPEAKER_06]: And what you do with the big ball of fire is you bounce it.
[SPEAKER_06]: and you actually will have lines of enemies that come at you and you can bounce the ball at and it'll just knock out completely lines of you know complete lines of enemies and the cool thing about the Cotton series though is that there was also this collector um thing that if you got different um
[SPEAKER_06]: Cotton Games, like Panorama Cotton was one.
[SPEAKER_06]: And keep in mind, they only made something about 600 copies in this game.
[SPEAKER_06]: And there were only 300 of these tea mugs, tea cups that they issued out.
[SPEAKER_06]: There was one with the original cotton version.
[SPEAKER_06]: There was the Panorama Cotton one.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's Cotton 2 cup, but they don't know how many of them are out in circulation.
[SPEAKER_06]: But these are like lots of money now, anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, for anyone who wants to play any of the Cotton games, if you've got a Neo Geo Pocket Color, and I think it actually came out on DS, I want to say.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's also a Super Nintendo version.
[SPEAKER_06]: They did release Cotton on a number of systems, but I'd have to say of the side scrollers, the best of them is Cotton 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just really, really a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I love that in the bonus stages, we pick up teacups.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just like the concept of a side-scrolling shooter game starring witches flying on brooms.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's just kind of rad and original.
[SPEAKER_06]: The whole story behind it is that Cotton is this little witch girl who's addicted to this candy called Willow that makes her throw up.
[SPEAKER_06]: And she rescues... Kind of like how I'm addicted to crack.
[SPEAKER_01]: It makes me throw up too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, um, and she rescues this, um, fairy, oh, this fairy named Silk comes to get her help.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's her, by the way.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a sexy mama that comes up there on the little stage selection screen.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that Cotton's lesbian lover?
[SPEAKER_03]: What is that?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the fairy Silk.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, of course, there has to be some gratuitous... And the whole point of this game is that, and the whole reason that the character is participating in this adventure at all is because either she wants candy...
[SPEAKER_06]: or someone is threatening her supply of candy and she's only doing it for the candy, she could give a shit about the trials and tribulations of the land she's rescuing because she wants candy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is she single?
[SPEAKER_06]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's also a little girl.
[SPEAKER_06]: Cotton is a little girl.
[SPEAKER_05]: She's a very little girl.
[SPEAKER_05]: The graphics are just awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rob's got something on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_05]: This, yeah, this, yeah, video one, and it's pretty much showing what the game is looking like.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the graphics, how old is this game?
[SPEAKER_06]: This came out on the Sega Saturn.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, I do believe, The graphics are awesome!
[SPEAKER_06]: I do, I do want to say that this game came out in 95?
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to say.
[SPEAKER_06]: Really?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because, yeah, the Saturn in Japan came out when, 93, Rob?
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, no, it came out in 94 because my, um, my, I had just started college, and my friend imported a Saturn that year.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um,
[SPEAKER_06]: But yeah, I want to say that Cotton Boomerang came out in 95, and it's, you know, for anyone who's a fan of 2D shooters, this game is gorgeous.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, really.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it really is.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's a ton of fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I'd say anyone who's got MAME or the equivalent, if you want to play it on one of your emulators, you'll find it as Cotton 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: But if you've got a Saturn, find this game if you can.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's really a ton of fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I can say that I have played through Cotton 2, or Cotton Boomerang, and it's really great.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't actually own it myself.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cotton Boomerang or Cotton 2 is the classic game of the week, as judged by DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: This game looks like fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm actually thinking I want to check that out too at some point.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, very cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm liking this new segment.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you guys think?
[SPEAKER_04]: Mailbag at OrangeLawnTrader.com if you want to send us an email.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you have a suggestion, a game that Jamie needs to check out to consider for the segment, even though I think you have like your next month and a half already picked out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, I make sure to pick them out ahead of time.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Dirtetsia, thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: He posted a link to the Panorama Cotton Mega Drive one that has the teacup with it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I actually do know somebody who has a copy of Panorama Cotton.
[SPEAKER_06]: If anybody wants to have a headache, then go on YouTube and look at... Well, actually, Panorama Cotton, I've played on the Genesis Emulator, but my friend owns a legit copy.
[SPEAKER_06]: It really is fun, but Rainbow Cotton was really fun, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was the Dreamcast version.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's the same type of game.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that's going to do it for Orange Lounge Radio, this Part A of our podcast.
[SPEAKER_04]: But don't worry, we're going to be right back with Part B. And in Part B tonight, we're being joined by Craig Howard and Ben Ward from Bizarre Creations.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're going to be here to talk about Geometry Wars Galaxies.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we'll be right back with Part B of our show.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: I made a bad boo-boo when I was late.
[SPEAKER_04]: I made myself look very unprofessional, but I'll tell you more about that in part B. For those of you guys listening on OrangeLawnsRadio.com, you're getting some music, specifically tonight, some of the music from the Wangan Midnight Maximum Tune 3 soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_04]: So don't drive right now, because you might drive really, really fast to this music.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll be right back in about 10 minutes.