[SPEAKER_07]: www.orangeloungeradio.com
[SPEAKER_07]: and now the conclusion of this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: I think it's around the same time as the Euro version.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway, same issues with the European model.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not going to have backwards compatibility with PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I stand corrected from what I said last week.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was a little confused with the chips and what they did and shit.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, originally they had taken out the Emotion Engine, which dropped the backwards compatibility a little bit.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now they removed the second chip that did the rest of the backwards compatibility for PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: So...
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not a software thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: It is something that they're doing to save money.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's still stupid, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: They took out one of the biggest marketing things they had.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, they were totally doing it around that emotion.
[SPEAKER_10]: You don't have to buy that version.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can spend $100 more and buy one that does play some... Basically, they removed its soul, or my soul, depending on how you want to look at it.
[SPEAKER_10]: But hey, that's okay, because you'll buy a 40-gig PS3 if you're in Japan, because they're wiped.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that makes all the difference.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're available in white, as well as black.
[SPEAKER_08]: Any chance we might get the other colors over here?
[SPEAKER_08]: Or do they say, well, are they going to be all Nintendo?
[SPEAKER_08]: We don't need to do different colors right now, even though we always do different colors, because the current consoles are still selling like crazy.
[SPEAKER_10]: We don't want to confuse people anymore, you know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Eventually, I'm sure there'll be different console colors, much like there is with the PS2.
[SPEAKER_10]: But PS2, they stuck with black for a long time until silver, which I think that was just this summer.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, I mean, shit.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're a little late to the game with the colors for the PS2 as well.
[SPEAKER_08]: Going to our chat room, chat.orangeloungeradio.com, GS68 says, White PS3s?
[SPEAKER_08]: I call racism.
Did anybody else do that ad?
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, you guys already probably covered it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It just reminded me of that ad for, I think, a PSP in Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: It just reminded me of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That white chick.
[SPEAKER_08]: Chris the Lesbian, taking us back to the sounds of 2006 here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Love you, Chris.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bite me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, so we know Sony has these white and black issues.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why not red?
[SPEAKER_08]: Where's the red love and the yellow love and the blue love and the purple love, huh?
[SPEAKER_08]: Where is it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Native American love.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, you aren't going to get any love.
[SPEAKER_10]: You see those extra colors?
[SPEAKER_10]: That costs money.
[SPEAKER_10]: And obviously they're trying to save money.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, I take it back.
[SPEAKER_08]: There is a red PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think they made like three of them because I seem to remember some Canadian contest where they were giving away like red PS3s in Canada.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or you can go on the internet and buy them in any color.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or you can go to Target and get a can of spray paint.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just be careful.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's a Krylon touch.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I have to have one that matches my carpet.
[SPEAKER_08]: You don't have any carpet.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm being hypothetical.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyhow, speaking of the Sony PSP, at least Chris was able to take us on the right path and take us over to the PSP.
[SPEAKER_08]: And we want to talk about some first-party PSP titles that are coming in the year 2008.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's going to be seven first-party download titles coming to the PSP.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, how does that work?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I haven't downloaded anything on the PSP yet.
[SPEAKER_08]: I haven't either.
Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I guess you take your PSP, connect to the Sony store, and you can download all of these.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's eventually going to be with the Sony store on PC or on the PS3.
[SPEAKER_10]: You just download it, and you transfer it to the memory stick.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hopefully it's a lot better than the stupid demos, because the demos you have to put in this fucking specific directory, and they have all these specific instructions.
[SPEAKER_10]: Instead of, throw it in the games folder, and it will work.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, something like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, there's going to be three action games, two music games, one shooter, and one racer.
[SPEAKER_08]: But if you were hoping I was going to name those seven titles, sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: That story's in another castle.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, sorry.
[SPEAKER_10]: This kind of brings me back to that WiiWare story that we did in Part A. But I remember there was also a Hudson karaoke game that's come in the WiiWare.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hudson's cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: Bomberman karaoke.
[SPEAKER_06]: As long as I can sing Fergalicious...
[SPEAKER_06]: No, that's okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: No one can hear you.
[SPEAKER_06]: So... So a new demo was announced for the PS3 store, which is Ratchet & Clank Tools of Destruction.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um...
[SPEAKER_06]: Also, I think out for demo is NHL 2K8 and Conan, but Sony's recent update was also saying that they were also going to be putting up demos for Uncharted, Folklore, and Fallout 3.
[SPEAKER_08]: Demos, demos, demos.
[SPEAKER_10]: Finally.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: Demos.
[SPEAKER_10]: When did EA become a contestant on Supermarket Sweep?
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: But who knows, Mass Effect 2, definitely going to be published by EA.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it's very interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why do you think EA is trying to buy all these companies?
[SPEAKER_08]: What's their strategy?
[SPEAKER_08]: Is it just like a Monopoly type thing?
[SPEAKER_08]: Or are they just trying to grab the, I mean, because BioWare doing Mass Effect, I mean, are they just trying to foresee that, oh, this is going to be a huge title, we want part of that?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because Activision is bizarre, so, you know, they got a monkey see monkey do, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Activision in like EA or in this pissing contest to who can make the best games.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hint to Activision, stay away from Spider-Man games.
[SPEAKER_10]: Not doing very good for you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry, I was looking up on YouTube some clips of Supermarket Suite, but I guess I wanted you all in the studio to know I'm not crazy.
[SPEAKER_08]: This was a real badass TV show they used to have on the telly.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you?
[SPEAKER_05]: My granny used to watch it, and I'd have to watch it when I went to Dothan.
[SPEAKER_08]: I used to make my grandma watch it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I used to watch it all the time with, like, one of the early morning game shows.
[SPEAKER_09]: Back when I was, like, ten years old, all I watched was game shows.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, when I was ten years old, the things that we watched were reruns of Press Your Luck.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, Ami, no, Ami, no, Ami, no, Ami, no, Ami, stop!
[SPEAKER_09]: Stop!
[SPEAKER_08]: Dude, when I used to go shopping with my mom and I would put these random Nintendo magazines and candy in the cart, my mom would be all, how did that get there?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm like, I'm practicing to be on Supermarket Sweep.
[SPEAKER_10]: Innocent look.
[SPEAKER_10]: White-eared 50 hams in our cart.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like ham.
[SPEAKER_08]: Christmas is coming.
[SPEAKER_08]: Didn't you get the memo?
[SPEAKER_08]: PlayStation Network is getting some updates, or actually got some updates.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not only the Ratchet & Clank demo to which Jamie earlier mentioned, but also a title that a lot of folks have been looking forward to, Everyday Shooter.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it's kind of cool that the PlayStation is now getting some kind of like, you know, indie-ish games you can't get other places.
[SPEAKER_08]: And Everyday Shooter is one of those games I've heard a lot of good things about.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can get arrested for that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_08]: If you're an everyday shooter.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not talking about like going out and shooting people from a clock tower or whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm talking about... Chris, your jaw just dropped and like hit the hardwood floor.
[SPEAKER_04]: While I was in Madison, I don't know the details, and you guys may have covered it, but some guy was going through one of the University of Wisconsin buildings.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if he had a weapon with him, or I forgot what exactly the details were, but he ended up jumping out of a window, and the reason he was running around the building like he was shooting things, because he thought he was playing the video game Doom.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_10]: And people wonder why video games are being persecuted.
[SPEAKER_10]: See, that's the problem.
[SPEAKER_10]: He was playing Doom still.
[SPEAKER_10]: He needs to really update his game.
[SPEAKER_10]: If we could ban him from Doom, we would.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: Darwin Awards.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a perfect candidate for the Darwin Awards.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, Everyday Shooter will set you back $9.99, or to the rest of us, that's $10.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also, on the PlayStation Network, you can get some Everyday Shooter wallpaper, and the cost of that, free.
[SPEAKER_08]: Some movie trailers as well, Spiderwick Chronicles, Walk Hard, The Assassination of Jesse James, and some trailers for some video games, Fallout 3, Folklore, and I believe some things that were already mentioned previously in the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that means you gotta tune in, yo.
[SPEAKER_06]: Listen to what we say.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, for those who were all, you know, happy about SingStar coming out, prepare to be unhappy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Completely not happy.
[SPEAKER_06]: It has been delayed past November 3rd, and it is hanging out, I guess, with Duke Nukem forever in Limbo Land.
[SPEAKER_06]: Going, uh, I exist in theory, but will I release?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, no!
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh no.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're not giving a reason for the delay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Although the theories are that it's licensing problems and PlayStation Network issues.
[SPEAKER_06]: But the Euro version will be out on time.
[SPEAKER_08]: This kind of makes me sad because I was looking forward to that whole YouTube-y channel that they were going to be doing with SingStar and I was going to tape Loki and Secret singing Britney Spears or something and then put that up for the internet to see and they would have loved it.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, damn it, when we made the tingle bet, we should have made the tingle bet around SingStar.
[SPEAKER_08]: Instead of Loki setting an eye of judgment on fire in a match with Bobby, what we should have done is we should have made him do something on SingStar and then upload it to the network.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know it would have been the number one video of all time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, you know, we still have I'm Staying In.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know, but that's like last year's joke.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, it's three years ago's joke.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what, though?
[SPEAKER_06]: At E3, I really liked SingStar because I had some random guy come up and we were singing...
[SPEAKER_06]: Motorhead at E3.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, they have the expandable store, so you could get probably tons of stuff there.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think everyone can get their emo on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, I'm sure there's one of those bands you can get your emo on.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have a video of Megzi singing that from her cell phone, so I think you would enjoy that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Megzi is very much now obsessed with My Chemical Romance.
[SPEAKER_08]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: She has the emo kid haircut now.
[SPEAKER_08]: She might be the first lesbian I've ever met who's obsessed with My Chemical Romance.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't... Usually, like... Oh, second lesbian.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry, Chris.
[SPEAKER_08]: What about, like... I thought lesbians listened to, like, Melissa Etheridge and Katie Lang.
[SPEAKER_08]: And, yeah, that I Kissed a Girl song and Sarah McLachlan.
[SPEAKER_08]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_08]: What happened to Lilith Fair?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, well, most people think that a lot of gay guys don't play video games, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the webcam can catch that look.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, what can we say?
[SPEAKER_08]: We're special here at Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Very special.
[SPEAKER_08]: We are special because we're getting back into the interview habit and getting some people on our program coming on here and talking about the latest.
[SPEAKER_08]: As you know, we here at Orange Lounge Radio have a strange fascination with the lolcats.
[SPEAKER_08]: So if you were listening a few weeks ago, you know that the advertisements for Geometry Wars Galaxies gave us a good laugh.
[SPEAKER_08]: We knew we had to get them on the show to talk to them a little bit more about the ads and more importantly the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: And guess what?
[SPEAKER_08]: We got them.
[SPEAKER_08]: Craig Howard is a game manager for Bizarre Creations and worked on not only Geometry Wars Galaxies but Boom Boom Rocket.
[SPEAKER_08]: We were also joined during the interview by Ben Ward, Bizarre Creations community manager.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sadly they couldn't be here live due to the time delay because they're over in the UK but let's listen in on what they had to say earlier this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: How are you doing out there, Craig?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I'm doing well, thanks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just a little bit cold at the moment.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll see you here as well as Ben Ward as well from Bazaar.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, great.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, welcome, both of you guys, to the program.
[SPEAKER_08]: And, of course, there's a little bit of a delay here since we are talking from such across a great distance because you guys are based out over there in the UK, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it rained in Liverpool.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll do that at the moment.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just great.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know, who came up with that idea?
[SPEAKER_08]: Was it Roger Sierra?
[SPEAKER_03]: It was just some crazy sort of idea that Sierra guys came up with, and it sort of went with the crazy commercial that we were running just before that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did you see the TV advert with all the guys dressed up as drum tour shapes?
[SPEAKER_08]: I did, and that's available on the internet, on the website, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that's one of my favorite songs you guys are using in the background for that advertisement.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a cover of a They Might Be Giants song, and so that's hilarious.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, you got it.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that was just something that the guys at Sierra came up with and they literally just wanted to make it a little bit quirky and a little bit sort of unusual and pull the sort of audience in that you wouldn't normally get in a Drunk Toys game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I mean, we did, one of the good things is it's not just like a sci-fi style advertising campaign of the guys at Drunk Toys.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's very interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: It tries to get more people interested in looking at the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, and it strangely seems to fit, you know, when you're hearing about Triangle Man and there actually are little, you know, triangle things that you're fighting in the game and everything, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, totally.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, we couldn't really make it too serious because that's not really what John Troll is about.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's about having fun with your friends and sort of really getting stuck into a fun arcade game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not about realistically fighting geometric shapes in outer space or something, you know, so it's all about having fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: Absolutely, I agree.
[SPEAKER_08]: It is all about having fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tell me about, you know, Geometry Wars started as a part of Project Gotham Racing, turns into this spin-off game that's hugely successful on Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_08]: Where did the decision come to take the game, the series, from the Xbox Live or the Xbox platform over to the Nintendo platform as a standalone series?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I mean, one of the things with Geometry Wars is it's always kind of used to test code as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: And when...
[SPEAKER_02]: We got the dev kits for Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: We started to have an experiment.
[SPEAKER_02]: Obviously, people started playing it and then our ideas were going.
[SPEAKER_02]: Initially, there was no channel.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was no WiiWare or anything like that for the DS or Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we thought if we were going to take it across into these platforms, what would we do?
[SPEAKER_02]: How would we get it to make it feel worthwhile on those platforms?
[SPEAKER_02]: It just seemed like a fun challenge.
[SPEAKER_02]: The controls are interesting
[SPEAKER_02]: Some people don't believe that it'll work well, but until you actually play the games and nunchuck, it just feels so much... It's different, but it still feels really good and fun and involved when you play the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it wasn't really sort of a eureka, hey, let's do Geometry Wars on the Wii or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: It just sort of built up when we saw the new platforms and we saw what they were capable of, and somebody sort of said...
[SPEAKER_03]: It'd be kind of cool if we put Geometry Wars on here.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we did, and then it built up and built up, and then we got the guys at Sierra involved, and they brought Kuju in, and it's just sort of built up into a full game over time.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did you guys put motion control in the game?
[SPEAKER_08]: I haven't really been able to get a sense of that from what I've read initially.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is there motion?
[SPEAKER_08]: Did you guys incorporate the Wii motion controls in the game?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I mean, what you do is you use the... You point with the wand, and you use the nunchuck to... to...
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry, I'm full of a cold at the moment.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's all very difficult to speak.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've got the controls working like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: It works a little bit like a keyboard and mouse in the way that the controls work.
[SPEAKER_02]: It does feel really nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: And obviously on the DS we support the stylus.
[SPEAKER_08]: Very cool, alright, so you're kind of like aiming either with the Wiimote or the stylus in the case of the DS version and then moving with the nunchuck or the directional pad That's right, yeah
[SPEAKER_08]: I think, well, I mean, the DS obviously hasn't gone anything like that, and the amount of fans...
[SPEAKER_02]: come back and say they'd love to be able to play the game on the move.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was really high, so it made sense to work on the DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Wii game, I mean, WiiWare still is quite a way off.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it's getting closer now.
[SPEAKER_02]: But at the time, yeah, it was a way for... It was just a way to take the game across to new people.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, we're not going for full retail price.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going for competitive price as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, you know, and you get a lot of gameplay there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I mean, it's a whole new campaign, though, since you've
[SPEAKER_02]: sort of like 60 versions of Geometry Wars.
[SPEAKER_02]: New enemies, you've got different sort of grid shapes, which make a huge difference in the way you play certain levels and the strategies.
[SPEAKER_02]: You've also got a drone, which is one of the big new additions.
[SPEAKER_02]: You've got an autonomous drone who, over the game, you build experience on this drone, you can nurture it to get new skills that can give you more battle strategies when you play the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a lot more there.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's also got the original retro involved in there as well for fans of the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: And also the big one is we've got multiplayer as well, which is also a nice new addition to the series.
[SPEAKER_03]: We did sort of see those questions coming when we first sort of came up with this whole concept.
[SPEAKER_03]: We did think that, hey, how are we going to justify charging however amount of money to buy this game?
[SPEAKER_03]: And, you know, we've really thrown in a hell of a lot of gameplay to make it worthwhile for people.
[SPEAKER_03]: We don't want anyone to feel ripped off once they've bought the game, but I don't think they will because, as Craig says, there's absolutely loads of content in there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I mean, if you have the
[SPEAKER_02]: There's quite a few ways of interconnecting the two platforms work.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you have both versions of the game, you can unlock an extra solar system within the game with new unique maps and battles.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's a reward people have brought on both platforms.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, if you've just got the Wii version or just the DS version, you can upload the whole retro evolved to your DS or your friend's DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, you know, again, a lot more people play in the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the theory behind all of this.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, by doing that, you know, with one cartridge in the office, a lot of people can be playing multiplayer games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Things like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: We try to be as generous as we can with the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I noticed the Wi-Fi seal on the game too.
[SPEAKER_08]: Does that mean you've got the online leaderboards and that too?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: We support full online leaderboards.
[SPEAKER_02]: One of the caveats to the game was we wouldn't
[SPEAKER_02]: wouldn't do it if we couldn't support online leaderboards.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because no matter how good you are, you want to see how good you are against your friends and against everyone else in the world.
[SPEAKER_08]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, where do you guys see Geometry Wars going in the future?
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you think there's a possibility of something based on Geometry Wars waves if the Nintendo Wii version, DS versions are successful at continuing and growing the franchise on the Nintendo platforms?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I mean, Geometry Wars is something that is its own beast and it's moving on in its own...
[SPEAKER_02]: but there's definitely things that we're considering in the future and looking at at the moment.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's great to be very careful with what he says because I'm sort of holding a hammer over his head at the moment saying, we haven't announced this yet!
[SPEAKER_02]: We're always looking at expanding.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a big fan base to the game and we listen to our fans and we're trying to set aside them and get more people playing the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, best of luck to you guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hope the cats sell tons and tons of copies of Geometry Wars, because it certainly is, you know, Geometry Wars Retro was one of, definitely my favorite Xbox Live download titles, and you gotta love the cats advertising the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: You definitely know you can trust them.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I gotta ask you, since I understand, Craig, you're the game manager not only over Geometry Wars, but you also worked on Boom Boom Rocket, right?
That's right, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, there's more to come from the world of Boom Boom Rocket.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know exactly what I can say, what I can't, but...
[SPEAKER_03]: We've made additional content and hopefully it's going to be releasing.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's still all sorts of caveats that we need to sort out with the publisher and Xbox Live Marketplace and all that sort of stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: So hopefully there will be something but I don't want to commit to anything because I don't know the details to be honest.
[SPEAKER_08]: Understandable, I understand there's got to be secrets.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, thank you guys so much for being on the show today, but before I let you guys go, we always ask all our guests that come on the program, we want to know, how is your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_08]: What kind of video games have you been playing besides the ones at the office?
[SPEAKER_02]: I've been playing Halo 3, obviously.
[SPEAKER_02]: Halo 3, and I've been playing Boarded Out on the Dreamcast, because it's a great show.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've been playing Halo 3 as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: and I've just finished World in Conflict on PC.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's an awesome game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Really, really love that.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I think Halo 3 and then when Gotham hits the shelves in the UK, I'll be playing that some more as well and beating all of our community on that or losing horribly to all our community on that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sounds pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, I think the entire internet is playing Halo 3 right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I have to ask the question, definitive question on Halo 3.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you prefer co-op or competitive?
[SPEAKER_03]: Co-op.
[SPEAKER_03]: Competitive.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just hope you keep checking our website and see the stuff we're announcing and
[SPEAKER_02]: www.bizarrecreations.com
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks a lot.
[SPEAKER_08]: Cheers.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, thank you very much to those folks from Bizarre Creations for joining us.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was Craig Howard and Ben Ward.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I have to actually kind of give a little bit of personal apologies because, you know, the whole time zone thing, I said I would interview them at 2 o'clock their time.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I thought for some reason when I looked it up on the Internet, it said 7 a.m., but it actually ended up being 6 a.m.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I roll out of bed at like 6.30 and I check my email.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're like, we're waiting for you to call.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm like, oh, no.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: Awesome!
[SPEAKER_08]: Awesome, I get a mic.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyways, so yeah, some fun information other than bizarre stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Our friends over at All Games, of course, they have some ties with G4 and stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: And this all goes back to, of course, Video Games Live.
[SPEAKER_10]: And so Video Games Live, wonderful show.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's been...
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: And, of course, it's a little bit different than, say, your usual concerts.
[SPEAKER_10]: All video game music, all done by an orchestra.
[SPEAKER_10]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you're in the area of one of those concerts, definitely worth checking out.
[SPEAKER_08]: All righty.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, you know the game Rock Band?
[SPEAKER_08]: If you want to have a concert of your own, you've got to get this game Rock Band because it's going to have the keyboards and the vocals and tambourines because you can use the microphone as a tambourine.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, unfortunately, the only way you're going to be able to get this game is in a bundle form.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's going to be bundle only in the year 2007.
[SPEAKER_08]: You cannot get these separate peripherals separately.
[SPEAKER_08]: E.A.
[SPEAKER_08]: has been telling us that's what's been going on.
[SPEAKER_08]: And now it was confirmed for the public this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now what I'm thinking, maybe there was like a third party, like are third party controllers going to be out and available?
[SPEAKER_08]: Possibly.
[SPEAKER_08]: Of course, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, so maybe that's what it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: But as far as the official first party peripherals, unfortunately those are not going to be out until 2008.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry, guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it's going to cost you $170 to play a rock band unless you want to use your existing guitars or microphones.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, this one's sort of interesting to me, although it's interesting in a quite different way than probably how they're listing it.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a group of graduate students that have mapped video game controllers onto different types of wearable fabrics where you can give massages while playing video games.
[SPEAKER_06]: On their website, they give instructions on how to make one for yourself.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, and I want to watch the video on this, however it's not loaded up.
[SPEAKER_06]: And given that, you know, I am a massage therapist, I have definite reservations for how safe this is.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I know, from personal experience, if you do it wrong, you can fuck somebody up.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, that's why we have to go to school for however many hours and learn how to do it right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let me ask your professional opinion, quote-unquote, since you have, you know, gone to the school, gone to the training and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's a lot of people, though, that give the casual massages, you know, like in the privacy of their own home, like, ooh, baby, I could really use a massage right now, you know, and no training and that stuff, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: So as long as they're not applying a lot of pressure, though, as long as it's like a I don't know what I'm doing type massage, do you think it's okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, you can.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is just going from what they said in school.
[SPEAKER_06]: Touch is very important for people.
[SPEAKER_06]: and even if it's really light there's still a lot of um emotion that you can bring out in another person um a lot of uh if they've got say that they have a circulatory issue you can actually cause problems with that lymphatic problems you can move um the lymph in their skin um
[SPEAKER_06]: You have to be kind of careful.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, they actually have a full-on hospital-grade lymphatic massage.
[SPEAKER_06]: For example, a lot of women who've had mastectomies, they remove a lot of the lymph nodes.
[SPEAKER_06]: And so you'll see these deposits in their arms, under their armpits, from excess lymph drainage.
[SPEAKER_06]: And so you run into... Anyone who's not a professional...
[SPEAKER_06]: Tries to give, and it seems to me that for, to use a controller like this, they'd have to be using a bit of pressure, don't you think?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, they run into a lot of risk with, especially it seems to me they're doing around the center back, you're dealing with problems dealing with the spine.
[SPEAKER_11]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can get into some nerve damage.
[SPEAKER_08]: Everything, the way it connects, I would not agree with letting an unprofessional... I'm looking at the official website for this, massage-me.at is the official site for this.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't see anything on the front page about doctor tests or anything.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now granted, I have not, to this website's credit, because I don't want to misrepresent anything, I have not looked through and through all these different pages that are here, so I don't know if they have any type of...
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, the doctor says it's okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: But this looks like, you know, university students.
[SPEAKER_08]: To me, I'm looking at this university students idea of, you know, something innovative.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, yes, it's innovative.
[SPEAKER_08]: But could it be dangerous, possibly?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm checking out their thanks.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm trying to look at their blog.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, their thanks didn't say any doctor.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's nothing on here about being an actual professional massage therapist.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm looking at...
[SPEAKER_06]: They're very true.
[SPEAKER_06]: Massage is very good for you.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know this from experience, but at the same point, if they're not professional, they don't have anything on their listing, any kind of credentials, I would not condone having this type of thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I mean, you know, and to these guys' credit, you know, I don't want to, again, misrepresent it or whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: It seems like a really interesting idea, and, you know, certainly they're thinking outside the box, but just for their own sake, I hope they've consulted a doctor on it, because I don't see anything on the website.
[SPEAKER_06]: They don't really have to consult a doctor, just consult another massage therapist.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm confused.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you do the massage on somebody?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or on the person?
[SPEAKER_06]: They're wearing this jacket that has the contacts in it.
Oh.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: Go through the jacket.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would not.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, there's actually a list on here that's telling you how to do it, but they're not doing it right.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're doing it wrong.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, if you want more information on that, it's called Massage Me.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we don't want to take too much time talking about it because we're not a massage podcast.
[SPEAKER_06]: I do not condone this.
[SPEAKER_06]: And on top of that, I'm actually going to be referring this site to the director of my school.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because this is actually potentially very dangerous.
[SPEAKER_10]: Narc.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_10]: So... Konami's made a little boo-boo.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or somebody has made a little boo-boo as far as advertising the brand new Castlevania Dracula X Chronicles.
[SPEAKER_10]: Unfortunately, the Belmonts have now become the Beaumonts.
[SPEAKER_10]: So... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a different family that's destroying Dracula.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just, you know, quite a coincidence that their names are so close together.
[SPEAKER_10]: And of course, there's been, you know, mistakes in ads before, including an ad for Tony Hawk's Downhill Jam, which was advertised as being on the Sony Wii.
[SPEAKER_10]: So... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Mistakes happen.
[SPEAKER_10]: Much like the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: The proofreaders out there are getting fired as we speak.
[SPEAKER_08]: What can we say?
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, um...
[SPEAKER_08]: The Gods and Heroes MMO is on indefinite hiatus.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: FU goes to the security at my work for saying, oh, there's nothing we can do.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which was bullshit.
[SPEAKER_06]: Pure and utter stinky bullshit.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I am going to go back and take a photo of the license tag of that car.
[SPEAKER_06]: Say they can't find them?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, fuck you.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can find them easily.
[SPEAKER_06]: I saw them just the other day, and I have a very good camera.
[SPEAKER_06]: I am not going to stop.
[SPEAKER_06]: Stop.
[SPEAKER_06]: Until justice is served.
[SPEAKER_08]: Judge Jamie's on the case.
[SPEAKER_06]: And if they decide to do nothing else, I'm going to address it with our CEO about how ineffectual our security is.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sorry to hear that follow-up.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was a kind of screwed-up story you told last week on the show, so that's kind of unfortunate.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: F that.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because remember, when I have my mindset to something, I get results.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anything else?
[SPEAKER_06]: Fuck a whole bunch of that shit!
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_10]: Um... I guess, fuck you, the fact that there's not a lot of good games out right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, it's a bit of a lull until, like, next few weeks when there's a ton of shit coming out, so... I need more stuff to play.
[SPEAKER_10]: I need more time to play it in, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll go next, and then we'll go to Puppy and Chris.
[SPEAKER_08]: My FU of the week obviously goes to the sad state of disrepair this show is in tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have no idea what's going on, but between the audio problems and now we have our internet problems that we don't have the live listeners right now, we're pretty much doing Part B for tape this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's like poltergeist is in the house tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know what the hell is going on.
[SPEAKER_08]: I apologize to the listeners.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know what's up.
[SPEAKER_08]: Shit happens, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: What can you expect?
[SPEAKER_08]: You get what you pay for, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a free program.
[SPEAKER_08]: What can you say?
[SPEAKER_08]: Damn straight.
[SPEAKER_08]: We try our best.
[SPEAKER_08]: We gotta keep it moving.
[SPEAKER_09]: We do better than Yaris.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, that's true.
[SPEAKER_08]: We do a better job at it than Yaris.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, Puppy, your FU's.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, let's see.
[SPEAKER_09]: Comcast gets one for internet going down at my apartment earlier today.
[SPEAKER_09]: And... Wow, I... Otherwise, I had a good week.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's a surprise.
[SPEAKER_08]: FU to you for having such a good week, bastard.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sucks to be you, then.
[SPEAKER_08]: Chris, your FU of the week.
[SPEAKER_04]: My FU of the week goes to my dad's girlfriend.
[SPEAKER_04]: She needs to know that she's 33 now, and not 13.
[SPEAKER_04]: It needs to kind of take some responsibility for her fucking actions.
[SPEAKER_04]: And also, this is the biggest one, needs to realize...
[SPEAKER_04]: that if you cannot accept the consequences of having a child, then don't get knocked up in the first place.
[SPEAKER_04]: She literally told me, and I quote, because I told everyone that I'm moving to Wisconsin in March.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, you cannot... She's Japanese, by the way.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not trying to make fun of her.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is exactly how she sounds.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, you cannot move to... You have to move here and take care of our babies.
[SPEAKER_04]: Elise, it's the parents' job to take care of the babies.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, being a parent is a full-time job.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah!
[SPEAKER_04]: No shit, Sherlock!
[SPEAKER_04]: God!
[SPEAKER_04]: I seriously thought, think, she thinks that I was going to stay there and take care of their little bundle of joy.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I'm going to be a big sister and all, but I ain't taking care of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It ain't my responsibility.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's just like, she seriously acts like she's 13.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know what my dad sees in her.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think he's having a midlife crisis.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's like 53.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is the level of stupid She got in a car crash the other week
[SPEAKER_04]: and they, everyone who was involved in the car accident got her information, got everything they needed to get.
[SPEAKER_04]: She didn't get their names even.
[SPEAKER_04]: She didn't get anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: There was nothing that she took away from this car crash except excuses.
[SPEAKER_04]: And of course it's her fault because she's the one who crashed into them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Damn woman.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's going to do it for the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Unfortunately, the Poltergeist is still affecting our network.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're still not live.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bummer.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know, it's like Halloween.
[SPEAKER_08]: This place is haunted.
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, thank you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Chris got the little picture of the kitty.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wait, I'll fix it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just what I need.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, maybe the mailbag will fix it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because if this keeps up, unfortunately, we're not going to be able to get to Skype tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I know some folks wanted to call in and do some game reviews.
[SPEAKER_08]: But at least there's the old mailbag.
[SPEAKER_08]: And when you email us at mailbag at orangelaunchradio.com, it's practically the old-fashioned way of interacting with a podcast at this point.
[SPEAKER_08]: But when the newfangled stuff breaks, we turn to the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_08]: So mailbag at orangelaunchradio.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura is going to open it up and pick some of her favorites right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm tangled up.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't do it by myself.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, listen.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is time for the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, um, first thing actually comes from Rob with two B's.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, he sent a link to a story, and this is very Darwin award-y.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, in Moscow, a ten-year-old committed suicide after parents banned computer games.
[SPEAKER_06]: And just to, uh, his name was, um, Andrei Smirnoff, which, I'm not gonna say anything.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um,
[SPEAKER_06]: who was a class 3 student jumped to his death after his parents were blaming his bad conduct in school and poor performance in class on video games and he had made a comment about it in his diary and then jumped out of a window so I'm like yeah that just means that your kid was fucked in the head also and to continue with his email
[SPEAKER_06]: Also, I loved your argument about microtransactions and other poorly named events.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you really want to draw a line objectively, a transaction, in quotes, is a payment in monetary units.
[SPEAKER_06]: A microtransaction would be a one-one-thousandth of a transaction, or less than one penny.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you remember, the office space embezzlement scenario was based upon taking the money less than one cent off every transaction and adding them up.
[SPEAKER_06]: So in that case, and if you are using pure terminology, a microtransaction would have to consist of less than one one-thousandth of a penny.
[SPEAKER_06]: So therefore, the term microtransaction is actually an incorrect term.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was right.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not going to have this stupid argument again.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, that's my whole thing that I hate about modern language use is this whole let's just completely define everything but use really bad definitions.
[SPEAKER_06]: LOL.
[SPEAKER_06]: ROTFL.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, that's not what I'm talking about.
[SPEAKER_06]: Preboarding.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, putting unnecessary prefixes to words.
[SPEAKER_06]: George Carlin did point that out, didn't he?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: But then again, there's also literal and, you know, applied means of things.
[SPEAKER_10]: For example, micromachines were not one thousandth the size of a car.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, I think that they were.
[SPEAKER_10]: They were smaller.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that they were one thousandth.
[SPEAKER_06]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: Shit.
[SPEAKER_10]: They were smaller.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's all that matters.
[SPEAKER_10]: No one's going to do the fucking scale shit.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is not model building.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: No fucking train sets here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Would you say this compares to how it works?
[SPEAKER_08]: There's an item on the menu called the cheese quesadilla.
[SPEAKER_08]: When a quesadilla literally means, you know, cheese.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it's like you're ordering a peanut peanut butter sandwich or something.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're ordering a cheese cheese sandwich.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or it's like ordering chai tea.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because chai means tea.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, you know, I think that it's more or less... You know, everybody in the world is stupid.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's accommodate the language to everybody's stupidity.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't like to...
[SPEAKER_06]: I do not like to live in a world where...
[SPEAKER_06]: She did show me the one I have in my cubicle with a picture of Captain Kirk saying, James T. Kirk, I'm sorry, I can't hear you over the sound of how awesome I am.
[SPEAKER_08]: Emails?
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: This one comes from One Night Stands.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hello, I just recently started to listen to your podcast and I must say that I really like them as they don't bore me, except for the Onion Audio and Video podcast.
[SPEAKER_06]: A few times on the show, Sky, I think I'm still trying to figure out the difference between the two guys, has mentioned that he's gay.
[SPEAKER_06]: The first time I thought he was just joking and then I was listening to your most recent one where Skye and Jamie went to the movies and started talking about the sanctity of marriage and then running off to Vegas to get married to immediately divorce.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just something about being gay.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I know it's tacky to dig into other people's lives and find out what their sexual orientation is.
[SPEAKER_06]: I long for the days when people like Perez Hilton were branded with a scarlet letter, probably G for gossip.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I've been wondering, are you gay?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm very happy to be on this program.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that it's great to hear that one of the three main people is.
[SPEAKER_06]: As a gay gamer, I think it's great to hear.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's great to see celebrities being out and proud and know the fan base is not swayed by their sexual preference.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sky, DarkSakura, Loki, keep up the good work.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is that person insinuating I'm a celebrity?
[SPEAKER_08]: Rad!
[SPEAKER_08]: Ooh, ego plus plus.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I look forward to hearing your next podcast.
[SPEAKER_06]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_06]: My handle is a Simpsons reference.
[SPEAKER_06]: Everyone thinks it's a sex thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's one night stands.
[SPEAKER_08]: One night stands.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now that, usually that's what you'd find on gay.com, one night stands.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, no, I'm Sky, the voice you hear right now is, or Rob, I don't really, not a lot of people call me Sky anymore, but Rob, and yeah, I'm gay.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, but that's not what the show's all about.
[SPEAKER_08]: The show's about video games, but I understand.
[SPEAKER_08]: I totally understand where you're coming from.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because sometimes, I can kind of speak from experience, it's kind of hard to find, gay gamers are in an interesting niche, I think, because in gaming culture, you know, obviously thanks to the Xbox Lives of the world, where, you know, fag, fag, fag,
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_08]: Click, click, mute, warn.
[SPEAKER_08]: Love Halo 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's because Rob is an attention whore.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, and then in the other side of it.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you have the gaming culture frowns on gays to some extent.
[SPEAKER_08]: Obviously not everybody.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a few bad apples ruining the barrel.
[SPEAKER_08]: But then you have in gay culture...
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, like, oh, you mean you don't shop at, you know, Nordstrom's and you don't listen to Madonna?
[SPEAKER_08]: And why don't you go to the club with us?
[SPEAKER_08]: Why do you have to stay home and play games?
[SPEAKER_08]: Come on, let's go out, you know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's go get Madonna tickets for $250 and, you know, let's do crack.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know, you know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not, again.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not saying all gays are like that, but unfortunately, you know, I felt that kind of judgment from some of those very superficial people that, you know, oh, you play games?
[SPEAKER_08]: That's like a, you know, that's a little kid thing, or that's not a gay thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, you know, who's to say what is what?
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, people like what they like.
[SPEAKER_08]: So anyway, you know, and I don't like to usually advertise the fact I'm gay on the program because this is not the, oh my god, the really big gay podcast about video games!
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay guys, I cannot wait to review Gears of War because that is hot.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, you missed Rob singing show tunes last week.
[SPEAKER_08]: We already busted out the show tunes last week.
[SPEAKER_08]: But no, in all seriousness, again, it's just that, you know, it is what it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm gay, but I also, I've been playing video games a lot longer than I've been dating men.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's put it that way, I guess.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Chris is a lesbian.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I'm a very big dyke.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dyke Power, Yo.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like boobies.
[SPEAKER_08]: But most of all, we like games, so that's what it really boils down to.
[SPEAKER_08]: And boobies.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like boobies too, so that's I guess something everybody... I think it's a unanimous vote in this room that boobies are great.
[SPEAKER_08]: Boobies, yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right, all in favor of boobies?
[SPEAKER_01]: Aye.
[SPEAKER_01]: All opposed?
[SPEAKER_10]: I was too late on the four boobies.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: We have unanimous...
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know what else to say to that email.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to have to tell William that somebody couldn't figure it out.
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_08]: Here's the thing, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: Perez Hilton totally sold out.
[SPEAKER_08]: He used to be cool a year ago, but totally sold out.
[SPEAKER_08]: You've got to find some new blogs to read, dude.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: Perez Hilton kind of sold out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Drawing coke coming out of people's noses isn't funny anymore, sorry to say.
[SPEAKER_08]: Perez Hilton?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, that website.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Gossip Blogger.
Oh!
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: Next email.
[SPEAKER_06]: Next email.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: God, this is such awful spelling.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sorry, whoever you are.
[SPEAKER_06]: Lycan.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: One more thing on the gay thing because I forgot to mention this.
[SPEAKER_08]: Praise and happy thoughts and thank yous to the folks who make websites for the...
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_08]: Praise to those people that make the niches on the internet for those kind of people to find each other.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I'm just talking in general too, not just gay and gaming, but all types of minorities.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, hooray.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now we can move on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey Orange Lounge, I'm kind of a new listener, but I already say you guys rock.
[SPEAKER_06]: I do have a question.
[SPEAKER_06]: You talk about Final Fantasy a lot, but I've never heard you talk about Final Fantasy X. Is there a reason, as I've been playing it a lot recently, this is from Lycan.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wait, am I on crack or wasn't there an email last week where we talked about Final Fantasy X?
[SPEAKER_08]: I swear to God it came up like last week or two weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think we did talk about Final Fantasy X. Maybe this person's behind in their podcast listening, so we'll give them a bye, but... That and Final Fantasy X's fucking old.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, if we're on like Final Fantasy XII now.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, seriously.
[SPEAKER_10]: Played that game like years ago.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was an awesome game, but it was years ago.
[SPEAKER_06]: X was great, but we've moved on.
[SPEAKER_10]: X2, not so great.
[SPEAKER_01]: We're with...
[SPEAKER_06]: This fandom is still on seven.
[SPEAKER_08]: The fandom for ten.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, you go to any, you know, anime convention, guaranteed you're going to see a Tubby Yuna.
[SPEAKER_08]: Somewhere.
[SPEAKER_08]: Always.
[SPEAKER_08]: So the fandom is never going to die.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then, you know, a Waka with a pooch.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, it's... You know what really bothers me is the pregnant fetish fan art.
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's on DeviantArt.
[SPEAKER_08]: All over DeviantArt.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: When I talked about the whole, like, minority subculture thing, maybe there are a few exceptions.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, they have a big, big subculture of people who like, what is it, inflated art?
[SPEAKER_04]: Where basically they make girls.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's mostly girls.
[SPEAKER_04]: With boobs that are three times the size of their bodies?
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they're, like, they're big, they're fat, like, way more physically than they should be.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, in any way, shape, or form.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not physically possible for these people to breathe.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think I need to rethink my argument on the counterculture thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe I need to rethink those kudos a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm so hypocritical because I sit there and I go, I don't have to look at that art, but then I see it on the favorites page and I just go, that shit should not be here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because it's so fucking... You know, most of it is really bad, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, these people can't draw.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the only reason that it ends up on the favorite page is because some... There's a bunch of morons out there who are wanking to this.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's disgusting.
[SPEAKER_09]: Are you sure they just aren't out of proportion just because they are bad artists?
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, sometimes I wonder.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, they accidentally got it really big.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, they draw fat very well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I can show you.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's really disgusting.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I can draw fat.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a circle with a stick.
[SPEAKER_09]: for leg, stick for arm, stick for neck, circle for head.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, like the chicken Willy Wonka when she ate the blueberry thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Next email, please.
[SPEAKER_08]: From Final Fantasy X to snozzberries.
[SPEAKER_08]: Look, you're going to ask us a question like that, that's what you're going to get.
[SPEAKER_08]: What do you think of Final Fantasy X?
[SPEAKER_08]: Snozzberries.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey OLR, it's Nintendo Maniac 64.
[SPEAKER_06]: I noticed something this week with the update for Kirby's Final Smash on the Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_06]: Brawl site.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you compare the bottom of the Japanese webpage to the English or any other language page, you notice that the Japanese version has some kind of extra sound clip recording.
[SPEAKER_06]: Any idea what this might be?
[SPEAKER_06]: Unfortunately, since Rob's computer is the primary, we cannot correctly answer this question.
[SPEAKER_06]: So next!
[SPEAKER_08]: But I will hypothesize, since they're saying it's an audio thing, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: I will hypothesize.
[SPEAKER_08]: Perhaps it is a piece of work that has not been translated or brought over yet.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or simply it was just an oversight.
[SPEAKER_06]: If it's curvy, why would it have any words to it?
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess that's true.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it's just an oversight then.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think you're being a little tinfoil hat-ish.
[SPEAKER_08]: I wouldn't worry just yet.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it's just an oversight, so don't worry.
[SPEAKER_08]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's an example.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, my God!
[SPEAKER_08]: What the hell is that?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's actually a lot better than... There's a picture on DeviantArt, and it's on the favorites page, and it's actually a lot better than the most of the stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: At least this girl is somewhat in proportion, but Jesus Christ.
[SPEAKER_08]: She looks like a walrus.
[SPEAKER_08]: She looks like she's about ready to go goo-goo-ka-choo, okay, for one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, for B, did you ever see... And this is great radio, by the way, because I'm responding to a picture...
[SPEAKER_08]: And I'm totally being a hypocrite right now with this whole thing that I said, you know, oh, the countercultures are great.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not this.
[SPEAKER_08]: Everything I said earlier, this is not a part of that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do not want.
[SPEAKER_08]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_08]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, did you ever see that face as a death where the guy had elephantitis of the balls?
[SPEAKER_08]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's what her tits look like.
What?
[SPEAKER_08]: What website?
[SPEAKER_08]: Is it DeviantArt?
[SPEAKER_08]: DeviantArt.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you want to have a fun time?
[SPEAKER_04]: Go to deviantart.com and in the search, type inflation and just watch the funny shit happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: I swear, it's just like, people that should not be.
[SPEAKER_09]: It looks like a bunch of freaking world record tumors like I saw on Ripley's Believe It or Not.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or you know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't and go play video games instead.
[SPEAKER_08]: You'll thank us later.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh no.
[SPEAKER_08]: That can't be real.
[SPEAKER_08]: You have to show me.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's like somebody's Halloween costume.
[SPEAKER_08]: See, now that's funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: Somebody looks like she has beach balls for titties.
[SPEAKER_08]: Next email, please.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do not want.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey guys, I love the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just wanted to know if you've seen the masterpiece that is Dead Fantasy 1.
[SPEAKER_06]: If not, check it out now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Congrats on another milestone.
[SPEAKER_06]: 250 is certainly an accomplishment for an independent podcast.
[SPEAKER_06]: Pat yourselves on the ass.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for reading this.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's from Resimo.
[SPEAKER_10]: It has some really kick-ass stuff, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, they have a picture of, like, Cloud as a chick on a bike, and it looks really good.
[SPEAKER_10]: But definitely check out, like, you know, the Haloid and Dead Fantasy stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll have to show it in the studio after the show.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it's seriously some kick-ass wire foo shit that a lot of it borrowed heavily from The Matrix.
[SPEAKER_10]: But really awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: Check it out.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's it for the emails.
[SPEAKER_06]: How about something that has nothing to do with inflation?
[SPEAKER_08]: Chris, put the inflation away.
[SPEAKER_08]: Although seriously, part of me wants to make the album art for Orange Lounge Radio this week, one of those pictures.
[SPEAKER_08]: If there weren't copyright issues, I'd totally do it.
[SPEAKER_08]: But anyway, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Shout, Chris.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not looking at inflation.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's his fault.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, it's your turn.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyways, let's get this train back in the tracks here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Um, anyways, um, Games for Windows Live is getting an update in November as well, and of course, you know, normally Xbox Live, those are spring and fall updates, so it sounds around the, about around the time, um, we'll be seeing an update for Live as well on 360, but Games for Windows Live will become 1.2, and with that, there's gonna be some improvements to, um,
[SPEAKER_10]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: And according to the site this originally ran on, quote, it's stylistically and gameplay-wise, the game has abandoned the dark edginess of the last two titles in favor of a fantastical cross between the Sands of Time, Ico, and Zelda.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know, when you put it that way, it sounds a little fanboyish to me, but you never know.
[SPEAKER_10]: At the same time, though, that's about the time I think that the Prince of Persia movies are supposed to be coming out as well.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, obviously the Prince of Persia series is not a dead series.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, big fat duh that there's another game coming out.
[SPEAKER_08]: But is it a prequel?
[SPEAKER_08]: That could be interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: And who knows?
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe it's actually the movie version.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because maybe they're going in a different direction with the movie.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe it isn't based on existing storyline and these games are there to support the movie.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_08]: Theories abound everywhere.
[SPEAKER_08]: But we don't know for sure until next year.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, this is...
[SPEAKER_06]: Fairly interesting as far as something that may or may not be.
[SPEAKER_06]: But one of SNK's, to me, one of the games that I like the best from them, Magician Lord, has an ESRB rating.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it most likely will not be only for Japan.
[SPEAKER_06]: We could see it coming out on the virtual console for Wii very soon.
[SPEAKER_10]: Fuck yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's what I got to say about that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Basically, you go through all these different levels that can turn your character into different types of, I guess, elemental type characters.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, it's a pretty good game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Magician Lord is pretty hardcore awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyways, other sorts of awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: There was before a problem with the Bioshock PC version, of course.
[SPEAKER_10]: People getting pissed off that you can only have three different activations available for that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, now they have a brand new tool that's been released officially.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's an activation revoke tool and will allow you to revoke some of the activations that you have so that if you want to install on a different PC...
[SPEAKER_10]: You can do that.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's basically allow you to race and reload copies of Bioshock onto your PC as many times as you want without using up one of your activation tokens provided you don't make any major changes to your current hardware.
[SPEAKER_10]: And, of course, the tool is downloadable on the Cult of Rapture website.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: At least that they're trying to fix some stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you for watching.
[SPEAKER_08]: See you next time.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, I want to call in sometime, but I'm just not around on Sunday nights.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a bad time for me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't forget, we have voicemail there at 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_08]: So if you wanted to call in tonight, call in and leave a voicemail, and we'll try to play it on next week's show.
[SPEAKER_08]: The only reason we haven't been playing voicemails lately is because we haven't been getting a lot.
[SPEAKER_08]: But if we get some good ones, we'll definitely play them.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just my only advice, try to just keep it under two minutes because when you go on and ramble and ramble, it makes us want to play it less because, you know,
[SPEAKER_08]: The show is for us to ramble and ramble.
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: We want you guys to definitely have a say as well.
[SPEAKER_08]: So the Skype line is there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or our email, mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: And apologies to our live listeners who got cut off tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: What can I say?
[SPEAKER_08]: The show was just all kinds of broken tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's like this whole year old now quit curse.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know what else to say.
[SPEAKER_08]: But we will go around and get some last minute stories, of which I'm sure Loki's got to have some.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyways, let's see here.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's some interesting pictures coming out from Postal 3.
[SPEAKER_10]: One of which features a new gun, apparently, that's going to be in the game, which features a guy's hand up a badger's ass, and he's firing a badger gun, apparently.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's like Laser Badger or something like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: So this is, and I've got to show this in studio here real quick.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, you don't have to.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, I do.
[SPEAKER_10]: Destructoid ran a little interview based on that, and I've got to say, I was already going to buy this game
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm thinking I may buy two copies of this game because it's fucking awesome looking.
[SPEAKER_10]: Go runny with scissors.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, well, they'll be on the badger's ass.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, I got to respect the fact that they leave nothing to chance as far as offending people.
[SPEAKER_10]: Good luck getting this past the ESRB, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's all I got to say.
[SPEAKER_10]: Other fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's going to be a new tool that's... I can't... Hold on.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just have to say I can't wait for the YouTube where somebody's going to film themselves doing this to the badger, badger, badger, badger, badger, badger, badger, badger, badger, mushroom, mushroom.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, seriously, let's take some over-unders on how long before those YouTubes show up.
[SPEAKER_08]: I say they show up before the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now that I've said that, somebody's going to take that picture and put it on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_08]: Send us the link when you get it done.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now, also, Mac's console has some pictures up of a brand new device.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's an adapter to let you use HDMI inputs on your first generation Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_10]: Of course, the ones without HDMI.
[SPEAKER_10]: And this is from the XCM 1080i HDMI.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's shaped like a disc, and it plugs into the back of your...
[SPEAKER_10]: 360, where the normal AV stuff goes.
[SPEAKER_10]: And we'll do HDMI out, and we'll also do DVI out.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that's pretty fucking awesome that that's going to be available.
[SPEAKER_10]: The other thing, there's a Phantom Hourglass DS bundle that's appeared on internet retail sites.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is for the UK, so it's a nice silver color with, looks like some silk screens of Zelda...
[SPEAKER_10]: from Phantom Hourglass and also the Zelda Phantom Hourglass logo.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that's kind of neat and that's probably coming soon.
[SPEAKER_10]: And also if you are pre-ordering Super Mario Galaxy and you want a free pre-order coin, just make sure you pre-order your copies at Amazon, Circuit City, Fred Meyers, Fry's Electronics, Game Crazy GameStop, Kmart, and many others.
[SPEAKER_10]: Pretty much every single store out there, so
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: And finally, and I'm sure you're going to hear this about the time that this podcast is released, some wonderful information, which was going to be for our live listeners, but since they're not with us, I'll just save it for the Part B. There is, each year, the ESA does kind of a, I guess a...
[SPEAKER_10]: Charity Drive with games.
[SPEAKER_10]: Last year, Sony got together and put some games, a PlayStation 2 collection together with a couple games.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now, and this will be announced officially on Tuesday, and it's actually what's going to be is three games.
[SPEAKER_10]: Robbie Bach of the ESA will announce the Holiday Bundle.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's going to feature three Xbox 360 games, including Cars, what was his...
[SPEAKER_10]: Car's Open Season and Fusion Frenzy 2, all for $29.99.
[SPEAKER_10]: And the proceeds will go to basically helping the ESA.
[SPEAKER_10]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_10]: To deliver this program, the game publishers unite together to work through issues such as waiving royalties, packaging costs, etc.
[SPEAKER_10]: in order to maximize charitable contribution.
[SPEAKER_10]: Last year, Sony delivered a bundle for the ESA, and this year, Microsoft has agreed to create a three-game bundle to sell at retail with the proceeds going to the ESA charity.
[SPEAKER_10]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: Then you'll probably see that in stores on the 23rd.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I guess that's it for the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Unfortunately, our stream never came back up.
[SPEAKER_08]: So if one of you that's still in chat, DarkSakura, I don't know, just let them know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Unfortunately, we've wrapped the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: And unfortunately, I'll just have to come back next week or download the show on Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_08]: But we thank them for sticking out, any of those folks that were still around, hoping we'd come back up.
[SPEAKER_08]: But unfortunately, the computer is screwed up.
[SPEAKER_08]: And now I have this dialog box on my screen that will not go away.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is just, oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_08]: Somebody put a gun in this computer.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's done.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we're going to go around and get everybody's final thoughts and wrap up tonight's broken show.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know about the other two games.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyhow, let's go around and get everybody's final thought.
[SPEAKER_08]: Chris, thank you very much for being here, even if now you think you're some type of bad luck charm.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I don't care.
[SPEAKER_08]: We still love having you here.
[SPEAKER_08]: And come back.
[SPEAKER_08]: Damn it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I am.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I didn't tell you.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to Disneyland next week.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I'll be thinking of you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Whore.
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: Get lots of pictures on the teacups.
[SPEAKER_08]: I will.
[SPEAKER_08]: Me and Extifer are going.
[SPEAKER_04]: Aw.
[SPEAKER_04]: That'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: He hasn't been in a long, long time.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I'm going to make him go on that Ferris wheel that sways back and forth.
[SPEAKER_08]: He's going to cry.
[SPEAKER_08]: It'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I won't go on that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yeah, you're probably going to see a lot more of me until March because I'm going to be moving out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: And hopefully you'll be able to hear me on my podcast.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, which just goes to further prove everybody has a freaking podcast.
[SPEAKER_08]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_08]: We were first.
[SPEAKER_08]: God damn it.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you very much for being here.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Puppy, thanks for coming back.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I'm glad you got to talk more this week, even if sort of, even though there was like
[SPEAKER_08]: Only two microphones, but what can you do?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's like your shirt says, Booched.
[SPEAKER_08]: The show is Booched.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is that a Puzzle Pirates thing?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, it is a Puzzle Pirates shirt.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow, what does Booched mean?
[SPEAKER_08]: You screwed up?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, that's basically what it means.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is like the worst rating you get on a puzzle.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, that was a very appropriate shirt to wear to the show.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have to see.
[SPEAKER_10]: There was another article I was reading on Destructoid that they had...
[SPEAKER_10]: is this game called Animal Kaiser and it's basically where you can pit different animals against each other in like deathmatch in the arcade.
[SPEAKER_10]: So they have snake versus black panther and Indian cobra.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it's awesome because you can just pick all sorts of different animals to fight each other.
[SPEAKER_04]: I swear to God, just pick a black mom, we'll yield one every time.
[SPEAKER_04]: I swear to God, there's like an entire video game craze that is just dead set on pissing PETA off.
[SPEAKER_04]: And as far as I'm concerned, have at them.
[SPEAKER_04]: PETA can kiss my ass.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, PETA came back with Super Chick Sisters or whatever that was.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was actually kind of cute, I gotta say.
[SPEAKER_08]: But that was, again, I'm visiting... Oh, now what?
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, this will double as your final thought.
[SPEAKER_08]: They have a shark versus a lion.
[SPEAKER_10]: That is the coolest shit I have ever seen.
[SPEAKER_09]: I gotta see this here.
[SPEAKER_10]: They've got to have this in the United States.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know this is one of those quirky... Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: We need to see.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry, I gotta... Brother.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a shark and a freaking lion.
[SPEAKER_04]: The shark is out of water and is kicking the lion's ass.
[SPEAKER_04]: How is that possible?
[SPEAKER_04]: The fucking shark won!
[SPEAKER_08]: If this is why Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_08]: got delayed, then I'm okay with it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Seriously, the new third-party character is being announced.
[SPEAKER_01]: Shark and lion.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_06]: First of all, everyone's still PMing me.
[SPEAKER_06]: on chat.
[SPEAKER_06]: My final thought is bitches.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Referring to work.
[SPEAKER_08]: And my final thought is sorry the show is broken tonight and you get what you pay for.
[SPEAKER_08]: But thank you anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_08]: What do you mean I'm doing it wrong?
[SPEAKER_08]: Can we just stop the show now?
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you very much for tuning into and supporting independent podcasting and independent radio, even when it's as screwed up as this.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you like what you hear, since we do this for free, tell friends about the program.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tell enemies about the program.
[SPEAKER_08]: Leave us a five-star review on iTunes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Post us in your signature.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just spread the word.
[SPEAKER_08]: We need it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you guys very much.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll see you next week, and hopefully things will be in working order and not
[SPEAKER_00]: have a good week you've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production for more information on our live and podcast programs visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com see you next week