[SPEAKER_02]: Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition E3 2005 Special Friday Edition You're tuned in to the Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition, your podcast home for all the latest video game news and gamer chat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, here are your hosts, DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, here we are back with our final day here at E3.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I don't know if my co-hosts are feeling it like I am, but I think I'm ready for this show to be about over by now.
[SPEAKER_04]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_04]: You might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_04]: My co-hosts, Loki, the one and only.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_04]: And also DarkSakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_01]: I need a new body.
[SPEAKER_04]: So what do you think?
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you ready for this show to be over or what, Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, for those people at home that are probably yelling at us going, Dude, I would kill to be at E3 for anything, and you guys are bitching about having to be there for three whole days.
[SPEAKER_04]: What would you say?
[SPEAKER_04]: Why is it that you kind of get burned out on E3?
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, how about this?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll tell you what.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's say you're on the East Coast.
[SPEAKER_03]: Start walking to E3.
[SPEAKER_03]: Once you get there, now you know what it's like to be there for three days.
[SPEAKER_03]: Your feet hurt like a bitch, and you're bored out of your mind, and you're thinking...
[SPEAKER_03]: Why?
[SPEAKER_03]: Why is it three days long?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, it's just you walk around pretty much everything, and you've already seen everything.
[SPEAKER_03]: Unless you're in meetings all the time, like we aren't, you really see pretty much everything in about two days.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: I found more stuff today.
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, I made today my standing in line day.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I got in to see something I'm going to talk about momentarily on the show.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I went into the Sega Theater.
[SPEAKER_01]: Again, I'm going to talk about that later.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I got to get in and see things and I got into running into people who get me into other things.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: so I think that about sums it up for me but I know a lot of us got to do some cool things on this third day so I would typically do the three things but well I won't put a cap on it today let's just say share things with our audience that you think was cool today we'll start off with DarkSakura since I know she's got at least two things right there
[SPEAKER_01]: I went into the Sega Theater today, got to see the new Sonic game that they're doing.
[SPEAKER_01]: I believe it's for the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's pretty damn good looking, and it was a real-time demo.
[SPEAKER_01]: So he was playing it, one of the developers there was playing it as they were doing.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's that serial killer game, Conspiracy, I think that's what it's called.
[SPEAKER_01]: Condemned, I knew it was a con something.
[SPEAKER_01]: See, my brain's fried, it's the end of the con.
[SPEAKER_01]: um, The Condemned, that was pretty spooky, but it seemed sort of, hi, I'm a big ugly thing, I'm gonna hit you on the head with this hammer, BAM!
[SPEAKER_01]: Ow.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, that type of game.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then, um, there was, uh, there's that Full Auto game, now the Full Auto was pretty cool, it was sort of like, I'm going to run into this building, wait, nope, I didn't want to do that, Rewind, called the Unwreck, and then Drive Forward.
[SPEAKER_01]: Keep going, that was pretty cool, and also, uh,
[SPEAKER_01]: Met somebody.
[SPEAKER_01]: His name was Eric.
[SPEAKER_01]: If he's listening, I introduced him to the show, so hi.
[SPEAKER_01]: New person.
[SPEAKER_01]: In fact, to all of you people who I have met at the convention, if you're listening to us, hi.
[SPEAKER_01]: I also met one of Jason's friends.
[SPEAKER_01]: Randomly.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sitting on the floor at Squinnix.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I'll go into that later.
[SPEAKER_01]: At any rate, I couldn't get into Squinnix and they were out of tickets by the time I got up there, which was shitty!
[SPEAKER_01]: So I trotted on over and I tried to peek at the Activision stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was like, eh.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I kept going.
[SPEAKER_01]: Made it over to where the PS3 line was.
[SPEAKER_01]: And for being wrapped around the building, the wait was not as long as I thought it was going to be.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're saying, this is a three hour wait.
[SPEAKER_01]: I got there in 25 minutes and I was at the tail end.
[SPEAKER_01]: Um, they did some type of HDTV demo thing, and then they actually let you take you into another theater where you can sit for a little bit.
[SPEAKER_01]: And, uh, you, they showed what the system can do.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's rad.
[SPEAKER_01]: They built a city there on screen.
[SPEAKER_01]: Um, they also showed some of the games that are currently in development.
[SPEAKER_01]: They didn't list names of the games, but some of us could tell one of them was a new Tekken.
[SPEAKER_01]: They showed Jin up there with sweat coming out of his body.
[SPEAKER_01]: And this apparently is done in-game engine.
[SPEAKER_01]: One that looked like one of the Romance of the Three Kingdoms games.
[SPEAKER_01]: Some type of off-road game.
[SPEAKER_01]: This was a very destructive off-road game.
[SPEAKER_01]: It shows this one scene with a motorbike guy getting back up on his bike with a car about to land on him after an explosion.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was pretty intense.
[SPEAKER_01]: I got out.
[SPEAKER_01]: I see the PS3.
[SPEAKER_01]: took pictures of the PS3, which will be on orangeislandradio.com.
[SPEAKER_01]: The other cool thing is that I played more Nintendogs.
[SPEAKER_01]: I played Romancing Saga, and actually I got into H-Tech.
[SPEAKER_01]: That was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: Got to play a new game.
[SPEAKER_01]: For anyone who is an anime fan or big importer of RPGs, coming out on the PSP, I do believe you said winter, is Popokuros, which has been a pretty big series.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's a 2D RPG.
[SPEAKER_01]: It is the first true RPG for the system to be released in the States.
[SPEAKER_01]: So be on the lookout for that.
[SPEAKER_01]: And also got to see Formula Front Armored Core.
[SPEAKER_01]: That was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: Working on right now is Wild Arms Ultra F, which has actually been delayed by about five months, but it gives them time to tweak the translation.
[SPEAKER_01]: Also, RPG Maker 3.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now that, I have to say, I was very impressed with.
[SPEAKER_01]: The last RPG Maker, you know, I was kind of into that, and I was into the first one because I was one of those people that was petitioning for it to get off the Super Famicom and get over to the U.S.
[SPEAKER_01]: This one was pretty, pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, it's not like you're playing, you know, this little ghetto game that you just piece together with duct tape.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is fully rendered trees.
[SPEAKER_01]: You can paint your textures onto mountains and
[SPEAKER_01]: You choose what style your sprites are going to look like.
[SPEAKER_01]: You can choose, you know how on RPGs it has a picture of your character over the text box.
[SPEAKER_01]: You can do conversation characters and have them in an anime style or you can have them in a conventional American style.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: There was a game maker that was supposed to be coming out on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is this the game maker?
[SPEAKER_03]: This is on PS2.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's one coming out for the PSP and there's so many things they could do for this, but I know they're not going to because they just don't think ahead.
[SPEAKER_03]: For example, the PSP, you could have it where you could upload your own pictures or something like that from the internet or your own music or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: You make your own game and then distribute that game over the internet.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would be cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, you know, they're not going to think of that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think of that.
[SPEAKER_03]: They don't.
[SPEAKER_01]: They might have thought of it, but it might take money out of their pocket.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, Loki, what kind of stuff did you look at today?
[SPEAKER_03]: I looked at a few things.
[SPEAKER_03]: I went back for a second peek at... What was that?
[SPEAKER_03]: That one erotic whatever... Feel 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: Feel 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: The cyber sex game that dominated... Yeah, I had to show that to Jason today.
[SPEAKER_03]: Apparently, there's...
[SPEAKER_03]: Peripherals for this game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sex peripherals for this game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll leave it at that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Use your imagination, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_03]: Basically, folks, this is the definition of cybersex.
[SPEAKER_00]: That puts the Rez vibration machine to shame.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, this is a device that vibrates that's not going to be confused with a transvibrator.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's just let the audience use their imagination on that one, shall we?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's very phallic.
[SPEAKER_03]: So yeah, that's interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll have to check out the website later.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like how he's like, it's kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I'll check it later.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have to check it out.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have to research it on behalf of our listeners, of course.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not that you have any interest in this.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're just doing it in favor of the listeners, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: I honestly don't want to buy this.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is one of those games that's going to be weird because, you know, I can't go about normal methods of distribution for this game.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: But anyways, I got to finally, finally play in the group today on Rockstar's new... Yes, which is interesting because they weren't showing the game on Wednesday when we went by the booth the first time, but today they actually showed the game on PS2.
[SPEAKER_03]: In the group, and I got to test out Red Octane's new pads.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're the metal ones.
[SPEAKER_03]: and I have to say that both disappoint me very much.
[SPEAKER_03]: And guess what?
[SPEAKER_03]: I still have the same opinion about In The Groove.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's still a knockoff of DDR and it's going to be treated as such in my mind.
[SPEAKER_03]: Those new pads, they look pretty solid, but they've got a few fatal flaws in them.
[SPEAKER_03]: One of them being that the arrows are recessed too far and it feels really awkward playing on them and I didn't like them one bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, it might be a personal opinion thing, because when I played them a couple weeks ago, they were great to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: I really enjoyed them.
[SPEAKER_03]: All they gotta do to fix it, raise up those arrows just a teeny little bit, just a few millimeters, just to make it, just set in a little bit, not too much, don't go crazy, and then instead of making them all rubbery,
[SPEAKER_03]: Make Them Metal.
[SPEAKER_04]: But then you played two other DDR mats as well, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, and then that one starts to look pretty good when you look at the other two, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, the second one was DDRGame.com, their metal pad with their bar.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which had a bar, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, the pads sucked.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, those pads, they were all shiny and it basically had soft pad syndrome where you can't tell where the hell the arrows are.
[SPEAKER_03]: And what's worse about the DDRGame.com ones...
[SPEAKER_03]: If you miss the pad, you're going to hurt your leg, because it's raised up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which happened to somebody, we know, actually.
[SPEAKER_03]: It happened to someone, so I cannot recommend this.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's the only one you're going to see that has the solo arrows actually on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although most just use the buttons.
[SPEAKER_03]: They did do something kind of neat, and I'll give them credit for this, because softpads, they're pretty much all the same out there.
[SPEAKER_03]: But they actually had a doubles softpad, which I thought was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: The only thing I can see that would suck about that is if one side breaks down.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh crap.
[SPEAKER_03]: So yeah, I tried that one.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: And really, I don't know, DDR pads, they're just all about the same.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then, what else did I get to try out today?
[SPEAKER_03]: I watched Kingdom Hearts 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: That looked pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then, really, it's just a lot of hanging around Konami's booth, checking that stuff out.
[SPEAKER_03]: and talking to like some of the people you know trying to get you know not necessarily press kits but on their email list for my work and that kind of thing and I have to say that the people EA can suck it because they have this you know we're better than everyone else attitude and I mean they've done that to our company as a whole like you know when our company yeah we're distributing games they're like yeah we don't care it's just like big deal you know
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, the hell with them.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it seems like, honestly, from hearing other people's... Did they have anything at their booth that interested any of us?
[SPEAKER_03]: They had their new test drive, Most Wanted.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was looking at the stuff for The Sims.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sims 2 for PSP is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: It was kind of a misconception, at least I certainly thought that PlayStation would be one I'd be waiting just as long in as Zelda.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the interesting thing is that the Zelda line ran out of shirts today.
[SPEAKER_04]: So some people that went through the whole thing didn't even get a shirt.
[SPEAKER_03]: I did get to play Nintendogs, and that game is so damn... I've got to get that game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I already knew I was going to buy the game before I actually played it.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's just...
[SPEAKER_03]: It's such a game, I don't even know.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is gonna, honestly, people are gonna play this game and it's gonna be just like Animal Crossing where you just can't get enough of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're just gonna be playing it all the time.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're gonna be worrying about your pets are not getting walked or something when you're out.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it is gonna be like the next Tamagotchi.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now don't shun it just because I say it that way, but...
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's going to be something that appeals to a more broader age range.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just the whole trade and everything.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, Jamie just brought up something to me I forgot to ask her.
[SPEAKER_03]: How was the boomerang?
[SPEAKER_03]: On the PS3?
[SPEAKER_03]: What was your impressions of the boomerang?
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm looking at my picture of it right now.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm trying to imagine how this thing would feel in my hand.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now for those that are a little bit lost, the boomerang is what we are calling the controller on the PS3 because it looks like, well, a boomerang.
[SPEAKER_01]: It does.
[SPEAKER_01]: It looks like a half moon.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what it looks like?
[SPEAKER_03]: It looks like an old school Microsoft Sidewinder.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, yeah, it does.
[SPEAKER_03]: And guess what, folks?
[SPEAKER_03]: The Sidewinder... I don't understand.
[SPEAKER_03]: Honestly, stick with DualShock.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what I say.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, I couldn't just... It didn't seem like it would be all that comfortable, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it's only conceptual.
[SPEAKER_01]: It said concept controller.
[SPEAKER_04]: So maybe they'll make some changes and make it less boomerang-y, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stuff I checked out today, I actually got to play a little bit of Kingdom Hearts 2, and very interesting, I have to admit I wasn't so into the first one, I know a lot of people consider it to be this great game, and I respect the game, but I couldn't get into it, because I got really, really bothered by the camera, like that whole 3D thing that can annoy me on some of those games sometimes.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't have these same problems in Kingdom Hearts 2, it looks like they went back and fixed some of that, and they added a couple new modes too, like they have this overdrive mode, like you might think of this from Final Fantasies, kinda similar, but more towards the Kingdom Hearts concept, where if you build up enough strength, you can go into overdrive mode, and you transform, and you have two blades, so that's kinda neat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_01]: Um, yeah, did you actually, uh, of course you had Auron there.
[SPEAKER_01]: Did you do the fusions?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I did not get a chance to do the fusions.
[SPEAKER_01]: With Goofy, that's the Valor one, that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: He dual-wields the Keyblades.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, having Auron in the game was kind of neat, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: I gotta say, that's kind of a neat addition to the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Another game I checked out today was Hello Kitty Roller Rescue.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now stop laughing, stop laughing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was drawn to this game because I love Batsamaru the penguin and I saw that he was in the game so I had to check it out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello Kitty Roller Rescue is very interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure there's an audience out there for it somewhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even though I do love Batsamaru I can't personally say I would buy this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would buy it for a child but I don't know if I could buy it for myself.
[SPEAKER_04]: I became too frustrated because Hello Kitty would not jump over everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: There was only certain things like some weird collision detection.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know what it is but just...
[SPEAKER_04]: It wasn't as interactive.
[SPEAKER_04]: It just felt weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: But a kid would be into it.
[SPEAKER_04]: A kid wouldn't be bothered by it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's what it was really for.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that was one of the other games I saw today.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess that's all I really want to say.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, one other game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I actually saw this yesterday, but I forgot to bring it up on yesterday's show.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Capcom Collection.
[SPEAKER_04]: It has a bunch of old school Capcom arcade games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ghouls N' Ghosts, Super Ghouls N' Ghosts, and the one I played, 1943.
[SPEAKER_04]: All in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kind of a neat collection.
[SPEAKER_04]: Seems like kind of the popular trend right now with the retro-ness.
[SPEAKER_04]: Having the Flashback console, Atari.
[SPEAKER_04]: Having the Capcom collection, the Namco one.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're doing a new one that's really big.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very interesting trend.
[SPEAKER_01]: Did you get to play any Final Fight?
[SPEAKER_04]: I did not play Final Fight.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's very wonky right now.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: The new Final Fight?
[SPEAKER_01]: The new Final Fight.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: I actually played the new Romancing Saga as well.
[SPEAKER_01]: Which thing?
[SPEAKER_01]: I was never big into the Saga games.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was kind of cool, but it looks like a freaking PS1 game.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's just not clean.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, Sagas were games that never impressed me either.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was like, I can sort of follow this.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, now since the show is all done, I'd like us to go around and think about the best games
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's do best booth at the show first.
[SPEAKER_04]: The best booth.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who there at the show do you believe had the best booth out of anybody and why?
[SPEAKER_04]: Anybody want to start?
[SPEAKER_01]: It's kind of... DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's places that did things better, I think.
[SPEAKER_01]: But overall, I have to give... It's actually a toss-up.
[SPEAKER_01]: It really is a toss-up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, a tie.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm going to have to say that between Konami and Namco, I mean, just Konami went all out with that show.
[SPEAKER_01]: That was really cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: So as far as their presentation, Konami had the better show.
[SPEAKER_01]: But as far as overall, like I was saying yesterday, friendliness, knowledge, the fun swag, I have to say that Namco really impressed me.
[SPEAKER_01]: Their lineup.
[SPEAKER_01]: I got to play, oh, I also played Pack'n Roll.
[SPEAKER_01]: And when someone came over and saw that I had the hang of playing it, they didn't harass me.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just got to play it.
[SPEAKER_01]: We talked a little bit about it.
[SPEAKER_01]: The people at Namco Mobile were fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: They were just happy.
[SPEAKER_01]: They ran out of the little squishy Pac-Man things, but they apologized for it.
[SPEAKER_01]: They knew what they were doing.
[SPEAKER_01]: They were happy to do what they were doing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Our co-host for...
[SPEAKER_03]: Outside of the Box, SlankyStyle, he actually got a short video clip of the Prince of the Cosmos breakdancing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: We're hoping to make a LiveJournal icon out of that.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll have to post that in our Orange Lounge LiveJournal community once that's done.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, so DarkSakura saying toss-up between Konami and Namco.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, what do you think was the best booth at the show?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, oh man, it's tough.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm so biased just because I hung out at Konami's booth a long time, pretty much the majority of the time while I was there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Only because of a few things.
[SPEAKER_03]: One, the whole stage area right there where they had the DDR games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Very open, you're not really feeling crowded in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Plus you can sit down and watch the little trailer reel that they've got there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Couldn't really do that anywhere else.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, I guess as far as being the least offensive booth of them all, because they didn't really have any booth babes jumping around.
[SPEAKER_03]: They had actually something that appealed to everyone.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: However, there is a close second, and that would be Game Infinity, and only because they had X-Tango in the sex game there.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Just sitting there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was like, I didn't get it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just didn't get it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And guys were standing there, probably sitting there thinking, I wonder if they'll do it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't get it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Probably my second runner-up would be actually the G4 booth because they had a pretty cool setup there as far as like sit down, chill, watch their shows, make a t-shirt, which at least you're guaranteed a t-shirt that way.
[SPEAKER_03]: They had the people giving out those ouch kits.
[SPEAKER_03]: Those are pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: I also have to give a special kudos to the Tylenol Ouch booth and the cute guy that gave me a back massage.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would say if I had to pick one booth of the show and I hate to kind of echo what somebody else already said but honestly for me there was one booth that I feel they put all their cards out on the table everybody there was really friendly I got to play their games they have a hell of a lineup this year
[SPEAKER_04]: and that booth would be Namco I would say would be my booth of the year I was just blown away by what they've got to offer I think between like We Heart Katamari, Soul Calibur 3, Pac-Man and even semi-decent mobile games as well and usually I'm not very impressed with cell phone games but the ones I played were pretty decent for a cell phone certainly more so than some of the other ones I played at the show and I just felt that Namco they also had various stage shows going on with the whole Soul Calibur battles and stuff
[SPEAKER_04]: It really was, for me, I think the most impressive lineup at the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that would be my booth as a show.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Best... You want to do best game or you want to do worst booth next?
[SPEAKER_04]: Worst booth.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_01]: For attitude, it was Capcom.
[SPEAKER_01]: Bunch of apathetic... You know, Capcom as a company has my love.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, been a long time Capcom fan.
[SPEAKER_01]: But the people who they had working the information booth...
[SPEAKER_01]: They were just rude.
[SPEAKER_01]: Rude as they could be.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, we kind of talked about it yesterday, so you guys know how we feel about it.
[SPEAKER_01]: They just displayed so much apathy that I can't say that Capcom really impressed me.
[SPEAKER_04]: They really didn't have a whole lot of games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, and I want to answer an email real quick, because while we're on Capcom, I'm so sorry to interject, but if I don't do it now, I'll forget.
[SPEAKER_04]: Somebody wrote us an email about Mega Man Battle Network and wanted to know how it would link up with the other DS...
[SPEAKER_04]: Battle Network Games.
[SPEAKER_04]: And basically what we found out is that there is some type of tournament mode, so you can play Battle Network against the DS Wireless, but we did not see anything in any of the materials so far.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't dug through the whole book, but in the little promo video we saw, we didn't see anything about it linking up to the Game Boy Advance versions or anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just a type of online battle tournament mode.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, I just wanted to interject that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: Everybody put on a really good display game
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, Gizmondo was also really excellent for... We're doing worse poof!
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm using it as a comparison.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because, you know, Gizmondo was sort of like, eh, we're Gizmondo last year.
[SPEAKER_01]: And this year, like, hey, we're freaking Gizmondo and we're bringing out people to rap and spin and dance for you and everything.
[SPEAKER_01]: But, Capcom was the same as they were last year.
[SPEAKER_01]: Just, we don't want to fucking be here.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, true, it may be work.
[SPEAKER_01]: But you should be happy in the work that you do.
[SPEAKER_01]: And the guys at Namco, they were having to do every bit of a boring job that you were.
[SPEAKER_01]: But they were all smiles and friendly.
[SPEAKER_01]: So Capcom must be the dullest place on earth to work for or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, so is that your worst booth?
[SPEAKER_04]: Or do you have an overall worst booth?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, like I said, the displays and everything were great.
[SPEAKER_01]: For everywhere, there wasn't anything really disappointing as far as their look.
[SPEAKER_01]: But...
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, I have to say that Capcom, it was just the attitude.
[SPEAKER_01]: The attitude soured their whole booth for me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: This one's easy.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'd like to give a big thank you to Rockstar for saving me time for having to play their games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because guess what?
[SPEAKER_03]: They rented out this huge, huge booth and put some buses there and said, Ha!
[SPEAKER_03]: You don't get to play anything!
[SPEAKER_03]: Eat that!
[SPEAKER_03]: You're gonna buy our games anyways.
[SPEAKER_03]: Suck it!
[SPEAKER_03]: And that was it.
[SPEAKER_03]: They didn't have jacked.
[SPEAKER_03]: The only picture I saw of Bully was in a magazine I got there for free.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I actually saw more of Rockstar's lineup from some stupid magazine than, you know, their actual booth.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what, I'm tired of these game companies thinking that their stuff's all kick-ass just because, you know, the last couple games, which have all been exactly the same, I might add,
[SPEAKER_03]: have sold really awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: But guess what?
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: Save Emergency sucked balls.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: I hope Bully does too because I'm not giving you my money just for the same damn rehash game with maybe a different genre.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not necessarily a different genre, a different time period it's set in.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, for my worst booth, again, I hate to echo what somebody else already said, but just because of the fact that it was an eyesore.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, the booth itself was an eyesore.
[SPEAKER_04]: And just the fact...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't want to stop and look at anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I know they're trying to show new games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't want to stop and look.
[SPEAKER_04]: Horrible position for them, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Their booth was in a bad spot, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: I understand if they want to do press-only for these games, because obviously they're probably in progress and they don't want any bad people to look.
[SPEAKER_03]: But even still, last year, I didn't see their games.
[SPEAKER_03]: They were behind closed doors.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can go and make an appointment to play it.
[SPEAKER_03]: This was just like rubbing it in your face.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like...
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, hey, guess what?
[SPEAKER_03]: You can go in here and play games if you're pressed and if you make an appointment.
[SPEAKER_04]: And just the chain-link fence and the giant buses were just an eyesore.
[SPEAKER_04]: They didn't need to be there.
[SPEAKER_04]: With all the other neon nice effects, just to have that ghetto-looking booth was just... You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: I honestly learned about Rockstar's lineup from posters that were outside on Hollywood Boulevard.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's where I learned about their stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: So when I saw their booth with the buses, I was like, whoopity-freaking-doo-dah, you know?
[SPEAKER_03]: There are so many good ones.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_01]: It's like a toss-up between three games, seriously.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, then name the three.
[SPEAKER_01]: We Love Katamari, definitely.
[SPEAKER_01]: Nintendogs and Animal Crossing DS.
[SPEAKER_01]: And Call of Cthulhu, but I'm not going to go into that.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I would have to say those three were the top of the show.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, actually, those three had me convinced to be the top of the show.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm gonna get We Heart Katamari, that's for sure.
[SPEAKER_01]: And why is that?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's because it's Katamari.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's also cheap.
[SPEAKER_04]: What does the sequel offer that the first one doesn't though?
[SPEAKER_04]: Why should people run out and get it?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's more of the same game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's why you want to get it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Everything you loved about the first game is in the second game and just wackier and better.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let me help.
[SPEAKER_03]: Co-op mode as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who cares about that?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just talking about more game.
[SPEAKER_03]: You finish the first game and you're like, I want more.
[SPEAKER_03]: Give me more.
[SPEAKER_03]: This will be cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nintendogs will be awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've got to get Animal Crossing just because everyone else is going to have it and I don't want to feel left out.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think those are probably the ones.
[SPEAKER_01]: Are you going to let your puppies play with my puppies?
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to call my dog Bacon.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: My game of the show, you know I love games that do something new that isn't just the same old crap over and over again and bring something new to the table.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like interactive games that help you do – like I loved Animal Crossing 1 because you could interact with other people in unique ways.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I just love originality.
[SPEAKER_04]: and this game was just damn good looking too and I had fun with it I had a lot of fun with it which is something I cannot say about most games game of the show for me would be Nintendogs
[SPEAKER_04]: which is odd because I'm totally not a dog person but I loved Nintendogs.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was so cute.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'd like to discuss this stuff right here.
[SPEAKER_03]: I pulled open my little show daily magazine here and they have one of .com awards for what they thought were the best in show stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can I finish my thought on best in show stuff?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I thought you were done.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I'm not done.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a runner-up.
[SPEAKER_04]: You all got a runner-up.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want a runner-up.
[SPEAKER_04]: My runner-up would be actually Meteos, the new puzzle game that's going to be coming out on DSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: The best in show, my thoughts, and runner-up to DS games, when I've kind of knocked the DS quite a bit over the past few months because they've had really a crap lineup.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, the DS is, it is true, the DS is going to get a hell of a lot better over the next nine months.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, you know, if you are in the DS versus PSP mindset, I still think both systems are very separate, and if you really want to experience everything, you're going to have to own both.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be a close contest for those looking at one or the other.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just look at it this way, people.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're not going to have to actually get an external keyboard if they put Linux on the DS versus the PSP.
[SPEAKER_01]: I had a moment of comedy, though, speaking of the DS stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was trying to download Electroplankton from the PSP area.
[SPEAKER_01]: And having a Sony person comment on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, yeah, Loki, you were going to get into what somebody else felt was the best.
[SPEAKER_03]: 1up.com, their awards, Game of the Show, they gave it to Legend of Zelda.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't seen the game, so... Yeah, I mean, to be honest, I think our awards, quote-unquote, you have to remember, are from our perspective, and our perspective was we were...
[SPEAKER_04]: Even though we're borderline media, we went in as non-media, just like the sales people, just like the students and the folks that are barely in the industry.
[SPEAKER_04]: From our perspective, Legend of Zelda was not easily accessible, so therefore it kind of gets a strike against it when it comes to really the most impressive thing at the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: Best visuals, Unreal Tournament 2007.
[SPEAKER_03]: Once again, another thing that you had to wait in line to go see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_01]: It is.
[SPEAKER_01]: It actually is sort of music-y, too.
[SPEAKER_01]: But yeah, Electric Plankton's really bizarre.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've been wanting that game for a while.
[SPEAKER_03]: What was that one game that we were playing that was on the... Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_03]: The other system.
[SPEAKER_03]: The other portable system that you were hyping up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Gizmondo.
[SPEAKER_03]: Gizmondo, yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: What was that game?
[SPEAKER_03]: The guitar one.
[SPEAKER_01]: The guitar game?
[SPEAKER_01]: It was called Johnny Wonder, I think it was.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: It had a little karaoke mode where you sort of...
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, hit directions and rhythm.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was like a music and rhythm game meets an action game, which was kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: You have like an action mode where you kill things by wailing hard on your guitar.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, next one.
[SPEAKER_03]: So one more award.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, how about we do, well, without a doubt.
[SPEAKER_03]: Again, this is coming from the show book from 1up.com's awards.
[SPEAKER_03]: Best simulation game, Nintendogs, without a doubt.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, yeah, you can find all this stuff on 1up.com or if you luckily have one of these things.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a game that they listed on here which is cool, Best PC Game Sport, which is by Will Wright, which, you know, it's going to be pretty good, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: Speaking of PC games, I was a little disappointed that I really didn't see any Civilization IV.
[SPEAKER_04]: I saw huge banners for it, but no place you could really go look at it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess they were doing trailers and teasers, but I was really hoping I'd be able to get my hands on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Couldn't do it.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: I went by it towards the beginning of the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Totally empty.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of sad.
[SPEAKER_03]: There was more people inside the Rockstar booth than there were in the Engage Arena.
[SPEAKER_04]: So kind of sad, but that's what happens.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess with that... Oh, and our podcast, of course, is always updated late Sunday night, early Monday morning.
[SPEAKER_04]: Check it once a week.
[SPEAKER_04]: We will have another show in a couple days here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kind of, once again, wrapping it all up from E3 and taking your questions.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just an FYI, our E3 at OrangeLoungeRadio.com address is now closed.
[SPEAKER_04]: Please do not use that address.
[SPEAKER_04]: The show's over.
[SPEAKER_04]: Those emails will bounce back to you.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you would like to give us feedback, though, or you want to comment on the show in general, we do still welcome those emails.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you have E3 show feedback or you want to comment on something, we'd still love to hear from you guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Togo, T-O-G-O, at OrangeLoungeRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: And if you're a game publisher and you want to send us free stuff, that's Loki at OrangeLoungeRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, let's go around and give everybody's final thought, final E3 thought.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: That pizza I had this morning wasn't cooked all the way, and there will be hell to pay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hell to pay!
[SPEAKER_01]: I had a bacon-covered wiener, and it was good, and it was cooked in onions.
[SPEAKER_01]: So it tasted like a bacon-covered onion wiener.
[SPEAKER_01]: And reject false icons.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, Loki, yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, you want to be my final thought?
[SPEAKER_04]: My final thought would be that I think it's very ironic that the ferret and the Orange Lounge Radio Media CD ended up within, like, a foot of each other on the giant Katamari.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I wonder where they're going to roll that thing to.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was just going to say that the Katamari claimed the ferret.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, so...
[SPEAKER_01]: It was the retard ferret, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it was the one that made all the cool sounds.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently I made a mistake.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I took the one that Loki had operated on.
[SPEAKER_04]: It wasn't the one you've been using on the shows because that's still in your green chair, so don't cry.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because the ferret is my special friend.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's with the king of the cosmos now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Deal.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: From us here at E3 to you guys, thank you for downloading us and checking us out, subscribing to the podcast, and tuning in to our E3 coverage.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, we'll be back in 2006.
[SPEAKER_04]: And next time, watch out because we are going to be storming the booze next year with all access passes if we have anything to say about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll try.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll see if the woman will let me next year.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Goodbye, everybody.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the end of another Orange Lounge Radio To Go edition.
[SPEAKER_02]: This podcast is a proud part of www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: See you next update.