Orange Lounge Radio
Who's your hosts? DarkSakura, Skie, and Loki
This week Tokyo Game Show 2018 announced new releases including those for the Playstation Vita
and Sony announces the discontinuation of shipments of the Playstation Vita next year.
There's plenty more news and sore less contradictory as well starting right now in the show
Wherever Gamer has a voice.
Orange Lounge Radio
Hi fam, welcome back
It's another week of the show where every gamer has a voice
Orange Lounge Radio
Live tonight September the 23rd, 2018
Episode number 745 of our show
My name's Rob Roberts joining you live here from our headquarters in Sacramento, California
with my co-host as he's been every week here lately
Say hello to Techmaster Loki
Hello
Hi Loki, how are you doing?
I'm good
So no food tonight, this diet thing you've been on is like a serious thing
It's not that, I mean
Well I see you have like a protein shake, you're doing the same thing my husband does
No, it's just I ate lunch late, I cooked, I had some chicken I bought last week so I had to cook it before it went bad
And so I ate that for lunch at like 2.33 so I mean
It's kind of too early to eat again and I thought well I can have like a taco or something like that
But it was a chicken taco, I'm like I just ate chicken, I don't really want to eat that again
So I don't know
The last few days I've been trying to come in under a thousand calories under my already 500 calorie
Under my limit of what I'm supposed to eat
Well just don't overdo it with some of those cutting corners
Well like yesterday I ate a whole pizza so then I had to play DDR for 90 minutes straight
So maybe it's like a weekly budget, I see how it goes
No no no, that was just a slip but no
Lately it's been, because I got a Fitbit for my birthday so I've been doing a lot more walking
So I walk 3 miles a day, well during the week, not necessarily on the weekends because I don't have time for that
The 3 miles during the day, I fast for 16 hours up until about 1pm
So I don't eat until 1pm and then I go for a 3 mile walk and then I pick up lunch
And I come back and then I come home after all that and then I play DDR for another 30 minutes or so
So for those that, you know, I don't think we've talked about this in quite a while but
Loki's really like slimmed down, I know it's a radio show at least for now
I mean we talked about how we're going to move to Twitch eventually but
Because I bought new pants is why, because these pants actually fit and not the other ones
The other ones are really baggy and like were too big
You've really slimmed down though, you've really slimmed down
I really haven't, I mean thank you but the scale says otherwise
Well since you started this whole thing, I don't mean like in the past week or two
I mean since you started this whole thing, anyway
We're keeping somebody waiting over there, unfortunately we've missed her these past few weeks
But she's back to terrorize us once again, say hello to Dark Sakura or Jamie Summers
I'm overwhelmed by being back
And all of the stuff that Ikuma sent us
Oh yes, so right before the show, one of our pals from overseas, Akuma JP, shout out
Sent a little care package
A little?
It ended up being a big care package, so a big thank you to Akuma JP and all these little
You can send him all the pumpkin spice things
I don't know if pumpkin spice is as big as a thing, but you can get kapocha
That's what I could send him in return, I could say here's a little taste of America
And just do like all the pumpkin spice garbage
Send him the ultimate white girl fantasy?
Yes, ultimate like now Akuma JP I know it's your fantasy to be a basic bitch, so here you go
That was like that Cinderella meme, it was like at midnight your character turns back into a pumpkin
Yes bitch
That is me, here's the thing
Here's the thing, it's not that like I'm obsessed with pumpkin spice
I think I'm just the only one in the group of friends that's like willing to admit it
Like fuck yes I'm excited pumpkin spice is in season
Hell yes I'm gonna order a pumpkin spice latte
You know why? Because pumpkin spice lattes are fucking good
I'm gonna be making pumpkin bread
And so I get teased for being that bitch
I'm not making it sweet
I like a lot of different food
Anyway it's not the food podcast Dark Sakura
Yes it is
I actually
I just ate filet mignon and it was great
Want me to talk about meat and potatoes? The meat and potato show
Have sweet potato, eat it
I need to go to our social media because over on Twitter
At twitter.com slash olr
I actually asked the listeners
I gave Twitter a little love and I said
She's in the studio tonight on a brief reprieve from her work schedule
Which of these recent headlines from the shows she's missed
Should Rob ask her about right at the top of the show
So you ready for what the listeners picked
For the video game topic that you've missed that we need to get into
With 87% of the vote
What are your thoughts on the new Animal Crossing game for Nintendo Switch being announced
It must happen, I need it
And it has to be as great as New Leaf was
And I have to be able to have
Going to all the villages and changing their shit
And planting stuff
I want more black tulips
And I want to be able to murder Tom Nook in his sleep
How about bug net violence
I want to be able to kick people out of my village
Banish people from the village
I want to banish people from my village
Do you want witch trials
No not that bad I just want to kick Ed out when he shows up
You know I create backstories for all the characters in the game
It's not the Animal Crossing game that I want
It's Animal Crossing after dark that I really want
I do want more villagers to be like night owls
Yeah I always hated when the villagers would go to bed
Like at the time that I want to play the game
I want there to be like 24 hour shopping
That isn't just like the club
Like club lol
So did you watch that whole little thing with the Isabelle reveal
And the new Animal Crossing
Like that whole little thing on Nintendo Direct
Did you watch the actual teaser
I just cared that they said Animal Crossing
And that apparently Isabelle is in Smash Brothers
Yes Isabelle is in Smash Brothers
So the whole thing
What are you going to do
Beat people up with you know bills and park projects
Yes
Well the villagers are in the game
And the villagers are in the game
So why not Isabelle
It made a lot of sense
But the whole set up was that it started with
And people are supposed to be misled to think
Oh it's an Animal Crossing reveal
But in fact it was Isabelle is in Smash
And that's how it started
But then it fades to black
And it fades back up
And it's Tom Nook sitting at the computer
Which has lent itself to so many wonderful memes
By the way those images of Tom Nook sitting at the computer
And then he talks to the camera
And reveals that Animal Crossing is under development
For next year for the Switch
And that's where that came from
So it's kind of like a back to back
Better not be more fucking happy home designer
Even though I love that game too
It got old though
Alright so there you go
Jamie's thoughts on Animal Crossing
In a word, yes
Where's my NES games
What if we get SNES games that'd be rad
Oh like in the
Free stuff for Nintendo
Those days are long gone
I know
It would be nice
You have to pay a monthly or yearly fee
To be able to play those classic NES games
That were free in the original Animal Crossing
What if they had an arcade like in there
And you like pay like a certain amount of like Nintendo points
To go into the arcade and play stuff
I've always been about like how
Don't they have a big enough development team at Nintendo
That a couple people could just be assigned to making little mini games
And they don't have to make it
Just make NES style mini games
And those would be what you would unlock
And it would just be like
Flappy Bird ripoffs
And you know like
Those types of things
But like with the little villagers
And you could like have high score competitions
With the villagers
Or your friends that you invited to the village
There's the fishing competition
And the tortomers island crap
Okay alright that's true
They have some of those silly little things
That's true
Yeah
So alright we'll see
Going to our chat
We do tape live of course every Sunday night
At the voice of geeks network
Of vognetwork.com
And if you are in our
Or if you are listening live
You should be in our chat room
It's over at live.vognetwork.com
All the info how to join our chat room
Is right there
Starting off SHG100 Matt saying
I would watch Jamie stream Animal Crossing
You gonna be doing any live streaming of
Oh shit yeah
Okay sounds good
You know something else just occurred to me
Because they let you do that in like
In the camp game
Pocket camp
You should be able to choose your skin tone
For your character
Instead of like
I mean you should still be able to like
Tan if you go to the beach and everything
Right
But you should be able to like
Choose your skin tone
Instead of it being like
Because I know that the intent is for
Everyone to be Japanese
I mean because
But when it comes out in a diverse place
In a more diverse location
It looks like default white
You know
Right right
And I think that they should definitely
Put in more
Choices of skin tone that you can pick
From the start of the game
Well I think Nintendo's been hearing
Some of that feedback
Because of what we're seeing
In the mobile game and stuff
So I would anticipate that's gonna continue
Into whatever you know
New Animal Crossing game comes out
And all that
So we'll see though
Let's see
Fifth Dream in chat says
It better have big text
So I can play it at work
That's a good call out
Is that since it is going to be something
That's designed to be portable
And docked
We will want to make sure
That the text is readable
When we're sitting there
Playing it in portable mode
I want my amiibos to work
I'm sure the
Oh come on
I want the villager amiibo
For Smash Brothers to work
Amiibo support is probably like
The first thing they thought about
In one of those meetings
How can we get more cash from our fans
Did you see how many are still left over
At target in those places
Because I think the bubble's bursting
A little bit on that
I kind of think the amiibo pool
Got too dilated
Like they did not need to make
I know you're not going to like this Jamie
But they did not need to make figures
For like every character in Animal Crossing
They did not need to make figures
For all of Kirby's friends
I need five different KK's
So like that's the problem
Is I think it just got too saturated
Like the Smash Brothers series
That was good
But that should have been like
That should have been the amiibo
You know maybe a couple others
Here and there like
But I have my Mr. Resetti
I know I know
But it's just I just think it's
It's too much
And act up I agree
There's never enough Kirby amiibos
There's always going to be someone
That disagrees with me
Let's get to our kickoff topic
Tonight officially
Even though the losers here
Twitch Prime changes 13% of the vote
Steam TV 0% of the vote
Jamie nobody cares about your opinion
On Steam TV apparently
I don't care about Steam TV either
Apparently Animal Crossing
Is just too dominating there
People want to know
People associate you with that game
I can't imagine why
Alright anyway
Let's talk about our official kickoff
Topic tonight
Let's get into
Actually unfortunately
This is kind of like shitty news
And it's
This is something that is inevitable
In the games industry
And something we hear far too often about
But I think in this particular stance
Actually both
We're going to hear about two tonight
Kind of a surprise I think
Jamie why don't you start us off
So we had a studio closure right
And this was
Kind of I don't know
Feels like a surprise
To me
It's kind of a surprise
But I also think it's karma
Telltale is closing
They are starting by laying off
Most of the employees
Are leaving 25 there
To finish their obligations
But they said that more information
Is coming out in coming weeks
They also though apparently
Haven't been paying severance packages
To their employees
Not in this most recent round
Well I'm sure that the management
Is going to be paying themselves
A nice you know
Chunk of money
So fuck them
Allegedly
No likely
Because that's all
It's capital
We don't know
I have to say allegedly
Because we don't know
I just want to say
When you say
Because
She's unhinged
She's back and she's unhinged
Which is fine
But when you say
Karma
I have hinges
I think it's important to state
You are targeting the management
In that
And certainly
None of the hard working
Story writers
Programmers
People doing their jobs
My ire goes to the management
Because it's their fucking fault
Yeah
Their decisions
All I'll say
Is it's a small world
And
This comes from
Things that we've heard
And that's all we can say
So to the management
Of Telltale Games
I want you to take
A wrought iron dildo
Stop
Just stop
They can also be used
As a metal file
For blacksmithing
They can be used
As a metal file
For blacksmithing
And they like for you to sit on it
And spin
In the opposite direction
I just
I
The anger comes from a place
Of not only did they
Kind of do their associates dirty
With this whole lack of severance
And all this stuff
But
We've heard some accounts
On Twitter where
New employees left
Their long careers
To start
On Monday
And they were laid off
On Friday
Like
What kind of planning
Is that?
Like
What kind of planning
Is that?
That's
It's
It's just a real
It's a real crappy way
To treat somebody too
That would have left
Like a long career
To come work
At this company
Who's
You know
Making some good
Good stuff
You know
Tons of people love
The Walking Dead
And again
I want to stress
The anger does not come
From a place
Whatsoever
To the hardworking
Frontline programmers
Talented artists
Story writers
The management there
Is garbage
You can fertilize
The shit
This is landfill
The views and opinions
Expressed by Jamie
Are true
I have to say
That dildo smithing
Is one skill tree
That I didn't put
A lot of points in
In Skyrim
But
I may have to change
My mind on that
Maybe next time
Yeah next time
Next playthrough
Let's see
Go into chat
At live.vognetwork.com
As Joe and Hunter Matt
Points out
Those employees
Live in the San Francisco
Bay Area
The highest cost
The North Bay Area
Was where specifically
This office was located
Yeah
They were right near
I used to work
I keep wanting to say
Martinez
That's not it
What's on the
Just out of Marin
San
Oh San
God damn it
Why can't I think of the name
San Rafael
That's it
San Quentin
No
across there
San Rafael
That's where they were located
If I remember right
When I was arrested
I was dressed in black
I was there too
But um
Yeah Telltale
Was right in that area
And I'm telling you
North Bay Area
Expensive
Real estate
Very expensive
And Loki
Fifth Dream says
This is a Skyrim mod
Waiting to happen
I'm sure it's a Skyrim mod
Already happened
But you know
I haven't delved into all of those
And Bones 006
I said shit has uses
You can fertilize with shit
Garbage
Dungeon Buster in chat says
That's BS planning
Management had to know
That things were going south
And yet they let those
Newcomers come in
There's no way their finance people
Could not have already known
Well before the hires were made
And that's an example of
Why there's anger about this
And where that's coming from
You know you want a concrete example
Of how was the planning garbage
There's your answer
But for what it's worth
I know the studio did make some
Pretty amazing games
You know all things considered
Certainly the Walking Dead series
Known and appreciated by a lot of people
They made games based on Jurassic Park
They had the Sam and Max
Was kind of the big comeback series games
They had those strong bad games
That were on the Wii
Back to the Future
They had the Batman
The Marvel stuff
Wolf Among Us
So I mean there was all
And I honestly thought
You know they were in good financial places
Because the types of games
They were putting out
Were in my view
Like long shelf life type of games
Like you know in a lot of games
Games have to sell
Like all of their business
It's like right up front
Like that's why pre-orders are so important
That's why launch day
Stuff is so important
Because so many games
Make their sales
Large percent of their sales
The first week
And I was always struck with
That Telltale games didn't necessarily
Have those same goals
Because they would
You know they had a long lifespan
Something like the Walking Dead
People are just now
Even getting into those games
I know and I still have
Like in my back catalog
In my PlayStation library
I think on PlayStation 3
I have like a ton of those series
But now again
If you want to believe
Everything you see on Twitter
And social media
So take it with a grain of salt
But apparently
Not all their games sold very well
Apparently the Minecraft
Story mode was doing very well
That game was doing well
But the Batman game
Was one of their worst performing games period
And that's kind of a stunning one
In a way
I don't know though
But in some way
Like the DC movies
Have not been very strong
We all know that
That's because they're garbage
With garbage writing
You're on a roll tonight
The DC movies are not very strong
I also kind of think
Batman was saturated
I'm not sure there was a place
For Telltale's very specific sort of
Batman game in the mass market
You know what there was a place for?
Lego Batman
And I think that's
People kind of associate
The console gaming with like
Lego Batman and that stuff
I think the Batman Telltale thing
Proved to be maybe too niche
I don't know
Apparently Tales from the Borderlands
Also did not do well
But like I hate to say it
I kind of
I mean that's a
That was
I don't even remember thinking this
When I first saw the game
Like the game looked really good
But I was like
This is a really niche thing
Like I'm not going to want to play this
If I don't already have some familiarity
With Borderlands
But I think the thinking that went into it
Was the reverse
Maybe we can bring more people
Into Borderlands through this game
But I'm not sure that's how it really worked
Whether the game was good or not
I'm not saying it was a bad game
Actually
Considering I knew very little about Borderlands
I actually enjoyed
What Tales from the Borderlands I saw
But I just think that
You know kind of
Limited the potential audience
But hindsight's
2020 right?
So anyway
It probably leads to why
The games did not end up
Performing as well as expected
And why we're where we're at today
Let's see
Going to chat at
Live.vognetware.com
Yeah Dungeon Buster says
I thought the Batman games were doing really well
So to read that rumor was eyebrow raising right?
But we don't
We don't really get game sales
In the same way we get box office
I mean sure we get MPD rankings
But there's only so much that tells us
You know there's so many games out there
And plus with digital distribution
And all these different platforms
PC isn't accounted for in MPD
So it's just you know
A little different
Brad from Pod Culture
Pushing back on the DC movies thing a little bit
Does want to point out Wonder Woman was great
So
There is at least maybe a diamond in the rough
Well you know a broken clock is right twice
Alright anyway
It used to be good
It's just up until recent
When they tried the
You know Marvel Cinematic Universe the thing
And then actually brought in somebody from Marvel Cinematic Universe
But anyway this is not a
This is not a DC Marvel show
It's a video game show
Unfortunately
I will say
Actually to end this on a positive note
To see how the industry has been reaching out
To the affected folks at Telltale
Is really awesome
Like there's a tweet out there
Where Ubisoft San Francisco
Is like
Hey if you work there
Come to BJ's Brewhouse
On such and such day
We're meeting and greeting people
Our treat
You know to try to fill positions
And I think there's a lot of people out there
Who want to help
Because many people recognize
This sucks
Because there's many people in the industry
Who have been through this
Far too many times
Because of
Bad decisions
By people that were
A little higher up on the food chain
Unfortunately
This is not the only example
Of this that's happened this week
Right Logie?
Yes unfortunately not
So
Capcom's
Vancouver studio
Has shut down as well
So
This isn't kind of
Unexpected I guess
Because they did
Lay off
30% of the studio
Back in February
But
Now they have
I guess
The remaining
158 people
Will lose their jobs
Due to the shutdown
They're going to keep
A skeleton crew remaining
Until January 2019
To finalize the closure
Operations and logistics
But
For those who may not know
Capcom Vancouver
Was best known for the
Dead Rising series
But unfortunately
They said as a result
Of reviewing titles and development
At Capcom Vancouver
Capcom has decided to
Cancel the development
Of projects at the studio
And will concentrate development
On major titles in Japan
So
No more Dead Rising
At least
I guess not
Not from this studio
Yeah and they were doing
Dead Rising and I guess also
They had a
Puzzle Fighter
Was the other thing that they
Worked on
Oh and that game kind of
They already announced that
That game was going to close
Not that long ago
Yeah that game
I don't think did that
Well
I think they went
The wrong model with it
Unfortunately
Yeah
But I thought the Puzzle Fighter
Was going to get a release
In kind of the
The more appropriate
You know pay
20 bucks up front
And get all the characters
Type of thing
I thought it was going to get
A release on Switch
PlayStation
I guess maybe not now
I don't know
I don't know where that stands
It's also kind of nebulous
With the Telltale stuff
I think it's kind of a given
That
Well they have like
The stranger things
The Netflix stuff
Is not going to be happening
Yeah that's unfortunate
I mean
And ironically enough
I want to say
Let's see
There's a game actually
Coming out
In just a couple weeks
You know that's from Telltale
Batman the enemy within
On the Switch
Oops
Maybe
In the sequel to the
Other Batman series
Which is weird though
Because if like it did so terribly
You'd think that they wouldn't
Make a sequel to it
Or well
You know but also
It's one of those
You have to weigh the cost
Of how much to port it
Versus you know
What's the likely return
On you know
Going to another console
Like the Switch
And we've seen so many titles
Kind of end up getting ported
Over to the Switch
That they must think
There's you know
Money to be made there
I mean
And in the case of Telltale
Not to you know
Take the spotlight off
Which is important too
But
Telltale does still have a
Skeleton crew
We just don't know how
For how much longer
So assumably
This crew that's left
Is dealing with these
Commitments that are already
There such as the Batman thing
And whatever else is left
But
For the most part
The studio's done
Yeah
And so for Capcom Vancouver
It's done done
Right
They'll shift all that to
Japan and what have you
Yep
Well
That is unfortunate
Fifth Dream in chat
Over at live.vognetwork.com
It says
Man I was looking forward to
Puzzle Fighter
The mobile one literally had
A bug in the tutorial
That prevented me from
Ever playing
Then again
Maybe that's a sign of
Why it went poof
Um
When yeah
When bugs are reported
You definitely need to act
On those bugs
It's very fascinating
I just feel like
It seems like nowadays
Testing is so sloppy
Like with just this stuff
Or that they just push
Not necessarily maybe
That the testing's like
Yeah
They're just like
Eh it's fine
Let's just put it out
I think it's definitely
I think the testing
Isn't sloppy at all
Picks up a lot of stuff
I think sometimes
It's a question of
What are we willing to
Push the game back
To do
Um
To fix and so forth
And so uh
That is uh
That is
Had a very interesting
Effect here in the year
Cause I think a lot of games
Have bugs that
Well and no
Get
They're identified in testing
But the game comes out anyway
I would bet
You know Bethesda's infamous
For all the bug stuff
I would bet so much of
That stuff gets called out
And they say
Um
We're gonna do it anyway
Because you know
Again it's
Cost to fix
And the time table
And are we gonna be able to
Meet the shipping day
And all that stuff
Because so many games
Have to be out in November
You gotta
That's why they don't
Bug fix
You know
Skyrim anymore
Oh but they'll fucking make
You know
More DLC that they can
Charge for
I mean
Mods
They can charge for
Well I'm hoping
You know
We've seen this happen
With movies
Over the past few years
That you get
Now not just in summer
And the winter
Holiday season
You're seeing
Big movies
Basically year round
You're seeing
Big big movies
Almost all times
Throughout the year
Except maybe early January
Is the one time
You don't really see
Big big movies
Anymore
But that's spreading
More year round
And I kind of hope
We're getting to a similar
Place with games
It sure feels like it
Especially amongst the years
We've done
OLR here
Is that I remember
It was like
All the games
Were in October
January
March
Fiscal year
Type of things
April
And so forth
We're getting stuff
Even in the summer
And so forth
We're getting like
A big release
At least every month
It's feeling a little bit
More year round
And maybe that's gonna
Help alleviate
Some of the pressures
From investors
To deliver a product
At a certain time
At the sake of
Keep the bugs in
You know what I mean
Yeah
So
It'll be interesting
Anyway
Let's see
Going to chat
Nope
It's just weird
When it happens
We can afford weird
Ship it
Let's see
Tigerclaw says
That's true
But even last year
Proved
You don't have
You don't have to
Release in the fall
To be remembered
For the Oscars
Get Out
I believe it had been
Released in like
February or March
It was earlier
In the year
And people remembered
How good it was
When awards season
Came around
So it doesn't
Always happen
But
You know
There's ways to
Remind voters too
You know what I mean
That's why you have
Those four year
Consideration campaigns
Around the Oscar season
Go to a website
Like deadline.com
Or variety.com
These are like
Industry
News wires
And they're
Targeted at people
In the industry
And look at the
Type of ads
That show up there
It's all this
Four year
Consideration stuff
Like all
All around awards season
Also don't ever
Ever ever ever
Look at TMZ
TMZ is where you go
When you want like
Gutter trash rumors
Well yeah
What's Lindsay Lohan
Doing these days
I'm saying now
That actually they're
On my shit list
For how they
Make money off
Of people's grief
Well that's
That's not a new thing
Yeah but they're
Absolutely on my
Shit list now so
I'm not trying to
Sound like a jerk
But they should have
Been on your shit list
Years ago for that reason
Well they were
But I'm calling on
Anyone who posts
Anything from them
Right now
But here's the
Interesting thing
About that
Their techniques
Are shitty
They do find things out
First unfortunately
Through that method
And there is this
Inherent human need
To want to be
First
At something
Or first
I knew about that
Firsties first first
Those people
Need a life
That's
I'll tie this back
To gaming
That's why that
Thing they did
In Pokemon Go
This weekend
Was so brilliant
It was really brilliant
And if you don't
Try it
When community day
Finished
There was this
New Pokemon
No one had ever
Seen before
Unless maybe
The nut thing
The little nut thing
The little nut
Ghost thing
That showed up
In the game
And because
Nobody had seen it
It wasn't teased
Every forum
Every website
Every chat I'm on
That's even tangentially
About Pokemon Go
You've got people
That are posting
Look what I found
Look what I got
The gag is
That thing was
Everywhere
Like who didn't see
That thing
If they had
Their game open
But people
Want to be first
And so Pokemon Go
Got all this free
Shout out on
Social media everywhere
Because of little
Nut monster mon
Which is probably
The bonus Pokemon
That's going to be
In Pokemon Let's Go
Because they teased
That even though
It's the 151
From Kanto
There will be an
Additional mon
That shows up
It's going to be
That little dude
Yeah but when you
Catch it
It turns into a ditto
That was their
Little clever way
Of not letting you
Really catch it
Until
Gen 8 is announced
Or whatever
Dippy little thing
They're going to do
I think they're just
Trolling people
I think it's awesome
It is
It is in a way
Let's see
SDG100 Matt
In chat says
That was such a good troll
He says
It was everywhere
Ten fold
For the first 30 minutes
It's still around now
But the first 30 minutes
After community day
Was over
Yeah it was everywhere
Well let's talk
A little bit about
Community day
Or whatever
You were doing
With your gaming week
And a little adventure
We do called
How was your gaming week
So Dark Sakura
You can really do
The whole month if you want
But what kind of games
You've been playing lately
Well it starts
With a purchase
And I might have brought
This up in one of my
Radio Magic things
But on September 1st
Was mine and Dan's anniversary
You did talk about
The pinball table
If this is where we're going
Well I'm bringing it up
Again because it's
Fucking gorgeous
I have a theater
Finally and it's in
Perfect condition
Dan was like
I don't know what to do
With the table
I don't have to work on
We just play the shit out of it
And it's great
It's beautiful
So we have theater of magic
We've also gotten
The Shadow
And
Last Action Hero
Which actually more has
Sentimental value for us
And
I don't know some other one
That I don't remember
What we got
But whatever
Then
I've been playing
A lot of Pokemon Go
I've played some Ingress
Just not a whole lot
I'm back to playing
Bejeweled for some reason
Which is actually
Kind of crazily addictive
And I'm still playing
Idolpouring
But
That's really about it
I've been very busy
Work is weird
And then all my volunteer
Stuff is taking up my time
Oh no I did play something else
Oh yeah
We have the Nintendo out
So I did actually play
The Guardian Legend
Without it slowing me down
I love The Guardian Legend
That's just
Let's just take a moment
Gaming perfection
No Rob needs a moment of silence
I do
For reasons
Other than that
I've just been looking at stuff
And going
Oh that'd be cute
Like gaming accessories
Like
Girlie shit
Like my Triforce necklace
That I wore last night
And I was like
Oh you're wearing a Triforce
Yeah it's a Triforce necklace
It's cool
You know just
Little stuff and
Oh and Dan and I
Watched a playthrough
That was done like
We weren't actually playing it
But it was funny
Because we were watching
A playthrough of like
Transformers Devastation
And it was done like a movie
With the soundtrack for
Transformers the movie in it
As in the real movie
Not these live action
Pieces of shit
Which by the way
I'm gonna see
Transformers the movie
On the 27th
In the theater
Bam
I know you're seeing it
The week before
I'm seeing Gaga in
A Star is Born
Because that came up
On Facebook this week
I'm going to see
The better movie
No you're not
Years won't win an Oscar
We've had people who
Were in that movie
On this show
No I know
I know
I'm not hating on
The Transformers thing
I've also still decided
That if anyone was gonna
Narrate my life
Maybe Morgan Freeman
Or Sammy L
Wanda Sykes for me
It'd be Greg Berger
As Grimlock
I'm sure he's very
Happy to hear that
Well he seemed to be
Alright
So no other games
To share for now
Alright let's move over to
I'm sorry she didn't
Talk about World of Warcraft
Because I was gonna
Talk about World of
Oh yeah I did play
World of Warcraft
Shit
This bitch right here
Yeah no because
I've been kind of playing
Eradically
Because she keeps yelling
At me that I'm not
Playing my Alliance
Character
If you hop on Alliance
And then do the
Argus stuff with me
So I can actually go through
Some of those dungeons
I haven't done yet
You need to bring back
Sassy Pants
She's still there
I didn't kill her
You can remake her
As a dark iron
Alright
Speaking of Pokemon Go
So this is like some
Late breaking news
Do do do do
So a friend of mine
Is said he needs
Three new friends
To finish his Mew quest
And so I'm like
But the thing is
All these people are
Replying to his post
Going
People are still playing
Pokemon Go
Whatever
This so last summer
You know type
That sort of thing
So I said
You know what buddy
His name's Curtis
Curtis I'm gonna try to
Actually help you here
Do you want me to give out
Your code on the radio show
And see what kind of
Strangers add you
And he said yes
So I would love it
If you would all add
My pal Curtis
As your friend in Pokemon Go
His code is
So get out your phones
Everybody
2 8 1 4
6 3 0 8
2 3 4 1
He said I could do it
So
I can't add him yet
Because I also
Need to add friends
For that quest too
At some point
Well then you both
Would get it
But yeah
But I have to wait
Until I actually have to
Do that so you know
Okay
This is completely real
As you know
Add him
Add him as your friend
This is my pal Curtis
I'll be there before
Too long so
My code will go out
I did the reality game
On Facebook
He was in it too
And he did a YouTube
He's on a YouTube show
That's a reality show
Called sequester
So
If you watch that
Type of garbage
You might have seen
This whole adding
Three friends thing
Makes me feel a lot like
The whole ingress thing
Where they want you to
Recruit people
And it's like
I can't recruit people
Because no one wants
To play this
Ingress
That badge doesn't do shit
It's like a vanity thing
Whereas in Pokemon
Like if you want to have Mew
The problem is
He really wants to have Mew
You
You have to actually
Add people
On Pokemon Go
So you have to add people
But I already added people
Why do I have to add more people?
I am actually in a Sacramento area
Pokemon Go player group
That all you have to do
Is post in there
And people will add you
If you want
Yeah
All right
Well we got
I see act deaf says
I'll add him
And so there's some people
Saying they're gonna add
So I appreciate that
Do that
Add him
All right
Loki
I played Pokemon Go a little bit
And
I don't know
What else
I loaded up an emulator
On my computer
To play
Ridge Racer R4
Because I saw the announcement
That came out
I was like
Oh yeah I like that game
Let me try playing that again
I did not age well
I don't know
It's all right
I like Ridge Racer R4
I mean it's one of the best
Ridge Racer games
But it does not look good
On that emulator
It just
I don't know
What magic they're gonna be able
To do on the TV
To make it look fantastic
Like I remember it
But that was not it
But it's still fun
And then
What else did I play
I tried a little bit
I was gonna download
The Forza Horizon 4 demo
But I'm like
Do I really need to download
A demo
I'll just buy the game
When it comes out
When you know
You're already gonna buy the game
Yeah it's like
I'll just buy the game
When it comes out
For what it's worth
It gives you a little bit
Of a jump start
On the game
And there's like
A clothing item
You unlock
Whoopty shit
But you get a little shirt
For doing the first part
Of the demo
A shirt for a driver
That's in a car
That I never see
Well actually no
You see the driver
Because they change
The little recaps
So you see the little driver
Standing next to the car
Going fuck yeah
I won
So you do see the drivers
In like the recap screens
Oh yeah
Well
It's very much a vanity thing though
It's very very much a vanity thing
You can't run over the sheep
The sheep will always avoid the car
That sounds like a challenge
Uh yeah
That was posted in our Discord
There was a little video
Where the sheep are programmed
So that they consistently
Run away from the car
So
Get enough cars
Lined up
Anything's possible
Loki wants to kill the sheep
It's just because they tell me
I can't kill the sheep
I mean come on
We're the classic days of
You know cruising
USA and stuff like that
Carmageddon
We're eating like
Smashing the deer
And it just
Gives everywhere
Gross
Alright anything else for your gaming week?
Um
No I think that was it
Okay my gaming week
Let me start with some of the stuff
That's been discussed already
So World of Warcraft
I am continuing my adventures
In World of Warcraft
So unlike Jamie
I've been playing Horde
Simply because my druid
Is on Horde
And I really wanted to play my druid
Um
And
Yeah
Although I was really kind of bored
Because my guild had like
Nobody playing in it
So I moved to a different guild
I'm in a guild with Dr. Ken
From Starboard Power Coupling
And so there's a few more chatty people there
So it's nice
It's nice to like
Not be playing an MMO by myself
Um
I think that helps World of Warcraft
Be a little better
And yeah I'm kind of into it
Like I'm
I'm into this expansion
I don't know how long I will be
Because I tend to like
Go through the leveling up thing
And then once I hit max level
I'm like
Eh fuck rating
And I kind of fizzle out
But we'll see
We'll see how long this keeps my interest
I like that they have
You know
It seems like there's more of a variety
Of things to do
As you level up
I like that they have like
This whole island expedition thing
It's kind of neat
I just did one of those today
And so it was like
Kind of like a
PvP
But it wasn't actually other players
It was computer controlled
AI
And it was like
You have to mine as much Azerite
As you can on the island
Faster than the other team
Um
And I thought it was kind of a neat
Little like minigame
So yeah
That was cool
Um
I played that
And uh
Yeah
It's kind of what I've been doing
In World of Warcraft
I also started Diablo 3
Again
Because season 15 just started on Friday
So
Gotta start another new character
And get all the cosmetic rewards
From getting to level 70
And all that stuff
So
I started doing that
Uh
Playing Diablo 3
Pokemon Go
Community day
Was this past weekend
Had a lot of fun
Just walking around the capital
I feel like with Chikorita
Man
Those were crazy
Like
I'm just talking like
The number of Chikorita
That were around
Like were more than any other
Community day
Yeah
And the shinies too
Because I got like three or four shinies
And I was able to evolve like two whole
Chikorita sets
And
Everybody in my group got five or six shinies
And we also
And we never do this
We took time out of Community day
To raid
So we went and re-rated
Over at um
The theater at the convention center
Had a Mewtwo that popped
You have to see my picture on Twitter
There were like 300 people
Swarming around this building
Where there was a Mewtwo
And just you know
Obviously you would go in
And the lobby would be full
Although we did
We ended up doing a private group
So that we could just
All increase our friendship levels
And all that
Um
So
And we took out Mewtwo there
And then we went to the church
You know at the capital park
Here in SAC
You know there's that church
That's right across the street
That's a gym as well
So Mewtwo popped there too
And so you had all these people
Lining the street
On one side
And all these people lining the street
On the other
Doing the same thing
And there was a Mewtwo that was there
So it was just
It was crazy
But it was cool
Um
But yeah it was
It was interesting
By 1.30
Which um
You know Pacific time
Community day goes
11 am to 2 pm
So by 1.30
We were like
It's getting hot
Supposed to be like 94 today
Um
Are we kind of done?
And everyone was like
Yeah we're done
We've got like five
Six shinies
We're good
So we called it a day
Like 30 minutes early
Which we never do
Yeah
Because like
With EV community day
There's like 10 shinies
Into each of the set
You know
Of EVs
So you could have like
A ton of different shiny EVs
Basically
But
I don't know
Chikorita is like
Eh
I don't really want this
Yeah
Well no
Chikorita is cool
It's actually
Ironically it's pumpkin spice
Chikorita
Is what it looks like to me
So
An appropriate fall flavor
I got a shiny Charmander
The other day
Oh just randomly?
Just randomly
Yeah it's nice that once you have
Like the community day
Then the shinies are kind of like
Good
They're just like
Less of a spawn
But you'll find them
Like the
Well they didn't get a community day
But those swabloos
Like I've
I just randomly have picked up
Two of them
Just catching like
Regular Pokemon
It's kind of
Kind of cool
Other games that I've played
Doesn't stop there
So I've also been playing
Forza Horizon 4
I downloaded the demo for that
So the
I did download the demo
Because I wanted to get in there
And
So it starts with
You rate
It's very much like
Shoving down your throat
Did you know that this game
Has seasons?
And so it's like
Race through the autumn season
Now race through the winter season
Now it's the summer
So you go
Does it change as you go
Throughout the year
Or is it just
Not in this demo
In the demo
I know the demo doesn't
The demo just kind of like
Like because it was four
Different type of races
Like it started with like
A very generic type of race
In the autumn
And then the winner was like
You were in this big dune buggy
Going through the snow
And you did like this big ramp
And then summer
I remember you're racing
Motorcycles
And the motorcycles all had
And it was a really cool effect
Like one thing I just love
About Forza
Is that it's extra as fuck
Like it's so extra
Like you'll be driving down
Like confetti cannons
Going off everywhere
And like the sheep
Chasing the sheep
I consider as like
An extra thing too
And it's just like
Extra extra extra
And since you know what
Since this week Mario Kart
Got ruined for a lot of us
I'll just leave it at that
Mario Kart
And one particular character
In Mario Kart
Got ruined for a lot of people
So people are gonna be funny
A break maybe
I think Forza
You know it's a very different
type of game
But I just love how
Over the top it is
It's why I prefer
The Horizon series
Way much more than the mainline
Forza Motorsport games
It's just
It's arcadey
And it's so extra
Like flying
So you do the season thing
And I honestly thought
That was gonna be it
I was like
Oh is that
I downloaded 25 gigs for that
That's gonna be it
But then no
The game starts up
It's like
So what do you want
Your name to be
And what's awesome
Like they've recorded
Like 500 names
So you can like
Have the announcer
Call you my name right
But one of the nicknames
You can be
Roberts
So they call me Roberts
So
Which is kind of funny
So I play the game as that
And it lets you start the game
So you do this race
You do another race
And then you do like a stunt
They're like
We want you to be a stunt double
In this new movie
And you do a stunt race
Where you go like
Flying through a windmill
And you fly off the cliff
Into a field
And it looks
Like I was playing
My PC
And my PC can only run
On like medium settings
Because you know
Even though my computer
Is like two years old
At this point
It was top of the line
When I got it
Well it's only two years old
Now you know
It's like
Might as well bought it
A decade ago
Um
But it looked beautiful
Even in the medium mode
So um
Yeah I was
Enjoying Forza
So cool
Cool
Um
I think that's probably it
Finally for my gaming week
I think that's most of the stuff
I've been playing this week
Bobby says the seasons
Change every week
Like real week
Yeah
Or
Because
I know it keeps telling me
It says um
Um
Progress towards autumn
And then autumn unlocked
But I haven't unlocked it yet
Because I had to stop the demo
Because I was just doing it today
So I had to stop the demo
To prep for OLR
I did the stunt race thing
And that's where I stopped the demo
But I saw a hella
Like other people
On my Xbox friends list
Like every race I did
Was completely full
With gamer tags
From my Xbox
Like I raced against
Black Wolf
I mean I know it's not really them
Because I whooped them all
And that would not have happened
If they had been the real drivers
But it's still kind of fun to see
You know
Stuff based off your friends
Or whatever so
That's pretty cool
Um
Bobby Black Wolf says
Yes every real week
The season changes
Interesting
Bobby also points out
That's just the Drivatar system
Yeah
Well the nice thing is
You'll all see my license plate
So my license plate was
Hi
That's my license plate
H-I-E
Hi
So enjoy that
Alright
S2100 Matt says
I need this game to come out already
I also wish I had an Xbox One X
And a 4K TV to fully enjoy it
Uh
What early access
On September 28th
I don't believe in the early
Like they want you to buy
The Ultra
Edition
You know
The like hundred dollar
Forza
Comes with early
You don't need the game that quick
Like give it a
I think it comes out
Like a week later
For everybody else
So
Oh
Yeah
Maybe you do need the game that quick
I don't know
It's your money
Spend it how you want
It's only on the second
I think
Yeah
You don't have to wait that long for it
It's coming out soon
Alright so that was my gaming week
Let's move on
Announcements
I don't really have a lot of
A ton of things to say
Um
Since we had the unexpected week off
Earlier in the month
We don't really have anything planned
Until probably
Um
I don't even know if we'll be off the week
Thanks
Probably not until the holidays
We'll be looking at any shows off
At least planned ones
Knock on wood
Hopefully nothing unexpected happens
Follow us on Twitter
Twitter.com
Slash O-L-R
We're also on Facebook
Facebook.com
And we also have
The Orange Lounge Radio
Let's get into some longer news tonight
And some other things that are happening
In the gaming world
Loki we'll start with you
Yes
It's the PlayStation Classic
You might think
Hey wait a second
Isn't Nintendo the one that releases
These consoles that are smaller
That are a hundred bucks
That have games in them
But no
Sony wants to jump in on that
Like they did on motion control
And they want a piece of that action
So
Coming out December 3rd
In US Canada
Europe
Japan and Australia
You're gonna get
A PlayStation Classic for
99.99
Or you know
The equivalent in your territory
And they will include 20 games
As well as two controllers
It won't include an AC adapter though
But it will be bundled with USB cable
That you can power it by
I think that's dumb
But whatever
Games that they've announced so far
They're gonna be in there
Final Fantasy 7
Jumping Flash
Ridge Racer
Type 4
Tekken 3
And Wild Arms
It's not a bad lineup so far
I'd be interested to see
How we can hack this thing
Cause you know it's gonna happen day one
It always does
I would even be more surprised
If it isn't running the same hardware
As the SNES Classic and stuff
Cause I think those you can actually run
PlayStation Emulators in as well
But yeah
This thing will be running Nintendo games
In no time
You know
Okay speaking of all that
Something I completely forgot
And left out of my gaming week
Was that I did play those NES Classics
On Tuesday night
Oh yeah
I got the whole online thing
And I purchased that
And I looked at that
I'm like
No I played
Bobby was streaming
So I'm still having the cable issues at home
So I can't stream to Twitch
I mean I can do the radio show
Cause it's low bandwidth
But I can't do Twitch
But I was like
Well if I can't do my own stream
I'll crash someone else's
So I went on to Bobby
You didn't fix your cable
When they came out here
Okay so long story short
The guy that was here
Like he definitely tried
And he was definitely like
Okay I do see a problem
And he showed me
And he listened to what I was saying
And he like
Okay yeah I get it
I see what your problem is
Cool
And he actually went up the pole
And looked and he's like
Look at what I'm seeing
He showed me
He's like
See all this noise here
This is a problem
I want to see which outlet
Is coming from
He looked at the outlets
He said
Okay your living room outlet
Is a problem
And he said
Okay so see
Now all the noise is gone
So give it 24 hours
And see where it's gonna be at from here
So I was like
Okay
At least this guy listened to me
He showed me something tangible
He was working on
I'm like totally like
Happy
But the problem is
He didn't fix it
I mean
He tried
You tried
But unfortunately he didn't fix the issue
So I gotta
In all fairness
Comcast was supposed to follow up with me
They haven't
So I'll have to run that up the flagpole again
I've just been kinda
On other things this week
Where I'm just kinda getting used to this life
Where it's like
I guess I'm not gonna be able to stream to Twitch
Although that's gonna be a problem
When this show wants to move to Twitch
But uh
We'll just have to cross that bridge
And we get to it
We may have to move the place we do this show
We'll see
Well I hear that Verizon's got
Their 5G or whatever that they're offering now
With their service
For 50 bucks a month
Gigabit down
And apparently
Um
It's in Sacramento
Sure
Not where I live
Yeah
Slightly outside of Sacramento
But in Sacramento proper
They get all the fucking nice shit
Does that count Sacramento County
Because I'm not in Sacramento proper
I'm in Sacramento County
Yeah
Exactly
So anyway
But you're closer
Than I am so
So anyway
No resolution to that yet
So I was crashing Bobby's stream
And we were playing
Now we tried to play the online multiplayer
It did lag a little bit
Like I could feel
A little sluggishness
Like playing
Muddy waters type of thing
Like when I was playing
Super Mario Brothers
Like this doesn't
This doesn't snap
The way it should
When I play it usually
Like it wasn't horrific
But it was definitely noticeable
But what we did
And we don't know what that could
Could that be my cable problems at home
Could that be the fact
He's streaming
And doing the NES
Who knows
So we put it into low latency mode
And it was fine
So if you have problems playing
Online with your friends
Go look for that low latency mode
And turn it on
Because I don't know why
Low latency isn't on by default
But for whatever reason it's not
Why is there even a mode to turn that on
If that makes it run good
I don't understand
Like what
I'm not sure
Maybe somebody in chat knows
Maybe Bobby or something
What are you sacrificing
To get low latency
Because that's where my mind is
Like why would that not be the norm
Is it that I can't stream the whole game
I mean literally the game downloads
Faster than a
You know
Than a web page
I don't understand what
What you would be
Sacrificing in low latency
Yeah I didn't understand that either
But anyway
To register participation
For this week's episode
Of Orange Lounge Radio
At vognetwork.com
Use the passphrase
COAST
It worked fine in low latency mode
And we had a good time
It's just that
There's not a lot of like
Riveting two player games
We played Dr. Mario
We tried to play Double Dragon
And then realized
Oh yeah
NES Double Dragon
They had that shitty little versus mode
For two player
But the game itself
Was not two player simultaneous
Like it was in the arcade
I think Double Dragon 2 had that
But not the first Double Dragon
So
It didn't
I know right
No it didn't
And so
I don't know
We were going to play
River City Ransom
But then by that time
Dinner was done
So we never
Got around to playing
That stuff
So maybe a stream
Later in the week
I don't know
But anyway
The reason why I brought all that up
It does tie into the Sony thing
I'm not trying to take the spotlight off this
But you were talking about
When does that thing get hacked
Well the Nintendo thing
Got hacked within 24 hours
They were running Kirby on that thing
By loading the ROM
So
And that's
Was kind of
A shocking
Well I don't want to say shocked
You probably weren't shocked Loki
But in some ways I think
I was so surprised
Some of us were really
Having to deal with the reality of
Nintendo was not doing anything
To tweak these games
To run online
They were not in there
Doing with the code or anything
Nintendo is artificially holding back
Releasing games on this thing
Because there is nothing
To prevent
Nintendo first party titles anyway
From being on Netflix today
Like Super Mario Brothers 2
No reason that should be missing right now
Kirby
Things that are first party
Now I completely understand
You may have licensing things with Konami
Although they have Gradius today
You may still have things with Capcom
You know I understand
Not everything could be there
Especially third party stuff
But as far as Nintendo first party stuff
It is artificially being held back
And so
I think a lot of us are kind of having to
Swallow that pill this week
That you know
Alright
This is how Nintendo is going to do it
I mean
Is it still the better alternative
To charging five dollars a game
Probably
But it is a little bit frustrating
That this could have been a big thing
This thing could have landed with a thud
And now it's kind of landing with a
Okay
Neat
Yeah they could have said
Hey Virtual Console 2.0
Now they have multiplayer
Here's a ton of games
We're going to sell to you
For like five bucks each
Or whatever
And people are like
Oh yeah
And they could have made so much money
And kept
And
Kept multiplayer free
So they would have
You know
The advantage of showing
Oh hey
We don't
Because you know
They could probably make up that
Twenty bucks in Virtual Console sales
Easy
You know
Because some people are going to purchase
More some less
And they could have
Hey look
We don't charge for our multiplayer
But no
No
They didn't do that
Instead
Nintendo fans
Are going to stop them
Hackers proved
That
This hold back is artificial
This week
So
Take
Take what it is
Uh
Let's see
Act Efton Chat says
I can play Kirby's Adventure
And I have it on the Wii
And 3DS on the 3D Classic
So I can wait
Uh
Dark Tetsuya says
My only explanation is
Perhaps they didn't want people
To be overwhelmed
With a hundred games at launch
Why not though?
Imagine what a bombshell that would have been
If it's like
Dude we just opened the fucking floodgates
I can think of one reason
Their eShop
Is
Fucking
Terrible
Is why
And discoverability on that
Would be fucking terrible
It's all in one package
Oh yeah
You're not downloading game
By game by game
It's one
NES
And then once you get in there
You have all the different box arts
And things
But I believe
I didn't play a lot with this
I believe you can rearrange them
And pin your favorites to the top
You can kind of play with it
It's no worse than
Actually using Netflix
And I'm sure when the library
Does get bigger
You'll probably see similar
Stuff
Is it to not devalue the
NES Classic
Maybe?
I mean
Maybe
Because like
Isn't there a lot of overlap
In the NES Classic
In what this offers
I mean as far as like games
Uh
There
It's not a hundred percent
But certainly
Things like Mario Brothers
Mario 3
Zelda
Absolutely there's overlap
But there are things
Like Simon's Quest
Is on the NES Classic
It is not on
The Nintendo Switch thing
Has
Um
I don't believe
Is on the NES Classic
No I don't think so
So
You know
There are games on the
Swi-
So it's not a hundred percent
Overlap
But the
The first party stuff
Is mostly overlap
I think
I don't think Ice Hockey
Is on the
NES Classic
It is
I only
Impartial of that
Because I actually
Some of those black box games
Man I could just do without
Yeah
I mean
Sports ones
Nah I know
Forget that
Alright
You need Blades of Steel now
I'm sorry
To deviate the conversation
But I thought that
That hacking point
Kind of opened the door
To this other thing
That was really important
So talking about
The Sony thing for a minute
Where's your head at
With this Loki
Because for me
I'm
I'm kind of burned out
On these classic things
And this Sony thing
I'm sorry
This Sony thing
Does not sound like
It's worth
The premium price
They're charging for it
Um
I have to see
What other games are in there
I like
The idea
Of it
Um
I like
The better idea
Of hacking it apart
Because
You know the storage on that sucker
Is going to be pretty big
If it's got
You know
20 CD-ROM games in there
I mean
Especially when you're talking
Final Fantasy 7
Is three CD-ROMs
Right
Um
And I think Wild Arms
Is multiple as well
So
It'd be interesting to see
How that works
But
See especially
Like Final Fantasy 7
There's a great title
That I'm just
I'm burned out on it now
Yeah
I don't really care about 7
So much being on there
I mean like
It would be better though
If it was just on the
Goddamn PlayStation 4
Thank you
Is what it is
And they sell them
On the PlayStation 4
It's like these remasters
But
So but
By the way guys
This thing
With the classes
This answers the question
When will PlayStation 1 games
Be playable on PlayStation 4
Here's your answer
Never
This proves it
This is not in Sony's plan
To ever make those
PlayStation 1 games
That you just pop in your disc
And play them on the PlayStation 4
Nope
So guys now showing them
Hey you could charge them for it
All over again
And get away with it
And now they're gonna do it
And
But for me honestly
Again
They're charging a premium price
For this compared to Nintendo
I realize it's a more advanced console
But it's
It's over 20 years old
None of it is that advanced anymore
They're charging a hundred bucks for it
And they are shorting you
With the power cord
Which I understand
Like 3DS's don't come with chargers
But this is
This is a different conversation
With these classics
Because what
It's USB power
So they
They plug it into your TV
That's USB powered or something
I don't know
Eh
So or you have a charger
Or buy a Sony charger
Uh
So for whatever reason
They're skimming on that
My biggest thing that surprises me
Is the lack of DualShock
That
When Sony got the DualShock
Was when the PlayStation
Really start to
Took off
Take off
Because I don't know
If you guys remember
The PlayStation at first
Did not take off
The way that it did
A couple
Like remember when the PlayStation games
Were in those big ol' boxes
That's when they
The first came out
The PlayStation games
Were in those big ol' boxes
It wasn't until like
A year or two later
When DualShock came out
They kind of soft relaunched
The system
With some of the games
That they had then
And then they started
They scaled it down
To the CD size stuff
And you know
It started selling a lot better
So it's really weird to me
That this mini system
Represents that earlier era
Of PlayStation
Even though it's in the mini form
Uh
And not the later era
Of PlayStation
It's just kind of weird to me
So
Yeah
I don't know
I'm curious
I
Kaijuto says
No I don't want that shit
On my PlayStation 4
Well
Okay
But some of us do
I still enjoy playing retro classics
They have like PlayStation
I have a copy of Tekken 3
Like
I have some of the old
Like PlayStation 2 games
That they've remastered
Or whatever
Like they have
Uh
Like the Warriors for example
Or
But at least they remastered those
At least they remastered those
Well
I mean
I still have my Blamecast
It would be nice
To be able to just pop in the PS1 disc
Like I did on the PlayStation 3
That kind of set that expectation
If you're wondering like
Why am I holding Sony accountable to this
Because you could do it on the PlayStation 3
And so it feels like it's a little bit of a step backwards
And
Let's not forget
Microsoft is sitting over here
Trying to work
To make original Xbox games playable
On Xbox One
Well here's the other funnier thing too
When you think about this too
Like
And I saw the comparisons almost immediately
When the PlayStation Classic came out
They're like
PlayStation Classic
Can play all these PlayStation 1 games
Or you could get a PlayStation TV
For like 30 bucks
Have DualShock support
And it could also play PlayStation 1 games
And Vita games
And whatever else that you want to throw on there
I mean
That's the other rub too
Is like
Well you could have supported that system
And it could have done all this shit as well
And it didn't cost as much
Bobby Blackwolf in chat is asking
So in 20 years what will be on the PlayStation 4 Classic?
Uh
Horizon Zero Dawn
Last Guardian
Um
Probably like a lot of the first party Sony stuff
Spider-Man
Oh sure
Oh yeah the Spider-Man game
Infamous
Uh
The Last of Us remastered
Definitive Edition
Whatever it is
Last of Us 2 inevitably will be something that would probably be on there too
Or the PlayStation 3 Classic
Which will not have Rumble either
Because it's gonna just be 6X's
It's not gonna be before they have the DualShock 3
You know back when they were like
You don't need Rumble
We didn't pay the license ad again
But you don't need it
Alright well speaking of classics
I know this is one that folks here at Orange Lounge Radio can get behind
Did you know
Dance Dance Revolution's 20th anniversary is this week
In fact in two days
Konami is scheduled to make some sort of announcement
Uh
To celebrate
Please don't suck
20th anniversary
Could that be a new home version?
Or is it more likely a new release in arcades
I think maybe a new release in arcades
Maybe
Hopefully not a mobile game
But like you know
Oh god
Not a mobile game
Shake out
I hope it's a new game
It's been a couple years since Ace
Yeah it's been a couple years since Ace
Although I thought Ace was supposed to be the game that's like forever expandable
But maybe you know maybe they'll
Yeah well so are like all the other like
Beatmania games
I know
So what would DDR be
Will be the big 20th anniversary
No they'll go with some stupid naming convention like they have with 2DX
Like it's just
Call whatever they want
Whatever the fuck they want to call it
DDR20
Yeah pumpkin spice
Pumpkin spice mix
I like that
You know I'd be down for that
Dark Tetsuya thinks
I'm thinking DDRXX
No too many people
Especially
They are gonna be thinking about America at least a little bit
And they know that DDRXX
Is too close to DDRXX
Which is gonna have a very different type of connotation
No I would
I would hope something that
I don't know
I just hope it's not lame
Maybe DDRXX or something
I don't know
But I thought about
Well and X is too confusing too
Cause X is it's own series so
True
And so they can't really
And they already have an X2
That's true
So they can't really do that
I mean
Let's just go max 3
That's just extreme
They already extreme too
DDR20th mix
Just call it that
20th anniversary yeah
Well I mean
It's
Isn't it weird to think though
DDR is 20 years old
And we were kind of there at the beginning-ish
I mean
What this show
OLR started
4 years into that right
Cause we started 2002
And I think most of us were playing DDR first in 2001
If not sooner
Like Jamie was probably there in 99
I remember seeing it in 2000
Well I had my
My birthday
I got my second mix
For Dreamcast
But yeah I think I was playing
I wanna say around 2000
Cause we had found
Where did we find that machine?
It wasn't at Golfland
It was
We all met in 2000
You were playing before then
Cause we all met in 2000
Cause that was
I played at Anime Expo
Yeah
That was the year I lived at Melrose Place
It was 2000
January 2000
Yeah
At Anime Expo Disneyland
And they had a third mix there
And they told me how to do Vivid
And I was singing along with Xanadu
You know
And like
I thought you never played before
People would say
And be like
But I've seen Xanadu 57 million times
It's Olivia Newton-John
Olivia Newton-John people
Is that why it's called the Olivia Pro-
No shit
As the same Anime Expo where
The Chair
The Chair was a character of that Anime Expo
I wasn't
I wasn't around for this
The Chair
I've never been to Anime Expo
And I plan to keep it that way
I have a picture of Chair
On the DDR machine
Okay
This was yeah
This was the one time it was the Disneyland hotel
And the cosplayers kept getting kicked out of the park
Oh I heard about all that fuckery
It's the reason why they didn't do it there again since
Alright anyway
SD200Matt talking about DDR20 in our chat saying
So a few months ago
The top DDR players took to Twitter
To ask Konami
Make things better with DDR with a number
I don't remember what it was
Konami actually responded to them
And said
We hear you and we have big things in the works
And then we got
Dancing Sta-
Or what was the
Dance Fl-
What the fuck's that new one
That everybody's losing their shit about
Dance Rush
Which I still haven't played
No me neither
Wah
That's what I should have done this weekend
Taken an impromptu trip to round one to play that
Cause I still haven't played it
Well
I can't wait for my fat old ass to get on that machine
Wait so long enough it'll be down here
Yeah it's true
It's true if I wait long enough
Alright
Anyway
Let's move on
To our Sakura
I mean god we've had all this news but
There was like a pretty big event going on
Across the ocean right
Yeah there was
And so I thought I would just go with
Some of the best
Ranked stuff that came out of Tokyo Game Show
And if any of this is
Comes up later on in the show
I'm not trying to step on any toes
I'm not gonna go into any
Type of detail about this
But I will just make the announcements
If that's cool with everybody
So Ace Combat 7 Skies Unknown
Is on the list
And it looks like it's got VR support
There also is going to be
Another Catherine game
Catherine Full Body
For PS4 and Vita
You know it's funny
I actually read the Catherine novels
Very interesting
I'll just leave it there
Also coming out is
Days Gone for PS4
But there was
A motorcycle to advertise it
Also
Looks like we have
Dead or Alive 6
And it looks very pretty with
Blood splatter for every punch
We also have
I'm waiting for some of these to load
Of course there's Death Stranding
So hopefully we'll know
More about this
Maybe
So you know what we saw
There was a trailer
With a dude in a golden mask
And it was revealed that
That guy was Troy Baker
And again
This game is very like
That's all I need to know
What is it?
What is this game?
There is a guy in like
Diving gear
Under water
But his gear is off
His face is
His mask is off
So whatever that is
So
God why is it taking so long to load
I'm sorry about this guys
There we go
So
Devil May Cry 5
Which
Yay
There'll be a little bit more about that
Coming up I know for sure
At least coming from the director
Of Devil May Cry 5
And then
Next up
Gosh I'm so sorry this is taking so long
Man Dead or Alive 6 looks awesome
Dragon Quest Builders 2
We knew that was coming
But we just haven't really
Seen the game itself yet
I don't believe
So
Or did
Did 1 and 2 never
I thought they were gonna get
A combo package on the Switch
Did that never happen?
I don't think so
Oh alright
I guess I thought that would've
Happened a long time ago
There's another game
Um
Coming up by Inti Creates
But they did a game
Um
Called Dragon March for Death
This is the same studio that did
Mega Man Zero
Um
The art style looks really nice
There's also everybody's golf VR
Whatever it's golf
Uh
Fortnite was at Tokyo Game Show
That's interesting
Yeah
But it looks like people were
Playing the shit off of it
Is it though? Because
If it was
Was it
At Sony's booth because
You know that is the best console
To play it on according to Sony
Well no I'm more saying the fact that like
It feels like everywhere you go here
People are playing Fortnite
And people know of Fortnite
So it's interesting that Japan
I don't know if it's
That big
But it's still
Big enough
There's a
Yakuza game called
Judge Eyes coming out
Um
It looks interesting
There's also
Kingdom Hearts 3
Um
Mega Man 11
For PS4
Xbox One
We're getting a new
Kingdom Hearts game?
Eventually
Well they showed off
It was a trailer with
Big Hero 6
So that's kind of cool
Yeah no the new footage was cool
There's another game called
Ninjala
That's um
Kind of
Splatoon-ish
From what it looks like
But definitely different
Mechanics for PVP
Um
I'm almost to the list
Let's see
That looks like arms
Uh
Persona Q2 Full Cinema Labyrinth
Um
It looks
Interesting for its style
But definitely has the same
Dungeon crawling elements in it
Um
There's also
Resident Evil 2 remake
Which I am super excited about
Because
Hello they should have
Remade this a long time ago
Um
There's Tetris Effect for PS4 and PSVR
So it looks like it's Tetris with
A musical element
It's amazing
It's fucking
They showed this at E3
It's the rez guy
It's Mizuguchi doing Tetris
It looks fucking amazing
And then there's Warriors Orochi 4
Um
You know which is
Just those usual
Warriors game
Um
But it's actually
Over there
It's actually Orochi Musou 3 in Japan
But we got it
As Warriors Orochi 4
Here in the US
Um
And then that's it
So those are things coming
The biggest hype coming out of Tokyo Game Show
I'd still like to go to Tokyo Game Show
One day
I know
My check will come
One day I'll have money
Alright
Let's move on
Loki
Maybe some not so great news
Coming out of Tokyo Game Show
Right
Yeah
So
Um
Unfortunately
The uh
Lack of Sony being into the Vita
Is finally caught up with the Vita
In Japan
Because remember
Japan is doing pretty good over there
But now
The Vita's dead
And
Unfortunately
Sony doesn't have
Anything coming out
That's been announced
As a successor for the Vita
Um
But yeah
Basically
As for portable gaming machine
There are no plans for anything
After the Vita
Um
And right now
That there's no
Yeah
Hardware successor
That they're working on
So
That's unfortunate
Too bad
I'm surprised with the Switch being so
Powerful and everything
That
They might reconsider
Since you know
They like copying Nintendo obviously
With
Everything that they do
Yeah
I um
I mean I don't know
I am and I'm not surprised
To hear this
About the Vita
Like I still thought the Vita
Had anything to do
With the Vita
But
Yeah
I still thought the Vita
Had
A lot of life span
Going for it
In Japan
You know
I feel like when we do the Japanese releases
We're still having quite frequently
Japanese releases on the Vita
So
I thought for that
You know
Purpose
There would still be
You know
Some sort of official support
From Sony
Because Sony
Those games don't have to stop coming out
This is the Vita
I'm not quite dead
I think I'll go for
Well just because
Yes
But Sony's like
No you're dead
You know
Just because Sony
They might as well
You know
It's kind of
Once the company's kind of
Officially stopped
I mean
I get it
There's still people making games
To the Dreamcast
But
A lot of the
You know
You realize these are different things
I feel happy
Those sorts of pet projects
Are very different from
You know
The
Weekly releases
And all that stuff
So
I mean
As far as the US is concerned
I'm not surprised at all
To hear this
The Vita's been effectively dead here
For some time
Yeah
But it's
But I
To be honest
I don't want Sony
Doing another portable system
If they're gonna treat it
Like they did that one
Why should Sony do
Another portable system
If they're just gonna turn
Their back on it
So quickly
Like they did the last one
Like
I think it's for the best
They don't
Do another system
Anyway
Uh
Kaijuto says
No no
This is different
This is not talk about
How it feels
Dead in the US
This is Sony saying
We are pulling the plug
In 2019
So
This is much different
Than what usually comes up
Deft says
Vita means life
Well
Now your Vita
Is a
Huerta?
I don't know what to
Say
Alright
Uh
Let's move on
And talk about
I kind of referred to this
Already earlier
So I kind of repeating myself
A little bit
Sorry
But I just couldn't help
The servers did indeed
Already breach Nintendo's
Online system
So what happened is
That they were uploading
New NES ROMs
Into the library
Essentially
Uh
What they
I don't understand
All the inner workings
Of how this works
Maybe Loki you know more
About this stuff than I do
All I know is I saw the receipts
Somebody posted a video
Yeah
And they fired up a game
And it was not the game
That was
It was not River City Ransom
It was Kirby
So they
They were able to
Like swap out
One NES file for another
Yeah basically
They were stored as plain
NES ROMs
So it's just
The normal
ROM file for
Um
For an NES cartridge
So like they have
Battletoads
Is one that
They had a video of
That they took
Oh yeah I saw the
Battletoads one too
So you know
And as we got into
A little bit earlier
So not to repeat
Ourselves too bad
But basically you know
This does prove that
Nintendo
Has done all this work
On the emulator
To be able to do
The online games
And all that
And release all of their
Games right now
If they wanted to
They have chosen not to
For whatever
Yeah but I don't know
Like obviously we haven't seen
This like play
In online or something
Like that
Like with other people
I would assume that
It's all emulator based
So but
Um
You know
They could use that
As the excuse of
Well these games
Need to be changed
For
I don't think so though
It's just
It's just they're not
Well also with the
Nintendo online
You know there's
Different filters
And different modes
And filters you can use
As CRT
Where you can kind of
Purposely make your screen
Look dirty
Like an old television
Would have looked
Which you know
Or if you have kids
You don't have to do that
At all
It's naturally dirty
If you want the authentic
Look or whatever
I guess you could go for that
Filters can be fun
But some people saying
Taking to social media
Saying
The CRT TV
Is causing
Burn in
On my
Or at least something
That kind of looks like it
This went up to Reddit
And basically said
Some NES games
There's discoloration
On the Switch screen
After this
So
They did
They posted all this stuff
But
Apparently
It's a rendering issue
And not actually
Any type of burn in
It's not
It's just a rendering thing
It's displaying
The
Stuff on the menu
Kind of like it's
Bleeding through
From the rendering
Of the NES game
Or something like that
Nintendo did not officially
Comment on all this stuff
But it doesn't sound like
It's as bad
As the internet
Was making it out to be
Because that's never
Happened before
But also
Eh
Don't use that CRT filter
Well that
And also like
I just
Eh
I would
Oh
Minimal viable product
Is a phrase I like to use
You know
At work
And with a lot of things
And
So for as long as this
Took to happen
There's still weird shit
Like this out there
Yeah it's just like that
You know
They used the same damn
Emulator that they made for
The NES Classic and stuff
I'm not gonna complain
That they were giving us
Online play for free
All this extra time
Since Nintendo Online
Real
Really the NES classes
Is really the only new thing
At least it feels like anyway
That we're getting with them
But it does feel pathetic
Though that they can't even
Get that to run correctly
I mean they shouldn't even
Have a mode that
Toggle low latency
You should just
Be on
If that's what it takes
To run
Like I don't even understand
The problem is
And not just a knock
Um
I do
I do want to stress though
Our situation with him
Streaming in my
But not even necessarily
Just this
Like the Capcom
Arcade collection
That just came out
That beat him up one
Is fucked
When it comes to
Online mode
And the Switch as well
And they have like
Lag issues like
It's just like
It's stuttery
It's so bad
But that's just
Another issue
It's like
Come on you guys
You know that this
Probably exists
Why
Why not
Hold it off
A little bit longer
Alright
Let's move on
We have a few more
Stories to get to
Uh
Darcyra
Well
As I might have teased
Earlier
There was
Uh
Something from
The Devil May Cry director
And this is not
Quite what people
Think it is
Um
Uh
There was
Um
An interview
With him
Very recently
Um
Uh
It's no
Hideaki
And he was asked
The question
If he would like
To
And I'm just gonna
Read his whole
Response here
If I was allowed
I'd love to remake
Love to make
Rival Schools 3
I'd love to make
Dragon's Dogma 2
Capcom vs. SNK 3
Street Fighter Alpha 4
Power Stone 3
And if I could
Even Street Fighter 6
Would be amazing
But the big one
The one that we'd need
To get resolution on
Is Rival Schools
Because in Japan
There are three years
Of high school
We've seen the first
Two years for these kids
So the third one
Would be their last year
In high school
Wouldn't that be cool
Yes
Please make this happen
I'm going to find his Twitter
And I'm going to post
Every day Rival Schools 3
Rival Schools 3
Hashtag
Um
So
We need to get on this people
We made President Kat happen
Ha ha ha ha
Or we didn't make it happen
It never did come out in the US
Still
We encouraged them
And
If some sites are to be believed
It was like the worst selling Wii game
Of all time
So I'm not sure we actually
Made anything happen there
Dr. Sakura
Ha ha ha
It was just too
Too early
I know
It was ahead of its time
Yeah we were just extremely hipster
That's all
Because now we have
You know other
Cat centered games
Like cat lateral damage
And stuff like that
Yeah
Can't tell me something
Cat based
Won't sell well
In this type of internet
Ha ha
See if we brought it out
Over here
It would be
Asshole CEO
All right
Let's move on
Loki
So YouTube is closing
YouTube gaming
Because
Nobody likes to use the app
And
That's unfortunate
But
It's not
Entirely bad
So basically what they're doing
Is they're getting rid of
The dedicated app
For YouTube gaming
Because once again
A lot of people are just using
The main YouTube app
To watch YouTube gaming content
Instead
If you still want to
You know
Interested in just
The gaming content
For one
It kind of
Focused like that
You can go to
YouTube slash gaming
And it will show you
The same damn shit
So
And they kind of
Kind of set up
A little bit like
Twitch as well
When you look at it
That way
With all your
You know
Top live games
Live streamers
Gaming videos
From your subscriptions
That type of stuff
You know
I don't know
Like I think
With YouTube gaming
Like it was hard
Most people didn't
But there was a
Separate thing
Like if you want to
Look up gaming videos
Just go to YouTube
Exactly
I'm not going to fucking
Go to a separate app
For gaming
And like
I'll just watch it
On YouTube
Yeah I think that
Kind of like
Never like
Truly caught on
I really think
The YouTube gaming thing
Was really primarily
For the app
But when anything
You link online
And stuff
Is going to open
In the default
YouTube app
Like if I
If I tweet
My YouTube or something
YouTube gaming
Was always just kind of like
This different shell
This different set of clothes
That nobody went for
A YouTube feature
That's not coming
Together correctly
No
Not my YouTube
Well
I'm pretty sure
YouTube has already
Been blocked in China
But now
Twitch can join them
In that circle
Twitch has been
Banned in China
That was some big news
That hit around the
Internet this week
This is because
I guess
Let's see
China took home
Two gold medals
In the Jakarta
Palembang 2018
Asian games
It's a pan Asian
Multisport tournament basically
So there's
There's many different
Games that are played
Amongst all these different countries
Think of it like the Olympics
But like eSports
Over in Asia
So China
You know made its mark
But unfortunately
CCTV did not broadcast
The event
So Chinese fans
Went to Twitch
So a huge spike
In downloads
For the streaming site
Now this pings it
On Twitch's radar
And now
Twitch's website
Is inaccessible
It's inaccessible
In China
You can't get it
On the iOS app store
And you know this
Many observers
And analysts saying
That this is kind of a regular thing
Western media platforms
That get very popular
End up getting blocked
Twitch has confirmed
They've been blocked
In China
But they don't have any other details
At this time
So in some ways
It's kind of a
You made it kid
And in other ways
It's a
Well that's a bummer
Because there were probably
Folks in China
That wanted to watch
But they can't
Because they were being streamed
On Twitch
And what
How does this affect
Overwatch League
I'm kind of curious
Because don't we have
An expansion team in China
And all those games
Were being broadcast on Twitch
Or do they go
Are they on a
Different platform in China
Maybe they are
I just may not be aware
That there may be a
China centric
Live streaming platform
That they use over there
So I'm kind of curious about that
So there you go
So unfortunately
When we
Just finally make our move
To Twitch
Which is you know
Still on the radar
If these cable issues
Get fixed
We should be
Making our own move
To Twitch
Folks in China
Won't be able to see it
Live unfortunately
But I don't think
Anybody in China
Is listening live today
If you are
You should let us know
Because I would love
To hear from you
But remember
The podcast is not
Going to be changing at all
So if we have Chinese
Folks that listen
On the podcast
Well that will still
Be the same
Similar sort of set up
That you get it today
So
Act F says
I think Overwatch League games
Are also on
Major League gaming's website
Gotcha
I was going to say
There's got to be
Another option
Because that would be a bummer
To have this whole expansion team
For Overwatch League
And then
People in that city
Can't even watch it
Even though everybody
Is living in LA anyway
But oh well
Alright
Let's go back to
When things were simpler
Let's go back to a time
When we couldn't
Live stream games
You wanted to watch
We play a game
And you'd come over
And sit on the couch
Or we had to put
Our video camera
In front of our TV
To videotape
The high sports
And the VHS tape
That's right
Or when I was playing
Ultima Exodus
I would use
The sight spell
To get the map
For the dungeon
And I would record it
So I could refer
To it later
I used to draw my maps
My Zelda maps
Nice
Alright
On old food foods
So I had them
On denim
And rolled up this fold
It is the classic
Needed this week
Dark soccer is gonna
Climb into the gaming vault
And find a game or two
Which she thinks
Hey
You kids
Play this game
You don't need
No hundred dollar
Stinkin' PlayStation
Classic to play this
This is pre-rumble pack
N64 shit here
That's right
Here it is
Your classic game of the week
Dark soccer
What did you pick
For the classic game
Of the week this week?
I picked Chameleon Twist
Yay
Um
It is a pretty difficult game
It has a weird
Continue system
But it's treasure
Wait
No it's not
It's done soft
It's pre-treasure
Stuff
Anyway
Um
Chameleon Twist
Is
We play as one of four
Chameleons
And you go over
Different worlds
Um
It has a very long
Tongue
To use as a weapon
And you can also use it
Kind of as a grappling hook
And you can use
The tongue
You basically
Move the tongue
On its own
With the analog stick
And you also have
Like a training area
That you can learn
How to master
The tongue
Um
So you have to go through
Different indoor environments
You have a boss battle
And then you have to keep
Collecting hearts to
Replenish your
Uh
Your health
And you play as
A chameleon
Called
Davy
And he follows
A white rabbit
Into a magical ground
In the hole
And he becomes
A humanoid
In Wonderland
His friends are
Jack, Fred, and Linda
White people names
I don't
Like seriously
Um
No
I would say
Probably like
Caitlin's
But spelled differently
Anyway
Um
So with the
B button
You stick out
Your tongue
By the way
This was on
Nintendo 64
And then you move
The tongue around
With the analog stick
Which controls
You know
The movement there
So you can use that
To get power ups
At a distance
Or just swallow
Enemies
And it will retract
Back
Or until it bumps
A wall
Which will also
Make it back
Uh
Go back
So it is just
A standard
You know
Tongue thing
When they swallow
The enemies
But you have the option
Of spitting the
Enemy back out
Um
At the other enemies
Kind of
You know
Uh
Roshi
Or Kirby style
I mean
Except Kirby
Actually spits out
All your cute stars
Um
You know
You can launch
Into the air
By using your tongue
Um
You get
Like
Pretty much
Tongue vaulting
Tongue pull vaulting
Um
So you actually
Can use a pull
Um
With the tongue
As a grapple
And swing yourself
Across
You also have
Multi player mode
Which is two to four players
That has a battle royale
Or a time trial
Where um
You have to be
The last chameleon
Standing on the platform
For battle royale
Um
For the time trial
You have to stay
On the platform
The longest
And that's
Really
It
Came out in 1997
That was a while ago
God damn these fucking ads
Ad block Rob
Ad block
I thought I had it
On this computer
It's just time to upgrade
YouTube
Uh
It's time to upgrade
A lot
But that's it
It's Chameleon Twist
I don't know why I had it
In my brain
This was a treasure game
Well
It is a treasure
Of a different sort
There it is
Poopy treasure
Your classic game of the week
Chameleon Twist
Sunsoft
Alright
Uh
We're gonna take a break
We haven't done that
In a little while
Cause we've had magic
To hold us over
We're gonna take a break
Rob Cluffy
When we come back
There'll be plenty more
Orange Lounge Radio
Including uh
Your emails
Your calls
At Orange Lounge Radio
On Skype
And some other
Rapid fire news
We'll talk a little bit
About pinball
And Fortnite news
But maybe
Yay
Maybe for some people
It's actually a positive
I'll tell you what we mean
After we come back
From the break
With more of
Orange Lounge Radio
Welcome back everybody
To Orange Lounge Radio
Live with our 745th episode
Already in progress
For tonight
September 23rd of 2018
Dark Sakura joining us
In studio
Who has um
Not been able to be here
At the show live
For about a month
And unfortunately
Probably for a couple
More months
But able to visit
Like once a month
Yeah and I'm
Because of work
Yeah because of work
I'm trying to
Get things together
You know
But I will say
Speaking of work
I know I don't
Want to get into
Too many details
Cause isn't anyone's business
What you do during the day
But I did hear
You got like a promotion
You were going for at work
So
I'll put it this way
Big ups on that
Congrats
It was actually
It was the first job
I applied and interviewed for
Was in this position
And it wasn't the one I got
Because I think they were
Opening it for other temps
At the time
But I have
Gone up through the ranks
As high as I could go
In one direction
And I finally am in the
Department I wanted to be in
So
So as much as it sucks
That you can't always be here
On Sundays
This is a good thing for your
You know
And I got a raise out of it
So
Yeah so for your
So as much as it sucks
For you not being here
The reality is
You know
You're part of what you got to
Do to make that happen
So
I just want to give you
Congratulations
I'm sure all the listeners are
Going to say the same type of
Thing in chat
Because y'all rock here at
Orange Lawn Radio
It's appreciated
And I'm happy to do my radio
Magic you know
Yeah
Come over and visit
And do what I can to make
Make sure y'all don't forget
About me
We would
We could never
We would never
You could
You need to do more streaming
And that type of stuff
To keep us remembering
Who you are
Actually
To get me back to doing
More World of Warcraft
And you know
Cussing at people
I cuss at the characters
In the game Rob
I tell them that they're
Shitholes
You kind of should
Like Sylvanas is totally a bitch
Now
Like what happened
Like
And I'm not just saying
I'm not saying that because
It's the cheap shot
Because she's a woman
And anything
She is a bitch
She has turned into full on
Cunt monster
Okay you said it
I didn't
No I'm like
They're ruining her
They are
I used to like her
And now she's like
Why are you such a bitch
Like what crawled up your mall
And died
You know
Oh yeah
She's already dead inside
You know what I still think
That it would serve her right
If they made her alive again
Like for the final thing
I've
I've heard fan wank theories
Nothing official obviously
Blizzard's keeping that under wraps
But fan wank theory
Seems to think that's how this ends
Like it would be a much fitting
End for her
As opposed to what happened to Garrosh
Yeah
So it'd be interesting
To get in that direction
So
And they've done all these books
Like with her and her sisters
Getting back together
In different books
And everything
So
But I'm still doing the Argus content
Because I want to make a void elf
Although I will probably still play
My demon hunty
Because demon hunters fun
Yeah
I kind of miss my
My monk
My tauren monk
But my monk
I have a pandaren
My one bitch about
Well I'll say this
Then we'll get back into some
My one bitch about
Wow
I do not like how they
Locked those races
Behind these dumb achievements
In the last expansion
That you have to
That's stupid
I'm sorry
I'm glad I got my
My
What the fuck elf
Nightfallen
Uh huh
When I did
Before they put it behind
Well actually no
I was already
I already had
Elevated?
Exalted
With
With the
With that faction anyway
So maybe that's why I got it
I don't know
I just don't like it
It's dumb
It's stupid
Alright
How dare they
You know what's awesome
Some more gaming news
Rapid fire news
Starting off with Loki
Yes let's talk about
One of my favorite franchises
Earth Defense Force
Right around the corner
Earth Defense Force 5
Another game where you'll be
Shooting giant bugs
And they don't really change
A whole lot each game
But
It's a new one
And it's coming out
December 11th
Right around the corner
On Playstation 4
Hopefully PC at some point soon
I'll have to pick it up
Because I do
Because it's Earth Defense Force
And it's you
Of course you're gonna pick it up
It's Earth Defense Force
And it's like the same
Like when I talk about
Roster update man
That game is just like
It's the same shit
All the time
But I'm down
I'll bite you
You're gonna eat that shit up
With a spoon
And there's nothing wrong with that
Yes I will
I will do that
There is a rumor
That there is a possible
Leaked
Character from Smash Brothers Ultimate
Of course
Oh it must be a day
Ending in Y
On some web forum
Of course
Remember that
There are a lot of
Faked screenshots
So take this
With a grain of salt
But the picture shows Ken
Of Street Fighter 2
It could see that
Being like an echo fighter
For Ryu or something like that
But
That is a very obvious
Sort of echo character
But
It could also be
Incredibly bullshit
Fakes
So
Keep that in mind as well
But it is something that
I can see
Where they pad the roster
With that
So
Yeah
Don't be surprised
If that's an announcement
But don't be not surprised
If it's completely fake
Because
You know
A perfect
Perfect way to say that there
Don't be surprised
If it happens
But you know what
Don't be surprised
If it doesn't happen
Just don't be surprised
It's the internet y'all
Darktotu in chat
Over at Live.com
And I'll see you
In the next one
Bye
Darktotu in chat
Over at Live.vognetwork.com
Says
I want to believe Ken
Is really in the game
But yeah
I'm trying hard
Not to fall for this
I mean
It's
It does make a lot of sense
They just
They don't really have to give
Him anything special
It would just be a different look
Just an echo fighter
Yeah
Alright
We'll see
Anyway
Moving on with some more
Rapid fire news
This is certainly deserving
Of a
Of a longer story slot
But there isn't a lot
To say on this
Nobuo Imatsu
He did every Final Fantasy
Soundtrack pre-11
He's done a lot of this stuff
Since then too
He did music for Chrono Trigger
You know
Lots of great RPGs
He can probably think of
He is ceasing his current work
Due to health problems
He hasn't said what the health problem was
But he did say on his blog
In a post that he made
He's been affected by
A unnamed disease
For a few years
And it's now at a point
Where he is unable to act
At full capacity
So he's taking time to rest
And considering if he's
Gonna be able to do
Any future projects at all
Again we don't know
What the illness is
I'm not going to speculate here
Certainly many people are
You know
Inventing the scenarios
In their head
I'm just gonna hope
That he gets better
This
This is a decision
He's come to with his doctors
That if he's
It takes a break from work
And the stress
That comes with it
For a little while
It's gonna help him get better
I'm really really gonna hope
That that is the case
Cause Nobuo Imatsu
He's not
He's in his 50's
His late 50's
Not an old guy
So it's just
Yeah
You know
Sending well wishes
And thoughts
And you know
Healing vibes
His way
And you know
Obviously his impact
To games
Has been extraordinary
But if he needs to take a break
He's fucking earned it
So let's give him his privacy
Moving on to Tetris Effect
Which Dark Soccer brought up
A little bit earlier
But I'll kind of
Finish the thought here
Because not only did
We get to see that
At the Tokyo Game Show
We got a date
For that game
November 9th
Is when you can all start
Feeling Tetris Effect
So I'll finally be in my
PlayStation VR
By November 9th
Go play Rez
Come on
And I need to play this
I understand that you have
Like space issues in your room
But here's the best part
About it
The camera
Doesn't have to be on top
Of the TV
You can face it and complete
Oh that's good
I played VR in my kitchen
Without a TV even hooked up
Alright that's good to know
It's good to know
But anyway of course
You know
Everything else we've heard
About Tetris
Nothing else has changed
That zone mechanic
Where you can freeze time
And kind of build up
Your Tetris clears and stuff
And all that
So PlayStation 4
On November 9th
That is the big day for that
DarkSakura
You've got a couple of things
For us
I do
There has been something
Sent to the Game Rating
And Admission
Administration Committee
Of Korea
They have a rating out
For Castlevania Requiem
Symphony of the Night
And Rondo of Blood
For PlayStation 4
For a Japanese
Language release
We don't have any announcements
From Konami out here
But I mean that would simply be
Not turn in the moonlight
And Rondo of Blood
So yay
I hope
Could use another copy
Of that game
And then also
Sega announced a release
Of Sega Genesis Classics
For Nintendo Switch
Will be a 50 plus game bundle
That includes Golden Axe
Fantasy Star
Sonic the Hedgehog
And the Streets of Rage series
Also including a few
Like Kid Chameleon
And Toejam and Earl
So there you go
Alright
Let's travel around the world
And check out some release
Dates of things you get
To play a little sooner
Than that collection
On the Switch
Loki starting us off
In the US
Okay
So we've got
Galmetal World Tour
Edition on the Switch
Giana Sisters
Twisted Dreams
Out to
Or Owl
To admit
Edition
Because an owl
That's on the Switch
Oh ho ho
We've got
Metal Max
Xeno
On PlayStation 4
Moonlighter
On the Switch
Pathfinder
Kingmaker
On PC Mac
And Linux
Punchline
On PC
PlayStation 4
And Vita
It's not dead
Zavarier
Delta
On
The Switch
And PlayStation 4
South Park
The Stick of Truth
On the Switch
This is The Police 2
PlayStation 4
And Xbox One
Valkyria Chronicles 4
On PC
Switch
PlayStation 4
And Xbox One
The Walking Dead
The Final Season
Season
Or Episode 2
Suffer the Children
On PC
PlayStation 4
And Xbox One
Dragalia
Lost
On
Android
And iOS
And we've got
Life is Strange 2
Episode 1
On PC
PlayStation 4
And Xbox One
Super Neptunia
RPG
On the Switch
PlayStation 4
Dragon Ball
FighterZ
On the Switch
And finally
Last but not least
FIFA 19
On PlayStation 4
PlayStation 3
Xbox One
Xbox 360
The Switch
And
On PC
No Wii U version
I'm surprised
But then again
not surprised
Alright
Welcome to Japan
and looking at some of the releases there
on the PlayStation 4
on September the 27th
Iyudensetsu Senokisuke 4
The End of Saga
from Falcom
comes out
on again
September the 27th
is when that is out
and this game looks like
I'm trying to think if it's something that's
localized here
but I don't think it is
Legend Heroes?
Maybe?
Something like that?
I don't know
This game
What's it called?
Iyudensetsu Senokisuke 4
The End of Saga
I don't know
Legend Heroes?
Might be?
Anyway
That is coming out
That seems to be kind of the big
Legend of Heroes is what
Dr. Tetsuya thinks it is
Utaware Urumono Zan
comes out also as well this week in Japan
Musou Orochi 3
out this week as well
and that same
Utaware Urumono Zan
has a premium edition with that as well
So Super Neptunia RPG
is this week
as well as
a
Eternal Preservation edition of the
Iyudensetsu game I talked about just a moment ago
Taiyutama 2
You're the Only One
is out this week
as well as Warriors Orochi 4
in regular and
limited edition
There's also
a collector's edition on that as well
Assetto Corsa is out
as well as MotoGP 18
Kind of a busy week there in Japan
Taking a look at the Nintendo Switch real fast
to see if we're getting anything there
Oh yes
The World Ends With You Final Remix
I think some folks looking forward to that
That is out in Japan this week on the Switch
Senju no Valkyria 4
which I imagine is Valkyria Chronicles 4
also out this week on the Switch in Japan
That's Super Neptunia RPG
also out this week
and
Warriors Orochi 4
also out
and
Dragon Ball FighterZ
is out on the Switch this week in Japan
So I'm sure some folks will be eating that up
Let's go to the UK to our Sakura
Oh there is a bunch
So
Just for the 25th
We have FIFA 19 Champions Edition
Early Access
Jagged Alliance Rage
Valkyria Chronicles 4
This is Police 2
Total War Warhammer
Dark Gods Edition
Valtherian Arc
Hero School Story
That's on the 28th by the way
Warhammer was on the 27th
Again on the 28th
Blind
Dakar 18
FIFA 19
Fire Pro Wrestling
Little Dragons Cafe
Moonlighter
Forza Horizon 4 Ultimate
That's the edition with
Early Access
Super Street The Game
and Dragon Ball FighterZ
on Switch
That's it
Alright I think we're about to
head off to the mailbag
Every week you guys email us
participate at
and we read your emails here live on air
as long as you keep them classy
appropriate and all that
and we're gonna get into the mailbag this week
so let's do it
Dark Sakura's here
So she should read the emails again
I've been doing it lately
but I think Dark Sakura should get back to reading emails
What do you think Dark Sakura?
Sure
So this comes from Ryan
Hey O.L.R. while hanging out in the VOG Network Discord
which you can also participate in at
vognetwork.com slash discord
Brilliant plug
Thank Ryan
I noticed that Alan plays a bit of Dark Souls
whether a newbie or a seasoned player
I'm curious to hear about his experiences with the game
or if he had any cool stories to share
Love the show, Ryan
Alan was not in here to hear this message
No, Alan was not in here to hear this message
I will fix that here shortly
I'll get him in here, see if he's available
if he's not in the middle of an Overwatch match
Do we have another email?
Why don't you read that one while I work on Alan
Okay
Last episode you were discussing the face
of each company and couldn't come with
one for Sony other than Kazurai
who left Playstation inside of the company
in 2012
Here are a few guys you couldn't think of
Andrew House, Adam Boyz, and Shuhei Yoshida
The former two were no longer with the company
but were arguably the faces for a while
as they were the ones who show up at PSX
or E3 every stage
up until they left last year
Shuhei is the current president
of Sony Worldwide Studios, i.e. the person
who oversees each of their first-party studios
and also gets a share of stage appearances
Perhaps the fact you couldn't think of them
lends credence to the idea that Sony
doesn't have a strong face
as Iwata or Miyamoto or Reggie
but when you think of someone of the well-known
Playstation clips, it's usually those people
Like, here's how you share games with a friend
on a PS4 dig at Microsoft
with Shuhei and Adam in the video
Shu does get mobbed at E3 and PSX
for pictures, so he's certainly well-known
among some groups, and much like Stan Lee
who was the kickoff for the topic
Shu has had cameos
in a bunch of other video games
Oddly enough, not usually first-party
but indie games like Super Time
Force Ultra, Everything, and Velocity
have used him or his likeness
and this comes from
Andrew, that's all I'm gonna say
I don't have a nickname on it
Probably the closest thing
to a mascot or whatever
Shu is mentioned in that
but I
still don't know if even that is
on that same level as something like Miyamoto
or Reggie Fils-May
or has that social media presence
that Major Nelson has on Twitter for Microsoft
or some of that. I still don't feel
like it's quite at the same level
You know what I mean? I don't know
I appreciate their perspective
I kind of get where you're going
some of these guys are really recognized in some circles
but I don't know if they're
the face on that same level
but I should have thought of at least
one of those last week. Anyway
I want to go back to the previous email
I actually made him die on a boss
so he could answer this question
Hi Alan!
Dark Souls
because they're on the Discord servers
they can see that you're playing Dark Souls
all the time. So tell us a little bit about
playing Dark Souls and your experience with that
or if you have cool stories
Just the remastered is out
and I've moved on to Dark Souls 2
because I finally got burned out on the remaster
just these last couple of days
just the versatility of creating a build
like having a strength character that wields
like a giant
basically like a tree
like an uprooted tree that's just like wham
like bam bam from the Flintstones
or like a Dex character
or like a caster
all the different types of weapons
it's a really
there's a lot of stuff under the surface
aside from jest, it's really hard
and then of course a lot of it's
muscle memory so when you
beat it
the incentive is there to do
the new game plus stuff because
you're going to have a way more
fun time your second and third time through
because you know how to
get through everything
Now you're
playing so much Dark Souls
you've actually accomplished the rare accomplishment
of getting what is essential
I mean you're playing it on PC not Playstation 4
but you're getting basically the equivalent of the platinum trophy
you've gotten every single achievement in Dark Souls right?
Yeah the remaster yes
Wow that's pretty crazy
Why do you think this is the game that you want to
and you guys don't live with him
but I do, he plays this game, it's like this and Overwatch
if he's playing something that's not this or Overwatch
I'm like what the hell's going on, you okay?
What is it
Why this game is what you're into right now?
And I'm not asking that in an accusing way I'm just curious
what is driving the passion for that?
I sort of just have a really addictive
personality so when a game catches my attention
I play to the exclusion of all else for three
or four months and then I move on
to something else I'll probably end up
playing Mass Effect again or Skyrim
at some point and you'll be like if you see Skyrim
you're going to see nothing but Skyrim for about three or four months
and then I'll move on to something else
so it's just whatever
You play a game, you play a game
Yes, until I am absolutely sick of it
so it's kind of like
you know
my Steam library
has 300 games that I have only beaten
like 20 of them and I just play those same 20 games
over and over and over again
like Dragon Age Origins and I can't
speedrun that game, if I do another
Origins career it's probably about a 60 or 70
hour commitment
Now you've played Dark Souls 2 as well right?
Yes. But not really 3? Correct.
Why? Just
it's
it's the one I know the least
and I have fear of the unknown
because I can play the other two
inside and out so I'm like okay here's how I get
this really
incredible weapon that makes me overpowered
at a really early level. You weren't always that way right?
True, but you just
I don't know, I just watch
Let's Plays of YouTubes of like here's how to
become a hex caster
by level 10 and it's like
alright so I just need to do that
for Dark Souls 3. Alright so maybe
maybe in the next 3 or 4 months we'll see
Dark Souls 3. Yes. Alright.
I think you've satisfactorily answered the email
Thank you Alan, round of applause for Alan
Thank you. It says something that
he's quite the spouse
that I can pull him from whatever he's doing to make him
answer a listener email so there you go
Alright were there any more emails?
Yeah there was one more. Okay. Kind of a long one.
Okay. Hey all, thanks for
promoting, this is from Placo Jones by the way
Thanks for promoting my Twitch channel
on the show last week. I was wondering what your
thoughts were about the issues of Nintendo cloud saves
not working for all games. They're really
plugging this feature in the build up to the reveal
of their paid online service. But
just before launch they announced that it won't work
for some games including arguably their best online
title Splatoon 2
There's still no way to back up your saves for
Splatoon 2 and whichever other
online titles they won't allow cloud saves
for. So if your Switch breaks or
gets stolen you lose all that data which for me is
nearly 99 levels in Splatoon 2
as well as my gear gold snail
etc.
They claim to be doing this because people
could use cloud saves to cheat. For example
lose a ranked match that you
that would rank you down. Just reload an old save
from the cloud before that match.
That type of cheating or save
scumming did run rampant in Splatoon
1 but in my opinion isn't really a game
breaking cheat since it only affects that players
rank or some minor gear
update, upgrade rules or whatever else
save scumming could be used for. Usually pretty
minor stuff. Meanwhile
cheaters are everywhere in Splatoon 2 because
if you hack your Switch it's very easy
to tweak anything from your rank to your
weapons abilities to even the maps you
can load onto. So why would cheaters bother
save scumming when they can already
cheat in far more effective and game breaking
ways by hacking. And Nintendo
has no anti-cheat installed to stop these players.
They only go off reports from other players
so a smart cheater would just tweak themselves
to be powerful enough to
dominate matches but not so much that it raises
other players suspicions. Ironically
enough I'm considering hacking my Switch
since only then would I be able to
create a backup save because Nintendo
won't put a little extra work
to do what online games like Overwatch
already do which is just save your account data
on their own server instead of pulling it from
your console. Anyway
that's my rant on the subject. I'm overall very
unimpressed with the implementation of
Nintendo's paid online service
but that's a whole other topic. Thanks for the
great show. Can't wait for your move to
Twitch. Falco Jones. Yeah I just
you know because I remembered oh yeah I downloaded
the Nintendo app. Their online
app. Let's see what I'm paying for here.
Voice chat. Game specific
services. Splatoon 2.
I don't own Splatoon 2.
That's no fucking
use to me.
Some comments in chat over at
live.vognetwork.com. Bobby Blackwolf
our pal also on the network here says
they designed their online system terribly
and are trying to cover it up. They shouldn't
store your online data on your local system
they should store it 100% on their servers.
Exactly. There's a couple people jumping
in going yes this.
And that wouldn't be that hard to fix either
patch the shit. You can
patch your games now Nintendo.
Start storing it on the server
and then just
don't store it locally anymore and then you can do
the backups. This online thing really
has some of the you know I consider
Falco to have always been somebody who's you know been pretty
pretty quick to defend Nintendo and appreciate
Nintendo and you know
it's not just him but I'm picking on him because
of the email at the moment but I feel like a lot of
Nintendo fans out there like this online
thing even the most
heavy Nintendo fans
are having a hard time like sticking up for it
and even saying Nintendo has been making some
pretty shitty decisions with this thing. Like I get
the fence with them like oh we're not
paying a lot of money for it.
Oh it's Nintendo and Nintendo makes good games.
You know what though? Sony makes good
games. Microsoft makes good
games. Lots of companies make good games.
Sony and Microsoft as we have seen
and discussed on the show are also not infallible
to making bad decisions. They're just
bad decisions of a different sort usually.
It's not usually the online thing that's
well no I take that back because
it's interesting because Microsoft kind of
had Microsoft's big screw
up was really in how they delivered
the message of their online.
I think if they had delivered that message in a
different way we'd be looking at a
completely different like ecosystem of gaming
right now with Xbox One.
If they had delivered the message in the appropriate way
and they could have maybe done that by not firing
their community outreach team but that's another story
that you know is again part of the problem.
But if Microsoft
had maybe delivered that message in a different way
I mean gaming would be so
I think different right now and I don't think Microsoft would have been
the bad guy this last generation as they
kind of ended up being for a time.
Yeah. It's just
at this point like
like how many times are we going to excuse
them. I'm sorry I'm jumping
because you don't chat says you mean if they lied. No that's
not what I mean. What I said was
if they delivered the message in a different way
I'll repeat that for you so you can hear that because I didn't
mean anything different. Thank you. It's just
at this point like it's kind of
like I get it like oh well we didn't
expect much from Nintendo but
why don't we like like look
at it look at look at their quality of their games
the effort that they put into the software
that runs on their stuff but they don't put
that same quality into
their networking. I mean like
that's kind of got to be a scar
on their brand because like Nintendo
is Nintendo not Nintendo is only
the games that run on it and only the hardware
but the the networking that's
absolute shit. Well that's
not Nintendo. You know bullshit
that's your fucking company. You got
to you got to put the same effort
into it. And this is ridiculous to not think
of designing your games while we're storing
all the player data locally.
You don't see anything wrong with
that. How
long has networking been a thing
like you know that's like basic shit
that you know that's not what you're supposed
to do. You store it in the cloud so
that they can't be manipulated.
I don't understand how this is
new information to them. It's like they've never
played another console
or never experienced
the world. I mean I don't get it.
Here's the unfortunate thing that's going to happen.
Nintendo is not going to change anything
why because Nintendo Online is going to
is going to sell just fine.
Plenty of people are going to sign up for Nintendo Online
because they want to play Smash Online
they want to play Splatoon Online they want to play Mario Kart Online
they want to play NES Classics even though
we all know it's not as optimal. And that's fine.
People are going to pay the money and to be
to be fair it's cheaper than the others
so they're going to pay the money to do all that
online and
Nintendo is not going to be motivated
to change it. And then that's fine. And you know
what it may not be a thing where it
affects them right now. It will
eventually eventually someone they're going to
hit everybody's breaking point to
where it's just going to they're either going to
fix it and it's going to get better
or they're just going to keep
doing this shit and eventually it's not going to be acceptable
anymore. It's like kind of like with
new phones that come out where
they hardly change anything you know
add a little bit of spit polish
to it and then they charge another two hundred dollars
on top of what they charged for the phone last year.
I mean it's
eventually some people
will keep upgrading and stuff like that but
eventually it's like OK really
what am I paying for. This isn't that different you know
it's going to end up like that.
Well it's like you know this isn't
really acceptable at this time like I can
get much better. Yeah I'm paying a little bit more
for the service on this
console but I'm getting a lot more
free games. No. Yeah.
Free games and just features
like I'm not even taught like free games aside
let's just pretend we don't even get those stupid NES
games. OK. Share play
is I think is a huge thing that yeah
Sony has no sharing share plays a huge share
plays a huge thing. People don't talk enough
about that. That's a huge deal. But like
even just like voice chat
on the console to be clear. I've said a lot
of negative stuff about Sony tonight with
the classic and everything but I give
credit where credit is due like that share play
is is truly an amazing
and under talked about feature. It really
does like it allows you to try games
that you don't fucking own.
It's pretty great. I mean just
just like even
basics left like voice chat
using the system not a phone
app. Why the hell do I have to have a phone
app to voice. That's stupid.
That's stupid. Any console
like you don't as Fortnite has demonstrated
you don't exactly
why Nintendo on their own
platform their own product
like they're supposed to be the best at
making games like they're just like fantastic
but yet it's
stupid. It's like who designed
this shit.
Like seriously what
programmer out there said hey
this is a good fucking idea.
Who did this.
I don't get it. It just doesn't
make any sense. But you
know what. Whatever.
It's just it's gonna be what it is.
It's just gonna be the hassle that we're gonna
have to deal with.
All right.
Bobby Black Wolf in chat
was point out no programmer said that it
was management. Exactly.
But who let them say that was a good who
ran with that idea though. Like
someone has to say you know what
you see in the modern age that
we're living in that's stupid and no one
does it that way.
And management said I don't
care that's what we're doing says Bobby.
Well
we've we've seen what bad
management can do. But but Nintendo
like the thing is like it's just
it's just not going to stop because for
the reasons I pointed out this
Nintendo online thing is going to do just fine.
They have to fall from their graces in order
for this shit to happen. It's
what has to happen is that
a kid has to get hurt
somehow due to this. And I
would never advocate for violence against children.
That's not what I'm saying. But I'm just saying you'll notice
Nintendo doesn't do like crazy things and like change
things up until kids could possibly
be in danger. Where are my paper cut stories
from Labo?
That's when things
will change. That's when like
they're not just going to change it they'll
full on delete it like they did with SwapNote
because kids may be in
danger. So that's
storing files on the
server. What has to happen is that there has to be
like threatening messages to children in
those files for that to stop.
Like we have the friend codes in there.
I hope you know I'm being ridiculous. Like why we have
friend codes in there if voice chat's
going to be turned off. Oh
well it could be a rapist that's
going to try to you know contact them. Then why
have the friend codes in the first place if it's not
going to stop anything. It doesn't
make it stupid. It's just so
many levels of stupid. Okay on
a different note we had a story
that got cut for tonight because in
my mind it wasn't really a story. It was something you posted.
It wasn't really a story. It was somebody sharing
their experiences and they said that they were playing
Mario Kart online
and using the voice chat app when
you would expect that playing online with
strangers is going to be a shit house
as it usually is on Xbox Live
on PlayStation Network is that you hear
all sorts of racial slurs
things against you know
gay slurs things like that
is the type of stuff you hear online. But apparently
some people's
experience on Nintendo's online service
has been very pleasant.
Apparently getting online playing Mario Kart it's like
oh well you know that's
quite the race wasn't it.
Yeah well
we're having a jolly time aren't we.
It's like I just
just have the option where you speak to only
your friends.
But you have friend codes. Apparently talking
to strangers on Nintendo online is not all
bad. Well so is it. You're not there.
As it is as it is on
like Xbox and PlayStation
it's the same everywhere. There's going to be assholes
everywhere. But there's also
not everybody is an asshole
out there like that. That's the thing. Don't just
assume it's going to be shit. If it was
all shit then they wouldn't offer it as a service.
Dark Sakura have you missed your weekly
Nintendo rants by Loki.
It's not that Nintendo rants
stupid if Sony did the same
thing I'd be just as mad at them. It's
dumb. All right
let's move on. Breathe in
breathe out Loki. We still have some news to cover
before we get to phone calls. Orange launch
radio on Skype. I believe we're done with
emails right. That was the last email. Yeah that was it.
All right. Thank you Flaco for the email.
Look at what you did. All right. Anyway
everybody follow Flaco on
Twitch especially because I can't broadcast right now.
So you should watch Flaco instead. You know
obviously there's many people I recommend on Twitch.
What I'd really recommend. Look at our
Discord server if you go to vognetwork.com
Discord because we have a Twitch channel
where people alert when they're live. And so
I would say watch all those people.
This is fantastic. All right. Let's get back into
some news before we get to some calls. Orange launch
radio on Skype. Loki. So
this week was the big old
Red Dead Redemption 2
media blitz where
they had allowed a lot of the
different outlets out there
to check out the game for a few hours.
Also they talked a little bit about Red Dead
Online which is going to be launching
after the game launches
the following month in November.
They're going to start a public beta.
They basically said as with most online experiences
of this size and scale there will inevitably
be some turbulence at launch.
So they're hoping
that with this beta test that they're
going to help iron those out.
You know
same with
I think Grand Theft Auto 5 had a big
shit show when it came to
Grand Theft Auto Online. Also
what we've learned from the experience when launching online
games at this scale there are bound to be a few
issues and we want to ensure that we have time
to gradually roll out the game and make sure
the experience is as smooth as possible for
everyone that we can. And we believe
this way of rolling out
will give people the best overall experience
both single player and multiplayer.
And from what I hear the game
the online portion is supposed to be pretty similar to Red Dead
Redemption
the multiplayer in that game
which is actually pretty fun. I did play
quite a bit of that. It was one
of the games that did support System
Link at the time so we ended up
playing that quite a bit but it was fun
there's the kind of free roam and do all that.
I'm
I can't wait to check it out though.
It sounds pretty cool.
It looks pretty.
And because
of all these media outlets and talking about the
detail because I remember the one thing with Grand Theft Auto 5
was the level of detail and
the one thing that stood out with me of course
because someone's going to ask that
they asked about the horse testicle
physics. Oh good god.
And apparently yes there are
horse testicle physics and not only
are there horse testicle physics
but they even went so far as
when your horse is walking through
wintery environment the testicles actually
shrink and expand and compare
depending on the heat.
That is some level of detail right there.
I appreciate
attention to detail.
OK. But I want to know
because look here's my
thing with horses. Whenever you
watch horses like you'll see the horses at
Disneyland you'll see the horses in a parade.
Everybody sees the horses in a parade. You know what
I associate those horses with? The fact
that right when they get in front of where you're watching they take
a gigantic fucking dump.
They probably will do that.
Well the horses in Red Dead
Redemption just like is it that thing
if you go too long without moving the controller
like you know how like idle animation
they might tap the screen like you know the whole thing
does the horse like if you just stand there for too long does the horse
just take a massive shit on the ground?
I don't know. Because it's bored.
But it just
that I can only imagine the level
of detail in the game is going to be incredible
just because in Grand Theft Auto 5
is incredible and it's been so many years after that
so I
can't wait. Bobby Blackwolf
in chat says imagine marching behind them in a band.
I have. I was a marching band in high school
and they used to tell us like well if
that happens you just got to march right through
it and no we marched around
it. No. Sorry.
Like you know oh the team's going to lose points.
I'm not going to step in that. No I won't be
doing that today. Let's see.
And Brad from Pod Culture confirms
there is horse crapping in Red Dead Redemption 2.
Oh. Oh happy day.
Hooray.
It's so realistic.
Mmhmm.
I just. I'm just
waiting for somebody to ask. I'm watching
chat like a hawk. I'm waiting for somebody
to ask.
Can you
fuck the horse?
be a horse fucker?
No.
Can you eat the horse?
Apparently horse is supposed to be
pretty delicious.
Alright moving on.
Hey let's talk.
Dartitsia said they'll probably be a PC mod for that.
You're right. No it'll never come out on PC
apparently they said. So it's never
come out. Sure. Red Dead Redemption 1 never
came out on PC. Oh I guess that's
true. So they said it's never coming out on
PC. Alright.
Anyhow let's talk about something that will be
coming out on PC and something very different from
horse shitting and fucking dicks.
There is no
way that you can make pinball
nasty. That's right pinball
is a wholesome family fucking. Until now with
horse fucker the table.
There have been some adult themed
pinball tables. Alright alright. Let's go
from one balls to another.
Talking about pinball. We've
talked in the past few weeks on the show about how
Zen Studios got the
Williams table. That should have been one of the
stories I put in the poll to ask you about
Dartitsia. But Zen Studios is getting that
license from pinball
excuse me from
Farsight excuse me who had the
Williams
and Bally license before.
We know Zen Studios got that.
And they've been testing. I actually
did the beta test in
Steam. You can turn it on and you can play
a demo
demo table and they're gonna make this table
free for everybody. The
Fish Tales is the table that
will be like the free for
everybody to get you to download the game and
check it out. And then if you wanna get
more tables you'll be able to get
the very first pack volume 1
on October 9th will
include Medieval Madness
Junkyard and the Getaway
High Speed 2. It will set you back
9.99. That's 9.99
US dollars. 9.99
euros. It will
be free. Fish Tales
will be free and the other games will
cost you. It's going to be out on Nintendo Switch,
PlayStation 4, Xbox One, Windows 10
Steam and Zen Pinball
2 on the Mac.
So even though Pinball FX3 never came out on
the Mac, Zen Pinball 2 on the
Mac will support these. That's kinda interesting how they
did that. So there you go.
I don't know if any of you are gonna
check that out. I
you know those tables are okay. I mean
Medieval Madness is kind of a classic. I'm not a fan. I've got
Medieval Madness in my house. I know.
You're not a fan of the emulated because you're so
attached to the real thing. Yeah.
But Fish Tales also isn't very fun to me.
For those of us that can't afford the real thing though.
This is
an okay substitute. But I really
Pinball is the one I really want. That's my favorite.
You may be selling Getaway.
Oh really? Wow.
If you're interested. Nah, I don't know.
This house has enough shit in it.
I'll say if I can get rid of three Pinball
machine size things worth of shit then
I'll allow a Pinball machine in here.
We'll see.
Alright. Let's move on.
Darcyra. Well
there is a new cause
of divorce in this
country and it's called Fortnite.
More than 200
UK couples filed for divorce
in 2018.
And they cited addiction to Fortnite
as their reason for divorce.
If that's all it took to cause
a divorce then somebody in that family
was boring the shit out of the other
person in that family.
But that's
actually about 5% of
the 4,665
petitions that
Divorce Online has
handled. It's actually
a UK company that offers divorce
services.
And that seems to be the
biggest one that came up.
And this is also
going hand in hand with the World Health Organization
saying compulsive video game playing now
constitutes a mental
health condition.
Um.
Yeah.
I don't know. I mean
if you want to pick an excuse I guess
that's as good as any. You could just say
we don't do anything
together. We don't communicate. We don't
leave the house.
So. That's kind of what Kaijuto is
referencing in our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com
says I'm sure they had problems
before Fortnite.
So maybe Fortnite is just kind of like the
objectification
of all those things into one
sort of tangible thing.
I don't know. Fifth Dream in chat says
I'd divorce anyone who likes Fortnite too.
Now now Fifth Dream. It's a very very
popular game. There's many people to play it.
Alright.
Well it's
always interesting when video games
get into other parts
of life like that. So.
I wonder what we'll be seeing on the divorce
court. The TV show
Divorce of My Man because he plays too much
Fortnite. S.S.J. remembers
S2100 Matt in our chat says
remember when World of Warcraft was the cause
of divorces back in the day.
Remember the good old days Dark Sakura when it was
my husband.
My husband plays a horde
and I just can't marry a man because I'm
I'm an alliance character.
They had like wow widows.
Oh yeah. That's what Victoria always
claimed to be herself was a wow widow.
When she had dated
that guy who was too busy as she
said storming the castle. That's what she called
raiding. He was too busy to go out because he was always
storming the castle with his friends. I just think of
the princess bride like that. Me too
but that's kind of what it is. Bye bye boys.
Have fun storming the castle.
That's what raiding is. You're storming the castle
with your friends. Alright
anyway. Let's move on. A few more
stories for you guys before the Skype line.
Orange Lounge Radio all one word on Skype.
Loki pretty big story here towards the end.
Yes so we kind of
alluded to it a couple weeks ago
talking about that there was a rumor that you're
going to be able to start downloading titles
as part of PlayStation Now which has always
been my gripe because PlayStation Now I think
is a terrible service
as far as having to stream all the time
and I wish they would let you download it like
you know you can with games pass
but now apparently you can with
most of the titles on there
and they're going to be starting I guess with
almost all of the PlayStation 4 games
in the service including Bloodborne,
God of War 3 remastered, NBA 2K16
and Until Dawn will be available for
download in addition
to the PlayStation Now lineup
of classic PlayStation 2 games
that they remastered for PlayStation 4
and then they said they've
they'll be rolling out that feature to
PlayStation Now subscribers over the next few days
so if you don't see it
just check back later.
A lot of people very happy about this change
that Sony was kind of pressured to do so
in response to Microsoft's system allowing you to
do this. Yeah and
like you know you still have to phone in
every once in a while to you know so you can't
play offline for a long time but it's
still nice to have
that option. Still don't want to
play the service though because
a lot of the games that are in there I already
own and
yeah. Fifth Dream says
and they will take advantage of PS4 Pro
hardware. That's good.
Is PS4 Pro
kind of the default now? Do you still get
regular PlayStations that aren't Pro anymore?
I guess you probably still do. Yeah they do.
I would imagine at some point PlayStation 4 Pro
would just be the default. Someday
but it has to come down in price
I think. Yeah that's true. And
they still do that with the Xbox too. The Xbox
One and S and X.
Alright
well finally here tonight before we
go to our Skype line at Orange Launch Radio
all one word on Skype although I'll ask if there's any
last minute stories as well. We do have a couple
stories here about game companies who have
helped to fulfill some final wishes
of younger folks
that are suffering with
some different diseases and it's kind of one of those things
where it's like ah man these are real like
you know just bad situations
and unfortunate but it's really cool
that these gaming companies are helping
these gaming fans
in their last days to be able to
play the games that they really want to play.
The first story I have here has to do with Bethesda
who showed up when
a 12 year old boy who had a rare form
of cancer wanted to play Fallout
76. The kid was from
Hampton Roads, Virginia. He was battling
stage 4 neuroblastoma
for half his life. He was diagnosed at 5 years old.
Doctors have
stopped his treatment but
then he realized he probably would not get to play Fallout
76 which is due in November.
And I realize you could probably say some
stuff here because I think Fallout is an M rated
series and he's a 12 year old kid but you know
what? That
that's the family's decision to make not yours.
So he wanted to play Fallout 76
and apparently
the assistant director at Bethesda actually
drove 4 hours from the company's
headquarters in Maryland to the family
home with a copy of the game and
a prototype of the power
armor helmet that's going to come with that
super special edition of the game
signed by the chief of Bethesda
game studios Todd Howard.
So unfortunately he didn't get to keep
the game because it's just too early
and to be fair in
these situations if it is
out there in the media that somebody has
something super special like this it makes
you a target for thieves
and so it's not that Bethesda's trying to
be dicks by just not letting the kid keep
the game but it's actually risky
to let him keep it if you really
kind of critically think about it. It's
it's an unfortunate thing but that's
what it is.
So anyway even though he didn't get to keep
the game still the hours of playtime
made him happy and they were all very
very very happy to
make the wish come true and all that stuff and
the kid got to play the game so
that's really cool. There is a GoFundMe out there
for Wes trying to raise money to pay
living expenses and trying to get the
doctors in New York City and all this.
So our thoughts with
him and
kind of a similar story here. This time
Nintendo allowing a fan
to play Super Smash Brothers
Ultimate. This guy is a little
older. He's in his early 20s so he's
not a kid per se but he's got his own
Twitter account and everything. Chris Taylor
a big fan of Smash Brothers and he
also kind of you know he's battling
cancer as well and even though
he's beat cancer twice before he's being
told that it's terminal and he recently wanted
recently made the tough decision
to stop treatment for that
but kind of realized that oh I
I may not get to play Super Smash
Brothers Ultimate. So there was a
big you know push online like
gaming subreddits and you know people
trying to amplify this his wish
to be able to play this and
what happened? Nintendo flew
out an E3 demo of the
game to him
earlier this week and
he got to play the game for three hours. They
took some pictures and you can see some of
this on Twitter on his
Twitter. He's a spooky wubler on Twitter
and you can see some of the pictures and
you know again some people are like well why didn't they
why did he only get to play the E3 demo?
Why didn't he get to play the full game? Game's not done
yet. Well yeah for one the game's not
done yet for two
you know again same things I mentioned before is
that when those types of things are in the hands
you know and people know about it because
of social media in fact
he couldn't announce that this was happening
until they already left
and again it's because you
know it would make you potentially a
target for thievery and all this other stuff
which really it's unfortunate but anyway
very cool that these gaming companies
are helping to make some
wishes come true and lots of
people in our chat over at live.vognetwork.com
giving a hearty
hashtag fuck cancer in our chat
and I agree but
I'm you know despite
the situation
I'm glad these gaming companies are
able to you know
help these folks out and let them play
what they want to play. Okay
let's on a different note head over to our
skype line at orange lounge radio all one
word on skype if there's something you would like to talk
about that we've gotten to tonight or maybe
we haven't gotten to yet maybe there's something you were hoping
we would talk about that we never did
you can send us a call
right now live call at orange lounge
radio all one word on skype while we wait
to see if the skype line goes off
Loki do we have any last minute stories you want to get
into?
No. No?
Yeah. Alright
not a lot going on
well dark sakura when do we get to see you
here again are you going to be here the last weekend of october
I'm going to try
yeah how are things going with
you know we didn't get asked
to ask a lot about this but I know sundays are also
a big thing for your sisters
our general meeting is every
fourth sunday
so I was up
way early this morning to go to the
sisters meeting had to leave that
fifteen minutes early to get
to work where
my
provisioning at my job had been
messed up so I didn't take any
calls today I did nothing but training
I was bored then I
left and now you're here
yes so you had a very busy day
hopefully I'll be able to make
I'll be able to perfect my pumpkin
bread not like a sweet bread
I'm planning on making a savory pumpkin
and that'll be the time where nobody can bitch about
the pumpkin stuff too because that'll be right around
Halloween when you're here next that'll be Halloween
weekend right October 28th will be that show
I think well I like savory
gourd stuff you know
like pumpkins and butternut squashes and stuff
like that I like it savory and buttery
and I've got my bread recipe
down like I can't bake cookies
and all that for shit but I can bake
bread some of the savory pumpkin
stuff's really good like we get this pumpkin
ravioli this time of year at Trader Joe's
it's really good so I think what I
do is just get like the pumpkin pulp
and spiral it in
in my dough and then
just let it bake from inside the dough
I think that would be good
and then just make it buttery and savory
again the Skype line is open hopefully somebody
will call but if not then not
Orange Tons Radio all one word on
Skype if you want to get through on the Skype line tonight
I'm not that intimidating boys
I will not be doing a live feed after the show tonight
because again I'm still limited with my
upload I do hope to get that fixed
I have my gears turning in my
head about some projects that I
might work on so stay tuned to my Twitch channel
at Rob Roberts I may
try some experiments with video
premieres this week and see what you guys like
what gets attention and what nobody
seems to care about also apparently today
is the 129th
anniversary of Nintendo
oh right because they started as a playing card
company way way way back in the day they were not always
about what's that
oh right the specific type
of not like Jack of Clubs
King of Hearts those type of playing
cards but a very specific type of
card so Nintendo was not
always about electronics that's just kind of
what it turned into and what they're most known
for now we do have a call coming in
let's get to it hi you're on Orange Tons Radio who's
this hey this is Akdeft
hey Akdeft it's good to hear from you buddy
what's up
well I do want to talk about
the PlayStation Classic
okay what are your thoughts on it
it's kind of stupid
why you say that
you know there's a lot of people that would be very excited
about this why do you say it's crap
well
mostly I thought it was a good
idea it is
a good idea but
at the same time Sony's doing
a lot of stuff that
makes my head baffle like
like really aside
the fact it
doesn't have like an AC adapter
because yeah it's
probably it's gonna be like a
phone adapter and mostly like
the SNES or
NES Mini
but the fact that the controllers
aren't DualShock it's like
one of the first things that
I really don't know what
Sony is thinking
is it like
the game selection or is it just the price
what is it that's like turning you off
to this
so again the first thing is
the controllers like
they should be DualShocks
like really I don't know why
Sony is making those
yeah I don't disagree with that
that's for sure I sure don't disagree with that
but yeah the price point
I would agree with it
if it had like at least
five more games
if it had a DualShock if it had the AC
adapter
but I really don't know
in the game selection
for 20 games for a classic
system like this
seems like really
really low and I understand
that the SNES
Mini also has only
20 or 21 games
but those are all
classics like in this case
of the five they have announced
only
like well a side
Final Fantasy and maybe
Tekken 3
the other the rest aren't
that like
popular even something
like Ridge Racer
I don't think many people are
excited about it and something like
Jumping Flash that personally I
like it isn't
that great of a game and not many
people like even like it so
I really don't know
what Sony is thinking about this
console or what's the idea
Well they're thinking
how can we make money? How did our
competition make money? Oh we can do that
so I just
I still sort of think that they could have
you know really shown the value
of making people
or enticing people to buy a PlayStation
4 because oh you already
have this old library of games that will
automatically work on this new system
so feel free to get rid of your old
system by buying this new system that will play
all of your old games and I get
like again I get that the chipset
changes and those changes that happen
within the system especially make this very
hard with the PlayStation 3
although I still think they could have got around it with
PlayStation now but whatever
they didn't want to allocate that type of server
bandwidth and all that stuff but you know
at least the PlayStation 1 and 2 stuff you
would think would still be able to work but
Sony just doesn't see the value
in that and so this is
what they're deciding to do instead so
it is what it is so you have to
make a choice if you want to support it
and to be fair
you know it is a cute little thing
just like the little NES classic
NES it's cute it's something
that I like for the look of it and not just
what's inside of it but I do have to
admit in retrospect you know now
that I've played the Switch Online one it's like
eh was it $60
cute I don't know so I think
I think in some ways some of that is almost making me
hesitate when it comes to wanting
to get like a classic Sony system
I don't know
and that's the thing
like I really like want
to get this
because again it sounds like a great idea
it's I wouldn't mind
a classic Sony
console and just
plug and play like the SNES
and the NES Mini
but again
there are many things that
I don't know what Sony is thinking about
that really
I have one pre-ordered
on Amazon but I'm probably
gonna cancel it the only thing
and many people probably
are gonna yell at me because of this
is that probably
those consoles are
Playstation TV or Vita TVs
that they didn't
sell so it's probably
gonna be hackable like really
easily hackable
and you're probably
gonna insert
many like roms or homebrew
and so that's
the only appeal I see right now
for the console unless it has like
a really
cool game that hasn't
gotten a real release like
I was talking in chat earlier like
InHander it hasn't
gotten a real release ever
so like oh the console
has it okay I'm gonna get it
but aside from that I really
don't know why I would
buy one of these you know you
kind of reference something there I think is a huge
missed opportunity from Sony like if you're
gonna charge a hundred bucks for one of these and get
them in people's homes why not
make them capable of doing
the Vita TV stuff like a Playstation
or the Playstation Now thing
or a lot of that similar functionality
the Playstation TV which if I
recall correctly also cost a hundred bucks right
so yeah the Playstation
TVs nowadays are so cheap
well that's right so the technology the price
of those things should have come way down in technology
I can't imagine that you wouldn't
be able to get a Playstation emulator
on one of those Playstation Vita things
and play you know the PS1
classics and charge you a hundred bucks for that
you don't even need to get a Playstation 1 emulator they
have Playstation 1 natively
so why not sweeten the pot
and don't just make it about being able to play 20
Playstation classics but holy
shit this thing will play newer stuff too
and then maybe Sony wouldn't have had to
been so quick to abandon the Vita
but I just they weren't thinking far enough ahead I guess
I think it's more about wanting to
just you know strike while the iron
is hot so to speak on these classics
and as soon as Nintendo had their runaway
success a couple years ago the
gears were probably turning on this
well it's
a little too late for
that I think but it will still
sell people will
buy it at least but
I don't know if
Sony is gonna like
see like a really really
great success from this I
really don't but
I don't know hopefully they
they change some of this
or again if
it's hackable I think that
that's gonna be the appeal for this because
for at least for my part
it's like no
no Sony
alright my friend I'm gonna let you go so we can
see if anybody else wants to call but thanks for your
thoughts
alright bye bye
they've got the whole lineup
too there's like a musical lineup
and everything while DJ's playing stuff so
check it out if you got some time
um
you know there's a Minecraft convention
going on this weekend I don't know if that's just here locally
it's just here locally MineCon
Earth is next week
um yeah the local one here
I see a lot of tweets about
it it's so expensive and it's just like
what is it really there they have like
some streamers that are there they do
like a Lego thing they do like some other Minecraft
stuff but it's like it's so god
damn it it's like 40 bucks a ticket
oh yeah that's a little pricey
MineCon world is next week and it's online
it's streaming so
interesting okay
alright well I don't think any other calls
are coming in so I think we're gonna call it with that
but if you you know thought
too late or something you can always send us an
email participate at orangelandtrader.com
is the place to send us an email and
we will consider reading some of those on a future
show you can always tweet us as well
twitter.com slash o-l-r you can post on our Facebook
page too we read it all I promise
you and we respond you know if it's something that necessitates
us a response we try to respond to it all but
you know we don't always get to everything
on air but we try to do as much as we can
so anyway that's gonna do it for
another episode of Orange Lounge Radio if you enjoyed
what you heard here at Orange Lounge Radio please tell
a friend or two about the show help us spread the word
because we are the show where every gamer has a voice but
if the voices aren't here to air live
then we can't
hear them I will hear your grievances
we had a lot
of grievances last week or the week before on the
show I just seem to remember why YR sent us an
email outlining all these things we got wrong
but not while you've been here
you're perfect you're beautiful you're just like
Linda Evangelista no thank you
speaking of Dar Sakura hey it's great
that you're back tonight we'll miss you for the next
month but thanks to Radio Magic we'll still
hear you next week
so do you have it
actually and I gotta sit down with you on when
we're gonna take care of that cause my weekend
next weekend is like crazy but like everybody's
frickin birthday is next weekend Thursday afternoon
Thursday after work
I can't so
I'll talk to you off air so
we'll have to plan it really early or like
at a weird time so alright
anyway
or we may not have Radio Magic next week we'll see
anyway it was great having you here tonight
any final thoughts to
carry us over for the next month
I'm just happy I had filet mignon for
dinner tonight cause it was
fucking amazing and
thank you again Ikuma JP
for also helping with obtaining
Dan's birthday present so
which I will not announce on air
yet I will also use my
final thought to pay tribute to Ikuma JP
this is very thoughtful what you did in sending
us the gifts I'm always tickled
when OLR people send us gifts
and it's not something you have to
do and it's very nice
but these are things that I would
these little wafer things what are these called
these are really good the wafer
those are pretty good
alright Loki your final thought tonight
my final thought
is
I don't know hopefully we'll play more games this week
yes play more games that's a good idea
everybody out there play more games
and we'll see you in 7 days to do it all
over again have a great week everybody and
good night
you've been listening to Orange Lounge
Radio
Orange Lounge Radio is a production of
OLR Studios
to join us for a live show
tune into VOG Network dot com
Sunday nights at 6 pm Pacific
9 pm Eastern
the views and opinions expressed
in this program do not necessarily
reflect those of the staff of Orange
Lounge Radio or VOG Network
but you know they were all
still true
see you next week
thanks for watching