Hi everybody out there on the internet welcome to a special podcast for this
Sunday April the 12th of 2009. Let me try to explain quickly if possible
what's been going on and why we have the podcast with no fancy intro or anything
like that tonight. The show started, we began taping as usual about six
o'clock tonight Pacific Standard Time and about 30 minutes into the show
during part A tonight the video card on the system we used to tape the show
started freaking out and dying so basically the video card overheated mid
taping of the show and it caused a lot of stuff to happen basically we we lost
all of part A unfortunately we weren't able to recover what we had taped so far
so it's gone and sadly only the live listeners got to hear it and then
basically the computer we use to tape OLR is fucked. Now don't worry you guys
we'll just get a new video card and everything will be okay come next week
so I don't want people like freaking out like oh my god is OLR dead no we're not
gonna let a stupid video card keep things down but it did screw us over
for tonight however what I've done I have two computers in the house it's
just that the second computer is not really hooked up to do audio or mixing
or any of that sort so we're actually not broadcasting on all games right now
because it's not configured for that we're actually live on all games radio
or not not all games radio sadly however we are live on Justin TV and we're gonna
tape a mini show tonight Doc Sakura is here with us as always me and my lungs
and Dan was joining us tonight and I'm really sorry to Dan cuz it's very rare
he gets here but you're here to get for not listening live we're so much more
of me and I'm awesome and Loki's here as well yeah yeah you guys really missed a
lot life tonight I had a diva I had a diva breakdown what what's the other
special guest jelly beans the jelly beans are here delicious all right but
you guys sadly missed a lot I but they don't want they don't want to hear about
what they missed on the podcast they just want at least to hear a little bit
about what's going on in the news this week so quickly let's talk about our
gaming weeks let's recap what's been going on in our gaming weeks this week
dark soccer I played shit Dan maim Loki I've been playing that Grand Theft Auto
for the lost and damned and recently during the show Arroyo Muramasa which is
Muramasa Dean blade on the week and I have been playing we fit surprisingly
enough I've been playing a lot of we fit I'm on a new little diet where I'm gonna
use we fit and DDR to hopefully lose a significant amount of weight before e3
so okay so that was our gaming weeks let's move into what's going on in the
gaming world tonight housekeeping our show was completely borked to this week
and we apologize but that's live radio good bad and ugly all on live radio so
Loki start us off quickly with some news tonight okay so I'm gonna kind of let's
see here is interesting enough Sony is actually patented a PSP controlled car
which I don't really you know that's interesting I guess it looks like of
course you're not real car obviously it's more of a you know RC car type of
thing but that's kind of neat and apparently the patent looks like based
off the instructions on there it's like it's gonna have some sort of camera or
something like that on it and you can kind of control it using the PSP maybe
an augmented reality game based off of what the camera sees will be interesting
they're actually because if you remember the Sony I will actually had you know a
camera built into it as well and one of the little Easter Egg features about is
you could actually control the eyeball with your PSP so this is something like
that I don't know it's kind neat maybe we'll see this at e3 I wonder if it's
just like I don't know this is what this is what this is I look at and go what
huh really like Loki do you think this is going to be something cool or do you
think this is like I have judgment this is probably not anything cool yeah well
we'll see the car judgment dark dark Sakura what what kind of story did you
want to cover tonight well there were a couple I was thought would be cool go
for it well just to do it in inch just to do it in short order there is gonna
be a Silent Hill shattered memories on ps2 and PSP and we we version you can
use a flashlight we talked about this last week though it's basically gonna be
a revamping I don't think we had confirmed that the we thing was gonna be
a flashlight but then they kind of confirmed it this week it's confirmed
that's awesome also silent scope is coming out iPhone which is pretty cool
the Beatles are re-releasing their entire music catalog to go out with the
Beatles rock band version and each of the records is going to have a little
documentary with it and also there's going to be a 10 collection a 10 disc
collection to go out but it's going to be in mono I guess you can hear it in
that record quality also Sega is considering putting out twin sticks for
virtual on for Xbox 360 which is gonna be sweet and we don't have to hack ours
and also there's gonna be a grudge game and I'm totally gonna get it yeah but
isn't it gonna be just like a bastardized version of the movies that
you love I don't care I'll still play it all right well some things I wanted to
cover really quickly Wii Sports Resort has gotten apparently some actual dates
we heard rumors about July last week on the show it looks like they've been
somewhat confirmed by Nintendo themselves they did a quick press
conference this week and confirmed that the game is coming out in June and then
an overseas release will follow the next month overseas meaning of course the US
in that circumstance Squeenix has created games for myspace they're
actually gonna they've created this new game called what's it called dive hunt
to dive to hunt sorbet's great adventure that's right it's a very strange kind of
not Final Fantasy it's Oh sorbet I said sorbet I don't know whatever this looks
very strange and not like any other type of game but what's kind of cool about it
is that it does use one of the moogles but the design from Final Fantasy 12
where they look more like rabbits so I thought it was kind of interesting but
yeah very interesting they're launching a game on myspace don't they know that
everybody went to Facebook by now no apparently not apparently not metal gear
is going to be getting an arcade release if a rumor is to be believed that that
is a trademark that happened the Konami is filed metal gear and tactical online
action apparently they are arcade games you know there was that shooter game the
Silent Hill shooter game this doesn't seem something that's completely
unbelievable to me I don't know there's also a game I saw e3 a few years ago
that was like an online play game where you could network through other arcades
yeah no problem with that though that was and a mirror it was in the mirror
Metal Gear look did you have anything else like do I talk to chat really quick
yeah there's some other stuff they put Honda put out a press release saying
that they're gonna be sponsoring the launch of Xbox Live primetime which
what's kind of funny though is they're actually gonna have a plane away a
plane win campaign and while you're waiting in queue to play you know the
big primetime games you'll have to watch ads for the car and then it kind of
slipped out that primetime will be launching May 15th with that which I
think is kind of the bigger point of the story but somehow that slipped in there
I don't know some other interesting stuff that's kind of just slipped out
there apparently perfect dark is going to be coming back to watch you coming to
the Xbox Live Arcade this was actually revealed in a teaser that they the
people at rare were showing off some of their premium themes for banjo-touille
and lo and behold in one the latest games there is an icon for perfect dark
in there for one of the I guess rare members that jug go so he had a lace
game he played as being one of those haha slipped out there that's kind of
funny and I'll see here Final Fantasy 7 has come out on the PlayStation 3 at
least the original game on the PlayStation Store however only in Japan
don't but if you do happen to have a Japanese PlayStation Network account you
can actually purchase the game I guess if you have your way to you know pay in
Japan and it is the international version which does have the English
language available as well for it so that's kind of cool and finally Konami
is putting out a new military action game called six days in fluja and this
is kind of getting a little bit of flack because people are saying it's too soon
but either way it is coming out and you know I was kind of surprised this week
with Konami's kind of gamers night going on we didn't really hear anything about
the stuff that was there I bet you the embargoed stuff did we get him by one
year we went yeah but it was usually embargoed until the next day you know
this was on a Thursday last week I mean unless they're just doing everything
next week but I don't know I surprised just nothing really coming out other
than this and you know the iPhone games that kind of stuff but oh well and
that's pretty much all I've got oh oh one last thing is gonna comment on
there's a rumor going around that there was going to be elite systems coming out
for $400 with Fable 2 and Halo 3 bundled in it yeah that's true so those
will be coming by the end of this month and they're gonna be around for about
two months and that's it rock band unplugged is coming out June 9th I know
what I'm getting that's that's the week right after e3 did you see the video for
it it looks just like well not exactly like amplitude but they've got a four
different you know tracks you switch between and of course they're the four
you know the same bass drum and guitar I'm very excited in a naughty spot it's
proof that harmonix loves us it really is harmonic and we love harmonix for
giving us this game honestly really they just need to just do frequency and
amplitude for the PSP it's got to happen mm-hmm well doesn't really need to
happen anymore now I mean think about it well sure but I mean they should just do
it anyway because those games are both great and I can't find a copy of
amplitude it is very hard to find now yes even for me and I can find anything
I want to mention this story really quickly as well because I thought this
was interesting about the whole you know digital stuff and downloads and things
like that Amazon right now will actually sell Xbox 360 video games and I'm not
talking about like the tangible kind I'm talking about they actually have an
Xbox live store now you actually can purchase the games through Amazon calm
and I guess the way you do it you go on there you buy with your Amazon account
and then you get a code to put in your Xbox 360 so this is kind of a way you
can get around using Microsoft points if you don't want to rumor is this coming
out soon for Sony and Nintendo as well and this means you would be able to
bypass Nintendo points and you'd be able to bypass the extra money left over in
Sony's wallet which is kind of interesting if true rumor I was actually
wondering though if it would be possible for me to make a statement about Amazon
sure that's what I told you earlier Amazon right now is the stripping the
the sales ranks off of the gay lesbian authors so that when you try to look up
a product you won't find anything from them it's really just to keep they say
it's to keep children from finding adult content yet run Jeremy's our biography
is still easily accessible his strip his ranks haven't been stripped so there is
a movement going to Google bomb them so just go to Google and type in Amazon
rank that's all interesting everyone should do it at least five times huh
what'd you read about this I'm curious several friends huh all right well
sometimes we get on side rants on the show I'm passing on the word if if you
support you know I'll check it out I don't want to go off until I know a
little more I've already gone off once tonight when we live so let me let me do
a little more research on it before I miss my shit if you want to the
information is out there no I'll check it out I'm curious I'm curious um I guess
that's it for the news we were going to cover tonight again I really apologize
for the board to podcast tonight we wanted to do something though instead of
nothing there was extreme frustration in studio tonight just with the whole port
card and everything like that but these things happen it's live radio you know
we try to do it every week but sometimes it's just not going to happen thank you
guys as always for your support for listening to our program and supporting
independent podcasting even when it's not so great and you know really as you
guys the chatters the live listeners that send us emails and all that that
really keep us going so really appreciate it and we will be back next
week with a proper episode 320 all we have to do is replace a video card we
can't just do it you know it would take us longer than you know an hour to do it
tonight but we will be replaced sadly dark soccer will not be here next week
she's happy in Disneyland but your happy birthday happy early birthday and I'm
sorry your pre-birthday show um was was fucked Danny what Dan please because
tonight was so fucked up why don't you come back next week and fill in for
Jamie maybe I don't know if you guys are lucky enough all right well if we if
maybe if we get enough love mail to the mail bag and mail bag at orange
laundry.com come in and be Jamie next week no he can't be me he can't even
contain me the great thing is I can wear her underwear so I'll grab some put a
pair on each leg oh my lord it'll be awesome
the chat room is I heard it too it's gonna happen the chat room is asking
what your classic game of the week was however let's just roll it over right to
the next week or and if Dan comes next week if Dan
what was the class of the week this week okay play me my music I can't the game
was Tetris and if you don't know anything about Tetris then get your head
out of your ass the end now day I'll make damn this offer he's not gonna be
able to refuse this Dan if you come to the show next week you can pick the
classic game of the week he's gonna pick life force I don't my force is in fact
great life force is amazing but I think you've picked it before dark soccer I
don't know I don't know a couple weeks ago we'll have to see no I'm talking I'm
taking over I I put in Parodius before okay I think I put in gradients or so
show Dan the list and see if there's something he believes needs to be on the
list and he can come put it on the list of classic games
Dan if you pick something that sucks annulment annulment I don't even know
what that is but I want one no no no because we our vows will till death do
his part so that'll be an ice pick to the face oh my god my face or your face
you know what this is your ice pick for a while are this Dan and Jay this is a
great radio right here ice pick let's get Nelly to come in here and nag on
you for a little while Loki will be awesome radio you know what then we'll
call my ex and see what he's everybody everybody I love my boy yeah Loki I feel
bad I know you're always rah rah rah about the show and everything and
probably disappointed with the way things turned out but please tell us a
little more about this game that you're playing I don't really know what it's
about I just know yeah because it's in Japanese it's pretty but is this again
although Muramasa mm-hmm which is kind of this Muramasa this game looks
friggin awesome what are you doing this you just go game I'm always sure what
I'm supposed to be doing in this but like when that whole thing comes up and
I attack ninjas and then my sword broke so I got switch swords and I attack shit
like crazy and go all or does not crazy sword and basically a button mash
because there's one attack button and I do all sorts of cool stuff yeah that's
basically it I mean hmm you get like huge combos like this is like frickin
dynasty warriors or something like that we have a 90 for the Odin sphere guys
yeah buddy I was only serious very similar and if you didn't play Odin
sphere and you like those kind of fruitiest Japanese action-adventure
games it's pretty cool all right well I think we're gonna go ahead and wrap up
for tonight again we'll be back like normal next week all we have to do is
get a new video card and we'll be better again hopefully if worse comes to us we
do have a second computer here in the studio we're just gonna move the sound
card over there will be new ORR next week sadly sans Jamie but hopefully plus
Dan if Dan if Dan decides he doesn't want to come we'll figure something out
for next week after all this time I finally got you to use a font other than
Times New Roman for show all I know I know that's why it that's why it all
fell apart you know no no no you cannot blame the show's lack of success on the
lack of serifs all right that's gonna do it for another week of Warren's launch
radio again thank you guys so much for some boy as a moment independent radio
you guys ice pick to dance face especially the live chatters that have
had to suffer for two through tonight's show maze-a-lack to me with ice pick and
I apologize to the podcast listeners this is just the downside of live radios
that sometimes your computer will decide to eat your show and that's what
happened tonight nom nom I hope it was delicious computer I hope nom nom I hope
it gives you diarrhea like eating an entire bag of marshmallow peeps I hope
computer welcome that's it no fancy intro no nothing we're out bye guys