[SPEAKER_08]: I, April 5th, 2009, Konami prepares to juggle two scary franchises, most Oblivion DLC gets a price cut, and have the release dates been leaked for highly anticipated Wii games?
[SPEAKER_13]: Hello everybody out there on the internet and welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: We are that video game show dedicated to video games, video gaming, gaming culture, and the gamer lifestyle.
[SPEAKER_13]: My name is Rob Roberts, joining you here every week, as well as the one and only Dark Sakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yo, what up?
[SPEAKER_13]: Good, how are you?
[SPEAKER_00]: I survive.
[SPEAKER_13]: You survive?
[SPEAKER_13]: On the souls of innocent children.
[SPEAKER_13]: FlashMediaEncoder3
[SPEAKER_13]: Ninja Blade
[SPEAKER_13]: and we do that video and then we do audio of the show.
[SPEAKER_13]: Now soon, we're going to upgrade and have a little switch box and then we can switch back and forth between the camera and the game and that would be super.
[SPEAKER_13]: It would be even cooler.
[SPEAKER_13]: What would that be?
[SPEAKER_13]: Picture in picture?
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know about that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Now you're talking money.
[SPEAKER_13]: Switch box like 1999.
[SPEAKER_13]: You'd be surprised.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's not as hard as you think.
[SPEAKER_13]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_13]: Maybe for the future.
[SPEAKER_13]: Joining us tonight, we do have a special guest.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm actually very excited because I didn't think we were going to have a special guest, but he just kind of showed up last minute.
[SPEAKER_13]: Boy, I'm happy he's here.
[SPEAKER_13]: Say hello to Casper the Gay.
[SPEAKER_13]: Who is now the Doctor.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, the Doctor.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_13]: How long ago did you change your name?
[SPEAKER_12]: About six months ago.
[SPEAKER_01]: A long time ago.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, Casper the gay doctor is here.
[SPEAKER_12]: Basically, yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, it still works.
[SPEAKER_12]: How are you doing, Casper?
[SPEAKER_12]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm really good.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm helping everyone with their medical problems.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: Ghost.
[SPEAKER_13]: Excellent.
[SPEAKER_13]: You're wearing a Legend of Zelda t-shirt today.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes, and a hat.
[SPEAKER_13]: See, I got the Hyrule symbol on my hat.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, look at you go.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm nerded out today for the show.
[SPEAKER_13]: I got to ask you real quick.
[SPEAKER_13]: Legend of Zelda spirit tracks, yay or nay?
[SPEAKER_13]: Ah.
[SPEAKER_12]: ZELDA FANBOY
[SPEAKER_02]: What they should have done is every time that he, you know, in the original game, every time that he got on the boat, they would play the Lonely Island I'm On A Boat song.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because that would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because, believe me when I say, Link F'd a mermaid.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm on a boat, you guys.
[SPEAKER_07]: In Hyrule, you guys.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: Do you think they're going to sell a lot of copies of that?
[SPEAKER_12]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, it's a Zealot title, so I'm sure, but it'll probably be boring.
[SPEAKER_13]: And if it sells a lot, then they're going to do a sequel, Spirit Tracks 2, Link on a Boat.
[SPEAKER_13]: That one I would actually buy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Busting Octoroks with my boomerang.
[SPEAKER_04]: If it had T-Pain as a character only, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, hell.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, let's get to how we always like to start the show off with a little bit of, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, I played, um, stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, I played Pet Society on Facebook, which I've become oddly addicted to.
[SPEAKER_13]: At least it's not Neopets.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck no.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, I played some more Cookie Mama on iPhone, and then I didn't actually finish what I was cooking, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mama fixed it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And we got something from Alva eBay that arrived in perfect condition for seven bucks.
[SPEAKER_07]: The item was fine.
[SPEAKER_07]: The box was nasty.
[SPEAKER_07]: It had mildew and shit, but it was brand new.
[SPEAKER_07]: We have a Capcom fighting stick for the Genesis.
[SPEAKER_13]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_13]: Why did you order that?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because we have several Genesees.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because I wanted one.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was seven bucks.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dude, why not?
[SPEAKER_13]: Just impulse buy.
[SPEAKER_13]: You didn't break it out to try anything with?
[SPEAKER_13]: You didn't get old school championship edition or anything?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, we already have all that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, just checking.
[SPEAKER_07]: And we got the FC Mobile.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, what is this all about?
[SPEAKER_13]: The FC Mobile.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a handheld NES.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's really all it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know how long the battery life is.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dan played it more than me, but we played Guardian Legend.
[SPEAKER_13]: The thing's got to be somewhat big if you actually put an entire cartridge into it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Is it about the size of an NES cartridge, the system?
[SPEAKER_07]: About the width plus another two inches.
[SPEAKER_12]: So it's not the Atari where it has all the games inside it in the memory.
[SPEAKER_07]: You plug in your cartridge.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's like a Game Boy, but it plays NES games.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's called the FC Mobile.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're like $40.
[SPEAKER_13]: Wow, that's not bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they're really light.
[SPEAKER_13]: Is that because of the whole thing?
[SPEAKER_13]: Like the same reason they were selling the third-party NESs at E3 a few years ago where it's something like the patent on the Nintendo property expired because it's been like 20 years?
[SPEAKER_13]: Something like that I want to say.
[SPEAKER_13]: So would that mean that in a couple of years we're going to start seeing like Super Nintendos and Genesis start coming out and all these things?
[SPEAKER_07]: You don't need to do a Genesis one, Rob.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm just saying.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because of the Nomad.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh my god, Dan was hilarious.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, also the fact Sega repackages their games like 50 times over.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dan was very hilarious about this, and if he hears it, he's going to be a little bit embarrassed, but I don't care.
[SPEAKER_07]: He was like, I wonder if, you know, they're going to do a super... Because it was like you were saying, it talks about doing a handheld Genesis.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's like, wait, wait, we have that.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's called the Nomad.
[SPEAKER_13]: So I was like, yes, sweetie, pat, pat, pat Question from our chat room, chat.orangeloungeradio.com Because we are the show where every gamer has a voice So be heard, join our chat live on Sunday night Hitstun asks, how is the hardware?
[SPEAKER_13]: Is the screen good?
[SPEAKER_06]: Pretty good, pretty good, I like it You don't have dead pixels?
[SPEAKER_13]: No Well, that's good
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: And then I played some WiiWare stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually played Bit.Trip Beat, which it's okay until they thought, hey, it's a great idea.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's have little blocks that are dark blue against a black background where you can't see them.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's when I stopped playing the game.
[SPEAKER_13]: And that was it.
[SPEAKER_13]: JustinFYIChat is giving us feedback that they can't hear us on JustinTV right now.
[SPEAKER_13]: They're not getting audio on there.
[SPEAKER_13]: They're getting video but no audio.
[SPEAKER_13]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: Another homebrew game, that's a demo for another game that I'd like not to mention on this show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let me just say it sucks as much as you would think it sucks, and the guy who made it is a douchebag, and I think we know who we're talking about here, but we are not mentioning his name, because that would be wrong.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then, my wife started playing Excite Truck again, in preparation for ExciteBots Trick Racing, so...
[SPEAKER_02]: Very excited by that.
[SPEAKER_02]: She is.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then, what else did I play?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got a lot of stuff that I was going to play, but I didn't get to play a lot of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I checked out that stupid, I think we talked about it last week, the Kama Sutra DS thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then, yeah, that's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have Rhythm Tengoku, or Rhythm Heaven, I guess, to try out.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then more Peggle DS, because that's fun.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_13]: NinjaBlade NinjaBlade
[SPEAKER_13]: and played that for a little bit.
[SPEAKER_13]: I know I've been gaining weight since I was sick last year and I wanted to see how much.
[SPEAKER_13]: So now you weigh 20 pounds.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, shut up.
[SPEAKER_13]: So I went back and played that for a little bit and was playing some of the old school classics on there like Legend of the Mystical Ninja and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: Cool, cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_13]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_13]: It still feels a little clunky to me.
[SPEAKER_13]: And when I say clunky, I mean the download speeds of the areas as you load them.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes, I realize you can download in the background and all this, but I kind of wish the thing was a little more intuitive.
[SPEAKER_13]: If I was going to start walking towards a particular map, it would be cool if that map would start loading.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's kind of a little...
[SPEAKER_13]: That's profiling.
[SPEAKER_13]: There's a lot of polish that still needs to be done in home, but it is getting slightly better and better at the same time.
[SPEAKER_13]: Just slightly, but I do see improvement in home, and I think that has to be acknowledged because it is a pretty ambitious thing.
[SPEAKER_13]: Is there a download yet that gives home a point?
[SPEAKER_13]: There are still more minigames popping up.
[SPEAKER_13]: The Guitar Hero area has a Simon Says-style minigame.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's nothing that awesome.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's free, but it's free.
[SPEAKER_13]: Again, might I remind everybody, you don't pay for home.
[SPEAKER_13]: Considering it's a free thing, granted, they microtransaction a lot of these clubs and things, but I have yet to pay a dollar.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you're not in home, you're homeless.
[SPEAKER_13]: And nobody wants to be homeless.
[SPEAKER_13]: Actdeft in chat says, Home is second life without the crazy antics.
[SPEAKER_13]: GameGuru says, The big picture of home is make money.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, it'll be interesting to see where the more nickel and diming comes in a little later.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_13]: What else?
[SPEAKER_13]: In my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_13]: Really not a whole lot else that I can think of.
[SPEAKER_13]: Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_13]: Just playing some of the old arcade titles.
[SPEAKER_13]: Pagle and so forth.
[SPEAKER_13]: But not a lot of new stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: I did forget one game I played.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Which is the game that we're playing right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Ninja Blade, I played during the week, actually, because I haven't really gotten a chance to play it since I got it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's actually not too... Sorry, if you heard an echo there, it's because I was checking JustinTV where we do have audio, thank God.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, because you unplugged something from your splitter coming out of your computer.
[SPEAKER_02]: The way you had it hooked up there would have been fine, but they wouldn't have been able to hear the music that we played during the little break.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyways, give us a quick walkthrough.
[SPEAKER_13]: I know this is radio, and we'll try to keep the references to the video minimum, but kind of walk us through this game a little bit.
[SPEAKER_13]: You were talking about, I know, earlier before we started, this big epic cutscene at the beginning of Ninja Boy.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's so over the top that it's hilarious.
[SPEAKER_02]: The main character looks like he's the spirit, you know, Sans crappy movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's actually very God of War-esque.
[SPEAKER_02]: You basically...
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_13]: What's the flippin' point?
[SPEAKER_13]: You say it's kind of God of War-esque?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, the point is you're this team of ninjas that...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's pretty much the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you like these over the top.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh yeah, it's awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: I do, but it's actually, you know, a lot of the games that are put out from software and stuff like that, they're not that great.
[SPEAKER_02]: But this is actually pretty good.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's been pretty entertaining so far.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it actually looks like it's going to start me from the beginning because apparently I didn't get far enough to save.
[SPEAKER_02]: But all the more exciting because I'm going to show you that whole skydiving part.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, this is a little cutscene that shows what happens when some old man sees some chick that's been infected.
[SPEAKER_02]: We don't need to see that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Skip that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let me go to Casper, sorry, the doctor, and we'll ask the doctor about his gaming week and we'll come back to you.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hopefully you're a little bit into Ninja Blade at that point.
[SPEAKER_13]: You can tell us a little bit about the gameplay.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, uh,
[SPEAKER_13]: The Doctor, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know if you guys ever played that, but there's lots of crazy minigames.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes, we have played that, or at least I watched Loki play it at PAX.
[SPEAKER_12]: The best minigame has to be the dancing.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's kind of like DDR, but where you have to move your whole body.
[SPEAKER_12]: Watching my friend get into this was hilarious.
[SPEAKER_12]: We were cracking up.
[SPEAKER_12]: But I'm with you.
[SPEAKER_12]: There's not a lot of new stuff on any system that I'm like, woo!
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, what does that even do?
[SPEAKER_12]: That's no point to me.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, it takes pictures, Doctor.
[SPEAKER_12]: Ah, I have a camera, and I don't need another one.
[SPEAKER_12]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right, well.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, yeah, but we're also watching Loki here.
[SPEAKER_12]: There are monsters and blood and swords and ridiculousness.
[SPEAKER_13]: Rawr!
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I'm just, you know, basically right now they're just, you know, kind of teaching you the basics of the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, you can do jump attacks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, you can do, like, heavy attacks and yada, yada, yada.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kill these guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, um, but it gets ridiculous because, like, your, like, sensei or whatever is kind of helping you out through the game and he gives you, like, these different weapons to use.
[SPEAKER_02]: Meanwhile, like, he's, like, flipping around and, you know, throwing people.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, there's a quick time event where I gotta jump and I dodge that thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: So now it's all Dragon's Lair where you just press a button.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I hit a button.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, there's a lot of interactive cut scenes and quick time events and a lot of stuff that I miss because it's hard to read them on this TV.
[SPEAKER_02]: But that's okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, well, and I'm looking at a comment in chat.
[SPEAKER_13]: For some reason, the JustinTV chat is borked tonight.
[SPEAKER_13]: Like, I'm not seeing anything in the JustinTV chat.
[SPEAKER_13]: So if you guys are trying to yell at us there, don't even bother.
[SPEAKER_13]: You've got to go to our main room.
[SPEAKER_13]: But I do see Misty saying, whoop blood.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, very bloody game.
[SPEAKER_13]: Can I get a whoop blood?
[SPEAKER_13]: Whoop blood.
[SPEAKER_13]: That game you were playing the other week on the GameCube, Mad World, that was way worse on the blood.
[SPEAKER_02]: I almost brought that again.
[SPEAKER_13]: I like this setup for the show where we have the game that we'll be running during the show and then someday we'll have the switcher so we'll go back to having the camera in studio when something exciting actually happens here in studio which is not that often.
[SPEAKER_13]: And the Interactive Cutscenes
[SPEAKER_13]: TigerClaw in chat says basically OLR wants to copy FNG which is Friday Night Gaming Bobby's show here on All Games Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: No.
[SPEAKER_13]: We don't want to copy Friday Night Gaming.
[SPEAKER_13]: They did their own thing.
[SPEAKER_13]: They fix stuff on air and we don't really get into that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: Plus they have that whole gaming center thing where people like that All Games Interactive used to have back in the day where people could like walk in and out as they want to and seeing as we tape this show at my house that's not exactly going to be happening.
[SPEAKER_13]: Although we have had Perfect Strangers show up here before.
[SPEAKER_13]: Remember Moe?
[SPEAKER_13]: Remember?
[SPEAKER_13]: We didn't even know her before we sent her an email on YouTube and she came here and sung the show, or sung the song on the show, so.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, we didn't do it.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, we've done the same shit for, what, seven years now?
[SPEAKER_13]: We're just slightly evolving a little bit as time goes on.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's get in.
[SPEAKER_13]: The entire class says, OLR could turn into a gaming center if more guests show up.
[SPEAKER_13]: I hope not.
[SPEAKER_13]: Again, this is my house.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's like, you know, at 10, 10, 1030, I want everyone to get that out.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, I just walked in, so I'm another guest.
[SPEAKER_12]: What about me?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, but you're different because I know you.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, I mean the doctor and me.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, shut up.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm different.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, housekeeping tonight before we get into the gaming news.
[SPEAKER_13]: We're like 20 minutes into the show, we need to get into the gaming news.
[SPEAKER_13]: Just a quick warning, kind of a disclaimer tonight.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was April Fool's Week this week, and while we think we've done a pretty good job of weeding the actual news stories from the bullshit, there might have been some bullshit that snuck through, but I don't think tonight.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think we got pretty much everything cleared.
[SPEAKER_13]: Also, don't forget to follow us on Twitter at UsernameOLR or follow us on Facebook, OLArmy, or follow us on LiveJournal at UsernameOrangeLounge.
[SPEAKER_13]: Also, I want to make a mention of Orange Lounge Radio March Madness.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's the thing that Bress Lowell really heads up, kind of spears it up for the Saturday night program here under Station Live.
[SPEAKER_13]: And, you know, we kind of give our commentary running on it.
[SPEAKER_13]: It finally ended this last week.
[SPEAKER_13]: Seems like it went on for a while, but considering you had like 64 games that had to get narrowed down to one.
[SPEAKER_13]: there were no ties this year there was one clear winner in the final no ties that we have to break Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_13]: 3 is your ultimate video game of all time per OLR March Madness this year which once again beat Chrono Trigger Chrono Trigger was the runner up for the second year in a row
[SPEAKER_12]: Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_12]: 3 Super Mario Bros. 3
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm not knocking on Chrono Trigger.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's a fabulous game, definitely worthy of the runner-up prize.
[SPEAKER_13]: However, you can't get mad that a game like Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_13]: 3 beat it.
[SPEAKER_13]: If Rock Band had ultimately won...
[SPEAKER_13]: I could see you, because that was in the final four I could see you getting mad if Rock Band won I would have stopped playing video games forever I would have joined you And I love me Rock Band But like a fine wine, it needs to age a little bit It needs to age a little bit before it can truly be the ultimate video game of all time Alright
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, Necessity Vampire in chat says, it's just a poll.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's just a damn poll.
[SPEAKER_13]: Don't cry.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right, let's get into some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_13]: Loki, you're going to have to pause your game so you can start us off with some gaming news tonight about Sony.
[SPEAKER_13]: Big press conference, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: and that is supposed to spike sales and allow the PlayStation brand to grow even more or it's just another way for them to say, hey look, look how many people we have on the PlayStation platform.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not the PlayStation 3 because the PlayStation 3 is in third place as far as the new consoles go but the PlayStation platform is number one because the PlayStation 2 is so popular.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's about time that they drop the price of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's old.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's over 10 years old now.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, not a big surprise.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then, also, other than the U.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: getting the price drop, of course, we're going to see a price drop in Europe as well to 99 euros.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, unfortunately, no price drop for the U.K.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: But...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think this is going to make any difference night and day
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, that, and they're like, oh, it can impact sales of the Wii.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, I don't think it will, because... Well, because that's the market they're going for.
[SPEAKER_13]: Instead of trying to... They're trying to make the price of the PlayStation 2 so lucrative that people will want to buy it instead of the Wii, because I think... I do think the PS2 is competing with the Wii for that sort of kids' bedroom toy.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know?
[SPEAKER_13]: And the Wii is not having the mass shortages that it used to have.
[SPEAKER_13]: That was kind of what was keeping the PlayStation 2 in some ways afloat, was that there was... Sometimes the Wii was gone, so people would opt for...
[SPEAKER_13]: PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_13]: You can't say PlayStation 2 is a bad system.
[SPEAKER_13]: You can't say there's no games available for the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's going to drop the new price and the used price.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it had to come eventually.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm kind of curious to see what the sales are going to be on the Wii in the next few months because they have met the demand and because of that I've had a lot less people buying them.
[SPEAKER_02]: When it meets the demand it's usually a time when the colors come.
[SPEAKER_02]: It might be a matter of time.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I wouldn't be surprised if the colors come during E3 because that's when they're going to announce stupid, superfluous shit like this.
[SPEAKER_13]: Comments from chat, comments from chat.
[SPEAKER_13]: TigerClaw says, It's amazing that Sony still supports the PS2 given its enormous library.
[SPEAKER_13]: You gotta give it to them.
[SPEAKER_13]: Unlike Microsoft or Nintendo that screw their fans by discontinuing their consoles, the fact that Sony still supports the PS2 shows that there are still a large contingent of people that still own their PS2s.
[SPEAKER_13]: All that from TigerClaw.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or because there's no backwards compatibility for the PlayStation 2 anymore on the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_13]: And that's exactly what Brad from PodCulture says.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, folks will pick one up, especially if your PS3 is not backwards compatible and your old, chunky PS2 is acting odd.
[SPEAKER_13]: Also, I want to say for Misty, kind of a dissenting voice here, it annoys me because I just replaced my PS2 since the beginning of the year and now it dropped to $99.
[SPEAKER_13]: Slanted angry face.
[SPEAKER_12]: And Nintendo still will repair the old systems.
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_13]: PSP, Rock Band Unplugged
[SPEAKER_13]: This news came out March 31st, which in a certain time zone might have been April 1st.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, I can see this happening because... This is legit.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's very legit because a lot of these songs cross over into the actual Rock Band games.
[SPEAKER_13]: I can see this.
[SPEAKER_13]: There is a way for me to check.
[SPEAKER_13]: For example, Blink-182, What's My Age Again, Billy Idol, White Wedding, Boston, More Than a Feelin', Foo Fighters, Everlong, Modest Mouse, Float On, Jackson 5, ABC, The Police, Message in a Bottle, The Who, Pinball Wizard, etc.
[SPEAKER_13]: Now also, the box apparently also confirms that there will be download content.
[SPEAKER_13]: There's going to be a music store.
[SPEAKER_13]: Unfortunately, there will be no multiplayer at all in the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: They had also some screenshots from it on the back of the box as well.
[SPEAKER_13]: I remember seeing the screenshots elsewhere on the internet, and it definitely looks like it's going to be an amplitude frequency type of game.
[SPEAKER_13]: Which, hey, fine by me.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I was just saying on Bobby's show earlier, Bobby Blackwolf, the guy who does the show before us here on All Games Radio on Sunday nights, was talking about the DS and DSi, and how Guitar Hero on Tour, one of the biggest selling third-party DS games, is kind of screwed by the DSi because the Game Boy Advance slot's now gone.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I was kind of, you know, we joked when we called on the show, like, well, who the fuck should be playing Guitar Hero on the DS anyway?
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, if they're trying to, like, emulate the whole... It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_13]: Play the actual Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_13]: It doesn't matter anyways.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a new system on top of the DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're still selling four colors of the DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there's still that many millions of DSs out there.
[SPEAKER_13]: They're not going to suffer one bit.
[SPEAKER_13]: But see, I give that a hard time, yet I allow Rock Band, this whole Rock Band on tour, because they're making a different game out of it that is really a throwback to something a lot of people have been salivating from.
[SPEAKER_13]: It doesn't have any peripherals.
[SPEAKER_02]: That too.
[SPEAKER_02]: They could easily... I wouldn't be surprised if they port this to the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Without the song store and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_13]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, anyhow, we will continue to watch Rock Band Unplugged and let you know more on it as soon as we know, which I'm sure will be E3.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm sure that game's going to be playable on the show floor, and I know that will be one of the first things I check out.
[SPEAKER_13]: What about you, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_13]: Are you interested in Rock Band Unplugged?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, not particularly.
[SPEAKER_06]: Really?
[SPEAKER_13]: I thought you were a big amplitude frequency type fan.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like it, but I'm... There's other things you're more interested in.
[SPEAKER_07]: They make me motion sick.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, I can see that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, there is going to be a new Jak and Daxter game for the PSP and the PS2.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: But there is.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's going to basically pick up from where the last game left off.
[SPEAKER_07]: And so you are in the last frontier.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you're...
[SPEAKER_07]: Going to help someone become a sage.
[SPEAKER_07]: Kira, I think is the name.
[SPEAKER_07]: And so it's an adventure up in the mountains.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or in the air.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or with pirates of the sky.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, you know, this series obviously still has its fans.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I think this goes right in line with the whole PlayStation 2 price drop.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's interesting to see, wow, they are still making freaking games for the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_13]: And this isn't like a...
[SPEAKER_13]: D-List title.
[SPEAKER_13]: This is at least the B-List.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, it actually is being developed by High Impact Games.
[SPEAKER_07]: So they're the ones that did Size Matters.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it looks like it's going to be fairly less depressing than the second one was.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_13]: Any interest in Jak and Dexter for you?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I haven't been interested in that ever.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's more of a kids franchise, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know we have listeners that are fans.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not necessarily a kids franchise.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not really saying that.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just like Ratchet and Clank.
[SPEAKER_02]: I tried to get into Ratchet and Clank because I had never really been a fan of it on the PlayStation 2 with the PlayStation 3 version.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tools of Destruction.
[SPEAKER_02]: I played it for a little bit and then I ended up selling it to my friend because I just...
[SPEAKER_02]: Tales of Vesperia
[SPEAKER_02]: And this is not really a big surprise since Tales of Vesperia came out on the 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: They did a similar thing with Eternal Sonata.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, of course, after the wait, not only do you get a game that is on par with the 360 version, but they've also added in new stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Including some new characters you'll get to play as that were kind of hinted in the Xbox 360 version.
[SPEAKER_02]: But now they are playable, which is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: and on another game they also announced Tales of Versus which is going to be a PSP title and it's kind of like the Tales version of Dissidia which is neat.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you got all the Tales characters fighting each other.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's still part of the Tales series, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: A little bit different, but they're putting out a lot of Tales games, that's for sure.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's selling like crazy in Japan, right?
[SPEAKER_13]: Didn't the Xbox 360 get a huge boost from this period?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that and Eternal Sonata, I think, did pretty good.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I never really noticed the Tales franchise that much.
[SPEAKER_02]: I haven't really played any of them, so I kind of feel bad in that sense, but I don't want to play any of them.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, Tales for Fantasia on Game Boy Advance is actually pretty good.
[SPEAKER_12]: Like for an old school, like 16-bit.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh yeah, Tales definitely has a very cult following to it.
[SPEAKER_13]: There's lots of fans of this series.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm not surprised this game is showing up on PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_13]: It is a little bit late to the party, but I think over in Japan it's going to mean more than it will here.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because in Japan, the PlayStation 3 has penetrated a bigger slice of the market.
[SPEAKER_13]: So I think it's going to be a bigger deal over there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would say put it out this year if you can because come the end of this year and possibly next spring, Final Fantasy XIII is going to come out and no one's going to care about anything else as far as the RPGs go.
[SPEAKER_02]: And whether it's good or bad, I mean, just no one's going to care.
[SPEAKER_02]: Speaking of which, remember, we're only like a couple weeks away and I'll be getting my copy of the demo.
[SPEAKER_13]: Ooh, that's right.
[SPEAKER_13]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_13]: Also, you can send, apparently, files to your friends as big as three megabytes now.
[SPEAKER_13]: And you can sort friends in your friends list now alphabetically or by online status and last login time.
[SPEAKER_13]: Which is good, because it seemed like there was no rhyme or reason to the friends list sorting before, so that was a feature that was needed.
[SPEAKER_13]: Also, there's some other features.
[SPEAKER_13]: a dynamic normalizer that will prevent sudden increases in volume between music tracks.
[SPEAKER_13]: For those games that don't know how to normalize their volume, that's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_13]: If you don't have a sound system, it'll do that as well.
[SPEAKER_13]: Also, the ability to cut and paste text, which I guess if you're a huge chatter in home might be useful or something.
[SPEAKER_13]: I can't think of a lot of chatty things I do on the PlayStation 3, but I guess cut and paste is needed.
[SPEAKER_02]: And now the dawn of the age of text spamming in...
[SPEAKER_02]: Out now!
[SPEAKER_13]: I actually upgraded earlier today before I went into home.
[SPEAKER_07]: but unfortunately those really aren't a lot of features I use very often except the friends list that will probably be the biggest thing for me well there's a particular series that I hate hate hate hate hate hate I won't see any of it I hate this whole series of movies the concept of it is disgusting and just repugnant to me what movie series is that Rob?
[SPEAKER_13]: Um, I would have to say Pokemon.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_07]: I really, really hate Saw.
[SPEAKER_13]: Pokemon and Saw?
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_13]: Would you watch that if the Pokemon started in the next Saw movie?
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck no.
[SPEAKER_07]: Pikachu!
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um...
[SPEAKER_07]: As I was saying, Konami has the Saw license.
[SPEAKER_07]: They pried it out of the dead fingers of Brash Entertainment.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank God.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because then it might actually be a decent game.
[SPEAKER_07]: But now, they were actually drawing comparisons between that and Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which I thought was more funny.
[SPEAKER_07]: Funnier!
[SPEAKER_07]: There's my grammar today.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um...
[SPEAKER_07]: The marketer David Daniels was telling what?
[SPEAKER_13]: Sorry, I'm laughing at the chat room.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hold on, we got DJ Tyrant.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hello, Ash.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'd like to play a battle with you.
[SPEAKER_13]: And Gold Anthro says, gotta saw them all.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dear chat room, they make Ritalin for a reason.
[SPEAKER_13]: Sorry, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: But the marketer David Daniels is quoted saying...
[SPEAKER_07]: that Silent Hill is more about psychological terror but Saw for Us is more about graphic intense horror that overwhelms you.
[SPEAKER_07]: We want players to turn away from the screen for just a moment because of the visual intensity.
[SPEAKER_13]: or because the graphics really really suck in other words it's going to be blood pornography these games are going to be just they're already preparing us for the fact that these games are going to be blood pornography well it's supposed to be out in the fall it actually has Tobin Bell doing the voice of Jigsaw
[SPEAKER_13]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, it's going to be out on PC, Xbox 360, and PS3, and guess who's not going to buy it?
[SPEAKER_07]: Me!
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not even going to let it come into my house.
[SPEAKER_13]: Aren't you worried this might have an impact on the Silent Hill series?
[SPEAKER_13]: I hope not.
[SPEAKER_13]: It better fucking not.
[SPEAKER_13]: I do like that he has the distinction.
[SPEAKER_02]: You mean it's going to get worse?
[SPEAKER_13]: I like that they've made the clear distinction.
[SPEAKER_13]: Silent Hill, psychological thriller.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because when I think psychological thriller, I think of great scary movies like The Silence of the Lambs.
[SPEAKER_13]: These types of classic psychological thrillers.
[SPEAKER_01]: More in a suspense sense.
[SPEAKER_13]: Right, but that's what Silent Hill is, right?
[SPEAKER_13]: More of like a suspense, mindfuck kind of movie, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: But it has the gross... It has the gore attached to it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It has... But it's not... The gore is not the focus.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: The gore is part of driving in the psychological part.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is... You are walking through a personal nightmare for your character.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's...
[SPEAKER_07]: In essence, that is Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_07]: You are walking through their nightmare.
[SPEAKER_07]: Everything in the game has some aspect of their personality or their guilt or something having to do with them that's going back to that person.
[SPEAKER_07]: It requires more thought than just splattering blood everywhere.
[SPEAKER_13]: But you know there are going to be people that are all about the blood orgy of Saw.
[SPEAKER_13]: It will sell.
[SPEAKER_13]: It'll sell, but... Loki, you're a big blood fan.
[SPEAKER_13]: Are you going to be purchasing the blood orgy that is Saw?
[SPEAKER_13]: No, because it's not going to be any good.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry, even if they could promise... Now, what they should have called it is Blood Orgy of the Game, but, you know... I'd buy a game called Blood Orgy.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, but seriously, though... I'm kidding, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry, but, you know, not to knock Konami or anything, it's not going to be any good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because it's made by Konami.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't want to knock them or anything, but it's... God damn, your game's going to suck.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hold on, though.
[SPEAKER_13]: To be fair, none of you have touched the game.
[SPEAKER_13]: And you're basing your review of the game off the movie, which isn't completely fair.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I'm basing my review off of the screenshot that I saw, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: And also the fact that Saw cannot be made into a game very well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because how are you going to do that?
[SPEAKER_02]: And no, I'm sorry, Konami's not clever enough to figure that out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Point and click.
[SPEAKER_07]: How about I have read enough about Saw to know that I have zero interest in playing the game or seeing the movies or anything remotely related to it, and I don't even watch the damn trailers.
[SPEAKER_07]: Then again, I don't watch TV, but still, I have zero interest in nothing but loathing for the franchise.
[SPEAKER_13]: Now, I noticed the consensus amongst chat, and I'm not going to read a lot of the individual quotes from chat here, because it seems like there's a consensus that Saw 1, decent, the rest, blood orgy, stupid porn movies, blood porn.
[SPEAKER_13]: The Leo Shannon chat, I will read this comment, blood orgy and titties would be the best selling game ever.
[SPEAKER_13]: It just might, it just might.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for watching, and I'll see you next time.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think I'll have to do that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actdeft is telling me to give the first movie a try, but I'm going to go ahead and explain this right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: The concept of that kind of thing, about putting people in that position, disgusts me like you have no idea how much it disgusts me.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's...
[SPEAKER_07]: It's so reprehensible of an idea that thinking about it makes me want to vomit.
[SPEAKER_07]: So no, I won't see it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I did see the first Saw movie, and it's one of those things where it's like, it's not that great.
[SPEAKER_13]: You can live your life and not see it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Like, there's a hundred other movies I would say a person has to see before they see Saw.
[SPEAKER_07]: C-Saw
[SPEAKER_02]: Continue the series without a new bad person and they've kind of done, they've made it as confusing as possible unless you've watched like the other movies and you're just like, oh, that's that dude from that other movie and wait, what?
[SPEAKER_13]: But next Silent Hill game, I am so there.
[SPEAKER_13]: I bought Homecoming.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was fun.
[SPEAKER_13]: Good game.
[SPEAKER_13]: I need to actually go back and beat it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: What's it going to be?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just like an adventure game?
[SPEAKER_13]: It doesn't make any sense.
[SPEAKER_13]: I would bet money this Saw game is going to sell even though we all hate it because there's an audience out there for it.
[SPEAKER_13]: There really is.
[SPEAKER_13]: There will be a Saw 2 video game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It will probably come out in October and it's going to be coming out at the same time as a bunch of other bigger games and I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: When this comes out there will be people that pick it up because it's Saw but think of the last really good movie title that's come out on consoles.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right, because most of them aren't that good.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_13]: This is just going to give ammunition to those people that say that video games are poisoning the minds of people everywhere.
[SPEAKER_13]: And those people that say Manhunt 2 is corrupting America and Grand Theft Auto is poisoning our children, etc.
[SPEAKER_13]: These saw games, especially if people's predictions that you are going to be the puppet in these games is correct...
[SPEAKER_13]: If you're the little puppet creature, that'd be awesome.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: I have a bad feeling that this game is going to be one of those things that certain lawyers, who I wish would stay out of the goddamn news, are going to use to propel their case into the next decade.
[SPEAKER_02]: They should be more offended by the movies because the movies are actually graphic and stuff, whereas this game, I don't think enough people are going to buy it to even care that it's violent.
[SPEAKER_07]: I will go ahead and say, by the way, it is not the gore that bothers me.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is the concept of what the people in the movie... Torture porn.
[SPEAKER_13]: Torture porn bothers you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Basically, that's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I do not... I can't stand torture of people who really haven't done anything wrong.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm so done with Saw.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the people have done stuff that's wrong.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the whole point of why they're being tortured.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know what I mean.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways, something that's not wrong in any way whatsoever would be Saints Row 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there's brand new download content coming out for it on April 16th, which makes me pretty excited because now I have a new reason to play that game again.
[SPEAKER_02]: The new download content will be called Ultor Exposed, which makes sense because there's areas of the map that you can't conquer yet, and they're all owned by Ultor.
[SPEAKER_02]: It will give you a few new things, including a co-op metagame.
[SPEAKER_02]: You'll be able to use porn star Tara Patrick as one of your homies.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, and new vehicles, new weapons, and some new multiplayer maps are also coming out along with that.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be available for the Xbox 360 and PlayStation 3 for 800 Microsoft points or $10 in real money.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I look forward to checking that out.
[SPEAKER_13]: All righty, let's move on to some release dates and let's travel the world and check out what's coming out in some other countries this week.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I'm looking over at Japan and in the next-gen systems, there's really not a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_13]: You get a price reduction on Tom Clancy's Ghost Recon Advanced Warfighter 2 on PlayStation 3, but not a lot of new stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I'm wondering if that's because you got the whole Advent Children coming out next week over in Japan.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: On the Nintendo Wii, you do have Oboro Muramasa comes out this week.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I'm not sure what this game really is, but it does look kind of stylized.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: This game is by the developers of Odin Sphere.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's all hand-drawn.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's very stylized.
[SPEAKER_13]: This looks kind of neat, actually.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like a side-scroll action game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's coming out in June here in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be called here Muramasa the Demon Blade.
[SPEAKER_13]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_13]: Arcana Heart 2
[SPEAKER_13]: A party-stylized concept game on the DS?
[SPEAKER_13]: What?
[SPEAKER_13]: and then lastly in Japan looking at the Sony Playstation Portable I don't believe I see a whole lot on the PSP where is my list here we do have another Evangelion game it's a Neon Genesis Evangelion called Setsu no Girlfriend Tokubetsu Hen Portable so you know what that means dating Evangelion Sim on the PSP again enjoy that
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, Sengoku Basara Battle Heroes is a big title coming out on the PSP I think that one is something you get a little more excited about
[SPEAKER_13]: Again, looks like this game's got some pretty sweet graphics too.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's another Dynasty Warriors game?
[SPEAKER_13]: It looks kind of, a little bit.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, there's like zero English in this game whatsoever.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's probably Shingoku Basara.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's, oh, I can't.
[SPEAKER_02]: Battle Heroes.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm thinking what it's called over here.
[SPEAKER_02]: They've only released one game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually have that for the Wii, and I haven't actually played it yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sky wants a guy version game that's Arcana Hearts style.
[SPEAKER_02]: To be fair, that's most other fighting games.
[SPEAKER_13]: Leo Shen says, Arcana Heart 2, get it, they have a freaking loli fighter modeled after Dorothy from the Wizard of Oz.
[SPEAKER_13]: There's no place like home, there's no place like home, punch!
[SPEAKER_02]: Does she roundhouse kick people with her ruby slippers?
[SPEAKER_13]: I guess so, let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's called Devil Kings over here, that's what it was.
[SPEAKER_02]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was Devil something.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not even going to ask.
[SPEAKER_07]: On the 10th, we have The Godfather 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: DSi Systems Rhythm Heaven Gravity
[SPEAKER_02]: Air Conflicts, Aces of World War 2 coming to the PSP because I don't think the PSP's had a World War 2 flight sim game yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Chronicles of Riddick, Dark Athena.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it was about time they got one.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was about time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Every system needs their World War 2 flight sim fighting game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, yes, definitely.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the Chronicles of Riddick, Assault on Dark Athena coming out on the Xbox 360 and the PlayStation 3 this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hannah Montana the movie, the game everyone's been waiting for, coming out on the PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, Wii, and DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then if you're not interested in Hannah Montana, you might be interested in Godfather 2, coming out on PC, PlayStation 3, and Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_13]: Those two, you'd be surprised how the fans... And if you're interested in both of those games, I think something might be wrong.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think most people would be interested in one or the other.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't really see somebody saying, yeah, GameStop employee, I'm here to pick up my copy of Godfather 2 and Miley Cyrus.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's for my daughter.
[SPEAKER_02]: Miley Cyrus is going to get an offer that she can't refuse.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because Miley Cyrus stars in the Godfather 4.
[SPEAKER_12]: Nobody knows this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Her and Sofia Coppola.
[SPEAKER_02]: Where the Godfather becomes hip and sassy.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some actual serious... Where RuPaul is the godfather.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to make you offer.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can't refuse, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: Girl, you better work.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then on PlayStation 2 and PSP this week, Guilty Gear XX Accent Core Plus coming out if you're looking for a good 2D fighting game.
[SPEAKER_02]: On PC, DCS, Black Shark.
[SPEAKER_02]: Looks like some flight sim game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Deer Drive is getting a re-release from Zoo Games.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a game where you drive your jeep and kill deer.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, and this is awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: On PC, apparently if you like crappy games or you're a girl, OMG High School Triple Play Pack featuring, I believe it's like the Cheetah Girls, Mean Girls, and... Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mean Girls, Clueless, and Pretty in Pink.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't know they had games for those.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like all of those movies.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think something's wrong with me.
[SPEAKER_02]: There is something wrong with you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see, Company of Heroes Tales of Valor coming out on PC.
[SPEAKER_02]: Elven Legacy on PC as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: And this is kind of cool, an Atlus PSP game, Hammer and Hero coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: And another crappy Wii game, Escape the Museum.
[SPEAKER_02]: And finally, you get a twofer here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not only do you get a crappy movie this week, but a crappy game based on said crappy movie that's based off of
[SPEAKER_02]: Dragon Ball Evolution The Game, The Movie, The Myth, The Failure Don't you think they need to make a video game out of that?
[SPEAKER_12]: Again, point and click.
[SPEAKER_12]: You dress the guys, you get them into their tucking panties.
[SPEAKER_13]: It would be a Wii game, because it would be a party game.
[SPEAKER_13]: It could be heel clubbing.
[SPEAKER_12]: And you gotta do the dance, but it would be like Spice Girls the game, too.
[SPEAKER_12]: I am all over this game.
[SPEAKER_12]: Let's put another girl through our paces.
[SPEAKER_13]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_13]: RuPaul's Drag Races.
[SPEAKER_13]: I like SSJ100 Matt.
[SPEAKER_13]: RuPaul GPS.
[SPEAKER_13]: Work.
[SPEAKER_13]: Turn to the left.
[SPEAKER_13]: Turn to the right.
[SPEAKER_12]: Any game where you replace the main character with RuPaul would be hilarious.
[SPEAKER_13]: I love RuPaul.
[SPEAKER_12]: God damn.
[SPEAKER_12]: RuPaul.
[SPEAKER_12]: RuPaul means her own game.
[SPEAKER_12]: I love RuPaul, but I think that'd be great.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think RuPaul would think that'd be funny.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh my god, is there a game developer out there listening?
[SPEAKER_13]: Please, call them and make this happen.
[SPEAKER_13]: There is an audience for that game.
[SPEAKER_12]: Like Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_12]: 3, RuPaul edition, but instead of the raccoon suit, it's the sparkly suit.
[SPEAKER_13]: Look, if you want to put in a little bit of money into this game, you're not going to sell a million, you're probably not even going to sell 100,000, but you'll sell like 25,000.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, I still think there should have been a gay X-Men where RuPaul was Storm.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_13]: that would be a great game here's something RuPaul should be in Oni Chambara
[SPEAKER_13]: No, seriously, I'm trying to tie this into the next story.
[SPEAKER_13]: Did you know there was actually a movie based off of Chambara?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's out here as well.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's localized here in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_13]: called Chambara Beauty, apparently.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, I got it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I haven't got a chance to watch it yet.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, you better hurry.
[SPEAKER_13]: I will.
[SPEAKER_13]: Guess what?
[SPEAKER_13]: Apparently, even though this movie got negative reviews across the board, who would have thought, for some reason, bikini-clad women slaying zombies with swords apparently had an audience for it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Chambara Beauty Vortex
[SPEAKER_13]: and I guess there is a game called Vortex as well that's going to be coming out as well.
[SPEAKER_12]: Amazingly enough though, for a Wii game, blood splattering on the screen, you get too much blood on your sword and it sticks into the zombies.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's not like a terrible blood fest, but it was a blood fest.
[SPEAKER_13]: Now something you should know, the star of the first film, Starlet Eri Otogoro, is not coming back for the second movie.
[SPEAKER_13]: So you know it's going to be a winner.
[SPEAKER_12]: So this is a live action Japanese movie.
[SPEAKER_12]: Is that what you're saying?
[SPEAKER_13]: No RuPaul game.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm just saying.
[SPEAKER_13]: Such injustice in this world.
[SPEAKER_13]: Such injustice.
[SPEAKER_13]: You would like Sky... I think I need to start one of those petition online things.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know those things that don't mean anything?
[SPEAKER_13]: But we need to start collecting signatures for a RuPaul video game.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I'll email fucking RuPaul somehow.
[SPEAKER_12]: Back to live action really quick.
[SPEAKER_12]: Akoge is a live action Japanese film about fag hags.
[SPEAKER_12]: Check it out.
[SPEAKER_12]: Akoge.
[SPEAKER_12]: Really?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes, yeah, because I dated a Japanese guy for a little bit and he showed it to me.
[SPEAKER_12]: It was awesome.
[SPEAKER_12]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because basically this chick likes to watch guys make out in the park.
[SPEAKER_13]: Gee, you know... I have no problem with that.
[SPEAKER_13]: A lot of straight guys like to watch girls make out in the park.
[SPEAKER_13]: Right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Like, hello, Cruel Intentions.
[SPEAKER_13]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_13]: Some girls like to watch girls make out in the park.
[SPEAKER_07]: La, la, la, la.
[SPEAKER_07]: Innocent, innocent.
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyway...
[SPEAKER_07]: Different stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes, how about different stuff?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, there's a game that's called Beyond Good and Evil.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's getting a sequel.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's inspired by the Trade Center airplane bombing thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: and I refuse to refer to the event by the date because I think that's fucking retarded so you can just refer to it as Loki's 21st birthday okay it happened on Loki's 21st birthday so when Loki was getting what liquor or something eating steak at a steakhouse that was empty okay
[SPEAKER_07]: But at any rate, the game is supposed to be based off of that.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're saying that that day's events actually gave across the same type of element of fear that he was looking for in the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: And so he's going to incorporate that same emotional sense into the sequel.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, um... He also, though, tried to compare it to Zelda.
[SPEAKER_07]: Saying that... Oh, come on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Saying that they're good games, but out of time.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I'm like, um... Is that like Majora's Mask?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, it just means that there's people who like happy, and some people who like to play fucking depressing stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: I had... Braid in a way was depressing to me.
[SPEAKER_13]: There's definitely depressing games out there.
[SPEAKER_13]: All the Silent Hill games are pretty depressing too.
[SPEAKER_07]: God, they're fantastic.
[SPEAKER_07]: I actually think that the UFO endings on Silent Hill are more depressing.
[SPEAKER_13]: I have really yet to play that game that makes me want to eat an entire canister of ice cream though.
[SPEAKER_13]: Getting that depressed.
[SPEAKER_13]: Watching a Lifetime movie or Steel Magnolias or something.
[SPEAKER_13]: I have yet to really see the video game equivalent of that.
[SPEAKER_12]: The only problem I have with games like that that'll be about an actual horrifying event like that, or even the World War II games, is the people who, when they play those games, are like, because I'm showing respect to the event and I'm remembering it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Nah.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I'm like, because you're sitting on your ass in your living room on a couch pressing buttons.
[SPEAKER_12]: So I'm like, that's the only  but it could be a good game.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: I have to say, and I'm just going to leave it here, and yes, it was incredibly awful, but making a big to-do about that is actually just perpetuating fear.
[SPEAKER_07]: We just need to go back to business as usual.
[SPEAKER_13]: It kind of seems like this person's reaching for buzzwords that are going to catch people's attention.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's the impression I get.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can understand trying to evoke an emotion, and I understand that was a very particularly...
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, for lack of a better description, that was definitely a unique sort of feeling, you know?
[SPEAKER_07]: The combination of gutted and really numb, I would think.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I can understand someone trying to evoke an emotion that is that unique, but at the same time, don't drag that into it, just fucking drop it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Klonoa
[SPEAKER_13]: Really?
[SPEAKER_13]: I never played that to completion.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's all, the game as you start it off, it's all cutesy happy, cutesy happy, get towards the end of the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh my god!
[SPEAKER_12]: Wind Waker also said.
[SPEAKER_07]: Really?
[SPEAKER_12]: I didn't really play enough of it.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, I thought it was.
[SPEAKER_12]: I was like, I've been playing this game for 15 years and then this is what happens to the kingdom?
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, I don't want to get a depressing show so let's go back to Lowell RuPaul for a minute here, okay?
[SPEAKER_13]: Apparently we have a friend at Sony that listens to the show and they're going to email some people about the RuPaul game and making it happen.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, God bless you.
[SPEAKER_13]: You are a public servant of the people.
[SPEAKER_13]: You are a brave man.
[SPEAKER_13]: It better have the word fierce in the title.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_12]: God bless you, sir.
[SPEAKER_12]: God bless you.
[SPEAKER_13]: I hope it happens.
[SPEAKER_13]: If they need input of any sort, please give them my email.
[SPEAKER_13]: Also, I want to point this out.
[SPEAKER_13]: SSJ100Matt made a good point.
[SPEAKER_13]: Rob, seriously, keep wishing because last time you did that, they made SingStar Abba.
[SPEAKER_13]: This is true.
[SPEAKER_07]: What if they did SingStar RuPaul?
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't think that would work as much.
[SPEAKER_07]: You could sing Back to My Root, which is actually... Okay, that song is a guilty pleasure for me.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, I don't think I'd want an entire SingStar game out of RuPaul.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think they could make a party game out of drag races.
[SPEAKER_07]: That'd be totally great.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think they could.
[SPEAKER_13]: RuPaul's Fierce Drag Race.
[SPEAKER_13]: ZakuPilot256.
[SPEAKER_13]: There's the name right there.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's got to have fierce in the title.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Most fiercest.
[SPEAKER_07]: It just has to be fierce.
[SPEAKER_07]: This game is fierce!
[SPEAKER_07]: Just buy it.
[SPEAKER_01]: The end.
[SPEAKER_07]: The title should just be This Game is Fierce.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, Lord Almighty, let's get past the RuPaul thing.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm so sorry to our listeners.
[SPEAKER_13]: You're the one who took us back to RuPaul.
[SPEAKER_13]: I know, it's my fault, but I neglected the chat.
[SPEAKER_01]: Candy!
[SPEAKER_13]: I was laughing so hard I couldn't see the chat, so I just went back and caught up on it and wanted to mention that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyways, so...
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a rumor going around that Mortal Kombat, the team that's working at least on Mortal Kombat, is trying to leave Midway.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess that's kind of like rats escaping a sinking ship.
[SPEAKER_02]: So they're looking for new developers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Probably going to buy them up.
[SPEAKER_02]: I could totally see that happening.
[SPEAKER_02]: It would be hilarious if Capcom bought them up.
[SPEAKER_13]: That would be cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: Actually, that would be all kinds of strange, because you know there would be that inevitable Street Fighter vs. Mortal Kombat game, and that's just gonna really weird a lot of people out.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's gonna be creepy.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's gonna be like when Sonic and Mario started showing up in the same place.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have a feeling if they were ever gonna leave Midway, which I doubt that they will, but if they were, EA would probably buy them up, because EA likes to snatch up properties like that, and...
[SPEAKER_02]: They've got enough money to throw around.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, I wouldn't be surprised if we saw that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because, you know, EA needs a good fighting game franchise.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because that Marvel game that they put out sucked.
[SPEAKER_13]: Didn't they do DC and Marvel?
[SPEAKER_13]: Midway did.
[SPEAKER_13]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_13]: No, it was Marvel vs. DC.
[SPEAKER_13]: Never mind, I'm stupid.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, it wasn't.
[SPEAKER_13]: Mortal Kombat vs. DC Universe, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: EA did Marvel Ultimate Alliance, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, that was Activision.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was Activision.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, EA did that, was it Rise of the Imperfects or something like that?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, yeah, the Silver Surfer?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, it wasn't Silver Surfer.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, Silver Surfer was also Activision.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, they did the Rise of the Imperfects game, which, so ironic that they had Imperfect in the title, but yes, it was not very good.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_13]: I just, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, I'm going to pull up a video here in studio, and I apologize you guys can't see this on the radio, but what's interesting about this, this is an unreal... Whoa, hello.
[SPEAKER_13]: This is Unreal Tournament, but it's a Sonic the Hedgehog level using the Unreal Engine.
[SPEAKER_13]: What?
[SPEAKER_13]: I apologize for the volume, good lord.
[SPEAKER_13]: See if I can turn that down, there we go.
[SPEAKER_13]: This is kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_13]: It looks a little bit like Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_13]: at most.
[SPEAKER_13]: It does kind of look like Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_13]: doesn't it?
[SPEAKER_13]: Very interesting level.
[SPEAKER_13]: Somebody spent a lot of time on that, that's for sure.
[SPEAKER_02]: They did something similar with...
[SPEAKER_02]: with Legos and stuff before they had Lego maps and stuff, mods.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's cool about stuff like this is, remember the PC mods do work on the PlayStation 3 versions, so you can actually get this for the PlayStation 3 as well.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, enough of that background noise there from the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Question for you though, which types of mods have you really been into for that?
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm not an Unreal Tournament player, so I can tell you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, what about, you know how they did with Quake?
[SPEAKER_07]: The Cube Mod
[SPEAKER_13]: Like the movie?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, like the movie.
[SPEAKER_13]: For Quake?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because Quake's kind of old.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, not for Quake, but for one of the later... Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: They did a cube mod, and someone tried to do a hypercube one where it would randomly regenerate the room.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: My whole point between that is that I don't really want to see people put into situations where they are forced to kill slash maim themselves or each other to get out of the situation because of something someone else perceives they did or they might have done.
[SPEAKER_07]: The cube, I think, is that you're putting the people together and they can either work together or they can kill each other and hypercube, they can just go crazy because time is freaking out.
[SPEAKER_12]: I totally, I just want to, I support you on the, I cannot stand the Saw movies.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm like, because I saw part of one of them, and the guy basically thinks he's helping them out by doing this, and I'm like, dude, no.
[SPEAKER_07]: I actually just went on Wikipedia to read the premise again, and while I, and for me, I'm always the type of person that tries to get my brain into the character, and that's something that just gives me a headache thinking about it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_13]: I didn't mean to open a can of worms.
[SPEAKER_13]: I just wanted to mention that real quick.
[SPEAKER_07]: I will also say another defense.
[SPEAKER_12]: How about those dolphins?
[SPEAKER_07]: I will say another defense about that versus Cube is that Cube, you don't technically have an antagonist.
[SPEAKER_07]: Technically.
[SPEAKER_07]: You have the situation as your antagonist.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_13]: More gaming news.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dude, gotta...
[SPEAKER_13]: What the DSI most needed in it to get me to buy one?
[SPEAKER_13]: Feature that the DSI needed the most to get me to buy one.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_13]: That might be a good one.
[SPEAKER_13]: Very topical.
[SPEAKER_13]: Think about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is it topical like an ointment?
[SPEAKER_13]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_13]: Maybe the chat room has some better ideas.
[SPEAKER_13]: If you have an idea for tonight's list, let's send it over.
[SPEAKER_13]: I got your joke.
[SPEAKER_13]: I got it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I just didn't laugh.
[SPEAKER_13]: Love ya.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, guess who I think is awesome?
[SPEAKER_13]: Me.
[SPEAKER_13]: Er.
[SPEAKER_07]: Steve Wiebe.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: and it turns out Billy Mitchell's a cock and sent in a videotape instead of coming in and doing it himself of him topping over a million points on Donkey Kong so Steve Weeby's going to be at E3 and that is reason enough for me to go I want to witness this
[SPEAKER_13]: Here's what's interesting, though.
[SPEAKER_13]: They did the same thing at E4ALL.
[SPEAKER_13]: And to be fair to our, I guess you could say, you know, I don't know what to call it.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's not really parent company because we own ourselves.
[SPEAKER_13]: But, you know, the company that enables us to do this live for you all every Sunday night, All Games had a ginormous booth at E4ALL.
[SPEAKER_13]: They had Steve Wiebe there trying to break the score for Donkey Kong.
[SPEAKER_13]: So it's kind of been there, done that.
[SPEAKER_13]: So it's just interesting that now people seem to care about
[SPEAKER_13]: because it's E3 and not E4ALL, which, you know, I get.
[SPEAKER_13]: This is going to have far more people.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, but I also, nothing would have gotten me to go to E4ALL, I think.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_07]: E4ALL, to me, was just a ginormous waste of time and I could have slept or done my laundry or, you know, washed dirty dishes with my tongue.
[SPEAKER_13]: It just looked better on paper, I think.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was one of those ideas that probably looked better on paper.
[SPEAKER_07]: at any rate um and this is funny because even the guys at Twin Galaxies were just saying that it was completely awful of uh Billy Mitchell and he's just such a dick oh my god he's such a dick I don't like him anyway um the other cool thing though is that with the two of them I think that I don't exactly agree with how my source says it because there have been other people who have hit the Donkey Kong kill screen but I think that those two are the only ones who have done it in a live event
[SPEAKER_07]: But the kill screen is basically after you pay so many levels of Donkey Kong, it'll just stop.
[SPEAKER_07]: It won't work anymore.
[SPEAKER_07]: It'll just be game over.
[SPEAKER_07]: It doesn't care how many extra lives you have or what your score is or anything.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just like, dead.
[SPEAKER_07]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mario will be running around, freeze.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, don't they show it in the movie?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, they show it.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I've seen someone do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: When?
[SPEAKER_07]: A long time ago.
[SPEAKER_07]: I had to have been like 11.
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: And apparently it was at a Godfather's Pizza.
[SPEAKER_07]: And citizens must be one of those people who just didn't care.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because we also had, I don't think I was that young.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think I was a little older than that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because we had one of the Mario machines, the Nintendo arcade machines.
[SPEAKER_13]: I bet there are a lot of people out there that could do it and just don't want to get in the scene.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_13]: They do it for themselves.
[SPEAKER_07]: I ask him if it broke.
[SPEAKER_07]: If he broke the machine, he's like, yeah, I broke the machine.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that's all I remember until I saw the movie.
[SPEAKER_07]: But anyway, I really, really would like to see him do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I would love to be there when it happens.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it would be fantastic.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I would like to see what Billy Mitchell does about it just because he's a dick and I'm kind of enjoying the drama a little bit even though it's kind of stupid.
[SPEAKER_12]: If he does, I will self-fornicate into my trousers.
[SPEAKER_07]: Can we put it on the internet?
[SPEAKER_13]: Can we broadcast that live on G4?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Remember, it's only porn if you tape it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Immediately following.
[SPEAKER_13]: Steve, we'll be breaking the record live on G4.
[SPEAKER_13]: We'll be live on G4.
[SPEAKER_13]: The doctor self-hornicating into his pants.
[SPEAKER_13]: Trousers.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_13]: Into his trousers.
[SPEAKER_01]: He might not be wearing pants.
[SPEAKER_01]: He might just be wearing the trousers.
[SPEAKER_13]: Ascetic Vampire in chat says, I'd go to see Billy's flowing hair.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't think he's going to be there at E3.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right, look, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_13]: Maybe he will.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm a little over the drive.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was just a movie, people.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was just a movie.
[SPEAKER_07]: GS68 makes the best point.
[SPEAKER_07]: And immediately thereafter, Billy Mitchell posts his new record on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right, a couple more news stories and we're going to take a break.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: So this is kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: For...
[SPEAKER_02]: April Fool's Day, Bethesda decided that they're going to go ahead and kind of do a half price sale on all the download content for Oblivion, which is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Except there's a catch.
[SPEAKER_02]: Horse Armor, they decided, you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Horse Armor's awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to double the price of that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just to be funny.
[SPEAKER_13]: To which I say, nay.
[SPEAKER_02]: I say nay.
[SPEAKER_07]: And after that, he goes, hey.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, I had to throw that in.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think this is their form of an April Fool's joke.
[SPEAKER_13]: Like, not that it's a joke.
[SPEAKER_13]: Like, it actually happened.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it actually happened.
[SPEAKER_13]: But I think it's like an April Fool's joke still.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_13]: Like, it was what they did in celebration of April Fool's Day.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because everyone realizes that, you know, including them, that horse armor is ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, I think even Bethesda realized, okay, you got us.
[SPEAKER_13]: Horse armor was pretty dumb.
[SPEAKER_13]: But people still buy it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Feature Net Guaranteed
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, look.
[SPEAKER_13]: Last week we brought you a story about a man who was suing Microsoft and Lionhead over reports that he was being harassed because he was gay.
[SPEAKER_13]: You might remember about this.
[SPEAKER_13]: Apparently, we're not going to get to see the drama unfold in the courtroom because there has been a settlement.
[SPEAKER_13]: The case has been settled out of court.
[SPEAKER_13]: Microsoft has released a very brief statement, and guess what?
[SPEAKER_13]: This is all you're going to hear on it, because usually with these settlements come gag orders.
[SPEAKER_13]: Microsoft says, We are pleased to have reached a makeable resolution to this matter with Mr. Durant.
[SPEAKER_13]: The terms of the settlement are confidential, but we can confirm that Mr. Durant will not continue his employment at Lionhead as part of the agreement.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's probably what he got for taking his case to the media, but hey, it sounds like everybody got what they wanted.
[SPEAKER_12]: Isn't Bill Gates gay?
[SPEAKER_13]: No, he has a wife, dummy!
[SPEAKER_13]: He can still be gay.
[SPEAKER_12]: Like, get my stuff!
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, shut.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, so there you go.
[SPEAKER_13]: Follow up to last week, to be fair.
[SPEAKER_13]: We wanted to follow up on that.
[SPEAKER_13]: We'll never know the real answer because of the settlement, but that's life.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, let's get into a segment we like to do here every week on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's called the Classic Video Game of the Week.
[SPEAKER_13]: And as part of this segment, DarkSakura will dig into her archive of classic gaming and find a title that she believes you all should be checking out.
[SPEAKER_13]: She's been doing this quite a while now.
[SPEAKER_13]: We have like over a year's worth of games that they're tracking on the OLR Wikipedia, which you can get to at OrangeLoungeRadio.com and go to that little thing that says, the little box in the corner with all the pictures that has the big W in it.
[SPEAKER_13]: And that's how you get to the Wiki on Wikia.
[SPEAKER_13]: I can't remember the name of the box.
[SPEAKER_13]: Extended Play.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I had a brain fart.
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyhow, what is the classic game of the week this week, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_07]: The classic game of the week is Incredible Crisis.
[SPEAKER_07]: That game is crack.
[SPEAKER_07]: And by crack, I mean crack.
[SPEAKER_12]: Welcome to Incredible Crisis.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is a game that came out on the PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_12]: Incredible Crisis with puppies.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, the game is about playing in a day in these family members' lives, the main character being Taneo, and they're trying to get everyone home early today for Grandmother Haruko's birthday.
[SPEAKER_07]: And this game very much is a parody of daily Japanese life.
[SPEAKER_13]: This game is incredibly what the fuck.
[SPEAKER_13]: For real.
[SPEAKER_13]: Like, I can't think of many more WTF games that have ever been made.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because, like, when you... Well, I'll let Jamie explain.
[SPEAKER_13]: Then I'll give my comment.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, the music in the game, if you'll listen to a little bit of it.
[SPEAKER_13]: They're dancing, by the way, in the office in this song.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's done by the Tokyo Sky Paradise Orchestra, so it's good music.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love them.
[SPEAKER_07]: So basically the way that this goes is you have a bunch of mini-games where you're playing through people's lives, and it's sort of sequential.
[SPEAKER_07]: Taneo, like, for example, this scene is him at work, and they are dancing to relieve stress.
[SPEAKER_07]: However, you've got this head-meter, and just the...
[SPEAKER_07]: The Redder and More Full That It Gets
[SPEAKER_07]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is it.
[SPEAKER_07]: There.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_07]: She tells you how to position yourself for the major boink action.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, technically, the translation says he's giving an erotic back massage.
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_13]: Dude, they're doing it on a Ferris wheel.
[SPEAKER_07]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_07]: And there's fireworks.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't think that's a back massage because that's not how we roll.
[SPEAKER_13]: DJ Terrence says, I jizzed in my pantsu.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I'll see you play as Etsuko, who is the mother, and she's out trying to buy stuff for Haruko's birthday, and she has to go to the bank, and it's being robbed, and just all this crap is happening to this family.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, um...
[SPEAKER_07]: No, and the last one is about the little boy, Tsuyoshi, and more weird stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's like turned into an ant or something, or shrunk to ant size.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like, the game's just freaking bizarre.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's so much weird crap this family has to go through, all for the sake of getting home early to, you know, have a birthday party.
[SPEAKER_07]: There are 24 minigames.
[SPEAKER_07]: Some of them do repeat.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it only is a one-player game, but it can still count as a party because really it's better to pass it around.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_13]: This game looks amazing.
[SPEAKER_13]: What the fuck was I thinking?
[SPEAKER_13]: I remember renting this game years ago and not liking it.
[SPEAKER_13]: FF7 and Puzzle Fighter
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: to actually translate the play of the game into it because of the way it involved the kanji.
[SPEAKER_07]: But one of them involved the daughter in the family singing karaoke, which I think would have been fun.
[SPEAKER_13]: Deathwishing in chat says, Seriously man, I wanted to break a brick over my head after I played this.
[SPEAKER_13]: It freaked me the fuck out.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was like taking acid, smoking crackpot, and then spinning around in a wash cycle.
[SPEAKER_07]: and actually if you want to know I'll link this in the chat room but if you want to know a little bit about part of the problem that went into translating the game or just stuff that goes into translating and localizing games there's an article and it's from last April actually that's called The Art of Translating Video Games and I will link that in the chat room for people to see if they're interested in it
[SPEAKER_07]: I love the game.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, I think it's crazy, crazy crack.
[SPEAKER_13]: This is exactly what the classic game of the week should be.
[SPEAKER_13]: One of those games that you kind of forget about, but you need to go back and say, wow, that game was like fucking nuts.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's going to do it for this part A of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: But stay tuned, guys.
[SPEAKER_13]: We have plenty more to come here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: Tonight's part B. We're going to do a listless game.
[SPEAKER_13]: I didn't see a lot of topics submitted in chat, although to be honest, I kind of missed a bunch of stuff when they were doing Incredible Crisis.
[SPEAKER_13]: So what do you want to do?
[SPEAKER_13]: You want to do the Excitebots thing or you want to do the DSi thing?
[SPEAKER_13]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_07]: I have zero preference.
[SPEAKER_13]: Zero preference?
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'd like to do What Kind of Flavor Does Jamie Want for Pie?
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't think that's going to work.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's see how creative we can get making up a trick.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, you want to do the Excitebots one?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I want to do the DSi one.
[SPEAKER_13]: You want to do the DSi one.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think the DSi one is a little more open and topical.
[SPEAKER_13]: So we'll do the DSi.
[SPEAKER_13]: We'll do the Sightbot when Sightbot comes out.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: So DSi, feature we most want to  or wish  no.
[SPEAKER_13]: How do we phrase this?
[SPEAKER_13]: Feature the DSi should have had that would have made me buy it yesterday or today.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: Feature the DSi should have had that would have made me buy it today because none of us bought it, right?
[SPEAKER_13]: But if it had this feature, I would have.
[SPEAKER_13]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, we're going to answer that question and do plenty more here on Orange Lounge Radio such as talking about Blizzard Entertainment and a possible interesting franchise they could be doing as well as a Silent Hill game on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_13]: We're going to talk all about that when we come back here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: And welcome back, everybody, to Orange Lounge Radio on this Sunday evening, April the 5th of 2009.
[SPEAKER_13]: We're taping live on All Games Radio, www.allgames.com, right after the Bobby Blackwolf show.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's about 6 o'clock Pacific Standard Time, 9 o'clock Eastern, every Sunday night.
[SPEAKER_13]: Join us for live taping, why don't you?
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura is with us as well
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't understand why you need it to be supported.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I would think if people, you know, have Guitar and Metallica, most people probably already have World Tour.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, you know, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: But hey, support for stuff is always good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, plus the lips mark is sparkly, you know, and all that.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, you know, who doesn't like sparkles?
[SPEAKER_13]: Me.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, good point.
[SPEAKER_13]: The lips mics are also wireless, says Actdeft in chat.
[SPEAKER_02]: True.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_13]: Isn't there a third-party wireless mic, too, though?
[SPEAKER_13]: Um, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, I've never played the Lips games.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm just kind of burned out on the karaoke games.
[SPEAKER_13]: Between the Rock Band, between SingStar, ABBA, and the other SingStar stuff that's available on PS3, I kind of didn't want to get Lips because I don't need another one.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, SingStar's, as far as karaoke games go, SingStar's rock solid enough, you know?
[SPEAKER_13]: Lips kind of was late to the party, if that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, hmm.
[SPEAKER_13]: Also, possibly late to the party, a revival of Redneck Rampage?
[SPEAKER_13]: Now, here's one of those things I look at and I go, surely this is an April Fool's joke, but I... I don't know, I mean, I'm looking at the... Redneck Rampage is pretty freaking funny.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it's a game about my hometown?
[SPEAKER_13]: I think it's stupid.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think it's like one of the stupidest video games I've ever seen.
[SPEAKER_13]: Like, I realize it's supposed to be a parody, but WTF, but okay, wait, I'm not done yet.
[SPEAKER_13]: But apparently this story broke on like the 4th of April or whatever, but here we go.
[SPEAKER_13]: Blizzard, apparently there's a rumor that Blizzard Entertainment actually has the Redneck Rampage brand right now.
[SPEAKER_13]: And apparently this is some research done by a website called INC Gamers.
[SPEAKER_13]: They were doing some trademark following or what have you.
[SPEAKER_13]: And apparently Redneck Rampage was originally trademarked in 97, then Redneck Rampage rides again.
[SPEAKER_13]: Redneck Rampage sucking grits on Route 66.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes, that was really the name of apparently the third game that was made.
[SPEAKER_13]: They're apparently all now under Blizzard's control.
[SPEAKER_13]: So Blizzard apparently owns the rights to these games.
[SPEAKER_13]: Is that through acquisitions and things like that?
[SPEAKER_13]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_13]: Apparently Activision actually acquired the Redneck Rampage thing.
[SPEAKER_13]: But why would it then be given to Blizzard and not Activision?
[SPEAKER_13]: Don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: But apparently there are some Blizzard folks on staff who actually worked on the original Redneck Rampage.
[SPEAKER_13]: I hope to hell this doesn't mean they're making a new one.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, talk about unnecessary.
[SPEAKER_13]: Unnecessaries.
[SPEAKER_13]: X-Link in chat suggests redneck for the iPhone.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_13]: I would rather it be something like that.
[SPEAKER_13]: And DJ Tyrant said, Blizzard isn't this stupid, are they?
[SPEAKER_13]: And hopefully not.
[SPEAKER_13]: DJ Tyrant, maybe it's something that's a nod to those employees who were there that worked on the game.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: But let's just hope it's just an interesting observation and nothing more.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know, DarkSakura, would you buy a new redneck rampage?
[SPEAKER_07]: Would I buy it?
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_13]: Definitely.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'll tell you what I'd buy.
[SPEAKER_13]: A new Hexic.
[SPEAKER_13]: Or Hexen.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hexen!
[SPEAKER_13]: Those games were pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Heck yeah, I love Hexen.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_02]: That game was awesome, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: What, Redneck Rampage?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was using the same engine as Duke Nukem 3D, but it had more features for it.
[SPEAKER_00]: How about they just bring us Duke Nukem forever?
[SPEAKER_13]: Didn't Hexen use the same engine as Quake, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, and it was awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just like turning people into chickens.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, as we covered on our last show, we're supposed to be getting...
[SPEAKER_07]: We're actually supposed to be getting those arcade games coming out for the Wii service.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, Sega is also taking a step to put actual arcade games on Xbox Live Arcade a lot more than what we've been seeing lately.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're getting, and this makes my heart soar, Virtualon or Tario Tangram.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't have to bake out my Dreamcast to play it, except...
[SPEAKER_07]: I have twin sticks, so it's better to play it on the Dreamcast, but I digress.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's release ratings for Shinobi and Altered Beast, so that means System 16 will be getting some of those.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, there is one that's rumored as a Sega Vintage Collection Volume 2, and there's also other Genesis titles listed as Comic Zone, Sonic 3, Gunstar Heroes, and Phantasy Star 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: Gunstar Heroes, of course, being one of the best Sega games ever.
[SPEAKER_12]: Now, Comic Zone was already on the virtual console, though.
[SPEAKER_12]: But this is the arcade.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is the virtual console.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is live arcade.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, but I thought you said for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: I started off with the Wii because we had talked about Sega arcade games coming out on Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: To recap, last week on Orange Downs Radio, Rob ate a live frog.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Loki's head exploded.
[SPEAKER_07]: Leaving Jamie as the victor in Battle Royale Orange Downs Edition.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, um...
[SPEAKER_07]: Dan got to meet him At E3 One year
[SPEAKER_13]: I got my hug on with, um, uh, not Koji Kondo, the other, Igarashi.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_13]: but I think a good game you have to have a passion for video games and you have to have your obvious favors and things like that so I I completely justify my you know screaming like a little 12 year old girl when I saw Akira Yamaoka okay so there you go that he's also it doesn't hurt that he's really good looking oh Black Wolf and DJ Tyrant both in chat said I met Rob Roberts at E3 yeah no we said celebrities
[SPEAKER_07]: Internet Celebrities Black Wolf said I totally squeed with fanboy delight when I met Rob Roberts He did actually I have yet to meet Rob Roberts Just so you guys know Oh my god, oh my god I totally blushed with embarrassment after running into Hideo Kojima Like three E3s in a row I don't know how this happens If it happens again this year I'm gonna just go off and cry Or tell him to give me a job
[SPEAKER_13]: All right, let's move on with more gaming news.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's stop talking about E3 and who we may or may not see at E3 this year.
[SPEAKER_02]: So this is kind of weird, I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: Last week we talked about how Filefront was going away and, you know, oh darn.
[SPEAKER_02]: But apparently it's back.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it says Filefront has been acquired by the original founders of the site and will not be suspended as previously announced.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is not an April Fool's joke.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's funny.
[SPEAKER_13]: So what once was dead is now back.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, congratulations to the folks at Filefront for inserting a coin to continue.
[SPEAKER_13]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's all it took, right?
[SPEAKER_13]: And in other news, EGM is coming back.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, wait, no, that's not true.
[SPEAKER_13]: April fools.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: That would have been a great EGM yearly joke, right?
[SPEAKER_13]: Because they used to do these epic April Fool's jokes every year.
[SPEAKER_13]: Remember, Ermac in Mortal Kombat was born of an EGM April Fool's joke.
[SPEAKER_13]: That could have been their epic joke this year, that they're coming back.
[SPEAKER_13]: And then, oh, April Fool's.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's a joke.
[SPEAKER_13]: That would have been too soon.
[SPEAKER_13]: Insulting for their fan base, yes.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_13]: It's a remake, sort of, of the first game, but they don't want you to call it a remake of the first game.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's a reimagining of the first game.
[SPEAKER_13]: Which, you know, means Boohoo, no Pyramid Head, but at the same time... The first game didn't have Pyramid Head.
[SPEAKER_13]: Right, Boohoo, no Pyramid Head.
[SPEAKER_13]: But the first game was pretty fucking phenomenal.
[SPEAKER_13]: And a lot of people still say it was probably the best game in the series.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, you know, definitely going to be a must-have for Silent Hill fans.
[SPEAKER_13]: And a quote from the magazine where this originally appeared, Nintendo Power...
[SPEAKER_13]: The characters play different roles Things don't necessarily happen in the same order And the story is taken in lots of new directions You still play as Harry Mason You're still looking for your daughter And you'll see familiar elements But they're all twisted to betray your expectations So this is kind of cool Because it sounds like maybe it's going to be fucking with what people are expecting in the game Because they think it's going to be a remake That's going to be kind of cool So um
[SPEAKER_13]: Apparently though, yes, they are going to exploit the Wii thing a little bit.
[SPEAKER_13]: They are going to use some of the Wii remote action.
[SPEAKER_13]: Some of the in-game puzzles will use Waggle in it.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, I heard, maybe I'm not supposed to repeat this, but I heard a long time ago rumors that there were some tests being done in Konami of a Silent Hill type game where you would use the Wii mode as the flashlight as you were moving around.
[SPEAKER_13]: And doesn't that sound scary?
[SPEAKER_13]: I hope that concept made it into this game somehow.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think that could be super creepy.
[SPEAKER_01]: Fantastic.
[SPEAKER_13]: And pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: If executed correctly.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, it could also be kind of dumb.
[SPEAKER_12]: And thank God, because they should have been doing this kind of stuff on the Wii since the beginning.
[SPEAKER_12]: So if they start doing that, great.
[SPEAKER_13]: By the way, also, fans, you should know, part of the thing that bugged about the first Silent Hill game, that locked doors were everywhere.
[SPEAKER_13]: Now there will be a way through every locked door.
[SPEAKER_13]: You will no longer have to find that most of the doors in the game are permanently shut.
[SPEAKER_13]: Sounds like it's going to be pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, I'm definitely looking forward to this.
[SPEAKER_13]: More information, at least.
[SPEAKER_13]: I bet this is going to be one of the big things we're going to see at E3.
[SPEAKER_13]: Or, Konami's having an event, if I remember right, this next week.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, we weren't invited, but they're doing the Saw thing, and I know they're showing that.
[SPEAKER_13]: I wouldn't be surprised if this shows up as well, along with your mandatory DDR and Yu-Gi-Oh for the year.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_13]: And, oh yeah, don't forget Winning Eleven.
[SPEAKER_13]: All those games, you've got to get your mandatory entries for the year in there.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_13]: Are you excited about the Silent Hill remake?
[SPEAKER_13]: You're a clever one.
[SPEAKER_00]: Robbie me go he.
[SPEAKER_07]: For a game on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, good.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's hope there's more Wii going Wii games later on.
[SPEAKER_13]: Do you think you might have one in this next story, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_07]: Project Ringo
[SPEAKER_07]: There's been talk going around about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It turns out that Project Ringo is a new Puyo Puyo game that's going to be on DS, Wii, and PSP.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, of course, we get it as Puyo Pop.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it will be, technically, it's just Puyo Puyo 7, which is more Puyo Puyo.
[SPEAKER_07]: But you also will have a transformation mode which will let you actually deflect attacks instead of, I guess, just preventing them from happening and have larger chain combos.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that would be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: But there should be some...
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm a big enough fan to pronounce it correctly.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, um... I don't know, we kind of talked a little bit in Part A about the new... Well, not really a new game, but Tales of Vesperia coming to the PS3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, there is a new Tales game coming to the Wii as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tales of Graces.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's been announced for the Wii, thanks to Fumitsu Magazine.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, um...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: Or is it just waggle, waggle, waggle?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: The last Tales game that they put out was okay on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then this is supposed to be coming out in Japan in the winter.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I guess we'll see more about this later on.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, some rumors are going around about upcoming Wii titles.
[SPEAKER_13]: There's apparently a list that was leaked to the internet this week showing an upcoming release date list of some various games coming out on the Nintendo Wii.
[SPEAKER_13]: But here's the interesting thing.
[SPEAKER_13]: It dates Wii Motion Plus and Wii Sports Resort on July 10th.
[SPEAKER_13]: It also dates, here's the other interesting thing, Wii Fit Plus on November 19th.
[SPEAKER_13]: Nintendo, repackaging something and slapping Plus in front of it?
[SPEAKER_13]: No, you don't say.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, now, here's something you should take, though, from this.
[SPEAKER_13]: And, you know, yes, chatters, I am aware.
[SPEAKER_13]: Apparently, this list came out of the Netherlands.
[SPEAKER_13]: It wasn't actually from the U.S.
[SPEAKER_13]: And, you know, take it with a grain of salt.
[SPEAKER_13]: But I think most of us are looking at this going, Wii Fit Plus?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, I can see that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: I can see that happening.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's innovation for you.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's innovation for you.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, but why, you know, why the, uh, Nintendo should be leaking their release dates?
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know what this secrecism is, it's like, my god, like, we're not gonna tell you.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's like, good god.
[SPEAKER_02]: Somebody might steal the idea to repackage something and add plus to it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, wait a second, Guilty Gear did it first!
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, doesn't, I mean, Loki, you kind of have an insider perspective on this, don't sometimes the retailers and the folks on the inside have to know this a little sooner before the consumer?
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: WEEFIT
[SPEAKER_02]: It's still, you'd be surprised, it's still hard to get from Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Same with Mario Kart.
[SPEAKER_02]: What the hell is up with Mario Kart?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't get that either.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, for whatever reason, I could totally see this happening.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's going to be something stupid.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if it's going to now support Wii Motion Plus for something, but...
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm not buying it, that's for sure.
[SPEAKER_13]: Probably more crappy minigames.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, well, I shouldn't say that.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, Wii Fit isn't bad, per se.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's just not for the hardcore gamer.
[SPEAKER_13]: But there's definitely an audience for it.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's not a bad piece of software.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's put it that way.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, let me put it this way.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is this what they're going to basically load their guns with for their E3 press conference?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because if they're like, and you thought we forgot you, Core Gamer, we fit plus.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, because right now it's looking like more of the same and that's scary.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, no, I actually think that the Motion Plus is going to be the big thing.
[SPEAKER_12]: But my concern is because Nintendo is such a bitch about revealing things to people or telling them stuff, I'm just afraid that they're going to alienate the developers and nobody's going to develop anything.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know, I think number one, they should have developed, I mean, the Wiimote should have had this extra sensor in it anyway.
[SPEAKER_12]: But then I just think they're going to alienate the producers again and nobody's going to make good games for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's what's going to happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to do Wii Sports Resort.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to throw in something that people need to buy.
[SPEAKER_02]: So not only is it the Wii Sports angle, but it's also the Wii Play angle at the same time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, and now we're going to do the same thing with Wii Fit.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to do Wii Fit Plus.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to add some other new thing that people probably don't need.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then we're going to try to resell it again because people eat up Wii Fit and they want to buy a Wii system for Wii Fit.
[SPEAKER_02]: What about the Core Gamer?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, well, you get some ported GameCube games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sweet.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then we get a version of Excite Truck, which has really been toned down kid-wise.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I hear they removed the whole custom soundtrack thing, which sucks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why?
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's go step backwards as far as innovation goes.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I will bet you anything there will be multiple colored Wiimotes and people will piss themselves over it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I gotta own a red remote now.
[SPEAKER_12]: I just have to disagree on the Motion Plus because for a lot of us that bought the Wii, we thought it was going to have one-to-one control from the beginning.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I still think it should have.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't understand why they didn't just make the Wiimote with this extra... And I've heard people, I've heard things online that say that it does add that one-to-one control and the possibilities are great.
[SPEAKER_12]: I just, I'm going to be pissed if Nintendo alienates all the producers again and doesn't actually... You know, like I heard that LucasArts was upset because they weren't aware of this before they came out with their...
[SPEAKER_12]: LightSaber Games, so I'm very upset.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, maybe we'll get knocked completely on our ass.
[SPEAKER_13]: That they're going to reveal that game for the core gamer.
[SPEAKER_13]: They're going to, you know, Reggie's going to whip it out and say, you know, here it is, Kid Icarus, the game you've all been waiting for, something like that.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, and it's going to rock.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hope.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right, and Konami's going to put out a good music game again.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: There are patterns for a reason.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, you know, what they're going to announce, what?
[SPEAKER_02]: A new Pikmin game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Big...
[SPEAKER_02]: Whoopin' shit, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, big deal, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: New Pikmin game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, you know, the fans have been crying for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yada, yada, yada.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe a new Zelda game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, are we really gonna get down to the point where we're just re-releasing the same franchise games over and over?
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's do something new, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, the Wii Sports stuff is okay, but let's create a new character.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's do something different.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's make, you know, something really epic.
[SPEAKER_02]: But no, we're gonna, you know, now, you see...
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_12]: I totally agree with you.
[SPEAKER_12]: My thing with the Wii Motion Plus is that this would open up the possibility for that true new style of gaming that we were all expecting with the Wii, where it's like your virtual reality, but I'm just afraid that the third-party producers are not going to feel like they're supported by Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think that is.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's going to happen is you're going to see a bunch of these games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now it supports Wii Motion Plus.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a sequel.
[SPEAKER_02]: Red Steel 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, but the controls still suck.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not going to help anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's good as a new tool and stuff, but it's not anything innovative.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not...
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just fixing a problem, that's all it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's another peripheral that they can sell for $10, bundle it with a game, and then they're going to include the remotes, they're going to have it built into it now, and then it's going to be something else.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be always something to fix the flaws of what the system was.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not new.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I won't be damn surprised if there's anything from this press conference that surprises me, but last year it was just like, yep, huh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Stupid peripheral, huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: Really funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, with the whole Wii Zapper.
[SPEAKER_02]: It used to be awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: The original Wii Zapper was really kick-ass.
[SPEAKER_02]: What they first showed off, you know, the prototype and all that stuff, they should have stuck with that.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, now it's a plastic shell that I don't even use anymore.
[SPEAKER_02]: The third-party peripherals are better than the goddamn Wii Zapper.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_13]: We are two months away from E3, and a lot of these questions will be answered.
[SPEAKER_13]: But in the meantime, we're going to answer some of your questions by going to a segment we like to do every week known as the Orange Lounge Radio Mailbag.
[SPEAKER_13]: By the way, I do want to remind everybody in studio and in our chat live that we are doing listless tonight.
[SPEAKER_13]: And the topic tonight for listless, which we'll get to a little later in the show, but everybody should be thinking about their lists, right, for listless.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's been a little while.
[SPEAKER_13]: It would be the feature that the DSI should have had to get me to buy one today.
[SPEAKER_13]: So be thinking about that.
[SPEAKER_13]: In the meantime, let's open up the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_13]: Mailbag at orangelaunchradio.com and read some of your emails right now.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_00]: We have one from Deathwishing.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hey guys, remember how I called and ranted about how Microsoft stole my $20?
[SPEAKER_07]: I do remember that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, patience paid off.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not only did I get my original points of $1,600 back, but I threw in an extra $1,600.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess this shows you that being polite and waiting gets you a reward better than bitching 24-7.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, I'm gonna sleep now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, thanks, bye.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm glad to hear all was resolved.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is... The next one is from Isabelle.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, first off, I want to start off by saying hi, how's it going?
[SPEAKER_07]: I haven't been able to listen to the show for a long while now, and I hope all of it is great for you guys.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now to get to the point of my email, I finally got to play Tatsunoko vs. Capcom after what seems like a million years, and all I have to say about that game is wow.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've heard how you guys said it was well done and really awesome, but I didn't expect it to be this awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: I played its arcade version, and for the arcade...
[SPEAKER_07]: and for an arcade game, it's really good.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, have you gotten to play the arcade version?
[SPEAKER_07]: Another arcade game I got to play was Tekken 6.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just from the arcade version, I can tell that once it hits homes, no one will leave their couches.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, it really was that good.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I wish you all the best and thanks for taking time for reading this email.
[SPEAKER_07]: I actually haven't played the arcade version yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: I never got a chance to go check it out at any of the local places, well, state local places that have it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, I had no idea there was an arcade version of Tatsunoko vs. Capcom.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's pretty rad.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, it originally was the arcade version.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, and I should have known that.
[SPEAKER_13]: But yet I didn't.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have played the Wii version, and I played with Jun and Ken as my team, and I was very happy with it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I still need to get out and play Tekken 6, because I love Tekken everything.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I can't really say anything else, more about any arcade versions of them, just that Tatsunoko vs. Capcom is super cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the last email, this comes from Spirit of Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've been playing video games since I was little and never been scared in any game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry but Silent Hill 2-3 are boring and controls like garbage.
[SPEAKER_07]: I will agree with some of the control issues.
[SPEAKER_07]: The only game that honestly gave me a hard time going to sleep was the original Manhunt.
[SPEAKER_07]: The concept of someone forcing you to do snuff films is the stuff of nightmares.
[SPEAKER_07]: Cool first time sending you guys an email.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, keep up the great podcast you guys.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, Manhunt is something that I find repugnant.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't really care for the game at all.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like the psychological type of edge.
[SPEAKER_07]: The stuff that requires intelligence and not, you know, ooh, blood!
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, yay for first-time emailers, if nothing else.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, thanks for emailing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Keep it up.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's it for the emails.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's over.
[SPEAKER_13]: Mailbag at OrangeLaunchRadio.com if you want to send us an email for reading in a future show.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_13]: In the meantime, let's get back to some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_13]: We just have a few more stories, and then we're going to get into tonight's list list, and we're going to respond to some of the tweets we got on Twitter this week.
[SPEAKER_13]: We're going to respond to those in just a little bit.
[SPEAKER_13]: We got one more round of stories, though, starting off with Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's interesting how April Fool's jokes can now become reality again.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: And funny enough, it actually made it into the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course, it shouldn't be a surprise that the company behind it, Volition, also puts out Saints Row.
[SPEAKER_02]: So they are, of course, very used to quirky, weird shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, Ostrich Hammer.
[SPEAKER_02]: That almost sounds like something that should be in Team Fortress 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sounds like the name of a real good metal band.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ostrich Hammer!
[SPEAKER_13]: But yeah, so you'll be able to hit people with an ostrich.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_13]: Apparently, he was really, really famous in the 1980s because he could actually press a button 16 times in one second.
[SPEAKER_13]: 16 times in one second, if you can believe that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Now, they made this little device back in the 80s to kind of cash in on this whole button mashing thing called the Shooting Watch.
[SPEAKER_13]: And you could use this to try and match, beat, or try and tie this guy's score.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, Shooting Watch has now been ported to the iPhone.
[SPEAKER_13]: So you can try and mash buttons as fast as you want.
[SPEAKER_13]: But here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't think this thing's going to be that...
[SPEAKER_13]: It's gonna cost you 99 cents.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's not gonna be as real as the real deal because I don't think the iPhone screen is good enough.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's not gonna match the electronics of an actual button.
[SPEAKER_13]: But look, if you just want a stupid app, pointless thing...
[SPEAKER_13]: Have fun.
[SPEAKER_13]: 16 times in one second.
[SPEAKER_13]: Like, imagine 16 times.
[SPEAKER_13]: Ready?
[SPEAKER_13]: One one thousand.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_13]: 16 times.
[SPEAKER_13]: Right in that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Crazy.
[SPEAKER_13]: One more story, then listless.
[SPEAKER_00]: That makes my brain hurt to think about.
[SPEAKER_07]: That would have come in really freaking handy doing the drinking minigame in Chrono Trigger.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, speaking of for iPhone, there is actually a good game coming out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Cooking Mama is a good game.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is a good game.
[SPEAKER_07]: There is a version of Galaga that is coming out, which was... You could actually play this particular version in... I do believe that it came out in 1981?
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: There was the 1995 one that was the Galaga remix.
[SPEAKER_07]: But Galaga remix is coming out on iPhone.
[SPEAKER_13]: I remember that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Wasn't that packaged with Pac-Man and Dig Dug remixes?
[SPEAKER_07]: I do believe so.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_13]: They have that at a local arcade around here.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's closed down.
[SPEAKER_07]: And actually, as far as I was always aware, the Galaga remix was based off of the Galaga 90 and Galaga 88.
[SPEAKER_07]: But that was just in my observation.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it's supposed to be coming out on the iPhone.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it will be $5.99.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you can use directional buttons, but there's also a sliding method and there is a tilt method.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which I'm going to use the buttons, I swear, because...
[SPEAKER_07]: Trying to play Pole Position and Tilt Mode is not fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, it's going to be pretty good.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's going to be good.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was watching a video about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It looks pretty good.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's have an interesting round table on this point here before we get into the list list tonight.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because an interesting comment was said in chat.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I think everybody might want to have to say something to this.
[SPEAKER_13]: GameGuru in chat says, I don't see how you love the iPhone and hate on the DSi.
[SPEAKER_13]: Apple's worse with updating hardware.
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't say I hate... No, you as in all of us.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I don't hate the DSi.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just haven't... I have other things to spend my money on right now, like Disneyland.
[SPEAKER_13]: As far as... For me, here it is.
[SPEAKER_13]: I already have a Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_13]: What does the DSi add to it that the DS didn't already have?
[SPEAKER_13]: Like, you know, I'm not saying the DS is a bad gaming system.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's not.
[SPEAKER_13]: And if you don't have a DS yet, the DSi is probably a pretty good purchase for you.
[SPEAKER_13]: I would actually recommend it over the DS at this point because you know there's going to be those games later on.
[SPEAKER_13]: and so on and so forth.
[SPEAKER_13]: Updating the software.
[SPEAKER_13]: Think about it.
[SPEAKER_13]: The iPhones, when they first launched, didn't have the App Store and the user-made apps and those things built into it.
[SPEAKER_13]: That was something that Apple added for everybody.
[SPEAKER_13]: Whereas I feel like with the DSi, there was nothing being given to current DS users.
[SPEAKER_13]: You can't update the firmware on the DS.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think for me, there's kind of the difference in...
[SPEAKER_13]: Those two things.
[SPEAKER_13]: And the iPhone's not perfect.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, yeah, Apple is a huge abuser of this whole let's upgrade the whole thing in a year and watch everybody buy it all over again.
[SPEAKER_13]: But, you know, we give them crap for that, too, and it's deserved.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, anyway, speaking of that, let's get to tonight's list list.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_13]: Then we're going to go around the room and each one of us is going to take something off of the list, leaving a list of eight.
[SPEAKER_13]: Then you guys in chat will vote on that list of eight and make our top three using your votes.
[SPEAKER_13]: And then we will have the definitive top three list.
[SPEAKER_13]: No arguments, no debates.
[SPEAKER_13]: It is the official list.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: I say that, but of course there's always room for debate.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, so that being said, tonight's topic...
[SPEAKER_13]: Feature that should have been on the DSi that would have got me to buy one today.
[SPEAKER_13]: Who wants to start us off tonight?
[SPEAKER_13]: How about Loki?
[SPEAKER_13]: Loki's always got some evil answers for us.
[SPEAKER_13]: Loki, what is your number three answer of the feature the DSi should have had?
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, I was thinking a bunch of different things.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let me say this.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_13]: Real quick.
[SPEAKER_13]: Chatters, if you have ideas, put them in our chat room because if one of us gets an answer stolen, like somebody else says the same answer we were going to use, usually we take backup answers from chat.
[SPEAKER_13]: So I just wanted to get that out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: which would be kind of neat I mean I don't really use this on the Wii but like the DSI message board you know basically allowing you to send emails and attachments and stuff like that to each other really you know DSI should have a lot of stuff that the Wii has but you know that's what I'm going to start with
[SPEAKER_13]: Doctor, what is the number three feature the DSi should have had to get you to buy one today?
[SPEAKER_13]: Voice recognition.
[SPEAKER_02]: Software.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think that would be an awesome feature in games.
[SPEAKER_12]: You speak and then it responds.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, now, I think about brain training and you have the blue and, you know, some of those things, but what would be... It's so rudimentary, like actual practical where you could say, you know, you cast a spell in a fantasy game and they do it, you know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Go in and cast magic missiles!
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, really fully developed voice recognition software.
[SPEAKER_13]: Improved voice... Okay, I can go with that.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'll go next.
[SPEAKER_13]: And my number three answer I'm going to use tonight is open app development like the iPhone that they should open up because they're going to have this DSI downloadable stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think they should open it up.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think open app development is going to be my number three answer that anybody should be able to make a DS game.
[SPEAKER_13]: because the community, I think, could come up with some good stuff and maybe like a message board.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I think it's been very good for the iPhone.
[SPEAKER_13]: So if we're going to make that comparison, then there you go.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, you're number three.
[SPEAKER_00]: Me.
[SPEAKER_00]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: I honestly think having your me being able to travel, you know, from your Wii to your DSi to go visit other people's memes, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Technically, they can already do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, they're going to have support for it, but yeah, they should.
[SPEAKER_07]: Have it integrated into the actual OS of the system.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I think it's kind of forgotten that you can put those things on the Wiimote, too, because there's not a lot of practical use for it.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_07]: I've brought mine over to your house before that way.
[SPEAKER_13]: I remember that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, so Mii integration, I guess we could say.
[SPEAKER_13]: Better use of the Miis on DS.
[SPEAKER_13]: I like that idea.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, Loki.
[SPEAKER_13]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what would be kind of cool?
[SPEAKER_02]: Bluetooth.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just think of it as you will.
[SPEAKER_02]: You could use your Wii Remote for motion sensitive games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not necessarily obviously waggling your Wii Remote around, but like racing games or something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: You could use it for wireless headsets.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Communication with other devices.
[SPEAKER_12]: The Doctor.
[SPEAKER_12]: What's your number two?
[SPEAKER_12]: The tilt feature, the motion feature like the iPhone has.
[SPEAKER_13]: Are you guys wanting to turn the DSi into an iPhone?
[SPEAKER_13]: What's going on here?
[SPEAKER_13]: I guess I did one too.
[SPEAKER_13]: What do you think the tilt feature would add to the DSi?
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, gimmicks, but it seems like that would not have been a useless feature like the camera.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, my number two answer I'm going to say is...
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, I'm going to give the first smart-ass answer of the night.
[SPEAKER_13]: A Virtual Boy slot would have been something too.
[SPEAKER_13]: Since they're going to get rid of the Game Boy Advance slot, give me a Virtual Boy slot to give me a use for those games that are just collecting dust from the great red headache machine of death.
[SPEAKER_13]: So a Virtual Boy slot.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, your number two pick for feature that you most would want to see in the DSi that would have gotten you to buy one.
[SPEAKER_00]: TV Tuner.
[SPEAKER_13]: Ooh, I like, I like that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, TV tuner.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, if the freaking Turbo Express, the handheld TurboGrafx could have a TV tuner.
[SPEAKER_07]: And NEC didn't really, well, they kind of did.
[SPEAKER_00]: But anyway, why can't, yeah, the Lynx had one too.
[SPEAKER_00]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_00]: Why the heck not?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, I'll tell you why not.
[SPEAKER_00]: The Nomad.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because they're getting rid of analog TV signals soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Doesn't matter, have a digital TV tuner.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's impossible.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_13]: Unpossible.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_13]: Now we're getting to the number one answers.
[SPEAKER_13]: The number one feature you want to see in the DSi that would get you to buy the system right now.
[SPEAKER_13]: Loki, what is your number one answer?
[SPEAKER_02]: My number one answer is... There's nothing they can do.
[SPEAKER_02]: Honestly, they would have to... It's made out of bacon.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: I have no number one answer.
[SPEAKER_02]: Made out of bacon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or at least scratch and sniff bacon smell.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: How about that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Made out of bacon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bacon integration.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, I like made out of bacon.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, the DSI would sell, you would have bought one today and it was made out of bacon.
[SPEAKER_13]: The Doctor, your number one answer for what would have got you to buy the DSi today.
[SPEAKER_12]: Since I guess the theme is crazy stuff now.
[SPEAKER_12]: Like, you know, you can interact with it.
[SPEAKER_12]: It can interact with you back.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, like, an energy hand will come out and, like, slap you in the face.
[SPEAKER_12]: Is that your real answer?
[SPEAKER_12]: That is.
[SPEAKER_12]: And my final answer.
[SPEAKER_12]: Energy hands.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know, there's so many apps for that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Slap in the face.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_12]: Helps with self-trouser fornication.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hands made out of pure energy.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, my number one answer... It's a little bit long, but this is a true answer, by the way.
[SPEAKER_13]: This is not a smart-ass answer.
[SPEAKER_13]: My number one answer for the thing that would have most got me to buy a DSi today... Virtual console games on my goddamn DS, you money-sucking pieces of shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: My runner-up answer would have been a multi-touch touchscreen, but, you know... Like anything with a multi-touch touchscreen.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're not just limiting it to the iPhone.
[SPEAKER_00]: Did you molest it some more?
[SPEAKER_13]: All right, enough about you.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's talk about me and my answer some more.
[SPEAKER_13]: Virtual console games on my goddamn DS, you money-sucking pieces of shit.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think that speaks for itself.
[SPEAKER_13]: I bought these games for five damn dollars.
[SPEAKER_13]: I ought to have the right to download it.
[SPEAKER_13]: PS3 does it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Why can't Nintendo do it?
[SPEAKER_13]: Why can't you do it?
[SPEAKER_13]: You got rid of the Advance slot, so don't give me that argument you released on the Game Boy Advance, because now I can't play them anymore.
[SPEAKER_13]: So he does when Nintendo...
[SPEAKER_13]: Roll.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, DarkSakura, your number one answer.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mine would be to take PictoChat and make it truly networking as in you can hop on the Wi-Fi and you don't have to be just in the general vicinity of somebody else with one.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can draw penises on full-blown PNOR on people's DSIs in Malaysia.
[SPEAKER_12]: Or an enhancement of that, it could be like there's a camera on it, like video chat.
[SPEAKER_12]: Can I just say PictoChat across the internets?
[SPEAKER_07]: That would be cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, there you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Although my bullshit answer could either be a jelly belly dispenser or gay porn.
[SPEAKER_11]: Gay porn, alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Gay porn always sells.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's see what the chatroom had to say, some answers there.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's see, we had a DDR pad.
[SPEAKER_13]: was one answer, Airport Tuner, Shortwave Tuner, Legend of Zelda Ghost Camera, a Vibrator, I think I saw different forms of Vibrator, a Trans Vibrator was one that came up as well.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's see, what do we have as well?
[SPEAKER_13]: LaserCat's DSi game at launch would have made it better.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's from S2100, Matt.
[SPEAKER_13]: Virtual Handheld from Actdeft.
[SPEAKER_13]: Kind of like my answer.
[SPEAKER_13]: How about a fart sound maker or a swear button from Dark Knight?
[SPEAKER_13]: All right, there you go.
[SPEAKER_13]: Some of the answers we have from chat.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, they did make a DDR pad for the Game Boy back in the day.
[SPEAKER_13]: Way back in the day.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have one.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because they brought out the Super MIDI version of the DDR.
[SPEAKER_13]: They were kind of shit.
[SPEAKER_07]: They were funny.
[SPEAKER_12]: Was it for your fingers, though?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: Actdeft wins a RuPaul game for the DSiWare.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, here's the list so far, but now we're going to get to the elimination round.
[SPEAKER_13]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_13]: DSiMessageBoard, voice recognition software, open app development, Miis, Bluetooth integration, tilt feature like the iPhone, virtual voice slot, TV tuner, made out of bacon, energy hands, virtual console games on my goddamn DS, you money-sucking pieces of shit, and PictoChat across the internets.
[SPEAKER_13]: Loki, which one of these is not worthy of the list?
[SPEAKER_13]: Uh... Energy Hands, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_13]: Energy Hands.
[SPEAKER_13]: Maybe just a little too soon for Energy Hands.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, The Doctor.
[SPEAKER_13]: Which one of these is not worthy of the list?
[SPEAKER_13]: The Virtual Boy Slot.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, you bastard.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, Virtual Boy Slot comes off the list.
[SPEAKER_13]: Um, I am going to say, I have to be honest, the one I've got to take out is voice recognition software.
[SPEAKER_13]: Sorry, doctor, that's not a retaliation thing, but I just think that would be whored to the extreme and would just make the thing crap.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura is going to be the last one to eliminate.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, which one of these is not worthy of the list?
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_13]: Check it out.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I like bacon, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bacon.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, seriously.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_07]: Every Friday after typography class, now I have to go have bacon because bacon is meat candy.
[SPEAKER_13]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: So here we go.
[SPEAKER_13]: Now here's the list you guys will vote on.
[SPEAKER_13]: DSI Message Board, Open App Development, Mies, Bluetooth Integration, TV Tuner, Made Out of Bacon, Virtual Console Games on my goddamn DS, you money-sucking pieces of shit.
[SPEAKER_13]: and Pictochats across the internet.
[SPEAKER_13]: Place vote now.
[SPEAKER_13]: Send a private message with your number one and number two answer.
[SPEAKER_13]: Make sure both are labeled or I will assume the first is your number one.
[SPEAKER_13]: Send those over private message to Rob Roberts in chat room.
[SPEAKER_13]: And if you don't know how to do that, ask somebody or maybe somebody will mention it in chat how to do that right now.
[SPEAKER_13]: Place those votes within the next 120 seconds you have to vote.
[SPEAKER_13]: And we will tally it up and reveal for you who won
[SPEAKER_13]: A little later on in the show.
[SPEAKER_13]: For now, while those votes are coming in, let's take a trip over to our Twitter.
[SPEAKER_13]: And we're actually going to look at... We put a call out on Twitter today saying, you know, we're a little short on stories this week.
[SPEAKER_13]: What do you guys want to see us talk about?
[SPEAKER_13]: And we put the call out on Twitter.
[SPEAKER_13]: And we did get some replies, some various tweets in our response here.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I wanted to read some of those for you guys right now.
[SPEAKER_13]: Although right now I'm seeing a lot of gaming weeks.
[SPEAKER_13]: Um...
[SPEAKER_13]: DSI, is it worth the upgrade?
[SPEAKER_13]: Can I get a side of handheld console wars as well, please?
[SPEAKER_13]: there hasn't been a lot of PSP bashing tonight I don't know is there is is is the DSI I mean okay let me back up the PSP is kind of a little bit behind in the console wars right now but the DSI is kind of out there to increase the lead so to speak I know what we could talk about did you hear about that news story where Sony apparently put out a press release saying that basically saying the DSI was a kiddie system and then touted that it had a Miley Cyrus game in the exact same press release did you hear about that
[SPEAKER_02]: DS, PSP
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, you know, I gotta disagree with that a little.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't like all these uber-violent, uber-serious games.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm like, I fall asleep watching COD.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_12]: So I like the more down-to-earth or the more silly games myself.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, but here's the thing, and I still feel this way, and you know, maybe, okay, the PSP is still like games and more.
[SPEAKER_13]: It might not be the best system at games, even though it still has, you know, it does have Dissida, it does have some games that are pretty awesome, but the PSP is still, you know, for that college kid.
[SPEAKER_13]: This is like the great college system, because you've got your MP3 player, you've got your little internet browser you can use at Starbucks, you've got your gaming system, you know, it's all right there.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I think the DSi was trying to
[SPEAKER_13]: Compete with that a little bit, but it didn't work because, you know, where's the internet?
[SPEAKER_13]: Where is the MP3 player built in?
[SPEAKER_13]: None of that is here.
[SPEAKER_13]: So I still think the PSP excels at being more than a gaming, but if all you want is handheld games, I think the DS still wins.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then also the DSi, though, I mean, their music player's kind of crap because it's only the AAC format or whatever, which I understand, you know, iTunes and stuff, that's fine, but really I think it should have been MP3.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, come on, man, give it the times.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: And then also, you know, there's the internet browser, which apparently is not very good anyways.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's like, ugh, you know, okay, whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then, you know, what, the photo manipulation stuff?
[SPEAKER_02]: Really?
[SPEAKER_02]: Is that what you're going to do?
[SPEAKER_02]: A photo manipulation?
[SPEAKER_02]: Is that really that important?
[SPEAKER_02]: Are we going to, like, throw those around the internet now and take pictures and manipulate them with silly faces like you couldn't do that in Microsoft Paint or something?
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's got potential, but they're never going to utilize it, and that's sad.
[SPEAKER_13]: I like Acidic Vampire's response in chat.
[SPEAKER_13]: In the PSP's defense, the games look saucier.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like that word, saucier.
[SPEAKER_02]: They could have had MP3 support if Nintendo had paid a license, just like the Wii could have played DVDs if they had paid the license for the use of DVD codecs.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what's more important than Nintendo?
[SPEAKER_02]: Money in their pocket.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_02]: So much for that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I guess the consumer loses because Nintendo needs to make a buck.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, but nobody uses their consoles to play movies anymore, I don't think, anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: I use my consoles to play movies all the time.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's my primary DVD player.
[SPEAKER_02]: PlayStation 3 is my primary movie player.
[SPEAKER_07]: We do use it for Blu-ray and our HD DVD player is our Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: and whatever I happen to have hooked up at the time.
[SPEAKER_02]: It would be kind of cool to have a DVD player for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't be surprised if that's not something that they're going to start selling too.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's just... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: And yeah, I know most people already have DVD players, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: People also have TVs too, but yet still buy tons of TVs out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: And who cares?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's another DVD player.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the point.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Wii may be in the kids' room or something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, boom!
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a DVD player in the kids' room.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Minor cost for another bullet point.
[SPEAKER_13]: So whatever.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm still trying to tally the votes, so let's move on to another topic here.
[SPEAKER_13]: Crows asked on Twitter, maybe talk about some April Fool's jokes that spread on the internet that were actually entertaining.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't like April Fool's Day at all, although I think, you know, for hating April Fool's Day, I think Dark Tetsuya did a pretty funny one on our site where he did for I Heart that song, he did Let Them Move from DD, which is like a total throwback to the old school days of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, like, I like dumb shit like that.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: Loki, DarkSakura, did you guys see anything funny on the internet?
[SPEAKER_13]: I kind of turn off the internet on April Fool's Day.
[SPEAKER_02]: This year, a lot of the sites that would normally do April Fool's jokes didn't.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're just like, I'm too busy with stuff, so forget it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically, I saw a few in the hacking communities.
[SPEAKER_02]: People were like, oh yeah, look, we're releasing a tool to hack the PSP-3000 or a new one to hack the Wii or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just, whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Those we kind of figured were fake.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm trying to think here.
[SPEAKER_02]: What are some of the other April Fool's jokes that were just very obvious?
[SPEAKER_02]: The new Metal Gear Solid game.
[SPEAKER_02]: They announced what the new character was going to be, which is kind of retarded.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm trying to think here.
[SPEAKER_02]: They were kind of lame.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it was, you know, the World of Warcraft thing that they did was kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then there was another one with IGN, you know, trying to do this Wii Extend or Wii Expand or something like that, which was supposed to be download content for, like, Wii games.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the first one was Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_02]: Brawl Extreme, where they were going to have, like, blood and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it just looked so fake and...
[SPEAKER_02]: They had Mario getting decapitated and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, despite all the shit we give the mainstream press sometimes on this show and all that stuff, I think their Zelda trailer will never be topped.
[SPEAKER_13]: That was a pretty fucking amazing April Fool's prank.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was great.
[SPEAKER_13]: Not for the fact that I don't think anyone really fell for it, but just like, god damn, they went all out with that shit that year.
[SPEAKER_13]: And Doctor, you're a big Zelda fanboy.
[SPEAKER_13]: Did you not get a huge boner, April's Fools or not, at that trailer?
[SPEAKER_12]: No, and obviously it was fake, but yeah, I mean, if you've ever seen the fan-made Zelda movies, I mean, this was like a bazillion, the production value was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_02]: And sadly enough, it will never come to fruition, which is, you know, I don't think it would cost that much, you know, for something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, this wasn't even an April Fool's thing, but have you seen, there's a trailer for a movie that someone made, a short movie, called Turbo, which is a little bit of a cross between, like, Street Fighter and Tron and, you know, the Karate Kid.
[SPEAKER_02]: And actually, it looks pretty cool, and that's also made, you know, with a really low budget and stuff, so, you know, nowadays, you can do pretty amazing stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hell, I mean, look at that, what is it, the Half-Life, um...
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: And then one other thing on Twitter I thought was pretty interesting.
[SPEAKER_13]: And, you know, our good friend Marin, or Tiara, whatever you want to say, kind of likes to pimp her own stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: But I liked it.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was actually a piece that she wrote on her own blog, which I've jokingly referred to as the Giggling Girls blog.
[SPEAKER_13]: But, no, it's what, AvengersTower.com?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_13]: I can't remember if it's Avenger Tower or Avengers Tower.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's Avengers Tower.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's Avengers Tower.
[SPEAKER_13]: Like the old...
[SPEAKER_00]: The Avengers Tower and the comic books
[SPEAKER_13]: Extra Microphones
[SPEAKER_13]: So maybe you could have more than one person singing?
[SPEAKER_13]: You'd have two people singing at once?
[SPEAKER_02]: To kind of go with the keyboard thing, their site, I don't know if it's viral or what, but their actual The Beatles site, they've been having instruments slowly being added to their studio recording room, and one of the instruments was a keyboard.
[SPEAKER_13]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_13]: Rumor number three, drums with cymbals, that maybe they're actually going to put actual cymbals or whatever on the drum kit for the rock band.
[SPEAKER_02]: well they did say that later on it's potential that they can have like say Rock Band 3 or something like that where the cymbals would be their own notes which is kind of cool another rumor two guitars instead of one
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's more of that is what's going to be why it's more expensive.
[SPEAKER_02]: The second guitar, I think, is going to be in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because they're going to model the bass.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're probably going to have an actual bass and then a guitar.
[SPEAKER_13]: And the last rumor, just milking the damn cash cow.
[SPEAKER_13]: Milking the damn cash cow.
[SPEAKER_13]: I really hope it's the keyboard one, but I think it's going to be one of their bass guitars with the regular guitar.
[SPEAKER_13]: Especially because you have the...
[SPEAKER_13]: And she goes into talking about the whole Hoffner violin bass, which, you know, it seems likely that, you know, with the Beatles and everything, they would have like a special Beatles bass.
[SPEAKER_13]: That seems likely.
[SPEAKER_13]: Some folks in chat are saying, you know, what about like a strobe light?
[SPEAKER_13]: You can already buy that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, no, they're talking about Nine Inch Nails.
[SPEAKER_13]: I guess their April Fool's joke or something like that has something to do with... Oh, it was the album.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, that Nine Inch Nails was putting out a new album that was produced by Timbaland called Strobelight.
[SPEAKER_13]: That was a good April Fool's joke that was out on the internet.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, let's get into the listless results.
[SPEAKER_13]: So we can get to your calls, last minute stories, and the end of the show pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_13]: Believe it or not, for being a slower news week, we sure seem to fill a couple of hours and then some here on the show.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, here are your top three tonight, the definitive list as you guys in chat have voted for the feature that they should have put on the DSi that would have made me buy one today.
[SPEAKER_13]: Number three, open app development, just like the iPhone, let anybody make an app, there you go, open app development.
[SPEAKER_13]: Number two feature that would have got me to buy a DSi today, made out of bacon, made out of bacon was the number two feature, there you go.
[SPEAKER_13]: Where there's bacon, there's profit.
[SPEAKER_13]: And the number one feature that would have gotten people to buy the DSi today?
[SPEAKER_13]: Virtual console games on my goddamn DS, you money-sucking pieces of shit.
[SPEAKER_13]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_13]: Your number one answer on the list.
[SPEAKER_13]: Lists.
[SPEAKER_13]: Segment here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_13]: Lots of votes spread around amongst all the choices, though.
[SPEAKER_13]: Everybody got a little love, but I think those three struck a particular nerve.
[SPEAKER_13]: People just love their bacon and virtual console.
[SPEAKER_13]: And open app development.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_13]: Actdeft makes a good point.
[SPEAKER_13]: If anybody can make an app, you know who will make his game a reality.
[SPEAKER_13]: That individual who has a game named after himself.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you know whose game sucks balls, because I've actually played the demo, and it
[SPEAKER_02]: It's as crappy as it looks.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't care if it's one person developing it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not good.
[SPEAKER_02]: If I paid retail for that, I'd have to kick myself in the junk.
[SPEAKER_13]: BlackWolf asks in chat, what if Bobby BlackWolf made a game, would you talk about it if I called it Bobby's Game?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes, I would talk about it every week.
[SPEAKER_13]: Every week, Bobby.
[SPEAKER_13]: Every week.
[SPEAKER_13]: As long as it didn't suck.
[SPEAKER_13]: In fact, I think you should beat him to the market because I would laugh my ass off at that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do it now.
[SPEAKER_12]: But only if the theme song to the game is la la la la la la la la Bobby's World.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_13]: Also, before we get to the Skype line and so forth, we have one segment we always do here on the show that we don't want to miss, but we just haven't had any really angsty stories.
[SPEAKER_13]: But perhaps the invoking of said name of said band individual from said show and just even thinking about his game should invoke anger and rage in a certain segment we do here every week on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: FU's of the week
[SPEAKER_13]: F you to this glass of wine I'm drinking for being so yummy and making me a little tipsy during the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's freaking delicious.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's a Moscato.
[SPEAKER_13]: Moscato.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's delicious.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's a sweet wine.
[SPEAKER_13]: It tastes like candy.
[SPEAKER_13]: It tastes like champagne without the bubbles, as my friend put it.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's delish.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hey there, Doctor!
[SPEAKER_13]: Do you have any FUs of the week, even though Loki's holding the mic?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, even though this is a little old news, I had a lady confirm me about this the other day.
[SPEAKER_12]: Fuck you to anyone who doesn't support gay marriage.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because you are fucking assholes.
[SPEAKER_13]: Props to Iowa, though.
[SPEAKER_13]: Props to Iowa.
[SPEAKER_13]: of all places props to them although I have heard those comparisons about well isn't Iowa just doing what California did like five years ago or however long ago it was like three years ago which ended up getting turned around by Prop 8 anyway maybe but I hear it's harder to pass a constitutional amendment in that state so if you live in Iowa please don't screw this up please don't screw this up
[SPEAKER_13]: But right now, hey, I think some person in Iowa is probably really concerned.
[SPEAKER_13]: I actually read about this somewhere, that they are concerned, the conservative moral majority, let's say, in Iowa, that there's just going to be this outbreak of gayness throughout the state.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's going to become a gay mecca.
[SPEAKER_13]: There's just going to be a sodomy outbreak within the state of Iowa because of this law passing.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_13]: Why is that a bad thing?
[SPEAKER_13]: Like, maybe people can come clean the place up.
[SPEAKER_13]: Throw a party in Des Moines that people want to come to.
[SPEAKER_13]: And make it fierce.
[SPEAKER_13]: Quick, when I say Des Moines, what do you think of?
[SPEAKER_13]: My crappy customer.
[SPEAKER_13]: Silent S. Corn.
[SPEAKER_13]: There's not a lot else I can think of.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, anyway.
[SPEAKER_13]: ZakuPilot256 in chat says, If gay people want to ruin their life with marriage, let them.
[SPEAKER_13]: Amen to that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_07]: Didn't I say it in my little rant that I put in my blog?
[SPEAKER_07]: That everyone should have as much right to mess it up like anyone else?
[SPEAKER_13]: Just like Britney Spears.
[SPEAKER_13]: We have every right to fuck it up like Britney Spears did.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, look, I don't want to turn this into a political show, but obviously it's an issue important to myself and the doctor.
[SPEAKER_13]: So yay, Iowa.
[SPEAKER_13]: F you, everybody else.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, Loki, please, your FU of the week.
[SPEAKER_02]: My FU of the week goes to some of my airsoft guns not working correctly, so... Did your airsoft thing, did you get to have that?
[SPEAKER_13]: Because I saw, like, multiple please on live, and we were like, pretty please, come play airsoft with me.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I felt bad, I wanted to go, but I had plans.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, we had, like, three people, including myself, and that's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it was alright, we had fun with the small group.
[SPEAKER_02]: I promise I will go airsoft with you in a future week.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's fine, I just, I have...
[SPEAKER_02]: Actdeft says, Bad Loki, what will the wife say?
[SPEAKER_02]: She doesn't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: And thankfully she doesn't listen to this show.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Damn.
[SPEAKER_13]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's open up the Skype line if we can here.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm going to do not disturb.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let me open it up there.
[SPEAKER_13]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: If you want to give us a call and interact with us, talk about anything we've brought up on the show tonight, or as long as it's gaming related, we'll talk about anything pretty much.
[SPEAKER_13]: So go ahead and call us right now.
[SPEAKER_13]: 1-877-GAME-OLR, username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: Do we have any last minute stories while we wait for these calls to come in?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, sorry, I'm fighting a giant slug thing.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, actually, you're getting saved.
[SPEAKER_13]: We've got a call right now.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hi, you are on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_10]: This is DSMaster26.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hey, DSMaster26, what is on your mind?
[SPEAKER_13]: Hey, hey, hey, wait, I'm going to ask you.
[SPEAKER_13]: How about the DSI?
[SPEAKER_10]: Seriously, I've seen, actually, one of my friends has one.
[SPEAKER_10]: She gets imports from Japan a whole bunch of times.
[SPEAKER_10]: PSP vs. DSi
[SPEAKER_13]: That's like on the Nintendo Wii.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's very, very slow.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, same thing with the DSi, but slower.
[SPEAKER_10]: And seriously, the music player is crap.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, besides, I already got that feature with my R4 card.
[SPEAKER_13]: Wait, didn't they actually put a music player in the DSi?
[SPEAKER_13]: I didn't even realize that was there.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's built in now?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, but you use your SD card and it always takes AAC.
[SPEAKER_13]: But yeah, I already have a PSP or more importantly, you know, an iPod and iPhone that will do it as well.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, I do use my PSP pretty much every day.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, same here.
[SPEAKER_10]: I use my PSP, like, but R4 does do videos, as I found out.
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually, that's the reason why I called in.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm giving a review on Silent Hill, which I just saw last night.
[SPEAKER_10]: The movie?
[SPEAKER_10]: Freaking awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_13]: Isn't it amazing?
[SPEAKER_13]: You're only about three years late, but go ahead.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm just messing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow, it came out three years ago?
[SPEAKER_13]: It was a while ago.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm just messing with you.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't remember when, but it was a while ago.
[SPEAKER_13]: What did you think?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, anyways, out of all the movie, out of the game movies I've seen, this is like probably the best ever.
[SPEAKER_10]: And plus on the fact you're seeing witch burnings and then the massive blood splatter in the awesome epic Pyramid Head, which I'm thinking of being for Halloween.
[SPEAKER_10]: Awesome flick.
[SPEAKER_13]: Now you know why we fangasm over Pyramid Head all the time on this show.
[SPEAKER_13]: He has sex.
[SPEAKER_13]: He just, he really is.
[SPEAKER_07]: And he has a lot of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: With the nurses.
[SPEAKER_10]: And plus not to mention, if you guys ever... Okay, have any of you played the DDR Extreme for the US version on the PS2?
[SPEAKER_13]: On the PS2, yes.
[SPEAKER_13]: Extreme 1, yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, the ending song, the Silent Hill for the ending credits, very reminiscent to the soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think it's like the last song you'll lock in Extreme, but it was very similar to me.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, I couldn't remember the first few times until the chorus came in.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm like...
[SPEAKER_10]: No, it was...
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, have you ever noticed there's a pump-it-up game for the PSP?
[SPEAKER_10]: I had heard there was a Pump It Up game on PSP.
[SPEAKER_10]: I found out on PlayAsia, and I'm like, what the heck?
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, I can understand DDR on this thing, but not Pump It Up, because it takes five icons.
[SPEAKER_10]: And we got the four external sort of square, I don't know what I'm supposed to use.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, what about the shoulder buttons?
[SPEAKER_13]: I just assumed it was the shoulder button.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, if you're going to play DDR on a handheld, Pump It Up makes sense to me.
[SPEAKER_13]: DJ Max DJ Max
[SPEAKER_13]: I would love that, but unfortunately, I think because of how Beatmania 2 did, or I'm sorry, not Beatmania 2, Beatmania on the PS2 did, I don't think they're in any hurry to put out a new Beatmania game.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't think it sold well enough for them.
[SPEAKER_13]: I had heard it exceeded expectations, but I could have always heard wrong.
[SPEAKER_13]: because they never did do a second one if it sold that well they would have done a second one I mean as far as I know DDR Universe 2 did not sell that great compared to older DDR titles but they still made a 3 and you know it wasn't just a reskinned version of the other ones because 2 was kind of just a reskinned Universe 1
[SPEAKER_10]: Just thinking of DDR, haven't you noticed there hasn't been a single one out for the PS3?
[SPEAKER_10]: They're still rehashing on the PS2.
[SPEAKER_13]: It is interesting there hasn't been one on the PS3, and I'm wondering if that's not going to be one of the things Konami pulls out of their hat at E3 this year, because you're right.
[SPEAKER_13]: The PS3 is one of those platforms that hasn't seen a DDR game on it yet.
[SPEAKER_13]: Maybe that will be where we start to see the download content and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_13]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: At the same time, I'm not going to hold my breath.
[SPEAKER_10]: Beatmania Guitar Hero Control 5 Keys Scratches the Strum Bar
[SPEAKER_10]: What do you think of it?
[SPEAKER_10]: I've actually bought the Guitar Hero DS, and, you know, it's pretty darn interesting, pretty good for what it is.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was surprised at the graphics for it, for a DS game, for Guitar Hero-wise, and the sound quality was pretty darn good.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think the style that they're going with the PSP version of Rock Band, though, is pretty darn interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: You'd think they would try to mod, like, redo the guitar grip, and then try to do some little quirky little drum sets.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, that you plug on top and then you just hit with your fingers.
[SPEAKER_10]: I didn't think that'd be kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, but at the same time, I like the idea that they're just doing like an amplitude type game that you're not going to need any of these stupid peripherals for.
[SPEAKER_13]: I kind of like that idea.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, but that's also the same control scheme for DJ Max on the PSP, which I kind of suck at.
[SPEAKER_10]: I try it with the two-hand configuration like you would for Beatmania, and I still suck.
[SPEAKER_10]: I can't do it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, by the way, one more thing before I go.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hopefully EA and the whole gaming industry of America does not call for a bailout from Barack Obama.
[SPEAKER_13]: That would suck.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do they need one?
[SPEAKER_13]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_13]: Would they be eligible?
[SPEAKER_13]: Probably midway.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, you seem like you're dying to comment on the bailout message.
[SPEAKER_13]: No.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are you guys talking about the... I think I was just saying, Am I seeing a glitch in Ninja Blade here?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because the monster has no health left and I keep hitting it and it's not dying.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, you just suck.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, let's go to the call.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_00]: It did the Mega Man 3 trick.
[SPEAKER_13]: Uh-oh, did it cut off?
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay, whoever... I have to explain this trick.
[SPEAKER_13]: What?
[SPEAKER_13]: Hurry, because we've got a call on the line.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay, we'll call her going.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_13]: Hey, it's DJ Tyrant.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hey, DJ Tyrant.
[SPEAKER_13]: I haven't heard you on the show in a long time.
[SPEAKER_13]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, not much.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm trying out the Skype for iPhone app.
[SPEAKER_05]: It seems to work pretty well.
[SPEAKER_13]: Whoa, you're calling us from iPhone right now?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: Wow, not too shabby.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: I forgot that that's available now.
[SPEAKER_13]: So those of you with iPhones, you can Skype us during the show on your iPhones.
[SPEAKER_13]: Thank you for reminding us of that.
[SPEAKER_13]: I have to check that out.
[SPEAKER_05]: It only works on Wi-Fi, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember that.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_13]: But still, your regular Skype will only work with an internet connection, too.
[SPEAKER_13]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_13]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, just, I know it's all the talk of today, but DSi, I really enjoy mine personally, um, I don't know, I think it's a pretty good upgrade, I got to play it last week, um, at an event I got invited to, and I don't know, I think it's pretty, a pretty good upgrade, but I can see, it's not for everyone, definitely, so.
[SPEAKER_13]: What about it makes it such a great upgrade?
[SPEAKER_05]: I really like the screens.
[SPEAKER_05]: The controls are much better.
[SPEAKER_05]: The D-pad and the buttons just in general feel a lot better and more sturdy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because the D-pad was really floaty on the Lite, I thought.
[SPEAKER_13]: Sometimes I keep forgetting this is actually the third DS now we've gotten between DS Fat and DS Lite.
[SPEAKER_13]: I sometimes forget that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyhow, do you still work in games retail?
[SPEAKER_13]: No, I don't.
[SPEAKER_13]: I haven't heard too much.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I haven't really heard anything.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, sorry.
[SPEAKER_13]: My bad for asking.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, no worries.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, okay, well, so you're more of a fan of the DSi then.
[SPEAKER_13]: Is there anything that you're looking forward to?
[SPEAKER_13]: Like, we've seen some announcements recently of the Zelda Spirit Tracks and so on.
[SPEAKER_13]: What are you looking forward to from Nintendo on DS?
[SPEAKER_05]: Definitely the Zelda game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm kind of, I honestly am looking forward to these new play control games because I missed out on them on the GameCube, so...
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm kind of looking forward to them, and they're not too badly priced either, which is a good thing.
[SPEAKER_13]: Cheap is good.
[SPEAKER_13]: You're right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Cheap is always a good thing.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't mind that.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, of course, the DSiWare.
[SPEAKER_05]: I really hope that that takes off like the App Store has on the iPhone.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know it's not open, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's really going to, I think, hurt it in the long run, though.
[SPEAKER_13]: I tend to agree, but at the same time, it is a double-edged sword, and I could see the other side of the argument where, well, look at all the shit that's on the iPhone store, because there's some real crap apps on the iPhone.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's so hard to comb through there and find some decent games sometimes.
[SPEAKER_13]: And you think there's supposed to be some quality control out there, but it's not much.
[SPEAKER_13]: It is not much.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: So I guess maybe by closing it off, Nintendo will release quote-unquote quality apps on the DSi, but at the same time, some of these games don't sound that quality.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, I guess that's true.
[SPEAKER_13]: Is there anything on WiiWare you enjoy?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if we really enjoy the Final Fantasy Crystal Chronicles.
[SPEAKER_05]: My Life as a King
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, but I agree with you that I really hope they have some sort of support like the PS3 and the PSP.
[SPEAKER_13]: I have a bad feeling.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm just dreaming with that.
[SPEAKER_13]: But you know it can be done.
[SPEAKER_13]: Look at the Nintendo channel that streams DS demos to your DS.
[SPEAKER_13]: It can be done.
[SPEAKER_13]: They just don't want to do it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Or they're leaving it in their hat to unveil at a later conference.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, that got me to buy Rhythm Heaven because they released a demo the day they gave it out at GDC.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I tried and I was like, well,
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for having me on.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't think of anything right now.
[SPEAKER_11]: Um, well, first of all, I'm... I'm burnt out on my 360, and second of all, I'm rejecting that, again, that, because, uh, for one month, because Operation Flashpoint, the new one's coming out, I think, next month.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, hold on, back up.
[SPEAKER_13]: Aren't you the same guy that was having the points problems earlier?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, so, obviously that's all fixed, and Nintendo, Xbox was very kind to you and all that.
[SPEAKER_13]: What did you end up running out and buying with those points?
[SPEAKER_11]: Um, I bought...
[SPEAKER_11]: Some rock band songs, my Call of Duty maps, and then with the extra points, I bought one rock band song and a pack of Burnout Cars that came with a Legendary Cars pack, which has like a DeLorean.
[SPEAKER_11]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_11]: Don't Stop Believin'
[SPEAKER_13]: No, I didn't buy that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Fail.
[SPEAKER_11]: I bought Trash Unreal from Against Me, Come On, Come On from the Von Bondys, The Joker from Steve Miller, Sick, Sick, Sick from Queens of the Stone Age, and My Curse from Killswitch Engage.
[SPEAKER_13]: Now look, those songs are all fine and dandy, but it needs more epic classic rock.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thing is, I would buy classic rock, but there's no Led Zeppelin.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's one of those bands that could put out their own game, like Aerosmith and Metallica.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't like Aerosmith.
[SPEAKER_11]: In fact, I hate Aerosmith.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm just saying, though, they were able to put out their own game.
[SPEAKER_13]: We can all argue about the success of that game.
[SPEAKER_13]: Leitzinger looks like a beat chick.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right, look.
[SPEAKER_13]: What did you really want to call in and talk about tonight?
[SPEAKER_11]: Operation Flashpoint.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think it's Dragon Rise or something.
[SPEAKER_11]: Remember the old Operation Flashpoint?
[SPEAKER_11]: Did you ever play it?
[SPEAKER_11]: What system was it on?
[SPEAKER_13]: It was a PC game.
[SPEAKER_13]: And it was Xbox, I think.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Xbox, I mean.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't recall this game, but I'm going to look up and see if I get screenshots.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm a very visual person, so sometimes that jogs my memory.
[SPEAKER_11]: I doubt it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a Call of Duty type of game.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's a military simulator, actually.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think, from what I remember, it was one shot, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_11]: You were dead.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, surprisingly enough, I think I saw this game once.
[SPEAKER_13]: So what about... Are they making a new one or what's up?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, sequel's coming out.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think it's next month.
[SPEAKER_11]: End of next month?
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm not sure though, but it's end of next month.
[SPEAKER_13]: Operation Flashpoint Dragon Rising.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, and it's just like...
[SPEAKER_11]: It's like what I like.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm this guy who wants these shooters that aren't, like, I'm tired of kind of seeing these really Call of Duty-esque Super Arcadia.
[SPEAKER_11]: I get shot, oh look, I sit in the corner, suck my thumb, I'm okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: I love this because it's like you get shot, you bleed out while moving around, or you're downed.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I love games because it has a medic system, that's simply it.
[SPEAKER_13]: You're a fan of shooters, and something that caught my eye this week was some of the screens from the new Wolfenstein game.
[SPEAKER_13]: What do you think of that?
[SPEAKER_13]: Is that a good... Oh, was that like... Jizz in my pants.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: I wasn't going to say that, but there you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it looks like crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shut up!
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, can you play a gag in his mouth?
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, well, he's playing a game.
[SPEAKER_13]: Wolfenstein Enemy Territory was so great, and it was free, too.
[SPEAKER_13]: What do you think of this new one?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but that's Enemy Territory.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shut up!
[SPEAKER_13]: Is it going to make everybody talk Wolfenstein again or what?
[SPEAKER_11]: It looks like an updated version of Wolfenstein.
[SPEAKER_11]: It looks like Wolfenstein to today's standards.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ironsight, sprinting, you know.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then all I notice is they better keep it class-based.
[SPEAKER_11]: They better keep it class-based and they better keep in that objective online campaign stuff that I saw in Enemy Territory where I will go to a school, go up to the principal, hit him in the balls, and then laugh.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then go home and make yourself a sandwich.
[SPEAKER_13]: Wolfstein 3D.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wolfstein 3D or Wolfstein 2D?
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, not that old school.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, Wolfstein 3D.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes and no.
[SPEAKER_11]: I do remember there being a robot, but maybe I just couldn't tell if it was Hitler because I was too stupid to know it was Hitler yet.
[SPEAKER_13]: Plus, you know what?
[SPEAKER_13]: He wasn't the boss in the shareware one that most people played.
[SPEAKER_13]: You have to have the full one to see that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hitler, Robot
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, well we're going to need you to call back when that game comes out because I need to hear it from a shooter fan because I don't follow a lot of the shooters so I need to know if the game is worth crossing over for.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, Deathwishing, any final thoughts before we let you go?
[SPEAKER_13]: I still play Street Fighter 4.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's still awesome.
[SPEAKER_13]: It is still awesome.
[SPEAKER_13]: Think they'll unveil any secret characters downloadable?
[SPEAKER_11]: I think they need to get that tournament mode out quicker.
[SPEAKER_13]: Deathwishing, we gotta let you go be careful when you threaten violence on the radio don't do it see you Deathwishing, take care buddy allegedly, bye hey Spazinator, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I just wanted to get your input on the whole Guitar Hero vs. Rock Band debate.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was wondering, compared to Rock Band, do you think they're kind of whoring out Guitar Hero a little bit?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, just a bit.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, they're whoring it out a lot, but at the same time, they can kind of get away with it right now because, you know, Best Buys and all these stores have sections upon sections dedicated to these games because they sell.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm not a big fan of the artist-based games.
[SPEAKER_13]: I am not a big fan of them.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't think they need the big fanfare they're getting.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, I was thinking more or less the same thing.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_04]: Although it's kind of a different genre altogether, you kind of saw the same thing with the Tony Hawk games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, they were releasing iteration after iteration with that series, and basically look what happened to that series.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, people kind of gave up on that series in favor of skates.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, you know, you can almost draw a few parallels between the Tony Hawk series and your Dark Hero almost.
[SPEAKER_13]: I will say this, though.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think Rock Band 2 has really succeeded with the store.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think it's succeeded in a place where Guitar Hero hasn't.
[SPEAKER_13]: Granted, Guitar Hero has released a lot of downloadable content and songs, but the place where Rock Band 2 has got them is that they've done it consistently.
[SPEAKER_13]: They've consistently put out a lot of songs on their store.
[SPEAKER_13]: Very few games can I say that six months after release, I'm still playing it at least once a week.
[SPEAKER_13]: Very few games can I say that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: In fact, I'm checking the rock band store constantly, and to some degree, I even do the same with Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_04]: And occasionally, I do see some songs at the Guitar Hero store that I do like, like Black Melon's No Rain and whatnot, but compared to rock bands, Guitar Hero really doesn't have a whole lot of
[SPEAKER_04]: that I would consider going out and getting compared to Rockbean, you know?
[SPEAKER_04]: But then again, that's just me.
[SPEAKER_04]: At least in my opinion, it seems like Rockbean has a better selection of music, though.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think rock band's got the better music too, but I do understand that Guitar Hero has to lean towards more guitar-driven songs, and sometimes, you know, that might not necessarily be the same stuff I listen to, but I like rock band because you do more band-based songs, you know, and some have guitar solos, but some have drum solos, some have vocal, like Don't Stop Believin', not a song really notable for its good, well, it does have a pretty bitchin' guitar solo.
[SPEAKER_13]: And it's really fucking hard on Rock Band Expert, by the way.
[SPEAKER_13]: I can't do that do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do part.
[SPEAKER_13]: But, like, most people don't stop believing for the vocals.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, you don't really get songs like that in Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, in Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, now, with me, one thing I noticed is, well, kind of like you, I can't really do the expert level stuff yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm still just getting started on the
[SPEAKER_04]: The medium level, because I'm kind of new to the whole music-y thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, you know, at least with Guitar Hero, since they're more or less emulating rock band sets, you know, you would think that even though the name is Guitar Hero, they would encompass some other varieties of music, you know, guitar-heavy stuff, you know?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, I don't know, though.
[SPEAKER_13]: Guitar Hero just... Guitar Hero feels like a bit of a scattered mess right now, and I hope if they're going to do another big Guitar Hero, what, five this year as their big game, I hope they find some focus.
[SPEAKER_13]: But Spaznir, we've got to let you go because we're running out of time.
[SPEAKER_13]: We want to end tonight so we can get to our afterbirth and so on.
[SPEAKER_13]: Do you have any quick final thoughts for the listeners tonight?
[SPEAKER_13]: uh, yeah, Final Fantasy, you know, Eleven Rules, Wild Sox, no, just kidding, just kidding, yeah, yeah, alright, get off the show, alright, see you Spazinator, thanks for the call, alright, have a good one, alright, bye, uh, by the way, I didn't mention during my gaming week this week, um, I actually went back to, um, World of Warcraft this week, because I'm a big fat addict, but I haven't been playing that much, look, we got one more call coming in, I want to take it, because I noticed it was a name I haven't heard from in a while, I want to let him on the show, hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio, who's this?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's Brad from PodCulture.
[SPEAKER_13]: I believe so, yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, then I'm going to have to go check that out.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, look, I know you didn't call to talk about Dollhouse, although you probably would anyway.
[SPEAKER_13]: What did you call in to talk about tonight, Brad?
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, I don't know if you'd mentioned it on the show before, but I've got an iPhone game that is just great.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hmm, what's that?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's Zombieville, USA.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm interested already.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's in Zombieville, USA?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just this little side-scroller cartoony shooting zombies game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Three simple controls, right, left, and you tap in the middle and you shoot.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is it a bloody game?
[SPEAKER_09]: Do you get decapitated zombies and all that fun stuff?
[SPEAKER_09]: You do, but it's kind of cartoony.
[SPEAKER_13]: I can deal with cartoon violence.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't like blood orgy.
[SPEAKER_13]: We already had the blood orgy discussion earlier in the show.
[SPEAKER_13]: Cartoony violence, especially with zombies, is okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, it's great.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's pretty much the same level over and over, but at the NH level, you can find cash, you upgrade your weapons.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is there a cost with said game?
[SPEAKER_13]: It's like two or three bucks.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's not that bad.
[SPEAKER_13]: Is there a demo or a movie or anything I can see online to get a taste for it?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm not 100% certain.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're not the developer.
[SPEAKER_13]: I shouldn't grill you on this stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm just curious how you found it.
[SPEAKER_13]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_13]: Check that out if you're interested in some zombie killing.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's good to hear about some good iPhone games, especially when we're talking about all the crap that's out there on the marketplace as well.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a good way to waste a lot of time.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes, I've wasted a lot of time with some of those games like WordFu and some of those iPhone games they have.
[SPEAKER_13]: Great time wasters, especially when I'm lying in bed but I don't want to go to sleep just yet.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'll reach over and grab my phone and play a couple games and it'll make me tired.
[SPEAKER_13]: Brad, we've got to let you go so we can wrap up.
[SPEAKER_13]: Any quick final thoughts for our listeners?
[SPEAKER_13]: Later on.
[SPEAKER_13]: Any final thoughts?
[SPEAKER_13]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_13]: We'll take care and have a good one, buddy.
[SPEAKER_13]: PodCulture
[SPEAKER_02]: Dirty Deeds Done Dirt Cheap Design Lessons Learned From Rock Band
[SPEAKER_02]: It's interesting though because he then released a PDF version or they released a PDF version of the session and all the slides are on there and it had an earlier version of the slide that had been omitted from the actual show and it reveals Lego Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_13]: I heard about this.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think Tigerclaw sent me a link to this, and I neglected to get to it in the Twitter part, but okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's interesting, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're also mentioning that the PSP rock band is on there as well, the Beatles rock band.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then there's a ton of Guitar Hero stuff, which really horned that stuff out.
[SPEAKER_02]: But they have Guitar Hero Modern Hits, Guitar Hero Metallica, Guitar Hero Van Halen, Guitar Hero Greatest Hits, Guitar Hero Arcade,
[SPEAKER_02]: Guitar Hero 5 and Guitar Hero Band Hero Guitar Hero Mobile 2 and Mystery Game
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, it's not exactly the way they go, but the way I look at it, it's a way to introduce Rock Band to younger kids, and you don't have to buy it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not like it's going to have songs in there that you're really probably going to need to buy, just that are only going to be available in LEGO Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whereas the Guitar Hero games, you can't port that shit over.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you buy Metallica, well, those Metallica songs are stuck on Metallica Games, so you can't really bring that over.
[SPEAKER_02]: which I think is where the developers kind of differ the most you know that's why I kind of respect Rock Band a little bit more because at least if you're going to put out you know a song or and they do do their track packs obviously though those are also optional since they're all available online it's an option you don't have to buy it but if you do buy it you can import it into your game and it all seamlessly works whereas Guitar Hero I gotta have a stack of discs
[SPEAKER_02]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, that's it for that story, at least.
[SPEAKER_02]: We also talked a little bit about Unreal Tournament 3 and how they had a mod for that to play in another video game, like Sonic the Hedgehog.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, Team Fortress 2, someone's made a map that's sort of like a Mario Kart track, which is kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, I mean, it's definitely not based on a real Mario Kart track.
[SPEAKER_02]: It just kind of has the graphics of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then, let's see here.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was another website, I guess, WeOperaSDK.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: They've released a tweeter, which is a Wii rapid blogging... I don't know if it's... I'm assuming it's like Twitter, but it's their own website that's formatted for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: Neat.
[SPEAKER_13]: Could have been that DSi message board, right?
[SPEAKER_13]: Could have been.
[SPEAKER_02]: And yeah, I guess they're going to have different things that they've incorporated to this.
[SPEAKER_02]: IRC style commands, smileys, possible integration with the WeMessage board, I guess email updates or something like that, web skinning, that sort of stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's neat.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, well we need to go around and get everybody's final thoughts before we wrap up the show tonight.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, you've been awfully quiet over there in the corner, poking away, talking to some of our AIM listeners and so on.
[SPEAKER_13]: Any final thoughts tonight?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yawn?
[SPEAKER_13]: Nap?
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't think you're going to nap.
[SPEAKER_13]: If you go and lie down, you're going to go to sleep.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm pretty tired.
[SPEAKER_00]: We spent three and a half hours in Ikea.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_07]: We went to eat and the intention was to spend two.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then we ran into some people that Becky knew because I went with Becky.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I sort of know one of them.
[SPEAKER_07]: But Swedish meatballs.
[SPEAKER_07]: And shiny.
[SPEAKER_13]: And Swedish meatballs.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, that's what I had.
[SPEAKER_07]: And there was shiny.
[SPEAKER_07]: There was so much shiny.
[SPEAKER_07]: I kept going, ooh, shiny.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ooh, shiny.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then staring at stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: So Ikea, evil.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: TheDokta, thank you so much for being here tonight and you definitely joined in on the conversation and we always appreciate having you here on the show.
[SPEAKER_13]: Please come back again.
[SPEAKER_13]: And thanks for participating in tonight's listless and all that fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: Do you have any final thoughts for listeners tonight?
[SPEAKER_13]: In honor of Rice Princess.
[SPEAKER_13]: Poop.
[SPEAKER_13]: Why is she here tonight?
[SPEAKER_13]: Shame on her.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: She didn't get my text.
[SPEAKER_13]: I didn't get your text either.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think you need to check your cell phone company.
[SPEAKER_13]: You need to call them and yell at them.
[SPEAKER_13]: My final thought is I need food.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm very hungry.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm dying of hunger pains.
[SPEAKER_13]: Loki, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't have anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: Boy, aren't you boring.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, I am.
[SPEAKER_02]: How was Ninja Blade?
[SPEAKER_02]: You've been playing that for like three hours now during the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's frustrating because you die pretty easy in it, so it's hard.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm playing on normal difficulty in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: The thing is, as you probably saw, there was a glitch, a level ending glitch where I couldn't defeat the boss because he ran out of life and I just sat there slashing at the dead corpse and it wouldn't trigger the event that I needed it to trigger.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I had to restart there, but...
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, it's alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's neat.
[SPEAKER_02]: They've got a lot of really over-the-top stuff going on, but it's a neat game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll probably finish it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, that's going to do it for another episode of Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: Thank you guys so much for tuning in to us and supporting independent podcasting and independent productions.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hey, if you like what you hear, please spread the word.
[SPEAKER_13]: Tell two friends you know about Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: Or hey, there's other ways you can do that too.
[SPEAKER_13]: You can post a kind review, a five-star review on iTunes.
[SPEAKER_13]: That helps sell the show and bumps up our ranking a little bit.
[SPEAKER_13]: Or mention us on your Twitter and Facebook and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm looking at Twitter right now and looking at some of the at OLR messages.
[SPEAKER_13]: DJ Ratchet says, I'm listening to OLR and laughing my butt off.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, I laughed a lot tonight too, so thank you.
[SPEAKER_13]: DJ Tyrant is pimping his appearance on the show tonight.
[SPEAKER_13]: We appreciate that.
[SPEAKER_13]: So thank you guys so much for all of that, supporting the show.
[SPEAKER_13]: You guys are awesome.
[SPEAKER_13]: We do it for you guys for free every week.
[SPEAKER_13]: And we'll do it all again next week.
[SPEAKER_13]: How's that sound?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's Easter.
[SPEAKER_13]: We're just tired.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, we'll see you in one week here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: Until then, I'm Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_13]: She's DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_13]: He's Loki.
[SPEAKER_13]: He's the Dokta.
[SPEAKER_13]: We're out of here.
[SPEAKER_13]: See you next week.
[SPEAKER_08]: See you next week!