And now for our feature presentation
[SPEAKER_19]: Orange Lounge Radio Live is now on the air.
[SPEAKER_19]: Orange Lounge Radio Live is a live talk program dedicated to all things Bomani and then some.
[SPEAKER_19]: Orange Lounge Radio may contain adult content, so you probably shouldn't let your children listen.
[SPEAKER_19]: If you do let your children listen to Orange Lounge Radio, they may turn into evil little demons from hell!
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh wait, most children already are evil little demons from hell.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now you see that evil will always triumph because good is dumb.
[SPEAKER_18]: Fast, drunk, and stupid is no way to go through life, sir.
[SPEAKER_18]: He jeopardizes my ability to effectively govern this student body.
[SPEAKER_16]: Well, makes you look like an ass is what he does, Ed.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hamburgers!
[SPEAKER_06]: The cornerstone of any nutritious practice.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was a huge one.
[SPEAKER_16]: Do you mind if I pick my new car for a ride?
[SPEAKER_06]: Catherine, the only thing you're going to be riding is me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have you seen Malcolm?
[SPEAKER_18]: Lena?
[SPEAKER_18]: Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to my underground lair.
[SPEAKER_18]: So it was you.
[SPEAKER_18]: I was going to expose you.
[SPEAKER_18]: I know.
[SPEAKER_18]: So I choose to expose myself.
[SPEAKER_18]: Please, there are ladies present.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be great if it wasn't for the fucking customers.
[SPEAKER_19]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh my god, I see a bloody stump!
[SPEAKER_19]: Any time, any place, baby.
[SPEAKER_19]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_12]: Ow, my foot!
[SPEAKER_12]: Why did I shoot myself in my foot?
[SPEAKER_19]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: We are live!
[SPEAKER_11]: And this is episode number 106 for this August the 8th of 2004.
[SPEAKER_11]: We are the internet's talk radio program dedicated to all things Vamani and then some.
[SPEAKER_11]: And with me, as always, are my awesome co-hosts.
[SPEAKER_11]: In this corner, the happiest bunny on the farm.
[SPEAKER_11]: Say hello to...
[SPEAKER_11]: Miss Jamie Summers, you know her better, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay, hooray for me.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hooray for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hooray for me.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm, I'm, and hooray for me.
[SPEAKER_02]: You put my meat on the camera, you whored out my meat.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes I did, I put your meat on our brand new webcam, available at www.
[SPEAKER_02]: And now my foot is on the webcam.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's all you'll ever see, is my foot.
[SPEAKER_11]: www.orangeloungeradio.com is our webcam address.
[SPEAKER_11]: Also with us tonight, say hello to our tech massa, Loki's.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, she's like Dr. Claw, but instead of the arm, it's a foot.
[SPEAKER_13]: But it's not the claw, it's just a hand.
[SPEAKER_13]: It just can't be Dr. Hand, because that's just stupid.
[SPEAKER_11]: Also with us tonight, we have very few special guests here, but they're plentiful in the talent they have to bring.
[SPEAKER_11]: We have somebody who has never been on the show before, and to be honest, I don't even know him that well.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I think he's hilarious in what I've seen of him at our local arcade.
[SPEAKER_11]: Say hello to Andrew.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, what's going on, everybody?
[SPEAKER_11]: I didn't know if he'd call you by your online, your real... No, I just got the right answer.
[SPEAKER_11]: Andrew.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, and Andrew is also well known for what?
[SPEAKER_11]: Locally here at Roseville.
[SPEAKER_14]: I dress up like a pirate at a golf land.
[SPEAKER_14]: If you've ever seen a pirate there, that would be amazing.
[SPEAKER_14]: Arr, he's a pirate.
[SPEAKER_13]: How ironic.
[SPEAKER_13]: I act like a pirate online.
[SPEAKER_11]: He dresses up as one.
[SPEAKER_11]: You act like one.
[SPEAKER_11]: You do the deeds.
[SPEAKER_11]: It all works.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, also with us tonight, we have somebody who frequents the show quite a bit.
[SPEAKER_11]: Do you recognize her from our chat room?
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm sure if you hang out there.
[SPEAKER_11]: Say hello to DDR Angel.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hello!
[SPEAKER_11]: How you doing today?
[SPEAKER_03]: Pretty good.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, I noticed we're wearing like matching shirts tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, what the hell is that?
[SPEAKER_03]: I wasn't even planning that.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're not technically twin shirts.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're close.
[SPEAKER_11]: We've got, she's got the one with the little piranha plant from Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_11]: It says, bite me.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then I have the Goomba that says, you lose.
[SPEAKER_11]: So it's like we're twins.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll go post on the webcam again real fast during the break.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're posing.
[SPEAKER_11]: Also with us tonight, we have another very special guest.
[SPEAKER_11]: He's somebody that has actually been on the show before.
[SPEAKER_11]: And he's our buddy from Kansas who now lives here in California.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's our buddy Shane, also known as Miquitas.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_11]: And if I'm not mistaken, you have a new name now that you go by as well, yes?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, you've been on the DDR Free Chords.
[SPEAKER_09]: I would be the new Vivid member, Seagird.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I'm the one causing you guys pain.
[SPEAKER_12]: I definitely have a lot of questions for Seagird when we get back from the break.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh yeah, tonight, I guess maybe you guys heard about this.
[SPEAKER_11]: We do have a little something.
[SPEAKER_11]: There's a
[SPEAKER_11]: A little song out there I think some of you guys are wanting to hear tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's all for right now.
[SPEAKER_11]: But it is Your Rain from brand new DDR Extreme.
[SPEAKER_11]: And we'll be playing that a little bit later in the show.
[SPEAKER_11]: But hell, while we have a captive audience, let's do our normal antics.
[SPEAKER_11]: Why don't we, huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because we love our listeners.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's a three-hour show.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's wait until 2.59.
[SPEAKER_11]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_02]: That works for me.
[SPEAKER_11]: The song's only like a minute long.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, no, we'll get to it somewhere after.
[SPEAKER_10]: Eventually.
[SPEAKER_11]: We definitely have to do How Was Your Week, How Was Your Day first, though, because that's when we start every show.
[SPEAKER_11]: But first, we're going to take a break, and in this break, we're going to hear the original Akira Yamaoka, Your Rain, from Silent Hill 4.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because that song is just so hot.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because the song rocked before they remixed it.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, I'm going to play it now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Quite literally, because it is rock.
[SPEAKER_11]: It is rock.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, enjoy.
[SPEAKER_02]: How perceptive.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, enjoy this, and then we will be back to play a little bit of How Was Your Week, How Was Your Day.
[SPEAKER_11]: Also tonight, boys and girls...
[SPEAKER_11]: Match Game.
[SPEAKER_11]: And to play Match Game tonight, you're going to want to be on Skype.
[SPEAKER_11]: Skype.org to download the client, and then you can talk to us live in the studio, and that's also available.
[SPEAKER_11]: So here it is.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll be playing a remix of it tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: But here's the original from Silent Hill 4, Kiri Yamoka.
[SPEAKER_11]: You're right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Enjoy it.
All that I need are some simple loving words You touched my body once, it hurted
Out of my head and I don't know what I found Over and over I feel it break me down
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_12]: Hiho, Kermit the Frog here, informing you that today's broadcast of Orange Lounge Radio is brought to you by the letter V, the letter A, and the number 59.
[SPEAKER_07]: Can you tell me how to get, how to get to Saturday?
[SPEAKER_11]: We are back and you are listening to Orange Lounge Radio, episode number 106.
[SPEAKER_11]: And if you are listening to the stream right now, consider yourself lucky because of that little song that we have we're going to play a little later for you guys.
[SPEAKER_11]: Tonight's show got whored out on a lot of different sites and because of that we have hit what is called the cap, the Live 365 listening cap.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're only allowed so many listeners and we never in our imaginations thought we would ever hit that limit.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll see you next time.
[SPEAKER_11]: DDR and 2DX
[SPEAKER_11]: We would be like the biggest dorks ever.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, we're pretty dorky to begin with, to even have this show in the first place.
[SPEAKER_11]: But to talk about nothing but DDR for like three hours?
[SPEAKER_11]: Come on, you couldn't pay me enough.
[SPEAKER_11]: There's other things out there.
[SPEAKER_11]: You gotta go outside once in a while.
[SPEAKER_11]: Get a job, get a girlfriend or boyfriend.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember, sunlight helps your body make vitamin D. Exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which you need to play DDR.
[SPEAKER_11]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because without it, you'll die.
[SPEAKER_11]: But no, we do, when all is said and done, we make a lot of fun at DDR on this show, we really do.
[SPEAKER_11]: But we're poking fun at ourselves when we poke fun at DDR, because really, we do have a lot of love for DDR.
[SPEAKER_11]: I would never have met Jamie, I would never have met Loki if it wasn't for DDR, 2DX and that stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: I would never have met anybody here if it wasn't for that, and for that we're thankful.
[SPEAKER_11]: And so we kind of always say, you know what, it's kind of like what happens when DDR gets taken outside the arcade.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's what happens with this show.
[SPEAKER_11]: This is DDR outside of the arcade.
[SPEAKER_11]: So this is just everybody sitting around having a good time, so.
[SPEAKER_11]: You think I summed that up pretty good, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_22]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_11]: That was pretty accurate.
[SPEAKER_11]: Why do you do this show, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_02]: I ain't got nothing else to do.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, good answer.
[SPEAKER_02]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's because, well, it's just fun, you know?
[SPEAKER_02]: We all get together.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like family time, you know?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because how many people just get around and have quality time?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_20]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: and then I get my little segment where I get to fuss and complain.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly, which we'll get to now.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll get to that later.
[SPEAKER_02]: I enjoy everybody's company.
[SPEAKER_11]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_11]: The fun doesn't stop just here because we actually do live shows throughout the week including, Jamie, you've got your own show.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have one called Pump Up the Volume named after the movie because that movie was awesome and had Christian Slater.
[SPEAKER_02]: But anyway, it's just a music request show.
[SPEAKER_02]: I play whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was supposed to do an 80s marathon last week.
[SPEAKER_02]: I sort of got bored with that and just played whatever.
[SPEAKER_11]: So it has nothing to do with DDR, but it's still cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: But every so often I will get a mad fit and just play nothing but Bimani just because I feel like it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the show is on Tuesdays.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pre-show starts at 7.
[SPEAKER_02]: The normal show is 7.30 to 10.30.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although, as of late, I've just been really bored and starting the show a little bit earlier and extending it a little bit to 12.30 range.
[SPEAKER_02]: So just tune in and listen as long as you can.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_11]: Also on this station, Monday night, tomorrow night, 7 o'clock, Diversion, which is our name for the Orange Lounge Radio Remix Show.
[SPEAKER_11]: And that's where we play all these different Bomani remixes.
[SPEAKER_11]: Fan-made ones, like things that were picked up in Tournamix and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_11]: All the way to, like...
[SPEAKER_11]: Remix has done so well, they're professional quality, and that would be like the Diverse Systems albums.
[SPEAKER_11]: We play that stuff on the show, really good Bomani remix stuff, and you know, we're going to be adding to the playlist this week because there was a new remix thing that just came out, but we'll talk about that later in the show, definitely.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, we'll get to that later in the show.
[SPEAKER_11]: Meanwhile, we have to start off tonight's show the way we always start off the show, because it's tradition, and that's a little segment we call, How was your week?
[SPEAKER_11]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_11]: You want to say something real fast, Loki?
[SPEAKER_11]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's looking at Anthony.
[SPEAKER_02]: He has a Happy Noodle Boy shirt, which is cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: Why do you do this show, Loki?
[SPEAKER_13]: Because I'm here.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_02]: I really don't.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because you sat on the floor for all of those months.
[SPEAKER_13]: I could be getting in three hours of quality Final Fantasy XI time right now.
[SPEAKER_13]: And look at this.
[SPEAKER_11]: Now who is sitting on the floor?
[SPEAKER_11]: Who are we forcing to sit on the floor?
[SPEAKER_11]: The guy that works at Konami.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're making him sit on the floor today.
[SPEAKER_02]: But he can sit there and pet Loki's cock.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: He has company.
[SPEAKER_11]: He has my cock in his hand, so that's all right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Would you put your cock on our webcam there?
[SPEAKER_11]: If you go to our webcam, www.orangelongeradio.com, it's right there on the front page.
[SPEAKER_11]: Loki's going to show off his cock to all you guys so you know what we're talking about.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, you know what time I got out of bed?
[SPEAKER_02]: Quarter after eight.
[SPEAKER_02]: My ass was there at nine o'clock.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't get rid of that, so it's cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I just worked an extra 30 minutes, and it was all good.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I got some extra sleep that day, but I was still tired all day.
[SPEAKER_02]: I finished one of my fanfics today.
[SPEAKER_02]: I finally completed it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's on fanfiction.net somewhere.
[SPEAKER_11]: What kind of fanfic?
[SPEAKER_02]: I write fanfiction.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, you don't want to tell us what kind?
[SPEAKER_02]: I write G.I.
[SPEAKER_02]: Joe fanfiction.
[SPEAKER_11]: A real American hero.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm also working on other stories, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm actually working on a novel, which is sort of on hold, because guess what?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not going to have free time anymore.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got my award letter from ARC, which made me all bouncy, and they still haven't freaking put my money on the stupid website, so I can't get my student loan yet, but that's okay, because in a couple weeks I'm going to have a laptop.
[SPEAKER_02]: That'll make it all better.
[SPEAKER_11]: Now, ARC, that's the local college here in SAC.
[SPEAKER_02]: American River College.
[SPEAKER_11]: Do you plan to be... They actually have a DDR machine there at the cafeteria.
[SPEAKER_11]: Are you ever going to touch that thing, you think?
[SPEAKER_02]: I might, but I don't want to get cooties.
[SPEAKER_02]: My plan was to go run track on Monday and Wednesday, because my classes are Monday and Wednesday.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I think after my Saturday class, I might go play some DDR.
[SPEAKER_11]: Right on.
[SPEAKER_02]: You do.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anything else you want to say about your week in a day?
[SPEAKER_02]: I had some angst.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had a good bit of angst.
[SPEAKER_11]: Very few times.
[SPEAKER_11]: We've done this, what, 106 weeks now?
[SPEAKER_11]: I think maybe two times you came in here not angsty about something.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, this isn't angry angst, okay?
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, this is real angst.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is like on the level of
[SPEAKER_02]: It's of the same intensity as teenage high school drama angst, which is pretty intense.
[SPEAKER_11]: Is it my fault?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, that's good then.
[SPEAKER_02]: If it was your fault, I'd tell you.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd be like, now listen up, bitch.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, and yesterday, I hung out with Iguana Girl and Tia, and we turned her hair from nearly jet black to bright red.
[SPEAKER_11]: Is this like a girls bonding kind of thing?
[SPEAKER_02]: Girls bonding thing over low carb ice cream.
[SPEAKER_02]: and I did something stupid.
[SPEAKER_02]: Milk carb ice cream is damn good.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's made with whole cream.
[SPEAKER_02]: I did something stupid.
[SPEAKER_02]: Look at this.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey, I like your hair, though.
[SPEAKER_11]: I like it like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I dyed my bangs blonde.
[SPEAKER_11]: I wish you weren't Cam Shies.
[SPEAKER_11]: You could show the others.
[SPEAKER_02]: They bleached out... They had to bleach out Tia's hair to turn it red.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I was like, hey, bleach my bangs.
[SPEAKER_02]: That'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Except the bleach was running out of activation power.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_02]: I, uh, only one side took the bleach very well and the other one's a lot lighter.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it looks okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Except I forgot that since I had dyed my hair black before, the ends are still dark.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess I could get on, this is the only time you're gonna get me on the cam, okay?
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, pass off the microphone to somebody.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, we'll go to somebody else while Jamie poses on cam with the hair.
[SPEAKER_11]: Uh, Angel.
[SPEAKER_11]: Angel, how was your week?
[SPEAKER_11]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pretty good.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm still kind of adapting to certain things, if you want to talk about that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because nobody really knows.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, they kind of know, but they don't.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you want to talk about that for a bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you?
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, sure, sure, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm sorry, I was reading some other stuff going on.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm having a laugh at some other stuff that I'm reading.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi, chat room!
[SPEAKER_03]: Please type!
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, anyway...
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, damn.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, so about three weeks ago, I moved out for the first time in my life, so I live here now.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's still very strange for me to say, but I assume I will get used to it as time goes on.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I don't know, that's about it, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: I work here, and duh.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: and I live with Magus.
[SPEAKER_03]: Everybody hide.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, the bad jokes go on and on and on and on.
[SPEAKER_11]: And if you haven't listened to our show before, 23 Magus is always full of bad jokes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Has he added another sheet of toilet paper to his joke book?
[SPEAKER_03]: He's added many sheets of toilet paper to his notebook.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wish I could sneak into his room in the middle of the night, take a...
[SPEAKER_03]: Match and Sprint, but that would be bad because then I wouldn't have a place to live.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, yeah, I'll just leave it in the bathroom so his brother can mangle it or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, okay, I guess I'm done.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, let's go over to somebody else.
[SPEAKER_11]: Brand new to the show, never been here before.
[SPEAKER_11]: How are you doing, Andrew?
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm very tired.
[SPEAKER_15]: How are you doing?
[SPEAKER_11]: How was your week?
[SPEAKER_11]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_15]: Very busy.
[SPEAKER_15]: This week was my last day working full time at my job teaching kids.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm very excited that I don't have to do that anymore because that was getting very stressful.
[SPEAKER_15]: But beyond that, just doing usual stuff, especially avoiding jailbait.
[SPEAKER_15]: I seem to have this 16-year-old fan club, which doesn't do me any good.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, I've heard a lot of DDR guys have this problem.
[SPEAKER_15]: Man, I don't know what it is.
[SPEAKER_13]: I had the same problem when I worked at Roundtable.
[SPEAKER_13]: For some reason, the fact that I was in a shift manager position, meaning I could provide free pizza.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, there you go.
[SPEAKER_13]: Get a lot of fangirls that way.
[SPEAKER_13]: In fact, one that would spread rumors, because my mom worked as a yard duty at the junior high.
[SPEAKER_13]: And so I'd hear rumors, this girl's saying that you guys are dating.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I'm like, what?
[SPEAKER_13]: That was funny.
[SPEAKER_15]: Wow, yeah, it's unusual.
[SPEAKER_15]: But I don't know what it is, if it's the DDR or what, or that I look like four years younger than I really am.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, so I guess we'll come over here then and talk to our other guest, Sigurd, as he's now known.
[SPEAKER_11]: Why the name change again?
[SPEAKER_11]: You had to go and change your name again.
[SPEAKER_11]: Everybody knew who you were before.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, not everybody.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nobody cared before you had the flashing foot.
[SPEAKER_09]: You were a nobody.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was a nobody.
[SPEAKER_09]: I changed it because I figured that would be the best course of action.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, apparently it doesn't matter, so, you know, I made that name for no good reason.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh well.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, so, what are we doing again right now?
[SPEAKER_09]: How was your week?
[SPEAKER_11]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, okay, my week?
[SPEAKER_09]: I worked.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's all I do.
[SPEAKER_09]: Every week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, then, yesterday, I went out to Dave & Buster's, which was really cool because it was my first time.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, all those people on DDR Freak...
[SPEAKER_09]: You guys, that's probably why you didn't get anything from any of the Vivid members last night, because we were all at Dave & Buster's, getting drunk.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, I had a good time, played some games, played that other dancing game.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, you mean Poop It Up?
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean Pump It Up.
[SPEAKER_09]: I like Pump It Up.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Don't discriminate against the other games, it's cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because you can do the pump jump.
[SPEAKER_09]: I worked.
[SPEAKER_09]: The end.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh!
[SPEAKER_09]: and I obviously got my vivid status on DDR Freak, which I swear you guys, Friday, me and Floatwalk, if you don't know who Floatwalk is, I'm not going to tell you, we had like a laugh a minute, and you guys are seriously creeping us out with the DNL Photoshop pictures.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was like looking at a Fark.com Photoshop contest, honestly, it was hilarious.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was creepy.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's really all I can say to that.
[SPEAKER_09]: But, you know, if you happen to want to do it again, it was funny.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was my week, and today I came to Sacramento.
[SPEAKER_09]: The end.
[SPEAKER_11]: Loki,
[SPEAKER_11]: How was your week?
[SPEAKER_11]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_11]: Since, you know, I know everybody out there on DDR Freak really cares how your week and your day was.
[SPEAKER_11]: What?
[SPEAKER_11]: No, I'm looking right now.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're all like, man, we are such big fans.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_11]: Just don't bother playing the song tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: You can save that until next week.
[SPEAKER_11]: I want to know about you guys this week and your day.
[SPEAKER_11]: Especially you, Loki.
[SPEAKER_13]: Especially me?
[SPEAKER_13]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_13]: You make it look like I had an interesting week.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, so this week what I was doing... Played Final Fantasy.
[SPEAKER_10]: I...
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes, I did, but that's not the point.
[SPEAKER_13]: I did that towards the end of the week.
[SPEAKER_13]: The beginning of the week was even better, okay?
[SPEAKER_13]: Basically what happened was... Final Fantasy on two computers.
[SPEAKER_13]: No.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's too slow to play Final Fantasy, and I don't want to have to buy another copy of it.
[SPEAKER_13]: For what would I do that?
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyways, so I was really bored at work, like usual, so I browsed websites.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, when I can't browse Bomani websites because I read them too fast and no one posts fast enough for me to read everything, I browse other things.
[SPEAKER_13]: And this week, it was theshadowlands.net.
[SPEAKER_13]: And what theshadowlands.net is, is a big paranormal website about all, like, hauntings and shit.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, I got this, like, paranormal kick for, like, this whole week, and basically just figuring all this stuff out.
[SPEAKER_13]: And so now, for some reason, I'm going to bid on a supposedly haunted possessed doll that's fucked up looking, and I'm gonna buy that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Those things are cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, it's supposedly a really fucked up, real, not the pictures that I posted, like, a real doll that is supposedly haunted.
[SPEAKER_13]: Like, and they have photographic proof and shit.
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyways, so I'm gonna buy that.
[SPEAKER_13]: and put it at my desk at work to creep out my co-worker.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's the whole point.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's beautiful.
[SPEAKER_13]: I thought that'd be great.
[SPEAKER_13]: So I might do that.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: It depends on how expensive it is because I have to also fix my cabinet because I found it earlier this week because the way I have it set up, there's like some conflicts with...
[SPEAKER_13]: Some of the controller things I have on there, so I need to buy a new keyboard encoder to get the main cabinet working.
[SPEAKER_13]: But I've been playing lots of games, more porno games again, and kicking ass at Gal's Panic and all that stuff, because it's fun.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, what else?
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: I actually had a pretty interesting weekend.
[SPEAKER_13]: On Friday night I went to a bar and hung out there with coworkers that I don't like.
[SPEAKER_13]: And there was a girl that supposedly asked me to dance, but it was so loud in there, I couldn't understand a word she was saying.
[SPEAKER_13]: I heard this, outside!
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm like, huh?
[SPEAKER_13]: And then she kind of walked off really pissed.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I don't know what the hell happened, and my friend standing next to me was like, she asked you to dance.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm like, oh.
[SPEAKER_13]: So that was fun.
[SPEAKER_13]: And so we did that.
[SPEAKER_13]: And they had a giant hippo head with a bagpipe in his mouth.
[SPEAKER_13]: So I thought that was kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_13]: And last night we went and saw some comedians.
[SPEAKER_13]: There was a guy that looked like Mr. Bean and another guy that looked like Ray Romano.
[SPEAKER_13]: That was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: Then there was this Mexican guy headlining.
[SPEAKER_13]: And because the guy was really cool, I bought his CD.
[SPEAKER_13]: So I'm going to give you a copy, Jamie, so you can play it on your show.
[SPEAKER_13]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's a 25-minute set of his.
[SPEAKER_13]: I can't remember the guy's name for the life of me.
[SPEAKER_13]: But, um, I think he was on Comedy Central.
[SPEAKER_13]: I could've sworn I remembered his stand-up bit on, uh... It's this funny comedy, you know, I'll play it.
[SPEAKER_13]: But yeah, he was like, there's these people that are drunk rolling, like, next to us and stuff, and he just ripped into them all night, it was great.
[SPEAKER_13]: Um, so that's what I did last night, and then, you know, Final Fantasy XI in the middle there, so... Uh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: And then, of course, there's other things I did, but we're gonna get into that later.
[SPEAKER_13]: More stuff I downloaded and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, my week and my day was pretty decent.
[SPEAKER_11]: This was the first week back from the East Coast.
[SPEAKER_11]: So I was just kind of trying to catch up on everything.
[SPEAKER_11]: And, you know, last night I was at Dave & Buster's with Sigurd and some of the other folks there.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I went to go play Pump It Up because they don't have any other Bomani there.
[SPEAKER_11]: Although somebody told me they have the I Can Dance game there, the iToy game.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm sorry, I Can Boogie, which is basically iToy Groove in the arcades.
[SPEAKER_11]: I could not find it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I didn't realize it was there and I should have thought to ask Mel or somebody who goes there all the time.
[SPEAKER_13]: Don't worry, you didn't miss anything.
[SPEAKER_13]: It sucks ass.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh my god, it sucks ass.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, it's alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: So fine, I didn't get to play it.
[SPEAKER_11]: So instead I decided to play it and I realized I decided to play Pump It Up and then I realized that
[SPEAKER_11]: I haven't really played DDR seriously in about three months or so, so I haven't really gotten any more stamina than I had before.
[SPEAKER_11]: And, of course, Shane gets up on there and wants to play, like, Ninefooters.
[SPEAKER_11]: What the hell was that song you made us do last that killed me?
[SPEAKER_09]: It was Clap Your Hands on Crazy, and, you know, we were just worn out, so we didn't pass it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I seriously thought I was going to die.
[SPEAKER_11]: I had to go out in the parking lot and go, like, it was horrible.
[SPEAKER_11]: So I ended up missing like an hour of some good gaming.
[SPEAKER_11]: Some good feeding quarters into the giant crane machine because I was going to die.
[SPEAKER_13]: I actually, I experienced the same thing you felt, except I'm really out of shape because I haven't played DDR in months.
[SPEAKER_13]: Lots of months.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I went and played seven footers on doubles and I was out of breath.
[SPEAKER_13]: Like, heart attack out of breath, and that's really sad.
[SPEAKER_13]: But, I'm working on the cabinet, it's gonna be done, DDR will be able to be played, and I will get back into shape again.
[SPEAKER_11]: How is that cabinet coming along?
[SPEAKER_11]: You built, now for those that haven't been listening to the show for, well, I mean, that's a lot of you guys tonight, I frankly know.
[SPEAKER_11]: You've been building your own home cabinet, which is like your dream machine.
[SPEAKER_11]: Tell us a little bit more about this cabinet you've been building.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, this thing's basically an all-in-one Bomani cabinet and arcade cabinet.
[SPEAKER_13]: Right now, the first part of it's done, which is the main part of it.
[SPEAKER_13]: So I have a four-player kind of control panel with two of the players having six buttons, three and four having just four buttons.
[SPEAKER_13]: And it's basically just set up for MAME right now.
[SPEAKER_13]: Later on, though, I'm working on a setup for DDR, Dance Maniacs, 2DX, and Poppin' Music all together.
[SPEAKER_13]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_13]: I was forced to do this by them.
[SPEAKER_13]: I was forced to spend $3,000 to fix up a nice cabinet so I have working games because I like playing arcade games and I refuse to go to an arcade that has broken games.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that they should put all the Golfland children in a pen and put like spider stomp in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And just leave them there.
[SPEAKER_11]: And we'll actually stomp on the children.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, that would be awesome!
[SPEAKER_02]: Or like a giant troubled board game instead of having dice in the middle have children in the pop-o-matic bubble.
[SPEAKER_11]: That would be wonderful.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they bang it and they go pop!
[SPEAKER_11]: I wish they had like a tail at Golfland.
[SPEAKER_02]: And how many seconds they scream is how long you get to move.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my god, it's kinematic trouble in giant size, Eep.
[SPEAKER_13]: Or how about a giant catapult with piano wire above them?
[SPEAKER_02]: Ooooooh!
[SPEAKER_02]: But no, if you kill them, you have to get more children.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that means that people have to breed.
[SPEAKER_13]: They're gonna breed anyways.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because they're stupid.
[SPEAKER_02]: I still think that they should make standardized testing for breeding.
[SPEAKER_11]: Not only are they gonna breed, they're breeding at younger and younger ages these days.
[SPEAKER_11]: There's gonna be like a baby that has a baby.
[SPEAKER_11]: Just wait.
[SPEAKER_02]: A ten-year-old had a baby.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it was a bad situation that produced it, but still.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't care what they say about the tradition...
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, the whole Christian look of this?
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh-uh, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: Depends on where you live.
[SPEAKER_02]: People are doing it early.
[SPEAKER_13]: You see, now, if I lived in Vacaville, at least there'd be plenty of sheep and stuff, but, you know, I don't have that kind of convenience here in, you know, Folsom.
[SPEAKER_13]: Do you love animals?
[SPEAKER_09]: I just wanted to say about the whole little kids having kids.
[SPEAKER_09]: My middle school, we had a couple kids there have children, and that's back in Kansas, so you know there's nothing to do there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's hear it for, you know, family values.
[SPEAKER_11]: Different strokes for different folks.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some are stroking it.
[SPEAKER_11]: And if more people stroked it, we wouldn't have a baby outbreak.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is why for the whole anti, you know...
[SPEAKER_02]: What is it they're doing in, was it in Texas, I think?
[SPEAKER_02]: The whole abstinence, teaching abstinence instead of safe, you know, forms of intercourse.
[SPEAKER_02]: Instead, they should just teach the joy of masturbation.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why go out when you can get it at home?
[SPEAKER_11]: On that note, I think we're going to go ahead and take a break.
[SPEAKER_11]: And when we come back from this break, I definitely, and I think it's hilarious because a lot of people that are listening to this show right now are like,
[SPEAKER_11]: Why didn't you guys play the song at 6.30?
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey, nobody said we were going to play the song at 6.30.
[SPEAKER_11]: We said we were going to play it during the show, which runs between 6.30 and 9.30.
[SPEAKER_11]: And if that happens to be at 9.29, you all just have to deal.
[SPEAKER_11]: But maybe we'll do 9.28.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, we'll get it in eventually here.
[SPEAKER_11]: When we feel like it.
[SPEAKER_11]: When Jamie says it's time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lord knows when that'll be.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: But actually, no, we do have some fun stuff coming up for you when we get back.
[SPEAKER_11]: I guess we can talk about DDR because, huh?
[SPEAKER_11]: I will.
[SPEAKER_11]: I will play.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're going to do some Akira this break, actually, for those folks.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Since everybody's been relatively good, even though there has been some shit talking on the forums out there, and that makes me a little bit angry, I guess we can do another little tease here.
[SPEAKER_11]: How about a tease?
[SPEAKER_11]: Do you guys want another little tease?
[SPEAKER_21]: Go tease it, Rob.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm going to tease it right now, you guys.
[SPEAKER_11]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, that's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_11]: That was a tease.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, so now that that tease has been done, let's go to a break.
[SPEAKER_11]: When we come back, I think we'll actually talk about some DDR.
[SPEAKER_10]: Make it big!
[SPEAKER_11]: I want to talk about how Sigurd's internet penis just grew enormous this week.
[SPEAKER_11]: Enormous.
[SPEAKER_11]: And people want us to talk hints.
[SPEAKER_11]: So we're going to talk hints, or lack thereof, when we come back from this break.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I will also be giving hints as well.
[SPEAKER_13]: but you don't even work for Konami and you've never played- I can give him- THAT'S BECAUSE I HAVE INSIDER INFO YOU FREAKIN' MORONS THAT EVERY- THAT ANYONE ELSE CAN GET BUT YOU'RE JUST TOO FUCKING STUPID TO REALIZE THAT WE TOLD YOU, LIKE, FOUR FUCKING MONTHS AGO OR EVEN BEFORE THAT WHAT THE HELL WAS GONNA BE IN THE-
[SPEAKER_13]: No!
[SPEAKER_13]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm gonna tell you that I told you so, and you can just kiss my ass again.
[SPEAKER_13]: You can blow me just like you blew me before when it came down to, you know, fucking saying, Oh, Sakura's not gonna be in DDR Extreme.
[SPEAKER_13]: Fuck you!
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_13]: That's what I have to say about that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Someone's full of the anger tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: That Loki guy screams into the microphone too much.
[SPEAKER_11]: He screams.
[SPEAKER_11]: He's screaming in the microphone.
[SPEAKER_11]: Why doesn't somebody give him a drug?
[SPEAKER_11]: Why can't he just shut up and play the song?
[SPEAKER_11]: Just shut up.
[SPEAKER_11]: Give us a hint.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have a hint for you.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's called Bite My Ass.
[SPEAKER_11]: Now, now, be nice.
[SPEAKER_11]: We want the listeners to come back when they realize that we're not that bad at people.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, we're not that bad.
[SPEAKER_11]: Really not.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're just messing with you guys tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_02]: Seriously though, just listen.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just stay patient.
[SPEAKER_02]: Patience is a virtue.
[SPEAKER_02]: Be virtuous.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know it's hard, but you can wait.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: We'll be back after some Akira.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for watching!
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for watching!
Hi, this is Mel B of RTF, and for an extra $1.99 a minute, my girlfriend Mel B can join us on all the fun together.
[SPEAKER_17]: Hey, if you're a broke ass like I am, why don't you come to the one place that costs absolutely nothing to go to and still the fun is just as great.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's Orange Lounge Radio, Sunday nights.
[SPEAKER_17]: Kick it with me and you just might realize the best things in life are free.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hello, we are back with Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's our buddy Mel B.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, well, hell, we all need to go.
[SPEAKER_02]: So Dan and I are going to have ourselves a hotel.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know Konami is having a showing there at Classic Gaming Expo.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wonder if there will be some Twinbee for me to play.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: I hear that Konami's going to make a showing, but I can't say what's going on.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I'm very glad, though, that it's in San Jose this year instead of in Vegas, because that would have been pricey.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, at least it's drivable here.
[SPEAKER_02]: The only good thing about it being in Vegas is that I would have been able to have seen Mar and John, but I'm making plans at another time if someone has $250 to lend me.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's a hint.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, it's not a hint.
[SPEAKER_11]: Jamie wants money.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's a hint.
[SPEAKER_11]: Be careful with the way you use the word hint on tonight's show because people are going to run with it.
[SPEAKER_10]: You don't think I said that on purpose?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm teasing them.
[SPEAKER_11]: Just so you guys know, if myself, Loki, or DarkSakura say something as a hint, we're pretty much talking out our ass because there's this little thing called NDA, called the Non-Disclosure Agreement, which means that even though our buddy...
[SPEAKER_11]: works at Konami, he can't tell us what's going on or they will fire his ass.
[SPEAKER_11]: We don't want that to happen to him.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, we don't want that to happen.
[SPEAKER_13]: But I can disclose anything I want because they can fire me all they want.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't work for them.
[SPEAKER_13]: No.
[SPEAKER_13]: I will disclose it all.
[SPEAKER_13]: Everything.
[SPEAKER_13]: But no, it's surprising.
[SPEAKER_13]: This information's been out forever and people just don't realize it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I can't think of anything.
[SPEAKER_11]: What we can talk about, I can mention this, is that a few months ago, and you can go back in the Orange Lounge Radio story archives, and you can look at, we had a story that talked about how some folks were hacking the disk for DDR, what disk were they hacking back at that point?
[SPEAKER_13]: It was probably a collection.
[SPEAKER_13]: And there's a master list.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, here's how it works.
[SPEAKER_13]: When they're making the games, there's a master list of all the songs that have been in all the games and that are going to be in all the games.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, basically, whatever they're working on up to that point.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's just a master list.
[SPEAKER_13]: Think of it like, if you're familiar with MAME, there's a master ROM list.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, well, this is a master song list.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, it's going to contain everything from the arcade versions, the home versions, and home versions that they're working on at the moment.
[SPEAKER_13]: So...
[SPEAKER_13]: Here's the thing right now, as I said before, you know, there's some songs in there that they, you know, they're all, oh, those are, you know, you know, don't believe that, because, you know, back in the day when DDR Max was first coming out, and remember there was that Orion Civilization, supposedly remix of that, but it was just under a different name, well, everyone's like, oh, well, those lists are wrong, and then they're saying, oh, well, Nemesis is supposed to be in Max 2 or something like that, or
[SPEAKER_13]: D.D.R.
[SPEAKER_13]: Extreme
[SPEAKER_13]: I agree that it's a dumb name.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, it's a dumb name for a song.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's so fucking wrong!
[SPEAKER_13]: And then there it was, you know, all in its piece of shit glory.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is where we point and laugh.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, but there are songs, I mean, a lot of songs actually that are in there that are going to be in, you know, extremes.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, I told you so.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm actually trying to find that list from when we posted it.
[SPEAKER_11]: We were posting that list, and I distinctly remember that Diving was in that list.
[SPEAKER_11]: It has been confirmed that Diving is going to be in DDR Extreme.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's no secret.
[SPEAKER_11]: Four Strings Diving.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because I remember we were talking about that list on an earlier show, and I saw Diving, and I said, oh, that's another song on that Four Strings album, so Diving must be in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Come to think of it, that was also in the pre-show.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was on the CD.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, there you go.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, okay, so...
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm going to dig through the archives a little more and we'll go through that list again and we'll see, you know, maybe there's some song titles in there.
[SPEAKER_11]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_11]: Is Konami capable of throwing red herrings our way?
[SPEAKER_11]: You bet.
[SPEAKER_11]: Do you think that there are songs that are supposed to be in DDR that don't make it into DDR in the final cut?
[SPEAKER_11]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes, there are.
[SPEAKER_13]: And there are songs that get, you know, cancelled.
[SPEAKER_13]: Like, for example, DDR Ultramix, The Humpty Dance.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, I would have dug it if The Humpty Dance was in DDR.
[SPEAKER_11]: Been awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: But how would you make steps for that and get it to look right?
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll come back to this subject a little later, but I wanted to keep things moving.
[SPEAKER_11]: I actually wanted to talk to Andrew.
[SPEAKER_11]: He's sitting there in the corner, and he's never been here before.
[SPEAKER_11]: Are you enjoying things so far?
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: It seems like everybody wants to talk to me.
[SPEAKER_11]: You came on a good night.
[SPEAKER_11]: Everybody heard you were going to be here, and now our caps are breaking and everything.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's what I heard, and I'm really happy that I can contribute like this to your show.
[SPEAKER_11]: No problem.
[SPEAKER_11]: You should come here more often.
[SPEAKER_15]: I should.
[SPEAKER_15]: I appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_11]: In all seriousness, for those who don't know you, you're the guy, and the reason why I wanted you to be on the show is because you dress up like a pirate when you play DDR.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_11]: Why?
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, at first it started because I'm just a massive attention whore.
[SPEAKER_15]: I mean, honestly.
[SPEAKER_15]: But, uh, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_15]: I mean, I got there, and I just started playing, and some people would watch, but I was never a freestyler because I'm too white for that shit.
[SPEAKER_15]: Basically, I just was like,
[SPEAKER_15]: I just stopped off at some party store after work one night, bought a cheap pirate costume, went into Golfland.
[SPEAKER_15]: I noticed I turn around and there's like 40 or 50 people.
[SPEAKER_15]: There's like 40 or 50 people watching me, so I'm just like, okay, I'll keep this up.
[SPEAKER_15]: So I just kind of whore it around in my signature now.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm a Toadie007 on GameFAQs, DDR Freak.
[SPEAKER_15]: Get a hold of me on the NorCal forums.
[SPEAKER_15]: Johnny Depp Fetish
[SPEAKER_15]: No, it was just an inside joke with some people at work.
[SPEAKER_15]: I have a friend that owns a production company called Shiver Me Timbers Productions and it kind of went off from there.
[SPEAKER_15]: I brought that thing into work the other day.
[SPEAKER_15]: My boss apparently lets me dress up like a pirate for work, so I thought that was kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: Now, we all know the Roseville Golf Line.
[SPEAKER_11]: When you go to play DDR there, there's something that we call the hecklers, or the assholes.
[SPEAKER_11]: All these people there that make fun of you when you're playing DDR.
[SPEAKER_11]: Fag!
[SPEAKER_11]: You look like a fag when you play that game!
[SPEAKER_11]: You're a fag!
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh wait, you're a chick.
[SPEAKER_15]: You're a fag!
[SPEAKER_15]: I get that anyway, even when I'm not playing DDR, but you know those people, they can kiss my ass, I don't care.
[SPEAKER_11]: But how bad is it?
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, what's the worst you've heard?
[SPEAKER_11]: Dressed up, not only playing DDR, but being a pirate playing DDR.
[SPEAKER_11]: What are some of the things you've heard?
[SPEAKER_15]: Ironically, I don't think I've gotten any shit for the pirate thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Really?
[SPEAKER_15]: If anything, I get shit when I bar rape.
[SPEAKER_15]: I thought you guys were going to cue up a boo sound effect when I say that.
[SPEAKER_15]: No.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because I get heckled on the show.
[SPEAKER_00]: No.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, the pirate thing, most people just kind of go up and go like, what in the hell is that guy doing?
[SPEAKER_15]: Because, I mean, you can see the little strings on the beard, you know, it looks totally fake, you know, but I don't really get anything.
[SPEAKER_15]: It just confuses the hell out of most people, so they think it's kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_15]: and it really ticks off all the good freestylers because nobody pays attention to them.
[SPEAKER_15]: Wait, we have good freestylers in this town?
[SPEAKER_15]: No, I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's totally a joke.
[SPEAKER_14]: Wait a minute, wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: There's no way I'm serious there.
[SPEAKER_11]: Are you going to take the pirate to any DDR tournaments in the future?
[SPEAKER_15]: I will try.
[SPEAKER_15]: I've only been to like two so far and I got...
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_15]: There's supposed to be a big one in Milpitas...
[SPEAKER_11]: Friday?
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know, it's like an improv tournament, I want to say?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, I have a wedding on that day, actually.
[SPEAKER_11]: I have my alter ego I wanted to take out for that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I don't think I'm going to be able to do it, which is too bad.
[SPEAKER_15]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_15]: Do you know if it's in the afternoon or at night?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, it's like a night.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's a Friday night, which kind of sucks for you if you're out of town.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't get those Friday night things.
[SPEAKER_11]: But sometimes you have to do a tournament when you can do it, when the arcade owner says you can do it.
[SPEAKER_15]: If it's a Friday night, I might be able to do it.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm not going to enter, but it'll be all good.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Um, okay, so, um... Anything else you wanted to share about... Oh, is there anything you want to plug while you're here?
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, when guests come on talk shows, they plug things.
[SPEAKER_11]: Is there anything you want to plug?
[SPEAKER_11]: You said you had a production company?
[SPEAKER_11]: No, my friend, my friend.
[SPEAKER_11]: You did a DDR video recently, didn't you?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, I was in a DDR video.
[SPEAKER_15]: I whored that onto my live journal.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm just a cam whore, I guess.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't know if you want to give out that link on your live journal, but... Do you want me to give it out in the chat room?
[SPEAKER_11]: Go for it.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'll give out the video link in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_15]: I look like shit in the video, but still, you know, I don't care.
[SPEAKER_15]: The more people that know my name, the bigger my ego gets, so... Right on.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's all good.
[SPEAKER_15]: Right on.
[SPEAKER_11]: Andrew, by the way...
[SPEAKER_11]: If you want to join our chatroom, just head on over to www.OrangeLaunchRadio.com, you can check out the camera while you're there, and then you'll just click on chat.
[SPEAKER_11]: And if you have a friend who's trying to get into the station to listen to us, because we have such a great show and it has nothing to do with the Your Rain song whatsoever, your friends want to hear Andrew talk some more, we are going to play that song again at 9.40.
[SPEAKER_11]: And Andrew will talk some more, maybe then too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my god, we have more than one Andrew now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Everyone hide.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's horrible.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, I found the link here.
[SPEAKER_15]: It looks like it's shivermetimbersproductions.com Yeah, my friend John, who was a colleague of mine at work, he produced that video.
[SPEAKER_15]: I owe him a lot of lunches for that.
[SPEAKER_15]: So go ahead and check his site out.
[SPEAKER_20]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_13]: This stuff I think I posted was just the licensed tracks that I recognized.
[SPEAKER_11]: This is a story that was posted on May 7th on our website, and you can go back into our archives and have a look.
[SPEAKER_11]: And these were the songs that were on the master song list that we speculated could be in DDR Extremes.
[SPEAKER_11]: This is nothing new, and certainly Shane is not going to confirm or deny anything and break his NDA, but...
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, if you look at it, since it is licensed stuff, you guys already know what it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, yeah, hey, the ones that you see that you know are in the game, they are totally in the game.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, the ones that are in the game, they are definitely in the game.
[SPEAKER_11]: So we have on there, Simply Being Loved, which we know is in the game, Diving, we know that's in the game, Ride on Time, I don't think we ever figured out what that one was, did we?
[SPEAKER_11]: Don't know about that one.
[SPEAKER_11]: Come Into My World, which makes me think of the Kylie Minogue song.
[SPEAKER_11]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_11]: Planet Rock, that did turn up in Extreme, we do know that.
[SPEAKER_11]: The Boys of Summer, DJ Sammy Song, we had Heaven and Max 2, we thought we'd get it in Extreme because it was on this list, but haven't heard about it yet.
[SPEAKER_11]: Humpty Dance, they're saying was possibly something that was coming over from Xbox, don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: And Mickey, so we don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: But...
[SPEAKER_11]: But what we do know is that in our chatroom it was said by one of our folks, I think it was Mel B over at DDR Spot, did say, hey guess what guys, if you're trying to find the list to Ultramix 2, which has, I think he said 46, I'm sorry, I'm going to look for what he said, where is it?
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know what he said.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was something like 46 more songs that have not been in DDR before.
[SPEAKER_11]: Is it 56?
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, 56.
[SPEAKER_11]: 56 more songs that have not been in DDR before.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_11]: And none of them are on that master list.
[SPEAKER_11]: So don't even bother looking, because they're not on there.
[SPEAKER_11]: So forget it.
[SPEAKER_18]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_11]: Of course he could be just throwing us off.
[SPEAKER_11]: Is that a hint?
[SPEAKER_11]: Are you guys dropping a hint?
[SPEAKER_10]: Is that a hint?
[SPEAKER_10]: Is that 56 mean something?
[SPEAKER_10]: If you flip the 6 upside down, it's a 9.
[SPEAKER_13]: Maybe it's a Japanese character.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_13]: Here's the thing about that.
[SPEAKER_13]: There's been a big, huge span between when Party Collection came out and when these new mixes are coming out.
[SPEAKER_13]: So obviously, you know, there's going to be a lot of stuff that's not on there.
[SPEAKER_13]: and I mean there's a lot of stuff that would be on there this is just stuff that they were developing a while back so there's a lot of work being done right now on it so it's not surprising that there's not a lot on there but there's some other ones that were not licensed songs that were on the master list that I've heard might be in there
[SPEAKER_13]: So, um, I'm not saying anything, but, uh, there was stuff that we knew about a long time ago, and I think I even quoted on the show seeing what the songs were a long time ago, but, you know, I can't see now because, uh, my balls are tied.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, you know, I just, I cannot say anything.
[SPEAKER_13]: But, that's it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: I feel like doing another tease.
[SPEAKER_11]: What do you guys think?
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's do another tease.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's tease them again.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's do it.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're going to do it soon, you guys.
[SPEAKER_11]: We have to make this last, alright?
[SPEAKER_11]: We only get to have fun like this, what, once every 106 shows?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: You guys won't listen to us otherwise.
[SPEAKER_11]: So we have to tease it now.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, a secret.
[SPEAKER_09]: And you know, after he plays, I'll probably get to have this little one-on-one chat with him, so if you guys are just sticking around for the Your Rain remix, you might miss out on some other stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: I want to chat with you first.
[SPEAKER_11]: I want to get that stuff over with, because I have to get something out there.
[SPEAKER_11]: Man, I've got to set some people straight.
[SPEAKER_09]: So then forget what I said.
[SPEAKER_09]: You guys can leave right after that song plays.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or no, you can't.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, hold on, let's tease.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, that's enough.
[SPEAKER_11]: That was pretty sexy, I like that.
[SPEAKER_11]: That was very sexy.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_13]: It sounded like you touched my something, yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: You touched my... Oh yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think she said boob.
[SPEAKER_11]: How many DDRs are going to love that?
[SPEAKER_11]: You touched my boob.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: For everyone that enjoyed our pre-show, we had porn on the webcam, but no one seemed, I don't know if anyone paid attention to that.
[SPEAKER_13]: I knew I should have got here earlier.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, we will get to it soon, but first, I want to talk to our buddy Sigurd.
[SPEAKER_11]: Do you want to go to commercial first?
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, Sigurd wants to go to commercial first, so we can, you're gonna, you're pissing off the chat room.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, when we get back, we're going to talk to Sigurd.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're also going to do some Bomani match game tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then maybe we'll do the song, but maybe we'll have a cage match before that.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_11]: Depends what time we're at.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll have a look.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: God, some people are going to kick our ass if we don't do it soon.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_11]: You can wait at how long?
[SPEAKER_11]: You can wait a few more minutes for us, guys.
[SPEAKER_11]: Come on, it's for us.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, come on.
[SPEAKER_11]: Come on, guys.
[SPEAKER_11]: You're pals, Sky.
[SPEAKER_11]: Be good, sports.
[SPEAKER_13]: There will be a song, holy shit, a song in DDR Extreme that will have mix in the title.
[SPEAKER_11]: That was an awesome hint.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's go to what I think was probably most people's favorite Akira Yamaoka song previously.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like a lot of people.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's kind of a stereotypical favorite Akira Yamaoka song.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Tonight, guys, I might change for you guys tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_11]: But from Night Style, let's take this break.
[SPEAKER_11]: Lionski.
[SPEAKER_11]: Enjoy.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching.
[SPEAKER_08]: Atsu no Owari Uri no Tsuake, Masa de Ode Takano ga Babushii Keiyokutai no Koro no Sakotsu na Kazuki ni Shitei wa Kaware Shitei ga Uchigateta Omaiku wa Hayase no Imeishan, Mayari no Waichikari no Tamawaketa Teretara soba wa Rake datte Yume ni Sota, Kishitei yuunan no Komogari
Abadito Voleo
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network
[SPEAKER_19]: And now, let's listen in to an Orange Lounge Radio staff meeting as they debate some of the new programming coming to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: Jamie, I have a suggestion about some of the music in our Bomani Music and More program.
[SPEAKER_11]: Can we talk about that?
[SPEAKER_22]: No subject will ever be taboo.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, I was thinking maybe we should move Pump Up the Volume from Tuesday Nights.
[SPEAKER_11]: Except, of course, a subject that was just under discussion.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, well, what would you think if maybe we cut back on some of the tack music we play on the station?
[SPEAKER_16]: I collect your fucking head.
[SPEAKER_16]: Just like this fucker here.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh my god, why did you do that to Loki?
[SPEAKER_12]: The holic thing on episode 69 was just a joke!
[SPEAKER_16]: Now if any of you sons of bitches got anything else to say, now's the fucking time!
[SPEAKER_19]: Orange Lounge Radio, where everybody has a say.
[SPEAKER_11]: Welcome back, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: And you know, I have to say, if you haven't figured it out, I'm kind of reading the DDR Freak thread on Xtreme during the show, and about the last four pages have been people talking about this show, and it's really starting to piss some of your moderators off.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry I'm not there to help.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm contributing to the problem.
[SPEAKER_11]: Stop spamming DDR Freak, please.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't want to have to go clean up.
[SPEAKER_11]: Some of the moderators over there aren't exactly happy cappers right now because you guys have hijacked the thread, so please steer things back on course.
[SPEAKER_11]: We do have forums of our own.
[SPEAKER_11]: Nobody posts there, but hey, you know, you could be a trendsetter.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_11]: Maybe later.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_11]: I said I wanted to talk to Sigurd.
[SPEAKER_11]: So let's talk to Sigurd.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, Loki.
[SPEAKER_11]: You said moving on.
[SPEAKER_13]: That was another song in DDR.
[SPEAKER_13]: Could it be?
[SPEAKER_11]: Again, I don't know shit about what is going to be in Extreme or Ultramix 2 or anything down the line.
[SPEAKER_11]: Even if I did know, I don't know as far as you're concerned, okay?
[SPEAKER_11]: That's it, alright?
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_11]: Again.
[SPEAKER_11]: Uh, Sigurd, how are you?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm doing pretty good.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, so, no secret now, you're a Vivid member on The Freak.
[SPEAKER_11]: That I am.
[SPEAKER_11]: So that must mean... I work for Konami.
[SPEAKER_11]: And what exactly do you do at Konami?
[SPEAKER_09]: I...
[SPEAKER_09]: Go to work for Konami.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's what I do.
[SPEAKER_11]: Are you allowed to talk about what you do there?
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: I have no clue.
[SPEAKER_09]: And since I have no clue, I'm going to say I work for Konami.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_11]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: But, well, you make a lot of money, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: So you must be doing... No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_09]: I wish I made a lot of money.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: So fine.
[SPEAKER_11]: We can talk about what you do.
[SPEAKER_11]: But you do have to come in contact with DDR Games at some point through your job.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's why I have the Vivid membership.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, alright, fine.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, okay, let's talk about life before Konami then.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: You were on the show before.
[SPEAKER_11]: Are we getting a backstory?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, but you've been on the show before, but nobody was listening then.
[SPEAKER_11]: But now people care tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: Nobody cared then.
[SPEAKER_11]: People seem to care tonight suddenly about this show for some reason.
[SPEAKER_11]: I can't, for the life of me, imagine why.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_11]: What exactly were you doing before Konami?
[SPEAKER_09]: I worked for EV Games back in Kansas.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's right, I'm from the Midwest, so...
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I worked there, and then I came out here.
[SPEAKER_09]: The end, I guess.
[SPEAKER_09]: What possessed you to come out here?
[SPEAKER_09]: I had been wanting to move out here for a while.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, I'm originally way long time ago from here, but...
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I moved to Kansas, then I decided, hey, Kansas kind of sucks.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because it really does.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I moved out here.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_11]: And how, now, I don't know how much you can or can't say about this, but how did you get the job at Konami?
[SPEAKER_11]: Because a lot of people want to know this, like, oh, I want to work in video games, I want to play video games all day.
[SPEAKER_11]: How do you, and I'm sure that's exactly how you would describe some of the jobs there, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, sure, right.
[SPEAKER_11]: How...
[SPEAKER_11]: That's pretty much how it works.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, so you went to a company, and you applied, and who knew it?
[SPEAKER_11]: They hired you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_09]: What were they thinking?
[SPEAKER_11]: They obviously don't know me.
[SPEAKER_11]: Now, since you do come in contact with some DDR games, you guys like to have a little fun on some of the big message boards.
[SPEAKER_11]: Of course, the biggest one that comes to mind, the Freak, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: So you've been posting lately in the thread, and what do you hope to gain from posting in this thread?
[SPEAKER_09]: Um...
[SPEAKER_09]: I hope to gain just pretty much some laughter, because that's what I've been getting.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I think what it's really doing is creating a lot of hype for the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: And if you had been on the DDR Freak boards, gosh, maybe before Friday, because that's when we all started coming into contact with the boards, it was really not a very happy place.
[SPEAKER_09]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: I think everybody's starting to realize, you know,
[SPEAKER_09]: This is DDR, this is why we're here, and we're going to enjoy it.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, I mean, people seem to be having fun again, instead of just complaining.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, I notice people are having fun with it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Especially all the photoshops.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh my god, the photoshops.
[SPEAKER_09]: You were just in the bathroom, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_11]: Look at this, look at this.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura kicks our guest from Konami out of the chair so she can sit down.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's beautiful.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: She's motioning for Sigurd to come sit on her lap.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think you should go sit on her lap.
[SPEAKER_09]: I would, but you might punch me.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sigurd's afraid of being punched by DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_11]: Come on, DarkSakura loves you.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, tell him you love him.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like a hole in the head.
[SPEAKER_11]: I love you!
[SPEAKER_11]: I want fanboys!
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't want fangirls, I want fanboys!
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, I see.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, come on, step it up.
[SPEAKER_09]: You and I have something in common, I see.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: And if you've listened to this show for the past 105 episodes, you know what I'm talking about.
[SPEAKER_11]: But for those of you that are just listening tonight, I don't feel like telling it again.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, you'll just have to be in the dark.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, yeah, anyway.
[SPEAKER_09]: DDR Freakboards, what were we talking about?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, DDR Freakboards.
[SPEAKER_11]: This thing, it happens every time there's a new mix, Konami puts out.
[SPEAKER_11]: Every time there's a new mix.
[SPEAKER_11]: The first mix, Konomics, all the way back there to DDR Max, Max 2, there's this thing called Hints.
[SPEAKER_11]: And we all know that a while back, Jason Enos, like back during comics days, used to come on the thread and drop hints about what was going on.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then, you know, some other folks picked up the slack for some of the later games.
[SPEAKER_11]: Death Tricks, Cryptic.
[SPEAKER_11]: Some folks you guys don't even know, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_11]: You work there and you don't know who they are.
[SPEAKER_11]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, because if we knew who they were, they'd probably have a Vivid foot next to their name.
[SPEAKER_11]: So now it comes to the point where you post as a Vivid member, not just any Vivid member, but one that works for Konami, you post anything and somebody assumes it's a hint.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_11]: It has to be a hint, you must be talking about a new song.
[SPEAKER_11]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because that is what you want to do more than anything is spoil your NDA.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, I really want to get fired.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, these people, I'm glad they're picking up on that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, so, how many hints have you posted in the DDR Freak thread thus far?
[SPEAKER_09]: DDR Freak listeners, we, as a collective group, have posted exactly zero hints.
[SPEAKER_09]: Zero hints!
[SPEAKER_09]: But, but, maybe that was a hint.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, no, seriously, no.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, zero one was in seventh style, he was the, oh my gosh, oh my gosh, you guys, zero one's in it.
[SPEAKER_09]: But, yeah, I mean...
[SPEAKER_09]: I posted this earlier on the thread, you know.
[SPEAKER_09]: But it was ignored.
[SPEAKER_09]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have a flashy foot by my name.
[SPEAKER_09]: Listen to me.
[SPEAKER_11]: So wait, but I seem to recall that one of the other folks over there posted a picture and it had like a party collection bucket and like a Max 2 thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: It had like extreme samplers there.
[SPEAKER_11]: And, oh, would you hold up the extreme sampler for the camera?
[SPEAKER_11]: Can you do that?
[SPEAKER_09]: Somebody else can, or I guess I can.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, we'll have to see.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'll do it during the break.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, we'll do it during the break.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll do it during the break.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because it's like way over by the camera, and I don't feel like going by the camera.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, you can hold that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, hold that.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's the same size.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's not it.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's something else.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's close enough.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: But yeah, that picture.
[SPEAKER_11]: Is that a porno you're holding up, or what?
[SPEAKER_11]: A Fahrenheit 911.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, that picture, you know, with the party collection bucket and all that?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was a picture with the party collection book and whatever else.
[SPEAKER_09]: I said, it has nothing to do with anything.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's the V rare.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_11]: So that picture with the party collection and the tip jar and everything, that's basically just you guys showing off that you have a humongous internet penis right now and you're not afraid to whip it out.
[SPEAKER_11]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're very family oriented.
[SPEAKER_11]: Just curious.
[SPEAKER_11]: So the picture meant nothing.
[SPEAKER_11]: There are no hidden clues in that picture.
[SPEAKER_11]: As a friend, you're swearing to me there is no hidden meaning in that picture because we go way back.
[SPEAKER_11]: We go way back.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm holding it up right now.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, you are holding it up?
[SPEAKER_11]: Stop it!
[SPEAKER_11]: Now you're even fucking with me!
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: I swear that there were no hints.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now, granted, you guys can't see me, so I could be crossing my fingers or something.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, stop.
[SPEAKER_09]: But, no, I said on the boards, you guys will figure out when we are actually giving hints.
[SPEAKER_09]: If I say we're not, we probably aren't.
[SPEAKER_09]: If I say we aren't,
[SPEAKER_09]: We could be.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's what keeps it fun.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, but seriously, there's no hints.
[SPEAKER_09]: Seriously, in that picture, there are no hints.
[SPEAKER_11]: When the hints start, you guys will know, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: When the hints start, you will know.
[SPEAKER_11]: And does that mean you're going to give us a hint tonight?
[SPEAKER_11]: No.
[SPEAKER_09]: Right.
[SPEAKER_09]: No.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm sorry, guys.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know that you guys are hoping to come on here and hope for a hint, but...
[SPEAKER_11]: because there are these things called the Dawn Disclosure Agreements.
[SPEAKER_11]: He can only say what he's allowed to say and we're not allowed to say anything else.
[SPEAKER_11]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_11]: We got the song and that's enough for me right now.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's more than enough.
[SPEAKER_11]: So certainly we can't give out any more hints.
[SPEAKER_11]: Certainly I couldn't give out anything else because I don't know what the hell else is in the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: So apparently there's porn in this, Mitch.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, was that a hint?
[SPEAKER_09]: That could have been a hint.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is it erotic?
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh my gosh!
[SPEAKER_09]: Erotic's in it!
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_11]: I did not know it was him.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was reading through the thread, I'm like, who's that guy?
[SPEAKER_11]: And I didn't even realize it was him.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's how secretive you've been being on there.
[SPEAKER_11]: I didn't even know it was you, but of course I was just being stupid.
[SPEAKER_09]: People who know me, there's two dead giveaways.
[SPEAKER_09]: One, I talked about my hair in the picture.
[SPEAKER_09]: I always talk about my hair, because I love it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Two, I said sadness.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's another trademark of me.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, sadness, I should have known.
[SPEAKER_11]: I should have known.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, guys, I think what we're going to do now is I think we're going to take one quick break here, and then I think we're going to do a Mamani match game, maybe.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's do the cage match now, actually.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's do that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's drag this out as long as possible here.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anything else you want to say to your adoring boys and possible fangirls out there, Sigurd?
[SPEAKER_11]: Just keep reading, and we'll be posting stuff as we normally do, and love me, please.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: So show Sigurd a little more love, and maybe he'll start dropping those hints later, if you'll show him some love.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, as soon as I queue it up here, we're going to get into the Orange Launch Radio cage match.
[SPEAKER_11]: The cage match, for you guys that have never participated before, you need to be in our chat room, www.orangelaunchradio.com, click on chat.
[SPEAKER_13]: All three songs in their completeness because there's so many new people.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm actually thinking, I think we ought to, since there's so many new people, I think we ought to make an exception tonight and play the entirety winner from last week.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because it is a really good song.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, either way.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_11]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_11]: So we're going to do that.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're going to be special because it was Loki's winner.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyway, the way the Cage Match works, we pick three songs, each host picks a song, and they're usually big dance hits or guitar hits or something.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're kind of songs that we think may make good Bomani selections, or we just think they're really cool and we want to play them for you guys.
[SPEAKER_11]: You guys vote.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or we want to torture you sometimes.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sometimes we want to torture you, like when Jamie brings J-Lo.
[SPEAKER_02]: I should have picked Britney Spears this week.
[SPEAKER_11]: Or Britney.
[SPEAKER_11]: But the thing is, you're going to pick your favorite of the three songs, and that winning song goes into rotation all week long here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: So there's definitely a prize to be won here.
[SPEAKER_11]: Now, last week's winner is actually pretty cool because it's a remix done by our very own Loki.
[SPEAKER_11]: And he remixed this song, you might know it from DDR, called Ecstasy.
[SPEAKER_11]: And it is an excellent remix.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's won two weeks now.
[SPEAKER_11]: And if it wins for four, we're going to have to retire it, so it's halfway there.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's see if it adds one more week on.
[SPEAKER_11]: But oh yeah, I've got to have the cage match music, huh?
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, last week in the Orange Lounge Radio Cage Match... Alright, last week in the Orange Lounge Radio Cage Match, Loki won with his pick, it's Ecstasy.
[SPEAKER_11]: And what did you remix this with here?
[SPEAKER_11]: Explain what a mash mix is real fast.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, if you're listening to most of the stuff that's out there, it's crap.
[SPEAKER_13]: But, uh, you know, MashMix is just basically just, um, taking two songs, not necessarily going, um, you're basically cutting loops and, you know, remixing it that way with loops.
[SPEAKER_13]: But, the problem with a lot of people is it's gotten a really bad rap because, you know, people just throw one song on top of it and another, you know, basically mixing it in gold wave.
[SPEAKER_13]: It sounds like utter crap.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, hopefully, you know, this stuff's a little bit better than crap.
[SPEAKER_11]: This song should be in DDR.
[SPEAKER_11]: End of story.
[SPEAKER_11]: I seriously think this song should be in DDR.
[SPEAKER_13]: Eh, it's okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: But anyways, yeah, this is remixed with the actual trance artists that got me into the whole genre in the first place.
[SPEAKER_13]: Tomski, with his song 14 Hours to Save the Earth, one of the only two songs he's ever done, the other one being Love Will Come, and he was pretty popular back in the end of the 90s, beginning 2000s, and he just kind of doesn't really make anything anymore, just some remixes, but you'll basically see him a lot with the Disco Citizens and...
[SPEAKER_13]: Decane, and also you see stuff with Dan Johnson and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_13]: He kind of hangs around with that clique.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, here it is.
[SPEAKER_11]: Less talking, more playing.
[SPEAKER_11]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_11]: Atomski vs. D-Complex with Ecstasy.
[SPEAKER_11]: 14 hours, club mix.
[SPEAKER_11]: Enjoy.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, that was song number one in tonight's Cage Match, Ecstasy, the 14 Hours Club Mix, and I think it's hilarious, because the people who can't hear the show right now are just in our chat room, and they can only see what we're posting, and I posted, you know, as I always do every week when we play the Cage Match songs, I posted, song one, Ecstasy, 14 Hours Club Mix, and somebody's like, oh my god, they're announcing the song list!
[SPEAKER_11]: Awesome, awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, no, that is not a song that's going to be extreme.
[SPEAKER_11]: That was a fan song, and it's song number one you can vote for tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, song number two you can vote for tonight is brought to us by DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_11]: What did you pick tonight?
[SPEAKER_02]: I picked something by someone.
[SPEAKER_11]: Do you remember what you picked, or do you need a reminder?
[SPEAKER_02]: I know what I picked.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yeah, it was low.
[SPEAKER_02]: With the moves.
[SPEAKER_02]: with, oh yeah, Astro Sexy.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Enflo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Enflo is awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: Enflo is in DDR.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes, Enflo is in DDR.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Enflo with Astro Sexy, song number two in tonight's page match.
[SPEAKER_11]: And if you like this, you can vote for it after we're all done here.
[SPEAKER_11]: Enjoy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Astro Nomikaru Expo, Expo, Enflo Zenkai Soshite Nexto Astro Nomikaru Expo, Expo, Expo, Expo Let's bring it back, back Astro Nomikaru Expo
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's start this story somewhere, with everything we haven't talked about, as it is, the two of us.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's start this science talk.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: And Flow Chemistry Yo, you know what I'm saying?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the global F
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, that was song number two in tonight's cage match, Mflow with Astro Sexy.
[SPEAKER_11]: And now we're going to go around and see what everybody thought of that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Take out the inner Simon Cowell in us.
[SPEAKER_11]: Jamie.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love Mflow.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now the whole, I have to say that the whole CD altogether isn't all that great, but it has some awesome tracks on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that one, it just, it keeps getting interesting, it keeps changing it up as the song goes on.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's a real progression through the whole song.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I really love it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'd have to say that one gets a 10.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not Taku yet, but you know, it still gets a 10.
[SPEAKER_11]: Angel.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, to me it sounds like Daft Punk kind of dancey so I really liked it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'd say 9.8.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know why I'm going to do that, but I guess it's because I can.
[SPEAKER_23]: Um, I'm sorry, Jamie, but it just stole a whole bunch from me.
[SPEAKER_23]: It was okay.
[SPEAKER_23]: It was a good song.
[SPEAKER_23]: I just like the style.
[SPEAKER_23]: Um, I don't even know if it's my style.
[SPEAKER_23]: I'm slow, actually, but...
[SPEAKER_23]: As far as the progression, I liked that.
[SPEAKER_23]: I thought it was interesting.
[SPEAKER_23]: I was like, what's going on here?
[SPEAKER_23]: Because I could tell something was changing in the song.
[SPEAKER_23]: And it's definitely got that, what do you say, dark punkishness.
[SPEAKER_23]: I was thinking of Move Your Feet that those guys do.
[SPEAKER_23]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_23]: You're a senior.
[SPEAKER_23]: So I'd have to give it maybe a 7.
[SPEAKER_23]: A good song, but not my style.
[SPEAKER_11]: Right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Good song, not your style.
7.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sigurd, what did you think?
[SPEAKER_09]: Cagematch?
[SPEAKER_09]: That's what we're doing?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, were you even listening to Emplo?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, because I remember commenting on it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've heard that song.
[SPEAKER_09]: I really like it.
[SPEAKER_09]: It gets a 9.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Is it going to be in DDR?
[SPEAKER_11]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, Loki.
[SPEAKER_11]: That was awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: I loved it. 10.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, you know, it wasn't that bad.
[SPEAKER_11]: Usually I'm kind of am with them flow, but that was fun.
[SPEAKER_11]: I give it an eight.
[SPEAKER_11]: Fun songs get eight.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_23]: Our other voter is in the show.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_11]: We're not the ones who get to pick the winner.
[SPEAKER_11]: You guys do out there in listener land, and I'm sure you have nothing better to do while waiting for your reign, which we will get to in like 15 minutes.
[SPEAKER_02]: We will make sure that you vote.
[SPEAKER_02]: The more votes, the faster we'll get there.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, we'll get it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, one more song.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's get to the last song then.
[SPEAKER_11]: My song, my pick this week is a group you also know from DDR, Four Strings.
[SPEAKER_11]: And they have a brand new single and it's called Turn It Around.
[SPEAKER_11]: And so that's going to be my pick for tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: So enjoy.
[SPEAKER_11]: This is Four Strings with Turn It Around.
[SPEAKER_07]: Turn it around baby Spend my time with me
[SPEAKER_07]: Turn it around baby Spend my time with me It's getting insane I know Let it not be true Turn it around baby
Thanks for watching!
Turn it around
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, welcome back, that was Four Strings with Turn It Around, the last song in tonight's Cage Match.
[SPEAKER_11]: Janie, what'd you think of that?
[SPEAKER_21]: It was... It was good.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was, it's trancy, you know, and I'm sort of, kind of, I mean, even though I went and downloaded this whole trance compilation, I'm just sort of tranced out a bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I've been listening to a lot of trance lately because of when I'm writing my stories, it's easier to listen to trance while I'm writing.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was very good, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love four strings.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd have to give it about an eight and a half.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Andrew, what did you think of that one?
[SPEAKER_11]: Pirate.
[SPEAKER_11]: Our local pirate.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, he didn't vote in the last... Oh, he's gone.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, I've been in the bathroom for the past three songs.
[SPEAKER_15]: I have no idea what's going on.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_11]: Angel.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm stuck.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, hi.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jeez, I'd probably say...
[SPEAKER_03]: and Ace, because, I don't know, I like the tranciness, I could probably, I don't know, go into the club, and I have no idea where I'm going with this, never mind!
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, on 110?
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, I'm sorry, I missed that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Holly, it's either you or Holly.
[SPEAKER_23]: Hey, um, I like it a lot, I'm into trance, um, uplifting trance is, uh, kind of a newer, happier kind of thing that's going on, um, so for uplifting, I guess, I think it's categorized as that anyway, it's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_23]: I give it a 9.
[SPEAKER_23]: I'm into Darker Trance, but it's good.
[SPEAKER_09]: I heard that song earlier today.
[SPEAKER_09]: I really don't like it, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's not as good as Diving, which might be on Xtreme, except it's already been announced.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think it is on Xtreme, Sigurd.
[SPEAKER_11]: Even I do that, and I don't work for them.
[SPEAKER_09]: I give it a 4.
[SPEAKER_11]: Aw, you suck.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_11]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was pretty good, but not as good as that trance remix that's on DDR Extreme.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh!
[SPEAKER_13]: Of another song.
[SPEAKER_13]: Another song!
[SPEAKER_13]: There will be a trance remix of another song!
[SPEAKER_13]: Uh, oh, where were we?
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm gonna give that a, um...
[SPEAKER_13]: No, I can't do that.
[SPEAKER_13]: That would be too obvious.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm going to give that a 7.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm right here.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think it's really a great song, even though it is a little bit repetitive.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I love it.
9.
[SPEAKER_11]: Is that a 9 in... Oh, a 9.5?
[SPEAKER_02]: Is that a 9 in the German sense? 9!
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, let's recap and then you guys can vote.
[SPEAKER_11]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_11]: And remember, you can only vote through private message.
[SPEAKER_11]: If you post something public in the chatroom, it is not counted.
[SPEAKER_11]: You have to send a private message to Sky.
[SPEAKER_11]: Do not flood the chatroom with your vote or I will come over there and punch you.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have to get the paddle and spank.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_11]: Song number one, Ecstasy, 14 Hours Club Mix.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, song number two tonight is M-Flow with Astro Sexy Song number three in tonight's cage match is Four Strings with Turn It Around
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, there you go.
[SPEAKER_11]: Send your vote over private message to Sky, and I'm going to type in the chat room how to do that real fast here.
[SPEAKER_11]: Are you okay there, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_11]: Do you need to regulate something in the chat room?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, just make sure all of you in the chat room do not try to send anything to Bimonicade.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is the name that we're all using.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's our personal slut name.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've been humping it all night.
[SPEAKER_11]: Secret's been on there, but it's actually our machine.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was on it too.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh yeah, you were on there too, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was on there too, and Andrew was on there for a little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't send anything to BinMoneyCade.
[SPEAKER_02]: No DCC chat, no nothing.
[SPEAKER_11]: Please don't initiate DCC chats, because that's not the way we can do the votes.
[SPEAKER_11]: Just double-click to open up a window, and it'll work that way.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll send the message to Sky.
[SPEAKER_13]: You're talking to my arcade cabinet, okay?
[SPEAKER_13]: It will not respond back or accept any files.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's merely there for arcade enjoyment.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm actually going to open up the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're very close to playing your reign.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think I just want to get it done and over with so that, you know, folks will stop bugging me about it.
[SPEAKER_22]: But I do want to open up... Huh?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, I want to get some opinions on DDR Extreme thus far.
[SPEAKER_11]: So Skype...
[SPEAKER_11]: Hello, you are on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_11]: Can you hear us?
[SPEAKER_20]: Hey, Skye's up.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, I can.
[SPEAKER_11]: You're dropping out, dude.
[SPEAKER_11]: Do you have porno torrents going?
[SPEAKER_11]: You gotta close them.
[SPEAKER_20]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_20]: Don't have any going.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: You're very spotty right now, though.
[SPEAKER_11]: Make sure, uh... You okay?
[SPEAKER_11]: Can you hear me fine?
[SPEAKER_11]: Aw, we lost him.
[SPEAKER_07]: Aw.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's a bummer.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, I'll try it one more time.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll see if we can get somebody in here.
[SPEAKER_11]: Aw.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's what happens when you get the... Oh, we'll try one more time.
[SPEAKER_11]: Same person.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hi, you're on Orange Zone Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_11]: Can you hear me?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, we can hear you now.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, good.
[SPEAKER_20]: I think because I had AIM on, I was dropping out.
[SPEAKER_20]: Who is this?
[SPEAKER_11]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_11]: This is Richie.
[SPEAKER_20]: Hi, Richie.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey, Richie.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_11]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_20]: Hey, people.
[SPEAKER_20]: Just want to give out a few P's about Xtreme.
[SPEAKER_20]: I'm pretty excited for it to come out here to the U.S.
[SPEAKER_20]: Just going to check out the whole new itoy support, whatever they're going to have for it.
[SPEAKER_20]: but the main thing I'm mainly excited about is they're bringing Love Love Sugar to the US, so I heard about Love Love Sugar yes, I know, now the greatness of Noria shall be spread throughout this country there you go yes, okay, I'm not ashamed to admit it, I am a Noria fanboy right I want her to have my children
[SPEAKER_11]: Richie, do you have anything you want to say to us for withholding on this Your Rain thing for like two hours now for some people?
[SPEAKER_11]: Are we jerks?
[SPEAKER_11]: Is this what you'd expect from us?
[SPEAKER_20]: Well, I mean, just be patient, you know?
[SPEAKER_20]: I mean, just because we're going to play a new song doesn't mean we're going to play it right at the beginning of the show.
[SPEAKER_20]: And for the people who keep asking us to drop hints about what song is going to be on Xtreme or what new songs, you know,
[SPEAKER_20]: They can't say anything.
[SPEAKER_20]: It's the same thing.
[SPEAKER_20]: Disclosure.
[SPEAKER_20]: Disclosure thing that they have.
[SPEAKER_11]: So basically you're saying, you know what, there's a reason you're not getting hints yet.
[SPEAKER_11]: There's rules.
[SPEAKER_11]: The man.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's the man.
[SPEAKER_11]: Blame it on the man.
[SPEAKER_20]: I know.
[SPEAKER_20]: All I have to say is they'll tell you when they can tell you.
[SPEAKER_20]: So, you know, just wait up.
[SPEAKER_20]: We'll be good.
[SPEAKER_20]: Good things come to people who wait.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, well thanks for calling.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, have a good one.
[SPEAKER_11]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_11]: That was fun.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm glad to hear from him.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'll give the other folks a chance to call just a minute here.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, yeah, we're going to do that debut of your reign, and then we'll go to Bomani Match Game.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think we haven't done that in a while, so I want to get to that.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then we're going to go to the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're going to have to kind of make it fast this week, though.
[SPEAKER_11]: We may have to limit our chatroom FUs, especially with so many people listening.
[SPEAKER_02]: We are going to guard our angst for you.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Again, if you guys have friends that are trying to get in and listen to the show and they can't get in right now, we will play the song again after the show at 9.40.
[SPEAKER_11]: And there might be other surprises, too, at that time.
[SPEAKER_11]: So stay tuned, and we'll get that for you after the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: For anyone listening in the chat room, please make an announcement for us that we will be playing the song again after the show.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, yes, we'll play it again at 940 so those that weren't able to get in now can get in.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, nobody else is calling on Skype line, so I think maybe it's about time for us to get to it.
[SPEAKER_02]: You've waited long enough.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, you guys have waited long enough.
[SPEAKER_11]: But first, I want to just give some shout-outs about this because I do definitely want to thank the folks at DDRSpot.com.
[SPEAKER_11]: I haven't said their name enough tonight, but they have helped us out in getting this premiere for you guys.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you very much to the staff at DDRSpot.com.
[SPEAKER_11]: Also, the KDEA team.
[SPEAKER_11]: has been very helpful.
[SPEAKER_11]: Some of our folks at Konami.
[SPEAKER_11]: So Sigurd, give them big kisses and hugs for us here at Orange Lounge for getting this for us.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: And just thanks a lot to you guys because, you know, it helped us get a lot of exposure.
[SPEAKER_11]: We've been doing this radio show for about two years now.
[SPEAKER_11]: And some folks are just finding out about us tonight, even though we've been doing it for two years.
[SPEAKER_11]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_11]: It may not be your cup of tea, but hey, thanks for checking us out.
[SPEAKER_11]: But if you did like us, we do the same shit every week.
[SPEAKER_11]: Every Sunday we do our talk.
[SPEAKER_11]: Some weeks we don't have a song to be teasing, so it's even crazier.
[SPEAKER_13]: Thank God you weren't here for the show where I sang.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: That was bad enough.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're staying in?
[SPEAKER_11]: We do have Karaoke Revolution 2 we've still got to cover at some point.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, all right.
[SPEAKER_02]: But seriously, also keep in mind we've got our remix show on Monday, Diversion.
[SPEAKER_14]: Mm-hmm, definitely.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which Rob is gracious and has fun with.
[SPEAKER_20]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then my show is on Tuesday where if you're hanging out in our chat room, then whatever you request, Bimani or not, if I have it, I'll play it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you can even send it to me if you really want to hear it broadcast on the show.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: As long as I don't think it's a piece of crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm flexible.
[SPEAKER_11]: Don't suck.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll play it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Maybe you'll play your reign again.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_11]: Maybe we can work that out.
[SPEAKER_22]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then Wednesday, coming back very soon, Vanilla Sky, my show where we talk about random video game stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: We just have to retool it a little bit.
[SPEAKER_11]: But hopefully soon.
[SPEAKER_11]: I might do something this week.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: And maybe sometime in the future, I'll do my show.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's a very, very, very...
[SPEAKER_13]: There's a .5 chance, somewhere around the 99 area Cut it out, cut it out Alright, anything else anybody wants to say before we do it?
[SPEAKER_11]: This is our big moment you guys, we're never going to have this captive audience ever again So anybody want to say anything?
[SPEAKER_11]: I have an important announcement Yes I like alcohol And I like meat Does anybody need to come out of the closet here on the show?
[SPEAKER_11]: Loki just, oh, Loki is actually running in the closet.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_13]: Um, yeah, I have something.
[SPEAKER_13]: Rob?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_13]: What?
[SPEAKER_13]: Rob?
[SPEAKER_10]: Rob?
[SPEAKER_10]: What?
[SPEAKER_10]: We are forgetting the... Oh, Jesus.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was scary.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was in unison.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're getting restless.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're about to punch us.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're about to punch us in the face.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_11]: Forget it, forget it, alright.
[SPEAKER_21]: I love you.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, you guys ready?
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm ready.
[SPEAKER_11]: You ready to hear this?
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, we are going to do right now the world debut of Your Rain, The Rage Mix.
[SPEAKER_11]: So enjoy everybody.
[SPEAKER_11]: Your Rain, The Rage Mix, made possible by www.orangeloungeradio.com and www.ddrspot.com.
[SPEAKER_11]: Enjoy.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_11]: That was sexy!
[SPEAKER_11]: I can't believe people have been waiting like two and a half hours for that one minute song.
[SPEAKER_11]: But there it is.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's actually a minute twenty-nine is what that song clocks in as.
[SPEAKER_11]: What did you guys think, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_02]: It was sexy.
[SPEAKER_02]: I still like the original better.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it was sexy.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was hot.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was very hot.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like, slow.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's my favorite Akira song, hands down.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's my favorite Yamaoka song, hands down.
Cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, I agree.
[SPEAKER_11]: What do you guys think?
[SPEAKER_11]: Andrew, you haven't really been, I don't know how much you've been following this fandom or how big a DDR fanboy you are, but what did you think of that?
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, I like that song.
[SPEAKER_15]: I think it's going to be pretty interesting to play.
[SPEAKER_15]: It sounds slow as hell, so I'm definitely going to have to bar-rape that at like 5x or something when I play that.
[SPEAKER_15]: Or excuse me, chair-rape that at home, I guess.
[SPEAKER_15]: But yeah, that sounds pretty good.
[SPEAKER_15]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_15]: It sounds interesting.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, Angel.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, like he just said, I'm totally going to have to speed mod that because I really suck at slow songs.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I speed mod.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know if that makes me a loser or not, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: Since I call myself DDR Angel, maybe I shouldn't speed mod anymore.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, I'm not funny.
[SPEAKER_23]: DDRholic.
[SPEAKER_23]: I can see Wendell freestyling to this right now.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's a very freestyling song.
[SPEAKER_23]: I can see the...
[SPEAKER_23]: I can see the butt shots and the kisses and everything.
[SPEAKER_11]: The video is great.
[SPEAKER_11]: We were able to actually see the video at E3 and play the song and the steps.
[SPEAKER_11]: The steps were pretty good, I gotta say.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think it was only like a six, but it was fun.
[SPEAKER_11]: The video, they made a custom video for it based around Silent Hill characters.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I gotta say, you guys, if you haven't looked at our picture gallery... It was a good video.
[SPEAKER_11]: Look at the picture gallery on our website.
[SPEAKER_11]: Just sign up for our website.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's free.
[SPEAKER_11]: We don't send you spam.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sign up for the website, and there's pictures.
[SPEAKER_11]: Dark Sakura has a gallery.
[SPEAKER_11]: I have a gallery, and...
[SPEAKER_11]: Sigurd even has a gallery on there.
[SPEAKER_11]: It says Mikla Tavit.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's actually Sigurd's photo gallery.
[SPEAKER_11]: All these pictures from E3.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also, just to expand upon the video information, in the video you'll see Cynthia from Silent Hill 4 and Henry from Silent Hill 4, and then some backup dancers, and they are not in Silent Hill 4.
[SPEAKER_09]: There is no dancing in Silent Hill 4.
[SPEAKER_02]: Unless you count writhing as dancing around when you're being eaten to death.
[SPEAKER_11]: You've actually seen the video for the song in a lot of these preview videos.
[SPEAKER_09]: I do wish, though, that there were dancing in Silent Hill, because then I could have Pyramid Head dance.
[SPEAKER_09]: That'd be the best thing ever.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would like to see the disembodied heads in the wheelchairs dance.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know some of you guys are probably dropping the stream right now, so I just wanted to say to you guys that are related to two hours ago that, hey, check us out again sometime.
[SPEAKER_11]: I hope you guys enjoyed it, and check us out again sometime, and thanks for stopping by Orange Orange Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: The show's not done.
[SPEAKER_11]: We still have an hour left to go, but I know there's some people that didn't want to have to sit through all this to hear that song, but you did, so thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: What does our resident arcade building genius think of it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because we didn't ask his opinion.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, what did you think, Loki?
[SPEAKER_11]: Eh.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, I think, you know, it's, uh, yeah, it's nice that Akira Yamaoka's doing songs and, you know, remixing them for DDR, but eh, I don't care for that stupid fucking, um, was it just shit?
[SPEAKER_13]: Um, I don't know, I don't care for that R&B crap that they have right there.
[SPEAKER_13]: Um, you know, give me a good, um, Akira Yamaoka hard, um, heavy metal, um,
[SPEAKER_13]: Fucking track from Contra That's the shit that I want in DDR You know, fucking hard heavy metal guitars Yelling, screaming, none of this I'm a survivor, I'm a survivor Look at me dancing, I'm a remix of a song It's really stupid, I want the heavy metal I mean, that's the shit that I want in there Fuck, if they had a, you know, a US Guitar Freaks That would be awesome There will not be a US Guitar Freaks, just
[SPEAKER_13]: They're making that clear.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think we're going to go to a break.
[SPEAKER_11]: And those of you guys that wanted to drop, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_11]: So the other people can get in.
[SPEAKER_11]: Remember, we are going to play the song again a little later.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're going to do a Bonnie match game when we come back.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's do that.
[SPEAKER_11]: It'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay, match game.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, we're going to do that.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I'm going to tell you guys who won the cage match.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm going to tally up those votes, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to do something really cool during the break.
[SPEAKER_11]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Fold my laundry.
[SPEAKER_11]: Have fun.
[SPEAKER_11]: And in this break, I think we're actually going to play songs from Max 2 USA.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think that'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_11]: So we're going to play some Max 2 USA songs.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because, you know...
[SPEAKER_11]: I feel like hearing them.
[SPEAKER_11]: Don't you guys feel like hearing them?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah!
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, sure, alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, so let's hear those songs, and we'll be back.
[SPEAKER_07]: I heard you were alone
I heard for the first time I knew we were meant to be
[SPEAKER_21]: Will I ever love you again?
[SPEAKER_21]: Will we be together again?
[SPEAKER_07]: Thought the love we had was strong
[SPEAKER_07]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_07]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft
[SPEAKER_07]: Take me away, millions of miles away from here Take me away, find a place for you and me You're taking me higher, high as I could be Take me away
Forever you and me Take me away
[SPEAKER_19]: Hey, I'm happy.
[SPEAKER_11]: A lot of you guys decided to stay on.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you guys for listening to us and supporting us.
[SPEAKER_11]: That makes me a happy boy.
[SPEAKER_11]: You're happy!
[SPEAKER_11]: This is the precursor to Mad Libs, honestly, if you think about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: basically we have two contestants in this case we're going to have somebody from one of our listeners call in on the skype line and then our newest guest on the show be our contestants basically you're going to be read a sentence and at the end of it the one word will be replaced with a blank and you have to fill in the blank of course the object is as it's called the match game you have to match us while we think of something and no the answer is not propel alright
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Every game, the answer was always Propel.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I don't drink Propel anymore.
[SPEAKER_02]: Propel is no longer a sponsor of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're now sponsored by Dr. Atkins, even though he's dead.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know about that.
[SPEAKER_11]: I can't say I'm into that, but okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because of that, there's less of me to be here.
[SPEAKER_02]: That and working my ass off.
[SPEAKER_11]: I've been trying to find the match game song clips because I lost it when I did my reinstall.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's been that long since we've done match game, I've got to say.
[SPEAKER_11]: We need a new match game theme.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, do the match game theme.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: Porn music.
[SPEAKER_02]: Play porn music because it's the same difference.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, then I'll find some porn music.
[SPEAKER_02]: Play the Price is Right music.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't have the Price is Right music.
[SPEAKER_11]: Does everybody get a piece of paper and a pen?
[SPEAKER_11]: I hope you guys have that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Here, I'll play some erotic, that's close enough.
[SPEAKER_11]: That'll work.
[SPEAKER_11]: This is our new match game theme song.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sex on the phone?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dear Rob.
[SPEAKER_11]: You might have to rip this up into little pieces.
[SPEAKER_11]: Now, Andrew doesn't get a piece of paper because he's going to be our contestant.
[SPEAKER_11]: And for contestant number two, we're going to open up the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_11]: And we'll see who gives us a call over on the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to write all over Hello Kitty's face.
[SPEAKER_11]: You should do that.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm hoping somebody will call on the skyline.
[SPEAKER_11]: If nobody calls on the skyline, we're going to have to take one of our chatters, and I don't know if I want to do that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Somebody's got to call us on the skyline.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, no, that piece of paper?
[SPEAKER_02]: It has clues as to what's in Extreme.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, shit.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm writing on the back of the Extreme V-Rare.
[SPEAKER_11]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_11]: I've got a copy list.
[SPEAKER_10]: It says milk, cheese, butter.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hello, can you hear us?
[SPEAKER_11]: You're on Orange Sounds Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hello, hello, hello.
[SPEAKER_11]: We cannot hear you.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sorry, buddy.
[SPEAKER_20]: Dismissed!
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, much better.
[SPEAKER_11]: Much better.
[SPEAKER_18]: Can you hear that?
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, I can hear that.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Turn it down.
[SPEAKER_11]: Turn it off.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_11]: Question number one.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know how the match game works, right, Richie?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know how this works.
[SPEAKER_11]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_11]: Question number one.
[SPEAKER_11]: Jamie was sick and tired.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know her also, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, you have to do this too, Loki.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura was getting sick and tired of all the children that would run in between her and the pad when she would try and play DDR.
[SPEAKER_11]: One day, one of them tripped right in front of her as they tried to run by.
[SPEAKER_11]: Jamie looked at the child and said, I've got one word for you, kid.
[SPEAKER_11]: Blank.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's when you play a song.
[SPEAKER_11]: You have to think of what would be in the blank.
[SPEAKER_11]: Now we can't.
[SPEAKER_11]: Jamie was getting sick and tired of all the children that would run in between her and the pad when she would try and play DDR.
[SPEAKER_11]: One day one of them tripped right in front of her as they tried to run by.
[SPEAKER_11]: Jamie looked at the child and said, I've got one word for you, kid.
[SPEAKER_07]: Blank.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Who's in ding?
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm in.
[SPEAKER_11]: Who's not in?
[SPEAKER_11]: Amy's still working.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're all still working.
[SPEAKER_07]: You got ten seconds.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Stop the music.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Richie, you still there with us?
[SPEAKER_20]: Yeah, I am.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Richie.
[SPEAKER_11]: Jamie was getting sick and tired of all the children that would run in between her and the pad when she would try and play DDR.
[SPEAKER_11]: One day, one of them tripped right in front of her as they tried to run by.
[SPEAKER_11]: Jamie looked at the child and said, I've got one word for you, kid.
[SPEAKER_11]: Owned.
[SPEAKER_11]: Owned!
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, Richie says owned.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's see what his opponent, Andrew, has to say.
[SPEAKER_11]: Andrew, I've got one word for you, kid.
[SPEAKER_11]: Owned.
[SPEAKER_11]: Jamey
[SPEAKER_11]: Oops is not a match.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_11]: DDRholic, what did you say?
[SPEAKER_23]: I'm not too creative today.
[SPEAKER_23]: Doctor.
[SPEAKER_11]: Doctor.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, that would be the nice thing to say.
[SPEAKER_11]: Unfortunately, the question was about Jamie.
[SPEAKER_11]: Everybody boo DDRholic.
[SPEAKER_11]: Boo.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wouldn't do that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Angel.
[SPEAKER_11]: I got one word for you, kid.
[SPEAKER_03]: Incomplete, DarkSakura, FashionEye Die!
[SPEAKER_03]: Die!
[SPEAKER_11]: Die!
[SPEAKER_11]: Die, alright, let's see Sigurd, you're playing knight I got one word, and maybe it's a hint, you guys No, you know what my battle cry is
[SPEAKER_11]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: Die of Death.
[SPEAKER_11]: Die of Death.
[SPEAKER_11]: I got one word for you, kid.
[SPEAKER_11]: Move your feet in extreme.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sigurd, I've got one word for you, kid.
[SPEAKER_09]: I came up with hardly anything, so I went with propel, even though he said it's not going to be it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Propel.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was propel.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, propel.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Loki, I've got one word for you, kid.
[SPEAKER_11]: Classic.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would say that.
[SPEAKER_11]: I said, I've got one word for you, kid.
[SPEAKER_11]: Abstinence.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's beautiful.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, no matches.
[SPEAKER_11]: No matches.
[SPEAKER_11]: Was that your second answer, Richie?
[SPEAKER_11]: What?
[SPEAKER_11]: Abstinence, was that your second answer, maybe?
[SPEAKER_20]: No, but more like...
[SPEAKER_20]: Haha, or I don't know.
[SPEAKER_20]: I'm not feeling creative tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, let's go on to question number two then.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, it's all tied up.
[SPEAKER_11]: Nothing, nothing.
[SPEAKER_11]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_11]: Second question.
[SPEAKER_11]: Get the music ready.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Loki was getting sick and tired of the fact that whenever Andrew went to Golf Land dressed as a pirate, he got all the crowds watching him play DDR.
[SPEAKER_11]: In order to upstage him and get the attention back, Loki decided to show up dressed as a blank.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh, this is going to be a stink.
[SPEAKER_07]: That music for some reason makes me want chicken.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm going to say Barwinch, because I think he'd make a very sexy one.
[SPEAKER_11]: Barwinch!
[SPEAKER_11]: Barwinch is Andrew's answer.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's see what the competitor Richie has to say.
[SPEAKER_11]: Dressed as a... French maid.
[SPEAKER_11]: French maid!
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, gee, this is a... That's a surprise coming from Richie, alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's see if we've got a match.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jamie, dressed as a... I finally saw this, so you'll laugh at me.
[SPEAKER_11]: Dressed as Divine's role as Edna in Hairspray Very nice, dressed as Divine, and nobody in the scene is ever going to get that joke, but that's okay.
[SPEAKER_23]: DJaholic, Loki's going to show up dressed as... An Oscar Mayer wiener!
[SPEAKER_11]: You're gay!
[SPEAKER_11]: And it's okay for me to say that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, Angel, show up... Okay, this is completely unlike me to say it, but I got to just because it's playing on words.
[SPEAKER_03]: I said he would dress up as a cock.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, not that one!
[SPEAKER_11]: Dressed up as a cock, alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sigurd.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sigurd, Loki, in order to upstage him, showed up dressed as a penis.
[SPEAKER_12]: Penis!
[SPEAKER_11]: You could have gotten two points going for the dick joke.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, Loki, what would you have to do?
[SPEAKER_13]: You'd have to show up dressed up as a... I'd have to dress up as Osama Bin Laden because he fucking rocks at DDR.
[SPEAKER_13]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_13]: Wow, okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, that would certainly get you attention.
[SPEAKER_13]: Or as a Nazi.
[SPEAKER_13]: A Nazi would rock, too.
[SPEAKER_13]: Or if we could combine them all, we would have to have, like, a white hood with a turban and then maybe a swastika painted on that.
[SPEAKER_13]: It could be like the, uh... The Antichrist.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know, the, um... Yeah, I... I don't get it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, whatever.
[SPEAKER_13]: That was stupid.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm sorry for wasting your 30 seconds.
[SPEAKER_11]: I said in order to upstage, Loki would show up dressed as a crack whore.
[SPEAKER_11]: And when in doubt, crack whore, you guys.
[SPEAKER_11]: Crack whore.
[SPEAKER_11]: Universal joke.
[SPEAKER_11]: But then I'd just blend into the crowd.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, I didn't think of that.
[SPEAKER_11]: You would.
[SPEAKER_11]: You'd totally bend into the crowd.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what I almost said?
[SPEAKER_02]: I almost said ninja.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because if you've ever gone to realultimatepower.net, don't you know that the mortal enemy of all ninjas are pirates?
[SPEAKER_13]: An L-shaped Tetris block.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be so rad.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_11]: One more, or no, I'm sorry, we have three more questions, actually.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're making a long one tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, because we haven't done it in a while.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, question number three.
[SPEAKER_11]: When Rob came home from work and saw Loki's main cabinet, the first thing he thought to himself was, gee, now that this thing is in my house, I can play nothing but blank all day long.
[SPEAKER_11]: It may not be the obvious choice.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, I can play nothing but blank all day long.
[SPEAKER_11]: Music.
Dude, that heavy breathing is so turning me on.
Alright.
I'm teasing you, Richie.
No.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Richie.
[SPEAKER_11]: Dang.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Richie's first this time, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: Richie, you're giving me a boner.
[SPEAKER_11]: Stop it.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_20]: Hey, Rob.
[SPEAKER_20]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_20]: No.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: What if Rob dressed up as a maid for you?
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wouldn't you even get like a little bit of a boner?
[SPEAKER_11]: Like a half boner?
[SPEAKER_11]: Like a bone?
[SPEAKER_11]: Um, no.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Not later, okay?
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, you're dropping out there, buddy.
[SPEAKER_11]: Careful.
[SPEAKER_11]: We gotta hear you for this answer, though, alright?
[SPEAKER_11]: Uh, here we go.
[SPEAKER_11]: G, now that this thing is in my house, I can play nothing but blank all day long.
[SPEAKER_11]: What?
[SPEAKER_20]: Okay, I was really gonna say, do you like horny bunnies, but then, I'm going to go with the chat room and say, um, let's see, girls panic.
[SPEAKER_11]: Gals panic.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, gals panic is what, um, what he said, Richie.
[SPEAKER_11]: Andrew?
[SPEAKER_11]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_11]: He's going to stay home and play blank all day long.
[SPEAKER_15]: I think he's going to stay home and play with himself, because that way Loki will be over here playing that, and that way he doesn't feel awkward when he's doing it, and Loki comes in and watches him like normal, so I think it'll be a lot more comfortable for Ron.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, so Andrew says he's just going to play with himself.
[SPEAKER_11]: Screw the machine, I'm going to play with myself.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, that's a very good answer, actually.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, Jamie, I'm going to stay home and play...
[SPEAKER_02]: BurgerTime.
[SPEAKER_11]: BurgerTime!
[SPEAKER_11]: The chat room was trying to get you guys to say it.
[SPEAKER_11]: BurgerTime.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, let's see.
[SPEAKER_11]: DDRholic.
[SPEAKER_23]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_23]: And by the way, for those of you who don't know, it's DDRcoholic, but I let Rob call me holic.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sorry, sorry.
[SPEAKER_11]: DDRcoholic.
[SPEAKER_23]: No, that's your name for me.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's your name for me.
[SPEAKER_23]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: I just like holic.
[SPEAKER_23]: Okay, I thought that Loki would love... Hold on, Richie.
[SPEAKER_11]: Enough with the heavy breathing.
[SPEAKER_11]: You're turning me on over here.
[SPEAKER_23]: I know I'm getting like all wet and stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wait, you are over 18, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, I am turning 21 this year.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, boy, that's hot.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_23]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_23]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_11]: Decided to stay home and play?
[SPEAKER_23]: And play Q-Bert.
[SPEAKER_23]: Q-Bert.
[SPEAKER_11]: Good answer.
[SPEAKER_11]: Q-Bert is a game I would play all day long.
[SPEAKER_11]: DDR Angel, what would you say?
[SPEAKER_03]: What were you going to call me?
[SPEAKER_11]: I almost said DDR Alcoholic again.
[SPEAKER_11]: DDR Angel.
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh, Pole Position.
[SPEAKER_11]: Pole Position!
[SPEAKER_11]: All these are great answers.
[SPEAKER_11]: I would play Pole Position all day long.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sigurd.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's only because I saw it today.
[SPEAKER_11]: Gals Panic.
[SPEAKER_11]: Gals Panic!
[SPEAKER_11]: That's a match!
[SPEAKER_11]: That's a match.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's a match for Richie!
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, Richie gets a point.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_11]: He decided to stay home and play.
[SPEAKER_13]: We wonder why we don't play this game all the time.
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyways, the answer would be Miss Mr. NudeWorld96.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's right, that's Miss World 96 with the boys in it instead of the girls.
[SPEAKER_11]: Good answer.
[SPEAKER_11]: My answer was, actually...
[SPEAKER_11]: My answer was I would stay home and play Miss World 96 Nude, actually.
[SPEAKER_11]: I also said that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Except I didn't say the Mr. version because that version is broken and it keeps crashing.
[SPEAKER_11]: So I just wanted to play the version that has the Move Your Body song.
[SPEAKER_11]: If you've never played Miss World 96 Nude, go download it right now.
[SPEAKER_11]: It rocks.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: That has been what I've been playing all day, too, honestly.
[SPEAKER_11]: I play that more than anything else.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Richie's up by one, but let's see.
[SPEAKER_11]: Two more questions to go.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ready?
[SPEAKER_11]: Ooh, this is a question about Sigurd.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sigurd can become very tired after having to be a Konami slave all day long.
[SPEAKER_11]: Luckily, Konami takes care of its employees and keeps Sigurd a very happy boy with all of the free blank.
[SPEAKER_11]: Music.
[SPEAKER_11]: Keep Sigurd a very happy boy with all of the free playing.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, I guess it's done.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, let's see what everybody thought.
[SPEAKER_11]: Starting off with our contestants.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sigurd can become very tired after having to be a Konami slave all day long.
[SPEAKER_11]: Luckily, Konami takes care of its employees and keeps Sigurd a very happy boy with all of the free... Andrew?
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm going to say something like caffeine or coffee or something like that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, free coffee, let's say.
[SPEAKER_11]: Free coffee.
[SPEAKER_11]: What?
[SPEAKER_11]: Free stimulants.
[SPEAKER_14]: Stimulants is good.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Richie, you there?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, I am.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're going to keep Sigurd a very happy boy with all of the free...
[SPEAKER_11]: Blowjobs.
[SPEAKER_11]: Blowjobs!
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, let's see if anybody gets a match.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, I didn't know, ooh, maybe I should go work for Konami.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Jamie, keeps him a happy boy with all of the free... Politary torture sessions.
[SPEAKER_11]: Politary torture sessions.
[SPEAKER_02]: That wouldn't make me happy!
[SPEAKER_11]: That would make me sad.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Keep Seegert a very happy boy with all of the free... Did you get a hug?
[SPEAKER_23]: How about Red Bull?
[SPEAKER_11]: Red Bull!
[SPEAKER_11]: That's a match!
[SPEAKER_11]: I think it's a match with the stimulants.
[SPEAKER_11]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, it's all tied up now.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's see, Angel.
[SPEAKER_11]: She's still writing.
[SPEAKER_11]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_11]: Shut up!
[SPEAKER_11]: All of the free... Junk.
[SPEAKER_11]: Junk!
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I didn't know what to put.
[SPEAKER_03]: I blame, I know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's alright, no worries.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, Sigurd, they keep you happy with all of the free.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, everybody would have thought I would say Akira Yamaoka anything, but no, I put Suikoden Yaoi fanfics.
[SPEAKER_09]: Suikoden Yaoi fanfics!
[SPEAKER_10]: That'd make me happy.
[SPEAKER_13]: Loki, all of the free.
[SPEAKER_13]: I said stimulants, and when I mean stimulants, I mean Akira Yamaoka porn.
[SPEAKER_13]: All of the home videos you don't get to see.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, I don't think that's a match though, sorry.
[SPEAKER_11]: A different kind of stimulant.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: My answer was, keep Sigrid a very happy boy with all of the free grape-feeding men in togas.
[SPEAKER_11]: That sounds pretty stimulating.
[SPEAKER_11]: Don't they have that room at Konami with all the great feeding men in the togas?
[SPEAKER_11]: They're still looking for hints.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh my god, Toga, that's the song.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_11]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_11]: Last question, guys.
[SPEAKER_11]: You ready?
[SPEAKER_20]: Alright, let's go.
[SPEAKER_11]: See, now this question isn't as funny anymore.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was going to do it before the big premiere, but just imagine we haven't done Your Rain yet, okay?
[SPEAKER_11]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_11]: When we told the listeners that it was all a big joke and we weren't actually going to play Your Rain tonight, the first thing the listeners did was blank the hosts.
[SPEAKER_11]: Music.
[SPEAKER_23]: Horn music.
[SPEAKER_07]: I swear this song makes me think it should also be for a chicken commercial.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, here it is.
[SPEAKER_11]: Tiebreaker.
[SPEAKER_11]: Here's your chance.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm going to start with Richie this time.
[SPEAKER_11]: Richie, when we told the listeners that it was all a big joke and we weren't actually going to play Your Rain tonight, the first thing the listeners did was blank the host.
[SPEAKER_20]: was to have spicy hot orgasms with the host.
[SPEAKER_11]: Spicy hot orgasms.
[SPEAKER_11]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_11]: Andrew, first thing they were going to do was what to the host?
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, tie them up and force them to listen to, like, Good Charlotte and Linkin Park, which is more punishing than anything I could think of.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's pretty bad.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's see if we get a match.
[SPEAKER_11]: Jamie, they decided to blank the host.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mooned.
[SPEAKER_11]: Mooned!
[SPEAKER_11]: They made us look at their minds.
[SPEAKER_23]: On their webcams.
[SPEAKER_11]: On their webcams.
[SPEAKER_11]: Good answer.
[SPEAKER_11]: Not a match.
[SPEAKER_11]: DDRholic.
[SPEAKER_23]: This might be close to the steamy orgasms.
[SPEAKER_23]: Queefed?
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think that's a little bit different.
[SPEAKER_11]: Are you sure?
[SPEAKER_11]: I think it's a little different, honey.
[SPEAKER_11]: A little different, honey.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: DDRangel.
[SPEAKER_03]: They decided to... Flash 90 bits on a webcam.
[SPEAKER_11]: Flash Naughty Bits on their webcam to the host.
[SPEAKER_11]: Nope, doesn't work.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sorry, bud.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sigurd.
[SPEAKER_11]: Richie.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes?
[SPEAKER_11]: Stop.
[SPEAKER_11]: You're making me... Later.
[SPEAKER_09]: Later.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was boring, and I just said murdered the host.
[SPEAKER_11]: Murdered.
[SPEAKER_11]: That was a good answer.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, Loki.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ban from DDR Freak.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be awfully hard.
[SPEAKER_11]: Considering one of our hosts is a moderator, that would be kind of hard.
[SPEAKER_11]: Unless it was April Fool's time again.
[SPEAKER_11]: That was a hilarious joke.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was funny.
[SPEAKER_11]: Did I ever tell you that?
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, Rob.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: What?
[SPEAKER_10]: Bitch, what?
[SPEAKER_10]: Fine, I won't tell you.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is it a hint?
[SPEAKER_10]: Is it a hint?
[SPEAKER_10]: The hint is the new ferret mix.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, here it is.
[SPEAKER_11]: My answer.
[SPEAKER_11]: When we told the listeners it was all a big joke and we weren't actually going to play your reign tonight, the first thing the listeners did was give money to the hosts because that's what I need them to do.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, bribe us.
[SPEAKER_11]: Give us money.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Webcam, yo, webcam.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's going to do it for tonight's match game.
[SPEAKER_11]: The final score, guys.
[SPEAKER_11]: Andrew, one point.
[SPEAKER_11]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_11]: Richie, one point, which means they tied.
[SPEAKER_11]: And you know what that means?
[SPEAKER_11]: You both lose!
[SPEAKER_11]: Good job!
[SPEAKER_10]: And now that you've lost the match game, how do you feel?
[SPEAKER_10]: What are you going to do now?
[SPEAKER_15]: I think I'm going to go back into the bathroom for another ten minutes.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_11]: You do that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Remember to flush.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Richie, thanks for playing, but you lose.
[SPEAKER_20]: Any last words you want to say?
[SPEAKER_20]: Amy, when I come on that show, I am going to stomp those bears down my pants.
[SPEAKER_20]: That is all.
[SPEAKER_11]: Bye, thank you.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, we've got it.
[SPEAKER_11]: We have not even talked about Bomani news yet, and we've still got the FUs of the week to do.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, Loki, Loki's going to cast, what, yes, Secret Dude.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just for the listeners that aren't in the chat room, there sounds like there will be hints coming next week, for real.
[SPEAKER_09]: Real ones.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, real ones.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, be on the lookout Alright, sounds good Let's get to some of our other Bomani news Loki's going to kind of run down what's been going on here
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, since we kind of bypassed that whole section of the show, because that's not important, no one really cares.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, first off, 2DX Red, or 2DX11, was testing now in Japan.
[SPEAKER_13]: Of course, we have the first, you know, song list that's out over there.
[SPEAKER_13]: There's some really cool stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: We've got a brand new DJ setup track, Spiritual Galaxy, a brand new 8th
[SPEAKER_13]: 8PLUS, which is Gigadelic, and then there's also a bunch of other tracks that are on there.
[SPEAKER_13]: New Walls track, which is pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_13]: Just a lot of cool stuff, check it out on Bomani Style, or Air Japan, or any other site that carries Bomani news, because you've got tons of info on it.
[SPEAKER_13]: New stuff that's going to be in there.
[SPEAKER_13]: They have a new ranking thing that's on the side of the screen as you're playing the game, which shows your combo versus the max combo on the machine, which I thought was pretty neat.
[SPEAKER_13]: And it's very red, hence the name 2DX Red.
[SPEAKER_13]: Of course, there'll be more songs coming out as time goes on right now, because with each test, of course, they add more songs to it and stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: Supposedly, there's going to be a lot more new songs coming, and it just looks pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_13]: Also, a Eurotrans-style version of Platonic X, which makes me sad.
[SPEAKER_13]: But yeah, and Secret of Love, new DJ Swan track, also did Gentle Stress, so that'd be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: Aside from that kind of stuff, well, I know there's a lot of Sim stuff...
[SPEAKER_11]: There was big sim news this week.
[SPEAKER_11]: If you've just been spending your time on the internet doing nothing but waiting for Extreme and Ultramix 2 hints, you're missing some of the stuff that's going on in the sim scene.
[SPEAKER_11]: And while that might be questionable or whatever, there is some good stuff going on.
[SPEAKER_11]: What is going on right now?
[SPEAKER_11]: There is some big stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: My god, there is a bunch of big stuff going on.
[SPEAKER_13]: First off, the best sim filmmakers on the face of the fucking earth.
[SPEAKER_13]: The FoonMix team, they released FoonMix Plus, which is awesome.
[SPEAKER_13]: You need to go check it out.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's 15 brand new songs.
[SPEAKER_13]: Most of the songs are from Diverse7, which is also out right now.
[SPEAKER_13]: Diverse7 is actually going to be featuring three different CDs with actual key sound files for BMS players.
[SPEAKER_13]: Basically, it's the Beatmania 2DX Sims.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I gotta say, these artists are fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_13]: They do really kick-ass Bomani remixes.
[SPEAKER_13]: and you need to go check them out.
[SPEAKER_13]: If you haven't heard of Diverse Systems before, you can definitely check them out.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's at www.diverse.jp and go check it out.
[SPEAKER_13]: They have an English page.
[SPEAKER_13]: You can order the CDs and they're really kick-ass.
[SPEAKER_13]: And they were actually the ones that were distributing Bounce Connected for a while there, so...
[SPEAKER_13]: Definitely check it out.
[SPEAKER_13]: But some of the cool stuff that's on there, you've got a few remixes I'd like to kind of just tease a little bit.
[SPEAKER_13]: Maybe we can play these in a break or something.
[SPEAKER_13]: There was some new ones.
[SPEAKER_13]: There was a new track by Offbeat, which did some really kick-ass stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: This would be the Holic remix called Holics.
[SPEAKER_13]: And it was pretty sweet, so let me just play a little bit in the middle here.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, that was pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_13]: And then, um, we've also got, there's a brand new, um, what was it, Innocent Walls remix, which, oh my god, it's fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_13]: Um, let's see here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Uh, let's see, ch-ch-ch.
[SPEAKER_13]: Just some really kick-ass stuff, and of course, they make awesome videos that go with everything.
[SPEAKER_13]: Steps are really good.
[SPEAKER_13]: Definitely go check it out.
[SPEAKER_13]: There's remixes of G2, Max 300, of course, but, you know, it's really awesome.
[SPEAKER_13]: There's remixes of 20 November, Brilliant to You, Holic, as I mentioned before, The Safari, just a bunch of really cool stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: Go check it out, and
[SPEAKER_13]: Since it is all in one pack, you do get the original Foon Mix as well, which there's tons of songs in that, all the same quality, just excellent.
[SPEAKER_13]: Go check that out.
[SPEAKER_13]: Aside from that, there's been more work being done on the front of starting to rip stuff from games.
[SPEAKER_13]: Actually, there's a guy working on ripping all the characters, the 3D characters from the PlayStation versions, and all the background graphics and stuff, and the progress so far has been really cool, and you can check that on DDR Maniacs.
[SPEAKER_13]: Step Mania Forums
[SPEAKER_13]: But that's pretty much what's going on right now.
[SPEAKER_13]: I've heard that there was going to be an Alpha 22 for Stepmania 3.9, but apparently not yet.
[SPEAKER_13]: But it's coming soon.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thanks for catching up on the news.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know we kind of got pushed aside because of all the other crap we got going on tonight, but there is other news going on out there.
[SPEAKER_11]: So thanks for bringing it up.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anybody want to comment on any of the news?
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, you guys are easy to please.
[SPEAKER_11]: Talkative bunch.
[SPEAKER_11]: Talkative bunch, aren't you?
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think what we're going to do now, actually, we'll take a quick break and we're going to play some songs.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, actually, I have to announce tonight's winner of the cage match.
[SPEAKER_11]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_11]: Tonight's winner of the cage match.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was actually kind of surprised by this, but Loki's remix has been dethroned and we have a new winner.
[SPEAKER_04]: ASTRO SEXY
[SPEAKER_11]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_11]: Good stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, so Mflow one tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think we're going to do it.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're going to take a...
[SPEAKER_11]: We're going to take a break, and we're actually going to play two tracks from FoonMix.
[SPEAKER_11]: I want to play the Max remix, because I think it's really good, and we're going to play the Safari, because I like that one.
[SPEAKER_11]: So I thought we'd play those for the guys.
[SPEAKER_13]: Those are pretty cool, yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're all good.
[SPEAKER_13]: They're all good, really.
[SPEAKER_13]: Really, my favorites of the new one have to be the Innocent Walls one.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, I'll take out... I'll put in Innocent Walls, too.
[SPEAKER_13]: The Innocent Walls one is fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, the guys from FoonMix did enter TourneyMix 5, but the entry that they picked was one of the worst ones that they did.
[SPEAKER_13]: But if they picked one of these, oh my god, it would have owned everybody.
[SPEAKER_13]: But whatever, you know, I'm sure they're not out to brag because they know they're kick-ass and they don't really need to prove it.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, yeah, rock.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, so we'll get that in there too then.
[SPEAKER_11]: I just got to remember, is that it?
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, sure is.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, then we'll do this song first, why don't we?
[SPEAKER_11]: We're going to do that Innocent Walls remix.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then when we come back, we are going to do the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_11]: However, we have to keep it fast tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: So we're going to run through everybody in the room.
[SPEAKER_11]: And unfortunately tonight, only selected chatroom FUs will be read.
[SPEAKER_11]: So if you send me a long one, not going to get read.
[SPEAKER_11]: So think of something really good if you have a good story, and I apologize in advance, but we are running on a limited schedule tonight, so keep them short.
[SPEAKER_11]: FUs from chatroom will be limited, but send those to Sky over private message.
[SPEAKER_11]: So here it is.
[SPEAKER_11]: Check it out.
[SPEAKER_11]: Some remix songs from the latest Foon Mix, starting off with an Innocent Walls vocal mix.
[SPEAKER_11]: Max remix, and then a guitar remix.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let me get the actual title.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hold on, because I want to be correct on this.
[SPEAKER_13]: This title of this remix here is called Made in Innocent.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's a short version by Onokin.
[SPEAKER_13]: Onokin, which fucking rocks, did P8107.
[SPEAKER_13]: Rumored to have a song in 2DX Red, but I think that's pretty much a rumor.
[SPEAKER_13]: It'd be awesome if he did, but just a rumor for now.
[SPEAKER_13]: So yeah, check it out.
[SPEAKER_13]: Awesome work.
[SPEAKER_11]: And don't forget, Your Rain will be back again at 9.40.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're going to play that again.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, anyway, here we go.
[SPEAKER_11]: Some stuff from Foomix.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll be back with the FUs of the Week.
You are saying Let's stay together You are saying Let's stay together
DarkSakura.com
Thank you.
Thanks for watching!
What should I do with my cuteness?
What should I do?
This randomness could only be brought to you by Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, we are a little bit random here on Orange Lawns Radio, if you haven't guessed.
[SPEAKER_21]: A little.
[SPEAKER_11]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_11]: A lot of guys stuck around after the Eurage thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: You like us.
[SPEAKER_02]: We appreciate you.
[SPEAKER_02]: You really like us.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, we do appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_02]: We like our listeners to stick with us because then we feel good about ourselves.
[SPEAKER_11]: We've been trying here, you guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: It validates us for the week.
[SPEAKER_11]: We think it's a fun thing to do on a Sunday night.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, you know, it's not like I'm going to church or anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not like we're getting paid for this.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, we don't get paid for this either.
[SPEAKER_02]: We pay for this.
[SPEAKER_11]: We do.
[SPEAKER_11]: With our souls!
[SPEAKER_11]: We have this whole buildup of angst and we need to have a big bad release of it or else we like explode.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, here we go then.
[SPEAKER_11]: Jamie, it's time to do the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_11]: You ready?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm ready, Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would like to give a big F you to the three root beers that I've had that facilitated that loud belch.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm normally not as unladylike.
[SPEAKER_02]: I usually am a lot more unladylike.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nah, really.
[SPEAKER_02]: A big F you to impatience, especially for people who drive.
[SPEAKER_02]: And another F you goes to ARC for not posting my financial aid stuff and certifying my loans so I can get my fucking money.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm being nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: F you to the freaking running out of time.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_11]: Loki, your turn.
[SPEAKER_13]: I fucking hate stupid skanky drivers who can't fucking drive.
[SPEAKER_13]: I had this stupid bitch last weekend still pissing me off.
[SPEAKER_13]: Fucking cut me off when I'm driving just to get behind a slow person that was in front of me.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh wow, guess what?
[SPEAKER_13]: You got to the intersection a whole half a second faster than I did.
[SPEAKER_13]: Good, now you can go fuck another sheep and have your next child.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: And then finally, because I'm going to keep this short, um, fuck you to sluts at my work who get higher up in the company about fucking your box.
[SPEAKER_13]: And openly admitting it and bragging about it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I fucking hate you and I will take you down.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I'm not talking about it in a good way.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_11]: My turn.
[SPEAKER_11]: And a few to myself for the fact that I'm paying about $13.95 a month to play Final Fantasy XI And I have touched it a whopping one time this whole week Because I found better things to do for once in my life For once in my life, no, because I found something even better than Ragnarok I went out and I went on a date this week, so that was something better to do, so...
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, that's finally.
[SPEAKER_11]: But that's all I'm going to say.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't want to talk too much because I might dig myself a hole.
[SPEAKER_11]: But anyway, I'm just glad I got out of the house.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_11]: Is that a hint?
[SPEAKER_11]: No.
[SPEAKER_11]: My other FU goes to that burning smell in my car.
[SPEAKER_11]: I thought I cracked my radiator or something.
[SPEAKER_11]: But actually, I just ran over a plastic bag and it wrapped itself around my pipe and caught itself on fire.
[SPEAKER_11]: So F you to people that leave plastic bags in the road.
[SPEAKER_11]: What the hell you do that for?
[SPEAKER_11]: Stupid.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's go to our other studio guests.
[SPEAKER_11]: Starting off with, who's got a microphone over there?
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, Mr. Andrew, what do you have to say?
[SPEAKER_11]: F you to what?
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, well I'd like to give a big fuck you to all the bar and speed mod haters out there.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'd just like to piss you guys off right now before I get started.
[SPEAKER_11]: I wanted to talk to you more about the bar raping thing tonight, but we just ran out of time.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'll come back.
[SPEAKER_11]: You gotta come back, alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: We ain't got time.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'd also like to give a big F you to everybody that lives in Glen Rose, Texas.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't care if I know you or not, but just that whole town needs to just be wiped off the map.
[SPEAKER_15]: And last but not least, if you're a friend that I told to listen tonight and you're not listening, fuck you guys.
[SPEAKER_15]: Don't ever talk to me again.
[SPEAKER_15]: If you are listening, I love you.
[SPEAKER_15]: In a platonic kind of way.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, that's all I got.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, very nice.
[SPEAKER_11]: Angel.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, I'm going to go through this real quick because I got one from Agus as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: He says, F you to sitting on my ass on a perfectly good Sunday doing nothing except for answering people's phone calls and they happen to be going to the wrong department.
[SPEAKER_03]: And he's the only one there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, I'd like to say a quick F you to the stoplight on Arden and Del Paso because it is the longest piece of crap I've ever waited on and it happened to be while I was trying to get over here.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'm going, okay, I can go now, really, I really want to get here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, because I'm like, you know, an Orange Lounge freak like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, next person.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, one more F you.
[SPEAKER_13]: Fuck you to Burger King for making me shit like crazy.
[SPEAKER_13]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_11]: TMI.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: DDR Coholic.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh, hey.
[SPEAKER_23]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_23]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_23]: I was going to originally start off by saying fuck you to not having any fuck you because I... I said fuck you.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yes, because I could never participate.
[SPEAKER_23]: I would have to pass the microphones.
[SPEAKER_23]: I don't have any fuck yous.
[SPEAKER_23]: I don't know what to say.
[SPEAKER_23]: But now I have a little something.
[SPEAKER_23]: I can say like, okay, fuck you to not having any good arcades anymore around town.
[SPEAKER_23]: Where are they?
[SPEAKER_23]: We should still build one, yeah.
[SPEAKER_23]: And then, fuck you to the post office thing that's at our apartment complex.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's like a mile away from my apartment.
[SPEAKER_23]: I have to actually drive to get there.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's a pain in the butt.
[SPEAKER_23]: And it's unbelievable.
[SPEAKER_23]: Our apartment complex is huge.
[SPEAKER_23]: And we're on the other side of the post office.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's all the way on one end of the complex.
[SPEAKER_23]: You could put it in the middle.
[SPEAKER_23]: No, they don't do that.
[SPEAKER_23]: They put it on one end.
[SPEAKER_23]: So anyway, fuck you to that.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sigurd!
[SPEAKER_09]: F you to relatives that start charging you rent after living there a month and you have to sleep in the kitchen.
[SPEAKER_20]: You're sleeping in the kitchen?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I'm sleeping in the kitchen.
[SPEAKER_09]: You are so Cinderella.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's horrible.
[SPEAKER_11]: I made that comparison the other night.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I didn't like it because that would mean I'd have to wear a dress or something.
[SPEAKER_09]: F you to the chatroom because it's funny.
[SPEAKER_09]: F you to people who read into what we say far too much and F you to your guys' crazy photoshop skills because
[SPEAKER_09]: It's really creepy, but funny, so keep it up.
[SPEAKER_11]: See, Konami employees are real people too, you guys.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, let's go to the chatroom FU, shall we?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I forgot another big one.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm very sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: And FU to not having time or money to go where I want to go and see who I want to see.
[SPEAKER_03]: One really quick one.
[SPEAKER_03]: FU to the post office for holding all of our mail because we're still trying to get forwards and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: That really sucks for three weeks now.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, you know, Miklatov or whatever the hell you go by now, don't stress out, just mellow out, be gentle.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have some gentle stress.
[SPEAKER_10]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, was that a hint?
[SPEAKER_11]: Was that a hint?
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god, Gentle Stress is in a version of DDR.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, here we go.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, this is going to be good.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm loving this first one already.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's go into the chatroom FUs.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're going to start a fight here tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: Tora would like to give an FU to Jamie, also known as DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why?
[SPEAKER_11]: Because she gave me warning points for no reason way back when.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, if I warn you, it's for a fucking reason.
[SPEAKER_02]: You did something wrong.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, keep in mind, you lose a freaking point a month.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's probably gone.
[SPEAKER_11]: How could you possibly piss off DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_11]: I could never imagine how you would make her mad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Look, you break the rules I warn your ass.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's that easy.
[SPEAKER_11]: Panda says, F you to my HDD with all my stuff for crashing on me when I needed it.
[SPEAKER_11]: John Field says, F you to PSO, Blue Burst, Hacker, Broom.
[SPEAKER_11]: Stop hacking this thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: Fancy Star Online.
[SPEAKER_02]: I haven't followed that game in years.
[SPEAKER_02]: Blue Burst is the one for PC.
[SPEAKER_11]: Unknown Gamer says, I want to say a big old F you to making me wait two hours to listen to your rain.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey, F you, buddy.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was going to be three.
[SPEAKER_11]: We were going to play it like the very last thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: We were being nice.
[SPEAKER_11]: Not my fault, you guys thought, because this show is from 6.30, 9.30, you'll be right at 6.30.
[SPEAKER_11]: Then what would we do with the rest of the show?
[SPEAKER_11]: What would we do with ourselves?
[SPEAKER_02]: It'd be the Listen to Rob Play With Himself show.
[SPEAKER_11]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_11]: At least we're better than G4.
[SPEAKER_11]: We are much better than G4.
[SPEAKER_11]: Absolutely right.
[SPEAKER_11]: At least the premiere wasn't on G4.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank your lucky stars.
[SPEAKER_03]: We got it first.
[SPEAKER_11]: El Mullet says F you to Pants.
[SPEAKER_11]: Damn Pants, the bane of all evil.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, fuck Pants.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, remember Pants was Rage?
[SPEAKER_23]: Ooh, Pants was Rage.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wizkid would like to say F you to old ladies who call the tech support line and yell at me because they're too dumb to understand what reboot means.
[SPEAKER_02]: How about boot to the ass?
[SPEAKER_02]: How do I reboot?
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: MJB would like to say, my FU of the week goes to my shitty internet for disconnecting me from Orange Lounge Radio, almost causing me to miss my FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we can't have that, can we?
[SPEAKER_11]: Any other week, you would have been okay with the cap thing, I swear.
[SPEAKER_11]: Tonight's just crazy.
[SPEAKER_11]: EvilMalke2DX says, FU to Aqua Teen Hunger Force ending next Sunday.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_11]: Jazz says, FU to me for leaving my cell phone on silent.
[SPEAKER_11]: I just found missed calls from two of my bestest friends.
[SPEAKER_11]: Rob, do you have brain cancer because you hiccup?
[SPEAKER_11]: Vandalus says, My FU is for the Sacramento Kings and their recent drama.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's like a friggin' soap opera full of spoiled millionaires.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, amen.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank God they're leaving.
[SPEAKER_11]: Now, now.
[SPEAKER_11]: Play nice.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, you're going to start another fight here.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think the people who get bent out of shape over sports rivalries really need to get a life.
[SPEAKER_11]: One more last minute one here.
[SPEAKER_11]: Arkara says, F you to Andrew for not giving me my sexiness.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know what that's supposed to mean.
[SPEAKER_11]: Is that a hidden message?
[SPEAKER_11]: Wait about two weeks.
[SPEAKER_15]: Do you need to take this offline?
[SPEAKER_15]: No, I think we're all good.
[SPEAKER_15]: Just give me two weeks or something.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's on.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: I haven't decided yet.
[SPEAKER_11]: Is somebody going to get served?
[SPEAKER_15]: I think Sucker's going to get chronicled.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's what's up.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Guys...
[SPEAKER_11]: It's the end of the show.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're already here.
[SPEAKER_11]: Cry.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know, cry.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, thank you guys for listening and making it a great show tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: I hope we don't need exclusives to make you guys keep listening to us.
[SPEAKER_02]: We are exclusive.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hopefully you liked it and you'll come back, but if not, hey, thanks for wasting three hours with us tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: I hope you liked the song.
[SPEAKER_11]: But we're going to go around and get everybody's final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's start off with D.D.
[SPEAKER_11]: Archaholic.
[SPEAKER_11]: DD Alcoholic, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's like Jerry Springer's final thought.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's your final thought.
[SPEAKER_23]: Um, well, quick shout out to my boyfriend, Jason, DarkChild999.
[SPEAKER_23]: I don't know if he's listening or not.
[SPEAKER_23]: He might be.
[SPEAKER_23]: Uh, and final thought, uh, chewing gum that tastes like grape is really good.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Um, Angel, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, I carry a mocha because I can.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: Uh,
[SPEAKER_15]: Hey, Akira is a good thing.
[SPEAKER_15]: Andrew.
[SPEAKER_15]: I just want to say thanks for having me on the show.
[SPEAKER_15]: I hope to be back in the future and this place kicks ass.
[SPEAKER_15]: But there's way too much fucking Pokemon in here, man.
[SPEAKER_15]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's creeping me the hell out.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hold that thought.
[SPEAKER_11]: Just one minute.
[SPEAKER_02]: And this is the time when we fill air while Rob goes away.
[SPEAKER_02]: Better than filling air for three hours while...
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm gonna put that on the cam, you guys.
[SPEAKER_13]: There's those moments that are really cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's kind of like watching bad movies.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, eventually you'll get to a moment that's really funny and stuff.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's like watching Xanadu.
[SPEAKER_13]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, I've never seen that, so that doesn't make any sense to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like watching Battle Royale 2.
[SPEAKER_13]: God, that movie sucked.
[SPEAKER_13]: Don't see Battle Royale 2.
[SPEAKER_13]: Instead, download the camera rip of Kashan, because that fucking rocks.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: and my final thought is please come back and listen to us again even though we're not going to have any more premieres.
[SPEAKER_11]: Please come back and listen.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know, I didn't say, do I always have to go last?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: No, if it's a low-carb cookie.
[SPEAKER_11]: A low-carb cookie.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was such a disbeliever for this stupid Atkins diet because, you know, it's sort of what your body does before it dies.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it works.
[SPEAKER_02]: So maybe I'm going to die.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then I'll lose a lot of weight.
[SPEAKER_02]: My final thought is that Diet Hansen's root beer is the best thing in the world.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_11]: Second best thing in the world.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's lovely.
[SPEAKER_11]: Next to orgasms.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I do have to say that orgasms are very nice.
[SPEAKER_11]: They are.
[SPEAKER_02]: They should just sell canned orgasms.
[SPEAKER_11]: They should.
[SPEAKER_02]: For all those people who do.
[SPEAKER_11]: Orgasm array.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sigurd, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_09]: My final thought is I hope everybody liked the remix of Your Rain.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's really fun in DDR, so look forward to that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also look forward to this week when it sounds like we might really be giving clues out.
[SPEAKER_09]: So that's going to be cool, and thanks for listening to me whore myself out over the radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, and final word of the show.
[SPEAKER_11]: Are we going to give it to Andrew?
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, let's give it to Andrew.
[SPEAKER_11]: Just one word that sums up the entire show, but it can only be one word that sums everything up.
[SPEAKER_11]: Suckers.
[SPEAKER_19]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_19]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_19]: Orange Lounge Radio is hosted by DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_19]: If you'd like to leave us a comment, send us an email at orangeloungeradio at yahoo.com.
[SPEAKER_19]: And now, here's your fortune cookie message of the day.
[SPEAKER_07]: Music
[SPEAKER_07]: Star Trekkin' across the universe On the Star Trek Enterprise, I'm the Captain Kirk Star Trekkin' across the universe We'll be going forward, cause we can finally burn
[SPEAKER_00]: Life, Jim, but not as we know it, not as we know it, not as we know it, it's Life, Jim, but not as we know it, not as we know it, it happens There are klingons on the starboard bow, starboard bow, starboard bow There are klingons on the starboard bow, starboard bow Star Trekking Across the Universe On the Star Trek Enterprise, on the Star Trek Earth Star Trekking Across the Universe Only going forward
[SPEAKER_00]: It's life, Jim, but not as we know it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Not as we know it.
[SPEAKER_05]: There are Klingons on the starboard bow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Starboard bow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Starboard bow, Jim!
[SPEAKER_07]: Starship Captain James T. Jackson Ah, we come in peace.
[SPEAKER_08]: Shoot to kill.
[SPEAKER_08]: We come in peace.
[SPEAKER_08]: Shoot to kill, ma'am.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's worse than that.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's dead, Jim.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dead, Jim.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, it's life, Jim, but not as we know it, not as we know it, not as we know it.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's life, Jim, but not as we know it, not as we know it, Captain.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's sling-ons on the starboard bow, starboard bow, starboard bow.
There's sling-ons on the starboard bow.
[SPEAKER_08]: Creep them off, Jim!
[SPEAKER_08]: Star trekking across the universe.
[SPEAKER_08]: On the Captain Enterprise, on the Captain Kirk.
[SPEAKER_07]: Star trekking across the universe.
[SPEAKER_07]: Only going forward and things are getting worse.
[SPEAKER_00]: You kind of changed the laws of physics, laws of physics, laws of physics You kind of changed the laws of physics, laws of physics, Jim Oh, we come in peace, shoot to kill, shoot to kill, shoot to kill We come in peace, shoot to kill, Scotty beat me up It's worse than that, he's dead, Jim, dead, Jim, dead, Jim It's worse than that, he's dead, Jim, dead, Jim, dead Well, it's life, Jim, but not as we know it, not as we know it, not as we know it It's life, Jim, but not as we know it, not as we know it, Captain
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_19]: Thank you very much for listening, and we'll see you next week.
[SPEAKER_11]: The secret part of the show, the afterbirth where we do things that we couldn't do during the show And you know what guys?
[SPEAKER_11]: We haven't even really talked about this in the room, but there's one other little thing we want to play for you guys This is why it pays to listen Yes it does, and it's not DDR, it's not a DDR thing, but Secret wanted to share it with you guys anyway It is something that hasn't been heard by a lot of people yet The Silent Hill thing
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, we're going to actually do that?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, we're going to do that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, I'm a DDR fan and all, but I'm more a Silent Hill fan.
[SPEAKER_09]: We are going to play you a track from the US OST.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's one of the 13 special exclusive songs to the American OST.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's Waverer, Slide Mix.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, so this is sweet.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's a brand new US song, hasn't been heard yet, but we're going to play it for you guys.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's Waverer, and it's a Kiriyamaoka.
[SPEAKER_10]: See you again, that's why it pays to stay tuned to the end of the show.
[SPEAKER_11]: It pays to stay tuned.
[SPEAKER_11]: Enjoy.
[SPEAKER_11]: Whoops, sorry, technical difficulties, my bad.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's try that again.
[SPEAKER_11]: Here we go.
DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network
Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, that was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was from the Silent Hill U.S.
[SPEAKER_11]: soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_11]: I kind of like that.
[SPEAKER_11]: That was kind of... That's like your favorite one, Sigur?
[SPEAKER_09]: That is totally my favorite Akira Yamaoka song.
[SPEAKER_09]: The original version of that is kind of boring, but that one with the crazy singing, I was listening to it on BARD at night, going home from work, and I was seriously freaking out.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was the best.
[SPEAKER_11]: It sounds kind of porno, in a way.
[SPEAKER_02]: It does sound kind of porno.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just porno.
[SPEAKER_11]: I like it.
[SPEAKER_11]: We promised we were going to do it one more time, so if you're back on the stream, welcome to Orange Lounge Radio, and thanks for tuning in to us tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hope you catch our show next week when we shouldn't have these listening cap problems.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're going to play Your Rain one more time, you guys.
[SPEAKER_18]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_18]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm excited.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_11]: OrangeLawnsRadio.com and DDRspot.com are proud to present the world premiere, Your Rain, the Rage Mix.
[SPEAKER_11]: Enjoy.
[SPEAKER_07]: You touched my body once, it burned.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm waiting for a gentle rain, a gentle rain, a gentle you On the sidewalk of the city, on the streets just a whisper Busy people going nowhere, see me smoking the rain No compassion, nothing matters, my resistance is way
[SPEAKER_11]: OrangeLoungeRadio.com, bringing you along with DDRspot.com, the world premiere of Your Rain, the Rage Mix, for the second time.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hope you enjoyed that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, anything else you guys want to say?
[SPEAKER_11]: We kind of had all that take up our afterbirth.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm going home.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, you know what, I've got to drive Secret back to the bay, so I think I've got to keep this kind of short, because it's a long drive home, but that's alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't mind.
[SPEAKER_11]: And you've got a way home too, right Angel?
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, good.
[SPEAKER_11]: Cool, everything's set.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, Angel.
[SPEAKER_03]: Someone call me at kthx, bye.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because nobody ever calls me.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can call you names.
[SPEAKER_11]: I can call you names.
[SPEAKER_11]: On the phone!
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you want me to call you on the phone and call you names?
[SPEAKER_11]: Did you want to just give out your phone number over the air so that random strangers will call you?
[SPEAKER_10]: For a good time, call 555.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, Sigurd, what's up?
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, you guys have been patient.
[SPEAKER_11]: The chat room has been grilling.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know, they're like rabid DDR Freak fans, or Orange Lounge fans, or fan fans.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hopefully both after tonight's show, that's the goal.
[SPEAKER_09]: But you guys were really patient, so I figured I'd give you one hint, because I'm nice.
[SPEAKER_11]: No way, you're actually able to give a hint?
[SPEAKER_11]: Totally giving one hint.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, very sexy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, what is it?
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, now you guys might have to read into this a little bit.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know you're good at it, so it's okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: One new song in Xtreme has steps.
[SPEAKER_09]: With up arrows.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_02]: Up arrows.
[SPEAKER_02]: We don't see enough of them.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_13]: Do not underestimate the power of that hint.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, it might sound like there's going to be a song with music in it.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, this isn't actual hints.
[SPEAKER_02]: With up arrows.
[SPEAKER_13]: With up arrows.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we like up arrows, don't we?
[SPEAKER_02]: Although I have to say I'm partial to the right arrow or the right diagonal on Solo.
[SPEAKER_09]: One more thing, you guys, Extreme's coming soon.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also, please don't forget about Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: It is awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have been... We didn't get a chance to talk about that much tonight, but... I have been...
[SPEAKER_09]: To do with Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know some things that are pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: Don't forget, it's already been mentioned, that there are only a few old Konami originals that will be in Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: The rest, you know what, it's awesome.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know what I heard the other day, and they were talking about this, they're changing up the $50 bills.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's going to be a mighty fine dollar when that comes out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, you know what, I would just be like, boom boom dollar KOGG3 about that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, fine, that's a little blatant, but... I did it before.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, tonight for our post-show, enjoy this marathon of music from 2DX.
[SPEAKER_11]: Everything from 2nd style through 10th style.
[SPEAKER_11]: Enjoy, you guys.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you very much for tuning in and listening.
[SPEAKER_11]: Great show, and enjoy.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey, Orange Launch Radio is always on, 24-7.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thanks for listening and supporting us.
[SPEAKER_11]: OrangeLaunchRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_11]: Love you guys.
[SPEAKER_11]: Good night.
We're headed for Venus, and still we stand tall
Thanks for watching!