[SPEAKER_16]: Orange Lounge Radio Live is now on the air Orange Lounge Radio Live is a live talk program dedicated to all things Bomani and then some Orange Lounge Radio may contain adult content so you probably shouldn't let your children listen If you do let your children listen to Orange Lounge Radio they may turn into evil little demons from HELL!
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh wait, most children already are evil little demons from hell.
[SPEAKER_15]: Now you see that evil will always triumph because good is dumb.
[SPEAKER_22]: Trash, drunk, and stupid is no way to go through life, sir.
[SPEAKER_22]: He jeopardizes my ability to effectively govern this student body.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, makes you look like an ass is what he does, Ed.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hamburgers!
[SPEAKER_15]: The cornerstone of any nutritious breakfast.
[SPEAKER_15]: I was used to it.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura DarkSakura DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_16]: Any time, any place, baby.
[SPEAKER_21]: Ow, my foot!
[SPEAKER_02]: Why did I shoot myself in my foot?
[SPEAKER_11]: We are live, and this is episode number 105 for this Sunday, August 1st, 2004.
[SPEAKER_11]: You're tuned in to the B-Mani-themed, most strip-poker-playing radio station of all things B-Mani.
[SPEAKER_11]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_11]: You might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_11]: Joining me as always are my awesome co-hosts.
[SPEAKER_11]: In this corner, the happiest bunny on the farm is Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know her better as the angsty Dark Sakura.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm powered by meat and asparagus right now.
[SPEAKER_11]: Meat and potatoes.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_11]: Meat and asparagus.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, meat and asparagus.
[SPEAKER_08]: Potatoes are evil.
[SPEAKER_11]: Evil!
[SPEAKER_11]: Are you on a low-carb diet?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, I am.
[SPEAKER_11]: Low-carb diets are the antichrist.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know why they're the antichrist?
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, first of all, I'm doing this to be supportive.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know, but... And second of all, you know how hard I've worked my ass off, so don't... Yes, I know, but they're the Antichrist for me, because anything that says that I can't have bread and potatoes is the Antichrist.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can still have bread and potatoes.
[SPEAKER_01]: Those are the two best foods ever.
[SPEAKER_01]: Just not all the time.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I want potatoes all the time.
[SPEAKER_01]: Don't take my potatoes away.
[SPEAKER_08]: God.
[SPEAKER_08]: Rob, Rob, Rob, Rob, Rob, Rob, Rob, I miss doing that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I couldn't do, I tried that last week with Matt and it just didn't work.
[SPEAKER_11]: Did he just beat you up?
[SPEAKER_08]: I was like, you have to have a single syllable that starts with an R for that to work.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, speaking of which, in the other corner, our favorite Orange Lounge angsty tech massa, Loki!
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm moving my chair back.
[SPEAKER_11]: Is that it?
[SPEAKER_11]: Is that hello?
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm moving my chair back.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_11]: We have some special guests in the house tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: Say hello to, well, he hasn't been here for a little while, but he is the resident pop and music whore in Sacramento.
[SPEAKER_11]: Say hello to Garrett.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm a hooker.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Also joining us in studio, say hello to somebody else who hasn't been here for a couple weeks.
[SPEAKER_11]: Say hello to Bugged.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hello to Bugged.
[SPEAKER_11]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_11]: And tonight he's the, is that Turbo Express you're playing?
[SPEAKER_11]: He's the Turbo Express 4 tonight, but that's Jamie's Turbo Express.
[SPEAKER_11]: I would love to have a piece of your meat, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_11]: What kind of meat is this?
[SPEAKER_11]: Try a tip.
[SPEAKER_11]: Meat!
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, somebody was telling me, I can't even remember, this is like how, what, like horrible memory I have, but somebody was telling me about the sodas online.
[SPEAKER_11]: Was that you, Matt?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, you were telling me about the sodas online, that you could get like beef and orange flavored soda.
[SPEAKER_10]: But we were thinking about like, but you can make your own sodas?
[SPEAKER_10]: Sort of, yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, you know what, we'll talk about this when we come back from the break.
[SPEAKER_11]: All that.
[SPEAKER_11]: How was your week?
[SPEAKER_11]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_11]: And I guess some Bomani news, because we have a whole shitload of Bomani news.
[SPEAKER_11]: And tonight, I'm not going to get to it in this first break, but we will get to it tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: The resident Poppin' Music whore was kind enough to bring us Poppin' Eleven stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, the soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_11]: So we're going to hear a whole lot of Poppin' Eleven stuff tonight, so that's good.
[SPEAKER_11]: but first we're going to play a mix of music because I want to hear some Eurobeat so I put on Daisuke because that song rocks so we will be right back after this break with Orange Lounge Radio join us in our chatroom www.orangeloungeradio.com click on chat and we have a webcam on orangeloungeradio.com now is it on the main thing still?
[SPEAKER_11]: no, it's on our actual studio alright, we'll be back
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm falling in my dreams, I can feel the love, and the money comes My love, my crush, but they won't feel it Will you tell me now, how do you feel me?
Will you show me now, I wanna dance with you right now I want to work for you, every time, everywhere I'll be showing up to your world, let's go DarkSakura
Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_11]: You are listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're back.
[SPEAKER_11]: Here we are live on this lovely August evening.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's a hot August night.
[SPEAKER_11]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not as hot as... My bad!
[SPEAKER_11]: That was our Hot August.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's our Hot August theme song.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hot August nights are this month.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, every time I bring up, you know, Hot August nights, we'll just, you know... Woo!
[SPEAKER_08]: Everybody tango!
[SPEAKER_08]: Can you play the song from Dance Maniacs?
[SPEAKER_11]: Which one?
[SPEAKER_08]: Heaven is a Metallic... Oh, the Heaven is 57?
[SPEAKER_08]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because...
[SPEAKER_08]: Because Hot August Nights is this month, which I'm going to actually think I'm going to get to go to this month.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, having Hot August Nights in August would be... But I don't think they have that at other places.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't think, yeah, they probably don't have it at other, it's a big thing they do in Reno.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't, oh, the term I've heard before.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, yeah, the term, but... It's from the 50s.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to go look at cars.
[SPEAKER_11]: Old cars.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's such a white trash event, though.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's the same weekend as Trucker Fest.
[SPEAKER_08]: Muscle cars are sexy.
[SPEAKER_09]: My work sponsors Hot August Nights.
[SPEAKER_07]: Muscle cars are sexy.
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_11]: You like little dick cars?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, little dick cars and SUV, Rob.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also known as Mommy Mobile.
[SPEAKER_11]: Soccer Mom Mobile.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: We are here.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was out last week, as you may have heard.
[SPEAKER_11]: No!
[SPEAKER_11]: No, I was here two shows ago.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was here Sunday, but then I flew out Monday.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I can tell you guys where I went now, because I'm not there now.
[SPEAKER_11]: I went to a little place in Pennsylvania called Allentown, and there's really not a whole lot there.
[SPEAKER_11]: I guess there is, like, arcades and stuff, but I was so consumed with my work that I honestly had no time to go out and look.
[SPEAKER_11]: I ended up buying Sword of Mana, which, eh, it's okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was a little bit disappointed, because Secret of Mana is one of the best games ever, and then Sword of Mana being kind of, eh, is a little disappointing.
[SPEAKER_11]: But then I also bought Mario vs. Donkey Kong, which was, you know, it's corny.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's what you'd expect.
[SPEAKER_08]: One thing I would like to say to Panda, I don't think he had a choice.
[SPEAKER_11]: What?
[SPEAKER_11]: With what?
[SPEAKER_08]: That you should have gone to Maryland instead.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, you're talking about our chat room at orangewatchradio.com.
[SPEAKER_11]: Click on chat.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, nice plug.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, no, I didn't have a choice.
[SPEAKER_11]: They sent me where they tell me to send me.
[SPEAKER_11]: They say, bitch, you're going to go here.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I'm like, yeah, okay, don't fire me.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyway, I figure we will start off tonight's show as we always start off our shows.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll be playing a little bit of How Was Your Week?
[SPEAKER_11]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_11]: And Jamie, you've got the other mic, so why don't you start us off?
[SPEAKER_08]: I have a mouthful of beef.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Beef is good for you.
[SPEAKER_11]: Do you like meat in your mouth?
[SPEAKER_11]: Do you like having meat in your mouth?
[SPEAKER_08]: Or meat?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's juicy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry, I had to slow that piece down.
[SPEAKER_11]: You should suck out the flavor a little bit before you bite down on it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll just take the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: My week sucked.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was hot.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't have an AC in my car.
[SPEAKER_08]: Busy as hell at work.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it's going to get busier.
[SPEAKER_08]: I finally got this stupid financial aid notice from ARC.
[SPEAKER_08]: And you know what I have to say?
[SPEAKER_08]: I have to say that I'm actually very surprised I was awarded my federal loans, which means I won't have any interest on them.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that makes me happy.
[SPEAKER_11]: Good deal.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm getting, I don't mind saying, I'm getting, because I'm a sophomore, I'll get $3,500.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I don't mind saying so because it's like damn near what everybody gets if you're a sophomore, so it doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_08]: That means I get my laptop in two weeks.
[SPEAKER_08]: In two weeks, I will be sitting here with a shiny Fujitsu on my lap.
[SPEAKER_11]: I want a laptop.
[SPEAKER_11]: Especially after that trip, I need a laptop.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're expensive.
[SPEAKER_11]: I can't afford them.
Go to school.
[SPEAKER_11]: I need to buy a used one.
[SPEAKER_11]: I only want one that will let me on the internet.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't need any.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know I'm actually thinking about getting a Mac laptop.
[SPEAKER_11]: Isn't that scary?
[SPEAKER_08]: Evil.
[SPEAKER_11]: Quit giving me bad looks.
[SPEAKER_11]: Stop it.
[SPEAKER_11]: All of you.
[SPEAKER_10]: First you start with the Xbox and now you're going to... How was my week?
[SPEAKER_07]: How was my day?
[SPEAKER_10]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: How was my week?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, how was your week?
[SPEAKER_11]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I ended up going to see on Friday, because one of my friends is moving back to Utah.
[SPEAKER_08]: We ended up going to see The Village that night.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I don't care what anybody says, that movie was awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Excuse me.
[SPEAKER_10]: I love the political aspect of it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like the whole premise behind it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I love the setting.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like how everybody talks in that movie.
[SPEAKER_08]: Everybody just talks like, I just like it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not going to give away anything because, of course, it's one of those, you know, twisty movies.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I'm not going to say anything about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just really, I love the whole color theme.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like the way this guy directs.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the movies are slow, but all the pacing makes sense at the end of the movie.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I thought it was really well done.
[SPEAKER_11]: Two snaps up from Jamie?
[SPEAKER_08]: It gets the Artsy Award from me.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: And what did I do yesterday?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yesterday I hung out with Iguana Girl all day and we over the cat.
[SPEAKER_07]: Her cat passed away.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I'm sad.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_08]: It was actually filling without the great tape.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, I see.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then I spent the whole rest of the night online.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then today I got up bright and early, read my errands, got myself my comics today, read them all, devoured them, bought a Dragon Ash CD,
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh, cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I love Dragon Ash.
[SPEAKER_08]: And Bumper Sticker is the best one ever.
[SPEAKER_08]: It says, stop whining and plot revenge.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is that not me or what?
[SPEAKER_11]: That's pretty you.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that's me.
[SPEAKER_08]: My week.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alrighty.
[SPEAKER_08]: Suck-O-Rama
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, you know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: I know a deaf whore, so I win.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know one.
[SPEAKER_09]: Did you sleep with one, though?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I was at the 7-Eleven, and this heroine whore came in.
[SPEAKER_08]: She had band-aids on her inner thigh.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, she was a whore.
[SPEAKER_08]: She was a real whore.
[SPEAKER_08]: Of course, we were right next to the Regency Triple X Theater.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, there you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: So...
[SPEAKER_11]: How long have you lived in Sacramento?
[SPEAKER_08]: The theater was right across from where I used to work.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the guys in the collections department would leave during their lunch break and go over there and watch porn.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wait a minute, Loki.
[SPEAKER_11]: How many years have you lived in Sacramento?
[SPEAKER_11]: A lot.
[SPEAKER_11]: And you just now learned that there is a place over on Watt that shows XXX films all day, all night?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I didn't know that.
[SPEAKER_08]: You don't know what's funny?
[SPEAKER_08]: When the whole April Fool's thing was going on DDR Freak?
[SPEAKER_08]: and we had the thread there listing our address and contact information.
[SPEAKER_08]: My address on there was the address for the Regency XXX Theater.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know there's some news about DDR Freak Forums today.
[SPEAKER_08]: Are there?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, you guys made something awful.
[SPEAKER_11]: Dot coms make fun of lists today or whatever they call it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's okay, it's not my page.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, there were no posts from you in there so you're okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, me, me now.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, sorry.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sorry, Garrett.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, well...
[SPEAKER_09]: Last week was kind of slow, but I made the best of it.
[SPEAKER_09]: My parents were out on vacation, and I only got 24 hours at work, so I had four days off.
[SPEAKER_09]: And only managed to go crazy on two days, and the rest I filled with stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I had a pretty good time on most of the days.
[SPEAKER_09]: I met someone new that I'm interested in, and
[SPEAKER_09]: And then I found out the bad news that I was hoping to find out sooner than later.
[SPEAKER_09]: And hopefully it won't totally fuck everything up, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just have to stop being obsessive and something.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then I had my party on Friday, and that was really fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I got really, really, really wasted.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have never been drunk, really, before now that I was that drunk.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I go, wow, okay, this is drunk.
[SPEAKER_11]: Which Orange Lounge regular showed up to the party?
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, there was Brad, Irene, Matt, and Anita, and then, um, Janae and James, the guy I met.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh, okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, um, and that was it, we had fun, and people that, I don't think Brad and Irene took off till like, well, all of them pretty much left around like 3.30 or so in the morning, so that was...
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_09]: Keep in mind, chatters, I'm kind of new to alcohol, so I don't know all these things.
[SPEAKER_09]: I am naive.
[SPEAKER_11]: Most of our chatters can't even buy alcohol.
[SPEAKER_09]: It doesn't mean they can't get it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who says anything about buying?
[SPEAKER_11]: Not that we would condone that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Of course not.
[SPEAKER_09]: Don't drive.
[SPEAKER_09]: My fingers were about 25% numb, and at that time I decided we needed to play drunk 2DX and poppin' music, and I still managed to beat Murmur Twins drunk.
[SPEAKER_09]: and I think I got as high as like a 31 on pop and music but then I tried a 39 right after that and I just stopped so I don't know, I probably ended up higher.
[SPEAKER_11]: It reminds me of the time I played DDR in Vegas and I was drunk, really, really drunk and I got like a huge crowd around me while I was playing though, it was cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: Cool, and then now I'm, like as of yesterday, I am officially on vacation for this whole week and I'm still trying to remember that I'm on vacation.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wait a minute, weren't you just on vacation like two months ago?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: You're always on vacation.
[SPEAKER_09]: I only get two weeks a year.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just decided to take it now.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I mean, we usually don't get to pick our vacation until... Shit, I didn't get to pick mine until after March, I don't think.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then we have to use it before November.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's weird the way it works.
[SPEAKER_09]: But yeah, I took it now, I'm on vacation.
[SPEAKER_09]: and I hope I find something good to do this week and oh yeah and then I got all the I got all those wonderful CDs and I spent way too much money on my newfound collections that I got in the mail all week and then yesterday my sister was a bitch when my CDs came because I had to go take Janae to work and then I come back and I see the mailman like on one part of our street like but like you know his car is pointing the direction like he would have had to pass mine
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm all, oh, I wonder, because I haven't checked my tracking number.
[SPEAKER_09]: I go home, check my tracking number, it says, your item arrived in Sacramento at 5.30 a.m.
[SPEAKER_09]: today.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm like, wait a minute, that means he would have come to my house already if his car's pointed in that direction.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I'm all, hey, Shannon, did the mailman come?
[SPEAKER_09]: She's all, yeah, but I didn't have any clothes on, so I didn't go get it.
[SPEAKER_09]: and she's upstairs laying in my parents' room naked in all of my comforters and blankets that I left in there from when I was sleeping in there in the week because she was gone camping with my parents so I'm all, you bitch and then so I go running outside and I'm going to go hunt for the mailman in my neighborhood because I hate waiting for it another day or going to the mail or to the post office and then I get in my car and then all of a sudden he's on the other side of my street so I get back out of my car and run across the street
[SPEAKER_11]: And then, you know, I see him... Chasing a mailman for some CDs.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I see him like at least three or four times a month.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's always him.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then I'm running up to him and he's looking at me like, why is he coming towards me?
[SPEAKER_09]: And, you know, like there's any other reason.
[SPEAKER_09]: He knows who the fuck I am.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then I'm all, hey, you know, my sister said, you know, can't you just say, oh, I haven't come yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm all, he's all, oh, no, I have.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then he gives him my thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: And so, yeah, I got, yeah, I got stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Right on.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think.
[SPEAKER_11]: Is there anything else from your week in your day?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, no, I just wanted to say that.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I don't remember what I was going to say.
[SPEAKER_09]: The Jaffro Sachs Remix Album
[SPEAKER_09]: And it was so bad that, okay, like, I was trying to just listen to it while I was kind of napping, but I wasn't really sleepy, I was just laying on my bed.
[SPEAKER_09]: I listened to about half the album while I was on my bed, and then I went to my computer, turned it off, and continued to go back to bed.
[SPEAKER_11]: Did you ever figure out what his connection to Bomani was?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I still haven't.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sana did one song with him.
[SPEAKER_09]: On this remix album, what was it, Hiroshi Watanabe did a remix, and that was a Bomani artist for like 5K a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have no idea who he is
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm the lazy bastard.
[SPEAKER_17]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_17]: How was your week?
[SPEAKER_10]: Um, well, uh, let's see, this week I didn't do much, I played a lot of games on my main cabinet, because I have to get the money's worth out of it.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, by the way, I figure it, I will have to play until I die on this cabinet to get the money's worth.
[SPEAKER_10]: Um, anyways, so, I went down, um, what was it, yesterday, we were looking for stuff to do, so...
[SPEAKER_10]: We went down to Golf Land to go play miniature golf.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's when we discovered, guess what?
[SPEAKER_10]: Now they have night... What was it?
[SPEAKER_10]: Night swims or whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's basically water slides in the dark.
[SPEAKER_10]: So they have that there now.
[SPEAKER_10]: So there's a ton of fucking people.
[SPEAKER_10]: The line was like zigzagging just to get into golf.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm like, fuck this.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm leaving.
[SPEAKER_10]: But at least I got to see what condition everything was.
[SPEAKER_10]: And the fourth mixer, Extreme 2 Cabinet...
[SPEAKER_10]: Not working still, and you know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: Don't care.
[SPEAKER_10]: Drum Mania seemed to be okay, and Guitar Freaks was okay, I guess.
[SPEAKER_10]: Then we decided to go see The Village, and The Village was okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I already knew what the plot twist was about halfway through the film anyways, so...
[SPEAKER_10]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that was alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: But you know what movie is going to rock?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's his next movie.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's going to be The Sixth Sign of the Unbreakable Village.
[SPEAKER_10]: Look for that in theaters.
2006.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's going to rock.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's going to combine everything that was awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's going to be a village of super humans that can see dead aliens.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's going to rock.
[SPEAKER_10]: You used to be funny.
[SPEAKER_10]: What happened?
[SPEAKER_10]: You left.
[SPEAKER_10]: So anyways, it's funny that you should mention a crack whore, Jamie, because I did see one earlier today.
[SPEAKER_10]: Whatever, it's the same shit.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, I guess, okay, maybe she didn't have a bloody nose and she just had less track lines or whatever, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's still the stupid bitch, I'll get into it later, I guess, in the FUs, but anyway, some stupid bitch tried to cut me off and I flipped her off and that was fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: Harry Camargo, White Castle
[SPEAKER_10]: And what is your favorite adult-oriented arcade game that you've come across?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, of course, this was before I even got maimed, Gals Panic, it rocks.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm awesome at Gals Panic.
[SPEAKER_10]: But then I was playing, I beat the stupid, was it that Poker Gals or whatever?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's stupid.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's kind of disturbing watching them masturbate with like a...
[SPEAKER_10]: Wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_10]: You mean John Waters?
[SPEAKER_10]: Uh, maybe.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's about fucking time John Waters came out with a new movie.
[SPEAKER_11]: It better be good, though, because, like, his movies, like, ever since Serial Mom, like, Serial Mom was the shit, and then, like, what was after that?
[SPEAKER_11]: It was, um, not, no, no, no, no, after that was, there was, Cecil B. Demented was one.
[SPEAKER_11]: I thought there was one in between, though.
[SPEAKER_11]: I might be, I might be losing, but, like, Cecil B. Demented was, like, kind of, like, eh.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was just eh.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, Pekker!
[SPEAKER_11]: I was in between there, too.
[SPEAKER_11]: Pekker was kinda, eh.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then, like, Cecil B. DiMena was even more, eh.
[SPEAKER_11]: So he needs to, you know, come back up.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like, Pink Flamingos, too, man.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm telling you.
[SPEAKER_11]: Even if Divine's dead, I don't care.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyways, it's about these bunch of perverts that go into this one town, and then everyone starts getting perverted and having sex with one another and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: But there's, like, one specific scene that I remember where this lady is, like, doing, like, some sort of dance or hokey-pokey type thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: And she's staring at this, like, um...
[SPEAKER_10]: One doctor there.
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess like these people are getting injured in the head or something like that and they turn all horny.
[SPEAKER_10]: Same way as she ends up setting down a water bottle and squatting over it and shoving it up her cooch.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that was, that was interesting.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, I'm looking at an internet movie database right now.
[SPEAKER_11]: It is A Dirty Shame is done by John Waters, which means I will have to see it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Even if I fucking hate Johnny Knoxville, I will have to see this movie.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'll watch it with you.
[SPEAKER_10]: See, now, did you see what it was?
[SPEAKER_10]: It was basically, um, it's when a bunch of head injuries are causing people to become sex addicts.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, I thought, I think that's pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, can't wait.
[SPEAKER_10]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: What was it?
[SPEAKER_10]: Uh, Wes Johnson, Fat Fuck Frank.
[SPEAKER_11]: This is all I care about is Mink Stole in it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because Mink Stoll is the greatest actress of all time.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't care what you say.
[SPEAKER_11]: And she is in it, as she has been in all of John Waters' other movies.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyway, the video game nerds out there have no idea what I'm talking about right now, so I'm just going to let it go.
[SPEAKER_10]: So anyways, that's all that.
[SPEAKER_10]: That looked pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_10]: Other than that, not really much happening.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just a little bit of Final Fantasy, not that much at all.
[SPEAKER_10]: And just working on my cabinets.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyways, how about your weeks?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, I was gone for a couple weeks in Pennsylvania, and to be honest, really not a whole lot of exciting stuff went down.
[SPEAKER_11]: I did get a chance to have one of my friends visit me over the weekend, because she lives out on the East Coast.
[SPEAKER_11]: She's somebody I knew from college, and we went out to New York City.
[SPEAKER_11]: We kind of drove around some areas around there.
[SPEAKER_11]: We found ourselves on Long Island eventually, and we went to Fire Island, which is this big gay haven out on the East Coast, for those that don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I don't know what possessed us to go there, but we were just like, oh, let's go to Fire Island.
[SPEAKER_11]: So we did, and it was like a giant gay slumber party slash summer camp that I really didn't feel like I was invited to.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, whatever.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_11]: See you next time!
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, I got some... Well, yeah, because when you pay... You have to pay to go on the tour.
[SPEAKER_11]: You have to pay to go on the little tour thing, and then you get little tokens that you can put in machines, and you get crayons and stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'll get out the crayons later, and we can draw on the walls.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: That was pretty much it, honestly.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, I haven't been playing any video games except for what I was talking about earlier on Game Boy Advance.
[SPEAKER_11]: There's only so many times I can beat Metroid Zero before I'm like, Jesus Christ, I need a new game.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, that was it.
[SPEAKER_11]: But then coming home was very interesting because the house, like coming back into the apartment at 4 o'clock in the morning, because Bugs picked me up at the airport.
[SPEAKER_11]: After, by the way, my airplane in Philadelphia sat on the runway for an hour, and so finally it comes back and it sits in
[SPEAKER_11]: We get to Vegas, and I was only supposed to have an hour layover in Vegas.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, now I have five minutes to get to my other plane.
[SPEAKER_11]: So I ran from one end of the Vegas airport to the other end, and it was like being on The Amazing Race.
[SPEAKER_11]: I swear, it was interesting.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I just barely made my plane to Sacramento, and all was well.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then Bug picked me up at the airport here in Sacramento, and then we went out.
[SPEAKER_11]: We ended up meeting Evan...
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_11]: So I came here, and then when I open the door and I walk in, I'm like, holy fucking shit, when did Loki finish his cabinet?
[SPEAKER_11]: Because our TV's gone, and it's inside the cabinet, and then, like, the whole room has been turned around 90 degrees, or at least it feels that way.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then, like, there's just all this stuff that used to be over here, like, piled up in piles on the side of the room, but I just thought it was cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then Loki was showing his cabinet to me yesterday, and, uh...
[SPEAKER_11]: MrWorld96
[SPEAKER_11]: so they have this but if you I don't know if you uncover certain bad parts of the picture then your bar goes down and if you fall into the bad like the picture of the girl turns into a picture of like the devil and like it starts playing this Eurobeat song that totally doesn't match it goes like everybody move your body I'm gonna play it for you guys later because I think it's just that cool I'm gonna have to do that after the break but um I'm sorry yes Jamie you want to share something with us get get Jamie Mike here
[SPEAKER_08]: Not that I'm meaning to interrupt, but Time Magazine is encouraging people to download movies off the Internet.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like what?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm reading this article about how a lot of the horror movies from Japan are being remade for the U.S.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like the original director for The Ring 2, well, for The Ring is doing A Ring 2 over here.
[SPEAKER_11]: Right, and The Grudge is a Japanese movie.
[SPEAKER_08]: Right, Ju-on was the name.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it's saying that, it says, why wait for remakes?
[SPEAKER_08]: All of these movies are available online.
[SPEAKER_08]: Right.
[SPEAKER_11]: They meant through Amazon.com or your favorite online retailer.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, Loki.
[SPEAKER_10]: I heard that the new Kashan movie is available on... Actually, I have it marked on Supernova, a cam of it, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: But still, cam that's subtitled in English.
[SPEAKER_10]: Good enough for me.
[SPEAKER_11]: Speaking of all this Japanese culture stuff hitting the US, Loki and I had the pleasure of going to a small little convention, quote unquote.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know what you got.
[SPEAKER_11]: It wasn't quite a convention, it was a fair.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like a fair with an E on it, like a renaissance fair, but it was an anime fair that they had at the mall here in Sacramento, which consisted of...
[SPEAKER_11]: Four vendor booths scattered throughout the mall.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then in what used to be McDonald's, they had a viewing room where they were showing crappy anime all day.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I guess they were going to show live-action Sailor Moon at some point.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, Sunrise Mall.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, the McDonald's closed at Sunrise Mall about three years ago.
[SPEAKER_10]: A couple months ago, okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: Not quite three years ago, a couple months ago.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: But still, it's closed.
[SPEAKER_11]: And they were showing anime in there now.
[SPEAKER_11]: The only cool thing they were going to show was today, but I'm not much of an anime geek.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, maybe there was some good stuff in there and I just don't recognize it.
[SPEAKER_11]: But they were going to show live action Sailor Moon today.
[SPEAKER_11]: And that would have been cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: But anyway, like, the vendor booths were not too thrilling.
[SPEAKER_11]: But they were, like, it was really cool to go to the mall and see, like, all the soccer moms and the brats.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then, like, all these cosplayers.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like, there were, like, tons of people cosplaying as all these anime characters.
[SPEAKER_11]: Not that...
[SPEAKER_11]: Not that there were many good cosplayers, but there were, you know, a lot of cosplayers.
[SPEAKER_10]: No offense to cosplayers out there, but why do the majority, not all of them, but do the great majority of them have the really nasty, ugly, fat chicks?
[SPEAKER_10]: Honestly.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, I saw some really... It's like, oh my god, when did that character put on 100 pounds?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's like, a blob has sucked her soul!
[SPEAKER_10]: It was really nasty.
[SPEAKER_11]: I only think that stuff is bad when they're cosplaying as Mai, or Chun-Li, or somebody really, you know, promiscuous.
[SPEAKER_10]: Then there was that chick who was next to me, who I thought was a guy.
[SPEAKER_10]: She looked like a dude.
[SPEAKER_10]: And she opens her mouth, yeah, how much for this?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm like, oh my god, ugly!
[SPEAKER_10]: And I started pointing.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was just disappointed because usually at those kind of anime, even an anime expo, I'm not that into anime, I have an appreciation for some of it, like the big mainstream stuff like Miyazaki and stuff, but usually at most anime conventions, you have your video game corner, or you have your video game vendor, or something video game related, I was hoping to see that there.
[SPEAKER_11]: Nope, not a damn thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: The only thing video game related I could find that was interesting was the Final Fantasy XI wall scroll.
[SPEAKER_11]: But it was just the generic stock art of the same thing that's on the cover of Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's the same art I've seen over and over and I have it in like a million different places anyway.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I didn't want to spend $15 on a wall scroll that looked like it was just a bad Xerox copy anyway.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, that was our experience at the...
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm actually surprised you didn't go, Jamie, just to check it out or you heard about it or anything.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because that was the one they were promoting over at A1 Comics.
[SPEAKER_11]: Which, oh, I didn't.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was this one.
[SPEAKER_11]: Do we have the little flyer here?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, I remember the flyer.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just threw my flyer away and said, eh.
[SPEAKER_08]: I had other things to do.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like laundry.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it was Saturday, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: It was Saturday and today.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's still going on right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was doing things.
[SPEAKER_08]: I remember I had to be over at Iguana Golf Course.
[SPEAKER_11]: You were being support.
[SPEAKER_10]: I feel sorry for anybody that was coming from like, according to this, they give in directions from Reno or South Lake Tahoe.
[SPEAKER_11]: What anime do they ever do in Reno or South Lake Tahoe?
[SPEAKER_11]: Do they ever have festivals like this up there?
[SPEAKER_11]: I highly doubt that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Go to a comic shop, you'll see more anime than there was at this place.
[SPEAKER_08]: Classic Gaming Expo was in Vegas, but... Classic Gaming Expo is in San Jose this year and I really want to go.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is it next month?
[SPEAKER_11]: It's like next weekend, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm going to check that out right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh crap, if it's next weekend, then I'm going to the Ren Faire.
[SPEAKER_11]: I already have plans to go to the Bay Area next weekend.
[SPEAKER_08]: And next weekend I'm going to the Ren Faire.
[SPEAKER_08]: Next Saturday.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm going to the Bay Area to visit people next weekend.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wait, I have to find out now when Classic Gaming Expo is, because I have to go.
[SPEAKER_08]: Classic Gaming Expo, for those who don't know, is supposed to be like the most tremendously awesome, neat, old school thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ooh, no, it's at the end of the month.
[SPEAKER_11]: 21st and 22nd.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, I'm not, because I don't leave until September, motherfucker.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I think I can skip my introduction to Windows class that day.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, I have no time to go test out of this.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is sort of an FU, but not really.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I'm going to try to make this an easy A to establish a good GPA.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ooh, Jamie, SNK just joined as a sponsor of Classic Gaming Expo.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ooh, SNK, we're out of business.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: We no longer support the Neo Geo.
[SPEAKER_08]: The last game is dead.
[SPEAKER_11]: And Konami's going to have an exhibit today.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, they're going to do Castlevania, I hope.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, right on.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, I have to go to this.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm so going to this.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe we can head to San Jose after my class.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: I get out of my class at 4.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll have to find out what time everything's at.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe we can broadcast from Classic Gaming Expo.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, maybe we should email them or something and figure out something we can do to promote stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: Even though we don't really do a whole lot of classic gaming, except for, you know...
[SPEAKER_11]: You talk about it on your spin-off show.
[SPEAKER_11]: Which, by the way, there's news about some of our spin-off shows.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, because I'm starting school in two weeks.
[SPEAKER_08]: Starting this Tuesday, Pump Up the Volume is moving back to Tuesday, so we can use the old promo again.
[SPEAKER_11]: Right on, okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: And, uh, I'm, uh...
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, you know, somebody in the chat room just brought up a very good point.
[SPEAKER_11]: Somebody in the chat room brought up a very good point that as far as us promoting classic gaming, we talk about BurgerTime, or at least I do, and I do a lot of promotion for BurgerTime, which I believe to be the greatest 80s video game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tappin'.
[SPEAKER_11]: What?
[SPEAKER_11]: Tappin'?
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, Tapper.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tapper.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Rupert Tapper.
[SPEAKER_08]: Which, the original one was like a beer game.
[SPEAKER_11]: We have a lot of good classic gaming stuff to talk about on here.
[SPEAKER_08]: and Tubin and Supersprint and
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Geographic games.
[SPEAKER_11]: So we're going to look into what we can do about Classic Gaming Expo.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, I think we're going to take a break.
[SPEAKER_11]: And when we come back, we actually have Bimani stuff we want to talk about, believe it or not.
[SPEAKER_11]: And, of course, the cage match.
[SPEAKER_11]: You have to use the week.
[SPEAKER_11]: All that fun stuff very soon.
[SPEAKER_11]: In the meantime, we're going to play you guys some new music from Pop and Music 11.
[SPEAKER_11]: And our resident pop and music whore is here to tell us all about the songs we're going to hear today.
[SPEAKER_11]: So what did you pick out for us?
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, well, I put on...
[SPEAKER_09]: He said three songs, so I picked songs that were not hosted on the Mani style, so they're songs you may not have heard.
[SPEAKER_09]: So that's why I started with this.
[SPEAKER_09]: The first one is, the genre is Nebuta, but the song is actually called Karasu instead of Tori.
[SPEAKER_09]: I actually got really curious when the song was reading the info on the page at the official site, and it's supposed to mean crows.
[SPEAKER_09]: Not birds, like generically like that, because it just has a kanji for bird, and most people would read it as tori.
[SPEAKER_09]: So there's that.
[SPEAKER_09]: I also put on the remix for Yokan Ko, the Death's Reggae song from 7, which I actually like, even though it's really minimal.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then there's another song called, what was that, Tozancha Tachi, and...
[SPEAKER_09]: It sounds kind of like an anime song to me, but it's actually an original song that the guy from the Parkettes made.
[SPEAKER_11]: So yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, cool deal.
[SPEAKER_11]: So this is the premiere of some Poppin' 11 music here on Orange Lounge Radio, and thank you very much for bringing this to us.
[SPEAKER_11]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're going to start off with Karasu.
[SPEAKER_11]: Enjoy.
Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_21]: Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching!
S, S, S, S, S
Saga-kun, Ue, Koni-kibiku Aru-kun, Kawawata-un Wakate-kun, Takimanaka-un Toshiyomi-kun, Koi-kun, Kaoru-kun Tengu-kun, Tengu-kun, Tengu-kun, Tengu-kun Tengu-kun, Tengu-kun, Tengu-kun, Tengu-kun, Tengu-kun
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah!
[SPEAKER_11]: After this song, we'll be having a Let Them Move Marathon.
[SPEAKER_02]: No!
[SPEAKER_11]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_11]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: Crap-free Bavani Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_11]: All crap-free.
[SPEAKER_11]: Except for this show, which you're tuned into here on this lovely Sunday evening.
[SPEAKER_11]: As promised, I wanted to walk over to the main cabinet and play this game for you guys.
[SPEAKER_11]: This is called Miss Mr. World 96 Nude.
[SPEAKER_11]: And if you want to see...
[SPEAKER_11]: If you want to see screenshots of this game, head on over to OrangeLaunchRadio.com because it's playing live right now on our webcam there.
[SPEAKER_11]: And even though it doesn't auto refresh right now, you have to click reload every 30 seconds or so.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're working on getting that fixed, at least for next week.
[SPEAKER_11]: Also, later this program, we'll be opening up the Skype line for your comments over at www.orangesponsorator.com.
[SPEAKER_11]: Look for our recent news article on Skype, and it'll tell you how to set it up.
[SPEAKER_11]: Also, in our LiveJournal community, there's a recent post there.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, we're going to try to get the sound, because I wanted to play the evil song for you guys, but Loki's still working on sound.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes?
I'm a host.
Give me my phone.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yes, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_06]: I saw asses.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm sorry, I'm not a ho There's a really lopsided lump of an outline of a penis on the screen right now But see, if you trace around the penis Like, see, watch If the little character traces around the penis Then you get to see it Oh, some of the ROMs are corrupt So some of the pictures don't work right But it's kind of a fucked up game I see more asses We're gonna see if Loki can get it hooked up I'm gonna start a game here
[SPEAKER_11]: and hopefully we can get the sound over and Jamie will tell you all what's going on here.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oops.
[SPEAKER_08]: Rob is playing with the dip switches.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hold on here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, the little line thing looks like a really stupid Pac-Man, but not.
[SPEAKER_11]: How do I insert coins?
[SPEAKER_11]: Up at the top, Rob.
[SPEAKER_11]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's not two player at the same time, so it kind of sucks.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Shit, I quit out!
[SPEAKER_11]: Dammit, I hit the wrong button.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was special, Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm very proud of you.
[SPEAKER_11]: This is wonderful radio right now.
[SPEAKER_11]: Any luck on the sound?
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm working on it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Loki's working on it.
[SPEAKER_11]: We could do a different topic and then come back to this, I guess.
[SPEAKER_08]: I now need to announce that I suck at R-Type.
[SPEAKER_08]: I used to be okay at R-Type.
[SPEAKER_08]: My fiance is like a god at R-Type.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's like me and DDR.
[SPEAKER_11]: I used to be really good at DDR, but I honestly have not played DDR in a month.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I'm going to play this for the chat room so you can hear how bad I suck.
[SPEAKER_11]: Got it?
[SPEAKER_11]: So we hear the sound now?
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, you will.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, I'm hearing Jamie's game.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hold on, take the mic away from that for a minute.
[SPEAKER_12]: This is our type.
[SPEAKER_11]: Can we hear this?
[SPEAKER_11]: Hold on, if I put the coins in and do it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Can I hear it?
[SPEAKER_11]: No, we don't hear it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, I'm going to see... Does it work if I hold the mic up here?
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, we'll hold the mic up there.
[SPEAKER_11]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm going to try and get to the evil stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: See, I'll trace around the penis first.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oops, I died.
[SPEAKER_11]: See, I got a penis, look.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, now I'm going to try and make it go bad.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm trying very hard here to get there.
[SPEAKER_01]: Go to the techno song, don't choke up on me on air here.
[SPEAKER_11]: I died.
[SPEAKER_11]: Again.
[SPEAKER_02]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, almost.
[SPEAKER_10]: Shit.
[SPEAKER_10]: I died again.
[SPEAKER_10]: Damn this game!
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, here it goes.
[SPEAKER_01]: Here it goes.
[SPEAKER_01]: Aw, shit, it froze up!
[SPEAKER_10]: Fuck!
[SPEAKER_10]: Fuck your cabinet.
[SPEAKER_10]: Fuck this.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let me do this shit.
[SPEAKER_10]: I gotta do it the right way.
[SPEAKER_10]: You gotta play this game, because... God damn it.
[SPEAKER_10]: What happened to all my controls?
[SPEAKER_10]: What did you guys do here?
[SPEAKER_11]: Loki is going to try to get that to work.
[SPEAKER_11]: In the meantime, I'm going to want to tell you guys about some general gaming news that's going on out there.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know if you guys heard about this, but WarioWare 2 is going to be coming out soon, which is kind of exciting for those of us who have video game attention deficit disorder.
[SPEAKER_11]: WarioWare is a great game to have because you're the only one who'll stare back.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're going to be coming out with this WarioWare 2, which should be exciting.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know that they're going to have one on the DS, too.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know if this is the DS version.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't think it is.
[SPEAKER_11]: But they are going to have that coming out.
[SPEAKER_11]: Also, it's updated on our website, www.orangetownsradio.com.
[SPEAKER_11]: Speaking of the Nintendo DS, Square Enix has been doing...
[SPEAKER_11]: Everybody moves our body Everybody moves our body Everybody moves our body
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm going to make a DWI of that.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's an awesome song.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wasn't that worth it?
[SPEAKER_11]: Wasn't that worth that wait of like 10 minutes of train wreck radio to hear that little sample?
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyway, moving on.
[SPEAKER_11]: If you want to vote on the Squeenix survey for what game should they port over to the Nintendo DS, head on over to our website, orangeonstrider.com.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's a very recent story we have on the site.
[SPEAKER_11]: Metal Gear Solid 3, Snake Eater, some new screenshots have been revealed.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm sorry, what did you say about that, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_08]: That game makes me hot.
[SPEAKER_11]: The minimum requirements for Doom 3 were announced
[SPEAKER_11]: You have to have a 1.5 GHz Pentium 4 chip or an AMD Athlon 1500.
[SPEAKER_11]: So you have to have a 1.5 something to play it.
[SPEAKER_11]: You have to have at least 384 megabits of RAM, which isn't that hard.
[SPEAKER_11]: Megabytes.
[SPEAKER_11]: And 2 gigs of hard drive space and of course an Nvidia GeForce 3 or an ATI 8500 graphics card.
[SPEAKER_11]: But fear not, if you don't have a computer good enough to play it, get an Xbox because it's going to be coming out on Xbox as well.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: So that's what's going on in the gaming world right now.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think what I'm going to do is I'm going to go ahead and open up the Skype line if anybody has a comment on something we've been talking about so far this show.
[SPEAKER_11]: I would like to hear about your favorite adult-oriented arcade game, actually, was something I'd like to hear about.
[SPEAKER_11]: But see, Custer's Revenge wasn't an arcade game.
[SPEAKER_11]: You need to get a mic, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_11]: You need to get mic'd up there.
[SPEAKER_11]: Also, if you want to talk about something going on in gaming news, we got that opened up for you.
[SPEAKER_11]: Our chat room wants to know who that is on our webcam right now on OrangeLaunchRadio.com with the iBook.
[SPEAKER_11]: And that is our wonderful Bugged is there.
[SPEAKER_11]: Did you know that for our webcam... Oh, we got a call.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's take the call.
[SPEAKER_11]: OrangeLaunchRadio, you are on the air.
[SPEAKER_20]: Hello, Sky.
[SPEAKER_20]: Siggy here.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey, Siggy.
[SPEAKER_11]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_20]: I'm doing fine.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, what is your favorite adult-oriented arcade game ever?
[SPEAKER_20]: Well, honestly, I've never played any kind of adult-oriented video arcade game.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ah, so you stick to just your basic pornography.
[SPEAKER_20]: Um, not really.
[SPEAKER_20]: Yeah, sort of.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, alright, yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's all right, we're all friends.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, so what are you calling about then?
[SPEAKER_20]: Well, I got some latest news in the local Las Vegas-Bimani scene.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ooh, Las Vegas-Bimani scene news.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know I was in Vegas for five minutes this week?
[SPEAKER_20]: Yeah, the McCarran Airport, huh?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_11]: I ran all the way from Terminal A, one end of Terminal A, all the way to the other end of Terminal B in five minutes.
[SPEAKER_20]: Oh, yeah, that's a quite far run.
[SPEAKER_11]: I impressed myself.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, so what's up in the Las Vegas-Bimani scene?
[SPEAKER_20]: As of last Thursday, the Orleans Hotel and Casino has got Easy to Dance, her second move.
[SPEAKER_20]: And her third mix from Suncoast.
[SPEAKER_20]: Where in New Orleans?
[SPEAKER_11]: No, no, just Las Vegas.
[SPEAKER_20]: The New Orleans Hotel and Casino.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's the New Orleans Hotel and Casino in Las Vegas.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because, you know, they have little bits of America all over Vegas.
[SPEAKER_20]: Yeah, it's far away from the strip, so... So a lot of people have been over there playing it?
[SPEAKER_20]: Well, I don't... You know, yesterday I went there.
[SPEAKER_20]: I went there yesterday, just to, you know, celebrate my 25 years.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, happy birthday, by the way, from Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_20]: I played it for the first time, and it was really hard, because, you know, it only has one judgment, you know, which is cool.
[SPEAKER_20]: I like the DDR, like, perfect, great, good, and... Agent's Dance's second move is only in one, which is, you know, which is complicated.
[SPEAKER_20]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_11]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_20]: And what's new about Easy to Dance, the second loop, is they have freezes, like freeze sensor and then freeze pad.
[SPEAKER_11]: The Koreans love those freeze things.
[SPEAKER_11]: I've seen it like in every knockoff of another Bomani game they have in Korea, they have a freeze something, like in Easy to DJ.
[SPEAKER_20]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_11]: But Easy to DJ rocks, it really does.
[SPEAKER_20]: Ah, I see.
[SPEAKER_11]: I see.
[SPEAKER_20]: Yeah, and...
[SPEAKER_20]: Circus Circus is not much fun to play, according to the Monty Locals here.
[SPEAKER_11]: Circus Circus is my favorite hotel to stay at, though, because it's so fucking cheap.
[SPEAKER_20]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_20]: I stayed there, you know, two Christmases ago.
[SPEAKER_20]: Why would you... Before I moved here.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, I was going to say, why would you stay in a hotel there when you lived there, but it was... Before I moved here.
[SPEAKER_20]: I know, I would stay in a hotel.
[SPEAKER_20]: Oh, by the way, Loki.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, Loki.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_20]: Oh, by the way, Loki, I suggest you should watch Superstar Club.
[SPEAKER_11]: What now?
[SPEAKER_10]: Suicide Club.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've seen it!
[SPEAKER_10]: I haven't.
[SPEAKER_10]: You've seen it already?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I haven't seen it.
[SPEAKER_20]: Ha ha ha, yeah right.
[SPEAKER_20]: They're doing blockbuster shelves right now.
[SPEAKER_20]: You know, it's a Japanese movie about 54 schoolgirls committing suicide in a subway station.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's not what the movie is about though.
[SPEAKER_20]: Well, yeah, it's a mystery of suicide.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's about J-pop and the evils of it.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's about the evils of... Actually, there's a really awesome movie.
[SPEAKER_10]: If anyone's seen Ichi the Killer, they're making Ichi the... Oh, I've seen that.
[SPEAKER_20]: I've seen Ichi the Killer, actually.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're making an anime version of Ichi the Killer.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's going to be a prequel to it, I believe.
[SPEAKER_20]: Yeah, I've seen the live version.
[SPEAKER_20]: I haven't read the manga or watched the actual anime over the years.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's also another movie called, I think, Three Monsters that's going to be coming out.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's basically, I don't really know what it is, but they have a scene where they cut off some chick's fingers while she's playing the piano or something like that.
[SPEAKER_18]: Lovely.
[SPEAKER_20]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, well we're going to go ahead and let you go, but thank you for calling in and letting us know what's going on here in the woods.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, have a good one.
[SPEAKER_11]: Be careful.
[SPEAKER_11]: Watch that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ichi the Killer in moderation there.
[SPEAKER_11]: Be careful there.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Skyblind's opened up.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll take another call if somebody wants to call in.
[SPEAKER_11]: Otherwise, we'll probably... We'll probably move into some other Bomani news.
[SPEAKER_10]: I hate it because I have all these... I know I'm going to mess up the pronunciation.
[SPEAKER_10]: Mahjong?
[SPEAKER_10]: Mahjong.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have no idea how to play it and I have all these porno games of it.
[SPEAKER_08]: You have to match the tiles.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, that seems easy enough.
[SPEAKER_11]: There's a 9 gig...
[SPEAKER_10]: Ah!
[SPEAKER_10]: There's a mic in my face.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, don't talk in this house without a microphone during the show.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, anyways, I was going to say, there was a 9 gigs zip that I was trying to download.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was before we fixed our cable problem.
[SPEAKER_10]: And so it wasn't downloading quite.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was telling me I had like, you know, 4,000 hours left.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I was like, fuck this.
[SPEAKER_08]: You also need to get the Sailor Moon Final Fight game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sailor Moon Final Fight.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's see if we can find that.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's cheese ball.
[SPEAKER_11]: I also have a personal request, because I noticed it wasn't on the machine, but you need to find me Ninja Gaiden, the arcade game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I need Ninja Gaiden.
[SPEAKER_11]: You need Ninja Gaiden on there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Soldier Sailor Moon?
[SPEAKER_08]: I think that's it.
Okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, anyway.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, we're not getting any calls over on Skype line, so I'm going to shut it off.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, so screw you guys.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, screw you guys.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're going to shut it off for a little bit.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll come back to it later, though, because I want to talk about some Bomani news.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't think you guys got to this last week, talking about Xtreme, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Do we ever talk about Bomani on the show?
[SPEAKER_11]: What did you two guys talk about last week?
[SPEAKER_11]: I haven't listened to this show yet.
[SPEAKER_11]: Pinball.
[SPEAKER_08]: We talked a lot about pinball, didn't we?
[SPEAKER_11]: Pinball's awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, I swear the guy that did Pin Mame, or one of his biggest promoters, is from Sacramento, because I've seen the car like three times now with the Pin Mame license plate.
[SPEAKER_08]: The guy who runs this one really big download site does live in Carmichael, near me and Dan.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, maybe that's it then.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, but we haven't talked to him or anything.
[SPEAKER_11]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, so DDR Extreme, DDRSpot.com, we borrowed an article from them talking about the full song list was released.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, not the full song list, but the pre-unlocks song list was announced.
[SPEAKER_11]: And a very wide mix of stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: So I'm going to run through this list real fast.
[SPEAKER_11]: Konami Originals, you're going to see in DDR Extreme.
[SPEAKER_11]: Firefly by B4U, Jeanne Jeanne, Jet World, Love Love Sugar, Mobile Moga, Paranoia Eternal, Pink Rose,
[SPEAKER_11]: Doomie.
[SPEAKER_11]: That was kind of a surprise to see that one when, you know, you say that there's the censors who may not go for that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ah, screw them at Texas Fox.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, this is extreme.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's for PS2.
[SPEAKER_11]: Theme from Enter the Dragon.
[SPEAKER_05]: That makes me happy.
[SPEAKER_11]: A Stupid Barber, .59, Bad Routine, Dropout, Ecstasy, I Feel, I'm For Real, Peace Out, So In Love, Sugaru, Wild Rush,
[SPEAKER_11]: and Your Rain, the Rage Mix, Kiryamoka, which some of those we've announced on the show previously.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then we get into the licensed songs.
[SPEAKER_11]: Some of these aren't a surprise because actually an article that Loki had posted a while back about going into the disc and looking at the master song list did prove some of these songs would end up in DDR.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I noticed, I recognized the first one right away because I was hoping for this, Diving by Four Strings.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, here's the thing, it's like, they made, okay, the Master Song List, I mean, you work on songs for a long time, they might not make it into the actual game that time, they might save them for the next game, but it's just like, you know, all the songs that they said that would be in there, eventually made it in there, so...
[SPEAKER_10]: Hot, all those people that say, well, it wasn't in that game, Nemesis wasn't in TDR Max!
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, tough, this is what happens, okay?
[SPEAKER_10]: But anyways, as you were saying.
[SPEAKER_08]: They could have an intention to put it in a mix and prepare it for the thing and never not put it in the final release.
[SPEAKER_08]: Things change from beta to final.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's very true, that's very true.
[SPEAKER_11]: I actually thought I had a clip of Diving, but I guess that's on a CD, I don't have an MP3 of it anywhere.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh yeah, because you ripped the Four Strings album, didn't you?
[SPEAKER_11]: We're going to see if we can... Because diving is an awesome song.
[SPEAKER_11]: I want to play a little clip for you guys if we can get it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ooh, you got it?
[SPEAKER_11]: Play a clip through the computer.
[SPEAKER_11]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_11]: Here's a little clip of diving.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's not coming through.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, well.
[SPEAKER_11]: Loki's going to see if he can fix that.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'll copy it over real fast here.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's alright, it happens.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's see, we're going to get a copy of it real fast here.
[SPEAKER_11]: Other licensed songs that are going to be in DDR, Go West by the Pet Shop Boys.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think it's kind of funny that they have Pet Shop Boys in DDR now.
[SPEAKER_08]: That makes me happy.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because there's a lot of Pet Shop Boy covers that have been in DDR before.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, there was just New York City Boy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wasn't...
[SPEAKER_11]: New York City Boy, and wasn't there another?
[SPEAKER_11]: There's others.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, Loki got it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_11]: A clip of diving.
[SPEAKER_11]: Whoa, whoa, whoa.
[SPEAKER_11]: Turn it down a little.
[SPEAKER_11]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_11]: Play it in the middle somewhere.
Now it's too quiet.
There we go.
[SPEAKER_01]: Aren't these guys a previous cage match winner with this song?
[SPEAKER_01]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_12]: Whatever it may take, I'll keep on trying
[SPEAKER_11]: Move Your Feet by Junior Senior
[SPEAKER_11]: With the video, so that's going to be very cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was kind of neat seeing that at E3.
[SPEAKER_11]: Music by Darude, which I believe I've got a clip of it somewhere.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it's the race to find the clip.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know, whichever one of us can find the file faster.
[SPEAKER_08]: So far, Loki is in the lead.
[SPEAKER_08]: He seems to be looking through his list of folders.
[SPEAKER_08]: Doing a search would be easier.
[SPEAKER_11]: I had it at one point, but I don't know if I do anymore.
[SPEAKER_11]: Damn.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's like the Iron Chef commentary.
[SPEAKER_11]: Somewhat.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh no, I have next to you.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't have music.
[SPEAKER_11]: Damn.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll see if we can get a copy.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, alright, Loki's got it.
[SPEAKER_11]: And Loki wins.
[SPEAKER_11]: Loki wins.
[SPEAKER_11]: Play a clip somewhere in the middle here of music by Daruk.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, you're blasting people's speakers.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Planet Rock, Paul Oakenfold vs. Afrika Bambaataa.
[SPEAKER_11]: We've played that before, I believe, on this show.
[SPEAKER_11]: The Reflex, Duran Duran, which was in Japanese Max 2.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's pretty exciting.
[SPEAKER_06]: You've gone too far this time.
[SPEAKER_11]: Simply Being Loved by BT.
[SPEAKER_11]: Don't Clock Me from DDR Solo Mix.
[SPEAKER_11]: I believe that's one of our... That makes me happy.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's one of our songs that's in normal rotation on Orange Lounge Radio, I think.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it is.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_11]: So we are definitely happy that Don't Clock Me finally made it into a USDDR.
[SPEAKER_06]: Booty-tastic.
[SPEAKER_11]: And Highs Off You by 4Real.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I have no idea why this song was... I know why this song is in USA DDR, but the rest of us veterans are going to cringe.
[SPEAKER_11]: Kick the Can by Bus Stop has made its way into a DDR extreme.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know that song never pissed me off until there was that little kid at Golfland.
[SPEAKER_08]: You were there.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was there.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then he went to another machine and played like some other song repeatedly.
[SPEAKER_11]: You'll enjoy this.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was before the song was out.
[SPEAKER_11]: The next song that's going to be in DDR Extreme is an old boy George cover that you like, Miracle.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ah, play.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't, I only have the original.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't we have that in rotation?
[SPEAKER_11]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'd have to dig for it though.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's max two.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Let me see if I have it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let me see.
Ah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Everybody knows what Miracle sounds like at this point, don't they?
[SPEAKER_11]: No, I don't have that one.
[SPEAKER_11]: We don't have that one.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, Miracle was the first one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Was it?
[SPEAKER_08]: I thought it was the second one.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, Max 1, not Max 2.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, let's hear a little clip of Miracle.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's a miracle, it's a miracle, it's a miracle, it's a miracle
Thanks for watching!
Look at what you see
[SPEAKER_11]: This is Radio Station's CJ Boogie, with a brand new world premiere song from Captain Jack, Only You.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, There You'll Be, which was not in the Japanese release, was not even in there, but we get it.
[SPEAKER_11]: There You'll Be, DJ Speedo featuring Angelica, horrible, horrible speed cover of a horrible, horrible song, but I know there's fans of it out there, so hey me.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wonderland by Xtreme, that'll be cool, and here's our last licensed song, YMCA by the Village People.
[SPEAKER_11]: That would be funny.
[SPEAKER_10]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, these are the same songs as were in, like, Karaoke Revolution.
[SPEAKER_10]: So basically, it's like, you know, the 80s songs, but sung by some retard.
[SPEAKER_11]: I see.
[SPEAKER_11]: So Konami got a little creative there, and they took their licenses from Karaoke Revolution, and they took the original, I mean, the singers that they used on these songs, and they made DDR mixes out of them.
[SPEAKER_11]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_11]: What a clever move by Konami, I must say, to get some very popular songs, including Believe by Cher.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh my god!
[SPEAKER_11]: Bizarre Love Triangle.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: But it's not going to be the original New Order.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's somebody else singing it for Carrier Revolution.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ladies Night, Waiting for Tonight, and Like a Virgin.
[SPEAKER_05]: Will that make you happy, Rob?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, it will make me very happy.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's not the Eurobeat one.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, yeah, it's not the Eurobeat one.
[SPEAKER_11]: Also...
[SPEAKER_11]: A whole shitload of news on the iToy modes.
[SPEAKER_11]: This is the funny thing about DDR Extreme.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's like having DDR, and then you've got this sequel to iToy Play in it, too.
[SPEAKER_11]: There's all these new modes in there.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's crazy.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like, of course, you know, hands and feet, clean the screen.
[SPEAKER_11]: We talked about that previously.
[SPEAKER_11]: Coconut Panic has nothing to do with DDR.
[SPEAKER_11]: You just shake these coconut trees.
[SPEAKER_11]: By the way, for those who don't know what the iToy is, that's the little camera.
[SPEAKER_11]: The Thing That Sucks Magical Ball
[SPEAKER_11]: If it had been magical balls, it would have been funnier.
[SPEAKER_08]: That would have been awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Almost as funny as Super Monkey Ball.
[SPEAKER_11]: There's going to be like a party mode that has some stuff, including Hyper Dash, which is like that old school Konami game, like track and field.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's going to be like that, but with the eye toy.
[SPEAKER_11]: So I'm looking forward to seeing what they do with that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Or no, no, I'm sorry, not eye toy.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're just going to use the left and right arrows on DDR pads.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's like bringing back the power pad.
[SPEAKER_11]: So that's going to be cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then basically you can hit the down button and it puts a pitfall in front of the other person.
[SPEAKER_10]: They have to hit the up button to jump.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's going to be very interesting.
[SPEAKER_11]: Feeding Frenzy, which is going to, it shows animals and then every arrow on the pad is like a carrot or a fish.
[SPEAKER_11]: And you have to feed the animal the appropriate food by stepping on the arrow.
[SPEAKER_11]: Isn't that weird?
[SPEAKER_08]: Sounds kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sounds kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_11]: Is what?
[SPEAKER_11]: and then there will be a challenge mode as well in DDR which is going to be interesting.
[SPEAKER_11]: Also, there were some videos released by another website and one of them gives you a sneak peek at what some of the interface music is going to sound like.
[SPEAKER_11]: So you kind of get a preview that they've done new interface music for it too.
[SPEAKER_11]: And it's all happy!
[SPEAKER_11]: It's fluffy and all happy.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it's not as awesome as a stupid barber.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, nothing is as awesome as a stupid barber.
[SPEAKER_11]: Which I noticed wasn't on that list.
[SPEAKER_11]: Or did I?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it was on there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Was it?
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, I must have just missed it completely.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because remember I went yay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Here's the thing, they should have really had like a porn star giant tits doing, you know, the little animation thing there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because they had that one chick jumping up and down that was not doing anything for me.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, we opened up the Skype line again.
[SPEAKER_11]: If you have any comments on DDR, Extreme USA, something you want to share, we'll go ahead and take your call.
[SPEAKER_11]: Maybe something we didn't mention that you really wanted to make sure we got out there.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know one thing that was pretty humorous was they actually ran an article on Yahoo News.
[SPEAKER_11]: Tell us about this, Loki, because you read about this.
[SPEAKER_11]: You actually posted the article, a link to it on our site, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, this guy is a professional game reviewer, and I honestly don't think he's ever played this game that he reviewed.
[SPEAKER_10]: Um, because honestly, he doesn't know shit about DDR at all.
[SPEAKER_10]: He has kept saying DDR Max from the Xbox, and just like, crap like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: He didn't know what the fuck he was talking about, and just comparing it with like, he pretty much was talking out of his ass throughout the whole interview.
[SPEAKER_10]: So the whole interview, the whole review of the damn thing was just completely shit, but, you know, at least it had pictures and pretty movies.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, that's where that movie I just played for you guys came from.
[SPEAKER_11]: Of course, you can't see movies over the radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: But, anyway, we're going to take a call real fast.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hello, Orange Lounge, you are on Z-Air.
[SPEAKER_18]: Hey, Rob, can you hear me?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, we can.
[SPEAKER_18]: Hey, this is Dark Knight off of the East Coast.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey, Dark Knight, how are you doing?
[SPEAKER_18]: All right.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, so a quick comment on those song lists.
[SPEAKER_18]: This is a pretty decent list, though.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, it's surprisingly different than the arcade extreme, which is good, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a little yellow different.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, but some of these songs, I'm probably going to be, like, feeling miserably.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey, it takes practice.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm looking forward, as much as I think the eye toy is kind of a one-trick pony, I'm looking forward to having my trick the day I get extreme and being able to play the eye toy modes on there.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think it's going to be pretty cute.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, but that sub-para-para mode, that's kind of questionable, though.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, you know, it's different.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's the closest thing we're ever going to get to anything like it in the U.S., so we might as well deal with it.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's true, that's true.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anything in particular on the list that you are very excited about?
[SPEAKER_18]: Wild Rush, mostly.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wild Rush?
[SPEAKER_18]: I could play that song easily.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wild Rush is awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: What about the... I know, I love Wild Rush too, but I thought maybe a licensed song, like, you know, diving.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm so excited about diving, because I love four strings.
[SPEAKER_11]: I love them.
[SPEAKER_11]: And so I'm excited that diving's in there, so.
[SPEAKER_18]: Some of the songs kind of cringe at Never Ending Story, because in my area...
[SPEAKER_18]: That song has been played out on our fifth mix machine every time we had it.
[SPEAKER_18]: Thank God it's gone now.
[SPEAKER_11]: Which song is that again?
[SPEAKER_18]: Never Ending Story.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, Never Ending Story.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey, don't you knock that song.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm sorry, man.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's been on everybody's play around.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm like, just skip it this once.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: In our chatroom, they're saying it's not Parapara mode.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's more like Dance Maniacs mode.
[SPEAKER_11]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_11]: Whatever you want to call it.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's the only Bomani hand thing we're going to have in the U.S., so deal.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's like Flag Down Taxi mode is more like what it is.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not even Dance Maniacs.
[SPEAKER_10]: I look like a fucking retard.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's what it is.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_11]: When I played Clean the Screen, I did look like a fucking retard, but it was fun.
[SPEAKER_11]: And you know what was cool about it is that it's more of a workout.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was the intention, I think.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, you know how a lot of people play DDR for the workout aspect of it?
[SPEAKER_11]: When you're moving your arms in it, too, that's like three, four times the workout.
[SPEAKER_11]: Would you rather look like a goofball or do the river dance?
[SPEAKER_11]: I would rather look like a goofball and then have a six-pack.
[SPEAKER_05]: How does moving your arms give you an ab workout, Rob?
[SPEAKER_11]: Just shut up.
[SPEAKER_11]: Don't ruin my fantasy, bitch!
[SPEAKER_10]: No, no, I want to see pure interactivity, just like Gal's Panic, where they actually had 1-800 numbers, you could call and talk to the women once you beat that level.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: You are being way too random.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyway, anything else you want to say about Extreme Dark Knight?
[SPEAKER_18]: No, that's about it, man.
[SPEAKER_18]: I just hope this game will be successful as everyone's, man.
[SPEAKER_18]: Just keep it going long enough for me.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think it's going to be huge.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know what I think, though?
[SPEAKER_11]: Is that this is going to get people... Between this and Ultramix 2, and I really think Ultramix 2 is going to surprise a lot of people.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think people who have been bashing the Xbox, and I admit, I was in this category.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then finally I got swayed and I bought Ultramix and I kind of ate my words on this show that it really isn't that bad.
[SPEAKER_11]: But Ultramix 2...
[SPEAKER_11]: Mark my words right here and right now, not all of you people out there that are bashing Xbox, but 80% of you are going to eat your words when Ultramix 2 comes out.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I admit, I had to eat my words at one point, you will too.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think between Ultramix 2 and Extreme, people are going to be rioting for a new arcade mix.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because I think this is going to show that US knows their shit when it comes to putting these games together.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think there's so many new things in there that people are just going to say, why can't we have a new arcade mix?
[SPEAKER_11]: Why, why, why?
[SPEAKER_10]: God, that they don't put a fucking Itoy thing on the arcade mix if there was ever one to come out, because that'd be the fucking stupidest thing ever.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I could go into why that would be retarded later.
[SPEAKER_06]: It would give you plenty of opportunity to make fun of people.
[SPEAKER_11]: But still, just the licenses, just the new interfaces, the new stuff, there's enough.
[SPEAKER_11]: You could take out the Itoy and you would have enough cool stuff for an arcade mix.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'd like to go into why that's stupid right now, okay?
[SPEAKER_10]: I played that stupid game I Can Boogie, okay, which is pretty much the arcade version of Itoy Groove.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let me just say this, it sucks.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just about as good as playing iToy Groove, it's just as sensitive, it didn't detect shit, I completely failed my song, even though I was hitting it just right.
[SPEAKER_10]: And they have really stupid music in there, like Barbie Girl and hot stuff, and like, all this like, gay-ass shit, okay?
[SPEAKER_10]: No thank you.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, guys.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thanks, man.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, we're just, like, holding you on the line, Dark Knight.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll let you get back to listening to the show.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thanks for calling in.
[SPEAKER_11]: No problem.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_18]: That was fun.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll open it back up.
[SPEAKER_11]: Maybe one more person let him through.
[SPEAKER_11]: DDR Extreme.
[SPEAKER_11]: Garrett, you've been awfully quiet over there.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know you don't care as much about DDR as you do 2DX.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hi!
[SPEAKER_11]: And pop music.
[SPEAKER_11]: But what do you think about all this?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well...
[SPEAKER_09]: The last time I played DDR was when you were over at my house and we decided to see if my red octane pad was still broken.
[SPEAKER_11]: And that was the last time I played DDR, by the way, which was about three weeks ago, was it?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: I had fun with it, but, you know, it's just... I mean, if they're not going to make anything new in Japan, I shouldn't be that concerned about them making anything new here because I don't really give a crap about licensed songs a lot of the time.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm more about the original stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: So... But the new modes and the new features don't do it for you?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, okay, like, remember...
[SPEAKER_09]: Back in the day, that PC game called Kai's Photogu
[SPEAKER_09]: No, no idea what you're talking about, but okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I've seen screenshots of these new eye toy modes for DDR Extreme.
[SPEAKER_09]: What the fuck is this?
[SPEAKER_09]: It looks like some goofy piece of crap like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: And, you know, it's like, they should just say it's a bonus game for Extreme.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's not a part of Extreme.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's Extreme bundled with eye toy bullshit.
[SPEAKER_11]: But see, I give Konami a little credit for, you know, giving us new eye toy bullshit or new bullshit at all and not just, you know...
[SPEAKER_11]: It's just not your cup of tea
[SPEAKER_09]: It lost its value.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wake you up when 2DX comes out.
[SPEAKER_09]: When I want to get some exercise on again, I'll break it out and then I might buy a new, like I might buy Extreme USA when that's here if I feel like getting in shape or something.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's about it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm going to put up a thing in our forums when Ultramix 2 comes out because I want to see how many people went out and bought an Xbox because of Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think it's going to be... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: I just... There's just too much hype about it, and I think it's going to live up to the hype.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're going to move on to the other Bomani news?
[SPEAKER_11]: Actually, I want to save that.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think I kind of want to get into Cage Match now, because it's 8 o'clock already.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're already halfway through the show, so we've got to get some of our regular bits out of the way here.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Are you doing more bad video game trivia that I can suck at?
[SPEAKER_11]: What, the Orange Crush stuff?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, the... No, no, that was a Vanilla Sky thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Darn.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: That was one of my spin-offs.
[SPEAKER_09]: Shows you how often I come here.
[SPEAKER_11]: Can they hear the Tetris over there?
[SPEAKER_11]: Somebody's saying, who's playing Tetris?
[SPEAKER_11]: Can they hear that over the air?
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hopefully not.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, yeah, we're going to get into the cage match right now.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, my bad, I thought they could hear it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Just a reminder, you have to be in the chatroom if you want to participate in our cage match, but it is the chatters that pick the winners of this stuff, so let's get into it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Last week on the Orange Lounge Radio Cage Match Oh, the way the Cage Match works, I should explain this Three songs picked by the hosts It used to be songs that would be good for music video games Like DDR and 2DX and stuff But it just kind of turned into What's a cool song?
[SPEAKER_11]: Is basically what it turned into, so that's okay But each song picks a host Each host picks, each song picks a host?
[SPEAKER_11]: No Each host picks a song And then...
[SPEAKER_11]: We let you guys vote on them, and then the winner goes into rotation all week long here on Orange Ones Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: Now, I hear that while I was gone, my song lost, and it was taken over by Loki's pick.
[SPEAKER_11]: And Loki, what did you put in the cage match last week that ended up winning?
[SPEAKER_10]: of the Ecstasy 14 Hours Club Mix, the one that I made and played.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was just being lazy.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, and I really like this mix, though, so we'll see.
[SPEAKER_11]: So here it is.
[SPEAKER_11]: You only get to hear a clip of it because it is last week's winner.
[SPEAKER_11]: So we only play a little clip of it because we assume you already heard it last week, like a good listener would.
[SPEAKER_11]: So here it is, a little clip of Ecstasy, the 14 Hours Club Mix.
[SPEAKER_11]: Enjoy, guys.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, that was a clip of song number one in tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_11]: A very sexy remix of Ecstasy done by our very own Loki.
[SPEAKER_11]: 14 hours club mix.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, yeah, wow, it's going to be tough to beat.
[SPEAKER_11]: But Jamie and I are certainly going to try.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think I have a song that might do it.
[SPEAKER_11]: But we'll give yours a try too, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I got to say, looking at your pick...
[SPEAKER_11]: This isn't what I would think you would listen to.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm very surprised by your pick.
[SPEAKER_11]: Turn on your mic.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a Metro Mix.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would listen to it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh yeah, you like those Metro Mixes.
[SPEAKER_11]: But the artist is somebody I would never expect you to like.
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_08]: Julio Iglesias has a sexy voice.
[SPEAKER_11]: You mean Enrique?
[SPEAKER_08]: Enrique.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I used to listen to him too.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, tell us about your cage match picks for tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'd take Enrique Iglesias' Hero, the Metro Mix, because it's a Metro Mix.
[SPEAKER_11]: And so is this something that you think would be good in DDR?
[SPEAKER_11]: It's just cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: It would be playable, but I mean, it's... It's just... Good voice, good music.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a Metro mix, that's enough for me.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll see what the folks here think.
[SPEAKER_11]: Here it is, Enrique Iglesias with Hero, the Metro mix.
[SPEAKER_11]: Jamie's pick for tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: Enjoy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Would you dance?
[SPEAKER_04]: If I asked you to dance?
[SPEAKER_04]: Would you run and never look back?
[SPEAKER_04]: Would you cry if you saw me crying?
[SPEAKER_04]: Would you save my soul tonight?
[SPEAKER_02]: Would you tremble if I touched your lips?
[SPEAKER_04]: Now would you die for the one you love?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hold me in your arms tonight
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll be your hero, baby I can kiss away the pain I will stand by you forever You kiss me, but let me do it for me
[SPEAKER_04]: Would you lie?
[SPEAKER_04]: Would you remind?
Am I in too deep?
[SPEAKER_04]: Have I lost my mind?
[SPEAKER_02]: I will stand by you forever You can take my breath away I just wanna hold you I just wanna hold you Oh yeah Come into me
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I don't care.
[SPEAKER_04]: You'll be here tonight.
I can be your hero, baby.
I can give away the fight.
[SPEAKER_02]: I will stand by you forever You can take my place
[SPEAKER_02]: I can kiss away the pain And I will stand by you Forever You can take my breath away You
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_11]: Song number two in tonight's cage match, Enrique Iglesias, Hero.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's go around the room now, and this is the part where we tell you what we think.
[SPEAKER_11]: But remember, it is up to you guys.
[SPEAKER_11]: You have to join our chat room, orangelawnradio.com, and then you can vote and tell us what you think.
[SPEAKER_11]: Jamie.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good voice.
[SPEAKER_08]: Metro Max, make it like a nine for me.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, nine from Jamie.
[SPEAKER_11]: Garrett.
[SPEAKER_09]: I hear the original version of that song all damn day at work.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't want to hear it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Scale of one to ten.
[SPEAKER_09]: Bel Air Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: No comment.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, uh, Bugs.
[SPEAKER_17]: I was playing Excited Bike.
[SPEAKER_17]: Excited Bike was better.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, Loki.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was eh.
[SPEAKER_10]: The original song was like eh, and this is just like eh with a new beat in the background.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like it was like a vibe.
[SPEAKER_11]: Um, I, it's definitely, I like it better than the original, I like it with the added beat, um, so it's above average to me, so I give it like a 7, so it's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: Um, but I've heard better Metro mixes, like I like the Daniel Bedingfield ones better, but that's alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyway, uh, moving on.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm going to try this from iTunes tonight, because this is a song I actually bought on iTunes.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hopefully it works for you guys.
[SPEAKER_11]: Song number three in tonight's cage match is my pick, and I don't know if you guys have heard, but Utada Hikaru is going to be coming out with a US album.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you to Utada.com
Everybody wants me to be your angel Everybody wants something special
Thank you for watching!
and many more.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, that was song number three in tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_11]: Utada with Devil Inside.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's her first American single.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, unless you count Simple and Clean, but that wasn't really a single.
[SPEAKER_11]: Devil Inside, the Richard Vision radio edit.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's go around and see what everybody thought.
[SPEAKER_11]: Jamie!
[SPEAKER_07]: I really, really dig her voice, but that was such a boring remix that I give it a 6.
[SPEAKER_08]: The voice gets a 10, the mix itself would get like a 4, so she gets a 6.
[SPEAKER_11]: I honestly thought the original was so repetitive that it wouldn't have worked in Cage Match.
[SPEAKER_11]: I agree, the remix is kind of... Garrett.
[SPEAKER_09]: I never heard the original or the remix, and I was pretty fond of it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I liked her voice a lot in that, too.
[SPEAKER_09]: Everything I usually hear from her...
[SPEAKER_09]: It sounds like they want to be like Britney or something, so it's good to hear something that sounded slightly more original vocally, so I give it a 7.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, 7 from Garrett.
[SPEAKER_11]: Bugs, if we can get him a mic.
[SPEAKER_11]: If he's not too busy playing something on the main cabinet.
[SPEAKER_17]: Actually, I was kind of listening to it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, okay, what did you think?
[SPEAKER_17]: It was better than the last one.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, what did you give it on a scale of 1 to 10?
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, scales, yeah.
[SPEAKER_17]: Uh, seven.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Uh, Loki!
[SPEAKER_10]: Um, you know, I swear to God I've heard that, like, beat in another song.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just don't remember what exactly it was.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, it was like, eh, it was, eh.
[SPEAKER_10]: I like her, I like her music, but that was just, like, really crappy.
[SPEAKER_10]: She should really just take everything she's done in Japan, just bring it over here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Don't try to, you know, make it, you know, more American by taking a shit on it, you know.
[SPEAKER_10]: So yeah, I'll give it like a 6.
[SPEAKER_11]: Me personally, it's very disco to me, and disco rocks, so I give it an 8.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, let's review one more time, and then you can vote in our chatroom, www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_11]: Song number one tonight, Ecstasy, the 14-hour club mix.
[SPEAKER_11]: Song number two in tonight's cage match is Enrique Iglesias with Hero, the Metro Mix.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's try that again.
[SPEAKER_11]: Song number two in tonight's cage match was Enrique Iglesias with Hero, the Metro Mix.
[SPEAKER_11]: And song number three in tonight's cage match was Utada with Devil Inside, the Richard Vision radio edit.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Send those votes on over to www.orangeonthrade.com, but then click on chat and then the sky in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_11]: So place vote now over your private message in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then we'll do this.
[SPEAKER_11]: I tried to do this two weeks ago, but nobody did it.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I will open up the Skype line if anybody wants to make a plea for one of those songs.
[SPEAKER_11]: If anybody has a plea for one of those songs to win.
[SPEAKER_11]: So we'll see if anybody calls in on that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Any predictions for which you guys think will win?
[SPEAKER_08]: Eh.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think Loki's will win again.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll see, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: I vote for Holic.
[SPEAKER_11]: You can't vote for Holic.
[SPEAKER_08]: One of these two, Holic's going to win.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, um, moving on, um, I guess we'll get into the other big Bomondi news.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, nobody wanted to call on that, so we'll just, uh, close the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, uh, let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know that someone said they're going, I can't get it to work!
[SPEAKER_08]: I have to make a comment, and I can't get it to work!
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Or not.
[SPEAKER_11]: Uh, it's alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Um, so who wants to tell us about the, uh, 2DX11th style news?
[SPEAKER_11]: Garrett's raising his hand.
[SPEAKER_11]: Me, me, me, me, me.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know what's the weirdest thing?
[SPEAKER_11]: I have to say, first off, are you sure this is legit?
[SPEAKER_09]: Because when I was reading some of this stuff, it sounded very... There's one part of it that makes me go, whoa, wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, it did have that kind of air to DDR Extreme 2 stuff that was going around.
[SPEAKER_09]: Right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, but, yeah, well, anyways, um, well, actually, the strangest thing is, um, DJP on Damani Style, like, I haven't talked to him in a long time, and then we just, like, he just messaged me, like, like, one morning, he was like, oh, they, we just found out, Eleven Style, la la la, um...
[SPEAKER_09]: The only thing that makes it look fake is all the damn speculation that's going on it because there isn't a lot of concrete information.
[SPEAKER_09]: There is a fax that came out.
[SPEAKER_09]: They always send these faxes out to arcades when there's a new style coming out and test locations seem to give arcades information about the next upgrade kit and stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: And that was what was sent to whoever, I forgot the whole chain of people,
[SPEAKER_09]: It went through, but they said their sources from where it came from are very legit, and I believe everything on the facts, but people are already saying that, oh, Coors K is doing the system music, oh, there's going to be an Iconoclasm song in it, and all this other crap.
[SPEAKER_11]: And it's not just wishful thinking.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because the part that got me was that they said that Ono Ken was going to have a song in it.
[SPEAKER_11]: And don't get me wrong, I think that should happen because he's a very talented guy.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's all the speculation that I have.
[SPEAKER_09]: But that makes me go, that's so fanboyish.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like I said, Chorus K doing the system music.
[SPEAKER_09]: DJ Taka's done all the system music except Slake did the theme for 8th style.
[SPEAKER_09]: Unless I'm disregarding old stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: But Kors K has kind of made more and more of a presence in 2DX, 9th, 10th.
[SPEAKER_09]: I would say it would make more sense for Ryu Star to do the system music.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because all of a sudden it went from one song in 4th, a remix in 9th, and then three new songs in 10th.
[SPEAKER_09]: And Kors K still only has two songs in existence.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was in a very Japanese-y mood to try and make out much of it, but one thing I did notice on there, because a lot of people are saying that it's going to be transplant-heavy,
[SPEAKER_09]: I think that they may have misread that, or I just didn't read it thoroughly enough.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's a part at the bottom where it mentions pop music, drum mania, and guitar freaks, but it says collaboration in Katakana.
[SPEAKER_09]: So it may be more artists from other games are crossing over into this.
[SPEAKER_11]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_11]: Also, speaking of artists, we just got this word in our chatroom.
[SPEAKER_11]: Mel B, who passes along some official news from Konami, mentions that Shoti... I don't think he's done anything in 2DX, but DDR, of course, is a stupid barber.
[SPEAKER_11]: Shoti has left... has parted ways with Konami, so we won't be seeing any more songs from him, which is too bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: Aw, no more Shoichiro Hirata?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, because... Aw.
[SPEAKER_09]: There was no more Akira Shunsuke in Poppin' Music 11.
[SPEAKER_09]: Once I got my damn CD, I rifled through the booklet and he's gone too.
[SPEAKER_09]: The only thing that I think is really, really weird about that fax is that it's Beatmania 2DX11-style red.
[SPEAKER_11]: What the hell is that?
[SPEAKER_11]: 2DX Red.
[SPEAKER_11]: Did you see the fax?
[SPEAKER_11]: No, you can actually see the actual fax?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, you can see the fax.
[SPEAKER_09]: They have pictures of Emall cards on it too.
[SPEAKER_09]: They said there's going to be an upgrade for the Emall machine or system or something.
[SPEAKER_09]: They said there will be over 300 songs included in the arcade, I think.
[SPEAKER_09]: But yeah, just go to Bimani Style real quick.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, I'm going, I'm going.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's see, let's check this out.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then, it's on the last... Thank God they don't have that god-awful music.
[SPEAKER_11]: Actually, I really like that song they used to play on here, but man, after hearing it for like three weeks... And then, down at the bottom...
[SPEAKER_09]: Bottom, bottom, bottom, bottom, bottom.
[SPEAKER_09]: Headlines.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, we're on our way.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll take a look at the facts here, because I haven't seen this.
[SPEAKER_09]: Remember, I was gone for two weeks.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sorry, where the hell did I go?
[SPEAKER_11]: I was completely out of the loop for like two weeks.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, there it is.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, just click on the first page.
[SPEAKER_11]: And it's a link right there.
[SPEAKER_11]: So when I came back home, I was like, oh, interesting.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_11]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's see, there's going to be more than... What?
[SPEAKER_11]: With a little screenshot and everything?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, okay, more than 45 new songs, more than 320 songs in the fucking arcade.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here's all those email cards.
[SPEAKER_09]: Blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_09]: See, there's the thing right here that says... It's like... I'm being lazy.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like Miscellaneous Spamani...
[SPEAKER_09]: Uh, series, something, music, collab, collaboration, no you can't translate it, it's a scan.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, collaboration.
[SPEAKER_09]: It doesn't say transplant, it says collaboration.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's an English word they're using.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, poppin' music, drum and guitar freaks.
[SPEAKER_09]: New something, something, participating, entry, user, something.
[SPEAKER_11]: Garrett's going through and actually reading what Japanese he knows.
[SPEAKER_11]: He's reading some of the Japanese.
[SPEAKER_11]: The facts is all in Japanese, but he's reading some of it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I can type it out later and do a lazy translation on it, too.
[SPEAKER_09]: Somebody obviously already translated it.
[SPEAKER_09]: All the people who did the speculating and said stuff about what was listed in here, I have no idea who actually did that or if they were going off their own guesses or actually translated some of it.
[SPEAKER_09]: They have a lot of Japanese users on there that can do that though Very interesting
[SPEAKER_10]: The pictures that they show are really shitty, but maybe, like, for instance, maybe the background for, like, that one screenshot was FMV from an Onukin song, because he does do his, you know, BMS files with, you know, full motion video, and so they might have recognized that, and that's where the speculation for that comes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just a guess.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_09]: I couldn't see anything in it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, we'll, uh,
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know, I mean, it's a scan of a fax, I mean, eh, you know.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, no, it's just the fax.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, yeah, actually, yeah, the scan of the fax, but...
[SPEAKER_09]: It's going to look the same either way.
[SPEAKER_09]: I want to spit out the machine where it was faxed from.
[SPEAKER_11]: Still, it's just that Onokan thing, it just reeks of fanboy.
[SPEAKER_11]: And it's not that I don't want to believe it's true, because I think that's awesome, but it's just so... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think if it is true, that's very cool that Konami did that.
[SPEAKER_11]: The Iconoclasm thing is very fanboy, too.
[SPEAKER_11]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_11]: It is.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't see how you would know what the...
[SPEAKER_09]: There were so many people who planted bullshit rumors when TenthStyle was coming out.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're being called out in the chatroom because it's not really 11th style, because now it's the 2DX Red.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's not 11th style, it's 2DX Red.
[SPEAKER_11]: But you know, how long were we calling it DDR6 mix before we found it?
[SPEAKER_09]: It still has an 11 in it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, there's a little 11 in there, so it's a reference to it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't think we're going to be seeing blue or yellow or any other color.
[SPEAKER_11]: Somebody suggested 2DX grape for 12.
[SPEAKER_11]: I want a purple 2DX.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's what I want.
[SPEAKER_11]: I hope they change the interface up and stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm sorry, what, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_11]: We can't hear you.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was taking a nap.
[SPEAKER_08]: 2DX burning.
[SPEAKER_11]: Burning Heat Burning Burning Burning Nation Mix Like a 2DX Muru Mix or something Alright That'd be cool Anything else you gotta think of on 2DX When the fax came out they said that the test location was going on that day, they were wrong
[SPEAKER_09]: They reconfirmed it, and they said that it should actually be going on within this next week, because when they send these faxes, all the test locations have happened within a week of them sending it, usually.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, that's kind of quick.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, it's just a fax.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just for the test location.
[SPEAKER_09]: They do think these things kind of last a moment anyway, so this week, hopefully, we'll probably sing...
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, but it seems like the time between 8th's release and anything on 9th and then 9th's release and anything on 10th was longer than 10th's release and now this first bit of indication that there will be a continuation of the series.
[SPEAKER_09]: 10th's kind of snuck up after 9th in my opinion.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: They'd hella jump on these things on the Drum Man and Guitar Freak stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: They just spew those things out.
[SPEAKER_09]: But they said that the test location should probably be going on within a week or so.
[SPEAKER_09]: They think that the actual arcade will be out in October.
[SPEAKER_09]: And also, if everyone didn't know, 8th Style CS will be released before the year is over.
[SPEAKER_11]: Good.
[SPEAKER_11]: Good news.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Lots of fun stuff in the 2DX front then.
[SPEAKER_11]: Good, so it's not a dying series.
[SPEAKER_11]: No.
[SPEAKER_09]: No.
[SPEAKER_11]: As much as people would like you to believe.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're going to reveal, if that's all you've got to say on 2DX.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll go ahead and open up the Skype line if somebody has a comment they want to say on 2DX 11, 2DX Red, whatever you want to call it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Why 2DX Red?
[SPEAKER_11]: Why?
[SPEAKER_11]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_11]: I guess, why Max?
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, why Max?
[SPEAKER_11]: Why anything?
[SPEAKER_10]: Why Pokemon Red?
[SPEAKER_10]: Why Pokemon Blue?
[SPEAKER_09]: Why do they have all their bad English titles and their banners and stuff?
[SPEAKER_11]: Somebody in our chatroom was comparing it to Dance Mania, being like Dance Mania Best Red and Best Yellow.
[SPEAKER_11]: Which is interesting because 2DX isn't really related to Dance Mania, yet that kind of makes sense.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Maybe it's a Japanese thing, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, here comes the call.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's check out what's going on.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hello, you're on Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_20]: Hey, what's up?
[SPEAKER_11]: We got a little bit of problem with your bandwidth.
[SPEAKER_11]: You're cutting up a little bit.
[SPEAKER_11]: Weird.
[SPEAKER_11]: Is your stream running?
[SPEAKER_11]: Stop the station if you have the station running.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ooh, he's cutting out really bad.
[SPEAKER_11]: Can he say something again?
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, buddy, you're cutting out really bad.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_11]: See, try calling back in a little bit.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know what's going on there.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sorry about that.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's too bad.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, um, well, we'll just, uh, try it again in a little bit.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll keep it open.
[SPEAKER_11]: Um, moving on.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, with the sky blind still open, if anybody's got comment on 2DX, what do you think of all this, Loki?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't play 2DX.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, Siggy's gonna try back.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're gonna see if it works this time.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, can you hear us now?
[SPEAKER_20]: Hey, what's up?
[SPEAKER_11]: Huh, weird.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, what's up?
[SPEAKER_11]: You know what, you're still cutting out really, really bad.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're going to have to... Send me a message in the chat room and we'll address your comments.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sorry, bud.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Why are we playing this game?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because it's Strider, which is the most awesome game ever.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nobody in video games is cooler than Strider, hear you.
[SPEAKER_11]: I asked Siggy to send me his thoughts over a private message, so we'll address those in a little bit.
[SPEAKER_11]: Meanwhile, let's talk about the winner of tonight's cage match, shall we?
[SPEAKER_11]: That'll be exciting.
[SPEAKER_11]: Tonight's cage match winner really isn't much of a surprise.
[SPEAKER_11]: Loki wins it again.
[SPEAKER_11]: with Ecstasy, the 14 Hours Club Mix.
[SPEAKER_11]: Congratulations to you, my friend.
[SPEAKER_11]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, so, hey, speaking of which, Loki, any sim news you got going on in the world of the simulations?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, there's a little bit.
[SPEAKER_10]: Starting off with a few things.
[SPEAKER_10]: I downloaded this really cool theme earlier this week.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was called Technolizer something to that effect.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyways, it's just some really cool Stepmania theme that's, I don't know, it just looks a little different than the rest of them.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can check it out on Stepmania.
[SPEAKER_10]: They have it under the themes form.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's under a thread called, I found this really cool Stepmania theme.
[SPEAKER_10]: What?
[SPEAKER_11]: Was that the theme you were showing me the other night?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because that was an awesome theme.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, that was the one I was showing you the other night.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyways, so there's that one.
[SPEAKER_10]: Other than that, some developments, as far as sim stuff goes, there's a guy that figured out how to rip the Polygon dancing characters out of the DDR games, so he's doing that now.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that's kinda cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: And with that, he's also getting all the graphics and background animations from the games, so pretty much everything is being able to be ripped from DDR now, so nothing really left.
[SPEAKER_10]: Aside from that, there's also...
[SPEAKER_10]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_10]: And, um, so those are on there.
[SPEAKER_10]: And, um, aside from all that, um, in case you haven't been following stuff, they actually do have support now being added in StepMania for a bunch of different game types, including BeatMania, DanceManiacs, and Technomotion, which I thought was interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: Um, so those you can download, actually, and play it, and I'm sure Alpha, um, I think 22 now will be coming out any time now.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that's pretty much all that's going on right now.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_11]: Now what we're going to do, we're going to go to a break, I think, and then we'll come back and we'll get into the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_11]: So if you have something angsty you want to send to us all, go to our chat room and send me a private message with your angst.
[SPEAKER_11]: In the meantime, we're going to hear a couple more songs from Poppin' 11, and I believe Garrett has another surprise for us.
[SPEAKER_11]: So tell us about what we're going to hear this break, Garrett.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, first, I picked another song for Rob.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a remix of one of his songs that has a Penguin-esque character in it.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a remix of Requiem from Poppin' Music 9.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then, after that, is a CS9 song.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, all the CS9 songs were on this soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's...
[SPEAKER_09]: Yumei Tou Genjitsu
[SPEAKER_09]: Another remix of Yo-Kon-Ko, but this is from Death's Rose album, and it's just like a pretty much all heavy metal mix.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's strangely, it's basically game size, but they added in another verse, so they cut off the beginning verse, and there's no reggae to it anymore.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, but it's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: So yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, let's check it out.
[SPEAKER_11]: Starting this set off with a remix of Requiem.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, enjoy.
Thank you.
DarkSakura
Thanks for watching!
and more.
[SPEAKER_21]: and the rest.
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_16]: And now, let's listen in to an Orange Lounge Radio staff meeting as they debate some of the new programming coming to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: Jamie, I have a suggestion about some of the music in our Bomani Music and More program.
[SPEAKER_11]: Can we talk about that?
[SPEAKER_06]: No subject will ever be taboo.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, I was thinking maybe we should move Pump Up the Volume from Tuesday Nights.
[SPEAKER_01]: Except, of course, a subject that was just under discussion.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, well, what would you think if maybe we cut back on some of the tack music we play on the station?
[SPEAKER_06]: I collect your fucking head.
[SPEAKER_20]: Just like this fucker here.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh my god, why did you do that to Loki?
[SPEAKER_01]: The holic thing on episode 69 was just a joke!
[SPEAKER_01]: Now if any of you sons of bitches got anything else to say, now's the fucking time!
[SPEAKER_16]: Orange Lounge Radio, where everybody has a say.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, everybody has a say here on Orange Lounge Radio, including you guys through our chat room, orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_11]: Click on chat.
[SPEAKER_11]: And yes, that promo works again because Jamie is moving Pump Up the Volume to Tuesday night starting this week.
[SPEAKER_11]: Jamie, I know you're over there playing something on Loki's main cabinet.
[SPEAKER_11]: Psycho Soldier, which you can see on our webcam over at www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: Put the mic up to it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's got DigiDice singing in it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Are we hearing it?
[SPEAKER_11]: You died.
[SPEAKER_11]: So tell us about Pump Up the Volume while you play Psycho Soldier here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, I play good music and that's about it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Why are you moving?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I'm going to school.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, so what time on Tuesday nights can we expect to hear your show?
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, I'm supposed to start my pre-show at 7 o'clock so I usually get forward and start it early.
[SPEAKER_08]: Subtitles by the Amara.org community
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_11]: I do miss Vanilla Sky, though.
[SPEAKER_11]: That was a great show for me.
[SPEAKER_11]: I want to bring it back.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_11]: And Loki, you ever going to do anything?
[SPEAKER_11]: Weren't you going to have a game show in 2004?
[SPEAKER_11]: Did that get pushed back to 2005?
[SPEAKER_10]: It got pushed back to 2000.
[SPEAKER_10]: Never.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm still running into problems with MAME.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've got to work on my cabinet a little bit.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have to install more RAM because I'm getting lag on some of the keys.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I have to take out Joy to Key and reset all my buttons and stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: The FU's of the week
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, this is bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: Here is justice.
[SPEAKER_08]: Big F you goes to work for being busy, busy, busy, busy, busy.
[SPEAKER_08]: And did I say it was busy?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's horrendously busy.
[SPEAKER_08]: And also a big F you goes toward, like,
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just that this week I've been too busy to be angsty about things, if you can believe that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'd have to say another one goes toward people who have big patience issues.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, there's some things it's okay to be impatient about, but not driving.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, do not change lanes when you are about to hit somebody.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like this stupid fucker behind me who was right on my tail the entire time on the freeway today.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just need to get a Humvee.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's all there is to it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I need to drive a Humvee with an assault rifle.
[SPEAKER_08]: Right on the top.
[SPEAKER_08]: and I'll need like a gunner to drive with me.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, it's eight turns.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll need a gunner, the person can drive.
[SPEAKER_11]: What was that game with the two, where you and your friend would sit in there and like crash and, it's like Crash and Dance or something.
[SPEAKER_11]: Bucky and Wild.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bucky and Wild.
[SPEAKER_08]: We had one of those at my arcade that I worked at.
[SPEAKER_08]: But yeah, I need something like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or I just need like, you know,
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sure it's very legal too.
[SPEAKER_08]: It is in South Africa, but damn we're not there.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just downloaded Lucky and Wild.
[SPEAKER_08]: You want to know what sucks though?
[SPEAKER_08]: As much as I would love to actually get a real Humvee and, you know, remake it, you know, you actually cannot get a Humvee anymore because they're now ordered to be destroyed due to some contract deal.
[SPEAKER_08]: Doesn't that suck?
[SPEAKER_11]: That's interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, when they're used up, Humvee goes to the scrap heap.
[SPEAKER_10]: Medical records in one of those.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or the military records.
[SPEAKER_11]: For those who didn't hear that whole sentence, Loki said they probably hid Bush's military records in one of those.
[SPEAKER_11]: They couldn't figure out which ones they have to destroy them all.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, it has to do with when they were put out on the market, there was like some order for them not to be resold, so they were actually, quote, given to a distributor who sold them for the military and got the money back.
[SPEAKER_08]: But that was all.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now they have to all be destroyed.
[SPEAKER_08]: Doesn't that suck?
[SPEAKER_02]: A little bit.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm still going to get a Humvee one day.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to paint it camo.
[SPEAKER_08]: And put myself a big old gun on top of it.
[SPEAKER_08]: And drive that shit around.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't care if the gun works, I'm going to have one on there.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's going to be like in Cruisin' World.
[SPEAKER_08]: Where you could drive the Hummer.
[SPEAKER_08]: With the gun.
[SPEAKER_18]: I remember that.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was always either that, the school bus, or the three-wheeled truck that I would use.
[SPEAKER_11]: You talking about Cruise and World makes me think about Nintendo arcade games, which makes me think about how I really want to play Killer Instinct.
[SPEAKER_08]: It still says Ultra 64 on it, isn't that sad?
[SPEAKER_11]: I want to play Killer Instinct.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dude, I love Killer Instinct.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyway, sorry to interrupt.
[SPEAKER_08]: F you to Killer Instinct for dying.
[SPEAKER_08]: We miss you.
Killer Instinct.
[SPEAKER_08]: And F you goes toward Mortal Kombat Annihilation, because I finally saw it.
[SPEAKER_11]: How could a movie that sucks... Welcome to five years ago.
[SPEAKER_08]: I knew it was going to suck, so I just didn't bother seeing it.
[SPEAKER_08]: But Ross made me watch it yesterday.
[SPEAKER_08]: I brought over The Last Samurai.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good movie.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know what you need to play in that main cabinet right now?
[SPEAKER_11]: Street Fighter II, the movie, the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ah, no.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hell no.
[SPEAKER_08]: I played that game.
[SPEAKER_01]: That game is the... It is so ass-tastic.
[SPEAKER_11]: You wouldn't even believe.
[SPEAKER_08]: Go back to the chat room for a second.
[SPEAKER_08]: I need to reply to something.
[SPEAKER_11]: The best thing about playing Street Fighter II, the movie, the game, though, is playing as Cammy.
[SPEAKER_08]: To address Anita, you actually cannot buy them army surplus anymore because they have to be destroyed.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: People are asking me stuff and I can't read the chat room.
[SPEAKER_11]: Street Fighter 2, The Movie, The Game.
[SPEAKER_11]: They have to see it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'll relay if there's any other stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: You'll have to buy your own M60.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: But another SU goes toward how long it's going to take for me to get done with school.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I'm probably going to be done probably...
[SPEAKER_08]: If I can do it right, 2006, which is going to... I mean, it's an okay thing because that means that I have more time to get in shape and everything.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I'm still planning on going into the Air Force Reserves.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, once I lose a little bit more weight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I just didn't want to have to wait another two years instead of one.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it's pissing me off.
[SPEAKER_08]: And another F you to Alabama for being so far away.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I want to go home.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's certain places that I want to visit, certain places, certain people I want to see.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I'm broke.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I have no time off.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have two days off for the rest of the year.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not counting, though, the one day where I have to go to the dentist.
[SPEAKER_08]: That means I can't get sick.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I got sick right at the beginning of the year.
[SPEAKER_08]: I had all that surgery and all this other crap.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then also, I need more days off so that I can do other stuff next year that I want to do.
[SPEAKER_08]: And...
[SPEAKER_08]: F you to me having to wait for two weeks to get my laptop because I want it now.
[SPEAKER_08]: See, it's okay to be impatient about getting a laptop.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because your laptops are cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I found a pretty one getting this nice Fujitsu with the DVD-R.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I can finally burn off all the crap on my hard drive and reformat.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I'm going to have to start sharing it with Dan.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because he turned his computer into a main machine.
[SPEAKER_08]: It built into a pole position.
[SPEAKER_11]: You're very angsty tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: This is the longest you've taken your FUs for a while.
[SPEAKER_08]: For a while.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm just... You know what it is, okay?
[SPEAKER_08]: You're on your period?
[SPEAKER_08]: Shut up!
[SPEAKER_11]: That's just the stock excuse for women being upset.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can just shut up.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know I love you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I'd love to kick your ass.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh my god, this is the worst thing I've ever seen, but he was cute, I have to say.
[SPEAKER_08]: The guy who played you in that movie?
[SPEAKER_08]: He was pretty cute.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh my god, though, I'm... Is this the Street Fighter 2, the movie, the game?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, I love how they play little clips from the movie and everything.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what, though?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think that it was all that bad.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, it was, the movie was, the game was actually kind of okay to play.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just thought it was very funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hope the chatroom's watching this, because this is damn hilarious.
[SPEAKER_11]: Webcam, moronsoundstrater.com Alright, anyway, any more FUs from Jamie?
[SPEAKER_08]: Excuse me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, I have an F.U.
[SPEAKER_08]: to, um, man, just stuff, okay?
[SPEAKER_08]: Just stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: A big F.U.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have an F.U.
[SPEAKER_08]: to, uh, politics and politary.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have a big FU that goes to QRO because they're doing a storage wipe.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that means that I had to spread 78 different individual items among four characters on QRO.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then I tried to freakin' vend so I could get rid of some of my shit.
[SPEAKER_08]: and it wouldn't let me vend.
[SPEAKER_08]: It said, it just wouldn't let, it said, the item's eligible to vend.
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I had the same items that other people were vending so this is really pissing me off.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, do I have to have a vending license to vend to this crap?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I can make so much zenny in that game but no.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then an FU goes toward me not being able to afford to do Final Fantasy XI because I was going to start playing again and also with my laptop I'd be able to keep typing to people while I'm playing Final Fantasy XI but now I can't do it so it's really pissing me off and I'm out of breath.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow, it's...
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm having to, like, write this all down to follow.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm, um, and if you do bad tasting, but perfectly textured low-carb cheesecake.
[SPEAKER_18]: What?
[SPEAKER_18]: Any more?
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm waiting.
[SPEAKER_11]: No!
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, then moving on.
[SPEAKER_11]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wait.
[SPEAKER_11]: What?
[SPEAKER_11]: Nevermind Let's see who our mystery guest is.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey Jonas!
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, just during a spare part of the show too.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, let's get to Loki's part.
[SPEAKER_10]: First off, fuck you, the crack whore that tried to cut me off when the lanes were merging.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, so I was driving to take my fiance home, okay, and the lanes were merging, we've already established, you know, it's already one lane, and we're just like coming together, you know, to be in parallel.
[SPEAKER_10]: So what does this dumb bitch do?
[SPEAKER_10]: She tries to cut around me, through a double yellow, on the opposite side of the street, like going the wrong direction, cuts through there, and like, passes me up to get behind this really slow guy that's in front of me.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm like, what the hell?
[SPEAKER_10]: So I flipped her off as I went by, and tried yelling at her, but, you know, she was ahead of me, so she probably couldn't hear me over my music.
[SPEAKER_10]: But, um, yeah, she was a dumb bitch.
[SPEAKER_10]: I normally don't flip people off, I just yell, but this bitch pushed me that far, so, fuck you to her.
[SPEAKER_10]: And...
[SPEAKER_10]: Fuck you the cosplayers that are fucking ugly, okay?
[SPEAKER_10]: If you're a big fat whore, you don't need to be dressing up like an anime character.
[SPEAKER_10]: It doesn't make you hotter, it doesn't make you any cooler, it just makes you ugly and stupid looking.
[SPEAKER_11]: And if you're a hairy man, please don't cosplay, Yuna.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, I really, I hate, you know, seeing these ugly ass people cosplaying.
[SPEAKER_10]: We don't need any more ugly people in the world to die.
[SPEAKER_08]: One thing in defense, I think that if you don't have the body to do like the scantily clad animatrix, that's one thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Last time I checked, um, Yuna didn't have a gut.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyways, and, oh, and that's another thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sailor Fatty, you're not part of the group.
[SPEAKER_10]: So get out.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_10]: And, um, also, you know, fuck you, the whole anime thing was just retarded, okay?
[SPEAKER_10]: It was just really a waste of my time.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, the overcharging stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: Last time I checked, you know, I don't think baseball cards had anything to do with anime, but, you know, hey, that shit was there, too.
[SPEAKER_10]: Um,
[SPEAKER_10]: And also, just plain, fuck you to my cabinet because for some reason the wheels are starting to push through the bottom, which is not good if I want to move this thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it's like on a little pedestal right now, so that kind of sucks.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then, fuck you to the sluts that I saw at the mall.
[SPEAKER_10]: I swear to God, they're just getting younger and younger.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just all these sluts out there.
[SPEAKER_10]: They were never around when I was in, you know, junior high.
[SPEAKER_10]: That really sucks.
[SPEAKER_10]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm going back to my old FU song because it was better than Bumblebee.
[SPEAKER_11]: FU to Lehigh County in Pennsylvania for being so goddamn boring.
[SPEAKER_11]: Although, you know what, FU to myself for not being more proactive about finding things to do.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think next time when I go back, because I'm going to have to go back eventually, I'll be better prepared for it, because I'm going to look up where I can go nerd out and play DDR and stuff, so I'll have a better time.
[SPEAKER_11]: But they did have one gay bar there, which I went to, and F you to the fact that there were only like 30 people in the whole place, considering this is the only gay bar for like hundreds of miles around town.
[SPEAKER_11]: Whatever, what can you do?
[SPEAKER_11]: Also, I'd like to give an F you for coming home and thinking the TV was stolen.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then realizing that Loki had taken the TV and put it in the machine.
[SPEAKER_11]: What?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, the TV had been liberated.
[SPEAKER_11]: But F you to my future friends' reaction when they come in this house and realize you're going to have to watch movies in an arcade machine.
[SPEAKER_11]: Until we can get something better figured out.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think it's interesting.
[SPEAKER_11]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_11]: FU to the fact that... FU to working 10 to 12 hour days, because that gets really old after a while.
[SPEAKER_11]: And FU to being on salary so I don't get overtime for it.
[SPEAKER_11]: And that's about it.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's really all I have to say.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm always the less angsty one of the bunch.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyway, let's move on and see what our folks in the other folks in the room here have to say angsty tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: Garrett!
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, by the way, some FU music tonight brought to us by Ryu Kosaka.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, no, I got an FU song.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think it was... No, you get this.
[SPEAKER_09]: You get candy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, damn.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: FU this song, even though I like candy.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I got tired of it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Played it out too many times.
[SPEAKER_09]: DDR.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fuck you starts off with my sister for being the bitch that she is.
[SPEAKER_09]: I haven't seen her in two weeks.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then the minute she walks in the door, she instantly starts being a bitch about everything.
[SPEAKER_09]: But fuck her for making me chase the mailman.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fuck her for lying to me and saying that mom knew she was drinking and that she could have some of my Smirnoff shit that was at my party and leaving it in my mom's room and stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oops.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I didn't get in trouble for it.
[SPEAKER_09]: She did.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fuck Tower for having such great sales and making me buy even more toys.
[SPEAKER_09]: They had a three day sale this week that was 25% off all their toys and I purchased twice online.
[SPEAKER_09]: Really big.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fuck me for having a crush right now that makes me feel like I'm 16 and the world is going to revolve around it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think it's fucking ridiculous and I hope I'm just having male PMS or something.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fuck me for being on vacation right now and not knowing what I'm going to do on vacation.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm getting kind of tired of that right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fuck my anal retentiveness and me not being happy with my room and stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I don't really have any more angstiness.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_11]: Bug, do you have any FUs?
[SPEAKER_11]: It's coming.
[SPEAKER_11]: A microphone's coming to you, Bug.
[SPEAKER_17]: mainly just a big ol' FU to my computer for not working.
[SPEAKER_17]: Not the Mac, of course.
[SPEAKER_11]: Next ever break.
[SPEAKER_11]: Nice, nice.
[SPEAKER_17]: Is that it?
[SPEAKER_17]: Uh, well, no, yeah, because everything else I fixed this week, like the car and...
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_17]: Picking somebody up at the airport at 2 a.m.
[SPEAKER_11]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: F you, buddy.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's go to Jonas, who showed up during the original angst there.
[SPEAKER_11]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_11]: Also known as Explicit with the triple X. Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_19]: Not much.
[SPEAKER_19]: Should I just put my F yous right now?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Get them out.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: Remember, it's a three-hour show.
[SPEAKER_19]: Don't worry.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't have that many F yous this time.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, we gotta turn, you gotta back your mic up a little bit.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, is it really that loud?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, yes it is.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, okay.
[SPEAKER_19]: F you to me for being long last minute this whole week.
[SPEAKER_19]: God, showing up to work like 15 minutes late is not good.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay, and since I've, anybody heard about the Biggest Field California Tournament?
[SPEAKER_18]: No.
[SPEAKER_19]: What's this?
[SPEAKER_19]: Good, because I went to hell, so I'm going to give an F you to some of the organizers for not taking, looking up how tournaments are supposed to be run.
[SPEAKER_19]: Because you know how tournaments are done by PA, right?
[SPEAKER_19]: They did it by score.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh dear.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, there's a lot of problems with that, and they're not taking constructive criticism from other people, which is another bad thing.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's not a good sign.
[SPEAKER_19]: They think it's all good and everything, but there are some flaws that they should listen to.
[SPEAKER_19]: On the other hand, F you to certain people who try to ruin a tournament for two hours.
[SPEAKER_19]: I heard rumors about a two-hour delay on that tournament.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm not sure if that's true or not, but I'll say F you to whoever screwed up my tournament.
[SPEAKER_19]: Even though I heard rumors that he was in Zuma at 4-6-9, the one who did the same thing to my tournament, if that's true, he's banned out of my tournament.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm serious, because nobody should be banning a tournament for that long.
[SPEAKER_19]: Screwing a tournament for two hours is not fun.
[SPEAKER_19]: Especially when people have to drive all the way back from San Francisco, California, or Fresno, or even SoCal.
[SPEAKER_19]: Just to go to the tournament, then later on getting delayed for a whole lot and getting pissed off because of all the blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_19]: Wah, wah, wah.
[SPEAKER_19]: Wah, my pussy hurts.
[SPEAKER_01]: Wah.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, damn pussy.
[SPEAKER_19]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_19]: Get this right, you guys.
[SPEAKER_19]: If you don't like the rules of the tournament, don't go.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's simple as that.
[SPEAKER_19]: If you go to the tournament and you know the rules are fucked up, and you go, you're going to argue.
[SPEAKER_19]: You're just causing some trouble.
[SPEAKER_19]: Now, what would you rather do?
[SPEAKER_19]: Would you do something like that, Dumb Sky?
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, but I'll probably... Sacramento's so sad now at Bomani, I'm probably not even going to ever run a tournament or even help run a tournament ever again, so we'll see.
[SPEAKER_19]: I mean, I'll still run tournaments, regardless of what's going on and stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I would never run one by score, that's for sure.
[SPEAKER_19]: I know, that's one thing.
[SPEAKER_19]: Never run by score.
[SPEAKER_19]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_19]: F you to squirrels for eating my damn food from camping.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't...
[SPEAKER_19]: Seeing a bunch of spit all over the damn steak that I've cooked for two hours and shit is not good.
[SPEAKER_19]: Therefore, even though I whipped the living shit out of those squirrels, I'm not sure if you all saw this whip right here.
[SPEAKER_19]: Did you borrow that from Erin?
[SPEAKER_19]: No, this is mine, dammit.
[SPEAKER_19]: I told you that I have my own whip.
[SPEAKER_19]: You should have showed Erin this whip.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm not sure if she's interested.
[SPEAKER_19]: And F you for getting bit by...bent the ass by ants during camping.
[SPEAKER_19]: No fucking comment on that one.
[SPEAKER_19]: And F you for losing my toothbrush during camping.
[SPEAKER_19]: Not brushing your teeth for two days sucks.
[SPEAKER_19]: Speaking of that, I saw a bear during camping.
[SPEAKER_19]: Did you see Bigfoot?
[SPEAKER_19]: Yes, I saw Bigfoot.
[SPEAKER_19]: I did not get eaten.
[SPEAKER_19]: He was just walking around sniffing on those pussies and stuff.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_19]: Was he pussyfooting around?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, he was pussyfooting around.
[SPEAKER_19]: and Effie for the horse for fucking sweeping the tail that he took a shit on in the back of my shirt.
[SPEAKER_19]: That was gross.
[SPEAKER_19]: You don't wag your tail with all that shit in your...
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay, I'm cutting you off, buddy.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, Garrett.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have one last major F you.
[SPEAKER_09]: F you to my dog for having to fucking dog sit it while my parents were gone.
[SPEAKER_09]: I had to wake up to that fucking garbage disposal vomiting peach pits one morning.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, anything else?
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay, that's all for now.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, alright.
[SPEAKER_19]: Told you it was going to be a three hour show, but...
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, let's move on to chatroom FUs.
[SPEAKER_11]: Brought to us, the music is Dive Into the Night.
[SPEAKER_11]: Camera nudity.
[SPEAKER_11]: What's the nudity?
[SPEAKER_11]: What's the nudity on camera now?
[SPEAKER_11]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_11]: What game is that?
[SPEAKER_11]: Is that Gals Panic on the camera?
[SPEAKER_11]: The cam's over at orangelonradio.com.
[SPEAKER_11]: These guys are crazy.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, like, it's supposed to be, like, the Zonk stage.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyway, moving on.
[SPEAKER_11]: Uh, let's go and, uh, let's see what our chatroom FUs have to say.
[SPEAKER_11]: Uh, Dark Knight says, uh, FU to Rain, Rain, Rain, nothing but rain all week long, another being a broke-ass person yet again, and a final FU to not having no car.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Uh, Dork wants to say an FU to myself.
[SPEAKER_03]: Aww.
[SPEAKER_11]: How sad.
[SPEAKER_11]: Uh, Yaki Tora, I hope I pronounced that right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yaki, actually, it's probably Yaki.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm white, okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: Just says, I want to send my FUs to the Kroger company because they love to fuck up people's paycheck.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ouch.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a grocery store change.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, okay, that's right, it is.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, they're Ralphs.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, they're Ralphs on here.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: StupidBaka says, wants to know if we do the FUs over PM or Skype.
[SPEAKER_11]: PM, we don't let people do them over Skype or else they'd go on as long as Jonas does.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkLionXPI says, only one FU tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: FU to the little blonde girl who broke my concentration while playing Paranoia Survivor on DDR Gameworks yesterday.
[SPEAKER_11]: She moved in front of me like not knowing I was there.
[SPEAKER_11]: People like those piss me off the most and I just wanna hurt them physically so bad!
[SPEAKER_11]: Panda says, F you to my hair for wanting to style itself every morning.
[SPEAKER_11]: And John Fields says, F you to getting food poisoning.
[SPEAKER_11]: F you to no one calling me back for a job.
[SPEAKER_11]: F you fake gamers who ruin competitive games for everyone else.
[SPEAKER_11]: Super Metroid died today because of one of these runs.
[SPEAKER_11]: Blown away by an emulator, the real time of 55 minutes taking down to 47 minutes.
[SPEAKER_11]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, DDRholic says, F you to Jason for taking off for some unknown period of time and not even talking to me about it.
[SPEAKER_11]: F you for taking things that I say to the extreme.
[SPEAKER_11]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_11]: I didn't see the message not to repost.
[SPEAKER_11]: I just got someone in trouble.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think she was only, like, kind of, like, joking with those.
[SPEAKER_11]: Don't send me FUs unless you mean it, because honestly, since the way I get the FUs, I can't.
[SPEAKER_11]: If you tell me don't read this or something, then I don't see it.
[SPEAKER_11]: So sorry, guys.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sharkskrull says, FU to the village.
[SPEAKER_11]: I won't ruin it for everyone, but it sucked.
[SPEAKER_11]: I want that two hours of my life back.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, that movie was awesome!
[SPEAKER_07]: This is the best news you've seen in a long time.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, VidPOWER says, F you to the whole www.ilovebees.com hype for Halo 2.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's boggling my mind.
[SPEAKER_11]: What is ilovebees.com?
[SPEAKER_11]: I can't hear you, bug.
[SPEAKER_11]: I can't hear Loki either, amazing.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's alternate reality gaming, I think.
[SPEAKER_10]: That site.
[SPEAKER_10]: That sucks.
[SPEAKER_10]: More nudity on the cam.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, anyways.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, uh, gosh, let's see, I guess at this time we're going to go to another break, and then we're going to come back and, what do you guys want to do, you want to do some Ask Orange Lounge, or do we have, alright, sure, why not, we'll do some Ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_08]: On the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, we'll do, we'll open up the Skype line if folks, and we'll open up the Skype lines for comments as well, and some Ask Orange Lounge to close out the show.
[SPEAKER_11]: Meanwhile, I'm going to pick some songs that sound cool for the Poppin' 11 soundtrack, I'm going to pick some on my own.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because I know I want to play the Orange Airport song.
[SPEAKER_11]: I definitely want to play that.
[SPEAKER_11]: The Orange Lounge song.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm going to play that one because it's called Space Dog.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, and it's Sana.
[SPEAKER_11]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: I didn't even know that.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I'll play... Okay, then I'm going to go back to number one and get some of the shorter ones.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's do... Wow, that has a really... Oh, we already heard that one.
[SPEAKER_11]: Um...
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know, what do you think?
[SPEAKER_11]: Hillbilly, I want to hear Hillbilly.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, we're going to do Hillbilly.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, so these are the songs I'm going to play this break from Poppin' Music 11.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're going to hear Orange Lounge with Orange Airline, Sauna with Space Dog, and Taisho in the Hillbilly genre with Pa La La 42.
[SPEAKER_11]: This should be interesting.
[SPEAKER_11]: Send your questions in for Ask Orange Lounge, and then we're going to wrap up the show when we come back.
[SPEAKER_11]: Enjoy.
Thank you for watching!
Hello, Pedro, I'm a play-store, to run a story over stars.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for watching!
and the rest of the cast.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kodou ga kurui datu Nobichiru Candy Corral Aimai na kotoba metato Kimi ga Rhythm
[SPEAKER_02]: Pararara, so kanda mo itsumo karanmamori de Kauzen na koi wo kizumo tomerare demo Pararara, ima wa nanimo dekinai kedo Yume no tsuzuki nara pra pra pra pra
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_11]: Orange Lounge Radio, Bomani Music, and more.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ask Orange Lounge
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's ask Orange Lounge some stupid question.
[SPEAKER_11]: What will we find out this week on Orange Lounge Radio?
[SPEAKER_11]: I know I have a question.
[SPEAKER_11]: One thing I want to find out.
[SPEAKER_11]: Why is Loki playing a game where guys are shaving other guys?
[SPEAKER_11]: Question number one comes from StupidBaka.
[SPEAKER_11]: Where did you go when you were out of town?
[SPEAKER_11]: I went to Allentown, Pennsylvania, which is about an hour north of Philadelphia.
[SPEAKER_11]: And it's very green out there.
[SPEAKER_11]: And there's a restaurant called Friendly's, which was cute.
[SPEAKER_11]: Which I think is actually a chain out there.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm so... Like, there's probably East Coast people listening to this show going, nothing special.
[SPEAKER_07]: The last time I was on the East Coast, there was that Roy Rogers place that was utter crap.
[SPEAKER_11]: I went to Cracker Barrel, and that place... Cracker Barrel owns...
[SPEAKER_11]: And I have clove candy sticks from Cracker Barrel in my room, because they got me some as a going away present.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you so much to the folks, I know that of course they would never listen to the show, but the folks out there were so good to me.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, they made that town bearable, honestly, and they bought me gifts and stuff, so that was great.
[SPEAKER_11]: StupidBanca also wants to know, and I can't believe somebody's asking this, but what is MAME?
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a multi-arcade machine emulator.
[SPEAKER_11]: Caller, hold on a minute, I'll get to you in a minute, but what is MAME, is the person wants to know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, they hung up.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh well.
[SPEAKER_11]: What is MAME?
[SPEAKER_08]: The Multi Arcade Machine Emulator.
[SPEAKER_11]: And what does it do?
[SPEAKER_08]: It emulates multiple arcade machines.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's good stuff though.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm going to call the person back that just called us.
[SPEAKER_11]: Aw, it says he's busy now.
[SPEAKER_11]: What's up with that?
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll see if he calls back.
[SPEAKER_11]: Moving on, we'll go to number two question.
[SPEAKER_11]: Number two question.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yaki wants to know, or Yaki Tora, or maybe it's just Tora, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Here's a question.
[SPEAKER_11]: Why is Jamie so damn angsty tonight?
[SPEAKER_11]: Her rants were as long as the horror of the village.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Village was good!
[SPEAKER_08]: I can't help it if the majority of people who saw that movie didn't stop to think about it, but still, it was a very good movie, okay?
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, well moving on, why are you so angsty?
[SPEAKER_11]: Is that why you're so angsty?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I'm angsty for other, other reasons.
[SPEAKER_08]: Many of them.
[SPEAKER_11]: Personal reasons.
[SPEAKER_11]: Many reasons.
[SPEAKER_08]: Many reasons.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's okay to be angry once in a while.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's this time of year is when I get really horribly angsty like that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Which is weird because with me, I'm... Tora would just like to point out they've actually never seen The Village.
[SPEAKER_11]: They were just saying that to ruffle some feathers.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well then go see it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a good movie.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was not just a good movie.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was an excellent movie.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was a movie.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was a very smart movie, okay?
[SPEAKER_11]: Shark Scroll says, I thought about the movie, and I still thought it sucked.
[SPEAKER_08]: Then you obviously didn't watch it with the right frame of mind.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well.
[SPEAKER_08]: It wasn't intended to scare.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think it's getting mixed reviews, so it's probably just getting mixed feedback from everybody, you know?
[SPEAKER_07]: It wasn't scary.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was very good.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was the type of movie I was right in the mood to see.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't see, but now I'm kind of like, I've heard so many negative things, but I've heard some good things, but I'm kind of like, now maybe I'll wait for video.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, Rob, you are going to go see it with me, and I'm going to pay for you to see it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, hey, free movie!
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, I'll let you guys know what I thought.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_11]: I got his questions.
[SPEAKER_11]: Kyle!
[SPEAKER_11]: Our old buddy Kyle Snyder wants to know, I've decided that for the next few songs I want to work on, I want to move away from techno and trance.
[SPEAKER_11]: Would you want me to work on some genres that involve vocals, like house, two-step, and jazz?
[SPEAKER_11]: Or should I do some non-vocal genres, like drum and bass, progressive, and big beat?
[SPEAKER_08]: I would love to hear some drum and bass.
[SPEAKER_11]: I like drum and bass, too.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I would like to hear some two-step from Kyle, actually.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think that would be kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: That would be kind of neat, I think.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I guess, does anybody else have any feedback?
[SPEAKER_11]: Anybody?
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_11]: Keep it to yourselves.
[SPEAKER_11]: DDRholic wants to know, do you still love me, Rob?
[SPEAKER_11]: And the answer is yes.
[SPEAKER_11]: Just like Whitney Houston, I will always love you.
[SPEAKER_11]: That was my rendition of Whitney.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've been moved, Rob.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: At least my stomach moved a little.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_11]: Somebody in the chatroom wants to say, what is Two-Step exactly?
[SPEAKER_11]: What is Two-Step exactly?
[SPEAKER_11]: Play some... I would say like Jack and Mark Get Busy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Distant Sounds.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know what's the funny thing about two-step?
[SPEAKER_09]: British people claim they're the only people who can make two-step.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just like they can only make trip-hop, because we're just supposed to be making down-tempo, because there's supposed to be a difference.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, Skype line is still open if you want to give us a call.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll see if anybody wants to call.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, but in the meantime, we have another question.
[SPEAKER_11]: Vid Palace says, Speaking of MAME, what is your favorite classic arcade Konami game?
[SPEAKER_11]: Mine is The Simpsons.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ooh, this is a good question.
[SPEAKER_08]: Super Konami World.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're all a bunch of Konami whores.
[SPEAKER_11]: Super Konami World.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's that one all about?
[SPEAKER_08]: It was a game where they took a bunch of...
[SPEAKER_08]: other Konami games made them into one game like these two people made it into the Konami universe or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: There were two of them.
[SPEAKER_07]: They were kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now that I think about it, I think they came out on the Famicom too, way back when.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anybody else care to answer this one?
[SPEAKER_11]: Bugged.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_08]: Twinbee.
[SPEAKER_11]: Twinbee.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: Bugged.
[SPEAKER_17]: Stop standing on the cable.
[SPEAKER_17]: it's hazardous for us both I can't stand the symptoms because I worked at a place that had it for two years and that's all I would hear every day was Bart and Lisa screaming like when they do that thing when they're running through it and that's when it sounded like a screaming baby yes, when I worked at Mountain Mike's do they have any shoot-em-ups?
[SPEAKER_11]: my favorite classic, and I'm going back to classic, classic Konami arcade game
[SPEAKER_11]: Motherfuckin' Time Pilot is my favorite classic arcade game by Konami.
[SPEAKER_11]: Time Pilot.
[SPEAKER_17]: Gradius, uh, what was the second one?
[SPEAKER_17]: Life Force?
[SPEAKER_11]: Gradius... It was Life Force on the NES in America, but it was Salamander in Arcade Japan.
[SPEAKER_17]: I didn't go to the Arcade in Japan.
[SPEAKER_17]: I just played it on the NES.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, Life Force is cool.
[SPEAKER_17]: Alrighty.
No.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't care if you're the motherfuckin' host.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ooh, Bugged and DarkSakura are having a fight.
[SPEAKER_11]: But you're holding your hand like it's a gun.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'll give her my mic if you're not careful.
[SPEAKER_08]: Parodius.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, specifically, Oshaberry Parodius.
[SPEAKER_11]: Garrett, I know you're a big Konami whore.
[SPEAKER_11]: What other Konami arcade game classic ones are your favorites?
[SPEAKER_09]: I never really got to play a lot of arcade games when I was a kid.
[SPEAKER_09]: The ones I did play, I don't remember who made them.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, it's kind of sad.
[SPEAKER_17]: And somebody did say Pervious.
[SPEAKER_11]: Just say, just say like, I don't know, what else was Konami?
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm trying to think of the old school Konami games.
[SPEAKER_11]: I can only think of... Track and Field, just say Track and Field.
[SPEAKER_17]: I love Track and Field!
[SPEAKER_11]: I can only think of the damn Capcom fighting games.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: They actually have a lot of games.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like, I think Konami was involved with Frogger at one point.
[SPEAKER_11]: But all I know is they didn't make BurgerTime, so, sorry guys.
[SPEAKER_11]: More questions from our chatroom.
[SPEAKER_11]: EvilNauki2DX wants to know, he just said, I have a question.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, here it is.
[SPEAKER_11]: What is that game being played on the webcam right now with all the naked anime ladies?
[SPEAKER_11]: It's Gal's Panic.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's simply just Gal's Panic.
[SPEAKER_11]: Not Gal's Panic 95 or anything like that?
[SPEAKER_11]: No.
[SPEAKER_11]: Loki says, Galspanic Super S2 is the one he's playing right now.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, uh... And it's beating his ass.
[SPEAKER_11]: He's on a really advanced stage at this point, isn't he?
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Um... I guess, uh, at this point, it's almost time to kind of wrap up the show, but I was hoping that somebody would call in on the Skype line, but we didn't get anybody!
[SPEAKER_11]: Boo!
[SPEAKER_11]: Boo to that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Nobody has a question.
[SPEAKER_11]: I cry.
[SPEAKER_11]: I see how it is.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm trying to see how long the fortune cookie is tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think it's a longer one.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, it is.
[SPEAKER_11]: So we'll probably start to wrap up the show here.
[SPEAKER_11]: since nobody's calling us on the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_11]: I guess let's go around and get everybody's final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm going to shut off the Skype line since nobody's using it.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, let's go around and get everybody's final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you very much for those that participated in tonight's Ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_11]: Meanwhile, final thoughts time.
[SPEAKER_11]: Bugged, final thought.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you, that was lovely.
[SPEAKER_11]: Final thought from Jonas.
[SPEAKER_11]: Jonas.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sucks to be late.
[SPEAKER_11]: Are you here to plug anything tonight since you were late?
[SPEAKER_11]: Do you have anything you want to plug while you're here?
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, not really.
[SPEAKER_19]: School's about to start soon and a state fair is coming up soon.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's practically all.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Uh, I thought maybe you had like a, a tourney or a sim file or something, but I- Oh!
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, I do have- I'm supposed to release Alpha Nova Vengeance, the one that Loki was asking for me to download.
[SPEAKER_19]: Did somebody already do that?
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_19]: I checked the sim file itself, it's not really that great to download, if you're in- if it's- because the sim file that I made was a little too repetitive.
[SPEAKER_19]: and Inconsistent pattern-wise.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_19]: Because me and MJ are supposed to make the sim file by now.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm not sure if Loki... Loki, didn't you say you wanted to do the background?
[SPEAKER_19]: Nah, you can do whatever.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay, I guess I'll do it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Garrett, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thanks for coming tonight, by the way, and bringing us poppin' music stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: What's your final thought?
[SPEAKER_02]: Hmm...
[SPEAKER_11]: Very well said.
[SPEAKER_11]: Loki, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_11]: I want animal cookies and there's none left.
[SPEAKER_11]: There's crumbs.
[SPEAKER_11]: My final thought is Irish car bombs make my stomach sad, but they were very good.
[SPEAKER_11]: Jamie.
[SPEAKER_08]: My final thought is I'm going to go home and have some ice cream.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mmm, ice cream.
[SPEAKER_11]: Mmm, ice cream is good.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, final word of the show tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm going to give it to Garrett.
[SPEAKER_11]: You can have the final word of tonight's show.
[SPEAKER_11]: What do you want to say?
[SPEAKER_09]: That's why I said home.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: One word.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ligament.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_16]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_16]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_16]: Orange Lounge Radio is hosted by DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_16]: If you'd like to leave us a comment, send us an email at orangeloungeradio at yahoo.com And now, here's your fortune cookie message of the day.
[SPEAKER_14]: I love to smoke.
[SPEAKER_14]: I love to smoke and I love to eat red meat.
[SPEAKER_14]: I love to eat raw fucking red meat.
[SPEAKER_14]: Nothing I like better than sucking down a hot steaming cheeseburger and a butt at the same time.
[SPEAKER_14]: I love to smoke.
[SPEAKER_14]: I love to eat red meat and only eat red meat that comes from cows who smoke, okay?
[SPEAKER_14]: Special cows they grow in Virginia with voice boxes in their necks.
[SPEAKER_14]: I tried eating vegetarian.
[SPEAKER_14]: I feel like a wimp going into a restaurant.
[SPEAKER_14]: What do you want to eat, sir?
[SPEAKER_14]: Broccoli?
[SPEAKER_14]: Broccoli's the side dish, folks.
[SPEAKER_14]: Always was, always will be, okay?
[SPEAKER_14]: When they ask me what I want to say, what do you think I want?
[SPEAKER_14]: This is America.
[SPEAKER_14]: I want a bowl of raw red meat right now.
[SPEAKER_14]: Forget about that.
[SPEAKER_14]: Bring me a live cow over to the table.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'll carve off what I want and ride the rest.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm going to open my own place.
[SPEAKER_14]: Open my own restaurant and get away from you people.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm going to open my own restaurant with two smoking sections, ultra and regular, okay?
[SPEAKER_14]: and we're not going to have any tables or any chairs or any napkins, none of that pussy shit, just a big wide open black space and all we're going to serve is raw meat right on the bone and only men are going to eat their naked men sitting around a big giant campfire and no men's room either, you have to piss, you mark your territory like a wolf and if some guy has a heart attack from eating too much meat, fuck him, we throw him in the fire more meat for the other meat eaters, yeah!
[SPEAKER_14]: because you've got to have goals
[SPEAKER_14]: Because everybody in this room knows everybody who's quitting me.
[SPEAKER_14]: You don't have that friend who's quitting you.
[SPEAKER_14]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_14]: The guy's quitting everything.
[SPEAKER_14]: I quit smoking.
[SPEAKER_14]: I quit drugs.
[SPEAKER_14]: I quit drinking.
[SPEAKER_14]: I quit meeting out here.
[SPEAKER_14]: I get up in the morning with a nice big bowl of oat bran.
[SPEAKER_14]: I go to the bathroom for three and a half hours.
[SPEAKER_14]: I have another bowl of oat bran.
[SPEAKER_14]: I go back in the bathroom for six more hours.
[SPEAKER_14]: All I do is eat and shit.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm going to live forever.
[SPEAKER_14]: My colon is the strongest muscle in my body right now.
[SPEAKER_14]: I could pass Elvis through my colon right now.
[SPEAKER_14]: And all these cereals they have, crackling oat bran and horking fiber chunks, you know Cereal used to come with free prizes, now it comes with a free roll of toilet paper in every box Guys get up on Sunday morning, forget about the New York Times, I'm gonna need the Bible, I got a big one brewing here Dad, there's a phone call, I'm on Genesis, goddammit You tell them to call back after the creation People checking their own feces for fiber, you have too much free fucking time on your hands, okay?
[SPEAKER_14]: Red meat, white meat, blue meat, meat, oh fucking Ranma, you will eat it!
[SPEAKER_14]: Because not eating meat is a decision, eating meat is an instinct!
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, and I know what it's about!
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't want to eat the meat because I love the animals!
[SPEAKER_14]: I love the animals!
[SPEAKER_14]: Hey, I love the animals too!
[SPEAKER_14]: I love my dog, he's so cute!
[SPEAKER_14]: My lovely little dog!
[SPEAKER_14]: He's so cute!
[SPEAKER_14]: There's the problem.
[SPEAKER_14]: We only want to save the cute animals, don't we?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: Why don't we just have animal auditions, line them up one by one, and interview them individually.
[SPEAKER_14]: What are you?
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm an otter.
[SPEAKER_14]: And what do you do?
[SPEAKER_14]: I swim around my back and do cute little human things with my hand You're free to go And what are you?
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm a cow, get in the fucking truck, okay pal?
[SPEAKER_14]: But I'm an animal, you're a baseball glove, get out of that truck I'm an animal, I have rights here, here's your fucking cousin, get out of the truck pal We kill the cows to make jackets out of them and then we kill each other for the jackets we made out of the cows
[SPEAKER_14]: You will eat the meat, folks, because this country was founded on two things, meat and war.
[SPEAKER_14]: You eat enough fucking meat, you want to kill somebody.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's the way it works.
[SPEAKER_14]: That was the ultimate American dream for me during that Persian Gulf War.
[SPEAKER_14]: I was sitting in my living room naked with a can of Budweiser and a three-inch steak watching the war live on TV.
[SPEAKER_14]: I had a six-foot erection with a giant cheeseburger on the end of it.
[SPEAKER_14]: I ate so much meat during the war, by the time it was over, three weeks later, I was like, no, no, no, we need to keep fighting.
[SPEAKER_14]: Make a couple of stops on our way home from the Persian Gulf.
[SPEAKER_14]: First stop, Vietnam.
[SPEAKER_14]: Surprise the fuck out of those people, huh?
[SPEAKER_14]: Did you make a movie?
[SPEAKER_14]: Not this time, pal.
[SPEAKER_14]: Personally, I think Mama Cass said it best when she said... All the leaves are... Monday...
[SPEAKER_16]: Thank you very much for listening and we'll see you next week.
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_11]: The Afterbirth The Afterbirth The Afterbirth
[SPEAKER_11]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Aw, it's naked with a horse.
[SPEAKER_11]: One of our Orange Lounge buddies wanted us to call them while we had a chance here over the Skype line, so I'm going to go ahead and give her a call here.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hopefully it'll work.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's see if it works.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm going to see if she answers.
[SPEAKER_01]: Please answer.
[SPEAKER_11]: Dope.
[SPEAKER_11]: Problem with remote sound device.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, that sucks.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, I'll open up the Skype line for an afterbirth call if somebody wants to call us.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_11]: Otherwise, what are your big plans for this next week?
[SPEAKER_11]: Anything exciting?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I'm going to try to slack off as much as possible except for gym time.
[SPEAKER_11]: I need to work out this week really bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm planning on going to the gym actually as much as I can during the next couple weeks.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, when I start school, I'm going to start running.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll be at ARC Monday and Wednesday, so I'll just go running.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or play DDR.
[SPEAKER_11]: I really should sign up for a gym, because I think I'd actually maybe use a gym membership if I was paying for it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sign up for my gym.
[SPEAKER_11]: You go to Family Fitness, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's the one I would probably sign up with.
[SPEAKER_20]: They're everywhere.
[SPEAKER_11]: In this area, yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_11]: The hotel I was at had a gym thing at it, but I was just too lazy to go.
[SPEAKER_05]: www.DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_11]: That's not a bad idea.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's what I did when I went to E3.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have my weights with me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: I hope we get to go to E3 again next year.
[SPEAKER_11]: That would be blissful.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll get to go.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll be there.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, we're getting a call.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hooray.
[SPEAKER_11]: You are on Orange Lounge Radio after birth.
[SPEAKER_18]: I joined a gym.
[SPEAKER_11]: Why?
[SPEAKER_11]: Are you calling me fat?
[SPEAKER_18]: No, I'm messing with you, man.
[SPEAKER_18]: No, it's a good thing to join a gym, but at the same time, your first week you're going to be in pain.
[SPEAKER_18]: I know.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've kind of worked out before.
[SPEAKER_01]: Couldn't I just play DDR?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, no, start off on the cardio, seriously.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's the easiest thing to start with.
[SPEAKER_08]: But the weight training, the first night I did weight training,
[SPEAKER_08]: I could not move my arms for like five days.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was so sore.
[SPEAKER_11]: I want to join one that has a big pool so I could swim.
[SPEAKER_11]: The one by my house has a pool.
[SPEAKER_08]: You need to come to spin with me.
[SPEAKER_11]: Didn't you say that spin kicks your ass?
[SPEAKER_08]: It did the first couple times, but they let you take it easy the first time around.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_11]: You're a Jamie Yeti dude.
[SPEAKER_11]: Do you go to a gym?
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, I do.
[SPEAKER_18]: I've recently joined one like about a week ago.
[SPEAKER_11]: And has it been effective?
[SPEAKER_11]: You got washboard abs and muscles now?
[SPEAKER_18]: Too early to say.
[SPEAKER_11]: Pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_11]: Soon though, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: Soon enough.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, I needed that, so thank you for yelling at me.
[SPEAKER_11]: I needed it.
[SPEAKER_18]: No problem, man.
[SPEAKER_18]: Later.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Later.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, that's going to do it for tonight's Afterbirth.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you guys for tuning in and supporting Orange Laws Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: Tomorrow night, Diversion.
[SPEAKER_11]: Don't forget, we're doing a little bit of a schedule switch.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's going to be permanent.
[SPEAKER_11]: Diversion will now be on Monday nights to accommodate Jamie going back to school.
[SPEAKER_11]: She will be doing Pump Up the Volume on Tuesday night.
[SPEAKER_11]: So definitely tune in.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then Wednesday nights, who knows what will happen soon.
[SPEAKER_08]: People have to put up with me bitching about school now because I'm having to take... The classes that I'm actually taking in a classroom are Business Law.
[SPEAKER_08]: which is my Monday and Wednesday class which is going to suck ass and my other class is going to be Intro to Windows on Saturday because I can't test out of it because I don't have time to make it to the damn test because I don't have the days off you're going to be stuck doing it for a whole semester
[SPEAKER_08]: Half semester.
[SPEAKER_08]: Which is one good thing, it's half semester.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I'm thinking about telling my teacher, excuse me, I know all this shit.
[SPEAKER_08]: Can't you challenge the course?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I can, I can test out of it.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I figured at the very least it would be easy A and get me started.
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess that's a true point.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's on a Saturday though, so I can, since I'll have my laptop, I'll just play on the internet during class.
[SPEAKER_08]: Play Ragnarok or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: Seriously?
[SPEAKER_11]: Good idea, good idea.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll see what his attendance policy is and I'll skip most of them.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: How's that for a good attitude to take going into school?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going home.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I would like to pass on my warm wishes to our listeners from the depths of my, excuse me, heart.
[SPEAKER_11]: Clusterfuck
[SPEAKER_11]: But first, I wanted to play this song in case my friend is listening and hopefully he is and he knows who he is.
[SPEAKER_11]: Mr. Bandicoot, if you're listening, here's a song that I know you wanted to hear.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then after this song from Castlevania, it'll go into Poppin' Music 11.
[SPEAKER_11]: So enjoy.
[SPEAKER_11]: And thanks for listening and tuning in to Orange Laundry.
[SPEAKER_11]: Everybody, good night.
Thanks for watching!
Thank you for watching!