And now for our feature presentation.
[SPEAKER_15]: Orange Lounge Radio Live is now on the air.
[SPEAKER_15]: Orange Lounge Radio Live is a live talk program dedicated to all things Bomani and Bensum.
[SPEAKER_15]: Orange Lounge Radio may contain adult content, so you probably shouldn't let your children listen.
[SPEAKER_15]: If you do let your children listen to Orange Lounge Radio, they may turn into evil little demons from hell!
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh wait, most children already are evil little demons from hell.
[SPEAKER_21]: Now you see that evil will always triumph, because good is dumb.
[SPEAKER_21]: Fat, drunk, and stupid is no way to go through life, sir.
[SPEAKER_21]: He jeopardizes my ability to effectively govern this student body.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, makes you look like an ass is what he does, Ed.
[SPEAKER_21]: Hamburgers!
[SPEAKER_21]: The cornerstone of any nutritious breakfast.
[SPEAKER_21]: That was huge.
[SPEAKER_21]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you mind if I take my new car for a ride?
[SPEAKER_02]: Catherine, the only thing you're going to be riding is me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have you seen my... Lena?
[SPEAKER_21]: Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to my underground lair.
[SPEAKER_21]: So it was you.
[SPEAKER_21]: DarkSakura, Sky, Loki, Orange Lounge Radio,
[SPEAKER_05]: We are live, and this is episode number 107 for this August the 15th of 2004.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're tuned in to the Bee Money Scene's most unexciting radio station of all things, Bee Money.
[SPEAKER_05]: My name is Rob Roberts, but you might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_05]: Joining me, as always, are my awesome co-hosts in this corner, the happiest bunny on the farm, Miss Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know her better as DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_19]: That was very anticlimactic, your little... I know.
[SPEAKER_18]: We're old.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're old?
[SPEAKER_05]: I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: You realize, you, me, Loki, we're about five years older than the Bomani average, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: If not, maybe ten.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't know if our show's ready for retirement or it's a nursing home or something.
[SPEAKER_19]: We're still kicking.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to turn our mics up just a tad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do not adjust your volume on your... Okay, we're up a little bit there.
[SPEAKER_05]: What was I going to say?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, you're ready to quit doing this show?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think you have to bring your hate to the masses.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm going to quit for like five seconds.
[SPEAKER_19]: I quit.
[SPEAKER_19]: Jamie!
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay, I'm not quitting anymore.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, good.
[SPEAKER_05]: Funny enough, that's not the first time she's threatened to quit the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: When have I ever?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also joining us is our third co-host, our third wheel.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Tech Master, Loki!
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi!
[SPEAKER_05]: The mic is quite loud today!
[SPEAKER_05]: That means you do not scream in it, you just talk like normal.
[SPEAKER_05]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: You got a loud voice.
[SPEAKER_05]: You got a loud man voice, so you can take it away from the mouth a little.
[SPEAKER_09]: The whole show I'm just going to be like, I'm going to mubble.
[SPEAKER_07]: How's it going?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm good.
[SPEAKER_05]: You going to go?
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also joining us tonight, we have some very special guests.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have somebody who hasn't been here in a few weeks.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's always kind of here.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's like our mascot.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think he's kind of like the mascot because he's here.
[SPEAKER_05]: He doesn't talk a whole lot, but neither does the guy in the chicken suit at the football game.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'm dubbing him our mascot.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Arcadian42.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yay, I had gas today.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oops, I'm in my car and I had gas today.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can I get a go team go?
[SPEAKER_10]: Go team... Stop, stop, don't go anymore.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, I'm not going.
[SPEAKER_05]: And where have you been, young man?
[SPEAKER_05]: Where have you been?
[SPEAKER_05]: At my apartment.
[SPEAKER_05]: You missed a big show last week.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I didn't have a guess last week, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: We actually had a big show last week.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm actually afraid to see how many people come back.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because last week, our show was dominated by this song.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know, this Akira song that I guess was big or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: We had to play, and there was tons of people here.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'm kind of curious how many actually come back to hear what the real train wreck sounds like tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because on tonight's platter, you guys, absolutely nothing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, also with us tonight, the lovely DDR Angel is back this week.
[SPEAKER_17]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_17]: I have cheese-its.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mmm, cheese-its.
[SPEAKER_05]: What kind?
[SPEAKER_17]: Uh, cheddar and jack.
[SPEAKER_17]: Don't ask.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, we'll be talking to all our guests a little bit more later.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to definitely play some How Was Your Week, How Was Your Day when we come back.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then I suppose we have some Bomani news too we should take care of.
[SPEAKER_19]: Attention, John Field, my name is not Jammie.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_19]: One M, please.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jamie, we'll scold you if you want to join our chatroom.
[SPEAKER_05]: www.orangeloungeradio.com, click on chat, and be berated by the lovely DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: This one?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, you're welcome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, in this break, I thought we could do some booty-rific music from DDR Solo 2000.
[SPEAKER_05]: because I wanted to hear I'm Alive.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll do some Don't Clock Me and maybe some Captain Jack too in this break.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we'll be back in a little bit with Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's dream a dream together A dream that is real
[SPEAKER_13]: I want to rock!
[SPEAKER_04]: Bitch, get a new song.
[SPEAKER_04]: An open letter from Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whoa, hello.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right, bitch.
[SPEAKER_05]: Get a new song, Orange Lines Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the old school promos back when it sounded like we were talking through two tin cans.
[SPEAKER_05]: Beautiful.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because we were at that time.
[SPEAKER_18]: We were emulating our hero, the tin can lady from DDR Solo.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like we have a budget all of a sudden, suddenly here on this show.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's amazing.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, two cents.
[SPEAKER_05]: Give us money.
[SPEAKER_05]: Give me money.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, I'm thinking about putting a poll on the website next week.
[SPEAKER_05]: You should go to our website and always take the poll.
[SPEAKER_05]: And take old polls, too, because polls are important.
[SPEAKER_18]: But remember, when you're done taking them, give them back.
[SPEAKER_05]: What is this week's poll, anyway?
[SPEAKER_05]: I forget.
[SPEAKER_05]: Over on OrangeLaundry.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it has something to do with Xbox.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it was about that quad mode.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which we'll talk about later, that quad mode on Ultramix.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I want to know what you guys think about quad mode on Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll talk about this later.
[SPEAKER_05]: We've got to go vote in our poll on OrangeLoungeRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: There will be a poll coming up soon about who wants to buy an Orange Lounge t-shirt.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I happen to have a friend at work who has a friend that owns a t-shirt business.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who can get us some deals on t-shirts.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm thinking about doing a little money making for the show, so...
[SPEAKER_05]: Especially if we're going to have to raise that cap thanks to last week's show, so we'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nobody's locked out of the stream tonight, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: Plenty of spots still available if you have a friend that wants to listen to the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: Definitely.
[SPEAKER_19]: And if they don't want to, make them.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: And certainly, you know, there's all these past polls on the site, too, that you can still go take.
[SPEAKER_05]: Then we'll see who wants a shirt.
[SPEAKER_19]: The polls are fun.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, the polls are fun.
[SPEAKER_19]: They're interesting.
[SPEAKER_19]: They are.
[SPEAKER_19]: In a poll-like way.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not a whole lot of sites that do DDR polling out there.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, of course there's DDR Freak, but unfortunately we only get one new poll a month there.
[SPEAKER_05]: And who else does polls on their site?
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't think of any.
[SPEAKER_19]: There's a few other, but they're not really Bimani related.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're not us.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the important thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, they're not us.
[SPEAKER_05]: So go support the Orange Lawn Radio poll.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course, tonight, lots to talk about in the Bimani world.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think what we're going to do tonight, because last week was kind of,
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_19]: We knew him back in the days of his old nickname.
[SPEAKER_05]: We listened to him when he was underground.
[SPEAKER_18]: We saw him dunk.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, here's the thing, is that the weekend he comes back, I don't know if I should say what weekend he might come back, because it depends on work.
[SPEAKER_19]: If it's the weekend I'm thinking it is, it's the weekend that Jamie might be going camping.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let me put it this way, it's the next weekend we're probably going to do a dunk show.
[SPEAKER_05]: When would that be?
[SPEAKER_19]: When I'm going camping.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, you suck!
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, alright, we'll see, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_09]: I want to go... Two weeks we're doing a drug show, or at least I'm doing a drug show.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you have Monday off or something?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I'll take Monday off on my birthday weekend.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Jamie will do... We'll celebrate the crashing of planes.
[SPEAKER_19]: If I'm here, I'll do a shot of tequila, but I'm not going to drink like I did last time.
[SPEAKER_19]: You know how I drank last time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, I remember that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tequila is not low-carb.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, we'll have Sigrid back in a few weeks.
[SPEAKER_05]: But since last week was kind of dominated by him being here, not only that, but us teasing everybody with the Uran thing, and then we also had Pirate Power was here, and who else was here?
[SPEAKER_05]: Angel was here, Anita.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we kind of pushed all the Mamani news aside, except for the Uran thing, and hints.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, the running gag last week was that everything was a hint.
[SPEAKER_05]: So...
[SPEAKER_05]: Now we're actually going to go back and talk about some of the Bimani news from last week and this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because there's been a lot in the past two weeks.
[SPEAKER_05]: A lot of Bimani news.
[SPEAKER_19]: I did notice, though, a general consensus.
[SPEAKER_19]: I think a lot of people like the original better.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't.
[SPEAKER_05]: I prefer the remix.
[SPEAKER_05]: I do prefer the remix.
[SPEAKER_19]: I have to say I like the original better.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's certainly better suited for DDR.
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, yeah, for DDR, but I mean as a song.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it would just depend on the mood I'm in.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, I think the original works better in the scope of a Silent Hill soundtrack, but the new one works better for a dance-y soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_18]: True.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll play it again tonight, because I know some people may have missed it last week, so we'll play it again tonight at some point.
[SPEAKER_05]: We won't make you wait two hours this time, we'll play it soon.
[SPEAKER_05]: but I'll have some other songs we have to play too because, you know, they announced a bunch of stuff for Ultramix and some of you guys, even though they're from 2DX, you haven't heard it before so we definitely want to make sure you hear this before the game comes out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm just getting out of the way early.
[SPEAKER_05]: Damn it.
[SPEAKER_05]: My baby won't work for you.
[SPEAKER_05]: My prop isn't working.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: All my work is about to fall off the table.
[SPEAKER_19]: Throw me the baby.
[SPEAKER_19]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_19]: Wee, babies.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, moving on.
[SPEAKER_05]: We've got to get this out of the way, though, because this is how we start off every show.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have to talk a little bit about how was your week, how was your day.
[SPEAKER_05]: And starting us off, as always, the lovely DarkSakura is going to say how her week was and how her day was.
[SPEAKER_19]: My week was pretty dull.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, it was just work.
[SPEAKER_19]: Except that I started class on Wednesday.
[SPEAKER_19]: I had my first orientation for one of my online classes.
[SPEAKER_19]: And I took another orientation on Saturday and dropped some really retarded class that they're making me take, which was Intro to Windows.
[SPEAKER_19]: When I found out what the last course was, I dropped it so fast.
[SPEAKER_19]: The last assignment in that class, Rob, is How to Rename and Move Files.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow, that sounds difficult.
[SPEAKER_19]: That sounds really stupid.
[SPEAKER_19]: Like, I know five-year-olds that can rename files, okay?
[SPEAKER_19]: So, I just, I dropped the class, and I'm going to petition the dean next quarter, next semester, to let me test out of it.
[SPEAKER_19]: Since I could do that with, like, you know, Windows 3.1, way back when.
[SPEAKER_19]: I could rename files in DOS.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_19]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember DOS?
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember?
[SPEAKER_05]: You were using Windows back when it was underground.
[SPEAKER_19]: I sure was.
[SPEAKER_19]: Back when this little, you know, kid in college thought he was brilliant and was going to make a different operating system.
[SPEAKER_05]: Back when they were an indie band, you were using Windows.
[SPEAKER_19]: No, but, um... But I'm going to... There's a bunch of classes I'm going to test out because they're really stupid.
[SPEAKER_19]: But, um... And, uh...
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm also planning on going back to finish... I'm thinking about double majoring, so I'm still sort of considering that.
[SPEAKER_19]: But it's just been work, school stuff, a little bit of personal drama in my life.
[SPEAKER_19]: Nothing major.
[SPEAKER_19]: I've been kind of stressed out, so... But I'm working on trying to stay positive, trying to stay happy...
[SPEAKER_19]: Trying to, you know, not erupt into random bouts of bitchiness over things beyond my control.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have a song to dedicate to you, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_19]: No.
[SPEAKER_19]: What?
[SPEAKER_19]: Why?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because it's no more drama.
[SPEAKER_19]: Haven't you heard this song?
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, it's from one of those stupid soap operas.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, it actually raps on the samples.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hold on, hold on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let it kick in here.
[SPEAKER_19]: That is desperation, okay?
[SPEAKER_19]: That's almost as bad as when the Sujis ripped that Enya song.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_19]: That's really, really bad.
[SPEAKER_19]: Really bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: This definitely should be in a DDR.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know a lot of people that could use... Yeah, that actually would be pretty good.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know a lot of people that could use that song.
[SPEAKER_19]: But, um... Yeah, I don't think that...
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't think that there's anything really all that major that happened in my week.
[SPEAKER_19]: Nothing of notable circumstance.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why aren't you boring?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, bite me.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just teasing you.
[SPEAKER_19]: You know, boring.
[SPEAKER_19]: There's a curse that says, may you live in interesting times.
[SPEAKER_12]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_19]: There's also another one that says, May the fleas of a thousand camels rest in your genitals, but I won't go into that one.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm going to pass on the mic.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, moving on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's talk to DDR Angel and see how her week and her day was.
[SPEAKER_05]: Angel?
[SPEAKER_17]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, geez.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, here, hold on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, Jamie wants to say one more thing.
[SPEAKER_19]: I broke Dan's main cabinet.
[SPEAKER_05]: How'd you break it?
[SPEAKER_19]: Actually, I pulled the joystick thing loose from the thing with my... You pulled the thing from the thing?
[SPEAKER_19]: The joystick mechanism, I pulled it... It's attached underneath the panel, and I pulled it loose, so it sunk into the panel.
[SPEAKER_18]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_19]: Because his machine could not withstand my mad Street Fighter Alpha 2 prowess.
[SPEAKER_18]: I see.
[SPEAKER_17]: Anyway, hi!
[SPEAKER_17]: Hi, Angel!
[SPEAKER_05]: How was your week?
[SPEAKER_05]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, pretty good.
[SPEAKER_17]: Um, just been working and stuff.
[SPEAKER_17]: Um, I signed up for classes yesterday, so... Yay!
[SPEAKER_17]: So, oh my god, we're all gonna meet in the cafeteria and be like... Lunchtime high school crap.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like Heather's.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, I guess so.
[SPEAKER_17]: Here, wait.
[SPEAKER_17]: Let the ferret talk for a second.
[SPEAKER_17]: See?
[SPEAKER_17]: He likes it too.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: I still want to set the ferrets on fire.
[SPEAKER_05]: No!
[SPEAKER_17]: No!
[SPEAKER_17]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe for Halloween.
[SPEAKER_17]: Just work and going to be school soon.
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_17]: My life's pretty boring now that I'm up here.
[SPEAKER_17]: But it's okay, I guess.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, moving on then.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was a nice space, Dead Air, thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Arcadian42, how was your week, how was your day?
[SPEAKER_10]: Uh, uh, a week has been work, and, and, apartment, uh, work, I've been at this place for about three months, and now they offer me that, uh, that I can be their actual employee instead of a temp.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm probably gonna take it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Right on.
[SPEAKER_10]: That'd be good.
[SPEAKER_10]: Which is nice.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, in a few months I get more money, so.
[SPEAKER_10]: That would be good.
[SPEAKER_10]: And not sitting at home all day every day like I usually do.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just go out to the stores and not play anything else.
[SPEAKER_10]: I haven't played any Mimani in like a long time.
[SPEAKER_10]: And because data entry all day doesn't really mesh very well with Beatmania.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's like the only thing I have at home that I can play anymore because I sold everything else.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, and that's about all.
[SPEAKER_10]: Today I just sat around
[SPEAKER_10]: I didn't do anything.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just played Final Fantasy.
[SPEAKER_10]: And, uh...
[SPEAKER_09]: I was working on my cabinet because I got the new thing to fix it so there's no lag.
[SPEAKER_09]: But that didn't work too well, so I need to rewire the whole damn thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Which will, in the end, be better anyways.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because it's a real mess as far as wires go.
[SPEAKER_09]: And, I don't know, just sitting there at work and reading the internet.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's pretty much all I do.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nothing interesting, I'm afraid.
[SPEAKER_09]: Damn, that would suck.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, so what's up?
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow, am I the only one that actually tried to go play some DDR this week?
[SPEAKER_07]: Which is... I played Step Mania.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if Step Mania counts.
[SPEAKER_05]: Step Mania is not DDR!
[SPEAKER_05]: It is not DDR!
[SPEAKER_05]: No, that's a message to everybody.
[SPEAKER_05]: Step Mania is not DDR.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you AAA something in Step Mania, it doesn't mean shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_09]: Why?
[SPEAKER_09]: Why does it mean shit?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I said so.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because it's not the same thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Using your fingers and using your feet are two different things.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, you're playing on a pad.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you're playing on a pad, it still doesn't count because Stepmania is not DDR and it's different timing.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can actually make the timing exact.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, what do you have to say about that?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's a load of crap.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's still not DDR.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you can bite me.
[SPEAKER_05]: So how was your week?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, my week?
[SPEAKER_05]: My week, I spent making fun of Stepmania people who say it's DDR.
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_18]: Ah, continuation.
[SPEAKER_09]: I forgot to mention, because I'm sure Rob wanted to talk about this anyways, the other thing I was doing this week is researching interdimensional communication.
[SPEAKER_09]: And, yeah, I'm going to build a device.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let me say that again for those that didn't catch it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki is studying interdimensional communication.
[SPEAKER_05]: And he's going to build a device.
[SPEAKER_05]: What kind of device?
[SPEAKER_17]: He's zipping in a portal to hell.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, it's a... No, it's not a portal to hell!
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the same thing I said.
[SPEAKER_05]: I said he's building a vortex to hell is what he's making right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: This show is a vortex to hell.
[SPEAKER_09]: I am basically recreating an experiment done by some guy who is now dead.
[SPEAKER_09]: And we know why.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, anyways.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's basically called a germanium communicator.
[SPEAKER_09]: The reason why it's called a germanium communicator is because isn't a germanium what you keep gerbils in?
[SPEAKER_18]: It's a plant.
[SPEAKER_18]: You're trying to talk to plants.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I'm not.
[SPEAKER_09]: Not Geranium.
[SPEAKER_09]: People at my work do that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Germanium.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like German with an I-U-M.
[SPEAKER_19]: Isn't that an element?
[SPEAKER_09]: Exactly, that's what it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's an element.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's like one of the... Number 37 on the periodical chart.
[SPEAKER_09]: It has the same compounds as silicon almost.
[SPEAKER_19]: You can make boobs out of it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Silicon, not silicone.
[SPEAKER_09]: God.
[SPEAKER_09]: Adding letters to my stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, so I'm gonna buy... I'm buying an ingo of this stuff off the internet since they don't really, you know, sell... Which you can make by synthesizing four of the ore plus a fire crystal, just for the record.
[SPEAKER_09]: And you say, I'm a Final Fantasy addict.
[SPEAKER_09]: God.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I'm buying an ingo of this stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: Basically what it does...
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you for watching.
[SPEAKER_09]: See you next time.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I don't see why it wouldn't work now.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know everyone thinks I'm crazy, but I'm gonna laugh at you when it works.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm gonna laugh at you.
[SPEAKER_18]: How do you know if they're dead?
[SPEAKER_18]: What if they're really demons?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: What if you're picking up, like, a baby monitor upstairs or something?
[SPEAKER_09]: I hear something noise.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, that's funny you should mention that, because this in no way can pick up radio waves or, you know, any sort of broadcast of that form.
[SPEAKER_09]: It only picks up, um, I think magnetic frequencies, so...
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry, it doesn't work that way.
[SPEAKER_18]: You can't tune radio with this.
[SPEAKER_18]: Do you have Final Fantasy XI in hell?
[SPEAKER_19]: No, it's hell.
[SPEAKER_19]: Of course we have it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyways, I will post in the chat room the website that I'm going to.
[SPEAKER_09]: They actually have recordings of this that's been done a while back.
[SPEAKER_09]: And funny enough, the guy that was basically doing this, who also won a Nobel Prize and has a PhD in experimental sciences... All things that you don't have.
[SPEAKER_09]: All things that I don't have.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't fucking care, okay?
[SPEAKER_09]: Because what I don't have, I'm going to make better because his device only had, you know, a small little piece that was a two millimeter by three and a half millimeter piece of germanium.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm using an inch by an inch piece of germanium.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's 25 times the size.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm just multiplying everything by 25.
[SPEAKER_19]: So are you an advocate that bigger is better?
[SPEAKER_05]: Notice how Loki has taken what you do for cookies.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like when you have too much cookie dough, you just double the recipe for everything, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: He's taken that and now he's going to multiply everything on this talking to the dead communicator by 25.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's going to build a vortex to hell, I'm telling you.
[SPEAKER_19]: So basically he's applying the math behind cookie dough to metaphysical communication.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, what I suggested over dinner when Loki was telling us the first time is that we could take this device to Golf Land and really mess with people.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, I think we should hook it up so that it's in that area between the pad and the screen so when little kids run in front of it, they get sucked into hell.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, first off, like I said before, it's not a fucking vortex to hell.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's another device to which I do not have the schematics for.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can you build one of those?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I really want to get rid of some of those people at Golfline.
[SPEAKER_19]: Didn't you ever see the gate?
[SPEAKER_19]: You have to dig a hole in your backyard.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, listen now.
[SPEAKER_09]: Honestly, seriously, I am interested in this stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know if it's a phase or something, but I am so fucking bored at work, I have nothing to do.
[SPEAKER_09]: And this is what they're forcing me to do.
[SPEAKER_19]: So first it's cursed dolls.
[SPEAKER_19]: Now it's communicating with the dead.
[SPEAKER_19]: You can touch your dolly.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh my god, that's what this is all about, is that Loki needs to talk to his dolls.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, you're a genius, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_09]: First off, I don't have any haunted dolls, because I forgot to bid on the goddamn thing in the beginning.
[SPEAKER_09]: And second of all... Second of all, okay, this doesn't have anything to do with fucking talking to dolls, okay?
[SPEAKER_09]: Goddammit.
[SPEAKER_19]: Don't you want to talk to the demon or dead thing that possessed the doll?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm loving this chatroom feedback we have here.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought there already was a vortex to hell.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's called Roseville Golf Land.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the Bomani.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's where Bomani machines go to die.
[SPEAKER_18]: Scandia is where Bomani goes to die.
[SPEAKER_05]: Scandia is where Bomani goes to die again.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, re-death.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, listen now.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: This basically, all this is right here, it's another form of EVP, as I was talking before, which is, you know, electronic voice phenomenon.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's basically, what happens is you can record...
[SPEAKER_09]: You record voices that you don't hear.
[SPEAKER_09]: And they're done through manipulation of the diaphragm and a microphone.
[SPEAKER_09]: Basically, you can record things that normal humans can't hear.
[SPEAKER_09]: They do this all the fucking time.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: and don't even yet, okay?
[SPEAKER_09]: Anybody can do this with a tape recorder.
[SPEAKER_09]: They can do this, and you can actually wire something up very simple with a germanium diode that they supposedly sell at Radio Shack, but I sure as hell could find it today.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyways, you can do that, and it'll actually only record just, you know, what you can't hear, and it'll block everything else out.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's very interesting hearing people do that, and you get some really creepy shit on there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Butcher, mock me as you will.
[SPEAKER_09]: I will fucking send the vortex after you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Speaking of mocking Loki, we have a comment from the chatroom.
[SPEAKER_12]: This is the best comment ever.
[SPEAKER_05]: UnknownGamer says, Loki does want to talk to his dolls.
[SPEAKER_05]: He wants to talk to his Final Fantasy figurines and see if Tifa and Yuna love him.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't even have dolls.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that's stupid.
[SPEAKER_19]: He wants to talk to his chocobo to see if his chocobo goes work at him.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can I make a joke?
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you're able to build this machine and talk to the dead, will you be able to communicate with Miss Cleo's career?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_19]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: Enough of this.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm just reminded of that scene from Bill and Ted's Bogus Journey.
[SPEAKER_09]: To hell with all you people.
[SPEAKER_19]: No, no, don't say that!
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't say that, Loki, because you will do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know you will with this machine.
[SPEAKER_19]: No, but like that scene when they're having the seance.
[SPEAKER_05]: Honestly, Rob, how many things have I built that have actually worked?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a very good point.
[SPEAKER_19]: You know, in defense of Loki's little idea, I'm supporting it.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm curious...
[SPEAKER_05]: Is this what we're calling it now?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's officially the little idea?
[SPEAKER_05]: Your little idea.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_19]: I will support this.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm interested to see how it turns out.
[SPEAKER_19]: But I'm also wondering, though, what you would use to record visual data.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, they have that.
[SPEAKER_19]: Really?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's been done.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's really strange how it works, too.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's basically everything revolves around white noise.
[SPEAKER_09]: In this case, what they use, a common way they use to record it, they have some other complicated devices, but the easiest way you can do it now is you take a video camera and you record, you basically put the output onto a TV, then you record that, and it creates interference because it's recording the same fucking thing over and over.
[SPEAKER_09]: But in that, when you record that, you go back frame by frame and you'll actually see shit on there.
[SPEAKER_09]: And they have pictures of it that have been done.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's very interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: But the guy that did the experiments, he actually had his own device because this is like way back in the day when TVs and shit were fucking expensive and computers were the size of football fields and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um...
[SPEAKER_19]: We need to have to take a bazillion magnets and put them in a room to make a kilobyte.
[SPEAKER_09]: So basically, this is something he made a while back, and supposedly what happened was later on people recreated this experiment in the 90s.
[SPEAKER_09]: The most recent I've heard of this experiment being recreated was in 2003.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't really know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I guess for some reason, for a few years they had no results recreating the same thing, because there's a lot of other factors that they can't figure in, that they don't know what the hell...
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, why it doesn't work or why it works.
[SPEAKER_18]: It goes to camera shy?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, it's not camera shy.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's complicated.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway, I'll give you guys the websites.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can go look at it.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can think I'm crazy.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_09]: But this is what I'm reading up on.
[SPEAKER_09]: And, I mean, I'm not a real believer in the paranormal and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I'm a believer in science.
[SPEAKER_09]: And, you know, they have scientific proof to prove this.
[SPEAKER_09]: They just can't explain it.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's obviously beyond our knowledge now.
[SPEAKER_09]: So...
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know, it just sounds interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: If it's so easy to recreate the experiment, then why not?
[SPEAKER_09]: But yeah, I'm crazy.
[SPEAKER_09]: But the thing is, though, there's another guy.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's another guy that created a thing called Luminator, which is basically... It's some sort of device that... It uses fans or something, and it blows water through rings of water.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or air through rings of water.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know how the fuck that happens, but... Anyway, supposedly that creates a weird field or something, and if you photograph someone with that field, you'll actually see...
[SPEAKER_09]: Like someone else's face on theirs.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_09]: Then the guy supposedly put three of these in like a triangle configuration and that created the vortex, you know, that you were also talking about.
[SPEAKER_05]: And he saw the Triforce.
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, um, I was going to ask something about the... I lost my train of thought because I made the Triforce joke.
[SPEAKER_05]: Never mind, keep talking.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyways, I will post the links in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_09]: But there's some interesting stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's a whole bunch of stuff on EVPs that you can listen to that are really creepy sounding stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: But it's a lot of documentation on this.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's a lot of people recreating it the same way.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, I mean, you're getting a lot of people that are getting these results.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, scientifically, you can prove it.
[SPEAKER_19]: Is it like the dead boy in Three Men and a Baby?
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh, what?
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what I was thinking is that you should take this whole little idea of yours and you should film it all and put it on like public access TV.
[SPEAKER_05]: You could be the new Mr. Wizard.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wouldn't that be cool?
[SPEAKER_09]: No.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, but, um, you know...
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know, their results were just kind of like weird because one thing that they were saying that's important about this is resonance and anyone that doesn't know what resonance means that's just like, for example, resonance on a radio would be tuning in because you have all the frequencies out there and each station has its own frequency so you tune it to whatever station and then you're in resonance with that station and you basically get audio that way.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, the thing with this is you have to be resonance with
[SPEAKER_09]: Your thoughts or basically your aura or whatever, and that's the thing that's difficult because it's not only you, it's the people around you, and those all affect your environment plus other factors.
[SPEAKER_09]: So it's a lot of complex shit there, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to do it until I get bored with it, and then I'll work on my cabinet some more.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm ready to talk about my week and my day now.
[SPEAKER_19]: You got my joke.
[SPEAKER_05]: What joke?
[SPEAKER_19]: Didn't you ever see the thing about three men and a baby?
[SPEAKER_16]: No.
[SPEAKER_19]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_19]: about the one scene where they're walking in front of a window and there's a little boy standing behind this curtain and he was supposed to have been like some ghost who imprinted himself on the film he like blew his head off with a shotgun or something and then they walk by again I've seen it, the shotgun's there you're crazy talking
[SPEAKER_19]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh god, now you got Loki on another thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now he's going to start inserting ghosts into movies.
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, no, seriously, because he's like, and you can fully see him there.
[SPEAKER_19]: And I wouldn't just say this if I had, I mean, I'm sure that the logical thing is that it's some prop or something, but the other is that, see?
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_19]: Didn't I tell you?
[SPEAKER_19]: It shows up several times.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can you post that link in our chat room for those that want to check that out?
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_19]: Your week, Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, my week.
[SPEAKER_05]: I actually went out and played DDR this week, one night.
[SPEAKER_19]: Holy shit, you did?
[SPEAKER_05]: I went to Roseville Golf Land, because my friend had never seen DDR before.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I mean, actually, he'd seen DDR, but he wanted to see me play DDR, because he hadn't seen, like, Extreme.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I went, and I played, and I felt really stupid.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, I don't know how you guys feel about playing DDR for your friends for the first time, when you're, like, pretty good at DDR, like...
[SPEAKER_05]: I can play at a maniac level like I'm sure a lot of people listening to this show can.
[SPEAKER_05]: And to those that don't really see DDR a whole lot, I think it really weirds them out sometimes.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe it's just me.
[SPEAKER_05]: But he seemed to get a kick out of that.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the thing was that the up arrow on Extreme was broken, so like half my notes weren't registering.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then I went to try and play Guitar Freaks, and frickin' that machine was suckin' too, so...
[SPEAKER_05]: The hell with that place.
[SPEAKER_05]: Machines go to die.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I did at least go out to play DDR this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was going to try and play at home, but my stupid ignition pad's broken.
[SPEAKER_05]: So either I'm going to have to buy a new ignition pad, or Loki's going to have to finish his DDR pads.
[SPEAKER_05]: But since he's too busy building vortexes to hell, it's probably not going to happen anytime soon.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was going to work on that, and that's why I'm rewiring everything.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sure, alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway...
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess that's pretty... I don't really have a whole lot to say about my week and my day.
[SPEAKER_05]: It wasn't that exciting.
[SPEAKER_05]: I had a fine weekend.
[SPEAKER_05]: I went to a little gathering last night and that was cool, I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then two days ago... What did I do Friday night?
[SPEAKER_05]: I went out to a party with some friends and then went to a bar.
[SPEAKER_05]: Isn't that exciting?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_18]: Excitement is now.
[SPEAKER_05]: They have pinball machines at this bar now, though.
[SPEAKER_18]: Which ones?
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh...
[SPEAKER_05]: Monopoly, and the one with the aliens in the hologram, Revenge of Mars.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's just kind of funny to see those at a gay bar.
[SPEAKER_19]: If anybody in town happens to find a Black Knight 2000 pinball, tell me.
[SPEAKER_19]: Because Black Knight 2000 pinball is the most awesome pinball ever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe they'll have one at the Classic Gaming Expo, which you know we're going to be making an appearance at.
[SPEAKER_05]: Woohoo!
[SPEAKER_19]: Classic Gaming Expo!
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_19]: Konami's supposed to be doing something there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, Konami is doing something there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some of our buddies at KDA are actually working the booth there.
[SPEAKER_18]: They're working a booth.
[SPEAKER_05]: I sort of know what's going on, but I think it's supposed to be a secret, so I can't repeat it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a secret to everyone.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not Bimani related, but it's very cool nonetheless.
[SPEAKER_19]: Unless we play track and field.
[SPEAKER_19]: That would be cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: That would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I definitely want to go.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we'll be making an appearance there next weekend.
[SPEAKER_05]: It may affect next week's show, actually, but we're not sure yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: We think we might still have a show next weekend.
[SPEAKER_05]: But Jamie's still going to be there.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm actually going to be there partly for the show and partly with my fianc.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll have to pre-tape a show if we decide to be at Classic Gaming Expo all next week.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, we'll figure something out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think what we do now is we're going to go to break.
[SPEAKER_05]: And when we come back, we'll actually talk about some Bomani stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because there's been lots of Ultramix 2 news and DDR Extreme news this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Speaking of DDR Extreme, I think in this break we're going to play some music from DDR Extreme, including... Why not?
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll do Your Rain the Rage Mix again.
[SPEAKER_18]: You touched my body once, it burned
Thanks for watching!
What you see is me, baby
All my brothers and sisters, all in all, over 10 billion listeners, many a year, we do want to hear the hypest and ripest sound of the year.
Up and kiss the butt of the agent, up, up, up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay y'all, this is it, I fucked it, it's a life we'll see soon as I touch it Through this smooth and easy life, so we might get hyped in here tonight Be nice, be light, MC for the back, if you ain't with that, I'ma have to attack you with a bad rap That can smash this mouth up, if they jack, we don't start no crap Giving a little bit of heart and soul, as we do it, so you in your ear holes
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: After this song, we'll be having a Let Them Move Marathon.
[SPEAKER_04]: No!
[SPEAKER_05]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_05]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Crap-free Bavani Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, mostly crap-free, except for this show, of course.
[SPEAKER_05]: You are tuned in to Orange Lounge Radio, and we're here with episode number 107.
[SPEAKER_05]: I went to take a little break there talking about some new songs that are going to be in DDR Extreme.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you know, not all new.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course, Your Rain was new, but we have some old classics there, Never Ending Story and Wonderland.
[SPEAKER_05]: I noticed this kind of seems to be happening quite a bit where they're getting a lot of old songs and putting them in these new DDR games we have coming out.
[SPEAKER_05]: What else did we have in Extreme that was going to be in there?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, Only You, There You'll Be, Kick the Can, Don't Clock Me from Solo, like all these old-ass songs.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's kind of cool, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sugaru, that's kind of old now, I don't know, .59.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, so we are here on Orange Orange Radio and kind of talking about some news that happened last week.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wanted to talk about some things that happened while we were here.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's got all these different songs in there, a new DJ Simon song, Back to the Dance Floor, new Orange Lounge songs in it, new Naoki song, and all this stuff in 2DX Red.
[SPEAKER_05]: And supposedly there's this really, really hard song that's in it, that has this really hard note pattern.
[SPEAKER_05]: And actually, one of my buddies was kind enough to send me a video of it, so I'll show you guys kind of what this looks like.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now he's playing it on random.
[SPEAKER_05]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_19]: I will, I guess, read just your eyesight or something, the way you can read it easier.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let me show you what the end of the song looks like here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, that part doesn't look so hard, but kinda, there you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kinda crazy song in the end there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like the video.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it looks like they've made the interface a lot prettier.
[SPEAKER_05]: That they have the, um, barred... They, they, basically what they did in 2DX Red, I noticed, is that they took...
[SPEAKER_05]: One half of the screen, you remember when you would play 2DX, the side, if you were just in one player mode, the other half of the screen would have nothing, like it would just be a blank place for notes to fall.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, what they've done is they've kind of done the keyboard mania thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know how many of you guys have played keyboard mania, but keyboard mania had two monitors, and if you were playing it just in one player mode, it would show you like a little bar on the other side that would show you like how you were doing with your combo and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not quite that what they're doing in 2DX Red, but they've taken it, and now it's showing a graph of your score compared to the top score on the machine.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I thought that was kind of cool, is that you'd have a little bar that would go up as you did really good or really crappy on the song.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, I thought that was kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_05]: FoonMix
[SPEAKER_05]: FoodMix Plus.
[SPEAKER_09]: There was a FoodMix Plus release last week.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's all I have to say.
[SPEAKER_09]: There was about 15 new songs that they added, brand new interface, brand new non-stop ONI courses, and it's beautiful.
[SPEAKER_09]: They made what FoodMix was before, which was really awesome and made it even better.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just really kick-ass.
[SPEAKER_09]: From what I hear, though, the double steps leave a little bit to be desired, but
[SPEAKER_09]: Their single sets are awesome because I haven't gotten to play doubles yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: But really beautiful, awesome brand new videos.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just really awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: They've got a lot of nifty stuff that you can do now in Step Mania.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, for instance, the results screen has a type of graph that you would see in Beat Mania where it shows you how you did and everything.
[SPEAKER_09]: And your combo and all that.
[SPEAKER_09]: And just some really cool stuff that they did with the background.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just really pushing Step Mania to its limits.
[SPEAKER_05]: I noticed something interesting they did with the movies, is that they put a watermark of the song name in there, like at least that one for Made and Innocent that had the anime girl in it and stuff, they kind of put a watermark on the movie.
[SPEAKER_05]: Was there an issue where some of their movies were being pirated on other step files or something?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, it was just a little cool thing in the bottom.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's all.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was just for the one song, it just...
[SPEAKER_09]: look cool but it was just they actually what I like about them is they use video and still images just like you would in BMS files because I mean these guys are coming from BMS files and just the animations that they do in that are just awesome I really wish a lot of the US people would go and start doing BMS sim files first and then going to DWIs but it's just amazing the amount of work that they put in these
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought maybe all of their movies had the little watermark in the corner because their movies are so kick-ass.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wouldn't be surprised if people were stealing them and putting them on their own step files and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it kind of ties it to that one song.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it was just the Made in Innocence that had that?
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought I saw it on another one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, so I'm on crack.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's a few of them that say Foon Mix Plus in them, but that's about... I mean, so what?
[SPEAKER_09]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_09]: They just have really awesome stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like I said before, a lot of the music that's actually featured on there is going to be on Diverse 7, which you can find.
[SPEAKER_09]: And that comes in three different varieties, which I could talk about now or later, either way.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sure, why?
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: is that they either have three CDs, and I think two of them are BMS files, which are basically your Beatmania sim files, and they're really awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, for instance, we'll go down with 5Key and what they have on there.
[SPEAKER_09]: We have a remix of Superhighway called Superhighway the Cafe Electromix by a guy named Oni, or Only, I should say.
[SPEAKER_09]: A remix of What's Next with the song title What?
[SPEAKER_09]: Keep On Movin' Romantic Blue Style T.O.
[SPEAKER_09]: Na Remix of Area Code
[SPEAKER_09]: Ska, The Good Mix, Ninja Blast, Hayabusa Mix, Acid Bomb, The Overdosing Remix, Slash Trax,
[SPEAKER_09]: Recycle, a remix of Cycle by Spelunker, which is awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: He's done some really good stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: SDZ, which is The Gleam, which is a remix of SDZ.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm not familiar with that one.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then...
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh man, I'm going to fuck this up.
[SPEAKER_09]: Notch Music, which is You Gotta Groove remix.
[SPEAKER_09]: And that's, of course, a remix of You Gotta Groove.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then Seven Keys, some of the other ones that they have on here.
[SPEAKER_09]: They have a remix of Murmur Twins.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh hey, we've got some demo MP3s here.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I'll get those later.
[SPEAKER_09]: We can play them maybe during a break or something.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyways, Murmur Twins, the 4-6-0 beat mix.
[SPEAKER_09]: Reality, the Alpha 0.2 mix.
[SPEAKER_09]: Some other song in Japanese.
[SPEAKER_09]: Bad Boy Bass, the Switchback to 93 remix.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maiden Innocent, which is featured in Spoon Mix Plus.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just hope that Bad Boy Bass remix has that sample still in it.
[SPEAKER_18]: One more time with the Bad Boy Bass!
[SPEAKER_09]: YSQ, Number 12.8, Holix, Loveheart Sign, X2, and Small Voyager
[SPEAKER_09]: And then they have one last one, which is other mixes.
[SPEAKER_09]: And that's Time Piece Phase 2, High Transparency Mix, which is One Phase Blues, I think, remix.
[SPEAKER_09]: Healing Vision remix, which is just that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Over the Drive.
[SPEAKER_09]: Mirrorball Satellite 2004, which is in the original Foon mix.
[SPEAKER_19]: That sounds awesome, because that's an inflow song.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, and it was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_09]: Then there's a few other ones I'll see here.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yama Da Jet, Coaster Girl, which is a Yama Jet remix.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_09]: Implantation, DV Mix, Lamb of God, Trip Machine, Dark Core Mix, and some other ones.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I'm going to get some of these demo MP3s and maybe play them on a break or something.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because they're usually about 30 seconds long, so we'll get a bunch of different songs there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sure, that sounds like fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, we'll do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to change gears here because I want to talk about Ultramix 2 because the Ultramix 2 news has been flying really fast this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's been a lot of new stuff announced for Ultramix 2 within this week and last week, and that's including some songs.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some new songs have been announced for these games, so I want to see if we can address what some of those songs are.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um...
[SPEAKER_05]: Some things that have been figured out is that we got some early songs that have been announced for Ultramix 2, including 321 Stars by DJ Simon, A by DJ Amuro, and B4U by Naoki, which were all, if I remember right, in the E3 demo, so none of that's a surprise.
[SPEAKER_05]: But get this, here's your first licensed song from Ultramix 2, Brick House by The Commodores.
[SPEAKER_05]: Isn't that crazy?
[SPEAKER_19]: That's kind of, is it like a remix of it?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, it's the original, she's on brick.
[SPEAKER_05]: Moonlight Shadow by Missing Heart from Fifth Mix
[SPEAKER_05]: Very popular licensed track.
[SPEAKER_05]: That makes me happy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, very popular licensed track.
[SPEAKER_05]: Getting a lot of people really geared up for Ultramix, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very happy about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: My Summer Love, Night in Motion, which was actually a licensed track.
[SPEAKER_18]: Night in Motion, cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: A lot of people think that that is a Konami original, but it was actually a licensed track from DDR4thMix.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you would know this song, definitely, because it has that really catchy hook at the beginning of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's a little bit of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait, let me...
[SPEAKER_05]: Let me get a little bit of the hook here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everybody knows that song.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, so that one's going to be in a DDR Ultra Mix.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right on the Light by Mr. T. Now, wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a 2DX song that's being ported over for DDR.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that is something brand new that we've never had in DDR before.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it doesn't stop there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Route 80s by Sampling Masters Mega.
[SPEAKER_05]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: From DDR.
[SPEAKER_18]: Attention.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're actually going to play some of these songs.
[SPEAKER_05]: For those of you that haven't heard them.
[SPEAKER_18]: Do that for the next break.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, we'll do that in the next break.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to play some of these songs for those that haven't heard them before.
[SPEAKER_05]: Star Mine by Ryu from 2DX4 style.
[SPEAKER_05]: You remember that?
[SPEAKER_05]: With Tran with a little fan.
[SPEAKER_05]: Star Mine will be fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's going to be very fun on DDR.
[SPEAKER_05]: Act 6 to do stuff well this is the interesting thing is that they have said they have said in the thread that different people are doing the steps than did them for Ultramix 1 so you're not going to see steps like you saw in Ultramix 1 and supposedly they have people that know their stuff on DDR that are making these steps so so it's not Konami of Hawaii well they didn't really I don't think they really said one way or the other I haven't been keeping tabs on the information thread um
[SPEAKER_05]: and also I don't want to cross the line from what I've been told.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know what I can say and what I can't.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'm just going to move on to the next song, which is from 2DX.
[SPEAKER_05]: VJ Army by Good Cool.
[SPEAKER_19]: Now that's cool.
[SPEAKER_19]: VJ Army will be fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: VJ Army is going to be fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: A lot of people have said that should be in DDR for a long time.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's very cool that that one's going to make it in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, it's okay if you've never played 2DX and you've never heard these songs before, we're going to play them for you in the next break.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you can get a feel of what you're going to be dancing to pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_17]: Goddammit, does that mean I have to buy an Xbox?
[SPEAKER_05]: This is very interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: When Ultramix 2 was first announced, a lot of people were like, yeah, whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I think Ultramix was very successful for those that already had an Xbox, but it didn't really convert a whole lot of people.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm an exception.
[SPEAKER_05]: I did buy an Xbox pretty much so I could play Ultramix.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ultramix and Halo.
[SPEAKER_19]: This new one sounds like it's going to be a big selling point.
[SPEAKER_05]: But this new one, Microsoft should be sucking Konami's cock for this one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because they're going to sell a lot of Xboxes with this mix, I think.
[SPEAKER_05]: Based on DDR fans alone.
[SPEAKER_19]: Microsoft better put out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_05]: Microsoft should be putting out.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's... I don't know, maybe I should put a poll up over and see how many people are seriously contemplating buying an Xbox just because of Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because a lot of people were saying, when Ultramix 2 was first announced, yeah, yeah, yeah, great, Ultramix 2, yeah, whatever, you know, Xbox people will enjoy it.
[SPEAKER_05]: But now that the song list is starting to come out and people are like, whoa, we're getting Moonlight Shadow and these 2DX songs that have never been in DDR before...
[SPEAKER_19]: Actually, I have to agree with Kyle in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_19]: I think I actually wouldn't mind seeing Get On Beat Wildstyle.
[SPEAKER_19]: Actually, I wouldn't mind seeing the original Get On Beat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, this certainly is not the full list.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is just what we know so far about Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or Lab.
[SPEAKER_19]: They need to put Lab.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's one thing I think is kind of different about Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: They just announced this this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's going to be a brand new dance mode in Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: What makes an Xbox different than a PlayStation 2?
[SPEAKER_05]: Other than the obvious Microsoft and... It has... You can store a small family inside of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Besides that.
[SPEAKER_19]: It has a really big hard drive and four ports.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ah, it has four ports, as opposed to two, which means what?
[SPEAKER_05]: You can plug in four dance pads at once.
[SPEAKER_19]: Which means you don't need a multi-tap.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, you don't need a multi-tap.
[SPEAKER_19]: To play Bomberman.
[SPEAKER_05]: But no, now you can plug in four dance pads at once, and you can play a brand new mode called Quad Mode.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to be in Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_19]: For four, wow!
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to be four, no, it's four pads.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a whole new set of steps for one person on four pads.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's doubles-doubles.
[SPEAKER_19]: Evil.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you could have arrows that take you all the way from pad number one, way on the left, to pad number four.
[SPEAKER_05]: And a lot of people were talking about, well, what's the configuration going to be?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because if you think about Tetris, you could have four squares a lot of different ways.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to be one giant line.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'd have to say that I copyrighted this about two years ago.
[SPEAKER_09]: They will be hearing from my lawyers.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, because I was making edits for two machines to use all four panels.
[SPEAKER_09]: Two different sets of edits to play one song.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was my quad mode.
[SPEAKER_09]: God damn it, they stole it from me.
[SPEAKER_05]: I actually remember doing something like this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, I remember one time at Arcade Infinity starting two machines at the same time to do some kind of, like, quad thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I don't even... I don't remember what the joke was, but there was something we were trying to do.
[SPEAKER_05]: But yeah, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: What does it seem like is happening with this mix, though, with the song list?
[SPEAKER_05]: It looks like they're listing their fanbase a little more, so I wouldn't be surprised if they did look out there and see that maybe there are people, crazy as they might be, that want this quad mode in DDR.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, me personally, I'm kind of like, well, I think it's a nice idea, like the quad mode, I think it's kind of cute, but...
[SPEAKER_05]: Who's going to have four dance pads?
[SPEAKER_19]: It's innovative, I'll say that.
[SPEAKER_05]: But then, okay, here's the argument to that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Quad mode is only going to be available in something called the party mode on Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it's obviously set up for DDR parties.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, as cheesy as that might sound.
[SPEAKER_05]: Where your friends bring their dance pads over to your house.
[SPEAKER_19]: Or maybe it's going to be something cool like two people can play doubles.
[SPEAKER_05]: They have doubles versus, aren't they?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I think they said it was going to be a full four.
[SPEAKER_05]: Beginner, light, standard, and heavy.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'd have to re-look through, but I'm almost positive they said it was going to be a full new set.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: So...
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's going to be very interesting, huh?
[SPEAKER_19]: I want them to do another Best Hits on Xbox and bring out the individual mixes on one DVD.
[SPEAKER_19]: Guild Arcade mixes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I mean, but remember, U.S.
[SPEAKER_05]: isn't Japan, so unless they put it out for Japanese Xbox, which, you know, but they'll never do it because Xbox wasn't really popular over there.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's selling stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, but not quite.
[SPEAKER_19]: I still think that it would be neat so that I can, you know, not have to break out my Dreamcast every time I want to play Second Mix.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, they do have Second Mix on PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_19]: You can go to that bowling alley in Auburn.
[SPEAKER_05]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see, what else?
[SPEAKER_05]: multiple players on this is another interesting thing about Ultramix 2 now you can have multiple players on one Xbox going on Xbox Live to play so now you don't have to be you have to stay home it's kind of going more into the multiplayer and party functions where you can have multiple people over the song list will contain 70 songs not including the song packs which means that
[SPEAKER_05]: If you buy your song packs from Service Pack 1 through 6 for Ultramix 1, you can use these on Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, think about this.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's 30 songs between Service Packs 1 through 6, right?
[SPEAKER_19]: And who speculated this while somebody was out of town?
[SPEAKER_19]: I do believe I did.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_19]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: But that's going to be 100 songs playable in Ultramix from the start.
Crazy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Crazy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you, Konami.
[SPEAKER_19]: We love you.
[SPEAKER_05]: And there's going to be inside that 14 Konami original DDR songs.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we kind of saw some of those.
[SPEAKER_05]: Star Mine and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's going to be very interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very, very interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: But they are going to have this downloadable edits thing, which I'm kind of curious how that's going to work.
[SPEAKER_05]: If anybody can submit edits, or if they're going to have some kind of screening process where they only take good edits or what they're going to do.
[SPEAKER_05]: It'll be very interesting.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, and Panda, I do believe the Xbox is region coded.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is it?
[SPEAKER_19]: Yes, I do believe it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm kind of excited to see this mix now.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know it's been difficult in the past to get excited about anything Xbox, but boy, they're really doing DDR right on there, I say.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm looking forward to it.
[SPEAKER_05]: How about you, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_05]: What do you think about this Ultramix 2 so far?
[SPEAKER_05]: This is just so far.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm going to get it.
[SPEAKER_05]: We still haven't heard everything about it yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm going to get it.
[SPEAKER_19]: You know I'll have it, even if I play it or not.
[SPEAKER_19]: I have Ultramix 1.
[SPEAKER_19]: You know, my Ultramix 1 is unopened.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really?
[SPEAKER_05]: Really.
[SPEAKER_19]: It is because I never had time, because by the time I got around to playing it, I was doing other things.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, at least you bought it.
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, yeah, I have it.
[SPEAKER_19]: I have the dance pad and everything.
[SPEAKER_19]: But it'll give me a good excuse to break it out and start downloading the songpacks.
[SPEAKER_05]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: What about you guys here that don't have an Xbox yet, like DDR Angel and Arcadian?
[SPEAKER_05]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_05]: Is this kind of making you go, oh boy, I might have to get an Xbox, or what do you think?
[SPEAKER_10]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm afraid that...
[SPEAKER_17]: If I ever decided to get one, Magus would kill me.
[SPEAKER_17]: He just has this thing against Xbox, I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's DDR.
[SPEAKER_05]: He'll get over it.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, he should get over it because he's a Halo addict.
[SPEAKER_05]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you can play Halo on it, too.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay, you know what?
[SPEAKER_19]: I want to know how his opinion should affect you buying something you want.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ooh, slam.
[SPEAKER_17]: I guess he'd get over it.
[SPEAKER_17]: So maybe I will.
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_17]: Damn straight he'll get over it.
[SPEAKER_19]: If you want an Xbox, you should get an Xbox.
[SPEAKER_19]: So they just have to live.
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting comment from the chat room.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not sure if I'm reading too far into this, but truthfully, it's going to be only those that don't know about the Sims that will get the Xbox, says John Fields.
[SPEAKER_05]: The others will download the steps as they have for every mix.
[SPEAKER_05]: But again, I go back to what I said earlier.
[SPEAKER_05]: Stepmania is not DDR.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's not.
[SPEAKER_19]: And I don't think that Stepmania is going to have... Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_19]: It doesn't have Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_19]: It does not have Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, but they're...
[SPEAKER_05]: Dude, they're saying rumor is that they're going to have an internet thing, whatever.
[SPEAKER_18]: Eh.
[SPEAKER_05]: They have Step Mania online already.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do they have Step Mania online already?
[SPEAKER_09]: How come I've never seen you play it?
[SPEAKER_09]: Because I just don't care.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, but they already have Step Mania online.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, I don't know, I'm still... I couldn't get that stupid thing to work.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because they're still working on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just, I think the percentage... But Xbox Live is already up.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think the percentage...
[SPEAKER_19]: X-Lax Live
[SPEAKER_05]: I just think it's such a small percentage of people that would opt out of Ultramix 2 for Step Mania.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that's why Konami hasn't sued the pants off of Step Mania yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's because it's going to be such a small percentage of people that it's really negligent.
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember, the DDR community that you see online and in chat rooms and stuff is not the scope of the DDR community as a whole.
[SPEAKER_19]: And there's going to be people who go, Oh, look, it's another game for the Xbox that's going to get my couch potato kid off of his ass.
[SPEAKER_19]: I've talked to plenty of parents who go into GameStop and say, oh, well, this is going to keep my kid from being lazy.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, I'm actually going to open up the Skype line because I'm curious what some folks out there think about Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: I especially like to hear from people who are contemplating buying an Xbox over this whole thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we'll open up that Skype line.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you want to call us, we have some information on our website, but just go to Skype.org and download the client there.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a free client.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a free program.
[SPEAKER_05]: All you have to have, you have to have a broadband connection and a microphone and just add Orange Lounge Radio, all one word, to your contact list and you will be able to call us.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_05]: Who is this?
[SPEAKER_05]: and Unknown Gamer.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's okay?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Was there any songs that you're getting really excited about that you're going to be able to play?
[SPEAKER_07]: Moonlight fucking Shadow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Moonlight fucking Shadow is the word.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, unknown gamer, if you can, turn up your mic volume on your end a little bit so we can hear you a little better.
[SPEAKER_05]: But he says Moonlight fucking Shadow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why Moonlight Shadow?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because I'm fucking obsessed with erotics.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because he's obsessed with erotic.
[SPEAKER_19]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_05]: I see how it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_19]: Are you like stalker obsessed?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_19]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hot.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very hot.
[SPEAKER_19]: That hot.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you already have an Xbox?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I do not.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, you do not.
[SPEAKER_05]: Are you thinking about getting one?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, I am.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is obsession.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just because of Moonlight Shadow?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now that is an obsession.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is definitely an obsession.
[SPEAKER_19]: You could get one of the nifty green Halo ones.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what I bought.
[SPEAKER_19]: Be like us, have a green one.
[SPEAKER_05]: They don't make them in hot pink erotic flavor yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe soon.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay, I don't think that erotic flavor would be hot pink.
[SPEAKER_19]: I think it would be like blood red or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: It would be sex.
[SPEAKER_19]: It would be, yeah, it would be nookie colored.
[SPEAKER_19]: It would be like purple.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have to clarify something for folks in our chat room because people are going, wait a minute, Moonlight Shadow is an erotic song?
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, do you want to explain this one, Unknown Gamer, or do you want me to?
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you want me to explain it with the way my microphone sounds right now?
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, yeah, you're right.
[SPEAKER_05]: I better explain it.
[SPEAKER_05]: The reason why Moonlight Shadow is tied to Erotic is that actually the old lead singer from Erotic went and she joined this new band called Missing Heart.
[SPEAKER_05]: She kind of went off on her own and did this Missing Heart.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's why it gets tied back to Erotic a lot because it's the same vocalist that you hear in a lot of the old Erotic songs.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's why Moonlight Shadow kind of has ties to Erotic.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the only difference is that she's not going, Carried away by a moonlight shadow.
[SPEAKER_18]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_18]: Never do that again, please.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll try.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe I screwed that up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Lunarius is correcting me in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_05]: He says it was originally sung by the vocalist for Erotic and then redone by the Missing Hearts singer.
[SPEAKER_05]: So maybe I fucked that up.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to type to you the story of what happened and then you just tell people what happened.
[SPEAKER_09]: You have dessert.
[SPEAKER_09]: I need dessert.
[SPEAKER_09]: I want dessert.
[SPEAKER_09]: I already ate it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have some Diverse System 7 tracks I would like to play.
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, wait, we have to wait for those, because we're getting another call real fast.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I'm going to take this call.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_07]: He wants Diverse System 7 tracks.
[SPEAKER_05]: He does not want dessert.
[SPEAKER_05]: We cannot hear you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Please speak up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Aw, bummer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh, call us back when you get your mic thing rearranged.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's too bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, hold on.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm getting the story with Moonlight Shadow here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I thought I was.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, we'll get that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Go to the Diverse 7 stuff and then... Yes, you do.
[SPEAKER_05]: Play the Diverse 7 stuff and then we'll come back to the story of Moonlight Shadow.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll open up the Skype line again later, guys.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: Oops, got to take that off there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyways, the next one, real quick, is a Trip Machine Dark Core mix, and my god, I have to say, this is, for Trip Machine, what P8107 was for Paranoia.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, it's going to be fucking awesome, that's all I've got to say.
... ... ...
Thanks for watching!
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, and then one that's really cool, I don't really know what exactly this is.
[SPEAKER_09]: It says it's Reality Alpha 0.2 mix.
[SPEAKER_09]: It sounds like what it is is just a bunch of different songs kind of mixed in the one, which is still kind of cool, but it's pretty hardcore, so check it out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, so that was a few of those.
[SPEAKER_05]: So if they want to order this album of all these Bomani remixes, although we'll be playing them on Diversions Monday night, where can they go to order the CD?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, Diverse Systems, that's www.diverse.jp, I don't think they're up for sale yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think, usually they have their own English page, which, you know, they sell most of their CDs, but it's not on there yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: So...
[SPEAKER_09]: I remember before, they did wait a little bit before they were available for the U.S.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know, you know, whether they're getting, you know, taking care of the Japanese first or whatnot, but, um, there's, I don't know when exactly these are going to be up right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was checking, um, right now, you can purchase them.
[SPEAKER_09]: They have a few links on, um, the right-hand side where you can purchase them from, um, and I don't know why they're selling them there, uh, Dojinci sites, um, so you can get those there, but, um,
[SPEAKER_09]: Right now available from their site, they don't have them yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, I'm looking to see right now if it's on their ordering page.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, actually it is on their Japanese ordering page, but not on their English ordering page.
[SPEAKER_09]: You might be able to, I don't know, you might be able to send them an email or something if you can speak Japanese, but...
[SPEAKER_09]: Right now, yeah, and it's going to be three different CDs.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're all pressed CDs.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're going to be about $15 a piece.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's D7 5 keys, D7 7 keys, and D7 Other Mixture.
[SPEAKER_09]: So definitely look for those, and I will be getting those as soon as I can order them.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, I was going to open the Skype line back up because our caller wanted to call back because he had something he wanted to share with us.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we're going to open back up that Skype line there.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you can call us if you want.
[SPEAKER_05]: Skype.org to download the client.
[SPEAKER_05]: And pretty soon we're going to be going to break here and in the break we'll be hearing some songs that are going to be in Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some of those port overs from 2DX.
[SPEAKER_05]: So those of you guys that haven't heard the songs yet can have a chance to hear them.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because, you know, we want you to be able to hear the songs.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, let's take this call.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hello there, Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hello, everybody.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is Mr. VXJasonXV, is it not?
[SPEAKER_06]: You would be correct.
[SPEAKER_05]: How are you doing, sir?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm doing pretty good.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: What do you want to talk to us with about Ultramix 2?
[SPEAKER_06]: I basically wanted to add in something about how the songpacks are going to work.
[SPEAKER_06]: For all of you that have Ultramix already and have gotten the songpacks and didn't know this,
[SPEAKER_06]: Basically what's going to happen is if you have the songpacks purchased and downloaded, when you fire up Ultramix 2, it's just going to work.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're going to be on the list, you're going to play them, it's going to be beautiful.
[SPEAKER_06]: The only catch is the songpacks... What was that?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's plug and play.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is plug and play.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's going to happen though is that the videos are going to be different.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because, you know, obviously Ultramix is going to cycle video content.
[SPEAKER_06]: But Order of Chaos on DDR Freak said that there's going to be exclusive videos, brand new videos for those songs now on Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: Really?
[SPEAKER_06]: So basically the media is going to be already on the DVD, but the steps and actually showing up is going to be off your hard drive for downloading the content.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've heard rumors that there's going to be a lot of new videos in Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what they're pushing for.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know how much I can say, but I hear that there's a lot of new videos in Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you're wanting to see some new videos, Ultramix 2 is going to give you plenty.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: You will still be able to buy the first six song packs on Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: The only catch is if you do that, you can only use them for Ultramix 2 and not for the first one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: So if you're smart, you'll buy your packs on Ultramix 1 now.
[SPEAKER_06]: That is what I want to do, because there's no word yet if the songpacks are going to be removed from purchase for Ultramix 1.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm hoping not, so I can get them too, but, you know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you actually have Ultramix 1 right now?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I don't even have an Xbox.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is Ultramix 2 making you change your mind here?
[SPEAKER_06]: I've wanted to get one for a while, I've just never really had a good amount of incentive, but this is definitely making me want one even more now.
[SPEAKER_19]: So you're telling me that Jet Set Radio Future was not enough?
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: I never played the first one.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was in... Halo 2?
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, now that you can get Jet... If you get your Xbox, you should also get Jet Star Radio Future since it's cheap now.
[SPEAKER_19]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a good game.
[SPEAKER_19]: And the Buffy game.
[SPEAKER_19]: The Buffy game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, Buffy, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, Jason, when you... I wanna look into that.
[SPEAKER_05]: When you get your Xbox, we're gonna have a battle on Xbox Live, alright?
[SPEAKER_06]: Sounds awesome.
[SPEAKER_12]: You're gonna get served!
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I'm gonna serve you on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh no!
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm actually thinking about this.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to kind of put some feelers out in the chat room and kind of see what you guys think about this.
[SPEAKER_05]: What would you guys think about starting up some kind of Sunday night Ultramix League?
[SPEAKER_05]: Like right after the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: We all jump on Xbox Live and play.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll even jump on there and play.
[SPEAKER_06]: Orange Lounge DDR team?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it'll be like our Sunday night, you know, Ultramix night.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like post-show thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know how many people would be interested.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or if that's like way too dorky for you guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: If it brings people together and gets us some good playtime in, sounds good by me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I've actually been on Xbox Live after the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's at least one person in our chatroom that sometimes likes to get on there and play different songs after the show sometimes.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'm thinking, why not expand it and get a lot of people on there?
[SPEAKER_05]: It might be kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've heard the people that are getting on live that there's very few people that play on live anymore.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, anymore, but think about when the first game came out, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, it's almost a year old now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course there's not a lot of people still on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, hey, that's the thing, is that we want to start something up, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's start it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's get Ultramix.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's kind of like an I Love the 90s thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember when the old stuff was cool?
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember when Ultramix was cool?
[SPEAKER_05]: Kind of bringing it back.
[SPEAKER_05]: So let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Somebody should buy me an Xbox and all the songpacks and a live subscription for a few years, because I don't have money yet, and I have bills to pay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I'm sure that's the same boat a lot of folks are in.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe they'll drop the price of an Xbox again.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not likely, but you never know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hopefully.
[SPEAKER_06]: What are they right now?
$150?
[SPEAKER_05]: $175?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think $150, but you could get a refurbed one at one of those places for $120, $130.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'd say version 1s are a lot better anyways.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have the Super Halo ones, so I don't know.
[SPEAKER_18]: You know you can hack them if you have a memory stick.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yep, I have heard.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's plenty of those.
[SPEAKER_19]: And you have to use the first release of, like, Mecha Assault.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, a friend of ours can do it.
[SPEAKER_19]: So we're going to test that theory soon.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, did someone get married?
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, well thanks for calling, Jason.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have a good one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Call back anytime.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anytime, my friend, anytime.
Bye.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, we'll keep the Skype line open if anybody else has something they want to comment on with Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm serious about this Xbox Live thing after the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it would be fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Would you guys play?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm making pouty faces and blinking my eyelashes.
[SPEAKER_18]: On Sunday?
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, wait a minute, Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: With Ultramix 2, multiple people can play from one Xbox, so you and I can both play on the Ultramix.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wow, really?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, don't say... Don't care.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll play Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jerk.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, Angel.
[SPEAKER_17]: Screw it, I'm gonna twist Magus' arm and make him buy me an Xbox.
[SPEAKER_09]: But don't worry, those demons that come through my demonic vortex can play with you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wonderful.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now some folks in the chat room are saying we should do it before the show.
[SPEAKER_19]: After the show would be too late, because honestly, I'm driving home.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_19]: And I also work an earlier schedule now.
[SPEAKER_19]: I have to get up at 5.30 in the morning to go to work.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I'll have to think.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_19]: Because my ass is going to school.
[SPEAKER_05]: At the same time, for me personally, I have to get my Sunday stuff done before the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll butt heads on it.
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, how about a different night?
[SPEAKER_05]: That might work, too.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, we'll see what we can do.
[SPEAKER_05]: If there's an interest for doing something like that, we'll set something up.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, as soon as I tell Magus what songs are on the new Ultramix 2, he'll probably get one.
[SPEAKER_17]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're not even... We haven't even really... We've only heard, like, one new licensed song, Brick House, by Commodores.
[SPEAKER_05]: We haven't even heard about any of the other stuff, and there might be some really good stuff that's going to tell us next time.
[SPEAKER_17]: Shit, I would just play it for the Commodores song.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's an inside joke between Pixie Dust and I, so, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: What we're going to do now, actually, I think we'll go ahead and take a break, and we're going to play those songs from Ultramix 2 that are being ported over from 2DX.
[SPEAKER_05]: So in this break, you're going to hear Route 80s, Star Mine, and VJ Army.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we'll be back right after this.
[SPEAKER_05]: You are tuned in to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: After the break, we might get into the cage match, I think.
[SPEAKER_05]: We need to do that at some point.
[SPEAKER_05]: And so much more, as soon as we can think of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, we'll be back.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_00]: Why isn't the movie on?
[SPEAKER_00]: You have the time!
[SPEAKER_04]: Why isn't the movie on?
You have the time!
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_00]: What is a movie and you understand?
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_19]: Hey, did you hear about that show?
[SPEAKER_10]: What show?
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, they play a lot of great Fermanian video game music, but if you listen to it, you have to listen to it again within seven days.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I've heard of that station.
[SPEAKER_19]: Really?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I even listened to it a couple weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, what happens to you if you don't listen to it again?
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, you die.
[SPEAKER_05]: I, what?
[SPEAKER_12]: Hey, wait, what's this crazy bitch doing coming out of my computer screen?
[SPEAKER_12]: Ahhhh!
[SPEAKER_08]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: Listen or die!
[SPEAKER_05]: D.D.R.
[SPEAKER_05]: Extreme
[SPEAKER_05]: There's actually some brand new eye toy modes in DDR, and it's very interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have the Clean the Screen, of course, which is nothing new.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was in the E3 demo, you remember that?
[SPEAKER_05]: But then there's one called Coconut Panic, which, by the way, has nothing to do with DDR at all.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which I thought was very interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just all these coconuts falling in, you know.
[SPEAKER_05]: And we have to clean the screen.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm trying to look at some of these screenshots, which we linked from OrangeloungeRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_19]: Cleaning the screen was neat, but it'd be kind of annoying to play, I think.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what I think is cool, though, is that for working out purposes, the eye toy thing is cool.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, that's the only reason I would use it, is that... Hands and feet mode, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, and then they have that Feed the Animals game, which I haven't really seen a whole lot about, but it looks very interesting, that's for sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the one where you're gonna step on the different food, and you feed it to the animal that's on the screen.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's crazy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very crazy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can I find some more information about some of these modes?
[SPEAKER_05]: What else do we have?
[SPEAKER_05]: We have the Hyper Dash, which looks like the old school track and field, which I have no idea how that's going to work with the Eye Toy.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it might actually just be using the dance pad where you're just going to run in place like all, every single old school Nintendo Power Pad game was just like running in place as fast as you can.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that was your workout, remember?
[SPEAKER_05]: And then they have...
[SPEAKER_05]: Dance Aerobics was a little different.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was cool 8-bit sounds and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Then they have this one called Magical Ball.
[SPEAKER_05]: This new iToy game, Magical Ball, which, again, doesn't appear to have anything to do with DDR.
[SPEAKER_05]: It just is like Breakout, you know, the old school game Breakout or Arachnoid.
[SPEAKER_05]: But now it's Arachnoid, whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you use your hands as a paddle, which I think is very interesting.
[SPEAKER_12]: Magical Ball.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can show Konami your Magical Balls.
[SPEAKER_05]: V-Rare
[SPEAKER_05]: Everybody looks so enthused.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'll have to order it.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, then again, my man does manage a webcam.
[SPEAKER_19]: A webcam.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to say webcam.
[SPEAKER_05]: What kind of business is your man in?
[SPEAKER_19]: Look, I was typing webcam on the thing.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's GameStop.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: You sure?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_19]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_19]: Bite me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I guess if no one has anything else to say on the DDR Extreme, why don't we just go ahead and have ourselves a cage match?
[SPEAKER_05]: How's that sound?
[SPEAKER_19]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, we'll do it.
[SPEAKER_19]: I got to be lazy today.
[SPEAKER_05]: What do you mean you got to be lazy today?
[SPEAKER_19]: I didn't have to bring one.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right, because you won last week, didn't you?
[SPEAKER_16]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_16]: Finally.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, so just as a reminder, the way the cage match works,
[SPEAKER_05]: You have to be in our chat room at www.orangeloundtrader.com Click on chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to play three songs for you guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: A clip of last week's winner because, you know, you were listening last week so you've already heard it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we're only going to play a clip of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then we'll hear two new songs brought to the table from each host.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you will vote on your favorite.
[SPEAKER_05]: and the winner goes into rotation all week long on Orange Lounge Radio's, I'm sorry, Orange Lounge Radio's Bomani Music & More program, which plays on this station 24 hours a day, 7 days a week when we aren't live.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, so here we go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Last week's winner was Jamie and she brought to the table a song by Mflow, which you know from old school DDR games and 2DX.
[SPEAKER_05]: So this is their new album.
[SPEAKER_05]: From their new album, it's a song called Astro Sexy Chemistry.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's last week's winner.
[SPEAKER_05]: And so here's a clip of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you can decide if you want it to win again tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Song number one, M-Flow, Astro Sexy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Astro Sexy Chemistry
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
Thank you for watching!
All right, that was a clip of song number one in tonight's cage match.
M-Flow with Astro Sexy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, the next pick in tonight's cage match, the first challenger comes from our very own Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, what did you pick for tonight's cage match?
[SPEAKER_09]: I picked a song, but I don't know what it's from.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's... They said it was from Outphase.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't think it's from Outphase, but it's called Nuance.
[SPEAKER_05]: So this is one of those songs where somebody has decided they are going to say it's from Outphase even though they have no particular proof of this, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you liked it anyway, so you're putting it in a cage match.
[SPEAKER_07]: That and I just don't care.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fair enough, so here it is, an unknown group that we're going to call, not Outphase, Inphase, maybe somebody will recognize us and help us out, who knows, and the song is called Nuon, and this is Loki's pick in tonight's cage match, enjoy.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, that was song number two in tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_05]: A group that they are saying is out-phased, but we're kind of skeptical at this point.
[SPEAKER_05]: But Nuon is the song, and Loki liked it so much he put it in tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_05]: What did the rest of us think?
[SPEAKER_05]: Jamie?
[SPEAKER_19]: That doesn't sound like any out-phase to me.
[SPEAKER_19]: I did not detect the presence of Taku in that.
[SPEAKER_19]: And I would know!
[SPEAKER_19]: Because, see, some people have various types of radar.
[SPEAKER_19]: I have Takudar.
[SPEAKER_19]: And it didn't go off.
[SPEAKER_19]: It didn't even blink.
[SPEAKER_19]: So, it sounds pretty generic-y trance, honestly, to me.
[SPEAKER_19]: So it gets the 7 for being average.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, 7 for being average from Jamie.
[SPEAKER_05]: DDR Angel, what did you think of Nuance?
[SPEAKER_17]: I thought it was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_17]: I mean, pretty good for like background music if you need to do your homework or something.
[SPEAKER_17]: You know, if you're just playing around, photo editing or whatever.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'd probably say an 8.5.
[SPEAKER_05]: Arcadian 42.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I'll say it sounded way too generic for me.
[SPEAKER_10]: It wasn't too bad.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll give it a 7.5.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, Loki.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll give it an 8.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, and my thought is if that is out phase, it's very generic and very sad direction for them.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I remain highly skeptical as to that being out phase.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a little generic, but it's not bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've just heard Better Trance, so I give it a 7.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, but our opinions don't count, it's you in the chatroom that has the final say, and now you get my pick in tonight's page match, and I am being very adventurous tonight, because I haven't even completely heard the song I'm putting in, ever.
[SPEAKER_05]: I heard it at the club the other night, and then I downloaded it, and now I'm putting it in, and I have no idea if I even like this song as much as I thought I did,
[SPEAKER_05]: Hold me my sweet, hold me now, hold me God
and many more.
Thanks for watching!
Power of New Life Sweets
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, that was song number three in tonight's Cage Match.
[SPEAKER_05]: A song I've never heard before.
[SPEAKER_05]: Royal Gigolos with California Dreamin'.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jamie.
[SPEAKER_19]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_19]: That was really... And I understand you... Had you heard it through all the way, I'm sure you would have reconsidered your choice.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: The mix I heard was actually a little different.
[SPEAKER_05]: That one was more repetitive than our... I remember it being, like, trancier, actually.
[SPEAKER_19]: I was kind of getting into it at first, because I was like, hey, this is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_19]: And then it was like, eh.
[SPEAKER_19]: And then the bitches singing, because I don't think it was a sample of the Mamas and the Poppers.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think it was either.
[SPEAKER_05]: In the video, it wasn't.
[SPEAKER_19]: If you're going to be a professional singer, a requirement is that you hold a key.
[SPEAKER_19]: However, there's Politary...
[SPEAKER_19]: However, where I would normally have given that a 4, because of the name of the band, I said I'd give them a bonus point so they get a 5.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: DDR Angel.
[SPEAKER_19]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_19]: I've actually heard better keys held by band newbies.
[SPEAKER_19]: By band newbies.
[SPEAKER_19]: And if you've never been in a saxophone class with 6th graders who have never played a saxophone before, it sounds like cows being beaten to death.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, DDR Angel.
[SPEAKER_10]: Moo.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_17]: Um, gee, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_17]: Uh, the song was okay.
[SPEAKER_17]: I mean, it was kind of dancey, it was kind of cool, so.
[SPEAKER_17]: And maybe I'll be generous and give it an 8.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, a pity point from, uh, DDR Angel.
[SPEAKER_05]: Arcadian.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, it was alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, nothing special.
[SPEAKER_10]: Uh, 6.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, Loki.
[SPEAKER_09]: If I'm going to follow the same guidelines that, you know, DarkSakura gives the song, I'm going to have to give it a 1.
[SPEAKER_05]: To quote Muffin Juice, it sounds more like an elephant getting a pineapple shoved up its ass.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, you guys are mean.
[SPEAKER_05]: That would be...
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: The chat room may have felt a little differently than the rest of you, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: I have no way to imitate that.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it is up to them to choose between these three songs.
[SPEAKER_05]: Song number one, M-Flow, Astro Sexy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Song number two, Not Out Phase with Nuon.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a horrible clip.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's try again.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, and song number three, Royal Gigolo's California Dreamin'.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, place vote now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Send a private message to Sky in the chatroom with your vote.
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember, you must send it over private message.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you yell it out in the main chatroom, you will not only not have your vote counted, but you will be mocked openly for not listening to the directions.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bye, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright, so... What else am I here for but public mockery?
[SPEAKER_05]: If caning were to be brought back, somehow I imagine you would be involved.
[SPEAKER_05]: You would be the administrator.
[SPEAKER_19]: Dude, that'd be cool.
[SPEAKER_19]: You know what I still think my opinion is to solve all the world's problems?
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_19]: Two methods.
[SPEAKER_19]: Standardized test and battle royale.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_19]: I seriously think they should take all the inmates, put them on nylons,
[SPEAKER_05]: They made a movie out of that with Ray Liotta.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was called No Escape.
[SPEAKER_19]: But they need to, when they have one left, and he thinks he's a winner and going back to become a productive member of society, then they sink his boat.
[SPEAKER_05]: You guys are horrible.
[SPEAKER_19]: New reality TV.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to take a break pretty soon here while we tally up those cage match votes, and when we
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: And this is where we determine on this show the definitive top three of something.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, because top shows are very popular.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like we have the top ten games and top ten... So we here on Orange Lounge Radio are going to come up with our very own top three.
[SPEAKER_05]: And tonight's topic...
[SPEAKER_05]: is I toy game I would most like to see on DDR.
[SPEAKER_05]: So some of you guys may have a suggestion out there in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you might want to type those out because you never know.
[SPEAKER_05]: One of the hosts or the guests might pick that up and use it as their suggestion.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we shall see.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Xbox is going to have a brand new Sonic Mega Collection coming out for it.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's going to be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: 20 different games, one Xbox, including Sonic.
[SPEAKER_05]: It has a nice game in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sonic Knuckles, Sonic 3D Blast, Sonic and Knuckles, when you put them together, is going to be on there, and a bunch of Game Gear titles.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then these other titles that seemingly have nothing to do with Sonic, The Ooze, Comic Zone, Flicky, and Ristar.
[SPEAKER_05]: You will notice, however, that Sonic CD is not on it.
[SPEAKER_19]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_19]: We need Sonic CD.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe it's an unlock, you never know.
[SPEAKER_19]: We need the Japanese version of Sonic CD that has better music.
[SPEAKER_05]: You never know.
[SPEAKER_19]: We need Nights.
[SPEAKER_19]: We need a new Nights game.
[SPEAKER_05]: We will see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Real quick.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rumor is that we'll get our first glimpse of Metal Gear Solid 3 Snake Eater this October.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to be launched in Japan this October is the current rumor.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll confirm that for you as soon as we find out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Coming out on the Game Boy Advance, you know those Nintendo games that you're paying 20 bucks for to play the same damn game you played 15 years ago?
[SPEAKER_05]: There's even more coming out this time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dr. Mario, Metroid, which seems completely pointless to me because if you want to play the old Metroid, fucking buy Metroid Zero.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because not only will you get the old Metroid, but you'll get a fucking awesome Metroid game with it based off the old Metroid.
[SPEAKER_19]: And wasn't there a way you could bring out the Guardian Legend?
[SPEAKER_09]: Wasn't there a way you could supposedly link your Game Boy Advance with, what was it, Metroid Prime?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, Prime and Fusion could link together and you could also unlock the original Metroid that way.
[SPEAKER_05]: So this will be the third time we've had the original Metroid available.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: In the past few years, yes.
[SPEAKER_19]: Guardian Legend.
[SPEAKER_19]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Guardian Legend.
[SPEAKER_19]: I tried to get people to vote for it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I told them Guardian Legend.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, there are two more that we're going to get.
[SPEAKER_05]: Castlevania!
[SPEAKER_05]: is coming out.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a must-have.
[SPEAKER_19]: Of course, if you have a PlayStation, you could also just get Castlevania Chronicles.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or you could just fucking get Symphony of the Night and get a really good Castlevania game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've been playing a lot of Aria of Sorrow recently.
[SPEAKER_19]: Castlevania III was the best of the Nintendo ones, the Japanese one.
[SPEAKER_05]: I haven't been playing a whole lot of new Castlevania games on Game Boy Advance, but I've been playing this Aria of Sorrow a lot.
[SPEAKER_05]: I actually really like it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, Zelda 2, The Adventure of Link.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think we all knew that was a given.
[SPEAKER_05]: That would make Dan happy.
[SPEAKER_05]: At some point.
[SPEAKER_19]: I could not get into Zelda 2.
[SPEAKER_19]: But he loves that game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also another video game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, Loki.
Hmm.
[SPEAKER_09]: Which is also tied in with the Final Fantasy 7 thing, so whatever that is.
[SPEAKER_09]: But it was rumored that they were going to be making a spin-off with Vincent being the lead.
[SPEAKER_19]: Now that would just make me so happy.
[SPEAKER_19]: Because Vincent was my favorite character in Final Fantasy 7.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, so... Like, my last party was Yuffie, Vincent, and of course Cloud, because you couldn't go without him.
[SPEAKER_19]: If I could have ditched Cloud, I would have so fast.
[SPEAKER_09]: www.adventchildren.net
[SPEAKER_09]: That is Sid.
[SPEAKER_09]: Whatever, okay?
[SPEAKER_09]: I was looking at Vincent.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's Sid.
[SPEAKER_09]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_09]: Kiss my ass.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here's another kick-ass one of Sid here hitting God knows what.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know what you could do.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why don't you post this link in our chat room so the chatters can play along and see some of these pictures because they are very nice pictures, I gotta say.
[SPEAKER_18]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Any other pictures you want to show us in the studio, though?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, there's a really kick-ass one of Vincent!
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_19]: Now that is my man.
[SPEAKER_09]: See, that's pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_09]: Then we've got, of course, Return of Red XIII.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what's funny is that the whole time I ever played Final Fantasy VII, I never got Vincent.
[SPEAKER_05]: UVS, Vincent, no.
[SPEAKER_05]: Go figure.
[SPEAKER_05]: Last call for cage match votes in our chat room, FYI.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also in other video gaming news recently, Metroid Prime will be having a GameCube bundle coming out, of course with the release of Metroid Prime 2 on the way.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you're thinking about getting a GameCube, now's a good time because Metroid Prime...
[SPEAKER_05]: will be released with the GameCube, and they'll also have a sneak peek at Metroid Prime 2 Echoes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, there's going to be some new games coming out for the Nintendo DS, which sounds kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Lots of games being announced.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to see what Konami's got planned.
[SPEAKER_05]: Konami is going to be coming out with a Castlevania game, as well as a game called Boktai?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know that one.
[SPEAKER_05]: SONIC DS
[SPEAKER_05]: There's going to be a Mega Man Battle Network game from Capcom.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course, the mandatory Bust a Move title.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know you must hate that name, but that is what they call it here in the U.S., or Puzzle Bobble, if you must.
[SPEAKER_05]: And for you, DDR Angel, Monster Rancher.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I'm sorry, not Monster Rancher.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I'm sorry, not that one.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was thinking Harvest Moon.
[SPEAKER_17]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what I was thinking of, Harvest Moon.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're a Monster Rancher.
[SPEAKER_17]: Anyway, do you want to know what book that really is?
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_17]: It's like a... I want to say it's like a vampire type thing, but like, I don't know, something more cartoony.
[SPEAKER_17]: But it's got some sun sensor thing or whatever on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, they have that game here.
[SPEAKER_05]: I forget the name of it here, but they do have it here.
[SPEAKER_17]: I thought that was Boktai.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, with the sunlight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe it was called that.
[SPEAKER_17]: Sorry, sorry, I'll move.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: I almost bought that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I almost bought that, but I bought Sword of Mana instead, and I wish I'd bought the other game, because I don't like Sword of Mana.
[SPEAKER_05]: So... Oh, well.
[SPEAKER_05]: You live, you learn.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's it for other gaming news tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we're going to wrap up the cage match voting.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you guys want to know who won tonight's cage match?
[SPEAKER_13]: Sure, Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: By one stinking vote, one vote, we have a new champion.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nuon is tonight's winner by one vote over Astro Sexy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who says every vote doesn't count, boys and girls?
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought Astro Sexy was guaranteed to win again.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, because the other... You know, if the one person that voted for California Dreamin' would have voted for the other song, it could have been different, but... The one person?
[SPEAKER_05]: The one person that voted for California Dreamin'.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, well.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, I'm not going to say every vote is cast in secret, but if you want to... If you want to out yourself on air, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'll just pick another Inflow song next week.
[SPEAKER_05]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_19]: Or better watch it.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'll pick Toxic.
[SPEAKER_05]: I almost put Toxic in tonight.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'll make you guys listen to Britney.
[SPEAKER_05]: You guys are getting Danny Minow again next week.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's all I have to say.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm not going to torture you guys that badly.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'll pick some inflow.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think we're going to go to a break.
[SPEAKER_05]: What should we hear in this break?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Somebody give me an idea for a theme for this break.
[SPEAKER_19]: Taku.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some Taku?
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some Tako?
[SPEAKER_19]: No.
[SPEAKER_19]: Play Thrashtrax.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is that Taku?
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_19]: Was it really?
[SPEAKER_19]: Thrashtrax and Tetraku.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, fine.
[SPEAKER_19]: I want old Taku stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, we'll hear some of that, and then we'll be back, and we're going to do tonight's episode of Listless.
[SPEAKER_05]: And remember, we're still looking for your ideas from the chat room.
[SPEAKER_05]: I toy game I'd most like to see in DDR.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll be back.
and more.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_15]: Easier to dance to than that freaking catch-up song.
[SPEAKER_15]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: We are back, and as promised, we're going to get into tonight's edition of Listless.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think we need a theme song for Listless.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's a good Bomani song that's like a theme song for Listless?
[SPEAKER_19]: Um, Holic.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can't do Holic again.
[SPEAKER_19]: Um, I know the one that was the poppin' music video.
[SPEAKER_19]: It sounds very game show-y.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, Linus.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh, shit, do I have Linus?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't have that song readily available to me, um, oh!
[SPEAKER_05]: But I thought, ooh, let's see if I can find, oh, damn, all my poppin' music special stuff is gone.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I know a good one, I know a good, because you said poppin' music, that made me think of a poppin' music song that would be really good, if I can find it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ah, crap, oh, here it is, here it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, it's that, it's that, um, that toy-sounding song from Nine.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's time to play Listless!
[SPEAKER_12]: You can't fire a rod, you're not on the cast.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're not on staff, you can't fire a rod.
[SPEAKER_12]: In tonight's edition of Listless, we will be determining the eye toy game we most want to see in a DDR game.
[SPEAKER_05]: The way that Listless works is that each host and each guest will make their list of three games that they want to see in an eye toy DDR.
[SPEAKER_05]: After that, we will have the elimination round, where each person will take one thing off of the list.
[SPEAKER_05]: After that, the chatroom will be able to vote!
[SPEAKER_05]: So if you're not in the chatroom, join it now!
[SPEAKER_05]: www.orangeloungeradio.com Click on chat.
[SPEAKER_12]: And now, let's play Listless!
[SPEAKER_19]: Rob, you've scared me.
[SPEAKER_19]: Beyond all capacity to be scared!
[SPEAKER_19]: Except there's no slugs involved.
[SPEAKER_19]: If there were slugs involved, I'd be even more scared.
[SPEAKER_05]: In all seriousness, let's get to tonight's list.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Eye toy game I most want to see in DDR.
[SPEAKER_05]: Starting off tonight, who always starts us off?
[SPEAKER_05]: The lovely DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_19]: Damn straight I'm lovely.
[SPEAKER_05]: She's a trendsetter.
[SPEAKER_19]: I sure am.
[SPEAKER_05]: Number three eye toy game you most want to see in DDR.
[SPEAKER_05]: Car wash the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Explain how this works.
[SPEAKER_19]: You'd have your buckets on the ground and one would be your...
[SPEAKER_19]: Your, uh, you know, sponge, and you'd wash the car, and then you'd have the hose, and you'd spray down the car.
[SPEAKER_05]: And this, would this actually relate to DDR at all?
[SPEAKER_19]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: How about you'll play Eurobeat while you do it?
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, there you go.
[SPEAKER_19]: I know, I know, better yet, how about Bikini Car Wash the game?
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_19]: Then, like, your icon, you just, like, you know, and so, like, the better you do, the hotter you are, and the more tips you get.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, Bikini Car Wash the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, fine.
[SPEAKER_19]: That works.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll change it there, alright.
[SPEAKER_19]: And if it's a guy, then it's Speedo Car Wash.
[SPEAKER_05]: See, I was thinking the movie Car Wash.
[SPEAKER_19]: At the car wash, yeah!
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, that could be playing in the background.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, Angel.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, then let's go to Arcadian42, since Angel's working here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Arcadian42, number three eye toy game you would most like to see in DDR.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just made a comment about that Car Wash.
[SPEAKER_10]: As long as no one's carrying around a bucket of piss.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay!
[SPEAKER_10]: 3.
[SPEAKER_10]: Lice Invaders
[SPEAKER_10]: Watch out, they're coming down from the sky to attack your head.
[SPEAKER_05]: Lice, Lice Invaders.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, Lice Invaders.
[SPEAKER_05]: And to relate this to DDR, Lice Invaders would also play Eurobeat in the background, correct?
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, alright, fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, Lice Invaders.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, DDR Angel.
[SPEAKER_05]: Number three eye toy game you would most like to see in DDR?
[SPEAKER_17]: I couldn't really come up with anything for number three, so I just said Mini Papa Music or Mini 2DX.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like a mini, like a chibi 2DX.
[SPEAKER_05]: How about I say that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Chibi 2DX.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, because I couldn't come up with anything else original.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, that's fine, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: A little chibi game.
[SPEAKER_05]: That'll be cute.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, Loki, your number three pick for a high toy game I would most like to see in DDR.
[SPEAKER_05]: My game is so awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's called Break Shit.
[SPEAKER_08]: Basically, um... You are so bad in the face.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Damn this yogurt!
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyways, um, no, basically... Is your yogurt that hot?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: It makes me giggle.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyways, um, no, basically what you do is an object would come on the screen.
[SPEAKER_08]: And you're breaking!
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, Loki's suggesting break shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the iToy game he would most like to see in DDR.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, and again, to relate this to DDR, Eurobeat Music would be playing in the background.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, she breaks shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, Daikin Kai.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, my number three game I would most like to see, iToy game I would most like to see in DDR, Whack-A-Child.
[SPEAKER_19]: That sounds brilliant.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whack a child.
[SPEAKER_05]: Basically, as you play DDR, little children come on the screen and you have to whack them away.
[SPEAKER_19]: So that would be my... Do you have the big orange bat icon?
[SPEAKER_05]: You could.
[SPEAKER_05]: That would be like the bonus stage.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Number two pick now from Jamie.
[SPEAKER_19]: It would be something like the candy bar doll maker.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't know if you've seen all the dolls I've been posting in my live journal.
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, well, I've been having this thing with the candy bar doll maker and this is...
[SPEAKER_19]: It's like an interactive thing where you make the outfits and choose the hair and everything.
[SPEAKER_19]: But you could use it to... If you want to see what the original candy bar was, it's candybar.co.kr.
[SPEAKER_19]: But there's also an English one if you look it up on Google.
[SPEAKER_19]: But anyway, you use the doll maker and you make your character for DDR.
[SPEAKER_19]: And then you play as that character.
[SPEAKER_19]: So you can drag the hair over and make him a boy or make him a girl.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the gayest game I've ever heard of, but all right, fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Candy bar doll game is what... And Eurobeat would play in the background while you do it.
[SPEAKER_19]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_19]: It would be like the Oha music.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, the Oha music.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Arcadian42, your number two pick.
[SPEAKER_10]: Originally, I came up with the idea of head explode mode.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or head explode mode, if you want to.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I thought it'd maybe make it cooler, be the Evade the Assassin's Bullet game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Where you see the red dot on your head, you have to avoid it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Evade the Assassin's Bullet game, so a little red laser would appear on your head.
[SPEAKER_10]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_10]: And if you don't move out of the way, then boom, your head explodes.
[SPEAKER_10]: And if it actually explodes, that would make it a little bit more dangerous, and maybe a bit more fun.
[SPEAKER_19]: It would work for Kami in Silent Scope mode.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yes, there you go, Silent Scope mode.
[SPEAKER_19]: There you go, Silent Scope mode.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, brilliant.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to put that in parentheses, Silent Scope.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Angel, your number two pick.
[SPEAKER_17]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_17]: Um, hell.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, how about Mini Flashwater?
[SPEAKER_17]: Do you remember that game from Mario Paint?
[SPEAKER_17]: The thing where you just take the mouse and then like swaddle the flies and crap?
[SPEAKER_05]: Mini fly, so the fly swatting game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, Nat Attack, that's what it was called, Nat Attack.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, I don't know, I just thought maybe that'd be kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm not funny tonight, oh well.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's alright, we're going to need some serious ones in here anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, Loki, your number two pick for eye toy game that you would like to see in DDR.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm looking at your list tonight because I can see your list over...
[SPEAKER_05]: on your computer, and I can't help it, because it's funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: Answer the damn question.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're number two pick.
[SPEAKER_12]: I can't.
[SPEAKER_12]: He's laughing to her.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: Say it.
[SPEAKER_12]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's all your damn fault.
[SPEAKER_08]: See, he starts giggling, and then I can't.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay, here's some serious thoughts.
[SPEAKER_19]: Things that you like.
[SPEAKER_19]: You know.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_19]: Shooting RBGL children in the head.
[SPEAKER_19]: Shh.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, my next one is awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's basically, I'm itchy.
[SPEAKER_09]: That sounds like a personal problem.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think it's pretty self-explanatory.
[SPEAKER_09]: You see this spot on your body, it gets red, itch it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you have jock itch?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm Itchy is Loki's number two pick.
[SPEAKER_05]: My number two pick, if Whack-A-Child wasn't quite good enough for you, then we have Whack-A-Parent would be the iToy game I would like to see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whack-A-Parent, because we all know that it's not really the kids' fault, it's their parents.
[SPEAKER_05]: So Whack-A-Parent is my number two pick.
[SPEAKER_19]: I would so own it at.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, Jamie, you're number two.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry, you're number one.
[SPEAKER_19]: My last one, the thing is, I don't, it would require that you be able to play with two eye toys, honestly.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, that's fine, you're innovative.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_19]: It would be called, fuck with the other player's arrows mode.
[SPEAKER_19]: Where you would basically reach over on their side.
[SPEAKER_05]: You would actually reach over and rearrange their arrows.
[SPEAKER_19]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, I like that idea.
[SPEAKER_19]: Seriously, think about how crazy that would be.
[SPEAKER_19]: That would, like, do a whole new spin on Dance Battle.
[SPEAKER_05]: Could you just, like, knock all your own arrows off the screen?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, you could do that.
[SPEAKER_17]: You could shove your arrows over to their side.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_17]: Actually, that reminds me of...
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't know if anybody played You Don't Know Jack, but Volume 4 has this mode where it's nail mode where you just pound the N key and all these nails go on the question so you can't read it and the person has to guess.
[SPEAKER_17]: They're like forced to guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, let's get the mic on over to Arcadium42 for his number one pick for iToy game I would most like to see in DDR.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: My number one pick will be Dandruff White Christmas.
[SPEAKER_10]: There would be little people on the bottom of the screen, and they're so wishing for a white Christmas.
[SPEAKER_10]: and you are the number one producer of Dandruff and you are going to give them a nice white Christmas by shaking your head in various directions to make sure they have a beautiful, beautiful Christmas.
[SPEAKER_05]: A lot of DDR players I know wouldn't need an eye toy actually for this.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dandruff white Christmas mode.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: DDR Angel, your number one pick.
[SPEAKER_17]: Actually, I'm going to be completely kidding and go with the mini butt game.
[SPEAKER_17]: Darn it.
[SPEAKER_17]: Laugh.
[SPEAKER_05]: The mini butt game?
[SPEAKER_05]: How does that work?
[SPEAKER_17]: The WarioWare thing, remember?
[SPEAKER_05]: You have to explain for those that don't know, though, our listeners.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, well, okay, well, I wasn't, I was actually kidding about this answer, but I guess I'll keep it.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, you didn't keep it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, I'll explain for those.
[SPEAKER_05]: In WarioWare, there's this game where it says shoot, and you have to shoot water on this flower to make it spin, but the flower looks like an asshole.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it looks like this moving bidet that you're using to shoot water up somebody's asshole.
[SPEAKER_17]: Do you want to know my real answer?
[SPEAKER_05]: So Angel wants to turn this into an eye toy game.
[SPEAKER_05]: What was your real answer?
[SPEAKER_17]: My real answer was going to be Mini Burger Time, but I don't know if that was going to work.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know, I like the mini butt game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to actually change that to Mini Water in Your Asshole.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, so this is a mini water in your asshole.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh my god, how old are we, people?
Oh shit!
[SPEAKER_19]: Roth is all red in the face now, this has got to be good.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh god, I love this.
[SPEAKER_19]: Here, take the mic.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright, I'll do it, I'll do it.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, make, no, make, make him do it.
[SPEAKER_19]: Make him do it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Make him say it.
[SPEAKER_19]: Come here.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_19]: Deep breaths.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, Loki.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, the next one.
[SPEAKER_09]: And my final one, number one.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have plenty more where this came from, too.
[SPEAKER_09]: This just happened to me.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: It comes to my head right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I pulled it out of my ass.
[SPEAKER_09]: This next one is basically like a quiz show game.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's kind of like You Don't Know Jack, where you get like three questions.
[SPEAKER_09]: And the problem will be that they're very hard.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, if you get the question wrong...
[SPEAKER_09]: You catch fire.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's called answer question or catch fire.
[SPEAKER_09]: And you can't flare around too much because otherwise fire burns faster when you're moving.
[SPEAKER_12]: Answer question or catch fire is Loki's choice.
[SPEAKER_12]: And don't flail around too much because the fire just grows that way.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now Loki's saying Burn Victim, the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nope, too late.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Answer Question or Catch Fire.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, and again, to relate this to DDR, Eurobeat Music would play in the background.
[SPEAKER_05]: I should play.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: My number one pick for iToy game I would like to see in DDR, you've seen Whack-A-Child, you've seen Whack-A-Parent, but the best one by far is Whack-A-Politary is my number one choice.
[SPEAKER_19]: Whack-A-Politary.
[SPEAKER_19]: Wacka Politary.
[SPEAKER_19]: Can't you just do that in, like, Tribuners Club?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, yeah, but that's a little different.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, Politary would come out on the screen.
[SPEAKER_05]: She would actually sing Broken My Heart, and you can punch her in the stomach to get her to stop.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, so that's my number one answer, Wackapolitary.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, now unfortunately comes the part where we have to eliminate one off the list apiece.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, right now, here is the list as it stands.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you want to read this, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_05]: Can you read it from back there?
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_19]: Bikini Car Wash the Game, Life Invaders, Chibi 2D Extra Poppin' Music, Break Shit, Wacka Child, Candy Bar Doll Game,
[SPEAKER_19]: Evade the Assassin's Bullet Silent Scope, Mini Flyswatter Nat Attack, I'm Itchy, Whack a Parent, Fuck with the Other Player's Arrows, Dandruff White Christmas, Mini Water in Your Ass all day.
[SPEAKER_19]: Stop that, you're just trying to make me bust up, okay?
[SPEAKER_19]: Answer Question or Catch Fire, or Whack-A-Politary.
[SPEAKER_19]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_19]: I should have read it like in that Margaret Cho, since we're talking about Margaret Cho in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_19]: I should have done, God, I've been clitoris.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is hard.
[SPEAKER_05]: Honestly, these are all really good.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've got my pick.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is a very difficult elimination round for us because there's a lot of these that are fucking funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, Angel?
[SPEAKER_17]: One comment about the whole thing is, oh, my God, it's iToyMeetsWarriorWare.
[SPEAKER_05]: iToyMeetsWarriorWare.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jamie, you've got to take one off the list.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which number is coming off?
[SPEAKER_19]: Uh, Dandruff White Christmas goes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, Dandruff White Christmas, number 12.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dandruff is nasty.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, that's too bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fired!
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh, Arcadian, your turn.
[SPEAKER_05]: You gotta take one off the list.
[SPEAKER_05]: I see I have too many whack things to say.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whack a parent.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's more fun to whack kids.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, because it's more fun to whack kids than whack parents, whack a parent is coming off the list.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Angel, one of these has to come off the list.
[SPEAKER_17]: Um, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_17]: Candy Bar Doll Game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Candy Bar Doll Game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, that was a little gay, Jamie, even you have to admit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, which one of these is coming off the list?
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, as much as I don't like her, Wackapolitary, because Wacka Child is the best.
[SPEAKER_18]: Wacka Child is pretty.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, Wackapolitary comes off the list, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Me, I have to take one off the list, and I've got to say, I'm just not feeling it for Chibi 2DX.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, Angel.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, why have a Bimani-related game in VR?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, why have a Bimani-related game in VR?
[SPEAKER_19]: Because I couldn't think of anything!
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's fine, it's fine.
[SPEAKER_19]: You could just use the Loki method and just pull it out of your ass.
[SPEAKER_19]: Ow.
[SPEAKER_12]: What did you say?
[SPEAKER_12]: What were you going to do?
[SPEAKER_12]: What?
[SPEAKER_19]: We are not putting that on the air.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, damn.
[SPEAKER_19]: See, that's why you people need to be in the studio to hear all of the really socially incorrect, politically incorrect statements that Loki makes when you can't hear him.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, here we go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Eye toy game I most want to see in DDR.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here is the list that you can vote for now in the chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Send one vote, your favorite, over to Sky via private message.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Number one, Bikini Car Wash the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Number two, Lice Invaders.
[SPEAKER_05]: Number four, Break Shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: 5.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whack A Child 7.
[SPEAKER_05]: Evade The Assassin's Bullet 8.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mini Flyswatter 9.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm Itchy 11.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fuck With The Other Player's Arrows 13.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mini Water In Your Asshole Game 14.
[SPEAKER_05]: Answer Question Or Catch Fire
[SPEAKER_05]: Place vote now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Send a private message to Sky in the chat room with your choice for what you would like to see win tonight's listless segment.
[SPEAKER_05]: And we'll put that all together and we'll put that out on the air as soon as we have everybody's vote.
[SPEAKER_05]: You got some other ones.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm a crappy raver mode.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, crappy raver mode would be fun.
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, you know what my original number one was?
[SPEAKER_19]: Interactive gal panic.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dangle baby over balcony mode.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm actually going to open up the Skype line right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: If anybody would like to send... Even though your suggestion is a little late to make the list, maybe there's something you want to vote for.
[SPEAKER_05]: You want to persuade other people to vote on the list.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or maybe you have a suggestion that was just really good and we missed it and that's just too damn bad because, you know, you don't make the list.
[SPEAKER_05]: So the Skype line is open right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see if anybody gives us a call.
[SPEAKER_05]: Otherwise, I guess we're just going to have to go to a break, aren't we?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's my ever...
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey Sky, this is John Fields, can you hear me?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi!
[SPEAKER_16]: Hey, I posted this a couple of times in the chat, but I guess you didn't see it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, we were too busy laughing at answer question or catch fire.
[SPEAKER_16]: They were all red in the face.
[SPEAKER_16]: It was cute.
[SPEAKER_16]: Actually, I was thinking you could combine the DDR pad with the eye toy to create something sort of like a samurai game.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's saying... We're having a hard time hearing you.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to say that he's saying something about you could combine the DDR...
[SPEAKER_05]: with the eye toy to make like a samurai game where you could run at each other type thing.
[SPEAKER_16]: Right, and then a punch to attack, basically.
[SPEAKER_16]: Kind of like mo-cap.
[SPEAKER_05]: See, now that's a good serious answer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Unfortunately, it's not funny, but it's actually a good answer as far as serious ones are concerned.
[SPEAKER_19]: I always thought they should have used the eye toy to make like a mo-cap boxing at home.
[SPEAKER_05]: Any other suggestions you got for us, John?
[SPEAKER_16]: That was it, basically.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, well that's actually a decent one, so you might want to send that on over to Konami.
[SPEAKER_05]: You never know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, thanks for calling.
[SPEAKER_05]: No problem.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see if I can answer this call real fast, it's coming in.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hello, Sky, Siggy here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, Siggy, how you doing?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, hey, I'm doing fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's your suggestion?
[SPEAKER_11]: I never had that kind of laugh since episode 69.
[SPEAKER_05]: He has not laughed that hard since episode 69 when Loki sang I'm Coming Out.
[SPEAKER_11]: I wasn't here.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know, you weren't even here, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, well, which one made you laugh the most?
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, of course, the one that says number 13.
[SPEAKER_11]: I really can, you know, the chatters right now.
[SPEAKER_11]: Go for number 13.
[SPEAKER_05]: Number 13, the mini water in your asshole game is the one that made him laugh the most.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was laughing really hard.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, my stomach, you know, my stomach's really hurting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I'm glad we could cause you such pain here on Orange Log Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Take a deep breath.
[SPEAKER_19]: Are you okay?
[SPEAKER_19]: Breathe in.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you have any suggestions you wanted to pass along?
[SPEAKER_05]: We can barely hear you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Speak into your mic a little more.
[SPEAKER_11]: Just, uh, that's it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Just an episode.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, I mean, uh, episode.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, uh, vote for number 13.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, he's just saying vote for number 13, Mini Water in Your Asshole Game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, we'll see, Siggy.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for calling!
[SPEAKER_05]: Later!
[SPEAKER_05]: Have a good one!
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, so we'll be back after this break of Taka music while you guys vote on tonight's list list.
[SPEAKER_05]: Enjoy!
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: My bad, I got a location test one in there, so let's do a better quality Takasong.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's do this one.
Thank you for watching!
Thank you.
Thanks for watching!
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_20]: From the Step Squad to Orange Lab, this PDR sucks!
[SPEAKER_04]: Holla, Holla, Holla, Holla, Holla, Holla, Holla, Holla, Holla, Holla, Holla, Holla, Holla, Holla, Holla,
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, you had to go worship the porcelain goddess.
[SPEAKER_19]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just teasing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we've got to get this in.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hopefully we have a little bit of time for Ask Orange Lounge, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: We definitely have to get this segment in.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why is it, Jamie, that we have to do these FUs every single week?
[SPEAKER_19]: Sometimes you've just got to let it out.
[SPEAKER_19]: My first FU goes to the almost entirety of traffic on the road today.
[SPEAKER_19]: Which is why I stand by my desire to have a Humvee with a freaking missile launcher on it.
[SPEAKER_19]: I finally saw it in action.
[SPEAKER_19]: I found a movie file on Military.com of a Humvee with a missile launcher blowing up a tank.
[SPEAKER_19]: And that was so hot to me.
[SPEAKER_19]: So, I decided that I really, really have to have one now.
[SPEAKER_19]: So, uh... So, I need one for traffic.
[SPEAKER_19]: Another FU goes toward, uh... I'm getting a little panicky about school, so I guess this sort of goes to me for being kind of panicky about it.
[SPEAKER_19]: Another FU goes toward not having time and money and the ability to go visit who I want to.
[SPEAKER_19]: Although...
[SPEAKER_19]: I am planning on going to Alabama in November, so I'll come back, accent and all, and you'll have to make fun of me, and I'll go, I'll fuck y'all.
[SPEAKER_19]: Another one goes toward, I'm going to be very general with this and say people who just don't get it.
[SPEAKER_19]: You know, you tell them, and you point it out, and they just don't get it, you know?
[SPEAKER_19]: Those people just, uh-uh-uh, no.
[SPEAKER_19]: Um...
[SPEAKER_19]: Another FU goes toward that stupid introduction to Windows class that I have to take.
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, you know what I say?
[SPEAKER_19]: Dear class, fuck you.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm petitioning the dean so I can test out of it.
[SPEAKER_19]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_19]: I think I'm done.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh yeah, another one goes to allergies and not having any sinus medicine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, let's move on to Loki and his FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_09]: My first FU goes to stupid trees which limbs keep falling off of.
[SPEAKER_09]: I swear to God, I know I'm going to be walking to the apartment during the night all of a sudden this limb is going to fall on me.
[SPEAKER_09]: And that's going to suck.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also, fuck you, the SUV drivers.
[SPEAKER_09]: I swear to God, I just saw, like, yesterday, two different instances where SUVs crashed into things.
[SPEAKER_09]: First one being into a truck.
[SPEAKER_09]: And the second time, a Humvee jumped the rail and hit another car.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because...
[SPEAKER_09]: It was an H2.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's not a real Hummer.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, it's not a real Hummer, but, you know.
[SPEAKER_09]: An H2.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it was a woman.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was a woman driving it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I bet you she was on a cell phone, too.
[SPEAKER_19]: I want to sort of insert a nephew there to the H2.
[SPEAKER_19]: They look like shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_19]: If you want a Hummer, you freaking get one that looks like it's, you know, armored.
[SPEAKER_19]: That it can run over buildings and live.
[SPEAKER_09]: See, I don't have a problem with women driving SUVs or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just when you drive with cell phones and don't pay attention to shit.
[SPEAKER_09]: Then you get into accidents and they kill people because I know there was a stretcher there and they were sure as hell blocking traffic, so...
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyways, fuck you to them.
[SPEAKER_09]: And, um... Fuck you to Alien vs. Predator.
[SPEAKER_09]: Goddammit, that was a waste of two hours.
[SPEAKER_09]: But it was a funny-ass movie.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alien vs. Predator.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, who'd have thunk it that it was a buddy comedy?
[SPEAKER_09]: My god, lame.
[SPEAKER_09]: But, you know, I should have known better going into it.
[SPEAKER_09]: And, finally, um...
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know, that's it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, that's right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fuck you to my co-worker.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, this is quite funny because this is the one that was sleeping around.
[SPEAKER_01]: She's getting demoted.
[SPEAKER_01]: She couldn't cut it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Shows you that it takes more than just sleeping around to get into sales, bitch.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, that's all.
[SPEAKER_05]: My turn.
[SPEAKER_05]: F you to getting sick.
[SPEAKER_05]: And F you to having a special friend that you keep passing diseases back and forth to.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, like, colds, people.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't think dirty.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, I would like to say a big F you to faggoty drama queens.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I know that faggot is a derogatory term, and I don't use it unless I really mean it, okay?
[SPEAKER_05]: This guy I know, he's a real faggot, okay?
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm gay, so I'm allowed to say that word.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, there's a difference between a gay person and, like, a total faggot, okay?
[SPEAKER_05]: And this guy pisses me off because he is such a fucking drama queen.
[SPEAKER_05]: You wouldn't even imagine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, I haven't seen this guy in, like, five years.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then, like, last night, I ran into him, and there was just this aura of just, like, drama-ness that you wouldn't even look me in the eye.
[SPEAKER_05]: As much as I just wanted to say hi and just be like, okay, so, like, hi, you know, our drama's five years old, let's get over it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nope, denied.
[SPEAKER_05]: So whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fuck that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_05]: But that's all I have to say.
[SPEAKER_05]: Moving on, let's go to Angel and Arcadian.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who has a mic?
[SPEAKER_05]: Arcadian!
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, first off, uh, fuck you to these horrible commercials, these horrible radio commercials, fucking kids.
[SPEAKER_10]: Uh, like every 15 minutes these goddamn kids come on.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, eh!
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, that's the commercial I fucking hate the Paul Zonka commercial.
[SPEAKER_10]: Those damn kids are so fucking annoying.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just want to shoot the goddamn radio for the stupid kids.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wish I could stab them through the radio.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh no, I'm dying.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, can't do more radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Uh, let's see, what else?
[SPEAKER_10]: Uh, fuck you to radio commercials that have songs that say, oh, I like this song.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then it's a fucking commercial.
[SPEAKER_10]: I hope your business goes down in flames.
[SPEAKER_10]: Unfortunately, it's like one of those damn car dealerships of Satan that will keep going forever in the space of a 20.
[SPEAKER_10]: Uh, fuck you to the trees that work that pour sap on my car.
[SPEAKER_10]: I can't really afford to, and fuck you that I can't afford to actually go to the car wash to get at least some of it off without having to scrape and scrub and everything.
[SPEAKER_10]: Uh, yeah, fuck you to not, uh, being nearly penniless, having to plan out months in advance where my money is going.
[SPEAKER_10]: But hopefully that'll change in like a month or two.
[SPEAKER_10]: And fuck you to not be able to go places.
[SPEAKER_10]: And not be able to go to the arcades or anything.
[SPEAKER_10]: and, yeah, that's all.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, DDR Angel.
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright, uh, well, I know you guys have, uh, said this FU over and over and over again, but see, now that I live here, I really know what you're talking about.
[SPEAKER_17]: Um, FU to the freaking stupid drivers around here, because they've almost killed us, like, I don't know, at least, uh, five times that I can recall this week while driving around Sacramento, so it's like,
[SPEAKER_17]: and also FU to the main post office in Sacramento because they have still decided to hold our mail so we're not getting all of it like we should be.
[SPEAKER_17]: But well, I guess that's the...
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't know, downside to moving.
[SPEAKER_17]: Also, Magus wants to send an FU to big work servers going down.
[SPEAKER_17]: Because now he's going to have to explain himself on Wednesday as to why the server went down for four hours.
[SPEAKER_17]: So he's going to have some extra work to do, it looks like.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh well.
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright, I guess that's it.
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright, let's move on to our chatroom FUs, shall we?
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Unknown Gamer wants to say, I want to send a big heaping F you to Loki for calling your reign R&B shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Go back and tend to whatever Bomani artist you're into.
[SPEAKER_05]: To his cock, fanboy.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you can throw in an I love DarkSakura thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: She's my online hag now.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's so cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Any response to you being an asshole for calling your reign R&B shit?
[SPEAKER_09]: No?
[SPEAKER_09]: Because it's still shit, even though, whether you think it's not or, you know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's still shit.
[SPEAKER_09]: It'll always be shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Panda wants to say...
[SPEAKER_05]: Panda wants to say F you to Sky for counting my vote as California Dreamin'.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyways, I like the version off the DJ Sammy CD better.
[SPEAKER_05]: For your information, Panda, I counted your vote for song 2 because I saw that you changed it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bitch!
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow, that was really brutal.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just probably, I just totally chastised one of our listeners.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: See, now this is crap, okay?
[SPEAKER_05]: This is crap.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_05]: ViolentHyperGirl says, F you to fabboys and F you to three-dimensional calculus when it involves solving the moment of inertia in some solid object.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because it involves three intervals, each of which takes almost a third of a page.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, I'm getting bored here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, F you to leaving my friend's birthday party on Saturday night.
[SPEAKER_05]: If I didn't have to go to Davis the next day, I would have stayed all night and just caught a ride with someone.
[SPEAKER_05]: But yeah, and F you to ants.
[SPEAKER_05]: They need to die.
[SPEAKER_05]: Heart raid.
[SPEAKER_05]: By the way, an FU goes to a particular person who acts like they know everything.
[SPEAKER_05]: You are an idiot, period.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't like saying FUs to individuals in particular.
[SPEAKER_05]: RightChan says, FU to drama queens that blame the drama on everyone else and break up a community in the process.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ooh, I agree with that.
[SPEAKER_05]: FU to garbage that is on welfare and feels they need to have children because their boyfriend is going to take care of me.
[SPEAKER_19]: Amen to that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dark Tetsuya says, F you to keyboard hotkeys.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hit one on accident and it shut down my computer.
[SPEAKER_05]: MJB says, my F you of the week goes to goddamn toysandjoys.com for sending me my Max 2 Japanese after two weeks of waiting but forgetting to send party collection.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hate you, Toys and Joys.
[SPEAKER_19]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_19]: I've got a free copy of Fantasy Star Collection.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: John Field says, F you to Microsoft and XP Service Pack 2 again because I'm still crashing.
[SPEAKER_05]: F you to the laws of physics.
[SPEAKER_05]: It would be much easier if I didn't need to use any fuel to drive my car.
[SPEAKER_05]: F you to moving between dorm rooms.
[SPEAKER_05]: Misty says, the closest thing to a real F you that I've gotten this week is to myself for not being able to think shit up for my RPG and the works of fanfiction I've got.
[SPEAKER_05]: Lunarius says F you to physical distance because I found a guy online that I really like but he lives hundreds of miles from me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dark Knight says F you to the USA basketball team for getting the ass kicked by Puerto Rico today.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: SaoZao, I hope I said that right, SaoZao says, uh, F you to my connection for being so shitty, fuck you, uh, F you Nickel City for ripping off Konami and using Step Mania, woo, uh, Konami, or uh, Nickel City.
[SPEAKER_05]: DDRHolic says, F you to people who get pissed at you when you aren't driving fast enough and when the reason you aren't driving fast enough is because the idiot in front of you isn't driving fast enough.
[SPEAKER_05]: F you to people who think that they own the entire public road system and drive like there are no fucking rules anywhere but their own rules, driving wherever they want, whenever they want.
[SPEAKER_05]: F you to people who think they have special privileges, such as parking in front of the grocery store in the red zone to load their fucking groceries.
[SPEAKER_05]: Load their fucking groceries like the rest of us motherfuckers.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've even seen someone pull their SUV out of the handicap parking spot to the front of the store to load their fucking groceries like they weren't close enough to the grocery store in the first place.
[SPEAKER_05]: And lastly, oh, that wasn't even an FU, but it was a personal question for me from somebody.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I guess that was the last one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sad, huh?
[SPEAKER_17]: Wow, about the Toys and Joys FU, that's the first time I've actually heard someone negatively bash them, except for when I didn't get my controller, but I got it five days later, so it doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_19]: I have never had a problem with Toys and Joys.
[SPEAKER_19]: When we were really big into the Sega Ages 2500, we had ordered a bunch of games from there, and all of our others arrived,
[SPEAKER_19]: They actually sent me an email saying, you know, Fantasy Star, we were at a Fantasy Star collection.
[SPEAKER_19]: Would you like to cancel the order?
[SPEAKER_19]: I said, well, sure, go ahead and cancel it.
[SPEAKER_19]: You know, we'll wait on that.
[SPEAKER_19]: And they had shipped it anyway.
[SPEAKER_19]: So we were actually never charged for a Fantasy Star collection.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, we are done.
[SPEAKER_19]: Actually, when I ordered my Guitar Freaks controllers, I had them two days later.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's it for the FUs tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: We've got all our FUs in.
[SPEAKER_05]: Are we ready to hear about tonight's listless?
[SPEAKER_05]: Sure, Rob.
[SPEAKER_18]: Are we ready?
[SPEAKER_05]: And now to announce the winners of tonight's listless.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck this song.
[SPEAKER_05]: As a reminder, here is tonight's topic.
[SPEAKER_05]: A iToy minigame I would most like to see in DDR.
[SPEAKER_05]: You voted, and here are the results.
[SPEAKER_05]: In third place, we have a tie.
[SPEAKER_05]: Our third place winner number one is Break Shit.
Yay!
[SPEAKER_05]: Our third place winner number two is Whack A Child.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_05]: Our second place winner in tonight's list list is Fuck With The Other Players Arrows.
[SPEAKER_05]: And tonight's winner for iToy minigame I would most like to see in DDR is... Mini Water in Your Asshole game!
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, and Answer Question or Catch Fire also got third place!
[SPEAKER_17]: This is where Angel's, uh, thought bubble goes dot dot dot, I won?
[SPEAKER_17]: What?! !
[SPEAKER_05]: I know, me too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dot, dot, dot.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, but you had a little help from the rest of us.
[SPEAKER_05]: You were going to say the WarioWare thing, and nobody got that.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was much funnier when we said water in your asshole.
[SPEAKER_17]: That is the WarioWare thing.
[SPEAKER_17]: Never mind.
[SPEAKER_17]: I guess it was better than that BurgerTime thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, and showing the true mentality age of most of our chat room chatters and our listeners, the game that has the word asshole in it wins, so good job.
[SPEAKER_17]: I think that's the first time that that's actually happened.
[SPEAKER_09]: Other thoughts of mine were like, regulate your brain.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: Or like, my favorite, call the assurance inspector at a toy factory mode.
[SPEAKER_09]: Basically, you get to throw in a bunch of sharp razor blades and stuff into the stuffed animals.
[SPEAKER_09]: But see, you have certain items that you can put in the animals, and you just have to get the right one, depending on what it is.
[SPEAKER_19]: I was thinking of one that's like that, there was one of those little flash games that was where you would have this
[SPEAKER_19]: Phallus, and shoot into these condoms as they went by.
[SPEAKER_19]: They should have, like, Condom Tester, the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Angel, I have some questions for you as the author of... Oh, shit.
[SPEAKER_09]: What, Loki, what?
[SPEAKER_09]: This is like, okay, there's the line, and I'm crossing it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do your own abortion mode.
[SPEAKER_09]: Stop.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're horrible.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Angel, as the author of Mini Water in Your Asshole Game, I have some questions.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have you ever played Eye Toy Groove?
[SPEAKER_17]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know how Eye Toy Groove takes pictures and video of you as you play?
[SPEAKER_05]: Would Mini Water in Your Asshole Game do the same thing?
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh god, now I'm thinking of that stupid, um... What was that really fucked up Japanese game that had the vibrator shit?
[SPEAKER_17]: Rez?
[SPEAKER_17]: Rez.
[SPEAKER_17]: God.
[SPEAKER_19]: I know, like, there's the Abunga game.
[SPEAKER_19]: Where you stick the finger in the ass.
[SPEAKER_05]: Abunga Bunga.
[SPEAKER_05]: Somebody in our chatroom actually suggested that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I saw that go by.
[SPEAKER_19]: I can't believe, though, that Abunga actually was, like, a real game and they had a party for it and everything.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um...
[SPEAKER_05]: My other question about mini water in your asshole game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Once you get the water in your asshole, would you be able to shoot it back out?
[SPEAKER_05]: On that note, it's about time to end the show here.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we're going to go around and get everybody's final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_05]: DDR Angel, your final thought, please.
[SPEAKER_17]: I did not expect the...
[SPEAKER_17]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_17]: People actually chose what I wanted to do.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Get over yourself.
[SPEAKER_05]: Arcadian42, your final thought, please.
[SPEAKER_10]: Things may be looking up.
[SPEAKER_10]: My future may be coming on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, your final thought, please.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm tired.
[SPEAKER_09]: I like my yogurt.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's going to suck later.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, my final thought is I hope you all have a wonderful week and listen to Orange Launch Radio lots.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I was going to make an announcement about Vanilla Sky coming back, but I guess we'll wait for next week.
[SPEAKER_08]: We haven't plugged the shows!
[SPEAKER_05]: I know we haven't plugged the shows.
[SPEAKER_05]: Listen to Orange Launch Radio every weeknight and hear something cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: The end.
[SPEAKER_05]: because the rewinds are coming back as well the rewinds will be back on Thursday Thursday nights by popular demand the Orange Lounge Radio Rewind and probably we're looking I actually might bump it up a little bit to like 6 o'clock so our East Coast friends don't have to stay up so late to hear the show maybe even 5 we'll see my final thought is actually listen to Pump Up the Volume on Tuesday night starting at I tend to start around a quarter to 7 if I get early but usually pre-show starts at 7 show starts at 7.30 goes to whenever
[SPEAKER_19]: I will likely be doing homework the whole time.
[SPEAKER_19]: Um, but, uh, I'm thinking, you know, I play a lot of dancey, happy, crappy stuff.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm just gonna go for broke and say, screw you, R-I-A-A.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm playing Metallica S&M concert and, like, a bunch of hair rock and, like, some Rammstein and, uh, and, uh, I don't know, I might throw in some, like, uh,
[SPEAKER_19]: Danzig, and Henry Rollins.
[SPEAKER_19]: Just for the hell of it.
[SPEAKER_19]: Nothing happy, dancy, poppy for me.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay, maybe a little bit.
[SPEAKER_19]: Maybe the pre-show.
[SPEAKER_19]: And some Enflo.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'll play some Enflo to make the Enflo people happy.
[SPEAKER_19]: I will play some Enflo and Crystal K. I love that.
[SPEAKER_19]: But it's mostly going to be the Metallica S&M concert.
[SPEAKER_19]: Because that's just really, really freaking rad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: That should be a very interesting show then.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, hell yeah!
[SPEAKER_19]: Excuse me.
[SPEAKER_19]: Vortex
[SPEAKER_15]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_15]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_15]: Orange Lounge Radio is hosted by DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_15]: If you'd like to leave us a comment, send us an email at orangeloungeradio at yahoo.com And now, here's your fortune cookie message of the day.
[SPEAKER_20]: Can't keep his mind on nothing else Stay in the barn for the good thing he's found If he's inside, he can't see it She can't do no wrong Rhode Island Red is his best friend He can't put her down
[SPEAKER_20]: I'm buying her fresh corn down at the grain and feed He'll build a nest for her comfort and sleep out in the cool If she said that's the way it's got to be
DarkSakura.com
We know exactly how he feels Shacked up into his house
[SPEAKER_15]: Thank you very much for listening and we'll see you next week.