Thank you for watching!
and many more.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: Tomei!
And now for our feature presentation
[SPEAKER_28]: Orange Lounge Radio Live is now on the air.
[SPEAKER_28]: Orange Lounge Radio Live is a live talk program dedicated to all things Bomani and Bensum.
[SPEAKER_28]: Orange Lounge Radio may contain adult content, so you probably shouldn't let your children listen.
[SPEAKER_28]: If you do let your children listen to Orange Lounge Radio, they may turn into evil little demons from hell.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh wait, most children already are evil little demons from hell.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh wait, most children already are evil little demons from hell.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my god, I see a bloody stump!
[SPEAKER_28]: Any time, any place, baby.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ow, my foot!
[SPEAKER_08]: Why did I shoot myself in my foot?
[SPEAKER_21]: We are live and this is episode number 109 for this, August the 29th of 2004.
[SPEAKER_21]: You're tuned in to the B-Money Scenes, most competitive radio station of all things B-Money.
[SPEAKER_21]: My name is Rob Roberts, you might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_21]: Joining me as always are my awesome co-hosts.
[SPEAKER_21]: In this corner, the happiest bunny on the farm.
[SPEAKER_21]: You know her better as Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_21]: DarkSakura!
[SPEAKER_21]: Can't hear you.
[SPEAKER_13]: I hate pollen.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I hate not having air conditioning.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I hate my throat and I hate my nose.
[SPEAKER_13]: I hate my sinus passages.
[SPEAKER_21]: Is there anything you like this evening?
[SPEAKER_21]: Meat.
[SPEAKER_13]: This is some damn good meat.
[SPEAKER_21]: I just wanted to end things on a positive note.
[SPEAKER_13]: Positive?
[SPEAKER_13]: How about a high note?
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: I would, except my throat hurts.
[SPEAKER_13]: So I did it on a low note.
[SPEAKER_20]: Works for me.
[SPEAKER_13]: I could try the high note.
[SPEAKER_13]: But I don't want to like, you know.
[SPEAKER_20]: You're hecka lame.
[SPEAKER_13]: That me!
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh my god, I finally saw a basketball.
[SPEAKER_19]: What'd you think?
[SPEAKER_13]: It's not my how was my week, how was my day yet.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, she's feisty tonight, Miss Jamie Summers is here.
[SPEAKER_13]: I just counted she because my flicks is all fucked up.
[SPEAKER_21]: She's here and she's feisty.
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't know, she's Catwoman.
[SPEAKER_13]: My nose is full of snot.
[SPEAKER_13]: Give me a new nose, Rob.
[SPEAKER_13]: Good Kmart.
[SPEAKER_21]: Also joining us tonight, the one and only Tech Massa Loki.
[SPEAKER_21]: And I was fixing a webcam and I stepped on something sharp.
[SPEAKER_21]: S, The Clumsy Professor, as always.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's metal.
[SPEAKER_21]: Ow.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's probably a piece of your vortex.
[SPEAKER_17]: No, it's a piece of wire.
[SPEAKER_18]: Also joining us tonight, say hello to DDR Angel.
[SPEAKER_18]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm here again.
[SPEAKER_18]: What, four weeks in a row?
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_18]: Damn, girl, get a life.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_18]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: I know.
[SPEAKER_18]: What is this, 109 weeks in a row?
[SPEAKER_13]: I think you're one to walk, talk, balk, cock.
[SPEAKER_13]: No.
[SPEAKER_21]: Can't wait till I get a week off, which I do get pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_21]: About three weeks, I have a week off.
[SPEAKER_13]: A forced week off?
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes, a forced week off.
[SPEAKER_21]: My doctor says this show's not good for me.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_13]: What?
[SPEAKER_13]: Your computer hates me.
[SPEAKER_19]: Why's that?
[SPEAKER_13]: It just does, but I'll make the supreme effort, but goddammit, while you're out of town, we better have guests.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, we'll... Or else we'll take a vacation too.
[SPEAKER_21]: We'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm sure I can... We'll re-record three hours of Loki singing.
[SPEAKER_21]: Just whip out, you know what, before I leave, I'll buy Karaoke Revolution 2 and you'll have yourself a whole three hour show right there.
[SPEAKER_21]: Can't hear you babe.
[SPEAKER_13]: How's that?
[SPEAKER_13]: You gotta hold the mic to the bottom sometimes.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm going to announce to everybody tonight that I am currently on Dayquil Tylenol Allergy Sinus and now Benadryl.
[SPEAKER_22]: In other words, Jamie admits that she's on drugs.
[SPEAKER_13]: I am fucked up tonight.
[SPEAKER_13]: So if I start saying something really weird, blame the drugs.
[SPEAKER_13]: But I'm going to have ice cream, so that should sort of negate it, because I'll be in happy chocolate mode.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's my Lincoln's ice cream.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, never mind.
[SPEAKER_19]: Low-carb ice cream is not ice cream.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, it's good.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's made with cream.
[SPEAKER_19]: All right, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's better than normal ice cream, because it's good.
[SPEAKER_13]: It has fat in it, and fat makes it good.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, we're going to take a quick break and we'll be back.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh yeah, there's Bimani stuff too.
[SPEAKER_21]: We do talk about DDR and stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's that Bimani crap?
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, what is that stuff?
[SPEAKER_21]: You know, I was actually playing Ultramix before the show.
[SPEAKER_21]: I want to talk about that when we come back.
[SPEAKER_21]: After this little break.
[SPEAKER_21]: I thought it would be funny.
[SPEAKER_21]: Because I want to address some folks that play on Ultramix, that's why.
[SPEAKER_21]: We're going to take a break.
[SPEAKER_21]: In this break, enjoy the music of Outphase.
[SPEAKER_21]: And we'll be back after this break with much randomness for you.
[SPEAKER_21]: Enjoy.
Thank you.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_28]: and now let's listen in to an Orange Lounge Radio staff meeting as they debate some of the new programming coming to Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_21]: Jamie, I have a suggestion about some of the music in our Bomani Music and More program.
[SPEAKER_21]: Can we talk about that?
[SPEAKER_03]: No subject will ever be taboo.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, I was thinking maybe we should move Pump Up the Volume from Tuesday Nights.
[SPEAKER_21]: Except, of course, a subject that was just under discussion.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, well, what would you think if maybe we cut back on some of the tack music we play on the station?
[SPEAKER_03]: I collect your fucking head.
[SPEAKER_01]: Just like this fucker here.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh my god, why did you do that to Loki?
[SPEAKER_29]: The holic thing on episode 69 was just a joke!
[SPEAKER_03]: Now if any of you sons of bitches got anything else to say, now's the fucking time!
[SPEAKER_28]: Orange Lounge Radio, where everybody has a say.
[SPEAKER_21]: We are back.
[SPEAKER_21]: Orange Lounge Radio episode 109 is live.
[SPEAKER_21]: Uh, in a... Damn it.
[SPEAKER_21]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_21]: Hold on a minute.
[SPEAKER_21]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_21]: I have an announcement.
[SPEAKER_21]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_21]: Uh, this message was brought to you by Diet Soda.
[SPEAKER_21]: Enjoy at your local grocer.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay, so we are live here
[SPEAKER_21]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_21]: and I hope I don't make people go, oh yeah, I forgot, and then they shut off the show and go watch it, but the closing ceremonies at the Olympics are going on right now.
[SPEAKER_17]: They're done!
[SPEAKER_17]: It sucked!
[SPEAKER_17]: And trust me, if you watch the closing ceremonies, they're like, well, that was cool, maybe I should watch it next year!
[SPEAKER_17]: But the women's handball team won the gold, right?
[SPEAKER_21]: He has glasses.
[SPEAKER_13]: The women's handball team won gold.
[SPEAKER_13]: And then Bjork would have sung... Okay, I need the new Bjork album.
[SPEAKER_13]: I am more excited about Bjork than the Olympics.
[SPEAKER_13]: Bjork makes me all horny.
[SPEAKER_21]: I have new Bjork stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: Give Turat a skull.
[SPEAKER_21]: I actually, uh, I was looking and I found photocopies of certain Bjork albums that are out soon.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, hold on, let me, uh... See, this is what you're missing at the Olympics right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm a tree that is big!
[SPEAKER_21]: Just kidding, I like Bjork, otherwise I wouldn't have the album.
[SPEAKER_19]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_13]: Wow, we've actually got people.
[SPEAKER_13]: here who showed up during the break.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, we do have people that showed up here during the break.
[SPEAKER_21]: We have Arcadian42 showed up with glasses.
[SPEAKER_21]: New glasses.
[SPEAKER_24]: They're not new.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, they look new because you haven't worn them around me in a long time, if ever.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah, well, these are, like, way out of date, actually.
[SPEAKER_24]: This is, like, five years.
[SPEAKER_24]: This is, like, a prescription I got, like, five or six years ago.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm only wearing it because my contacts are, like, weeks old.
[SPEAKER_24]: I can't buy any new ones until I get an eye exam, and I can't afford an eye exam for a while.
[SPEAKER_24]: Last time I came here, I just wear them every so often.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm only wearing them for a few hours, but I can't wear them all day, because the contacts I have right now are way too old to wear every day, or I might get an infection in the eye or something.
[SPEAKER_24]: So it wouldn't be a good idea.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_21]: Also here with us tonight that came during the break was Jonas, also known as Explicit with three X's, because he's triple X rated.
[SPEAKER_21]: He's a porn star.
[SPEAKER_26]: Hey, everybody.
[SPEAKER_21]: Is that stinking state fair still going on by your work?
[SPEAKER_26]: Uh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_21]: I want to come play DDR at your work, but the stinking state fair's gone.
[SPEAKER_26]: You can actually play in the weekdays.
[SPEAKER_26]: The reason why it was closed on Saturday and Sunday is because that's where the business is racking up.
[SPEAKER_26]: Friday's you can actually go.
[SPEAKER_26]: Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday, and Thursday as well.
[SPEAKER_21]: So the parking lot doesn't spill all the way back there on the weekdays?
[SPEAKER_26]: No.
[SPEAKER_26]: Only Saturday and Sunday.
[SPEAKER_21]: Maybe I will go during the week.
[SPEAKER_21]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'll think about it.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_26]: Is there anything else?
[SPEAKER_21]: Uh, maybe later.
[SPEAKER_21]: We'll talk to you more a little bit later.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh, yeah, I forgot to talk about competition.
[SPEAKER_21]: We had the Olympics going on, and Bjork's singing.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, no, actually, she sang at the Olympics.
[SPEAKER_21]: She's not singing again.
[SPEAKER_21]: I was kidding about that.
[SPEAKER_21]: Uh, we had the Olympics going on, and the Video Music Awards are going on right now.
[SPEAKER_21]: In Miami.
[SPEAKER_21]: Is going on, and I think a lot of people ditched our show to go listen to that, and, uh, you suck.
[SPEAKER_21]: Why?
[SPEAKER_21]: I know, seriously.
[SPEAKER_21]: MTV is so done.
[SPEAKER_26]: MTV is so done, and overrated, and, ugh.
[SPEAKER_21]: Who won?
[SPEAKER_21]: Can we just get a spoiler out there?
[SPEAKER_21]: Don't we know who won now?
[SPEAKER_21]: Let's just get the spoilers out there and who made out with who this year and who punched who in the face.
[SPEAKER_21]: Let's just get it all out.
[SPEAKER_21]: That way the guys don't have to watch.
[SPEAKER_21]: You can feel free to listen to this show and watch our webcam on www.orangelongeradio.com You can also join our chat room there.
[SPEAKER_21]: www.orangelongeradio.com Just that easy.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, we do have some Bomani news I want to talk about tonight, but first, we have to start off tonight's show as we start off every week's show by playing a little bit of How was your week?
[SPEAKER_21]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_21]: And starting us off tonight for How was your week?
[SPEAKER_21]: The lovely DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_13]: My week was... Oh.
[SPEAKER_13]: My week was okay until my allergies started to hate me.
[SPEAKER_13]: I had a perfect score in my classes.
[SPEAKER_19]: Congrats.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm being like a good little nerdlet.
[SPEAKER_13]: And the Benadryl finally kicked in.
[SPEAKER_13]: I can breathe.
[SPEAKER_13]: But I haven't yet fallen into a coma, okay?
[SPEAKER_13]: But it's just been kind of a druggy week.
[SPEAKER_13]: I've been on the DayQuil all week.
[SPEAKER_13]: And then I had to double up all doses of everything.
[SPEAKER_13]: I've been just so drugged.
[SPEAKER_13]: But my air conditioning isn't working again at my house, so I'm going to have Dan Fusset, the apartment manager, for me.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, sniff.
[SPEAKER_13]: I finally broke down and bought a box of tissues, so they're going to be my best friend all weekend.
[SPEAKER_13]: But yeah, it hasn't been very interesting.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's just been filled with lots of tissue, lots of drugs.
[SPEAKER_13]: I feel like some kind of celebrity, because I'm popping pills all weekend, you know?
[SPEAKER_13]: Maybe I should rent a hotel room and throw a wild party and throw the bed sheets out of the window into the pool and all that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: But I'm hoping to feel better by next weekend so I can participate in much random shooting of things.
[SPEAKER_13]: This hasn't been too interesting.
[SPEAKER_13]: Very drugged.
[SPEAKER_13]: Very, very drugged.
[SPEAKER_13]: And Rob snores.
[SPEAKER_18]: What?
[SPEAKER_13]: See?
[SPEAKER_13]: You weren't even paying attention to me.
[SPEAKER_18]: I was trying to research the VMA so I could spoil it for everyone.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_21]: Sometimes you have to take the radio show by the horns and drive it yourself for a little bit.
[SPEAKER_13]: I could have said, and Rob suddenly likes pussy.
[SPEAKER_13]: And you would go, I wouldn't know.
[SPEAKER_21]: There are certain keywords that set off my alarm inside.
[SPEAKER_21]: Pussy being one of them.
[SPEAKER_21]: And I would have got you.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, it's actually, it's just been stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, I didn't even know the Video Music Awards were going on, because I don't watch cable.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't watch TV.
[SPEAKER_21]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't watch crap either, so.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, especially since the TV is now being taken up.
[SPEAKER_21]: Except for Survivor.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm allowed one crap show to like, and that is my crap show.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_13]: You can download Survivor on the Swin Channel on BitTorrent, I found.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, I don't need old ones.
[SPEAKER_21]: I need new ones.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, these are the new ones.
[SPEAKER_13]: How can they be the new ones?
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, I mean, whenever the new ones are on, there's one that does all the reality shows.
[SPEAKER_13]: And on top of that, I'm so happy because they put up the Stargate episode within 15 minutes of it airing.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's how I was keeping tabs on The Amazing Race, which most people generally agree is not a crap show.
[SPEAKER_13]: The Amazing Race is cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: I like the old army guy in it.
[SPEAKER_21]: I haven't been watching this year, though, because when Sharla and Myrna got kicked off, it just lost interest.
[SPEAKER_13]: The army guy is so kick-ass.
[SPEAKER_13]: This old guy and his daughter are a team.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_13]: And he had fallen, like, in the first part of the race and sliced up his leg.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_13]: But he continued.
[SPEAKER_13]: They still stayed in the race.
[SPEAKER_13]: And then he did the whole, um, what's the thing with the pulley and the line?
[SPEAKER_13]: From the top of the swim building into a swimming pool.
[SPEAKER_13]: Of course, chlorine with an open wound.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_13]: This guy was hardcore.
[SPEAKER_21]: Have you watched all the episodes yet?
[SPEAKER_13]: No, because I don't have TV.
[SPEAKER_13]: I just caught it over at Iguana Girl's house.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, catch up to Current.
[SPEAKER_21]: There's some good stuff that happens in the series.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm busy watching Stargate.
[SPEAKER_13]: Watch my pretty scientist man.
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_21]: Anything else you want to share about your week and your day?
[SPEAKER_13]: Uh-uh.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right, then.
[SPEAKER_21]: Loki, how was your week?
[SPEAKER_21]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_17]: I played a lot of Final Fantasy this week because it's too hard.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, whatever.
[SPEAKER_17]: Wait till you hear what he did today, but I'll let him tell.
[SPEAKER_17]: I am lazy, okay?
[SPEAKER_17]: I am extremely lazy.
[SPEAKER_17]: Extremely, extremely lazy.
[SPEAKER_17]: Let me make this clear.
[SPEAKER_17]: I am extremely lazy.
[SPEAKER_17]: and, you know, before... I have a question.
[SPEAKER_17]: So, Loki, are you in fact lazy?
[SPEAKER_17]: Yes, extremely lazy.
[SPEAKER_17]: Anyways, so, before, you know, I had farmed, you know, for, you know, really expensive items for over three weeks.
[SPEAKER_17]: Today was just not one of those days.
[SPEAKER_17]: I felt like not earning my money at all.
[SPEAKER_17]: So I bought it.
[SPEAKER_17]: I bought in-game money.
[SPEAKER_21]: So in other words, you gave somebody real life money so that they could give you in-game money.
[SPEAKER_21]: I just want to make that clear for our listeners.
[SPEAKER_17]: That would be correct.
[SPEAKER_17]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_17]: They can kiss my ass because I got that money within 15 minutes of paying it.
[SPEAKER_17]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_17]: That saved me a good 10 hours of gameplay.
[SPEAKER_17]: Think about it.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's opportunity cost.
[SPEAKER_17]: Any economics teacher will teach you.
[SPEAKER_17]: You want to spend the 10 hours or pay the $20.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, that's what it is.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's especially amazing considering that it takes about 45 minutes to get a GM sometimes.
[SPEAKER_21]: And Loki got his money in 15 minutes.
[SPEAKER_17]: That was enough time for me to take a power nap and then go back into the game and have my money waiting for me.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, in Ragnarok, all I have to do is play for 15 minutes and I'll get, like, 400,000 zeny.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, that's because that money's worth nothing.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, so your money's not worth anything?
[SPEAKER_13]: I could go buy a goat headband.
[SPEAKER_13]: And it looks cool because I have big goat horns.
[SPEAKER_13]: Which would be very perfect for your portal to hell.
[SPEAKER_17]: No.
[SPEAKER_13]: I haven't touched Ragnarok in a week.
[SPEAKER_17]: I have my magnet wire coming.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh yeah, so then I have some other stuff that's coming for my so-called portal to hell.
[SPEAKER_17]: I have an eight and a half pound spool of that shit, so I'll be able to make something with that.
[SPEAKER_17]: And what else?
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh yeah, I had to go to the doctor about my ingrown toenail that's nasty.
[SPEAKER_17]: But, well, he better fix that shit because you can get blood poisoning.
[SPEAKER_17]: Anyways, so I...
[SPEAKER_17]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_17]: Angel, how was your week?
[SPEAKER_17]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_17]: Hello, okay, um...
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's see, just schoolwork and other crap, nothing too damn exciting.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's see, I played a little DDR, but not too much, which kind of sucks.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm watching Rob make a funny face!
[SPEAKER_21]: Jamie's making you try her diet food.
[SPEAKER_11]: I played a little pop music as well, that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: Other than that, I did nothing except for homework.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yay, homework.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, anybody else want to go next?
[SPEAKER_11]: Hmm, maybe.
[SPEAKER_21]: Arcadian.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_24]: This week was mostly work.
[SPEAKER_24]: And on Friday we finally talked about employing me, and so we just did the pre-work and now I'm not an attempt anymore.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_19]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_19]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_24]: And so one day will be the first day of not being an attempt, which is good.
[SPEAKER_13]: That is such a good point.
[SPEAKER_13]: We have a bush and a dick in the White House.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's an old joke.
[SPEAKER_21]: I can't believe you've never heard that before.
[SPEAKER_24]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_24]: Sorry, Arcadian.
[SPEAKER_24]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_24]: Well, she wanted to talk, so I gave it to her.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_24]: Fuck MPB!
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm sorry, I keep getting interrupted.
[SPEAKER_21]: Was there anything else?
[SPEAKER_24]: Too bad that Explosion didn't kill seven at the MTV Music Awards.
[SPEAKER_21]: That would be nice.
[SPEAKER_24]: Just kill them all.
[SPEAKER_21]: Actually, I have something that somewhat relates to the news, what's going on.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm going to continue to interrupt Arcadian's little story he's trying to tell.
[SPEAKER_24]: Not going to have much of a story, anyway.
[SPEAKER_17]: More than 100,000 protest bush in New York City.
[SPEAKER_17]: Those are some mean, mean feminists there.
[SPEAKER_21]: Actually, it's interesting, because did you hear about those planes that were crashing, or the Russian planes that crashed earlier?
[SPEAKER_21]: Apparently this is, I'm like the last one to ever hear anything funny that's going on, but apparently Tom Brokaw said on the news, he tried to pronounce one of the Russian city names, but he got it wrong.
[SPEAKER_21]: and he said something else instead.
[SPEAKER_21]: And here it is.
[SPEAKER_21]: Thank you, Unknown Gamer, for passing this along to me.
[SPEAKER_21]: This is pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_23]: Two Russian planes carrying a total of more than 100 people crashed almost simultaneously today.
[SPEAKER_23]: The first crash happened in Bukhaki.
[SPEAKER_23]: He said Bukhaki.
[SPEAKER_29]: He said that in the next intro.
[SPEAKER_29]: Tom Brokaw said Bukhaki.
[SPEAKER_17]: Next intro.
[SPEAKER_17]: I say that it goes in the next intro.
[SPEAKER_23]: Hold on, one more time, one more time.
[SPEAKER_23]: Crash happened in Bukkake.
[SPEAKER_21]: There was a crash that happened and it made Bukkake.
[SPEAKER_29]: Tee hee.
[SPEAKER_21]: We're seven years old.
[SPEAKER_29]: Poopy, poopy, Bukkake, Bukkake.
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't care how old you are, how mature you think you are, that is funny when Tom Brokaw says Bukkake on accident.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm sure he must not have, when he caught his mistake, if he even knows what the word means, I'm sure when he caught his mistake, he was probably pretty pissed.
[SPEAKER_23]: I have to do it one more time.
[SPEAKER_23]: The first crash happened in Bukkake.
[SPEAKER_21]: Anyway, Arcadian, I'm sorry to keep interrupting.
[SPEAKER_21]: How was your week?
[SPEAKER_21]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay, uh, let's see, NovamaniMoves, uh, this weekend, like, on Friday, uh, I found a praying menace that was, uh, on the ceiling of my bathroom, and he hung out for, like, until today, and then I decided to take him outside, and then, seemed like it was too hot outside, he seemed, I put him in a shady spot, but he seemed to be, like, uh, melting or something, so I put a little bit of water on him and threw him in the bushes, and he disappeared about a week, I mean, about an hour later, so he may have been
[SPEAKER_24]: Birdfood, or may have crawled off to find some bugs.
[SPEAKER_24]: Or, who knows.
[SPEAKER_24]: The Circle of Life.
[SPEAKER_24]: And the rest of the day was just boring.
[SPEAKER_24]: Watched a few episodes of Upright Citizens Brigade that I had on CD.
[SPEAKER_21]: That show rocks.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_24]: And Play on the Computer.
[SPEAKER_24]: And I don't know what else.
[SPEAKER_24]: That's about everything for me.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'll talk about my week and my day, and then we'll get to Jonas.
[SPEAKER_21]: My week and my day was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_21]: Didn't do a whole lot during the week, just a lot of work, you know, the usual stuff.
[SPEAKER_21]: Then yesterday, I actually met some friends of mine from LiveJournal who live up in Seattle, and they're also on our Final Fantasy XI link shell, so I've known these guys for a long time.
[SPEAKER_21]: They go by Wither and Ataluta on our Final Fantasy XI link shell, and they were down here from Seattle on a total whim, where I guess they were going to go to Marine World for one of the birthdays.
[SPEAKER_21]: And so they called me up and was like, hey, let's hang out.
[SPEAKER_21]: So I'm like, okay.
[SPEAKER_21]: So I went down there and I took them to San Francisco and we all went to the Metreon, which, you know, kind of a famous place in NorCal DDR history.
[SPEAKER_21]: It was one of the first two places that really had a lot of DDR and had big tournaments.
[SPEAKER_21]: So I took them there so they could, you know, be at the Metreon.
[SPEAKER_21]: And there's just other cool stuff there too, like the official Sony PlayStation Store and things like that.
[SPEAKER_21]: and I actually played a game of DDR.
[SPEAKER_21]: Adeluda forced me to play a game of DDR up on the third floor where the movie theater is.
[SPEAKER_21]: They have a DDR machine.
[SPEAKER_21]: And I played a game.
[SPEAKER_14]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, Jamie, you and I played on that back when it was a fifth mix, I think.
[SPEAKER_21]: But now it's an extreme...
[SPEAKER_21]: And, um, we would have gone to Pier 39.
[SPEAKER_21]: Now, we would have gone to Pier 39 had we had more time.
[SPEAKER_21]: I was a little pressed for time yesterday, so I just, I only had time really to take them to the Metreon, because public transit goes right by there, the bar, and to get on, get to Pier 39, we would have had to take a bus.
[SPEAKER_21]: It would have taken too long, but next time, I'll make them come back.
[SPEAKER_21]: But we went to the Metreon.
[SPEAKER_21]: and played a game there, and you know what?
[SPEAKER_21]: DDR still gets crowds of people.
[SPEAKER_21]: Like, we were playing Cowgirl, which is not that complicated of a song, it's just a fun one, but there were just huge crowds of people that hear the little gallop, you know, because we're trying to get extra stage, right?
[SPEAKER_21]: So we were playing that, and it was funny.
[SPEAKER_21]: And then he played Doubles, and he got a hell of a crowd doing that.
[SPEAKER_21]: It was pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_26]: Cowgirl...
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm just surprised that DDR still gets big crowds like that.
[SPEAKER_21]: But I guess in a city like San Francisco, big touristy spot, maybe people come there, they don't get out that often.
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_26]: Well, the reason why DDR is still popular is because, one, it's the only game that has exercise involved.
[SPEAKER_26]: Really.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_26]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_21]: But then I went downstairs and I bowed down to the DDR 1.5 mix that they still have there.
[SPEAKER_21]: I miss 1.5 mix a little bit.
[SPEAKER_21]: Actually, I miss 5th mix and I miss 4th mix plus.
[SPEAKER_21]: And I miss some 3rd mix Koreans too.
[SPEAKER_21]: Because they're all either extreme or they're extreme these days.
[SPEAKER_18]: Maybe you see a max 2 still once in a while.
[SPEAKER_18]: Maybe you get a 4th plus if you're lucky.
[SPEAKER_18]: But what happened to all the 5th mix?
[SPEAKER_18]: I remember when I used to hate 5th mix, but I totally have a respect for it now.
[SPEAKER_26]: I always loved Fifth Mix, but there's no place outside anymore.
[SPEAKER_21]: When it first came out, I hated it.
[SPEAKER_21]: But the reason why I hated Fifth Mix when it first came out was because I was still kind of in that new phase to DDR.
[SPEAKER_21]: I was in that transitional phase.
[SPEAKER_21]: When I first played DDR, USA was all I knew.
[SPEAKER_21]: I played USA, USA, USA.
[SPEAKER_21]: And then finally we picked up a fourth mix.
[SPEAKER_21]: So I was really just starting to discover a bunch of those older songs, like the old erotic songs and stuff like that, which were really my...
[SPEAKER_21]: My Thing That I Love, and then right as I was discovering those, Fifth Mix comes out, and when that came out, what was the first thing that Fifth Mix did?
[SPEAKER_21]: It was the first mix to delete songs from older mixes, in mass.
[SPEAKER_21]: Now, I'm not talking like onesies, twosies, like Strictly Business, So Many Men, deleting songs like that, but I'm talking Fifth Mix was the first time they cut a whole bunch of songs from second and third mix, and I was pissed, because like all the good erotic songs I like to play were gone, and all the
[SPEAKER_21]: Cheesy stuff from 3rd Mix, like If You Can Say Goodbye and Flashdance, all that shit was gone.
[SPEAKER_13]: I would like to point out that 4th Mix deleted stuff from 3rd Plus.
[SPEAKER_21]: They deleted a couple of the Korean songs, right?
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: And one other.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was one other I thought that they did that wasn't... But I'm talking about like 30, 40 songs.
[SPEAKER_21]: 5th Mix got rid of like 30, 40 old songs.
[SPEAKER_10]: And so I kind of...
[SPEAKER_21]: I know.
[SPEAKER_21]: But too bad Konami won't put them in.
[SPEAKER_21]: I mean, like Moonlight Shadow, or Moving On, or...
[SPEAKER_26]: It's like a lot of songs in Fifth Mix are so good.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, the nice thing is a lot of those songs are coming out now in the US.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's like, it's kind of weird because between Extreme and Ultramix 2, we're getting a lot of Fifth Mix songs.
[SPEAKER_21]: Moonlight Shadow is going to be in Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_21]: Ooh, interesting.
[SPEAKER_26]: I heard about Ultramix 2 who's making the steps and stuff.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, but, you know.
[SPEAKER_21]: Crazy stuff.
[SPEAKER_26]: And I heard this Maximizer song.
[SPEAKER_26]: Did you actually hear this song?
[SPEAKER_26]: No, I just heard news about this Maximizer.
[SPEAKER_21]: We'll talk about all that a little bit.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'll get into the extreme news a little later because there was big extreme news this week.
[SPEAKER_21]: I want to ask you guys some stuff about it.
[SPEAKER_21]: But first off, where the hell was I?
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh yeah, the Metreon.
[SPEAKER_21]: So we left the Metreon and then I came back and I went to a Halo party last night.
[SPEAKER_21]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_21]: That was pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's all that's worth saying about my week and my day.
[SPEAKER_21]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_21]: Jonas, how was your week?
[SPEAKER_21]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_26]: My day was pretty, actually, this whole week's pretty good so far.
[SPEAKER_26]: I got new shoes.
[SPEAKER_26]: I actually can play DDR hella good with them.
[SPEAKER_26]: Started to double lay a lot of stuff with it.
[SPEAKER_26]: And heard some news about Tuesday's tournament in Scandia.
[SPEAKER_26]: Not sure if you all heard about it.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh, yeah, you heard about the overnight one or something?
[SPEAKER_18]: They're doing like a lock-in?
[SPEAKER_26]: It's called Back to School Bash.
[SPEAKER_26]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_21]: Weren't we going to go crash this tournament?
[SPEAKER_21]: Weren't we talking about going to crash it?
[SPEAKER_21]: I was going to go as Dr. Dick.
[SPEAKER_17]: I could if my foot was better, and it still hurts, but, you know, after ten days, that's, you know, up there.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm so out of shape, I cannot play anything.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jesus, man, Jesus.
[SPEAKER_21]: But anyways.
[SPEAKER_21]: Blow out everybody's speakers.
[SPEAKER_26]: I'm kind of worried about how the rules are going to turn out.
[SPEAKER_26]: All he says is P.A.
[SPEAKER_26]: and freestyle.
[SPEAKER_21]: When is this tournament?
[SPEAKER_26]: Tuesday at 7 o'clock.
[SPEAKER_21]: Tuesday?
[SPEAKER_21]: Tuesday at 7 o'clock P.M.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's during Jamie's show.
[SPEAKER_18]: I know.
[SPEAKER_18]: I think I'm going to go.
[SPEAKER_21]: I want to go win it.
[SPEAKER_21]: The prize is a trophy.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's a trophy?
[SPEAKER_21]: Because I'm betting all the good players in Sacramento don't know about it, like Toadie and Moogle Hunter and all that.
[SPEAKER_21]: They don't know about it.
[SPEAKER_26]: They actually know about it a little bit.
[SPEAKER_26]: God damn it.
[SPEAKER_21]: Who told them?
[SPEAKER_26]: Who told them?
[SPEAKER_26]: DDRUK.com.
[SPEAKER_26]: Fuck.
[SPEAKER_26]: Blame them.
[SPEAKER_21]: Why the fuck would DDRUK be talking about a shitty little tournament at Scandia?
[SPEAKER_21]: Why?
[SPEAKER_21]: Why would anyone want to give that tournament the time of day?
[SPEAKER_26]: Well, because people are like... Some of my workers at Paradise Island went to Scandia and stuff, just to see... I'm gonna go and I'm gonna break Toadie and Moogle's legs, and then I'm gonna win it.
[SPEAKER_21]: And I'm gonna win me a shiny trophy.
[SPEAKER_26]: You could also get it for freestyle as well.
[SPEAKER_26]: There's like two people, only two people entering.
[SPEAKER_26]: That's right!
[SPEAKER_26]: White people can't dance!
[SPEAKER_20]: I'm totally... I'm gonna... Oh, I'm gonna... It's on.
[SPEAKER_20]: It is so on.
[SPEAKER_26]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_26]: No way, I'm not competing.
[SPEAKER_26]: So, you have a high chance.
[SPEAKER_26]: Bring it.
[SPEAKER_26]: Oh, you want me to compete?
[SPEAKER_26]: Alright, I'll compete.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm going to make something up, and I'm going to beat you up.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's already been brought in.
[SPEAKER_26]: You came close on the Marsh Madness.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's just because I know how to work a crowd.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_26]: Or you can reserve for SPGL on December.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm not talking about these things yet.
[SPEAKER_26]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_21]: We'll discuss that later on.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, we can say now there is a tournament that's going to be at Sunnyvale Golf Line in December, but I'm thinking about doing something special.
[SPEAKER_21]: But I don't know yet.
[SPEAKER_26]: It's only DDR4++, I'm assuming.
[SPEAKER_26]: They're not using Xtreme's old 4++ for freestyle.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, I know.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's the reason why I want to do it.
[SPEAKER_26]: Same here.
[SPEAKER_21]: Xtreme is used.
[SPEAKER_21]: 4++, like retro.
[SPEAKER_21]: Old is new again.
[SPEAKER_21]: I love the 90s all over again, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey Rob, if you're going to that thing, can I go?
[SPEAKER_11]: Because you need a cheering section.
[SPEAKER_21]: I hella need a cheering section.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm sure I'll end up going.
[SPEAKER_21]: The question is if I'm going to enter or not.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm thinking about doing my very first actual freestyle.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's the thing.
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't know yet.
[SPEAKER_26]: You got two days, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_21]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm talking about Spiggle.
[SPEAKER_26]: Oh, oh, ooh.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was going to say, because there you go.
[SPEAKER_26]: Make that five months or so, I'm assuming.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was going to say, if Rob goes, then...
[SPEAKER_11]: Magus and I will carpool with him, maybe, if he lets us.
[SPEAKER_11]: And we will be his cheering section, because we can.
[SPEAKER_21]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'll let you guys know if I end up going to this tournament Tuesday at Scandia.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'll let you guys know.
[SPEAKER_26]: I'll probably be there, since I didn't get any tickets for the WWE Event Arc Arena.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_21]: See, there's more competitors that are going to be gone, because they'll go to that.
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_21]: Shit.
[SPEAKER_26]: You got that SmackDown event.
[SPEAKER_21]: I got three days to come up with a routine.
[SPEAKER_21]: Damn.
[SPEAKER_21]: I gotta find my copy of Extreme.
[SPEAKER_26]: Okay, let's see what else.
[SPEAKER_26]: It's also on DDRfreak.com since everyone heard about it from DDRUK.
[SPEAKER_26]: Okay, also I wanted to say fair.
[SPEAKER_26]: It was pretty good, except the prices are too damn expensive.
[SPEAKER_26]: 10 bucks for a ticket, 25 bucks for a wristband, or 20 if you get a Coke can.
[SPEAKER_21]: How much for a hot dog on a stick?
[SPEAKER_26]: Don't ask, it's like 8 bucks or so.
[SPEAKER_21]: How much for an egg roll on a stick?
[SPEAKER_21]: And cheesecake on a stick?
[SPEAKER_26]: Let's just say the lowest price for the... And your mom on a stick.
[SPEAKER_26]: That's priceless.
[SPEAKER_26]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_26]: Okay, okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah, most of the stuff there is like not even... The least expensive is like six bucks.
[SPEAKER_26]: And those are the funnel cakes.
[SPEAKER_26]: The most expensive is like 25, just for regular dinner.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, 25 bucks for one of those shitty little carts serving you dinner?
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah, one of them is that much.
[SPEAKER_26]: Jeez.
[SPEAKER_26]: Most of them you can see on the other restaurants.
[SPEAKER_26]: There's only one that you cannot get.
[SPEAKER_26]: It's only exclusive for State Fair.
[SPEAKER_26]: And those are the funnel cakes and the fried Twinkies.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, the fried Twinkies.
[SPEAKER_26]: Unless you know how to make them, then you can make the fried Twinkies yourself.
[SPEAKER_26]: But funnel cakes is exclusive to the State Fair.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh yeah.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_26]: And the fact that parking is expensive as hell.
[SPEAKER_26]: Like seven bucks for parking.
[SPEAKER_26]: Used to be like six.
[SPEAKER_26]: And I'm assuming that there's a DDR arcade section at the State Fair on the kids section.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh yeah, don't they usually have DDR at the State Fair every year and people go to dance to show off and try to get crowds, the people that love attention and stuff?
[SPEAKER_21]: Which I'm certainly not accepted from that.
[SPEAKER_26]: I think it's on the Eastern Gate, I'm assuming.
[SPEAKER_26]: Because I haven't been there yet.
[SPEAKER_26]: Since I'm going there on a Saturday yet again.
[SPEAKER_26]: There goes my wallet.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wait, did you say you were going on Thursday, Jonas?
[SPEAKER_21]: Saturday.
[SPEAKER_11]: Damn, I'm going on Thursday.
[SPEAKER_11]: Somebody in here knows why I'm going on Thursday.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes, I know what's going on Thursday.
[SPEAKER_21]: There's a concert Thursday she wants to see.
[SPEAKER_21]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, anything else you want to share about your week and your day, Jonas?
[SPEAKER_26]: Not much.
[SPEAKER_26]: Just work, school.
[SPEAKER_26]: And that's about it so far.
[SPEAKER_21]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, I opened up the Skype line if anybody has a comment so far.
[SPEAKER_21]: If you don't know anything about the Skype line, it's time to educate yourself.
[SPEAKER_21]: Head on over to our website, www.orangeloungeradio.com Click on that little tab that says interact with us.
[SPEAKER_21]: Remember, when we're in that do not disturb mode with the little red circle with the line through it, it means do not disturb.
[SPEAKER_21]: We're not taking calls.
[SPEAKER_21]: But we are right now.
[SPEAKER_21]: That icon's not on right now.
[SPEAKER_21]: We are taking calls.
[SPEAKER_21]: We're going to go to a break if nobody wants to call.
[SPEAKER_21]: Ooh, we're getting a call.
[SPEAKER_21]: Hello, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_21]: I hope we can hear this person.
[SPEAKER_21]: Can you hear us?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, I can.
[SPEAKER_21]: There you are.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, turn up your volume just a little bit more.
[SPEAKER_21]: Who be's this?
[SPEAKER_02]: Legend of Zaku.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's Legend of Zaku calling in, but he's very, very quiet.
[SPEAKER_21]: If there's any way you can turn up your mic volume, go for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, I can.
[SPEAKER_21]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_21]: A little bit better.
[SPEAKER_21]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_02]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, uh, let me see, I just moved.
[SPEAKER_21]: You just moved?
[SPEAKER_02]: I, uh... I think, ah, oh, yike!
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay, I'm up?
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes, I can hear you better now.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh... You know, I'm trying to prepare, I need help trying to, like... No, I just need help for a freestyle routine, because I have this big tournament in Jacob Javits Center in New York City...
[SPEAKER_21]: He needs help with a freestyle routine.
[SPEAKER_21]: What advice can he give to somebody?
[SPEAKER_21]: I'll ask Jonas.
[SPEAKER_13]: I have one suggestion.
[SPEAKER_13]: Don't use an orange bat.
[SPEAKER_13]: You will lose.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes, don't use an orange bat.
[SPEAKER_21]: You'll lose.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jamie and I know this from experience.
[SPEAKER_21]: We're losing the connection, Zaku.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm going to let you go.
[SPEAKER_21]: Tune into the show.
[SPEAKER_21]: We'll answer your question.
[SPEAKER_21]: Thanks for calling.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, let's finish answering Zaku's question.
[SPEAKER_21]: How do you prepare for a freestyle?
[SPEAKER_21]: Jonas, what do you go through?
[SPEAKER_21]: What are the motions you go through when you're preparing for a freestyle routine?
[SPEAKER_26]: Okay, the first thing to do is, the best is to put a step chart.
[SPEAKER_26]: That's my recommendation.
[SPEAKER_26]: A step chart would work because you can tell what moves you want to do, you know, like a documentary.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay, I'm losing you, Jonas.
[SPEAKER_21]: Grab the bottom of the microphone there.
[SPEAKER_21]: Push that cord back in a little bit.
[SPEAKER_21]: And try again.
[SPEAKER_21]: Sorry, bud.
[SPEAKER_21]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_26]: Does it work?
[SPEAKER_26]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_26]: Damn it.
[SPEAKER_26]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_26]: The best bet is to print a step chart, like ddrmain.com.
[SPEAKER_26]: Look for the song you want.
[SPEAKER_26]: Print out the step chart and use that as a document, which you want to do for the song itself.
[SPEAKER_24]: All right.
[SPEAKER_26]: Like you can write, ooh, I could do a spin here, or a splits, or wave your hands.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay, actually, yeah, he's correcting us in the chat room right now.
[SPEAKER_21]: He doesn't want to know how to set it up.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, fine.
[SPEAKER_21]: He wants to know what song he should do.
[SPEAKER_21]: What song should he do?
[SPEAKER_21]: What songs have not been used to all hell that are freestyable songs, in your opinion, Jonas?
[SPEAKER_26]: Depends on what song he wants to do.
[SPEAKER_26]: Like if he wants to do, like, hachas or salsa, like, he can go, like, La Bamba, La Copa de la Vida, or...
[SPEAKER_26]: Anything like that.
[SPEAKER_21]: I want to see a really good routine to Gamelan Day Couple, personally.
[SPEAKER_26]: That was actually pretty tough, but it's doable.
[SPEAKER_26]: If you want to do something like, um, like, oldies, like, sweet style, like, Heaven This Is 57 McTodd Grey would work.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alrighty.
[SPEAKER_26]: Hey, God, for the love of God, no, no knee dropping!
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_26]: I saw it, I'm...
[SPEAKER_26]: It's Raining Men.
[SPEAKER_26]: No comment.
[SPEAKER_21]: Heck yeah, it's Raining Men.
[SPEAKER_21]: Heck yeah.
[SPEAKER_26]: I'm just reading the post of Unknown Gamers.
[SPEAKER_26]: If you want to go feminist, just go for it.
[SPEAKER_26]: It's Raining Men, I Do, I Do, I Do, Cowgirl, any of those B4U songs.
[SPEAKER_26]: And if you want to go old school, just play anything that's from Naoki.
[SPEAKER_19]: That works.
[SPEAKER_19]: All right.
[SPEAKER_26]: And if you want to challenge the hell out of yourself, play like those Maxes.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right.
[SPEAKER_21]: We're going to go ahead and go to a break here.
[SPEAKER_21]: And in this break, since we were talking about Fifth Mix, I thought maybe we could, you know, respect Fifth Mix a little bit by playing some songs from it.
[SPEAKER_21]: So we will be right back after this, you guys.
Thanks for watching!
S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, for this last song in the fifth mix break, Jamie wanted to play this one especially for you guys.
[SPEAKER_21]: This is DarkSakura's pick just for you.
[SPEAKER_13]: I love you guys so much that I thought that you'd really want to hear this.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, there you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think I did it again I made you believe We're more than just friends Oh baby
I played with your heart, got lost in the game Oh baby, baby, oh, you think I'm in love That I'm sent from above I'm not that innocent
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm a fool in so many ways But you lose all my senses That is just so typically me Oh baby, ooh, oops, I did it again I played with your heart Got lost in this game Oh baby, baby, oops, you think I'm in love Then I'm running from it
S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_27]: Please listen to Orange Lounge Radio Because real radio makes Captain Jack cry We are back
[SPEAKER_21]: Excuse me, I'm eating a gummy worm.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's very pleasant.
[SPEAKER_21]: You are listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_21]: Here we are back with episode 109.
[SPEAKER_21]: We were talking about freestyle a little bit before the break there.
[SPEAKER_21]: And, um... Oh yeah, if you were wondering what the hell happened in the chatroom, if you were in our chatroom, orangehoundsradio.com, click on chat.
[SPEAKER_21]: We had what's called a net split.
[SPEAKER_21]: And this happens from time to time.
[SPEAKER_21]: IRC, it's a bunch of computers all linked together for the purposes of chatting.
[SPEAKER_21]: And when you connect to our server, you're connecting to one of them.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, sometimes the communication line breaks.
[SPEAKER_21]: And that means half the people go one way and half the people go the other way.
[SPEAKER_21]: So we had a little bit of a net split there, but it looks like it's fixed.
[SPEAKER_21]: We're okay now.
[SPEAKER_21]: So, um...
[SPEAKER_21]: Don't be afraid of our chat room.
[SPEAKER_21]: There's many other reasons to be afraid of our chat room other than the net splits, that's all.
[SPEAKER_21]: Jamie picked that one just for you guys, by the way.
[SPEAKER_21]: The Rochelle with the oops, I did it again.
[SPEAKER_13]: People liked it.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, I threw in a little bit of the Bukkake thing, too.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because Tom Brokaw likes Bukkake.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes, he does.
[SPEAKER_13]: You heard it here on Orange Challenge Radio.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm going to run this joke into the ground tonight.
[SPEAKER_21]: I like having jokes so we can run into the ground.
[SPEAKER_23]: Crash happened in Bukkake.
[SPEAKER_13]: Tom Brokaw's getting old.
[SPEAKER_13]: He's been doing news since I was five.
[SPEAKER_21]: He's quitting, finally.
[SPEAKER_21]: Like, this year, I think.
[SPEAKER_13]: He needs to retire.
[SPEAKER_13]: Him and Dan Rather.
[SPEAKER_13]: Dan Rather's still doing the news.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, Phil Donahue got his clue.
[SPEAKER_13]: He ended his show.
[SPEAKER_13]: Way back.
[SPEAKER_21]: But then he got a new one on another network.
[SPEAKER_13]: No.
[SPEAKER_21]: And then it tanked.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes, he did.
[SPEAKER_21]: He was on MSNBC for about three months.
[SPEAKER_21]: And then it tanked.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because they got too used to his talk show.
[SPEAKER_13]: See, once you go, you know...
[SPEAKER_13]: Public Mass, you know, audience, you can never go back.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's over.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's why Ricky Lake will never act again.
[SPEAKER_21]: Except in John Waters movies, and that's okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: Except in John Waters movies.
[SPEAKER_21]: There's a new John Waters movie coming out soon, I'm so excited.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's NC-17, so it's back to his roots.
[SPEAKER_21]: Good stuff.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_21]: Anyway, I thought we could actually talk about some actual Bomani news that's going on this week.
[SPEAKER_21]: Didn't we finish?
[SPEAKER_21]: How was your week?
[SPEAKER_21]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, that's right, we did.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm like drugs, remember?
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, Jamie's on drugs tonight, you guys.
[SPEAKER_21]: Since we about doubled our listeners since the start of the show, why don't you explain to everybody what's going on, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_13]: My nose hates me.
[SPEAKER_13]: I've been, like, major allergy attack since, like, Friday.
[SPEAKER_13]: So I'm on Dayquil and Tylenol allergy sinus and this Afrin stuff that you shoot up into your nose.
[SPEAKER_13]: And then this Vic stuff that looks like a dildo.
[SPEAKER_13]: Look at this.
[SPEAKER_13]: I got this, one of those little...
[SPEAKER_13]: It has the Vicks stuff in it so you inhale the fumes when you put Vicks on your nose.
[SPEAKER_13]: But if you take the wrapper off of it, it looks like a dildo.
[SPEAKER_13]: I put it up on the cam before, doesn't it?
[SPEAKER_22]: That kind of looks like a tampon.
[SPEAKER_13]: It does sort of look like a tampon, too.
[SPEAKER_22]: Can I go put that on our webcam?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, I did it once.
[SPEAKER_13]: Here, put it on the cam again.
[SPEAKER_21]: Join our site at orangeloungeradio.com and you can see the webcam right on the front page.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm going to go show off this nasty little thing.
[SPEAKER_13]: I got another drug, I got Benadryl now, and they have Dayquil Sinus, so I'm taking that too.
[SPEAKER_13]: Don't put that, Rob, I had that in my, Rob is sick.
[SPEAKER_13]: Rob put a tampon in his nose.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ew, Rob, you didn't like that?
[SPEAKER_19]: That wasn't really in my nose, Jesus.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_13]: But, um, I don't know what I like, what I hate more.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because I've been, like, sniffy-drippy all day, and my nose had this burn in it, like I had to sneeze.
[SPEAKER_13]: I sneezed the whole way here.
[SPEAKER_13]: I nearly ran into some truck that was carrying, like, panes of glass.
[SPEAKER_13]: I thought I was going to die.
[SPEAKER_13]: Um, by the way, Rob, will you put this back on the show for me?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, my bad.
[SPEAKER_13]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_13]: Um, so I took Benadryl right before I came in, and I've had ice cream.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, I'm hoping that they counteract each other, but if I fall into a coma halfway through the show, blame the drugs.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'll be just like Ozzy Osbourne, back when he was cool.
[SPEAKER_21]: He's still cool, what are you talking about?
[SPEAKER_13]: You know what's funny?
[SPEAKER_13]: In my law book, because I'm taking business law, they brought up that case from the 80s where the kid listened to the Ozzy Osbourne suicide song and shot himself.
[SPEAKER_13]: Ah-ha.
[SPEAKER_13]: Law is funny.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyway, I'm just going all the way off on tangents.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_13]: And Legend of Takuno, the one that I'm referring to was Ozzy Osbourne because I did my homework and read my book.
[SPEAKER_13]: So they talked about an Ozzy Osbourne case.
[SPEAKER_13]: About the song that's...
[SPEAKER_13]: It was, uh, no, I read the goddamn book, don't argue with me, okay?
[SPEAKER_13]: You are not taking my business law class, I am taking the business law class.
[SPEAKER_13]: They referred to, Ozzy Osbourne's first name is John, okay?
[SPEAKER_13]: It had him by his name in my goddamn book, and it was freaking, okay, do not argue with me because I am always right, okay?
[SPEAKER_13]: It was an Osbourne case where it was a song about how easy it is to kill yourself.
[SPEAKER_13]: About you can slowly drink yourself to death.
[SPEAKER_13]: and then it was and the guy killed himself and his parents were trying to blame Ozzy Osbourne for killing himself for killing the kid but they actually it got turned over because it was had they ruled in the parents favor it would have been a violation of the constitutional right for freedom of speech by the way speaking of freedom of speech
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_13]: The federal government basically, well, the Ninth Court of Appeals basically turned over that the person-to-person share programs like BitTorrent, BearShare, LimeWire, those like that, are legal.
[SPEAKER_13]: Also, they shot down the plans that they were wanting to do in the copyright laws because it would...
[SPEAKER_13]: I think some of the commercial law under the constitution and I think it's pretty neat.
[SPEAKER_13]: And the ironic thing is that the 9th Court of Appeals though also was the one that did the Napster case back in the day.
[SPEAKER_13]: But yeah, I was peeking through the news and I saw that and that was really cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: So...
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm sorry, I didn't mean to.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, that's alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: That affects all of us.
[SPEAKER_13]: That affects the show.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know you all pirate.
[SPEAKER_13]: They're also saying that, you know, like what we did through Life 365, perfectly fine.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, what we did through Life 365 was always legal.
[SPEAKER_21]: So, anyway.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_21]: Anyway, I want to get into some Bomani news, some actual Bomani news that's going on in the Bomani world this week.
[SPEAKER_21]: And one of the biggest stories actually broke on Monday, so it's almost old news to a lot of you guys right now, but I kind of want to talk about some of the repercussions behind this.
[SPEAKER_21]: For those of you that may not have heard, get out from under your rock, and here's what's going on.
[SPEAKER_21]: GamePro.com ran this article on Monday that talked about the upcoming DDR Extreme that we're all getting in the US.
[SPEAKER_21]: And in this article, it included some screenshots.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well...
[SPEAKER_21]: Whoopsie daisy, somebody let them have a copy of the already unlocked version of the game and because they showed off the screenshots, they blew about 18 of the unlocks.
[SPEAKER_21]: And I know for, well, I guess I shouldn't say this, I know this for a fact, but I know that one of them was kind of one of the ones that I think Konami kind of wanted to keep a surprise.
[SPEAKER_21]: And that was You're Not Here by Heather from Silent Hill 3.
[SPEAKER_21]: Konami kind of wanted that to be a surprise when the game actually comes out.
[SPEAKER_21]: Whoops!
[SPEAKER_21]: Cover got blown on that one.
[SPEAKER_21]: As well as the cover got blown on 321 Stars, A, Absolute, B4U, the B4ZA beatmix, Trip Machine, Trip Machine Survivor, Sugaru, V, and of course you're not here, and the article went ahead and said, oh by the way, Maximizer's in the game.
[SPEAKER_21]: What did I say?
[SPEAKER_17]: What did I say?
[SPEAKER_17]: Uh-huh, I think so.
[SPEAKER_17]: Now you should listen to me, you fucking idiots.
[SPEAKER_21]: Now, for those that just started listening to the show, what exactly do you mean by that?
[SPEAKER_17]: I only called Maximizer, like, what, how many months ago?
[SPEAKER_17]: How many months ago?
[SPEAKER_17]: It was like at least three or four months ago?
[SPEAKER_17]: Probably even before that?
[SPEAKER_17]: I think it was when DDR Extreme came out for the Japanese console system, so whatever the fuck that was, probably... I don't know, but I called it a long-ass time ago, and everyone said, No!
[SPEAKER_17]: That's so wrong because Max Period's the last one!
[SPEAKER_17]: But, ha!
[SPEAKER_17]: I was right!
[SPEAKER_17]: I like being right.
[SPEAKER_21]: Uh, message from the chatroom, UnknownGamer says, tell Loki to shut the fuck up, he's a dork.
[SPEAKER_21]: WE BAN YOU!
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, um, I'll play You're Not Here for those guys who haven't heard it, because this is an Akira Yamaoka song, it rocks, from Silent Hill 3, I will play that in this next break, but...
[SPEAKER_21]: What do you guys think about this?
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, I forgot to say Sugaru Apple Mix, my bad.
[SPEAKER_21]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, but then the screenshots also revealed that some of the Oni songs now have basic Trip Maniac steps, but some don't.
[SPEAKER_21]: Like the Wild Rush?
[SPEAKER_21]: Don't.
[SPEAKER_21]: But I think, I want to say it was Sugaru?
[SPEAKER_21]: Does.
[SPEAKER_21]: What's up with that?
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, the Apple Mix does.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, I think it was the Apple Mix.
[SPEAKER_21]: I know one of them I was looking at had basic Maniac
[SPEAKER_21]: And it was like, okay, so they went and did them for some, but not for others.
[SPEAKER_17]: It might even be for you, the Before the Beat mix, and I know Hysteria2001, they have basic trick and maniac steps thanks to, what was it, the Dancing Stage games.
[SPEAKER_17]: So, it's very possible those might be your mixed steps.
[SPEAKER_21]: This is true.
[SPEAKER_21]: Somebody told me that the Love at First Sight, you know how the maniac steps were in?
[SPEAKER_21]: There were maniac steps in Dancing Stage, but they were really easy.
[SPEAKER_21]: It was like a four-footer.
[SPEAKER_21]: That is the exact same steps as Max 2 USA's trick steps.
[SPEAKER_21]: Somebody told me that a while back.
[SPEAKER_21]: I never went back to verify that, but it sounds legit.
[SPEAKER_21]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_21]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_18]: But I don't know, any reaction to this?
[SPEAKER_21]: Because I was kind of, with all the clue giving, you know how those folks that work at Konami, they like to give clues, and we had Sigurd here a couple weeks ago, and he was kind of telling us why they don't go to the extreme threat anymore.
[SPEAKER_21]: But nonetheless, they give out clues, they work hard to keep this stuff a secret, and then, kaboom, it's all spoiled.
[SPEAKER_21]: What do you guys think about that?
[SPEAKER_17]: I think it's hilarious, trusting GamePro with anything, because that magazine sucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, me too.
[SPEAKER_17]: They don't even provide free demos.
[SPEAKER_17]: What the hell is that?
[SPEAKER_17]: God damn it.
[SPEAKER_17]: If you want to stay competitive at this day and age, you need to provide free demo discs so that people can steal them out of your magazines.
[SPEAKER_21]: If you have a comment, you can call in on our Skype line if you have something you want to say.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, I'm being told that the challenge songs do not have new steps.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, let me see where I got that from.
[SPEAKER_21]: It was somewhere in that preview story.
[SPEAKER_21]: It talks about the screenshots.
[SPEAKER_21]: Let's see if I can find it.
[SPEAKER_21]: Where one of them had... I'm going to the site, and I'm going to post the link in the chat room if I can find them.
[SPEAKER_21]: There they are.
[SPEAKER_21]: Sugru Apple Mix, light, standard, heavy.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, right there.
[SPEAKER_21]: And they say the screenshot is off-center.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, so maybe somebody was scrolling around or something was going on there.
[SPEAKER_21]: So maybe that's what happened there.
[SPEAKER_21]: Not sure.
[SPEAKER_21]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, looking at it that way, it does look like the song's a little bit off, so maybe the steps hadn't updated yet.
[SPEAKER_21]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_21]: All right, well, nevertheless, it's adding fuel to the fire that there are hidden steps.
[SPEAKER_21]: And Ultramix 2, there we go.
[SPEAKER_21]: GamePro kind of blowing the lid on this stuff.
[SPEAKER_21]: Do you think it could affect them getting demos from Konami in the future?
[SPEAKER_21]: Or do you think Konami's just kind of like, eh, we were done with the extreme people anyway.
[SPEAKER_21]: Forget it.
[SPEAKER_21]: Let the list be spoiled.
[SPEAKER_21]: Or what do you guys think?
[SPEAKER_13]: It was bound to happen anyway.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because you know that always happens.
[SPEAKER_13]: Someone's going to leak a list or something is going to happen that's going to just totally throw off the plan.
[SPEAKER_13]: Although, honestly, I really think that before you print any screen captures or anything, you should run it by, you know, the people who are giving you the authority to do the article.
[SPEAKER_19]: Right.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, that's very true.
[SPEAKER_17]: Very true.
[SPEAKER_21]: Let's go to the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_21]: Zaku's trying to call back, so let's see if we can hear him now.
[SPEAKER_21]: What's up, Zaku?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm hearing... Hold on.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm hearing that...
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I'm hearing Starmine is going to be up for Ultramix 2, is that true?
[SPEAKER_21]: Is there any other Beatmania 2DX songs confirmed?
[SPEAKER_21]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_21]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_21]: some other beat manias actually we're going to talk about Ultramix 2 in a little bit but those are the only ones I can think of off the top of my head but there are brand new ones that are in Ultramix 2 it's pretty cool okay anything else?
[SPEAKER_02]: let me see I'm trying to think right on the light was another one thank you Jason alright alright well if you think of it if you think of it call us back later dude
[SPEAKER_21]: All right, bye.
[SPEAKER_21]: So, yes, Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_21]: A nice little segue in Ultramix 2 because we did get some new songs announced for Ultramix 2 this week.
[SPEAKER_21]: We had two songs announced.
[SPEAKER_21]: Paul Oakenfold doing an Elvis remix of Rubberneckin', which was a fairly popular hit a couple months ago, earlier this year.
[SPEAKER_21]: So it's kind of neat to see that in DDR.
[SPEAKER_21]: And we have a Beatmania song.
[SPEAKER_21]: From Beatmania the final, we have an Athletics song that was confirmed.
[SPEAKER_21]: and the song is Hit and Slap and I'm going to play that for you guys right now.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's only like a little over a minute.
[SPEAKER_21]: So here it is, something you'll be dancing to in Ultra Mix 2 this fall, Athletics with Hit and Slap.
Thank you for watching!
B-Track, HudaWa, Muscatra, Control Your Messalance, WayUnaida
[SPEAKER_21]: Athletics with Hit and Slap, a new song announced for Ultramix 2 this week.
[SPEAKER_21]: Kind of some mixed reaction there in our chatroom that, boy, it's rap, and usually you don't hear a lot of that in DDR.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, I remember when Sigurd was here, he said that Ultramix 2 was kind of...
[SPEAKER_21]: Echo Image with Skulk
[SPEAKER_21]: and of course a song we were lucky enough to be able to announce on air, Zonk with Tittle Tattle.
[SPEAKER_21]: So it's a little weird, but I kind of like it.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's got a different little sound to it.
[SPEAKER_21]: I think it could be fun for DDR with the right steps.
[SPEAKER_21]: And they have promised us, the folks that made Ultramix 2, that the steps this time, different people making them, going to be different stuff.
[SPEAKER_21]: Going to be good stuff.
[SPEAKER_21]: So we will soon see.
[SPEAKER_21]: This November is when they rumored that that game would be out.
[SPEAKER_21]: So we will see.
[SPEAKER_21]: So let's see.
[SPEAKER_21]: Should we go to a break and play the other songs we said we'd play?
[SPEAKER_19]: All right, why not?
[SPEAKER_21]: We're going to play in this break Akira Yamaoka with You're Not Here, which is going to be a song that's going to be in DDR Extreme USA.
[SPEAKER_21]: We're going to play that for you guys.
[SPEAKER_21]: And then we're going to play Paul Oakenfold with Elvis and Rubberneckin, because that's going to be in DDR Ultra Mix 2.
[SPEAKER_21]: So you get a little bit of both mixes.
[SPEAKER_21]: And actually, I encourage you all to go vote in the poll on our website right now, because we're kind of taking a little poll over at OrangeLoungeRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_21]: Look in the upper right-hand corner.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm kind of curious, which...
[SPEAKER_21]: One of these two mixes, are you planning on buying this fall?
[SPEAKER_21]: Or are you going to buy them both?
[SPEAKER_21]: Or are you going to buy neither one?
[SPEAKER_21]: Go to OrangeLawnsRadio.com and look up in the upper right-hand corner.
[SPEAKER_21]: Right now, 41% plan to buy DDR Extreme.
[SPEAKER_21]: 41% also plan to buy both mixes.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_21]: And only 6% plan to buy Ultra Mix 2 only.
[SPEAKER_21]: So it sounds like most people that get Ultra Mix 2 are buying Extreme as well.
[SPEAKER_21]: Kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_21]: But go vote in our poll.
[SPEAKER_21]: OrangeLawnsRadio.com
[SPEAKER_21]: All right, here we go.
[SPEAKER_21]: We're going to go to this break, and we'll start off with Kiri Yamoka from DDR Extreme USA.
[SPEAKER_21]: You're not here.
[SPEAKER_21]: These, by the way, are full versions, so they're about three minutes in length, not the DDR edits.
[SPEAKER_21]: We'll be back.
We'll be back.
[SPEAKER_05]: Blue sky to forever, green grass blows in the wind It would be a much better sight with you, with me If you hadn't met me, I'd be fine on my own, baby Never felt so lonely when you came along
So now what should I do?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm strung out, addicted to you My body aches now that you're gone My sublime fell through You let me give me everything you had and more You craved my happiness when you made me feel torn
and many more.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you for watching.
[SPEAKER_08]: See you next time.
[SPEAKER_21]: And now, as promised, from Ultramix 2, Elvis Presley vs. Paul Oakenfold, Rubberneckin'.
That's all right with me Look and listen, baby My philosophy Call up and back and baby That's all right with me They don't really know Like what I see See why all I count
Thank you.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: From the Step Squad to Orange Lab, this PDR sucks!
[SPEAKER_05]: Holler, holler, holler, holler, holler, holler, holler!
[SPEAKER_21]: Welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_21]: Certainly a different style of music there in Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_21]: I think it's pretty cool, though.
[SPEAKER_21]: I like the direction they're going in.
[SPEAKER_21]: I think a lot of people are kind of getting sick of all the... Now, not me, personally.
[SPEAKER_21]: I love the trance music and the Japanese mixes and stuff, but I think some people... I think there was a call out there for some different stuff, and Ultramix 2 is certainly stepping up and answering that call, so I think it's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: Honestly, I have to say that I was getting kind of tired of the trance myself, but
[SPEAKER_21]: How could you get tired of trance?
[SPEAKER_21]: But that's not to say Ultramix 2 won't have its share of trance.
[SPEAKER_21]: I mean, it does have some trance.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm just getting tired of the happy stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, like, love, love, sugar, cavity.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, that type of stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: And speed mixes.
[SPEAKER_13]: I like the occasional speed mix, but, like, too many of them.
[SPEAKER_21]: Hold on, Rice Princess is calling into the station, wants to say something.
[SPEAKER_21]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_21]: Are you there?
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, if you can hear us, we can't hear you.
[SPEAKER_21]: Double check your mic and call us back.
[SPEAKER_30]: Bummer.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, also as a reminder, when you call us, when our little red circle is on, we're probably not going to see your call because when we're in Do Not Disturb mode, that means we're doing other pieces of show.
[SPEAKER_10]: It means we're doing naughty things.
[SPEAKER_21]: Irene lucked out and I happened to be glancing over when she was calling in there.
[SPEAKER_21]: But it didn't work, that's alright.
[SPEAKER_21]: We'll get back to her later.
[SPEAKER_21]: Meanwhile, I actually wanted to mention this before the show tonight, and I actually kind of want to make doing this a regular thing.
[SPEAKER_21]: Remember how I talked about starting up the Ultramix League?
[SPEAKER_21]: I was actually online on DDR Ultramix before tonight's show, and it was actually kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes, there are still people, believe it or not, that are playing Ultramix.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's amazing.
[SPEAKER_21]: And I was on there playing, and that was the first time you'd ever really seen that in action, huh, DDR Angel?
[SPEAKER_21]: You saw that.
[SPEAKER_21]: What'd you think of that, Angel?
[SPEAKER_21]: The Ultramix stuff.
[SPEAKER_21]: I know I put the voices through the TV for a little bit, too, although you can barely hear it, but what did you think of that?
[SPEAKER_11]: I thought it was really cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: I kind of want one now, see?
[SPEAKER_11]: But then again, I said that last week, so it looks like I need to save up my paychecks and just go for it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Just get everything in a big, fat bundle.
[SPEAKER_11]: If I need to save up until Ultramix 2 comes out, I'll do that, and I'll just buy 1 and 2, the system, just everything, and play.
[SPEAKER_11]: So you have a DDR buddy now.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_21]: Also, what I noticed about Ultramix that I thought was kind of funny is that there's people on there that love to sing along to the songs with their Xbox headsets on so that you can hear.
[SPEAKER_21]: And like, I was playing Count Stop Falling in Love and I heard this girl going, Kids of our love, kids of our love.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh yeah, blame me It's all my fault I blame you
[SPEAKER_13]: I invoke female privilege to just offer my opinion.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm laying down like this so that one side of my nose will drain into the other and I won't be all stuffed up.
[SPEAKER_13]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm not on camera.
[SPEAKER_13]: My feet are.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Look at the webcam, see my feet!
[SPEAKER_13]: Have you played DDRXbox at all?
[SPEAKER_13]: Um, I haven't even unwrapped the shrink wrapping off of it.
[SPEAKER_21]: You should, sometime.
[SPEAKER_13]: I was gonna go download the songpacks, but I got school, I do stuff now.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, I only played for like 30 minutes before the show, it wasn't that much.
[SPEAKER_21]: I would actually sign on to Xbox Live and play live on the show, but I don't know how well the voices would come out.
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't know, should we try logging on right now?
[SPEAKER_21]: See if anybody's on?
[SPEAKER_21]: Sounds like a good time waster.
[SPEAKER_21]: No, Matt doesn't want to try it.
[SPEAKER_21]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_21]: I thought it could be an interesting piece.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's wait and do it when we know it'll work.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm sure it'll work, it's just...
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't think it makes for great radio.
[SPEAKER_21]: The only problem with it is that the music drowns out the people talking.
[SPEAKER_21]: I think it would be hilarious if we could go on there and mess with people live on air, but unfortunately the music of the songs, they totally drown out the voices if you're running it through the TV, so I don't think it's going to work.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh well.
[SPEAKER_13]: This poster is disturbing and frightening.
[SPEAKER_13]: What one?
[SPEAKER_13]: One for Rojin Z, which I've always wanted to see that and never have.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's a really creepy thing.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's a creepy old man.
[SPEAKER_21]: So anyway, my call to those of you that play on Xbox Live, please stop singing.
[SPEAKER_21]: Or wait until Karaoke Revolution Xbox comes out.
[SPEAKER_10]: I am so getting that.
[SPEAKER_21]: See, now the chat room is saying do it.
[SPEAKER_21]: They want us to try it and do it.
[SPEAKER_21]: I should have kept my mouth shut.
[SPEAKER_21]: Maybe after the cage match.
[SPEAKER_21]: I want to give Loki time to set it up if we're going to do it.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, we're going to do the cage match first though.
[SPEAKER_21]: Uh, we will do... Hold on, I'm trying to find Holic.
[SPEAKER_13]: I vote for Holic.
[SPEAKER_21]: We have to set up our wires if we're going to get on DDR Ultramix, so... Hey, Rob.
[SPEAKER_21]: What?
[SPEAKER_13]: If I, like, bring Holic and then, like, add, like, an extra beat to the end, does that count as a remix so I can use Holic?
[SPEAKER_21]: No.
[SPEAKER_13]: Damn.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right.
[SPEAKER_21]: Uh, let's see.
[SPEAKER_21]: We're going to go on to the cage match.
[SPEAKER_21]: I've got to get the song skewed up, though.
[SPEAKER_21]: Before we get to the cage match, let's plug our spin-off shows.
[SPEAKER_21]: Monday night, Diversion, 7 o'clock, Bomani Remixes.
[SPEAKER_21]: It rocks.
[SPEAKER_21]: Listen to it or you suck.
[SPEAKER_21]: Tuesday night.
[SPEAKER_13]: Is Pump Up the Volume?
[SPEAKER_13]: It's supposed to start at 7 for a pre-show, but I usually get really bored and start things around a quarter till, sometimes 6.30.
[SPEAKER_13]: Of course, that's a specific time for all of our other time zone people.
[SPEAKER_13]: 7.30 starts the real show.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because I now have to get up for work at 5.30 in the morning the next day.
[SPEAKER_13]: I have been cutting it off right at 10.30, 11 o'clock.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, if I don't have to do anything the next day, or, you know, if I don't foresee the need for sleep, I'll just keep going, because I'll be like, oh, wait, I'm still running the show, huh?
[SPEAKER_13]: It's supposed to be a request show, but it's really been more or less me just marathoning types of music.
[SPEAKER_13]: The past few weeks I've been playing whole albums.
[SPEAKER_13]: In fact, this past Tuesday I played the Silent Hill 4 US soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_13]: Maren-chan
[SPEAKER_13]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_21]: So, definitely tune in for that.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay, do you want to do Xbox Live before or after Cage Match?
[SPEAKER_21]: Let's do it after.
[SPEAKER_21]: After.
[SPEAKER_21]: Because I said we were going to do after.
[SPEAKER_21]: We'll get some folks some time to sign on there too.
[SPEAKER_21]: Although, we don't want to play against people we know.
[SPEAKER_21]: We want to play against random people so we can mess with them.
[SPEAKER_21]: So don't log on just trying to find us.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's a good thing my name on Xbox Live isn't Orange Lounge Radio or something.
[SPEAKER_21]: So people won't know which one's me.
[SPEAKER_21]: So that's good.
[SPEAKER_21]: Isn't it going to be awesome?
[SPEAKER_21]: What?
[SPEAKER_17]: If, uh, like, they make microphones and shit for, um...
[SPEAKER_17]: The Xbox, you know, karaoke game, and we can plug it in where, like, you know, the normal, um, you know, headset thing would go.
[SPEAKER_17]: Um, I might be able to wire something where our output can go into there.
[SPEAKER_17]: You know, while they're playing, you know, that'd be fun.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, you know, I think you can use just a normal, um, micro, the small jack ones on your, uh, controller.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, because I broke my headset one time for PSO.
[SPEAKER_21]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_13]: And we just went, there was one that got like a radio shack.
[SPEAKER_21]: Maybe we can do something.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, anyway, let's get to the gauge match so we can do the Xbox Live thing.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, the way the cage match works, we have some new people listening tonight, so let me explain this.
[SPEAKER_21]: We're going to play three songs for you guys.
[SPEAKER_21]: Each host brings one song to the table.
[SPEAKER_21]: You pick your favorite of the three songs by placing a private vote in our chat room, www.orangelondradio.com.
[SPEAKER_21]: Click on chat and our kind regulars there will tell you how to place a vote.
[SPEAKER_21]: Remember, you can't vote until all three songs have been played, so wait for me to tell you to vote before you vote.
[SPEAKER_21]: Three songs.
[SPEAKER_21]: You only get to hear a clip of last week's winner, though, because, you know, it's the winner and you heard it last week.
[SPEAKER_21]: So you only get to hear a clip.
[SPEAKER_21]: And last week's winner in this case was... Loki with two-time champion Nuon, which is by, supposedly it's by Outphase.
[SPEAKER_10]: By Phase Out.
[SPEAKER_21]: But we know that the MP3 had to have been mislabeled, so we're calling it Phase Out.
[SPEAKER_21]: So, Phase Out is our two-week-in-a-row winner, and here it is, a clip of last week's winner.
[SPEAKER_21]: Song number one you can vote for tonight, Phase Out with Nuon.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, that was song number one in tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_21]: That was Outphase with Nuon.
[SPEAKER_21]: Song number two comes from... That's not Outphase, actually.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's Phase Out.
[SPEAKER_21]: We're calling it... Song number two comes to us from Jamie.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay, Jamie, you want me to introduce your song, then?
[SPEAKER_21]: Jamie has brought to the table Bond.
[SPEAKER_21]: You know, those four chicks with the violins that play classical music.
[SPEAKER_21]: And it's called Shine.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's the dub Chakra mix.
[SPEAKER_21]: And the reason why she picked this one is, well, she likes...
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, but it has samples from Afronova.
[SPEAKER_21]: It has samples from Afronova in it.
[SPEAKER_21]: And for those that said she picked this song already, she's saying it's a different mix.
[SPEAKER_21]: And I think it is.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, you picked a different one.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, it has Bond and samples of Afronova, so see if you like it.
[SPEAKER_21]: Although it's not really samples of Afronova, it's just the fact... Yeah, they're public domain samples that Afronova also used.
[SPEAKER_13]: The one that I used before was... It started off with a really...
[SPEAKER_13]: I'll play it on Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_13]: I picked a different song before.
[SPEAKER_19]: All right.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's fine.
[SPEAKER_19]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_13]: I played this one on the show before to play the samples.
[SPEAKER_13]: Right.
[SPEAKER_13]: I remember that.
[SPEAKER_21]: I remember that.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right.
[SPEAKER_21]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_21]: Bond with Shine, the Dub Chakra mix with that same sample in Afronova.
[SPEAKER_19]: All right.
[SPEAKER_19]: Here we go.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright, that was song number two.
[SPEAKER_21]: Tonight's cage match, that was Bond with Shine, the Dub Chakra mix.
[SPEAKER_19]: What do you guys think of that one?
[SPEAKER_13]: I really like that song, it's just really laid back, I listen to it all the time.
[SPEAKER_13]: It gets a 9 from me, I mean I've listened to it a whole bunch.
[SPEAKER_13]: but I intended to use it for cage match once and never did so I just figured I may as well do it now.
[SPEAKER_13]: I played it on my show a few times.
[SPEAKER_13]: I just really think it's different.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's really different.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_19]: Jonas.
[SPEAKER_26]: I give it a 9 out of 10.
[SPEAKER_26]: It's pretty good, soothing.
[SPEAKER_26]: I don't have that Afronuva part I heard.
[SPEAKER_26]: Other than that, it's very well done with the violin and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_19]: All right.
[SPEAKER_19]: A scale of 110?
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_19]: I missed the knife.
[SPEAKER_19]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_19]: Angel?
[SPEAKER_11]: Damn it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: The mic's working.
[SPEAKER_11]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_11]: I heard myself.
9.5.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: I like it.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's Bond.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's like a given.
[SPEAKER_20]: All right.
[SPEAKER_20]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_17]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_17]: Honestly, the samples of whatever, Afronova, the tribal people do not fit in the song at all.
[SPEAKER_17]: But, whatever, you know, it's Bond.
[SPEAKER_17]: So I'm going to give it a lower score because it's Bond.
[SPEAKER_17]: Because Bond doesn't do any original shit.
[SPEAKER_17]: Anyway, so they're going to get a 7.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, because I just, you know, I've heard that song and I'm just tired of them.
[SPEAKER_17]: You know, they can stop anytime.
[SPEAKER_17]: Uh, Bradley.
[SPEAKER_24]: I thought it was really cool.
[SPEAKER_24]: What was the beat?
[SPEAKER_24]: Give it a 9.
[SPEAKER_21]: I actually like that song a lot.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's a song.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm just not sure I'm down with it for like a cage match.
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's bouncy, dancey as the others.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think it would be very freestyle-able.
[SPEAKER_13]: We were talking about that.
[SPEAKER_21]: I give it an 8.
[SPEAKER_21]: As a song, I give it a 9.
[SPEAKER_21]: As a cage match pick, I give it an 8.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_21]: My turn.
[SPEAKER_21]: and I've picked a song by a band that's actually already in rotation on our station because they were on one of the Fantasia albums.
[SPEAKER_21]: They're a really popular trance band.
[SPEAKER_21]: They're on Robbins Entertainment here in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_21]: Same label as Ian Vandal and Paul Oaken... No, he's not on that label.
[SPEAKER_21]: Ian Vandal and DJ Sammy is another big one on that label.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm kind of surprised they haven't ended up in DDR yet.
[SPEAKER_21]: The band is Lasko and this is their brand new single that just came out.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's called Surrender.
[SPEAKER_21]: Just came out in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_21]: this week, actually.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's been out in Britain a little while, but just came out in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_21]: this week.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's my pick, Lasko with Surrender.
[SPEAKER_21]: Enjoy.
[SPEAKER_05]: I said I can't trust you, I don't know Every time I'm near you, I lose control I must be out of my mind to let you in
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, that was song number three in tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_21]: That was Lasko with Surrender.
[SPEAKER_21]: Let's see what everybody thought of that.
[SPEAKER_21]: Jamie.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm going to say the same thing that I say every week.
[SPEAKER_13]: Trance is old.
[SPEAKER_13]: Trance is very boring.
[SPEAKER_13]: You have to be in the mood for it and too much is too much of anything.
[SPEAKER_13]: However, that was still good.
[SPEAKER_13]: I like the song.
[SPEAKER_13]: But I'm just so burned out on Trance right now that I can't
[SPEAKER_13]: I actually heard this song before in one of the Dream Dance volumes, I think.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'll give it an 8.5.
[SPEAKER_13]: I have some repeated samples.
[SPEAKER_26]: It kind of sounded a little repetitive, but the singing was pretty good, and it still sounds pretty good.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right.
[SPEAKER_21]: Angel.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, let's see.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know I'm a Lascaux fangirl, so you know it's going to get a 10 from me.
[SPEAKER_21]: At least I got one supporter.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_21]: 10 from Angel.
[SPEAKER_21]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_21]: It gets a 10 because it's not Bond.
[SPEAKER_20]: Ouch.
[SPEAKER_20]: And a glare.
[SPEAKER_20]: I see a glare coming from Jamie.
[SPEAKER_20]: All right.
[SPEAKER_20]: Arcadian.
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_24]: To me, it's like the quintessential trance pop song.
[SPEAKER_24]: Like if somebody were to say, Rob, play me some trance pop, I'd play that.
[SPEAKER_24]: I like it.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's cute.
[SPEAKER_24]: I give it a 9.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay, here it is.
[SPEAKER_21]: We're going to recap the three songs you can vote for tonight.
[SPEAKER_21]: Let's see if Nuon goes three weeks in a row, or if we get Bond or Lasko as the new champ tonight.
[SPEAKER_21]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_21]: Here's a recap.
[SPEAKER_21]: Song number one, Phase Out with Nuon.
[SPEAKER_21]: I always pick that clip.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't like it.
[SPEAKER_21]: Song number two tonight is Bond with Shine, the dub Chakra Mix.
[SPEAKER_21]: And song number three tonight is Lasko with Surrender.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright guys, place vote now.
[SPEAKER_21]: You may place your vote in the chat room by sending a private message to Sky in the chat room with your votes.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_21]: As promised, we're going to try this horrible...
[SPEAKER_21]: Experiment Out.
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't think this is going to go over very well, but the chatroom asked we do it, so we're going to get on to Xbox Live and harass people randomly on Ultramix, alright?
[SPEAKER_21]: So, let's see, I have to get suited up here, though.
[SPEAKER_21]: Let me head over to get suited up.
[SPEAKER_21]: Let me get the mic over.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, so you'll have to say bye to the chatroom for a minute, Jamie, because we're going to switch it over.
[SPEAKER_21]: And I have to get suited up.
[SPEAKER_21]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_21]: Somebody talk while I get suited up.
[SPEAKER_13]: Ah, he's putting on the headset.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, I remember that thing.
[SPEAKER_13]: I remember having an indention in the side of my head from playing Phantasy Star Online for six hours.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm kind of glad I quit.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, Rob...
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright, wait, are we going to switch the cam over to Xbox, right?
[SPEAKER_19]: Eh, it'll be fine.
[SPEAKER_19]: Hold on, we're going to switch the cam over to Xbox real fast.
[SPEAKER_21]: My headset broke, we have a catastrophe.
[SPEAKER_30]: There, put it over here.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm getting suited up, sorry guys, I broke my headset.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright guys, first things first, I have to make sure that both my mics are working.
[SPEAKER_21]: Then I have to set it up so that we can hear the voices through the TV, which hopefully we will.
[SPEAKER_21]: So I just changed the settings so that the voices will come through the TV so hopefully you guys can hear the folks that chat with me on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_21]: Now, chat listeners, don't join the game just because we're in it.
[SPEAKER_21]: I know who you are.
[SPEAKER_21]: So I'm going to set up a match.
[SPEAKER_21]: And let's do a light song because I'm going to pretend to be somebody that doesn't know how to play DDR.
[SPEAKER_21]: And then I'm going to regulate the game, okay?
[SPEAKER_21]: So let's see.
[SPEAKER_20]: Let's do... You want to do DXY?
[SPEAKER_20]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_20]: They want DXY.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's the old DXY banner.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, so we're going to do a match on DXY.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay, let's see if anybody joins.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm going to do three public slots.
[SPEAKER_21]: We'll see if anybody joins.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm going to mute my mic for now.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, so I'm waiting for people to join the match.
[SPEAKER_21]: So we'll see what happens here.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think you'd get more players if you were in a harder setting.
[SPEAKER_21]: No, actually, you'd be surprised.
[SPEAKER_21]: You get a lot of people on the light settings here.
[SPEAKER_21]: So we're going to see if anyone joins.
[SPEAKER_21]: Loki, any feedback from our chatroom?
[SPEAKER_21]: Because you're a little closer to the chatroom over there.
[SPEAKER_21]: I know you're overworked here on this show.
[SPEAKER_21]: They're talking about... Leave it to somebody to try and ruin the goddamn... Did you see what happened there?
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, somebody's trying to come in and ruin our live experiment here.
[SPEAKER_21]: But that's okay.
[SPEAKER_21]: I think I can block them.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm going to try that again.
[SPEAKER_21]: Who do you think?
[SPEAKER_21]: Who always wants attention on this show?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, the moron?
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm pretty sure I can boot him.
[SPEAKER_21]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_21]: Hold on here.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm pretty sure we can do this.
[SPEAKER_21]: Let's try this again.
[SPEAKER_21]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_21]: If they join, they're muted, so we wouldn't be able to hear them, so it doesn't know good to join anymore.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right.
[SPEAKER_21]: God, I love Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_21]: Let's try this again.
[SPEAKER_21]: Now we're sitting in there waiting for somebody to hopefully join, so... Blocked.
[SPEAKER_13]: Ha ha.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, they're not blocked, we just can't hear them.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know.
[SPEAKER_21]: So they can do whatever they want.
[SPEAKER_13]: So it doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, it doesn't matter what they say.
[SPEAKER_13]: Stupid idiot.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right.
[SPEAKER_21]: I actually wonder if there's a way we can... Try booting.
[SPEAKER_21]: There is no boot option.
[SPEAKER_21]: You know what, chat room?
[SPEAKER_21]: If this is all we're going to get is one loser with nothing better to do, then we're going to end this segment.
[SPEAKER_21]: And you guys suck for suggesting we should do it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I wonder if you can send a screaming feedback.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm not going to bother.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm just going to... The thing's muted, so they can't do anything anyway.
[SPEAKER_21]: There's no good to be on.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, we got somebody.
[SPEAKER_21]: Finally.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes, we got a match.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay, now hopefully everybody says they can start.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, take your mic down.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll do commentary.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_13]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_13]: Are you ready?
[SPEAKER_03]: Dance!
[SPEAKER_19]: Does anyone know how to play this game?
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't stop, Player 3!
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh yeah!
[SPEAKER_06]: Player 2!
[SPEAKER_06]: It looks like Player 1 can take this one!
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, let's hear it!
Player 2-0 on fire!
Player 1 has the advantage!
[SPEAKER_06]: Call the fire department!
[SPEAKER_06]: We've got a five alarm dancer!
[SPEAKER_05]: Just disturbed, guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, God!
[SPEAKER_05]: Quick, call the fire department!
[SPEAKER_05]: We've got a five alarm dancer!
Oh, no!
[SPEAKER_06]: I missed like one step at the end there.
I'm so excited.
I got three points.
[SPEAKER_21]: Those guys were losers.
[SPEAKER_21]: They didn't even talk at all.
[SPEAKER_21]: What a waste of a segment that was.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm never letting the chatroom pick a segment for us again.
[SPEAKER_21]: You know the only good thing we got out of that segment was getting to hear DXY.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_21]: What?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'd like to play the chatroom.
[SPEAKER_21]: You want to play against chatroom listeners?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I would like to... Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, we'll switch it back over to chat.
[SPEAKER_21]: Don't worry about that.
[SPEAKER_21]: Loki's getting to work.
[SPEAKER_21]: Great.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_21]: What a fun thing that that was.
[SPEAKER_21]: What did we get?
[SPEAKER_21]: We got one person with nothing better to do than to stalk this show.
[SPEAKER_21]: And we got two people who didn't even talk when we tried to, you know, get them to say stuff.
[SPEAKER_21]: Boring.
[SPEAKER_21]: I think someone has a... And everybody got to see me break my combo at the end there and see what a horrible DDR player I am.
God.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, I was going to come up on the show today and apologize for, you know, bringing old drama...
[SPEAKER_21]: You can't apologize for something that somebody else keeps perpetuating.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's fucked up.
[SPEAKER_13]: You need to stop that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Here.
[SPEAKER_13]: That message in the chat room is for Loki.
[SPEAKER_13]: He's mumbling incoherently at the stupidity of some people.
[SPEAKER_21]: At least I won, so I feel a little better.
[SPEAKER_21]: At least I didn't get my ass kicked.
[SPEAKER_13]: At least dumbass got nearly last.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, that made me feel a little better.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's pathetic.
[SPEAKER_21]: No.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, I guess what we'll do is we'll go to our break, and when we come back, we'll find out the winner of tonight's cage match, and we'll do the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_21]: But please don't send the FUs yet, because we'll get to those a little bit later.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay, guys?
[SPEAKER_21]: I've still got to tally the cage match votes.
[SPEAKER_21]: So in this break, what do we want to hear in this break?
[SPEAKER_21]: We want to hear... Let's do five-key stuff.
[SPEAKER_21]: I want to hear five-key stuff.
[SPEAKER_21]: I want to hear Prince on a Star.
[SPEAKER_21]: So we're going to hear Prince on a Star.
[SPEAKER_13]: You have to play Lin 1999.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right.
[SPEAKER_21]: Jamie wants to hear Lin 1999.
[SPEAKER_21]: And how about the Metal Gear Solid song from Beatmania 3?
[SPEAKER_13]: Hey, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right.
[SPEAKER_21]: We'll be back after this.
[SPEAKER_21]: Enjoy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching!
I want to see why a white woman will not stay when she's gone
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_25]: Solid Snake, Solid Snake, Solid Snake, can you hear what I'm saying?
[SPEAKER_25]: Well, this time the chicken man, better watch your back I'm gonna kick your ass, beat him, kill him, oh Don't, what am I gonna do?
[SPEAKER_25]: Don't, what am I gonna do?
[SPEAKER_25]: Don't, don't Have you ever seen a cool game like this?
[SPEAKER_21]: After this song, we'll be having a Let Them Move Marathon.
[SPEAKER_05]: No!
[SPEAKER_21]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_21]: Orange Lounge Radio, Crap Free Bobani Radio.
[SPEAKER_21]: We are back with Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_21]: Hey, can you hear me?
[SPEAKER_15]: A long time listener, first time caller I really like that show you play on Wednesdays, what's it called?
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, that's a good show, everybody should listen to that Hey, that would be a great time, I think everybody should listen to that show
[SPEAKER_15]: And is it true you guys are going to play a remix of that song, what's it called, from Silent Hill 4?
[SPEAKER_21]: Which one?
[SPEAKER_21]: The Your Rain?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, aren't you going to play a Your Rain remix?
[SPEAKER_15]: I heard about that.
[SPEAKER_21]: That was a couple weeks ago that we did that.
[SPEAKER_15]: What?
[SPEAKER_21]: We did that a couple weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_15]: Are you saying I missed it?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yes, you missed it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, fuck!
[SPEAKER_21]: You know what, just for you, kind sir, I'll play it again later in the show.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, you're welcome very much.
[SPEAKER_21]: Thanks for calling.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right, bye.
[SPEAKER_21]: See, that's a good Skype call right there.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: I've played it every week on my show.
[SPEAKER_21]: Have you?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes, I have.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, then, you know.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because I marathoned the Silent Hill 4 U.S.
[SPEAKER_13]: soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, people should turn it in.
[SPEAKER_13]: If people listened, they would know.
[SPEAKER_21]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_13]: No one ever requests anything on my show, either.
[SPEAKER_21]: So Skype line's open if you want to call in.
[SPEAKER_13]: Call us.
[SPEAKER_13]: Pick up the phone.
[SPEAKER_21]: 1-900-HOT-POTATO I had to block some people there because certain people are still trying to get through.
[SPEAKER_13]: Some people never learn.
[SPEAKER_21]: Hey, I'm just glad they're listening and keeping our ratings up.
[SPEAKER_21]: This is good.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_13]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_13]: I have a theory.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think that
[SPEAKER_13]: There was no sperm involved in that person's creation.
[SPEAKER_20]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think that it was Jell-O.
[SPEAKER_21]: Let's talk about who won tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_21]: We have a new winner in tonight's cage match, finally.
[SPEAKER_21]: Finally, Loki has to pick a new song, because we have a new winner.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't have to do shit next week.
[SPEAKER_21]: Bond won the cage match, and better yet, we're getting another call.
[SPEAKER_21]: Howdy, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_21]: Hey, it is Dark Knight.
[SPEAKER_21]: Hey, Dark Knight, how you doing?
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm alright, how about y'all?
[SPEAKER_14]: We're pretty good, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_14]: Not much, I'll tell you what, that last call should make Classic Call of the Week.
[SPEAKER_20]: Yeah, I think we should make that Classic Call of the Week.
[SPEAKER_20]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_20]: I'll just put the blunt side of it.
[SPEAKER_18]: You don't want to do anything to try and one-up that call?
[SPEAKER_21]: I can't come up with anything close.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, alright.
[SPEAKER_21]: Hey, what do you think about how Ultramix 2 is shaping up?
[SPEAKER_21]: With some of those new songs announced this week.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's pretty decent, but I'm still like, no Xbox for me, I'm not touching it.
[SPEAKER_21]: It was so hard for a long time to have to kind of finally say, oh, I gotta cave and buy the Xbox, but I tell you what, once I got it, there was actually some decent games on it.
[SPEAKER_21]: One or two, but DDR is one of them, so it's worth it.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's worth it.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'll tell you what, though, on that suggestion about having other people play against you, like somebody said, Chamberlain, why you didn't play a hard song?
[SPEAKER_21]: because I wanted other people that don't listen to the show to come into the game and play and we would kind of mess with them a little bit like I'd say I'd never played DDR before and hopefully they would talk because usually the lamer people are the ones that play the light songs so I sort of was trying to bait some of the younger players and stuff but it didn't work we only got a couple losers that can't get over themselves that wanted to join and people that don't talk so what can you do?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey Dark Knight Hey Angel Hi
[SPEAKER_11]: Hi, this is Dark Knight.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_11]: And he's cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hey, Rob.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_13]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_21]: What?
[SPEAKER_13]: We've got Dark Knight on the phone.
[SPEAKER_13]: What are you talking to me for?
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, I'm going to let him go now.
[SPEAKER_21]: So, you take care, Dark Knight.
[SPEAKER_21]: Thanks for calling.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Have a good night.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_21]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_21]: You know, Zeno in our chat room raises...
[SPEAKER_21]: Zeno in our chatroom raises a point about the folks on Ultramix.
[SPEAKER_21]: There's hardly anybody that wants to play the heavy stuff because a lot of them are actually on dance pads.
[SPEAKER_21]: And it's kind of hard to play heavy stuff on dance pads.
[SPEAKER_21]: So he says nobody plays heavy.
[SPEAKER_21]: And from what I've seen, that's kind of true.
[SPEAKER_21]: Zaku's calling back, so I thought we'd pick up his call.
[SPEAKER_21]: What's up, Zaku?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just wondering, what are the chances of another...
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, spit it out.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just wondering exactly why, you know, why does Microsoft have favoritism towards, you know, why do they have favoritism towards Konami in that sense?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because they get downloaded songs, and while PS2 users get crapped on, because even though we already have a hard drive, there's no way in God's green earth we're actually going to be able to download songs, so we're basically screwed.
[SPEAKER_21]: Good points.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm going to go ahead and let you go because our connection is a little crappy, but I'm going to talk about this point.
[SPEAKER_21]: So tune back into the show.
[SPEAKER_21]: We're going to talk about this, okay?
[SPEAKER_21]: Why is it that Ultramix 2 folks get to download songs but the PS2 folks don't?
[SPEAKER_21]: Why do you think that is?
[SPEAKER_21]: My own thought is that I think they've been trying to take PS2 games in one direction and Ultramix in the other direction because if PS2 had everything the Xbox game had, same song list, same everything, you wouldn't buy both of them.
[SPEAKER_22]: I would.
[SPEAKER_21]: The few hardcore folks that would just be all about supporting Bomani, yes, they still would.
[SPEAKER_21]: But the majority of people would not buy both games.
[SPEAKER_21]: But if PS2 is allowed to have its iToy thing going one way, and Xbox has its live thing going one way, then, you know...
[SPEAKER_21]: That's, to me, kind of, I think, Konami trying to shape both games in a way.
[SPEAKER_13]: They're taking two of the strongest points of each system and making that the focal point.
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't think it has anything to do with Microsoft sucking Konami off to get them to do that or anything, although I do know that Microsoft uses DDR Ultramix to show other developers, hey, look what you can do with a game and how you can make money, because they've been making a lot of money off those songpacks.
[SPEAKER_21]: So...
[SPEAKER_21]: GameCube
[SPEAKER_21]: I mean, sucks to be a GameCube user, because you're never going to see a DDR mix, probably.
[SPEAKER_13]: Probably not.
[SPEAKER_13]: The only thing the GameCube has going for it as far as online play is the new PSO that's coming out for it, but apart from that... Yeah, I mean, but that has nothing to do with Konami and stuff.
[SPEAKER_21]: Again, it's nothing to do with favoritism or... PS2 just has, of the three, the worst online.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, seriously.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's not all that strong.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, I talk to people who get booted off of it all the time.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, Xbox is built to be an online system.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, you have to look... You know, I look at it this way.
[SPEAKER_13]: A system is only as good as the games that are on it.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I have said this, you know, since the days where people are going, Well, the Saturn sucks.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, no, it doesn't.
[SPEAKER_13]: You're just playing games that suck.
[SPEAKER_13]: But if you take a look at the Xbox, it's built with the online capacity.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's built with a hard drive.
[SPEAKER_13]: Look at the PS2.
[SPEAKER_13]: These are peripherals, you know.
[SPEAKER_13]: These are things that were added on later.
[SPEAKER_13]: The first model PS2, I have a Japanese PlayStation 2, it doesn't have anywhere to put a hard drive in it, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_13]: It has to have an external hard drive.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's an afterthought.
[SPEAKER_13]: You have to look at what a system is built to do and then see, well, am I going to use this capacity that the machine has?
[SPEAKER_21]: I do understand though the points being brought up, but it just kind of sucks that you have to pay an Xbox Live fee over and above, because on PS2 you don't usually have to pay extra fees, maybe certain games, but on Xbox, if you want to play anything online, you've got to pay that extra fee.
[SPEAKER_13]: What's $10 a month?
[SPEAKER_13]: It's nothing.
[SPEAKER_21]: But it's still, I mean, it's a lot of money.
[SPEAKER_13]: But a lot of the games that have online don't often require that you pay for the online with the game.
[SPEAKER_13]: They're getting their back in this.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, that's sort of the trade-off is that then the games don't really charge.
[SPEAKER_13]: The only games that I really see justifying having that extra fee, like for example, Phantasy Star Online, because they have to keep the servers up, right?
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, it costs for maintenance there, so of course they're going to have to charge what the $9 a month that it is.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's the thing is that
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, you're paying that little bit a month for the Xbox Live, but for most of the other online, you're getting that for free.
[SPEAKER_13]: And then some of the others, you're paying a very minimal amount to get it over.
[SPEAKER_21]: But then, of course, it comes up the fact that Xbox Live doesn't support dial-up.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, that's just because it's so intense, all the bandwidth.
[SPEAKER_21]: I mean, you saw while we were playing there, we have voice going over.
[SPEAKER_21]: You can't do it dial-up.
[SPEAKER_21]: You can do dial-up, but you have to get extra stuff, right?
[SPEAKER_21]: How would you hook that up, Loki?
[SPEAKER_21]: Hell if I know.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_21]: I know you can do it.
[SPEAKER_13]: If you go to the Microsoft site, I think that they have a dial-up adapter.
[SPEAKER_21]: There's a way to do it.
[SPEAKER_21]: I think over on DDR Freak there's a thread about how to get the service packs with dial-up.
[SPEAKER_21]: I know somebody wrote an FAQ on that.
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't remember who or where it's at, but...
[SPEAKER_13]: On top of that though, these days there's hardly any excuse not to have broadband.
[SPEAKER_21]: You may still live in an area that doesn't have it.
[SPEAKER_21]: Very possible.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, if you live in an area that doesn't have it, that's understandable.
[SPEAKER_13]: But if you're thinking of expense, broadband now is sometimes cheaper than another phone line.
[SPEAKER_21]: Very true.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, I'll open up the Skype line for a little bit more here, see if anybody wants to call in, but otherwise we're going to get into the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_21]: We did, by the way, boys and girls, we had another net split, so about half our chat room can't get in.
[SPEAKER_21]: So let's take this call.
[SPEAKER_21]: Our old buddy Jason's calling in.
[SPEAKER_21]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_30]: Hello, Rob.
[SPEAKER_21]: Hi, Jason.
[SPEAKER_21]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_30]: I just heard you guys start mentioning the ILF Connections to Xbox Live and thought I'd give you a ring again.
[SPEAKER_22]: Okay, yeah, what's up?
[SPEAKER_30]: Well, you know, as we all know now, as soon as DDR Freak comes back up... Yeah, it's down today.
[SPEAKER_22]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_22]: Who broke it?
[SPEAKER_22]: Did you break it?
[SPEAKER_30]: I talked Blue and J-Dog, and they're hashing something out, so they'll get it up, hopefully sometime tonight, if not tomorrow morning.
[SPEAKER_20]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm sorry I broke it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I was just too much for it, you know?
[SPEAKER_22]: She coughed on it, and it broke.
[SPEAKER_13]: It caught my cooties.
[SPEAKER_22]: What's up with the dial-up stuff in Xbox Live?
[SPEAKER_30]: So when it's back up, there's two really good resources that Cutris posted in the console games forum.
[SPEAKER_30]: One of them is dial-up users that want to connect to Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_30]: It's basically you have to get a connection on your computer and then have a way of running another network cable out to the Xbox, because that's the only way of plugging it in, and then do internet connection sharing so Xbox connects.
[SPEAKER_30]: and then it just uses your PC's bandwidth to, well, to do the work.
[SPEAKER_22]: What a pain in the ass.
[SPEAKER_30]: It's something that I did for a while before I got my router, as a matter of fact.
[SPEAKER_22]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_30]: ZXP makes it really, really easy.
[SPEAKER_30]: If you have anything else, Google.
[SPEAKER_18]: All right, Google.
[SPEAKER_18]: All right, well, thanks for the tip, Jason.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm sure some of our listeners appreciate that.
[SPEAKER_30]: No problem.
[SPEAKER_22]: All right, you have a good one, buddy.
[SPEAKER_22]: Anything else you wanted to say?
[SPEAKER_22]: Anything else about Ultramix or any of that stuff?
[SPEAKER_30]: They'll appreciate it a lot more as soon as DDR Free comes back up and they can actually read how to do it.
[SPEAKER_18]: Hey, was it just me or did that Ultramix segment kind of suck?
[SPEAKER_30]: The start of it sucked.
[SPEAKER_30]: Yeah, it did.
[SPEAKER_30]: Nobody talked.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, well.
[SPEAKER_21]: I tried, Jason.
[SPEAKER_21]: I tried for you.
[SPEAKER_30]: You're very good for doing so.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, take care.
[SPEAKER_21]: Thanks.
[SPEAKER_22]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_22]: We're actually getting a lot of people on Skype now.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_22]: So, open it up one more time.
[SPEAKER_22]: See if anybody else wants to call in.
[SPEAKER_22]: If not, we'll go into the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm kind of waiting for our net thing to reconnect.
[SPEAKER_22]: So...
[SPEAKER_22]: BlackDevilRx, what's on your mind tonight?
[SPEAKER_16]: Not much, I was just sitting here listening to the whole Ultramix thing.
[SPEAKER_22]: Little program we have, right?
[SPEAKER_22]: Have you ever listened to the show before?
[SPEAKER_16]: No, actually, this is my first time.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, it kind of sucks, huh?
[SPEAKER_22]: No, it's alright, it's alright.
[SPEAKER_22]: I think we suck.
[SPEAKER_22]: Don't answer that.
[SPEAKER_22]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_22]: What do you think about Ultramix 2 coming out?
[SPEAKER_18]: I mean, I don't know, I just kind of see how this works.
[SPEAKER_18]: Are we your guinea pigs for testing this program?
[SPEAKER_16]: Sort of.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, well, that's all right.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, what do you think about the new DDR games coming out this fall?
[SPEAKER_22]: Are you planning on picking one of them up?
[SPEAKER_16]: I think they're both great.
[SPEAKER_16]: I mean, they have, you know, an awesome selections of, awesome selections, really.
[SPEAKER_22]: What do you think about the whole fact that PS2 is not online and Xbox doesn't have iToy?
[SPEAKER_22]: Why do you think, what's your opinion on that?
[SPEAKER_22]: Why do you think the games are going in completely different directions?
[SPEAKER_16]: I don't know, I mean, they're both made by different companies, as I understand, and they're, you know, PS2 has the eye toy thing.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, so sort of, you're referring to those rumors that Harmonix had something to do with Xtreme, right?
[SPEAKER_18]: Uh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_22]: From what I understand, those were proven to be false to some extent.
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't know the details on that, but regardless.
[SPEAKER_16]: But we have Konami of Hawaii.
[SPEAKER_22]: I can't really go...
[SPEAKER_16]: There's some sort of thing that's wrong.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm getting some sort of double post, like some sort of echo.
[SPEAKER_22]: Turn down your Win app because you're hearing us twice.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's why.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's all right.
[SPEAKER_22]: Don't panic.
[SPEAKER_22]: Everything will be okay.
[SPEAKER_22]: Okay, you're talking about how Ultramix is made in Hawaii and Extreme is made in Japan, right?
[SPEAKER_22]: Kind of that?
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_22]: All right.
[SPEAKER_22]: So you think maybe that has to do with it?
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's an interesting theory.
[SPEAKER_22]: All right.
[SPEAKER_22]: Anything else you want to share?
[SPEAKER_16]: No, that's it.
[SPEAKER_22]: All right.
[SPEAKER_22]: Have a good one, buddy.
[SPEAKER_16]: All right.
[SPEAKER_16]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_22]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm liking this Skype line thing now that people actually use it.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, let's get into the FUs of the week, shall we?
[SPEAKER_21]: Actually, wait.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, there was one more person we hadn't heard from that was trying to call in.
[SPEAKER_21]: So I'm going to see if that person can get through.
[SPEAKER_21]: If you've already called us this segment, please don't call back.
[SPEAKER_21]: I can't pick up because we already talked to you.
[SPEAKER_21]: But there was somebody else trying to get through that we hadn't talked to yet.
[SPEAKER_21]: I was going to give them a chance to get through.
[SPEAKER_21]: Let's see if they call.
[SPEAKER_21]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_21]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_21]: This is certainly a new thing for us, too.
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't know of any other internet radio station that does this for their listeners, where they can talk on Skype and stuff.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, yeah, there's one.
[SPEAKER_21]: I forgot that they do that, too.
[SPEAKER_21]: Bad Me.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, our parent station, Understation Live.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right, for that, for my mistake, I will give them a free plug.
[SPEAKER_21]: www.understationlive.org.
[SPEAKER_21]: Listen.
[SPEAKER_13]: They're awesome.
[SPEAKER_13]: Travis and Jenna.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_21]: They're still doing their show on, like, Saturdays, right?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, and they have spinoffs occasionally, too.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Speaking of which, we have to give a shout out to the baby, because the baby turned one this week.
[SPEAKER_21]: Aww, their baby turned one.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_21]: Big radio baby.
[SPEAKER_11]: Kira.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, I guess that person didn't want to call in, so we'll give them another chance later.
[SPEAKER_21]: But for now, we're going to do the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay, now this is the way the FUs of the week is going to work tonight.
[SPEAKER_21]: If you are on the wrong end of the split, you can send an email with your FUs.
[SPEAKER_21]: Here's the address.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm only going to give it once.
[SPEAKER_21]: Get a pen and paper ready.
[SPEAKER_21]: Ready?
[SPEAKER_21]: Rob, R-O-B, at OrangeLoungeRadio.com If you have FUs and you can't get them in on the chat room because of the split, send them over email.
[SPEAKER_21]: Rob at OrangeLoungeRadio.com Ooh, I did it twice.
[SPEAKER_21]: I said I only do it once.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_21]: Let's get to tonight's FUs.
[SPEAKER_21]: Jamie's.
[SPEAKER_21]: Jamie, why do we do the FUs of the week?
[SPEAKER_13]: We're so full of anger.
[SPEAKER_13]: A big F you goes to my damn nose for being full of snot.
[SPEAKER_13]: I hate you allergies.
[SPEAKER_13]: I hate you.
[SPEAKER_13]: I hate pollen.
[SPEAKER_13]: I hate the trees.
[SPEAKER_13]: I hate the grass.
[SPEAKER_13]: I hate the little animals.
[SPEAKER_13]: I hate anything that's setting off my allergies right now.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, I don't hate Shermie though.
[SPEAKER_13]: She's forgiven.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because Shermie is, of course, the official cat of Warner Sounds Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: Also, F you to the H2 for looking stupid.
[SPEAKER_13]: And F you to the Hummer for being expensive, because I want one.
[SPEAKER_13]: Another big F you goes toward it being so busy at work because it's hard to talk with my...
[SPEAKER_13]: FU to it getting hot again.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was nice and cool for a few days, and then the hot came back.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was like 97 degrees today, that sucked.
[SPEAKER_13]: Um, and FU goes toward, uh, shoot, I had another one to name.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, my air conditioning for not working.
[SPEAKER_13]: And also to, uh,
[SPEAKER_13]: The repair guy, I don't know if it's the repair guy or my apartment complex manager.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, she's nice and everything, but... The first time the repair guy came in, he just put Freon in it, and it was cool for like three hours.
[SPEAKER_13]: And then it got hot again.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I called the apartment manager to have the guy come back and do it again, and I don't think he ever came, so I'm having Dan go talk to her.
[SPEAKER_13]: Dan is 6'4", okay?
[SPEAKER_13]: Dan is very tall and very large.
[SPEAKER_13]: And when he asks somebody to do something, usually they will.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_21]: Not that you're threatening or anything.
[SPEAKER_13]: Not that we're threatening, no.
[SPEAKER_13]: I hate my nose again, because, like, at least it's not dripping like it was earlier, because it was, like, all day, and I was sneezing all day.
[SPEAKER_13]: But, like, the left side was all blocked up, and now the right side is, and I, like, want it to make up its mind just not to be blocked up.
[SPEAKER_13]: And also, a big F you to Benadryl.
[SPEAKER_13]: Where Benadryl works, it, like, makes me all, like, goofy.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, I hate my sentences and everything.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, that's it.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, then, let's move on to Loki and his FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, so, my fault, actually.
[SPEAKER_17]: I bit on the wrong wire, the wrong magnet wire, because I could have gotten this other stuff much cheaper, and it would have been much better for what I'm doing.
[SPEAKER_17]: And, um, so that sucks.
[SPEAKER_17]: And then also...
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't know, really nothing else to be mad about.
[SPEAKER_17]: Just stupid drivers in general.
[SPEAKER_17]: People just
[SPEAKER_17]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_17]: It's like these factors.
[SPEAKER_17]: I swear, people do not need to be on cell phones while driving.
[SPEAKER_17]: I never answer my cell phone while driving.
[SPEAKER_17]: So, that really sucks.
[SPEAKER_17]: And, um, other than that, really not too much else to be mad about.
[SPEAKER_17]: Other than, um, you know, McDonald's food sucking, but I keep eating it for some reason.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's all.
[SPEAKER_19]: My turn.
[SPEAKER_19]: All right.
[SPEAKER_19]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_21]: My FU of the week basically goes to, now don't get me wrong, I absolutely love my job, but work on Friday, I just had it.
[SPEAKER_21]: I reached my breaking point Friday where I was like, Calgon, take me away.
[SPEAKER_21]: And I'm not looking forward to next week incredibly much either.
[SPEAKER_21]: But I'll get over it.
[SPEAKER_21]: I do love my job and I love the people I work with.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's just that there's too much drama sometimes.
[SPEAKER_18]: I can't deal with it.
[SPEAKER_18]: Also an FU to The Bart.
[SPEAKER_21]: The Bay Area Rapid Transit System Because if I want to use my ATM card on BART I have to buy a $20 ticket minimum $20 When it only costs like $8 To get to San Francisco and back Bastards That's highway robbery I'll lose the damn ticket Bastards Alright, let's go to some other FUs From our folks assembled here Starting off with Explicit Uh
[SPEAKER_21]: 3 hour show buddy, keep it short.
[SPEAKER_26]: Okay, I'll keep this one short, okay.
[SPEAKER_26]: Alright, I would like to give an F you to the State Fair for being so damn expensive.
[SPEAKER_26]: I mean, not only have the spot like my friends, you know, I have to be nice to my friends and all, but my wall, my bank's almost depleted just for the State Fair and shit.
[SPEAKER_26]: F you to Shane for squashing the hell out of my stomach.
[SPEAKER_26]: I know I ate like funnel cakes before riding on a few rides, but
[SPEAKER_26]: Squashing me in this one ride in my stomach killed my appetite.
[SPEAKER_26]: I have not eaten any lunch nor dinner both today and Saturday.
[SPEAKER_26]: An F you for Scandia for not posting what the hell the rules are for this tournament Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_26]: Like how the hell are we going to know?
[SPEAKER_21]: It's whatever they feel like doing.
[SPEAKER_26]: Who knows what's going to happen?
[SPEAKER_26]: Would it screw up or would it not screw up?
[SPEAKER_26]: And F you to the drama about, ooh, sim makers versus actual people who play DDR2 actually hired for the Ultramix game.
[SPEAKER_20]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah, like, you know, how some people say, ooh, people get hired for connections and stuff.
[SPEAKER_26]: You know, like, everyone knows that AJ and Lil B are working at Ultramix.
[SPEAKER_20]: Right, right, right.
[SPEAKER_26]: Some people are starting drama towards it.
[SPEAKER_20]: Where's this drama at?
[SPEAKER_26]: I think it was...
[SPEAKER_26]: I think it was in AaronInJapan.com, I'm not... Interesting.
[SPEAKER_26]: I'm not F-U-ing Scandi, I'm just F-U-ing some of the people who did not post the rules.
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah, Scandi has a broken pad.
[SPEAKER_26]: If they don't fix the pad before the tournament, then how are you going to have a fair tournament, basically?
[SPEAKER_21]: I think, in regards to your other F-U, I think people need to withhold judgment until the game comes out.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_21]: And I think no matter what happens, no matter who did the steps, if God himself came down from the heavens and wrote the steps to the next mix, somebody out there would say they sucked.
[SPEAKER_21]: There is no pleasing everybody.
[SPEAKER_21]: You're just going to have to deal with it.
[SPEAKER_26]: I know.
[SPEAKER_21]: Honestly.
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah, people just cut it out, wait till the game comes, wait till Ultramix 2 comes out, and then just from there, it goes, if it's shitty or not, or if it's good as hell or not.
[SPEAKER_21]: From what I've heard of Ultramix 2 so far...
[SPEAKER_21]: You guys are going to be very surprised.
[SPEAKER_21]: Some folks that are all anti-Xbox and stuff, you're going to be hopping on the Xbox train soon enough.
[SPEAKER_21]: Ultramix 2 is going to be very, very good.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's all I have to say.
[SPEAKER_26]: We'll see first when the game comes out.
[SPEAKER_21]: I... I can't say why I'm saying it, but just, it's going to be great.
[SPEAKER_21]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_26]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_26]: And FU2 School, some of the teachers in school.
[SPEAKER_26]: Ah, nope.
[SPEAKER_26]: Ah, that's going to be too long for the FUs.
[SPEAKER_26]: So let it speak for itself.
[SPEAKER_20]: All right.
[SPEAKER_20]: Angel.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, here is my comedy for the FUs, if you want to laugh at it or not, Rob.
[SPEAKER_11]: FU2 Ants Trying to Attack You When You're Trying to Get a Good Night's Sleep.
[SPEAKER_19]: Ew.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, I know, it's not good.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then when you're trying to sleep, you have nightmares of them trying to kill you.
[SPEAKER_22]: Ah.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know, doesn't that suck?
[SPEAKER_22]: Like big giant ants, or red ants, or what?
[SPEAKER_11]: No, I mean, they're regular house ants, but it's just like, it's annoying as hell.
[SPEAKER_22]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, you know, black ants.
[SPEAKER_11]: Little sweet ants, or whatever you want to call them.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then, like, even though you spray around the house, like, not even a week later, they'll come back.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then when you try to squish them, they start walking after you squish them.
[SPEAKER_11]: So you have to like squish them multiple times.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's really annoying.
[SPEAKER_11]: So F you to that.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then also, to add to Loki's F you, F you to stupid drivers that try to clip you when you're just, you know, minding your own business in your own lane.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because I almost got killed going to Walmart.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because we had to get some stuff or whatever.
[SPEAKER_11]: But that really sucked.
[SPEAKER_11]: So I almost died today.
[SPEAKER_11]: Or not today, but this week.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's not good.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, it's not.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_26]: Let me add that to the female drivers of referring to what Loki said.
[SPEAKER_26]: After you did this one lady, you threw a fucking soda can on my windshield.
[SPEAKER_29]: What?
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah, I was like, ooh, he cut me off.
[SPEAKER_26]: Ooh, let's throw a windshield on my windshield.
[SPEAKER_26]: Let's throw a soda bottle on my windshield.
[SPEAKER_26]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_26]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_26]: Luckily it didn't hit any of my paint or else I would really go after that son of a bitch.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm gonna rant her over.
[SPEAKER_26]: And F you too, there was some girls flicking us off in the...
[SPEAKER_26]: and the Ferris Wheel.
[SPEAKER_26]: What the hell did we do?
[SPEAKER_26]: We just flipped us off out of nowhere.
[SPEAKER_20]: I would have flipped him off back.
[SPEAKER_20]: I would have flashed my penis.
[SPEAKER_20]: But anyway.
[SPEAKER_26]: Well, I mooned him, so.
[SPEAKER_20]: Okay, that works.
[SPEAKER_26]: Well, even though they don't deserve to taste some of that.
[SPEAKER_20]: Anyway, let's move on and see what Arcadian has to say.
[SPEAKER_20]: Are we done, Angel?
[SPEAKER_11]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_11]: If I think of my last one, it's all good.
[SPEAKER_24]: All right, Arcadian.
[SPEAKER_24]: Fuck you, the heat's coming back.
[SPEAKER_24]: Fuck you to TreeSap for still getting on my car, especially because of the damn heat.
[SPEAKER_24]: And even, and fuck you to the people, the, the, by the, like the rental place or whatever it is that rents out the place that my company works at for choosing these shitty trees that actually drop this stuff all over cars in the winter, in the summer.
[SPEAKER_24]: You better search the damn things and find one that don't drop that shit on you.
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay, fuck you to traffic that comes up like 8.30 a.m.
[SPEAKER_24]: Damn it, you're supposed to be at work already!
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't want this fucking traffic when I'm coming to work late.
[SPEAKER_24]: But what's cool about my work, I can actually come in late.
[SPEAKER_24]: Actually, why don't you start coming in later?
[SPEAKER_24]: Because now that I'm an employee, I can actually be there late.
[SPEAKER_24]: And also, fuck you to my fucked up sleep schedule and my damn body for fucking waking me up
[SPEAKER_24]: Sometimes, like, at 5 a.m.
[SPEAKER_24]: in the morning, get to sleep at, like, between 12 and 1, and then for some fucking reason I wake up, like, 5 or 6 a.m.
[SPEAKER_24]: in the morning.
[SPEAKER_24]: It was really weird.
[SPEAKER_24]: Like, last Monday I slept for, like, 7 hours and I was, like, dead all day.
[SPEAKER_24]: And then the next few days I wake up, like, after 4 or 5 hours of sleep and then actually awake for half the day.
[SPEAKER_24]: And...
[SPEAKER_24]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_13]: I was commenting on them doing the every little thing, and Bush blew his nose today.
[SPEAKER_13]: We have reported this on CNN, PSNBC, and the Discovery Channel.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, looks like our net split is fixed.
[SPEAKER_22]: However, if you submitted the FU over email, do not send it again.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_21]: Flaronay also says, FU to Zim for breaking the Scandia DDR machine in Santa Rosa.
[SPEAKER_21]: Make that Rohnert Park.
[SPEAKER_21]: Angel's freaking out because that's where she's from.
[SPEAKER_11]: You suck!
[SPEAKER_11]: But, uh, you suck, but, um, I don't live there anymore, so, ha ha!
[SPEAKER_21]: Legend of Zaku says, F you to having to wash pots in a summer camp this summer.
[SPEAKER_21]: F you to the fact that I start school tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_21]: Ooh, ouch, I could have a lot of people start school tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_21]: Sorry, guys.
[SPEAKER_21]: Um, F you to President Bush for exploiting 9-11 for another four years in office, hence picking New York City as the location for the Republican National Convention.
[SPEAKER_21]: F you to the hip-hop being the dominating force in this year's VMAs and in mainstream music in general.
[SPEAKER_21]: Did you get my FU?
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, yeah, we said... Yeah, fuck you to the video music and we'll... Oh, yes, I have to spoil those, don't I?
[SPEAKER_21]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_21]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_24]: Who fucking wants to know?
[SPEAKER_21]: It's all stupid crap.
[SPEAKER_21]: I know it is, but I... I want to spoil it for those people that were thinking about going to watch it.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, good.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'll get to it, you guys.
[SPEAKER_21]: Here, let's see.
[SPEAKER_21]: Um... Da-da-da-da-da.
[SPEAKER_21]: Where's the winners list here?
[SPEAKER_21]: Video of the Year was OutKast, Hey Ya, which also won the award for most overplayed song of the year.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh wait, no, that was me.
[SPEAKER_21]: And Best Male Video, Usher, big surprise.
[SPEAKER_21]: Best Female Video, Beyonce, big surprise.
[SPEAKER_21]: Best Group Video, No Doubt.
[SPEAKER_21]: Great.
[SPEAKER_21]: Now you don't have to watch.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yay, you don't have to watch.
[SPEAKER_21]: A public service announcement.
[SPEAKER_21]: You don't have to watch one of the 500 million trillion, six billion repeats that they play every fucking day.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_21]: El Mullet would like to say, F you.
[SPEAKER_31]: I have nothing original.
[SPEAKER_21]: HellMullet would like to say F you to the Japanese DDR elitists who have no idea what they're talking about and an F you to my college classes that start tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_21]: DarkKnight says an F you for not having a car and an F you for not thinking of another F you.
[SPEAKER_21]: BlackDevil says F you to my iTunes radio connection when I was calling over Skype.
[SPEAKER_21]: I heard an echo of my voice and your voice.
[SPEAKER_21]: It was like six voices in my head and it was hard to concentrate.
[SPEAKER_21]: Turn down the volume next time you call in.
[SPEAKER_21]: Misty says, F me, because while I did find my karaoke revolution mic, I think it's broken.
[SPEAKER_21]: And in a lesser F you to me for not getting off my ass and driving, I could have kicked some ass in a DDR tournament this weekend.
[SPEAKER_21]: And VXJasonXV says, F you number one to Other Side IRC, why are you unstable at the moment?
[SPEAKER_21]: F you number two from all of us at Orange Lounge Radio and then some, F you to Newt.
[SPEAKER_21]: And F you number three, F you to NetSplits in general.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_21]: Now let's take a look at the FUs that came in over email, because I promised that I would read the ones on email.
[SPEAKER_21]: I apologize if I mispronounce this name, because it has an extra E from what I'm used to, but it looks like Renee says, FU to Japanese hentai censorship, and at myself for probably setting a record kick action to myself so fast for a first-time user.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, that's okay.
[SPEAKER_21]: You live, you learn.
[SPEAKER_21]: As long as you're being good now, that's the important point.
[SPEAKER_21]: Uh, Zeno would like to say, F you, damn IRC network splits.
[SPEAKER_21]: That and fractions.
[SPEAKER_21]: Numbers of the devil.
[SPEAKER_21]: And this weird cut on my hand that doesn't want to heal.
[SPEAKER_21]: And lastly, uh, I don't have an alias for this guy, I only got the full name here, so we'll call him Robert B. Robert B says, a big F you to dial up for being so shitty, and another F you to me for not getting cable.
[SPEAKER_24]: Frown.
[SPEAKER_21]: Fractions?
[SPEAKER_21]: The number of the devil?
[SPEAKER_24]: but call me the devil's friend.
[SPEAKER_21]: Weren't you a math major or something?
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_21]: I see how it is.
[SPEAKER_21]: You're in cahoots with the devil.
[SPEAKER_21]: Now even I'm scared.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yikes.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right.
[SPEAKER_21]: I think what we'll do is we're going to go to a break, and when we come back from a break, we'll do a little bit of Ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, but first, I wanted to mention some more Bomani news going on, because, you know, there was other news that happened this week, besides the Extreme Unlocks being revealed.
[SPEAKER_21]: There was a preview movie for Dancing Stage Fever that came out, and you can actually see a link to this video right on our website at OrangeLoungeRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's about the fifth story down.
[SPEAKER_21]: What this video showed, it was very interesting, it showed some of the song banners and stuff, but it also had karaoke lyrics.
[SPEAKER_21]: Now, granted, it's the Europe version of DDR, not the USA version of DDR, but, hmm, typically they use very similar engines.
[SPEAKER_21]: So, hmm, you kind of wonder, is karaoke lyrics something that's coming?
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_21]: Especially with the Karaoke Revolution crossovers, it would make a lot of sense, but,
[SPEAKER_21]: Despite that, if you do live in Europe and you have access to dancing stage games, then...
[SPEAKER_21]: Hey, there you go, you get karaoke lyrics, and you get a really good song list, by the way.
[SPEAKER_21]: You guys get an awesome song list.
[SPEAKER_21]: And DDR Festival was confirmed by Konami.
[SPEAKER_21]: It is coming, it does support the iToy, and it's coming November 18th.
[SPEAKER_21]: You want to know why it's confirmed?
[SPEAKER_21]: Because they set up a website for it, and you can see this link right there on our website, orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's right there on our front page.
[SPEAKER_21]: All righty?
[SPEAKER_21]: All right.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oops, it was Dancing Stage Fusion, not Fever.
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_21]: It says in the headline, Fever.
[SPEAKER_21]: We've got to fix that.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's actually Fusion.
[SPEAKER_29]: Our bad.
[SPEAKER_22]: Our bad.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right.
[SPEAKER_21]: We will be right back after this break.
[SPEAKER_21]: Jamie wanted more 5-key, so I said sure.
[SPEAKER_21]: Because she wanted to hear more Rugged Ash.
[SPEAKER_21]: So why not?
[SPEAKER_21]: We'll do some Rugged Ash.
[SPEAKER_21]: Rugged Ash is fun to play.
[SPEAKER_21]: And we'll do Logical Dash and The Fall.
[SPEAKER_21]: Fall Another Hey, do you have Believe Again?
[SPEAKER_21]: Or Beginning of Life?
[SPEAKER_21]: Sorry, Angel Alright, so four names
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, I did, it was not Renee, it was Rini.
[SPEAKER_21]: But I didn't think that was right, because that would be too obvious, and usually people's names aren't quite as obvious unless you're named Rob, like me.
[SPEAKER_21]: It was Rini.
[SPEAKER_21]: My bad, my bad.
[SPEAKER_21]: You try doing a radio show and pronouncing everything right, alright?
[SPEAKER_21]: We'll be back after this break.
[SPEAKER_23]: Two Russian planes carrying a total of more than 100 people crashed almost simultaneously today.
[SPEAKER_23]: The first crash happened in Bukovka.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_29]: Hi-ho, Kermit the Frog here, informing you that today's broadcast of Orange Lounge Radio is brought to you by the letter V, the letter A, and the number 59.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can you tell me how to get, how to get to Sesame Street?
[SPEAKER_21]: We are back, and I thought since we have a little bit of show left, maybe we'll do some Ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_21]: So you can actually send a question over private message right now to Sky, and we'll do a little bit of Ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_21]: But first...
[SPEAKER_21]: Cry, cry
[SPEAKER_21]: Zaku's calling us again, what's up?
[SPEAKER_21]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, I'm gonna go ahead and go because our connection is a little messed up, but I'm gonna answer that for you, okay?
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, keep listening.
[SPEAKER_21]: How do you make the jump from 5 key to 7 key?
[SPEAKER_21]: But before we answer the question, I have to do the theme music.
[SPEAKER_21]: Let's ask Orange Lounge some stupid question.
[SPEAKER_21]: What will we find out this week on Orange Lounge Radio?
[SPEAKER_21]: When we use the Skype line, random people call in, but I sure hope that one guy doesn't call us anymore, and I hope he got a live...
[SPEAKER_21]: But I'm not going to wish for things that won't happen.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right.
[SPEAKER_21]: Anyway, let's go back to people we do like to hear from.
[SPEAKER_21]: Zaku, how do you make the jump from 5Key to 7Key?
[SPEAKER_10]: You just do it.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, honestly, you just have to do it.
[SPEAKER_21]: My advice, honestly, when you play 2DX, don't play 5-key, ever.
[SPEAKER_21]: Because you'll just be kind of ruining it.
[SPEAKER_21]: But here's the thing, start on light 7, use beginner mode if you can.
[SPEAKER_21]: Just whatever it does to ease you into the 7-keys.
[SPEAKER_21]: Just because you can do a 4-star on 5-key, it doesn't mean you can do a 4-star on 7-key.
[SPEAKER_21]: Adding those two extra buttons will do so much.
[SPEAKER_21]: So just go back to the 1s.
[SPEAKER_21]: And that's really the only way you can do it.
[SPEAKER_21]: Put your turntable on the same side that you had it in five key games if you're playing from there.
[SPEAKER_21]: If that helps you, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_21]: Otherwise, you just have to practice.
[SPEAKER_21]: There's no magic way to do it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Learn how to pinky scratch.
[SPEAKER_21]: Drill mode.
[SPEAKER_21]: If you have 6th or 7th style, or I'm sorry, 5th or 6th style, and I think it was in 7th too, use drill mode.
[SPEAKER_21]: It really, really helps and it teaches you a lot of the tricks.
[SPEAKER_21]: It can be a little repetitive at first, but it really, really helps.
[SPEAKER_21]: So do yourself a favor and try that.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_13]: You might want to also, when I first started doing it, I had to learn to recenter my hands.
[SPEAKER_13]: A lot of people will do 5 to 5 keys and then use 2 to the other.
[SPEAKER_13]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_21]: I want to take some questions that came in from the chat room.
[SPEAKER_21]: Including, Puppy has a question for us.
[SPEAKER_21]: Puppy wants to know, when are we going to go out and have boba with him again?
[SPEAKER_13]: Whenever I can cheat.
[SPEAKER_13]: When you buy me my Humvee.
[SPEAKER_21]: I do think a boba trip is in order, I just don't know when yet.
[SPEAKER_21]: Sorry guys.
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't know when yet.
[SPEAKER_21]: I've been kind of busy lately.
[SPEAKER_21]: We do have a three-day weekend coming up, but I promise, promise, promise a special somebody that I would go to the club with him Sunday night after the show next week.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_21]: But maybe next time.
[SPEAKER_21]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_22]: Certainly by the next time VXChase and XV visits.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's for sure.
[SPEAKER_21]: Zaku wants to submit another question.
[SPEAKER_21]: Skyplane's open too if you want to call in.
[SPEAKER_21]: What was the worst summer job you ever had?
[SPEAKER_13]: I worked at a grocery store for a week.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was supposed to be my first job.
[SPEAKER_13]: I was going to work at the grocery store.
[SPEAKER_13]: I had been offered a job at the game room during orientation at my college, but I wasn't actually a student yet, so to earn some money over the summer, I was going to work at a grocery store.
[SPEAKER_13]: And it turned out that they were... If I was supposed to get off at like 9, I didn't get off work until midnight.
[SPEAKER_13]: I was like, excuse me, screw this, so...
[SPEAKER_13]: I quit, took my last paycheck, and then like two weeks later I was working on campus.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, we're going to go to the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_21]: Siggy's on the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_21]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_31]: Hello, Sky.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes, how you doing?
[SPEAKER_31]: Are we still in the Ask Orange Slown segment yet?
[SPEAKER_21]: You sure can.
[SPEAKER_21]: I just wanted to share one thing real fast, though, to answer Zaku's question about the worst summer job.
[SPEAKER_21]: I once worked at a video store, and we happened to rent pornography, and one of my friends from childhood, his dad came in to rent a porno once.
[SPEAKER_21]: That was really awkward.
[SPEAKER_21]: Anyway, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes, you had a question, Siggy.
[SPEAKER_31]: Well, here's just a simple question.
[SPEAKER_31]: Didn't you get my instant message over the forums lately?
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, yes, about Poppin' Music 12.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_31]: Yeah, I was just wondering.
[SPEAKER_21]: You want us to whore out Poppin' Music 12.
[SPEAKER_21]: We can do that.
[SPEAKER_31]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right, we'll talk Poppin' Music 12 just for you, Siggy.
[SPEAKER_31]: Just after this.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_31]: After this segment.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, we don't have much time left in the show, so we'll probably get to that and finish out the show here.
[SPEAKER_31]: Just finish this right now.
[SPEAKER_21]: All righty.
[SPEAKER_21]: Thanks for the reminder.
[SPEAKER_31]: All right.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right, later.
[SPEAKER_31]: Later.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes, I did want to get to that.
[SPEAKER_21]: DarkLine had sent us a message over the forums.
[SPEAKER_21]: Let me go grab that right now.
[SPEAKER_21]: We actually have to wrap up the show, so I just want to do a few more news items, and then we'll finish up here.
[SPEAKER_21]: Let me see.
[SPEAKER_21]: Let me get in there.
[SPEAKER_21]: We did briefly mention it in one of our other news articles, but Poppin' Music 12 is location testing right now.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's really high for a Bomani game.
[SPEAKER_21]: 12 Mix or whatever, but they don't call it Mix.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's just Poppin' 12.
[SPEAKER_21]: It has a bunch of new licenses in it.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, not a bunch, but at least three that have been announced so far.
[SPEAKER_21]: Cruel Angels Thesis is one of them.
[SPEAKER_13]: Dude, that's like the Evangelion theme.
[SPEAKER_21]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_21]: So tons of people are going to love that.
[SPEAKER_21]: And then some new Konami originals as well.
[SPEAKER_21]: I see the Parkettes are in there.
[SPEAKER_21]: Jimmy Weckl has one, and D.Crew has a song.
[SPEAKER_21]: You can head over to Bomani Style.
[SPEAKER_21]: They actually posted about this a couple days ago.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'd feel a little weird just copying and pasting what they wrote, so honestly, just head over to Bomani Style.
[SPEAKER_21]: They've got all the news on it.
[SPEAKER_21]: They also have screenshots, and it looks like they're kind of... You know how the recent pop-up musics, they've kind of had a theme?
[SPEAKER_21]: Like, Pop-Up Music 11 was like world travel, was kind of what that was all about?
[SPEAKER_21]: It looks like Pop-Up Music 12's theme is traditional Japan.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_21]: Because you notice that the mascots are wearing the kind of kimono and all the artwork looks, for lack of a better word, looks a little chinky.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's basically what it's about.
[SPEAKER_21]: PopMesa 12, we will definitely, when we find out more information about it, we will post it on over to our website over on OrangeLoungeRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right.
[SPEAKER_21]: What else was news?
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, I know.
[SPEAKER_21]: Not necessarily a Bomani game, but you know Taiko No Tatooine, right?
[SPEAKER_21]: You know that game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, you know it's coming to the U.S., and it's going to be called Taiko Drum Master here in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_10]: Close enough name.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, guess what?
[SPEAKER_21]: The song list has been announced for Taiko Drum Master, and there's some very interesting stuff in it.
[SPEAKER_21]: Like to be expected, you have your classical songs.
[SPEAKER_21]: You have your Beethoven Symphony No.
[SPEAKER_21]: 5, Carmen, William Tell Overture, Hungarian Dances No.
5.
[SPEAKER_21]: You have all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_21]: Then you have Namco originals, such as Soul Calibur II's Brave Sword, Braver Soul, and the Ridge Racer theme.
[SPEAKER_21]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_21]: But then we get the licenses.
[SPEAKER_21]: Some very interesting license songs in Taiko Drum Master.
[SPEAKER_21]: My Sharona...
[SPEAKER_21]: Material Girl, Lady Marmalade, the theme from Jimmy Neutron, and the theme from Dragon Ball Z, and then get this, Toxic, and DDR Crossovers, Tub Thumping, you remember that, second mix, Tub Thumping, and that's the way, uh-huh, uh-huh, I like it, uh-huh, uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_13]: I wonder if they're going to make the drum any more stable.
[SPEAKER_21]: If you want to see that list, it's over on our website, orangelauntredo.com.
[SPEAKER_21]: We did post the whole list.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's the fourth story down right now.
[SPEAKER_21]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_21]: Donkey Konga is almost out.
[SPEAKER_21]: I think there's only a couple more weeks until that's out.
[SPEAKER_21]: And if you go to GameStop, they have the demo set up so you can try it out.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's interesting.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, I can't personally be too excited about Donkey Konga after I played it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because the clapping thing is aggravating, you know?
[SPEAKER_13]: But I wonder, though, have they put out a song list for Donkey Konga yet?
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes, it's way back in our archives.
[SPEAKER_21]: You'd have to do a search, but there was a song list announced.
[SPEAKER_13]: I know that the Japanese version had a bunch of J-pop in it.
[SPEAKER_13]: It had a pretty good song selection.
[SPEAKER_13]: I just sort of blanked out over Donkey Konga, but it's really cool that it's coming out over here, but
[SPEAKER_13]: It's one of the ones I never thought that we'd see.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, I'm going to jam through the last few questions here then we've got to wrap up the show.
[SPEAKER_21]: Three more questions.
[SPEAKER_21]: No more questions, please.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm going to get these last few ones.
[SPEAKER_21]: Dark Knight, a quick question.
[SPEAKER_21]: Has anyone visited Virginia before?
[SPEAKER_21]: The reason why was because Loki had that Virginia shirt on the webcam.
[SPEAKER_17]: As I said before in the chatroom, but no one was paying attention, my aunt and uncle live in Virginia.
[SPEAKER_17]: And so, you know, as a staple, everyone has to bring you back the shirt that says what city they visited.
[SPEAKER_17]: So, you know, I have this shirt.
[SPEAKER_17]: Basically, you know, if you want to know the logic with me wearing this shirt, it was on top of the clean pile.
[SPEAKER_17]: It was the first shirt I saw.
[SPEAKER_17]: And that's how it goes.
[SPEAKER_21]: Thank you for watching.
[SPEAKER_21]: See you next time.
[SPEAKER_21]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_21]: question from BlackDevil when I call and I want to not hear an echo of the conversation do I turn down my master volume or microphone volume don't turn down your mic volume turn down your speakers or well I shouldn't say your speakers turn down your Winamp or if you're iTunes turn it off while you call the show whatever you're using to listen to the station turn it off while you call the show because that's what causes the echo but don't yeah don't turn off your speakers because then you can't hear us through Skype and then you're talking to nothing so yeah
[SPEAKER_21]: Shut off Winamp or iTunes or whatever you use to listen to the show.
[SPEAKER_21]: And lastly, Legend of Zaku, one more question.
[SPEAKER_21]: What are the chances that we Americans will get other Bomani besides DDR and Karaoke Revolution?
[SPEAKER_13]: We did get Keyboard Mania.
[SPEAKER_21]: To some extent.
[SPEAKER_21]: Not necessarily on PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_13]: But we got the Yamaha.
[SPEAKER_21]: A little hard to get.
[SPEAKER_21]: A lot of people don't even know about it.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's so rare.
[SPEAKER_21]: Um...
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't want to say never.
[SPEAKER_21]: Never say never.
[SPEAKER_21]: Let's just put it that way.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know what I want to see come out in the States is some of the Namco music games.
[SPEAKER_13]: Namco did... I'm not talking about Taiko no Tatsujin.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm talking about the guitar game that Namco did and the drum one that Namco did.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because they did a bunch of... They're supposed to be really good music games, just we haven't seen them.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's all on the Namco.jp site.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, we are going to wrap up the show now, guys.
[SPEAKER_21]: It is time.
[SPEAKER_21]: We're almost running over here, so please let us get everybody's final thought.
[SPEAKER_21]: And we'll start off tonight's final thought with Angel.
[SPEAKER_11]: Um... Well, no, I wanted to save it for last word.
[SPEAKER_11]: If you want it, let me have it, but, uh... Uh... Buffalo Wings.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright, uh, Arcadian.
[SPEAKER_19]: Final thought.
[SPEAKER_19]: If we can get him a mic.
[SPEAKER_19]: Final thought from Arcadian42.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yay, more money soon.
[SPEAKER_21]: Jonas, your final thought?
[SPEAKER_26]: Tournament Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_21]: Loki, your final thought?
[SPEAKER_17]: I am working on next week's winning song.
[SPEAKER_17]: Bond will be the Thrundeezy.
[SPEAKER_13]: You're just mad because Bond won't put out for you.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_21]: My final thought is, listen to Outside the Box on Wednesday.
[SPEAKER_21]: Listen, or I'll come to your house and beat you up.
[SPEAKER_21]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_21]: Jamie, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_21]: I hate my allergies.
[SPEAKER_21]: and for the final word of the show we actually have a celebrity final word of the show tonight you guys so here is tonight's final word of the show and thank you very much for listening everybody have a great night
[SPEAKER_28]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_28]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_28]: Orange Lounge Radio is hosted by DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_28]: If you'd like to leave us a comment, send us an email at orangeloungeradio at yahoo.com And now, here's your fortune cookie message of the day.
[SPEAKER_08]: and even Alan Cooper.
[SPEAKER_08]: You gotta be trendy if you wanna make some money Everybody's saying that he sure sounds funny
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you very much for listening, and we'll see you next week.
[SPEAKER_21]: Hello, there we are.
[SPEAKER_21]: We are back with the Orange Lounge Radio Afterbirth, the part after the credits have faded to black.
[SPEAKER_21]: Right now I'm trying to upload that Bukkake clip to our website so I can let you people download it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Nice pun, Rob.
[SPEAKER_21]: She'll have tons of fun.
[SPEAKER_21]: What?
[SPEAKER_11]: I said nice pun.
[SPEAKER_11]: The ACDC back and forth.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, whatever.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, I'm not funny.
[SPEAKER_11]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_21]: You don't get paid to be funny.
[SPEAKER_21]: You get paid to sit there and look pretty.
[SPEAKER_11]: I live with someone who's not that funny.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, just kidding.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm not going to go there.
[SPEAKER_21]: I think he's starting to rub off on you.
[SPEAKER_21]: Be careful.
[SPEAKER_11]: I hope not.
[SPEAKER_21]: Ah, God.
[SPEAKER_21]: You all at home are very glad you did not hear what Jamie just said.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's for damn sure.
[SPEAKER_21]: I can repeat it.
[SPEAKER_11]: No!
[SPEAKER_21]: You can't repeat it?
[SPEAKER_11]: Because none of it is true, damn it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't want to hear about the person she lives with rubbing off on anyone.
[SPEAKER_21]: That sucks.
[SPEAKER_21]: I wish I still had that drumroll noise.
[SPEAKER_21]: People should pay us to do this show, you know?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, and I'd get less than minimum wage.
[SPEAKER_21]: I want to tease the... Oh, you want to tease your new remix, Loki?
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, tease it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wait.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hi, puppy!
[SPEAKER_21]: Loki wants to tease his newest remix for you all.
[SPEAKER_21]: Fine, do it.
[SPEAKER_21]: That was more than a tease.
[SPEAKER_21]: You grabbed my balls and fondled them right there.
[SPEAKER_21]: That was very interesting.
[SPEAKER_21]: Wow, that is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_21]: What's that all about?
[SPEAKER_21]: Tell us about that one.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's just something with radical faith.
[SPEAKER_17]: I heard this one remix that someone did and it sucked, and I thought, I'll try something like that.
[SPEAKER_13]: I was instantly drawn to the tech.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_17]: Now listening to it through your speakers, I have to change a few things, but it's just the beginning of it.
[SPEAKER_17]: The end kind of gets weird sometimes.
[SPEAKER_17]: Let me play a clip here.
[SPEAKER_17]: Because I can't really transition in this part yet, but it's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_17]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_17]: Anyways, that stuff.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_11]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_21]: Two Russian planes carrying a total of more than 100 people crashed almost simultaneously today.
[SPEAKER_23]: The first crash happened in Bukalki.
[SPEAKER_21]: I played it ten times tonight and it's still not old.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_21]: It is still funny.
[SPEAKER_11]: Nope, still funny.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_21]: For some reason I can't get that uploaded right now, but... I'll just try it again later.
[SPEAKER_21]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_21]: Flare One uploaded it, there's the URL in the chatroom Flare One was very kind to upload that to you all
[SPEAKER_21]: I know it's on GeoShitties, but hopefully enough of you guys can get it before GeoShitties locks them out.
[SPEAKER_21]: Good luck, you guys.
[SPEAKER_21]: Enjoy the post-show tonight.
[SPEAKER_21]: Have a great one.
[SPEAKER_21]: Thank you again for tuning into and supporting Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_21]: We love you.
[SPEAKER_21]: Good night.
[SPEAKER_21]: I forgot.
[SPEAKER_21]: The thing has this whole little intro, so you just kind of have to sit through it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Nice.
Ah, a city man?
[SPEAKER_12]: You are about to embark on a musical journey, a journey made up of beats and bass lines.
[SPEAKER_12]: Prepare yourselves, for you are about to enter the Deep Dance.
[SPEAKER_08]: You want this, you need this, let's party here and we like this.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yo, party over here, party over there, deep dance everywhere.
[SPEAKER_06]: You want this, you need this, let's party here and we like this.
Yo, party over here, party over there, deep dance everywhere.