[SPEAKER_11]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and released to our podcast stream twice weekly To listen to the first half of this episode visit www.orangeloungeradio.com for links to websites with listings of past episodes Now the conclusion of this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_12]: Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_12]: Be good or Santa's not going to bring you the games you want.
[SPEAKER_12]: But we will keep bringing you the gaming news you want, whether you've been good or bad.
[SPEAKER_12]: So we're going to get right back into some gaming news, aren't we, Loki?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, and this game's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know how popular it's going to be because you've got kind of conflicting elements to it.
[SPEAKER_10]: For example, Mario and Sonic at the Olympics.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now, Mario and Sonic games, those are good.
[SPEAKER_10]: Olympic Games, those are usually bad.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it's kind of... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know if it's going to be good or not.
[SPEAKER_10]: Either way.
[SPEAKER_10]: This could go either way.
[SPEAKER_10]: There will be 16 characters, including your favorites from both the Sonic and Mario and, I guess, Nintendo universes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Although, what's weird, though, is I do see the villain from one of the alligators from the Donkey Kong Country franchises, yet no Donkey Kong.
[SPEAKER_10]: Odd.
[SPEAKER_10]: Fencing, Archery,
[SPEAKER_10]: Shooting, Skeet, Gymnastics, including Trampoline and Vault, High Jump, Pull Vault, Long Jump, Triple Jump, Javelin Throw, Hammer Throw, Single Skulls for rowing, of course, Table Tennis, Aquatics, both the 100 meter and, of course, the 4-lap 100 meter.
[SPEAKER_10]: And let's see here, Tracks, of course, 110 meter, 400 meter, Hurdles, Freestyle,
[SPEAKER_10]: 100m Relay, and the just normal 100m and 400m.
[SPEAKER_10]: So lots of running and stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: I still don't understand how Mario is ever going to beat Sonic in running.
[SPEAKER_12]: Nobody's been able to explain this logic to me.
[SPEAKER_12]: Did they give Sonic some drugs to slow him down?
[SPEAKER_12]: Or Mario some steroids?
[SPEAKER_12]: How is that ever going to be an even match?
[SPEAKER_10]: The characters in the game, they've kind of broken them up like they did with Mario Kart, where you've got the power types, the ones that
[SPEAKER_10]: are more of the robust characters, like Bowser and Wario, stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: And Knuckles is in there too, so apparently Knuckles is a fat ass.
[SPEAKER_10]: He's a fatty.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, he does have a little bit of a gut.
[SPEAKER_12]: What they're saying, Dark Knight says in our chat room at chat.orangelongery.com, they balance the characters.
[SPEAKER_12]: I understand they balance the characters, but that still doesn't make sense in the regards of that Sonic runs very fast and Mario runs quickly.
[SPEAKER_10]: They also have all-around characters, which Mario falls under, as well as Luigi.
[SPEAKER_10]: And apparently also the two chicks from the Sonic universe.
[SPEAKER_10]: So Mario and Luigi, you're as powerful as chicks.
[SPEAKER_10]: Way to go, pansies.
[SPEAKER_12]: Whoa, I think there might be some women a little angry at that comment.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I mean, honestly.
[SPEAKER_12]: Mr. DeBucket in chat says they wouldn't let Bowser into the Chinese Olympics.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Uh...
[SPEAKER_10]: And then, of course, for the speed types, you have Sonic.
[SPEAKER_10]: You actually have... What's his name?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, the crappy game.
[SPEAKER_10]: What was the crappy game?
[SPEAKER_12]: Driver.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, Sonic game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Crappy Sonic game.
[SPEAKER_12]: Sonic the Hedgehog.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, the last one that came out before Sonic... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: The guy with the gun.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, Shadow the Hedgehog?
[SPEAKER_10]: Shadow, yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry, they all look alike, and those games kind of blend together, so...
[SPEAKER_10]: Part of me for forgetting that crappy game.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then, of course, the skill types where you have Princess Peach, Tails, Waluigi, and Dr. Eggman.
[SPEAKER_12]: I hope Princess Peach will be able to use her emotional power in the Olympic Games somehow.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, that would be a skill, I guess.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_12]: Some type of skill.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it's going to be all split up.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: To be honest, I don't think I'm going to buy this game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe I'd rent it.
[SPEAKER_10]: All it seems to me is it's like, hey, we put out another crappy Olympics game, but we have Sonic and Mario this time, so you're going to buy it, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_10]: And maybe we'll have advertising for these games during the Olympics and that kind of crap, so cross-promotion stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: Be honest, though, I think you guys are going to get suckered into buying another crappy Olympics game because it has characters that you like, so have at it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll be busy playing Super Mario Galaxy instead.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I will be busy playing Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_12]: Brawl when that comes out.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: Upon its release, yes.
[SPEAKER_12]: And one thing that has lots of fanboys and girls very excited, especially if you're a David Hader fanboy or fangirl, which I believe DarkSakura is a David Hader fangirl.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because he could just talk to me all day and I'll be happy.
[SPEAKER_12]: Do you watch his YouTube?
[SPEAKER_12]: Apparently he has a YouTube site where he does all these little Q&A things and does stuff on there.
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't know that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll have to check.
[SPEAKER_12]: You definitely should check that out.
[SPEAKER_12]: This guy named Archduke Chocula was checking it out and sent David Hayter a question.
[SPEAKER_12]: It said, Hello, David Hayter.
[SPEAKER_12]: I have to say you are one of the greatest voice actors ever.
[SPEAKER_12]: And you do a great job as Snake.
[SPEAKER_12]: I was wondering, are you going to voice Snake in the Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_12]: Brawl?
[SPEAKER_12]: To which David Hayter responded, I am indeed voicing Snake in Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_12]: I recorded it already, and I believe that fans of both games are going to be extremely happy.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's very cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's all I can say.
[SPEAKER_12]: So this is authentic Snake now because it's the same voice actor and everything.
[SPEAKER_12]: So that's just one more cool thing that you can put on the ever-growing list of cool things in Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_12]: Brawl.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, seriously.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love David Hader.
[SPEAKER_12]: Got Resetti in there.
[SPEAKER_12]: Dude, they put fucking Resetti in Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_07]: Brawl.
[SPEAKER_07]: What is he going to do, bitch at you until you die?
[SPEAKER_12]: He comes out and lectures you on the mechanics of how to play the game, I think.
[SPEAKER_12]: Was that the impression I got?
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't think he's like an item or anything.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think he lectures you on how to play the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want Mr. Saturn still in the game as an item because I love Mr. Saturn.
[SPEAKER_12]: I just want Ness.
[SPEAKER_12]: Is that too much to ask?
[SPEAKER_12]: PK Fire?
[SPEAKER_10]: Or how about, like, was it Howard and Nestor?
[SPEAKER_12]: Dark Knight says, I would love to have a Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_12]: on the DS.
[SPEAKER_12]: Dude, I bet that'll be the next one.
[SPEAKER_12]: I bet that'll be the next one.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, speaking of things Nintendo, for Virtual Console coming out in the UK, Sin and Punishment is the recent edition, which is a Nintendo 64 game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Pretty cool game, and...
[SPEAKER_07]: The Legend of Hirotanma
[SPEAKER_12]: Anticipation Anticipation Anticipation Anticipation Anticipation Anticipation Anticipation Anticipation
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, check out this game.
[SPEAKER_12]: You get to go save a princess and do shit.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm saving the best for last.
[SPEAKER_12]: So it's Mario?
[SPEAKER_12]: No.
[SPEAKER_12]: Zelda?
[SPEAKER_12]: Just, you know, some princess.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wonder Boy!
[SPEAKER_07]: Wonder Boy and Monsterland did come out, didn't it?
[SPEAKER_12]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love Wonder Boy and Monsterland.
[SPEAKER_07]: But anyway, Gradius 3, which was a SNES game.
[SPEAKER_07]: 900 Wii points.
[SPEAKER_07]: And dude, it's fucking Gradius, so you won it right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think that's also part of that Japanese gamey thing that, you know, the releasing games in the UK that we don't have over here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Gradius 3.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sad.
[SPEAKER_07]: I actually have Gradius 3, though.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's in the Gradius collection on PSP.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, but I actually have the cart.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, can I touch you?
[SPEAKER_12]: You're just so cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have Gradius 2.
[SPEAKER_12]: I just want a little piece of your coolness.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have Gradius 2 on Turbo Duo, which is the best version of that game ever.
[SPEAKER_12]: GATE OF THUNDER
[SPEAKER_10]: and I'll be coming out for 800 Wii Points as well as Super Air Zonk will be coming out as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: Air Zonk was such a bizarre little game.
[SPEAKER_10]: The TurboGrafx-16 was a bizarre little console, so it makes perfect sense.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it had some great stuff on it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, I pressed the bathroom door to get a copy of Pac-Land.
[SPEAKER_07]: Remember the button?
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh my god, that was so long ago.
[SPEAKER_12]: I know, that was great.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, we were at Classic Gaming Expo, right?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: And they were selling Pac-Land on the TurboGrafx-16.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was with $5 short.
[SPEAKER_12]: And Jamie was like, I want that.
[SPEAKER_12]: I just need $5 to get it.
[SPEAKER_12]: And so there was this little... God, this is so stupid.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was the bathroom.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't believe we're telling this story.
[SPEAKER_07]: There were three doors that had the automatic button.
[SPEAKER_12]: But seriously, Jamie, this was like you had to be there thing.
[SPEAKER_12]: The listeners are going to be like, this story isn't funny at all.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I will do stuff for TurboGrafx games.
[SPEAKER_12]: This little girl we saw, she ran up and pressed the button to open the handicap restroom and then ran away.
[SPEAKER_12]: And for some reason, this is the most hilarious thing in the world to us.
[SPEAKER_12]: Like, we were laughing and laughing at this little girl.
[SPEAKER_10]: We were that bored.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, I guess so.
[SPEAKER_12]: So I said to Jamie, I said, Jamie, if you mimic what that little girl just did, I'll give you five dollars.
[SPEAKER_12]: And she did it.
[SPEAKER_12]: We took pictures.
[SPEAKER_12]: They're somewhere.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you know how many times I've played that copy of Pac-Land?
[SPEAKER_07]: Once.
[SPEAKER_12]: Really?
[SPEAKER_07]: Not even on the actual duo.
[SPEAKER_07]: I played it on a Turbo Express.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, my five bucks back.
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can come play my game, though.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't want to.
[SPEAKER_10]: Other game, well another TurboGrafx game announced as well, Samurai Ghost.
[SPEAKER_10]: But of course that's not a TurboCD title.
[SPEAKER_12]: Wow, more people just entered the studio.
[SPEAKER_12]: Keep going with the story, ignore them for a minute.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that's it, all your TurboCD games.
[SPEAKER_12]: Was that it?
[SPEAKER_12]: No more news on TurboGrafx CD games?
[SPEAKER_12]: Nope, that was it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Going back to Nintendo Wii, Fatal Frame is being developed for the Nintendo Wii.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's being developed by Grasshopper and it's being published by Tecmo.
[SPEAKER_12]: And it's being worked on very soon, I guess, right now.
[SPEAKER_12]: And it's kind of cool because Fatal Frame is very popular.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, it's no Silent Hill or Resident Evil, but it's probably on that secondary tier of scary video games.
[SPEAKER_12]: And so we're always curious to see how games translate over to the Wii.
[SPEAKER_12]: But you can bet there'll probably be something to do with photography.
[SPEAKER_12]: and the Wiimote and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: All that stuff is very specific, Rob.
[SPEAKER_12]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, this makes me a happy, happy, happy bunny.
[SPEAKER_07]: One of my favorite games ever... They're distracting me, Rob!
[SPEAKER_12]: Ignore them and read the story.
[SPEAKER_07]: One of my favorite ever games is Samba de Amigo and there is...
[SPEAKER_07]: A statement that it is going to be on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's supposedly this cover scan from Nintendo Power that's floating around ye old interwebs showing a Samba de Amigo for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_12]: Samba de Amigo on the Wii is going to be awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's nothing, though, in the issue regarding gameplay.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anyway, let's introduce, you know, Extifer and Rice Princess barged in here, so I thought I'd let them say hello.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, hello there.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm British now.
[SPEAKER_01]: What are you kids up to this evening?
[SPEAKER_01]: We basically came here to say hi.
[SPEAKER_01]: I haven't been on Orange Lingerie in a while.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, I mean, since I called in.
[SPEAKER_01]: I like it that way.
[SPEAKER_01]: Aww.
[SPEAKER_10]: Were you here last week?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, no, I called in last week.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, that's right.
[SPEAKER_01]: um but i i decided to it's me and rice princess say hi say hi rice princess hi rice princess okay and um we just want to say hi and oh yeah we want you to do a song that we want on the cage match
[SPEAKER_01]: The Game of Life Rice Princess
[SPEAKER_06]: That is what you said last week.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've been playing WoW and I played Super Puzzle Fighter 2 Turbo last night at a certain party that was thrown that I attended and it was fun.
[SPEAKER_12]: Now, I have a question about Puzzle Fighter 2 because you loved the one that was on Sony PlayStation and the old school one.
[SPEAKER_12]: How does the Xbox 360 one compare?
[SPEAKER_06]: The game itself isn't bad, but the controller is god-awful.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, when I wanted to press down, it would go, like, to the left or to the right.
[SPEAKER_06]: It made me mad.
[SPEAKER_06]: Am I being too quiet?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sorry about that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I will raise my voice.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, the game itself isn't bad, but the controller is, like, a nightmare to use to play that game.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, yeah, I enjoyed it thoroughly.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_12]: Did you try the remix mode with the different drop patterns and stuff?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: I only went into one mode.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just kept pressing A until the game started.
[SPEAKER_12]: There's like way more to the game.
[SPEAKER_12]: There's like all these different, like you can play modes where you don't even just make bricks.
[SPEAKER_12]: You make like different things and you need to check out the game a little more thoroughly.
[SPEAKER_12]: That was a very bad review job you did.
[SPEAKER_12]: Fired!
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, listen, son of a bitch.
[SPEAKER_06]: You should have told me.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would have done that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just kept pressing A because I really wanted to play the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, because I, you know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm like the best at the game out of all of you, so...
[SPEAKER_06]: That's why you're making fun of me, because you're jealous of my skills.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right, no more derailing the show.
[SPEAKER_12]: We've got to get back to gaming news.
[SPEAKER_12]: So you can stay if you want to contribute to news.
[SPEAKER_12]: Otherwise, get out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, we actually are going to go.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: Way to put me on the spot.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, well, we can stay and listen.
All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: You do that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Let's get back to some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_12]: All the listeners are like,
[SPEAKER_12]: Back to gaming news?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, now Irene's like, I gotta go look at Puzzle Fighter.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyways, so apparently the BAFTA nominees are coming around.
[SPEAKER_10]: For those not in the know, that's the British Academy of Film and Television Arts.
[SPEAKER_10]: They've announced their nominees for the 2007 Video Game Awards, and topping the list is Wii Sports.
[SPEAKER_10]: with seven nominations, including Innovation and Best Game categories.
[SPEAKER_10]: And, of course, there's also a four-way tie for the second-most nominations with Crackdown, awesome game, Gears of War, also awesome game, Akami, and God of War II, all awesome games.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know if it should be Game of the Year, though.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's pretty rad, though, that they give it such good recognition, though, over there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Other nominees, of course, Bioshock, Crysis.
[SPEAKER_10]: How could Crysis be nominated?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not even out yet.
[SPEAKER_10]: Gears Award, Guitar Hero 2, and Kanan Lynch.
[SPEAKER_10]: Also, Kanan Lynch is not out yet.
[SPEAKER_12]: They need a Gaming Oscars.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I'm not talking about the Spike TV Awards or whatever that crap is.
[SPEAKER_12]: Does that even exist anymore?
[SPEAKER_12]: I think it's now like a segment on X-Play.
[SPEAKER_12]: It doesn't even matter.
[SPEAKER_12]: None of that stuff counts.
[SPEAKER_12]: I want a Gaming Oscars.
[SPEAKER_12]: Something that's not a joke.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh well.
[SPEAKER_12]: Forget it.
[SPEAKER_10]: The Howard and Nestor Awards.
[SPEAKER_10]: No.
[SPEAKER_12]: The Howard and Nestor Awards.
[SPEAKER_12]: That would actually be pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: Winners will be announced of course on October 23rd.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, Xbox 360 games seem to be moving over to the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_12]: Heck, Viva Pinata, as you know, was announced to have an incarnation coming out on the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_12]: Guess what?
[SPEAKER_12]: Blue Dragon is also on its way to the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_12]: Now, normally you'd kind of go, well, that doesn't seem like too big a surprise.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, it kind of seems like the kind of game that could have been on the DS.
[SPEAKER_12]: But when you consider that, you know, Mistwalker made it for Microsoft, it is kind of interesting that the game is going to have an incarnation on the DS.
[SPEAKER_12]: This was coming from a recent issue of the manga Shonen Jump.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, it's funny.
[SPEAKER_10]: When I asked my Microsoft rep about Viva Pinata and who was publishing it, he got on a plane and left.
[SPEAKER_12]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: He didn't have the answer for me.
[SPEAKER_10]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then he got on a plane and left.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was your answer.
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess so.
[SPEAKER_12]: The answer was... He's like, uh, look over there.
[SPEAKER_12]: The answer was, what's that?
[SPEAKER_07]: The answer was, um... Run away!
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, thanks, bye.
[SPEAKER_12]: For real.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know, really.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, um...
[SPEAKER_07]: There is a little speculation regarding Legend of Zelda Phantom Hourglass, and it was confirmed that the producer, Eiji Aonuma, basically did agree that the game was a remake of the very first Zelda game.
[SPEAKER_12]: or it must have started off that way, but it certainly hopefully hasn't ended up that way because I don't want to pony up that kind of money.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, the game's already out, and I know people who play it who didn't say that it was just like it, but it was supposed to be... What the crap?
[SPEAKER_12]: Phantom Hourglass came out?
[SPEAKER_07]: In Japan.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Remember, my friends have a Ninja Pass.
[SPEAKER_12]: Sorry, I was like, wait, wait, it came out over here?
[SPEAKER_12]: I missed that.
[SPEAKER_07]: But at any rate, it's saying that in his attempt to return to the root series, he unintentionally remade the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it's not really a complete remake, it's more like a... An homage.
[SPEAKER_12]: A spiritual remake, I guess.
[SPEAKER_12]: When I hear that though, I go, well if it's an original, I don't know if I want it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I'm gonna get it.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, I know, I'm gonna get it too.
[SPEAKER_12]: Heck, even if it was a remake of the first game, I'd probably get it, because I'm a consumer whore.
[SPEAKER_10]: And how.
[SPEAKER_10]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyways, so funny that you mentioned remakes because the Sex Pistols are actually coming together to re-record Anarchy in the UK.
[SPEAKER_10]: And of course this is going to be for Guitar Hero 3.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why should you care?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because it's a pretty cool song.
[SPEAKER_10]: But yeah, they've come back together.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it's the Sex Pistols getting back together.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_10]: and so apparently they're going to be reissuing Anarchy in the UK as well as part of the celebration they're going to be our Guitar Hero 3 is going to be sponsoring the band's performance at the London Brixton Academy on November 8th all in thanks to a video game well they're re-releasing it's kind of co-advertising here it's basically they're re-releasing their album Nevermind the Bollocks here's the Sex Pistols
[SPEAKER_10]: And that's coming out on the 29th, which is actually the day after Guitar Hero comes out over here.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know why they decided to re-record it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Probably because it's good press.
[SPEAKER_12]: Going to our chatroom, chat.orangehoundsradio.com, DarkTetsuya asks, wasn't that in Guitar Freaks at one point?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes, it was, but it was a shitty cover of it was in the game.
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, why don't you start us off with tonight's FUs of the week?
[SPEAKER_12]: Um... My FU of the week goes towards, um...
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it's actually going to go to work.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just in general.
[SPEAKER_07]: I actually went and got my business license on Wednesday so that I can hopefully quit my job and get to working at a spa.
[SPEAKER_07]: That'd be so nice.
[SPEAKER_07]: And so, it really, really just sort of made me realize how much more futile what I do is.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, F you to work.
[SPEAKER_11]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_10]: After the bad drivers, I was commuting back from
[SPEAKER_10]: Oakland Today, and there are just some people out there that don't really follow any of the laws of the road.
[SPEAKER_10]: In fact, just weave in and out.
[SPEAKER_10]: I watched a truck almost flip itself because it turned so tight, you know, trying to go between cars and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, you know, there's just some people, and there's a guy with some riced up car or something that just decided, oh, I'm going to just cut through cars and stuff, no signal, no nothing, just
[SPEAKER_10]: Try and kill people.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, fuck them.
[SPEAKER_10]: Um, I'm gonna give an F you.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, sorry.
[SPEAKER_10]: One more thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: F you to the California Highway Patrol for stopping the freeway, you morons.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, you know, they do all these things to stop people from speeding.
[SPEAKER_10]: So one of those things apparently is to stop traffic on the freeway completely.
[SPEAKER_10]: All lanes at one time.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because that solves the problem.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, it doesn't.
[SPEAKER_10]: That causes more traffic.
[SPEAKER_10]: People become late and they speed more, you stupid dumb fucks.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_12]: That does seem like a little silly idea.
[SPEAKER_12]: Unless there's an axe in the head.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, they just... For no reason?
[SPEAKER_10]: No reason.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're bored today.
[SPEAKER_12]: Let's screw with traffic.
[SPEAKER_12]: My FU of the week goes to my ass.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hear me out here for a minute, because I was a little bit intoxicated, and I slipped and I fell on this chest that's in my room, this little green, not a treasure chest, but a chest for clothes and stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: I slipped and I fell right on the corner of that, so my butt hit that corner, and now it's red and practically bruised.
[SPEAKER_06]: I saw Rob's butt.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, I showed it to Jamie earlier, but only because I'm gay and she's a married woman, so it's okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: I gave Rob drugs.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, and she evaluated it and gave me some ibuprofen that was very strong.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you feel better?
[SPEAKER_12]: I do, actually.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't feel it at all.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's nice.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's it for the FUs of the Week.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hooray.
[SPEAKER_12]: Let's go back to some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_12]: And, you know, this is almost FU of the Week worthy.
[SPEAKER_12]: Did you know, I found this on Dig.
[SPEAKER_12]: There's this site, eBizMBA, that tracks the top 25 gaming sites on the Internet.
[SPEAKER_12]: Orange Lounge Radio is nowhere to be found
[SPEAKER_12]: DMN did the interview with a gal from Nintendo who got fired over her blog.
[SPEAKER_12]: DMN actually interviewed her for their own show, STFU, which is on Thursdays on the station.
[SPEAKER_12]: We were going to rebroadcast it because it's kind of an in-the-news current thing that we thought you guys would be interested in.
[SPEAKER_12]: Apparently, their connection sucked and the audio quality wasn't worth it to try and bring it to you guys.
[SPEAKER_12]: We made an editorial decision to cut it out.
[SPEAKER_12]: What about the guy that proposed over... I didn't hear back from him on MySpace.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: Maybe he's listening.
[SPEAKER_12]: We'll still have him on the show.
[SPEAKER_12]: Call in.
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_12]: The Quantcast monthly visitors.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't even know what that is.
[SPEAKER_12]: And the Alexa ranking, which, by the way, I think is bullshit.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think you should not use... Oh, God, I fucking hate Alexa.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's like one of the biggest plagues on the internet.
[SPEAKER_12]: Who owns it?
[SPEAKER_12]: Like Amazon or some shit?
[SPEAKER_12]: All it is is a spyware bar that you basically have to install on your computer and it tracks what websites you visit.
[SPEAKER_12]: And they have the balls to release this ranking of the top sites based on who has this Alexa toolbar installed.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_12]: That's not... I mean, like, because if you are anti-spyware, anti-toolbar, all this stuff, you probably visit different sites than people who get suckered to putting this stuff on their computer.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anyway, I could just go off all day.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because I... One of the things I hate about Wikipedia is that they use the Alexa ranking as some of their, like, is a site worthy to be on our page.
[SPEAKER_12]: Which, how we've managed to keep our article up on Wikipedia for so long, I'll never be able to figure that out.
[SPEAKER_12]: But thank you all to the listeners who made that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anyway...
[SPEAKER_12]: Sorry, I have my soapbox there.
[SPEAKER_12]: Top 25 sites.
[SPEAKER_12]: Number one video game site, IGN.com.
[SPEAKER_12]: Followed by GameSpot.com at number two, GameFacts.com at number three, GamesRadar.com at number four, which kind of surprised me.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'd never really heard of it until a few months ago.
[SPEAKER_12]: UGO.com at number five, GameSpy, CheatCC, Kotaku, Yahoo Video Games, and GameTap rounding out the top ten.
[SPEAKER_10]: Filefront is a gaming site.
[SPEAKER_12]: Apparently Filefront is a gaming site, number 11.
[SPEAKER_12]: Fileplanet.
[SPEAKER_12]: Some other big blogs, 1UP, who does a bunch of podcasts, they're number 13 on the list.
[SPEAKER_12]: Destructoid is number 20.
[SPEAKER_12]: Joystick is number 19.
[SPEAKER_12]: And that's all I care to mention.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're getting beat out by Strategy Informer.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, you know, life sucks sometimes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, we don't have the budget.
[SPEAKER_10]: I bet you all these people...
[SPEAKER_10]: None of these are, of course, independent sites.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, maybe Kotaku, I guess.
[SPEAKER_10]: And Joystick.
[SPEAKER_10]: And Destructoid.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't want to get into the politics of it all.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anywho.
[SPEAKER_12]: Some of the chat is asking, where's All Games?
[SPEAKER_12]: Nope, All Games didn't make the top 25 either.
[SPEAKER_12]: But All Games doesn't really do news.
[SPEAKER_12]: All Games is only shows.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think if there were more to it, there might be more people going there.
[SPEAKER_12]: Maybe someday.
[SPEAKER_10]: I trust that we're at the top of
[SPEAKER_10]: Our favorite sites.
[SPEAKER_10]: And that's all it really gets.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's alright, we're just underground, yo.
[SPEAKER_12]: We're just underground.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're way under the radar.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're like... We're like underground.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_10]: In a bomb shelter.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not in a bomb shelter.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm in the land of awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, speaking of something that could be awesome, but I sincerely doubt it, is that there is a rumor about a Mortal Kombat game that will feature characters from the DC Universe trying to do a versus type of thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, yeah, I don't know how I feel about that.
[SPEAKER_07]: In fact, I feel that it's going to be kind of dumb.
[SPEAKER_10]: What is that?
[SPEAKER_10]: A ramp I see there and a tank with sharks.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's going to happen soon?
[SPEAKER_10]: I wonder.
[SPEAKER_07]: DC vs. Mortal Kombat DC vs. Mortal Kombat
[SPEAKER_12]: In fact, this reeks of fanboyism to me.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't even think it's true.
[SPEAKER_07]: The difference between Mortal Kombat and Street Fighter is that Street Fighter is a good game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mortal Kombat's fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: The next game that they're going to do is going to be a versus game.
[SPEAKER_10]: They never said it was versus DC.
[SPEAKER_10]: Although that would make sense.
[SPEAKER_10]: To be honest, I think the Mortal Kombat series, DC, I don't think would go for it if you think about it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, granted, I think DC versus Street Fighter makes sense because it's more comic book-y and stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: Mortal Kombat is just kind of violent.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, maybe they're going to change Mortal Kombat's image.
[SPEAKER_10]: They should be like Mortal Kombat versus Monsters of Horror or something like that, where they have Freddy and Jason and shit like that.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know why I like the Mortal Kombat games, especially the more recent one?
[SPEAKER_12]: I like them because they have more than just the fighting game stuff in them, like the kart thing, the adventure modes.
[SPEAKER_12]: The games have quite a bit of depth.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, they're not like OMG, drop everything.
[SPEAKER_12]: They're no Soul Calibur 2, that's for sure, but they're fun.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think you guys are being too hard on Mortal Kombat.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: You guys are just tough to please.
[SPEAKER_10]: I am tough to please.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyways, one game though that I do like is Saints Row.
[SPEAKER_10]: And Saints Row 2 has been confirmed for PlayStation 3 and the 360.
[SPEAKER_10]: Some of the changes coming with the brand new version of the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Of course, it's going to bring back Stillwater as well as including some improvements.
[SPEAKER_10]: to the online game, both the online co-op now being added and multiplayer, open world multiplayer matches, so that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, don't get me wrong, the multiplayer is okay, but I kind of wish that it was open world, like Grand Theft Auto on the PSP and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, after a while, those three maps that you have for deathmatch really get old, so...
[SPEAKER_10]: DanceOnline.com
[SPEAKER_12]: Dance Online is that dancing MMO that was created by David Perry, who also made Earthworm Jim.
[SPEAKER_12]: I played it a long time ago, and I wasn't that impressed with it.
[SPEAKER_12]: It didn't have a lot of songs that really grabbed me, but now I've got to go back and take a look because Dance Online has gotten some updates, and they have apparently made some type of agreement with Warner Brothers Records or Warner Music.
[SPEAKER_12]: There are now songs from...
[SPEAKER_12]: Ashley Tisdale, The Ramones, The Click 5, 30 Songs from Warner Music, also in the game now, Paris Hilton.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know you wanna.
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_12]: No, I don't.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know you wanna.
[SPEAKER_12]: Also added more items to the shop for more customization.
[SPEAKER_12]: Over 150 hairstyles.
[SPEAKER_12]: And apparently the game has also added
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkTetsuya says, pass.
[SPEAKER_12]: MrDeBucket says, David Perry for the lose.
[SPEAKER_12]: Ouch.
[SPEAKER_12]: ShadowCharlie says, play Supernova 2 for Ashley Tisdale.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know, a sad time or a sad sign that things are changing.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know how like our show started off like, you know, because we met all playing DDR.
[SPEAKER_12]: We were all about the DDR.
[SPEAKER_12]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: I just don't want to buy... Well, first off, I'm not buying DDR Haas Party unless I get it for free.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then Supernova 2, I listened to the music.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was disappointed with the Trip Machine remix.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was crap.
[SPEAKER_10]: So...
[SPEAKER_10]: And then... Is that your official review?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I did like the Fascination Max remix, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: It reminded me a lot of Healing Vision and then Healing Vision Angelic.
[SPEAKER_10]: That kind of remix of it.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then I didn't... Some of the songs, though, they didn't have ripped from it, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like Volcano, I didn't get to hear.
[SPEAKER_10]: But some of the other ones were okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think, though...
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll have to try it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want an actual machine to be out here, though, instead of having to play it on the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: But hopefully I'll get to play it soon.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right, well, one thing we're going to get to do very soon is open up the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's right, you guys email us every week at mailbag at orangelaunchradio.com and we read some of our favorites here on the program.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, DarkSakura, jump in the mailbag, pull out some letters, let's see what we got.
[SPEAKER_07]: First email.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dun-dun-dun!
[SPEAKER_07]: It comes from, uh... Well, you didn't give a nickname, so I'm just gonna say Aaron.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi, first of all, I want to say I love the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's the only podcast I listen to that doesn't ever bore me.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's funny, entertaining, and informative.
[SPEAKER_07]: As for Rob's comments about Facebook, I totally agree.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's so annoying to log in and have, like, five invitations for apps that you don't care about.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't think that it's as bad as MySpace, but I do think Facebook is headed in that direction.
[SPEAKER_07]: I am not alone.
[SPEAKER_07]: I got a Facebook, too, and I...
[SPEAKER_07]: I hate it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, I do kind of like getting the notifications on my phone sometimes, but that shit gets old.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, to continue.
[SPEAKER_07]: I also have a few comments on Halo 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love the first game.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's the reason I bought an Xbox.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was disappointed in Halo 2, and not long after Halo 2, I stopped telling people that I played it because I didn't want them to think I was a stupid frat boy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, that was gross.
[SPEAKER_07]: I eventually stopped playing Halo 2 with anyone I didn't know because of the ignorant people on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm excited for Halo 3, but I won't be going to the midnight release because of the people that will be there.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think the Halo series started out well and the games are still solid, but the atmosphere surrounding the games has dissolved into one blatant commercialism and poor sportsmanship, for lack of a better word.
[SPEAKER_07]: Love this show, guys.
[SPEAKER_07]: Keep it up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Erin.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, I seem to remember we were talking about last week, you know, who's actually going to the midnight release.
[SPEAKER_12]: Do we hear from anyone who actually went?
[SPEAKER_12]: This guy said he wanted to go.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, shall I move forward to the next one, Rob?
[SPEAKER_07]: You may.
[SPEAKER_07]: OLR Dudes and Chicks.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm playing Worms 2 Open Warfare on my PSP-2000.
[SPEAKER_07]: T-A-R-D is TARD
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, TARD is slang for retard, which is a naughty word.
[SPEAKER_10]: They also censored death, because I had a team death something.
[SPEAKER_12]: Can you play this online?
[SPEAKER_12]: No.
[SPEAKER_12]: You can play it on Wi-Fi.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, then why bother censoring it?
[SPEAKER_12]: The person's got to be in the room with you.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't get it.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's overdoing it.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's from Dark Raven.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, it's being censored because I guess TARD is a bad word, and so anything with that in it, you know...
[SPEAKER_12]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_07]: I just wanted to say how great a birthday present it would be if it ended up happening.
[SPEAKER_12]: Let's take a minute to talk about Galaxy Wars Cats.
[SPEAKER_12]: Genius Marketing Campaign, those folks at Geometry Wars Galaxy.
[SPEAKER_12]: Have you seen the site, gwgcats.com?
[SPEAKER_12]: Somebody's taken the lolcats trend and made an advertising campaign out of it.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think the advertising campaign for Geometry Wars Galaxies is brilliant because you can even watch the commercial.
[SPEAKER_12]: Like, wait, hold on.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm going to go to the site.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't care if I sound like a consumer whore, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_12]: I've seen so many lame video game commercials, and you might think this is lame.
[SPEAKER_12]: But I don't care.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think it's funny.
[SPEAKER_12]: They have this in theaters.
[SPEAKER_12]: This is so great.
[SPEAKER_12]: There's Geometry Wars and they have all these things like, I'm in your solar system on top of your leaderboards.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm in your battle grids topping your highest score and just all this funny stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: But then if you actually go to the website for Geometry Wars Galaxies, the little trailer for the game has a remake of Particle Man, which is so awesome.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hold on, I gotta play a little clip of the song from the trailer.
[SPEAKER_12]: This is from geometrywarsgalaxies.com slash US.
[SPEAKER_12]: Particle man, particle man, doing the things a particle can.
[SPEAKER_11]: What's he like?
[SPEAKER_11]: It's not important.
[SPEAKER_11]: Particle man, is he a dot or is he a speck?
[SPEAKER_11]: When he's underwater, does he get wet?
[SPEAKER_12]: Or does the water get him instead?
[SPEAKER_12]: Cause get it?
[SPEAKER_12]: Cause it's like triangle man and I don't know, it's funny.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is that They Might Be Giants?
[SPEAKER_12]: No, it's like... Oh, unless they redid the song.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's definitely not the original.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I mean, I was going to say, because the voice was kind of... A little bit.
[SPEAKER_12]: Could have been.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: Great.
[SPEAKER_12]: Love it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, then the next email, then, if you are ready...
[SPEAKER_12]: Actually, real quickly, I just want to say, Black Wolf, of course, our old buddy Bobby B is in chat right now, and he does his own show, of course, on all games.
[SPEAKER_12]: It also airs on Sunday nights, and sometimes when he's done with his show, he'll come listen to ours for a little bit because he's awesome.
[SPEAKER_12]: And he says, oh, man, that email was a mass email to a lot of podcasts.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think he said that about the last email, the one about the worms, too.
[SPEAKER_12]: So somebody is, like, mass emailing podcasts with the same question.
[SPEAKER_12]: Amazing.
[SPEAKER_12]: We got spammed.
[SPEAKER_12]: I wonder if they're trying to see if the different podcasts give different answers, if it's some type of survey.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well then, I wonder if they're spamming all the podcasts about whether their penis needs to be larger too.
[SPEAKER_12]: Or maybe they're trying to spam all the podcasts with a Worms 2 email so people will actually talk about Worms 2 on the podcast.
[SPEAKER_12]: We just bought it, hook, line, and sinker.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's a bunch of people who think that I need a bigger penis too, apparently in my email.
[SPEAKER_07]: So we actually deleted my email address.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't think it'll work, but good luck.
[SPEAKER_12]: You never know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, if they get them back, then they have auto-delete things or some shit.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm actually thinking about changing it anyway.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: But anyway, next email now, please, please, please, please.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes, yes, yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Can I has email, Rob?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes, you can has email.
[SPEAKER_07]: Last episode, Loki said, nothing is original anymore.
[SPEAKER_07]: Originality is hard to find.
[SPEAKER_07]: One of my favorite quotes is from one of my design teachers is, you are only as original as your sources are obscure.
[SPEAKER_07]: Games are the same as design.
[SPEAKER_07]: I do agree with that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Talk about a reward for good gaming.
[SPEAKER_07]: or the end for Final Fantasy 2 in the US.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's Final Fantasy 4 overseas.
[SPEAKER_07]: The page turning with the great music, it was incredible.
[SPEAKER_07]: I sat and smiled contentedly for a good half an hour.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can actually say the same thing about Final Fantasy 6, well 3 over here when it came out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Was that I actually finally decided to wait and be patient and wait for Shadow to catch up with you so that he doesn't die.
[SPEAKER_07]: Spoiler!
[SPEAKER_07]: And got the ending with everybody alive.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that made me happy.
[SPEAKER_07]: and even retarded Gogo.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Stupid Mimic
[SPEAKER_12]: It was weird.
[SPEAKER_07]: At any rate, now I look for these things.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want to care about my characters on normal story-based games.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not always easy to find.
[SPEAKER_07]: I get by these days with a good triple Windfury crit on any gnome anywhere, or seriously just killing anything alliance, but that kind of quick fix can't replace the more in-depth stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: What are some of the moments that got you guys all teary-eyed or made you jump like an idiot?
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's hear it for the gamers.
[SPEAKER_07]: Spelled G-A-Y-M-E-R-S Apparently Seattle is the gamer mecca Really?
[SPEAKER_12]: And that comes from No Soul Boy I knew there was a reason I liked Seattle No, uh Let's see, games that got me Well, okay, games that got me a jump would be Silent Hill Like any of them Games that got me all Well, I actually Cared when Eris died in Final Fantasy 7 I cheered You're a bitch I'm not a bitch, I hated her the entire fucking game
[SPEAKER_07]: and oh my god, I hated her and I was so happy when she died.
[SPEAKER_12]: I got a little choked.
[SPEAKER_12]: I got verklempt when that happened.
[SPEAKER_12]: Actually, I got a little verklempt playing Eternal Sonata the other day.
[SPEAKER_12]: That game is sad.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's about all these dying kids and stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's kind of sad.
[SPEAKER_07]: I laughed my ass off during the bitch slap fight in Final Fantasy VII between Scarlet and Tifa and...
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh God, there was a game, though, that made me completely freaking bawl.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I couldn't remember what it was, because it was a few years ago.
[SPEAKER_07]: I do know one game that completely cracked me up, and that was... Now, crap, I can't remember the name of it, but it had the girl with the red pigtails, and she used a...
[SPEAKER_07]: The Rings, The Chakram for her weapons, and you could play as either the girl or the boy.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it had a really cool name in Japan, and then it came out with, like, Winds of Fate in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_07]: But that game had lots of crack me up bunny moments, because she was just over the top.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't remember the game that made me freaking bawl like a baby, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was, like, people dying in the game.
[SPEAKER_12]: Mario is Missing.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't believe he's missing!
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't believe I'm playing this game!
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't find him!
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm so mad!
[SPEAKER_07]: People go to YouTube and look up Asshole Mario.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's some talent.
[SPEAKER_12]: I love Asshole Mario.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's people who what they did is took Super Mario Brothers and did ROM hacks with it to make these intensely hard levels.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the thing about these hard levels is that they are not unplayable.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can beat them.
[SPEAKER_07]: But you have to have the mad skills to do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And time and patience and be willing to die.
[SPEAKER_07]: The only thing that's annoying about the Asshole Mario levels is that they keep showing people dying over and over and over again.
[SPEAKER_07]: And what they should do is just show someone playing through the level and then show them dying.
[SPEAKER_12]: My favorite was how they showed just the very start of the game and the very first level the guy goes into.
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like an invisible coin block.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, back to the email, shall I?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is addressed to me, and then you guys in parentheses.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is Rob with 2Bs, by the way.
[SPEAKER_12]: Who's it from?
[SPEAKER_07]: I just told you, Rob.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, hi, Rob and 2Bs.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's a little war of words going on between a site called GameTwat.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think that's great.
[SPEAKER_07]: It just gets funnier each time you think slash say it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And GamePolitics, as well as GP versus JackiePoo.
[SPEAKER_07]: GameCock is a publisher, or a developer?
[SPEAKER_07]: Developer.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think people need to lighten up and realize how we secretly enjoy the antics between Jackie Poo and GP Butting Heads.
[SPEAKER_07]: GT is funny if you let it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I personally believe that porn court filing story on Jackie Poo was his attempt to show the judge was biased against him in the case versus the Florida Bar.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mission accomplished, but now the legal system is against him.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry for the misquote, but if you strike Jackie Poo down, he'll become stronger than ever.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'd rather we adopt a meh attitude and maybe he'll start eating crayons as recreational drugs.
[SPEAKER_07]: Raw bubba.
[SPEAKER_07]: And he wrote bubba afterwards.
[SPEAKER_12]: This GameTwat site looks like Perez Hilton.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's awfully pink and that joystick looks like a cock.
[SPEAKER_12]: Um...
[SPEAKER_12]: BlackWolf in chat says something interesting.
[SPEAKER_12]: He says, wow, GameTwat is getting really too much publicity over this.
[SPEAKER_12]: So what's the debate?
[SPEAKER_12]: What are they mad at each other about?
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't get it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hold on, I'm trying to figure this out, because GameTwat interviewed him.
[SPEAKER_12]: I can't believe he would have interviewed with a site called GameTwat.
[SPEAKER_12]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_12]: Hi, we're with GameTwat, we want to interview you.
[SPEAKER_12]: Whatever, I don't want to get involved in the drama.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's more publicity for both sites.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, we just reported on it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Congratulations to both sites.
[SPEAKER_12]: We need to start a fight with somebody.
[SPEAKER_12]: Who can we start a fight with?
[SPEAKER_12]: How about all games?
[SPEAKER_12]: No, that's too obvious.
[SPEAKER_07]: How about Bobby?
[SPEAKER_07]: Bobby, we're going to start a fight with you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is that okay?
[SPEAKER_12]: That's too obvious.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's too obvious if we start a fight with somebody.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll start a fight with you when it makes sense.
[SPEAKER_10]: What about the developer of the Eye of Judgment?
[SPEAKER_12]: I wanted to make a correction to that rather formal review of Earth Defense Forces sent in last week.
[SPEAKER_12]: There are more enemy types than just ants in the game but it turns out they're the best.
[SPEAKER_07]: By the way, having played Metal Slug Anthology this week, I agree with Loki that every Metal Slug game is exactly the same, even if they are really fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: Enemies, weapons, and even goddamn mini-bosses are repeated.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what, so.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can get turned into undead in the later ones.
[SPEAKER_07]: To continue, last one.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dun-dun-dun.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi, OLR people, this is Maury again.
[SPEAKER_07]: earlier this week I was able to get a Wii with money from various sources and so far I've been enjoying it immensely my house has been lacking in a home version of DDR for quite some time so I splurged and picked up the new DDR hottest party bundle that came out Tuesday I think anywho the game's in a nutshell excellent
[SPEAKER_07]: It's easily the best DDR home version in a while.
[SPEAKER_07]: The song list is a tad shorter than the average game by about 50 total, but most of those songs are actually fun to play.
[SPEAKER_07]: About half of it consists of licenses.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're all covers, but they range in quality from good to questionable.
[SPEAKER_07]: For some reason, the 80s ones tend to be the most fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: Blue Monday by New Order is the first one that comes to mind.
[SPEAKER_07]: The original songs in the game are pretty awesome, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: Furthermore, whoever did the step charts for this game needs to stay around forever.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's a wide range of difficulty.
[SPEAKER_07]: A couple of genuine 10-footers in the other charts are fun without being mind-numbingly boring.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Wii remote motions are kind of hard to get the hang of, though, and the game doesn't give you any advice besides swinging the controller.
[SPEAKER_07]: As far as I can tell, the best way to do it is to hold the remote and nunchuck in front of you vertically and swing them forward.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, and the new Love Shine remix is rad.
[SPEAKER_07]: Finally, a quick question.
[SPEAKER_07]: What other Wii games are good at the moment?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm into quirky stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Cheers, Mori.
[SPEAKER_07]: I still love Trauma Center.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you really want quirky, escape from Bug Island.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_12]: The possible fight between OLR and Blackwolf He says, we tried to fight However, Loki refused to play Chromehounds So I won by default Dude, it was like me and some other person I think I already sold my copy back GS68 says also that we should be fighting with Bobby Blackwolf See, that doesn't work Mr. DeBucket suggests that we should have a fight with Tekken Games
[SPEAKER_12]: BlackWolf suggested that we fight one up.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I'm like, I'll fight him with a cricket bat.
[SPEAKER_12]: That fight's so 2006.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm over my issues with 1UP.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm over my issues.
[SPEAKER_10]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_12]: I guess so we can't fight anybody, so we have to love everybody.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hugs and kisses all around.
[SPEAKER_12]: We love everyone.
[SPEAKER_10]: The Nintendo Wii online development staff, how about that?
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's fight them.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, but we need a good fight, like a really good bang-up fight that people will report on.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because it's like, you know, OLR threatened to kill somebody's family or something.
[SPEAKER_12]: No.
[SPEAKER_10]: Can't threaten to kill families.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's illegal.
[SPEAKER_12]: I know, it is illegal.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_12]: We need to get some really good dirt on somebody and start a fight with them.
[SPEAKER_12]: Be good for publicity.
[SPEAKER_12]: Can you work on that, Loki?
[SPEAKER_12]: You have ties in dark places.
[SPEAKER_12]: Get some dirt on another cast.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right, anyway.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, don't you know, I'm just like the fucking sleuth.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right, then get some news.
[SPEAKER_10]: God.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyways, so, you know, when I'm not digging up dirt, apparently, we're going to be talking about Square Enix, and they're focusing on overseas.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, that's a surprise.
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess, you know, of course, since they're only known, well...
[SPEAKER_10]: Square Enix is mainly known for the Final Fantasy and Dragon Quest series.
[SPEAKER_10]: A lot of other stuff that they used to do, unfortunately, never saw remixes.
[SPEAKER_10]: I really want Einhander.
[SPEAKER_10]: But now apparently they're going to be focusing on overseas markets that have increased more than three times the size of the Japanese market.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank God!
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe that means we'll actually get Final Fantasy XIII in a timely manner.
[SPEAKER_10]: So they're having to wait for Japan to get it and then us getting it way afterwards.
[SPEAKER_10]: So they had apparently two strategies planned to seize the opportunities.
[SPEAKER_10]: First, they're of course going to increase their distribution channel ties throughout both the United States and I believe in Europe.
[SPEAKER_10]: And of course, the second is developing more titles overall.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Gary's Mod
[SPEAKER_12]: 59.99 on the 360, 49.99 on the PC, Half-Life 2, 1 and 2, Team Fortress 2, and as Loki said, Portal, all in the orange box.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, maybe this is the perfect opportunity for me to check it out because I haven't really played Half-Life a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, a little bit.
[SPEAKER_12]: But I don't play a lot of these first-person shooters and stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: So if you're going to buy it, Loki, then I'll check it out when you get it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: But it's gone gold, so those of you guys that are excited about it, I know there's a couple people on my Twitter that are really excited about the Orange Box.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's on its way very soon.
[SPEAKER_12]: So take a look for it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I can't say that I'm too excited about this bit of news because honestly I don't give a crap about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: But some people are happy about it, so for anyone who's interested in the Sam & Max series, Season 2 will be on GameTap starting November 8th for those who have subscribed for it.
[SPEAKER_07]: and it has Ice Station Santa.
[SPEAKER_12]: For the person who emailed earlier about the quirky games, here you go, Sam & Max.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think this is a good little quirky game.
[SPEAKER_12]: Fun to play.
[SPEAKER_07]: Enjoy.
[SPEAKER_07]: You don't like Sam & Max?
[SPEAKER_07]: I never got into it.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's fun.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's cute.
[SPEAKER_12]: And funny.
[SPEAKER_12]: I like how it's the only episodic game I can think of that actually continued to put out episodes.
[SPEAKER_12]: Most episodic games you hear about die after two episodes.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_07]: Shenmue.
[SPEAKER_12]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: Shenmue was supposed to be a series of... They were supposed to have a whole line of them giving episodes of What's-His-Face's quest.
[SPEAKER_12]: But see, somebody just pooped and quit along the way, and this...
[SPEAKER_12]: I blame all the Dreamcast haters.
[SPEAKER_12]: So hooray to it being a good episodic game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I did not drop my microphone.
[SPEAKER_07]: So.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right, we're going to open the Skype line very soon.
[SPEAKER_12]: If you want to give us a call, 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: But one more story before we get to that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyways, so it's a little bit disappointing because this was one of the big features of Unreal Tournament 3 for the PlayStation 3, but no cross-platform play.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was apparently too hard to make, so they scrapped it.
[SPEAKER_10]: So you'll only be able to play people on the PC if you have the PC version, and only be able to play people on the PlayStation 3 if you have the PlayStation 3 version.
[SPEAKER_10]: So sad.
[SPEAKER_12]: So people on PCs cannot play people on PlayStation 3s.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's correct.
[SPEAKER_12]: Which is kind of sad.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's a bummer.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right, well, we are going to open up the Skype line over at OrangeLoungeRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_12]: Our username, of course, is OrangeLoungeRadio on Skype, or our phone number, 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_12]: Let's open up the Skype line and see who can get on through.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hello, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_13]: It's the one and only Legend of Zaku.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hello, Legend of Zaku.
[SPEAKER_12]: What's on your mind, my friend?
[SPEAKER_13]: Just dealing with the aftermath of Digital Life this weekend.
[SPEAKER_12]: I was hoping some of the New Yorkers would call in and tell us all about Digital Life.
[SPEAKER_12]: I didn't get a chance to go.
[SPEAKER_12]: As you know, I wanted to go and I didn't get to go.
[SPEAKER_12]: Somebody on my Twitter said, well, not that I should be thankful I didn't go, but that it wasn't that good this year.
[SPEAKER_13]: You should be glad that you didn't go.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's just say a lot of drama is... Oh shit, what happened?
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, what happened, Zaku?
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, I just want to make this a short story.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't want to get people entangled in our current, you know, in the current affairs of our community.
[SPEAKER_12]: Wait, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, Saku, wait, hold on.
[SPEAKER_12]: Remember we were talking about that fight earlier?
[SPEAKER_12]: Here we go, I bet we're about to start a fight right here.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_13]: To sum it up, basically, the biggest complaints right now were regarding freestyle and the way the rest of the other tournaments were run.
[SPEAKER_13]: Basically, the
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, for starters, the way freestyle turned out, in other words, people accusing the judges of favoritism, and, you know, people pissing and moaning on why certain of their, you know, their favorite, you know, freestylers didn't place at all, and there was a lot of name-calling.
[SPEAKER_13]: A lot of, you know, it even got to the point where one of the players from Expert Tech actually cursed out one of the organizers right there.
[SPEAKER_13]: And he got DQ'd but then ended up staying after apologizing.
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_13]: Just, you know, it's just a lot of immature bullshit that's just spanning four pages on the Freak right now.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't want to get into it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, hold on.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, so fine.
[SPEAKER_12]: Go to DDR Freak for your DDR drama.
[SPEAKER_12]: However, did this ruin digital life single-handedly?
[SPEAKER_12]: Did one little fight ruin the show?
[SPEAKER_12]: How did that go?
[SPEAKER_13]: No, it turned out pretty good.
[SPEAKER_13]: There was a lot of people that really complimented and really praised the organizers for running it.
[SPEAKER_13]: The Padmisses were another issue that certain people had sour grapes over.
[SPEAKER_13]: The way it was set up was that the machines were on the stage, and since the stage itself is not as secure as something like the ground,
[SPEAKER_13]: They have no choice but to put it up there.
[SPEAKER_13]: They have no say in where the machines are actually placed.
[SPEAKER_13]: The sponsors, the people running Digital Life, require them to put the machines up on the stage.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, it's not even that.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's just...
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's just put it this way.
[SPEAKER_13]: Pad misses were just caused by the instability of the stage.
[SPEAKER_13]: Just having all the machines and people up there.
[SPEAKER_13]: The censors just going off like that.
[SPEAKER_13]: That was one of the biggest complaints by certain people.
[SPEAKER_13]: They agreed with the judgment calls because the people running and taking down the scores were very meticulous.
[SPEAKER_13]: and making sure that whatever score was received was the fairest and most accurate score out there.
[SPEAKER_12]: Tell me one thing in digital life that was cool that has nothing to do with DDR.
[SPEAKER_13]: Guitar Hero 3.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's alright though, but I mean... It's fine.
[SPEAKER_12]: He was within the confines of the question.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, so Guitar Hero 3, how was it?
[SPEAKER_13]: It was alright, I mean...
[SPEAKER_13]: I only played it once, but so far it's just nice graphics.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's all same gameplay.
[SPEAKER_13]: New songs.
[SPEAKER_12]: New songs, same gameplay.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, but I just can't get my mind off of, you know...
[SPEAKER_13]: of the 800 pound gorilla in the room, which is the DDR tournament.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's still lingering right now.
[SPEAKER_13]: I just hope next year we just fix what we had to that went wrong this time.
[SPEAKER_12]: I can't take the DDR talk anymore.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_12]: I had to hit the red button to end it.
[SPEAKER_12]: I can't deal with the DDR drama anymore.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm sorry, guys.
[SPEAKER_12]: If you'd like to give us a call, 1-877-GAME-OLR
[SPEAKER_12]: Username OrangeLoungeRadio.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hi, you're on OrangeLoungeRadio.
[SPEAKER_12]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's GS68.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hi, GS68.
[SPEAKER_12]: What DDR drama would you like to report on tonight?
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, not really DDR drama.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just want to say drama in general sucks ass.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, drama in general is kind of crappy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, someone...
[SPEAKER_04]: Violated the card line thingy today when I was playing Maximum Tune 3
[SPEAKER_12]: Now we get into it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Can't we all just get along?
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, seriously, people?
[SPEAKER_12]: Y'all are fighting each other over... And here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_12]: You're starting fights over Dance Dance Revolution.
[SPEAKER_12]: Can't anyone see the comedy in this?
[SPEAKER_12]: And then now you're calling people a fag because they beat you to playing Midnight Maximum Tune.
[SPEAKER_12]: And this gives you the right to call other people gay?
[SPEAKER_12]: Come on!
[SPEAKER_07]: Because, you know, making it to a machine first is a really different sexuality.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh my god, I know.
[SPEAKER_12]: His penis must be so large that I'd be like, you know... How would you deal with someone hogging the machine when your turn was next?
[SPEAKER_12]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_12]: Drama sucks.
[SPEAKER_12]: Tell me something.
[SPEAKER_12]: I need to hear a happy story, GS68.
[SPEAKER_12]: Something good happened this week, didn't it?
[SPEAKER_12]: Anything?
[SPEAKER_12]: Something?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, since news sites don't cover arcade games, I'll cover the arcade games myself.
[SPEAKER_04]: I finally got to play Initial D for...
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I didn't even know Initial D4 came out.
[SPEAKER_04]: How was that?
[SPEAKER_04]: It was alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like the drifty physics because it felt more like drift racing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that something that's new over Initial D3?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, Initial D3, there was some drifting, but you couldn't see it unless you were in third-person view, which was useless because the camera wasn't right on your butt, so it's very hard to control your car.
[SPEAKER_12]: And does it still have all the fabulous Eurobeat in Initial D4?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but I heard you can't pick your own song and just randomly choose for you.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's so that the same person doesn't play Heartbeat over and over and over again because they don't know how to change the song.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's probably a good thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, now I'm hearing Speedcar over and over.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, the song goes, Speedcar, Speedcar, AE86 is coming.
[SPEAKER_12]: Now suddenly we've turned into a singing karaoke show.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, that's right.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, all Eurobeat songs sound the same.
[SPEAKER_12]: This is the strangest Skyblind segment ever.
[SPEAKER_12]: 877-GAME-OLR or username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio Give us a call, let's talk
[SPEAKER_12]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_12]: This is Brad from PodCulture.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello, Brad from PodCulture.
[SPEAKER_08]: So good to hear from you.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, you said you wanted to hear from somebody who was crazy enough to be in a midnight launch of Halo 3.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, and let me guess.
[SPEAKER_12]: It was you, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: So why?
[SPEAKER_12]: Why did you have to be there at midnight?
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, you couldn't wait till the next day?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's more of a social thing than anything else.
[SPEAKER_10]: I agree with that.
[SPEAKER_10]: He had to be there because someone cut in front of him for Midnight Maximum Tune 3 and the stage was unstable for DDR.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, when I had pre-ordered my copy at Best Buy, they had said that they were going to be open until midnight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ours here in Louisville weren't.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_08]: Louisville?
[SPEAKER_08]: Louisville.
[SPEAKER_08]: Louisville, Kentucky.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry, for a second I thought it was Lowellville.
[SPEAKER_12]: It looks like Louisville.
[SPEAKER_08]: Only city can take a horse race and turn it into a three week party.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: My uncle used to live there for a little while and that's exactly the same way he described it.
[SPEAKER_07]: He lived there for a little while with some woman that he was seeing and then he moved to right outside Nashville.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which is almost as bad.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right, so you were in the line in Louisville.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, I went to three different lines, actually.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dang, so you had to go all around.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, the Best Buy wasn't open, so our co-host, Glenn, had his pre-order at a GameStop over in Indiana.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that's about 15, 20 minutes away.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I drove over there to meet him, and they didn't have any more of the collector's edition.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I drove over to meet a friend at another GameStop here in Louisville.
[SPEAKER_08]: They didn't have any and wound up in line at Circuit City.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, okay, Circuit City.
[SPEAKER_12]: There's not a lot of people seem to shop at Circuit City anymore, so that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, there's only like 20 or 30 people in line.
[SPEAKER_12]: See what I mean?
[SPEAKER_12]: I remember when we went out, when the Nintendo Wii went on sale, we went around to all the different lines, which, by the way, yes, there is a difference between the Wii Midnight launch and this, is that you knew everybody was going to have Halo 3 coming out the ass the next day, but when the Wii came out, you had to be in line at midnight, or you weren't getting a Wii.
[SPEAKER_08]: I finally saw a Wii on the shelf the other day.
[SPEAKER_12]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_12]: Big difference.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anyway, yeah, there was like, what, four people at Circuit City?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, there was less than 20, 15, 20, 25 people, something like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: But so you got it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I got it, and the guy ahead of me spent like 800 bucks.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's right, you sent us a private message earlier, so he went all out.
[SPEAKER_12]: Did he say why he was so crazy for Halo?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, if he hadn't actually had his girlfriend with him, I would have thought he hadn't moved out of his parents' basement yet.
[SPEAKER_08]: He was pretty geeky.
[SPEAKER_12]: Maybe the girlfriend lives with him in the parents' basement.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, that could be it, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: Some girlfriends will visit their boyfriends in their parents' basement.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sometimes.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then they'll realize that he's kind of, you know...
[SPEAKER_07]: Not desirable.
[SPEAKER_07]: But he loves me.
[SPEAKER_08]: 800 bucks for a game.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was crazy.
[SPEAKER_07]: He hits me because he loves me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, you know, we are in Kentucky here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, hey, I'm not from too much farther away from there, so...
[SPEAKER_08]: It was actually a lot of fun hanging around talking to people.
[SPEAKER_12]: Now you sent me a private message about some of the voice acting in Halo 3 that you discovered during the credits.
[SPEAKER_12]: Some pretty popular sci-fi stars.
[SPEAKER_12]: I know you love your sci-fi.
[SPEAKER_12]: Who can we find in Halo 3 in the voice acting?
[SPEAKER_08]: Nathan Fillion, Adam Baldwin, and Alan Tudyk from Firefly.
[SPEAKER_08]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: And Katie Sackhoff from Battlestar Galactica.
[SPEAKER_12]: She is awesome and Bionic Woman now.
[SPEAKER_12]: of which I missed on Wednesday, but I have a T-vote.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm going to watch it a little later.
[SPEAKER_08]: She's freaking nuts on that show.
[SPEAKER_12]: I hear she's the reason to watch that show.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: So I'm definitely going to want to check that out.
[SPEAKER_12]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_12]: Maybe not A-list actors.
[SPEAKER_12]: In the sci-fi world, they're definitely on the A-list, but some pretty well-known actors there for the Halo 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: Every time I think of dude, I still cry over the end of Firefly.
[SPEAKER_12]: Let's not do spoilers.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not saying anything.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, come on.
[SPEAKER_08]: The movie's been out two years.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was just a sucky way to die, okay?
[SPEAKER_07]: That sucked.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm a leaf on the wind.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, you're a leaf pinned to a chair.
[SPEAKER_07]: Splat.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, man.
[SPEAKER_07]: I wanted to hunt Joss down and burn my Joss Whedon is my master now shirt.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right, nerds.
[SPEAKER_12]: We've got to wrap up this call and take some more nerdy calls.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to watch the Sarah Jane Adventures, I promise, since the new episodes are out.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, catch you later guys Alright, take care Brad, thanks for calling Ask and ye shall receive We asked to hear from crazies that were in the Halo 3 line and we heard from one, that was great Let's go to the next call Hello, you're on Orange Lawns Radio, who's this?
[SPEAKER_12]: Hello, can you hear us?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, hello?
[SPEAKER_12]: Hi, hello, who's this?
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, what's going on, this is GZ This is who?
[SPEAKER_12]: GZDR4E Okay, what's on your mind buddy?
[SPEAKER_03]: Digital Life Retro Arcade Area Big Problem Apparently on VIP Day on Thursday, they wanted Billy Mitchell to have a photo op with the Donkey Kong machine I was playing on the machine, they told me to get off the machine
[SPEAKER_03]: I refuse.
[SPEAKER_03]: They threatened to take my VIP pass and kick me off the premises.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I just let them have the machines.
[SPEAKER_12]: Were you going for a high score or something?
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, like, were you about ready to be the new King of Kong?
[SPEAKER_03]: What was that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Just playing the machines.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, I mean, how does that feel that they had to just kick you off there because somebody more important was in town and needed a photo op?
[SPEAKER_12]: That's kind of got to suck.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it's all about power there, I guess.
[SPEAKER_12]: You're going to have to actually get the world record on the machine and then you'll be able to get on any Donkey Kong machine you want in the world.
[SPEAKER_12]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_12]: So were you so mad that you just kind of left or did you walk around and check out other stuff that was at Digital Life?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I just left.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was mad.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, I'll try again next year.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anything else you want to share with our listeners?
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, take care.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, take care.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think there was connection problems there or something.
[SPEAKER_12]: Thank you for sharing the injustices of Donkey Kong in this world.
[SPEAKER_12]: Sorry to hear it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, let's go to the phones and take more calls.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_09]: So I heard that they were holding the bar and that wasn't cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: Welcome to DDR Drama Chat.
[SPEAKER_12]: How can we help you?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, this is Bobby.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's going on, guys?
[SPEAKER_12]: Hi, Bobby.
[SPEAKER_12]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_12]: It's good to hear from you.
[SPEAKER_12]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_09]: You were asking about people that were in a Halo 3 midnight launch.
[SPEAKER_12]: How did I know you'd call about this?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, what happened?
[SPEAKER_12]: What's your story?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, actually, the full story I'm not going to go into, but I was actually up in Bellevue, Washington as a guest of Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I attended one of the big midnight launches.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was not standing in line for it.
[SPEAKER_09]: But it was a huge party.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, it was actually fun being there.
[SPEAKER_09]: I had fun and I wasn't even getting the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: And Master Chief, he's skinnier in person.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just wanted to throw that out there.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: So what did you guys get to do?
[SPEAKER_12]: Didn't you guys get to go hand out goodies to people in line and stuff?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I handed out some Halo 3 shirts and we had some Halo 3 lanyards and these little $5 Burger King credit card things.
[SPEAKER_09]: so we were giving out like it doesn't get you a Happy Meal or anything but it was at least $5 towards something and we were just giving those out to people in the line for doing stupid stuff or just throwing them out that sounds like fun were there tons of people there?
[SPEAKER_09]: there were probably about 400 wow 400 to 500 people there all in line like stretched all the way down to the Home Depot that was across the parking lot dang
[SPEAKER_09]: and everything and like Mountain Dew was giving out like big game fuel and all their other stuff and Ball showed up with this big huge van and Fungi showed up in a big charter bus coming straight from their launch party so they were all boozed up and giving out calendars and swag and Bill Gates showed up he shook hands with the first like 50 people in line right after he rolled out of bed but it was a big party I think Warren Moon was there and everybody was like we love you and Tecmo Ball
[SPEAKER_12]: I wish we could have been there to hand out orange soda and cookies in our traditional fashion, but maybe for Halo 4.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh wait, I guess there can't be a Halo 4, can there?
[SPEAKER_12]: They'll find a way.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just the end of the story arc.
[SPEAKER_09]: They never said it was the end of Halo.
[SPEAKER_12]: But doesn't the box advertise the end of Halo?
[SPEAKER_12]: Halo Wars.
[SPEAKER_12]: There'll be more.
[SPEAKER_12]: There'll be another game to get excited about later.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now they did throw out these stress balls that were oranges.
[SPEAKER_09]: and they were actually throwing them at people.
[SPEAKER_09]: Did you save one for us, Bobby?
[SPEAKER_09]: They didn't pelt them at me.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm so sorry.
[SPEAKER_12]: We'll just put that on the list of reasons to start a fight with you, that's all.
[SPEAKER_12]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: People were walking out of there with big Halo clicks, the big huge Spartan stuff because they were the WizKids stuff and
[SPEAKER_09]: and people were walking out of there with hundreds of dollars worth of stuff and I'm like, you guys realize this is just for a DVD?
[SPEAKER_12]: Did you see people dropping like $800 like the guy Brad said he saw that bought the Xbox?
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_09]: We did see somebody walk out with like the big huge Halo action clicks figuring it was a couple hundred and
[SPEAKER_09]: The Legendary Edition, and then I did see one Xbox 360 sold along with that stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: So yeah, I can fully believe.
[SPEAKER_09]: Was that people just caught up in the moment, you think?
[SPEAKER_12]: Or do you think there's just people that are that hardcore for their Halo?
[SPEAKER_09]: I think it'd be people that are that hardcore, or to buy the 360, it might be somebody who never got a 360 until Halo came out.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, like that would make sense because, you know, I got the Halo Xbox.
[SPEAKER_12]: The original Xbox is a Halo one because I didn't buy it until Halo was out.
[SPEAKER_12]: And, you know, it had been out a little while and they did those special green Xboxes.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I was like, oh, I have to get one of those.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, yeah, I guess that was it.
[SPEAKER_12]: I didn't wait a no midnight line for it either, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: And you don't you didn't need to wait in the midnight line because, like, as I've been telling some people, the Fry's Electronics near me.
[SPEAKER_09]: We walked in yesterday.
[SPEAKER_09]: There are ten Legendary Editions sitting on the shelf.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, I went to Fry's too, and they just had tons and tons of Halo 3.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I didn't even get the Limited Edition.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm not that into Halo.
[SPEAKER_12]: I just got the regular game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, they only gave us the regular game, so I don't have any of the cutscene discs or anything else that came with it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, Loki had the other one early, because he's sly like that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_12]: Which reminds me, I still need to load the bonus stuff that you have on your one disc, Loki.
[SPEAKER_12]: Don't let me forget.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, anything else you want to share with our listeners, Bobby?
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm glad to hear you had a good time.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, no, that's it.
[SPEAKER_09]: You just wanted to talk about the Halo 3 launch, but really, that guy, when he touched the bar and we just really all got pissed off at him and stuff, that just, they didn't kick him out.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, I had to hang up on Bobby because I didn't want to hear about DDR drama.
[SPEAKER_12]: and there is no bar raping in Halo, come on.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio, who's this?
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey guys, it's SSJ100 Matt.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, hello SSJ100 Matt, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm exhausted from digital life.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dare I ask about... I don't know, there's no drama on this call.
[SPEAKER_02]: Even though I judged... Praise you, you're a great man.
[SPEAKER_02]: Even though what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Even though I was helping the judge on the elephant in the room.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, well, tell us about Digital Life, like what else you saw there and some of the other stuff, because I have yet to hear what else there was at Digital Life besides DDR.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, for the most part, this is my first time going.
[SPEAKER_02]: From what I understand, it was a lot smaller than last year, but gaming-wise, I had a really good time.
[SPEAKER_02]: They've premiered a lot of games that haven't been out yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mostly PC stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got to play World of Conflict, World in Conflict I should say, which I thought was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wanted to try to get on Hellgate London, but the line was too long for that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the biggest surprise I would say, and Loki's going to hate me for this, was the Eye of Judgment.
[SPEAKER_12]: Really?
[SPEAKER_12]: Is this a positive review of the Eye of Judgment?
[SPEAKER_12]: You thought it was cool?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, yeah, I don't have a PS3 yet, but you know, I would seriously consider it.
[SPEAKER_12]: This is not the first person that's called in to say the Eye of Judgment is better than you think.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, I was hearing some good reviews from the Game Crazy managers when they got back from conference.
[SPEAKER_12]: What the crap is going on?
[SPEAKER_07]: That you don't have to photocopy or buy any booster packs or anything, that it comes with all of the cards available for the game.
[SPEAKER_12]: But Jamie, seriously, you did see the same thing we saw at E3 last year, right?
[SPEAKER_12]: with the eye of judgment.
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't go to the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: It doesn't come with all the cards because that's why they sell booster packs and assorted decks.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what they were saying at the Game Crazy Managers Conference that's coming with them all intact.
[SPEAKER_10]: I bet you it's not.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's from the vendor.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm misinformed.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_12]: Let's go back to the caller.
[SPEAKER_12]: What caller?
[SPEAKER_02]: From what I understand, from what I was told, actually Wizards of the Coast is handling the game packs, I believe.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I actually should because they were the one hosting the event.
[SPEAKER_02]: But anyways, they're going to be giving out 150 cards when you buy the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: At least that's what they say.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, maybe that was what it was.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, because they figured out probably that everyone's going to pirate them anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, actually, you know, I'm going to be sending you guys a couple gifts.
[SPEAKER_02]: And one of the gifts is actually a couple cards from the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you guys will get to check that out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Awesome!
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm actually thinking about getting the game, honestly.
[SPEAKER_12]: Go right ahead.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's not going to sell millions.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think this turnaround is hilarious in my own mind.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just from what I was hearing from the feedback from the managers conference, I was like, well, I'll give it a try.
[SPEAKER_07]: So maybe.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_12]: What else in digital life would you think was cool?
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, they touched on it before, but I really like Guitar Hero 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was kind of hard to hear any of the songs, because, you know, the whole convention itself was loud as hell.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it just reminds me, it just seems like a better version of 1 and 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: And someone said it seems like modifiers, but there are involved, but I don't know how true that is.
[SPEAKER_02]: But...
[SPEAKER_12]: So it didn't just feel like Guitar Hero 2 with new songs?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it didn't seem like a copy-and-paste, like, 80s style or whatever, 80s mix.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, which basically was a copy-and-paste job, but that's a whole other story.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right, so if you had to judge digital life on a scale of 1 to 10, what would you give it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, considering this was my first one, I'd have to give it, like, 7 out of 10.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right, that's not bad, not bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I'll be sending you guys out a couple of stuff, including some viewers I got from the elephant in the closet.
[SPEAKER_12]: The game we can't speak of tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to give it the JT treatment, I guess.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, we do love DDR, which is why it pains us so much to hear about all this drama.
[SPEAKER_12]: Can't we all just get along?
[SPEAKER_12]: You people are playing a dancing game.
[SPEAKER_12]: Don't take it that seriously.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, SJ100, Matt, we gotta let you go, but thank you so much for calling in and giving us a drama-free report from Digital Life.
[SPEAKER_12]: We appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't mention it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yep, take care.
[SPEAKER_12]: I love this.
[SPEAKER_12]: Mystic Gohan in chat sums this up perfectly.
[SPEAKER_12]: After this, who knows?
[SPEAKER_12]: Africa could be Loki's favorite game ever.
[SPEAKER_12]: Only if I get to run over the animals.
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, I like beer.
[SPEAKER_12]: My final thought is I need like another air conditioning vent in here because it's getting too hot.
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_10]: My final thought is Asshole Mario is hilarious.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hilarious.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like you can't stop watching it.
[SPEAKER_12]: I can't.
[SPEAKER_12]: We'll see you back here next week, boys and girls, for Orange Lounge Radio episode number 250, if you can believe it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm telling you, you know, I know how G4 is desperate for television to play all these back to back.
[SPEAKER_10]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's a good hour block.
[SPEAKER_07]: Isn't it a three-day weekend?
[SPEAKER_12]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: Next weekend.
[SPEAKER_12]: Is next weekend a three-day weekend?
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: Unless you get Columbus Day off.
[SPEAKER_07]: I get Columbus Day.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's why.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because I work for... I think it's Columbus Day.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because I get banking holidays.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, lucky you.
[SPEAKER_12]: Not me.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to get... I'm going to bring some Metoxa and drink it on the show.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: Stay tuned and see how that goes.
[SPEAKER_12]: We'll be back.
[SPEAKER_12]: Next week with more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: See you guys then.
[SPEAKER_12]: Thank you for supporting Independent Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: If you like what you hear, tell two people you know about the station or give us a review on iTunes and spread the love that is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: Have a great week.
[SPEAKER_12]: We'll see you next week.
[SPEAKER_00]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_00]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_00]: For more information on our live and podcast programs, visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com See you next week!