Orange Lounge Radio
There's a host, Dark Sakura
Sky and World of War
Tonight September 30th, 2007
Halo 3 breaks big records
Blue Dragon gets free download content
Could Katana someday do battle with Wonder Woman?
Orange Lounge Radio
Red Dragon gets free download content
priorities!
I want to know where the Tootsie Rolls are
There are no Tootsie Rolls
I do have brownies
There's no joke there
I really do have little yummy brownies
They taste like coffee too
Like the Starbucks ones
I'm hoping that if we can get all the computer issues worked out
We can go out into El Garage
I mean the studio
That's not a converted garage door
Remember change under the couch
We can go out there for next week's program
And I'm pretty excited about that
So it'll be fun
And no laundry baskets to be found out there
But there is a washer and dryer that will be off during the program
Anyhow
Let me also introduce the chatroom
Aren't you glad you subscribed us?
That's going to be just like, MOM! I'm recording my show!
Get out of here!
Gosh damn
Luckily I don't live with my parents
That's one good thing about the program
I don't live with my parents
We live with our parents
Good job everybody
You guys all have spouses though
I'm the only unmarried one
I haven't lived with my parents since I was 15
Ow
Mommy wow
Anyway there's the chatroom
chat.orangelaungeradio.com
We too says put up pics
Well we actually simulcast on operator11
So if you head on over to operator11.com
Of which I saw Frisbee put up the link in chat earlier
Or for those of you guys listening on the archive
And search for Orangelaungeradio
And you can look at the simulcast of our webcam
It's all archived on there
Because operator11 is cool and they let us eat up tons of disc space
With our big talking heads doing the podcast
Someone asked special brownies
Once again there is no budget
For special brownies
Like we could afford marijuana even if we wanted to eat it
Which I'm not really into that
Why would you want to eat marijuana?
Well apparently it gets you high
Yeah but it tastes like ass
I can't still
Stay on the smell of marijuana
Remember kids don't do drugs
Don't we do video games once in a while?
Here on this show
DarkSakura please save us from turning into the hashcast
And tell us about your gaming week
I play a lot of Ragnarok online
A lot
Dude I played this game called Ragnarok
You're so cool
Hey Rob shut up
I'm a level 91 assassin now
Been beating the shit out of ogres
And I've also got
People are going to yell at me
Because you're not supposed to do one
But I'm working on
Well I was going to make an agility spear knight
And now I'm making an agility
One handed sword crusader
So
But I am going to do a spear knight next
Because spear knights are cool
They have long pulls and poke things with them
Wow
Sounds kind of
Nevermind
I've not played any World of Warcraft
In fact I'm going to stop paying for it
While my computer is down
And I actually did not play any pinball this week
But
Excuse me
Halo 3 in my house
We had a bunch of people in our house
Doing multiplayer Halo campaigns
And then the other night
Dan decided to get all of his buddies
We had Will in one of the rooms
And then
Our friend Alex
Who is a crazy psycho ex-marine
Was that a LAN party?
A local area nerd party?
Yeah
But they beat it on Legendary
According to Dan
The way to beat Halo 3 on Legendary
Is to be an uber sniper
Good times
I've compared Legendary
To Nightmare on Doom
That's like old school Halo 1
Because that's the only way you could network back in the day
Was LANing it
I'm glad to hear
Actually I saw Dan online
And I saw that he was playing campaign
On Legendary and co-op
I was like wow
I play the game on normal
I would play on easy
But you don't get achievements on easy
I play on normal
I seriously died 10 times in the first level
I suck at Halo
So bad
There should be a charity for me
It's sad
Oh oh oh
It was this week
It's a flash game
What's that?
I think someone
IM'd it to me
I'm trying to find
Give me a second I don't get the name of it
It's basically like a stick figure
Stick figure version
Of Dragon's Lair
It's fucking fantastic
Down to having
Little music and death scenes
And the cut scenes
And all that fun
It's called Dungeon Escape
And it can be found
And I'm trying to get the
Address for people
It's at
Ok studiohunty
H-U-N-T-Y dot com
Slash dungeon
And I'm going to link it in the chat room
It's hilarious
It's not just hilarious it's HILARIOUS
HILARIOUS
Yeah I'm going to link it in the chat room
Alright well while that's being linked
If there's nothing else for your gaming week
We'll move on over to Loki, how was your gaming week?
My gaming week was fine
Let's see
I started off
Playing Halo 3 on
Legendary, single player
Because no one wants to fucking enjoy my games
Fuck you all, I'll beat it myself
And I'm better than you
I'll play with you but I'll probably hold you back
Whatever, I've been playing it
By myself
Wait I want to know where all this sand in your vagina is coming from
Are you sending out invites to people on your friends list?
No I don't send out invites at all
Well then if you don't invite people
Then how do you expect people to join your party?
I'm supposed to be an internet celebrity or something that says people
Wake up call
You are not famous
I have no patience to sit in the lobby for like
A long time
It's because I have boobies
But no it's fine
Actually it's funny because I'm getting stuck in the same spots
I did in the normal game
Wait what about Bobby?
I thought Bobby Blackwolf was your only friend
On Playstation 3
Isn't he your friend on Xbox Live?
Yeah but he's not on there
He plays the Halo
I've seen him on Halo a couple times
Well you should give him a call or something
Say hey Bobby
Oh yeah let me just
My phone that has everyone's phone number in it
Oh there it is, Bobby's number
Oh wait no I don't have Bobby's number
I don't have a whole phone that doesn't exist
Ok now
Really I could sit here saying hey
You know
Want to play some Halo 3 but to be honest
I don't know when I'm going to be online to play Halo 3
You know
I'm doing all sorts of busy stuff like
Going to see Eastern Promises and crap
So I don't know
But um
So other than playing Halo 3
I've actually, well of course more scenes
Row multiplayer and people are certainly pissed off
Because
It's kind of unfair for them
I've been playing on other people's systems
You know while
They were gone or something and
Yeah my system is way
Better
Like if I get caught on fire
I burn out a lot quicker
My rockets seem to have better accuracy
I can kill them a lot easier
I don't know why
But that's just the way it is
Anyways
Other than all that stuff
On the PSP I've been playing
Jackass the game
And I love it
It's so stupid and simple
It's so
It's such a you game
It's really, I mean it is not hard at all
To play through the game at all
And it's fun
It's just stupid little things
It's a great rental game
And I think it's also probably a good game
To have friends over
You can play it and laugh
On the PSP how do you play
Well not on the PSP but like
It's also on Playstation 2
I don't have the Playstation 2 version
Because my sister is still borrowing my Playstation 2
You need to call her up and say hey
Bring it back
I did say hey bring it back
But she hasn't brought it back yet
You send out the troops
And then let's see
Other than that I tried Driver 76
For the PSP
Much like every other Driver game known to man
I'm not going to try the Driver series anymore
I'm going to stay away from it
And I think that's pretty much it
Oh I played with
I've updated my firmware
On my PSP Slim
To the 3.71 CFW
Or whatever the new
One that's done by Team M33
Which ends up being Dark Alex anyways
The guy that did all the other custom firmwares
So now since I have
3.71 CFW I can put the official themes
On there and so I have
A cookie theme on my
Because it comes with it
A cookie theme?
Like
Like peanut butter cookies
Or Cookie Monster
It's chocolate chip cookies
And I will show you
It's hilarious
Sony would like to remind you
Not to eat your PSP
No but it seriously is the cookie theme
What about the OLR theme?
What happened to that?
I haven't made that yet
And I will get into that later
I was going to say I just had to pay to renew OLRPSP.com
Our PSP site this week
Oh it does look like someone ate your PSP
Oh I see
It changes all the icons into cookies as well
Hold on I'll put that on the OP11 cam in a minute
Get it?
Don't eat the PSP Jamie
It's not healthy
There's actually one thing that
I didn't make tonight
The Japan Playstation site
Released the official tool to make themes
So yes
We can make an OLR theme
For the PSP
And it's pretty sweet
But there's some other ones on there
They have like wipeout
And some pretty pink one
That I'm not going to put on my system
I'm sure Nellie would want that on hers
I don't know
So
It's neat I guess
I don't know if I'd upgrade it
To just get that
But it's neat
ShadowSlayer says
Lowkey's PSP is delish
Darktachidea says
This is a PSP made of chocolate chips and cookie dough
Could you imagine if the PSP could just make cookies?
It would be awesome
It would be totally worth the price
Even though the PSP
I've been growing fonder and fonder
This year and last year
When the thing first came out
I've been more fond of the PSP this year
It would be even awesomer if it made cookies
I think more people would buy those than DS's
If that happened
It would be hilarious
If they had an
Easy Bake Oven
Attachment for the DS
You know how they always put all these weird attachments
In the Game Boy Advance slot
Something like that
Where you actually program stuff in there
And you can cook a cookie at a time
It's a DS
That would be kind of neat
I don't know
Going on to my gaming week
I haven't played a whole lot
I did play some more Halo 3
Which you know I'm not a big fan of first person shooters
I do like Halo
I love that they
Just added all this crap into it
I don't know what else to call it
It's all this crap in the game
You can go back and watch your multiplayer matches
And take pictures
I don't know
There's not a lot I can say
Really the only people this is benefiting
Me talking about Halo 3
Is people that don't already own an Xbox 360
Because I think most people that do
Probably went out and got the game
Unless you hate first person shooters for some reason
In which case I find it hard to believe you got
Xbox 360 in the first place
To be honest I was never a fan of Halo
And Halo 3 is pretty cool
I think the matchmaking is pretty good
I do admit
I've played and certainly there's been news about that
This week which we'll get into a little later
But you know what it's not all about graphics
And they are bright though
And vibrant
The only reason I've always loved Halo before was multiplayer
And multiplayer doesn't disappoint
I mean in regards it is just
Halo 2 but you know
With more and that's okay
But if you're not a fan of Halo
At all I don't know if this
Is going to do it for you
Especially the single player mode man
There's no back story no nothing
I find it hard to follow because
I'm not good at single player therefore I
Don't really play the campaign modes of the other games
So anyway
That's that
Halo 3 and then
World of Warcraft I finally went back to after
About a three week vacation
I decided to go back to World of Warcraft this week
And
Trying to think how that's been going
I just hit level 66
Ran some instances with some friends
Over in uh near Thrallmar
I can't remember what that zone is called
But yeah back into World of Warcraft
Which I missed a little bit
And I'm glad I waited because now I have a bunch of friends in the guild
That are on the same level I am so we're running instances together
Good times
Other than that not a whole lot
There was no new arcade release this week
Did you notice that?
Am I the one that noticed that?
Like that they decided you know on Xbox Live arcade
That since Halo 3 came out they didn't need an arcade release this week
I mean I guess they released like a Bomberman pack
Or something there was nothing new
Am I the one that noticed that?
I was looking forward to something new on Wednesday
Well there wasn't anything new
I think just like you said
You know you almost didn't notice
Well I think probably a lot of people
Almost didn't notice
Yeah I think a lot of people probably didn't care
They've been doing two a week
So I mean that's pretty good
Yeah in our chat room HendersonMan says
I noticed I want Puzzle Quest
Yeah I kind of feel the same way like there's all this cool stuff
That I want
But Puzzle Quest isn't probably coming out until November
Because that's when the console versions are coming out
But then you know there's Res and there's
Res ain't coming out this year okay
I can tell you that much
You're a jerk
Just other stuff would be cool
Omega 5 maybe
I don't think Res is coming out this year
How about Castle Crashers?
Where the fuck is Castle Crashers?
There you go wasn't that supposed to be out last year?
Yeah
In our chat room sometimes our chatters like to post
About their gaming weeks
And I think my favorite gaming week goes to AJ Mix
In our chat room says
My gaming week, Legend of the Mystical Ninja
On Wii Virtual Console and Halo 3
And I think he wins because
Legend of the Mystical Ninja is awesome
It is a pretty awesome game
Have you gotten to the place where you can play
Gradius in one of the arcades
Like little shops in game
It's pretty awesome
Take a look at that
Anyhow
Let's get into some housekeeping for tonight
Of which again we don't have a whole lot
There's not been a whole lot of news going on with our show recently
So of course we'll continue to plug the community
Such as our LiveJournal community at Orange Lounge
On LiveJournal our username
Our MySpace at MySpace.com
Our Facebook
I think it's called the OL Army
Or the OLR listeners or something
On Facebook and
If you listened to our show a couple weeks ago
I don't really use Facebook that religiously
You can go to www.OrangeLoungeRadio.com
Next week is episode 250
And although we're not planning
A whole lot of big stuff for it
Because we already had our 5th anniversary show this year
So we already kind of did fun stuff for that
We're hoping to actually switch our location a little bit
Which for those of you that listen to us live and watch on the webcam
Might get a kick out of that
And we're hoping to also bring some more interviews
And just do some reshuffling of the show
If you have ideas go post on our forums
What kinds of things you'd like to see on Orange Lounge Radio
So we go into our next 50 episodes
And 100 more after that
And who knows how much longer we can get this show going
Anyway
Let's get into some gaming news
We'll start off with Loki tonight, some gaming news
Anyways of course the big news this week
Was Halo 3 came out
And it sold a lot of copies
In fact
Game Daily estimates that
They've sold
2.48 million units
On day 1
And of course of that most of them
Of course being standard editions
And then of course it tears down from there
Limited and legendary
But that's a whole lot of games
I don't know
I mean I'm not surprised
We knew it was going to sell like crazy
And
Yeah it's going to continue to sell like crazy
Weren't they touting on
Xbox.com or somewhere
That it's like biggest entertainment day ever
Well they're saying that
There are sales
Top that of like
I don't know
Spiderman 3 or something like that
The box office gross
To which I say Spiderman 3 wasn't that great of a movie
Well also it costs
You know what 9.50 maybe 10.50
Depending on where you live to go to the movies
To see Spiderman 3
And if you're cheap like me you'll go to like a matinee for 7 bucks
But Halo 3
60 bucks plus tax
For Halo 3 so of course it made a shit load of money
Right?
I mean I don't know
Is my math that screwed up
I mean we can do the math and figure out exactly how much it made
I just don't care
It says
We all knew Halo 3 was going to make shit loads of money
And that's really what the press release should have said
Confirmed Halo 3 makes shit load of money
It made a lot of money
And I mean it's just going to
It'll help them out it'll sell consoles possibly
I mean although some people
From other companies have come out and said
No it's not people that already wanted
You know
Halo 3 have already bought a 360
Or some shit like that
But it will sell consoles
Because there are people that were waiting for Halo 3
Before they bought
I don't know
It's good for Microsoft
Misty in our chat room says
What? It's Halo 3
Even Burger King is advertising it
Money aside I wonder why
Considering it's an M rated game
Good point
It's like the child movies in Dora the Explorer
Here's the reason
Burger King still advertises R rated movies
And that kind of stuff
Do they?
I think so
I don't know
Can you get little toys with your meals there?
Well you can get different things
Actually no Jurassic Burger is PG-13
But here's the thing though
And it kind of goes back to the whole
ESRB ratings
There are no laws in place
Forbidding people from playing the game
If it's
If they're under 18
Or whatever
It's really all just
Store policies
And stuff like that
Unless of course you're in specific states
Which makes it a felony to sell
The game to a minor
But
It's still
It's not a law
TigerKlon our chat room says
He ends up as an unlockable character in Halo 3
That'd be awesome cause then he could shoot it over and over again
That would be the best ever
Cause he's really freakin' disturbing
Then I want Ronald McDonald in the Grimace
I would rather not have him in there
To be honest
No it would be kind of jumping the shark
Yeah it would be
They've already hoarded themselves out enough for Halo 3
Maybe in Halo 4
It was everywhere
We don't need it to be quite that everywhere
Brad from Pod Culture
Is in our chat room and says
The guy ahead of me in line for Halo 3
Dropped 800 bucks
He bought the legendary edition
The Halo version of the 360 console
The two Halo controllers and some other crap
800 bucks on Halo
And he's a consumer of horror
And how?
Well I see
The 360
Halo 3 system I think is not selling as well
I think they thought it would
I think it's butt ugly
It's a paint job for 50 extra bucks
I think cause most people already bought
The 360 that were anticipating
Halo before they announced this
It's a system that doesn't
Include Halo 3
That's for 50 extra dollars
That's a weird color
I mean
That's kind of stupid
Least you could do is throw in the game
I mean come on
Did anyone go out to the midnight sales or hear about them?
No
God damn I meant to get
My husband was that one cause he sold
And what did he say? Did he say anything about it?
He said they were butt ugly
The people? No
I was gonna say
Actually our manager
In Dallas Texas
He dresses up like a Spartan
He has an actual Spartan costume
It looks cool too
He went out to some Dallas launches
And stuff
And walked around and did fun stuff like that
I don't get it
I mean
It's cool
I just don't want to do every single midnight
It's like you've seen a midnight launch
Then you've seen them all
It's just someone else cosplaying as something else
And a long ass line
And people waiting
And excited about something
It's interesting cause Halo 3 is pretty awesome
But it's not gonna be the game of the year for me
And I think for a lot of people
I don't think it's gonna be the game of the year
Oh it's gonna be worth the wait
It's good
It's better than good, it's great
But I don't think it's gonna be game of the year
I can already think of at least one game
That's very similar to Halo that's better
It didn't even have multiplayer mode
Well I mean
I don't think a game really needs to be
You know
To have the best graphics
It's all about the best gameplay
And has great gameplay
Halo 2 before Halo 3 came out
Was still on the top 10
Most played
Game on live
And now Halo 3 will just take that spot
And
People will still buy it
It's just what
Makes a good game though
Is the fact that even throughout time
As new games come out
People are still interested in that game
It's just like
When Saints Row
2 comes out
Are people gonna be still playing
Crackdown or
The original Saints Row
Or Grand Theft Auto 4
When that comes out everyone's gonna forget about
A lot of other games as well
I don't know if it's just me or the people on my friends list
But I notice a lot of my friends list
Don't play
They're very much in the now
I only ever see people playing the current games
Or the games that have come out within the past month
Obviously this week it's been Halo 3
I'm sure everybody's friends list is like that
But before that it was all Bioshock
And you don't see anybody playing
You know, Ridge Racer 6 anymore
Or you know, it's just very interesting
Not a lot of people playing the old stuff
I don't know
Thought it was interesting
Anyway, I think this is kinda interesting too
Is that there's some Halo 3
Errors, some disc errors
That are pissing people off
The legendary, I'm sorry not the legendary
But the limited edition versions of the games
Apparently have some
Disc copies of Halo 3
It's causing some disc read errors
Even on some consoles the red's ringing of death
Well, that's bullshit
Yeah, I don't know about that
If like one little disc skip can cause that
But you know, the things are all under warranty anyway
So I mean it shouldn't be too big of a deal
But certainly people that wanted to get their Halo
On launch night are pretty pissed off
That the limited edition copies are scratched
Now naturally they have a replacement disc program in the works
And all that stuff
I'm not sure that somebody's probably getting fired over this
Well, all it was was the crappy packaging
And the cause of the disc
To fall off the hub
Because it was a piece of crap
And I don't understand why
Because in other countries they had a piece of foam
And they're holding the disc in place
There is a replacement program in place right now
For both the essentials disc
And the normal game disc
And also on top of all that
The whole red ring of death thing
Could it possibly be
This is kind of a stretch for me
Could it be possibly that you're playing it for so many hours straight
That the console is overheating because of that
Because it's poorly ventilated
I think that's what the red ring of death would be caused by
In fact, I mean
It's because of a chip overheating
It's not because of
A disc read error is not going to cause your chip all of a sudden to explode
No, it's
It's Bill Gates' fault, obviously
Right?
Obviously
Because he did it himself
That's right
Because he went out there with a
With a knife
An X-Acto knife
To kind of draw a parallel here
I would say, for example
Let's just say
This is about as ridiculous as saying
Okay, if there was a certain car that had problems with their tires popping
Or something like that
Now there's a rumor going around
Saying that if you insert a certain CD into your CD player
That your tire is going to explode
I mean, that's about how ridiculous it is
Interesting comments from chat
Wiedu says
Not so in New Zealand, Loki
My store's limited editions were all scratched
Pika Uno says
All Japanese editions had foam inserts
That's a good idea
Because they package games better there
Yeah, they do package games a little better there
They should also
You know what they should do?
They should have cases that have rose petals and daisies inside them
Well, it was stupid
They had these little hubs on there
Kind of locking ones
That they'd have in normal DVD cases
So yeah, some did fuck up
And it's stupid
Luckily, mine was not scratched
Alright
Well, good for you Loki
Not having a scratched Halo 3 game
Ours wasn't scratched either
I bought the regular one
I walked in the day
After the midnight sale
I walked in the next day
I walked right into Fry's
Looking out Master Chief's ass
I mean, there were so many games
I was just like, oh, pick one up
That was it
Well, speaking of Master Chief's ass
You should check out this charity
Halo 3 action figure of the Master Chief
It's very chickly
There is
It's an 11.5 inch figure
Right now going for $241
It only has
3 bids on it at the time of this article
But they are donating
10% of the profits to the
American Breast Cancer Foundation
And it's
Master Chief is a very hot chick
Mistress Chief
You know, Ms. Chief if you're nasty
I don't know
I don't know, it looks stupid to me
It looks like someone took
Like a fucking figure
For like Witchblade and stuck the Master Chief
Helmet on it
I mean, that's seriously what it looks like
I'm not really interested to figure either
And as the comments to the story
Even kind of
They're like, okay, seriously though
There's no body armor
I mean, you could just like
Shoot her in the boobs and she'd keel over
Does she have her ass cheeks?
Does it have the assless
Suit on it?
Hmm
It looks kind of retarded
The hell game have you people been playing?
Can't you set your character as a female
Yeah, but she doesn't look like that
Yeah, and it changes nothing
Of course, it's body armor
It's unisex body armor
That's right
Hey, do we remember text
In Red vs. Blue?
I don't really watch it
I don't watch it
I don't get Halo jokes
Why don't you watch everything that's great?
I know, why can't I be like everybody else?
Seriously
God, anyways
Why can't I be a robot instead of an alien?
Hero's joke, by the way
Hope you all saw it
Someone save this show please
This is the first episode
Of the new season
Anyways, so
This is a complete shocker
There's going to be some new bundles
Coming for the Xbox 360
And of course this is kind of
Very similar to the same thing that
I believe was announced for the UK
Where they were going to be getting a bundle
Including Forza 2
And Marvel Ultimate Alliance
This is going to be for both the premium system
And for the elite system
And both of those systems will be still
The same price as they are now
Just to get two free games
Hooray
Then, of course
The other new bit of info
Is that the core system is going to be discontinued
And in its place
Is going to be the Xbox 360
Arcade SKU
It's going to have a 256 megabyte memory card
A disk with five Xbox Live arcade games
Including Boom Boom Rocket, Pac-Man
Uno, Feeding Frenzy, and Luxor 2
And it's going to have an HDMI out on it as well
With a wireless controller
All for $279.99
Which I think is
Good that they're getting rid of the core
Because I know a big complaint
I always hear is
Why would you get the core system you can't save your game?
So now you can
Because you buy the core and then you buy a hard drive
But at least this way you don't have to
Right out of the box you can save your game
I just think that because
When I got my Xbox 360
That's what I had to do
I bought a core and then bought a hard drive
Because you couldn't get Xbox 360s
Like anywhere when they first came out
Remember that? They were like Wii's
A couple years ago you couldn't get them anywhere
And of course this is just a rumor right now
Well yeah but you know what we say about Microsoft rumors
They're always true
Pretty much
All the time unless somebody completely pulls it out of their butt
But usually you know
Usually there's any sense of legitimacy to it whatsoever
I'm going to go on a limb here and say back
About a month ago when they showed that whole
UK rumor
They actually had pictures to go along with it
And I've seen pictures to go along with this stuff
So I'm going to take a wild guess
And say that
I think this is actually going to happen
Alright well
Back in the 80s we had Pac-Man fever
So this week we had Halo fever
Because Halo is huge
And a news story out of Seattle
There was a high school student who was on TV
He was on the TV going
Look ma I got Halo 3
And I'm standing here with Bill Gates
His name was Ritesh David
Ritesh David
And he was buying the very first copy of Halo 3
At a Bellevue Best Buy store
And shaking hands with Bill Gates
And this all went down of course early Tuesday morning
Bill Gates autographed David's copy of the new game
Pretty awesome
David's parents actually called the school
And said he was ill that day
And then here he is on the TV
Hi here I am
Somebody got caught
Also if you wanted to also draw
Straws a little bit more
He was either 18 or 17
Well no not if he was nice
Well get this
Did he get carded for the damn game?
Well no because M is 17
So he's probably okay
It didn't say if he was a senior
Or what we'll assume he's a senior
Alright but he told the radio station
KIRO that he was being
Feared that he would be put in detention
Or that other students would taunt him
Or whatever and he has no regrets about
Halo fever and says that meeting Bill Gates
Was the greatest moment of his life
And I find that kind of shocking
That the school did not bust him
And that the parents called him sick
For him with this whole Halo 3
I mean wasn't it kind of
You know what
Is this kind of messed up
When I was in school all I had to do to get out
Was like if it was a family function
Or something important I had to go to
All the parents had to do was just say
Um she could go to school today
So why did they have to lie?
He should be publicly spanked
Naughty naughty naughty
Caning
In Singapore
Hey your BFF Bobby Blackwolf
Is in chat Loki
I believe Bobby was there
From when I was reading in his LJ
I don't know if I have it all together
Blackwolf says he was not the first person in line
He was the first person who was of age
There were two people in front of him
That were underage
They were skipped
So then he was of age
Then what's the big deal
Why is his parents calling for him
He's over 18
I remember when I was in high school
You could check yourself out because you're of age
Oh wait
He might be 17
I think he should be disciplined
You should not be skipping school for a video game
Not that I ever did that when Final Fantasy 7
First came out or anything
But I should have been spanked for doing that
It was very naughty
Sometimes
I can tell you right now
Probably skipping work when Grand Theft Auto 4 comes out
Naughty naughty
Whatever
Jamie, surely there must be a
Disciplinarian inside of you that thinks
There's something wrong with this picture
That he's not getting in trouble
Or his parents are not being mocked openly
For basically lying for him
For this Halo 3
I don't think that there was a necessity to lie
But at the same time
It's their choice in how they raise him
So
Anything that comes back on him
Is their fault
That's how I see it
It's the parents choice
So he stayed up past his bedtime
God damn
No dessert for a week
He needs to suck it up though and still go to school the next day
So what if you're tired
Suck it up, come on
That's right, I've done that
Now I've had those late night games
When I first came out on the Super Nintendo
I must have stayed up until 2 AM in the morning
Playing that game
And then I had to go in to like band the next morning
I was so tired
I did take a week off the school to play Final Fantasy 3
Cause was my mom
Was my mom gonna call the school and say I was sick
Cause I was playing video games too late
She'd say, hell no, you did this
You still gotta go to school and you just suffer
Anyway
Moving on
Too much time on this story
Yep
Alright
Well
For anyone who was curious as to the details behind
Bizarre
And Activision
Basically
It was actually
quoted by their
commercial director saying that they were
trying to find a long term
partner association
that they wanted to
work on just making good games
and not have to deal with
the development side
of everything so that's why they brought them in
They made hot sweet
love
Yes they did and hopefully we'll get a nice baby out of it
What's that? Activision's
been buying people up lately cause they did the whole
They took over Guitar Hero
too
Remember?
Activision's got money
They bought Red Octane
Well sorta
No they bought them, they acquired them
Well right now though as far as any
upcoming releases the only thing
really titled right now
is that Bizarre has
Project Gotham Racing 4
They also have the club coming
out from Sega so that's gonna be
the last game that Bizarre's doing
If you count I guess
Geometry Wars Galaxies which is also being
released by Sega as well
So after all those
What happens to Project Gotham 5?
Well it will be probably put out
by Activision or
Does that mean it's gonna be multi console?
PlayStation 3, Project Gotham 5
How can this be?
I don't know
Or Project Gotham 5
will be developed by another studio
You know
Much like Guitar Hero
now is being developed by
someone else as well
Anyways
Something kinda cool
Tetris Splash is coming to
Xbox Live Arcade
and
Apparently
It's gonna be Tetris all over again
Hurrah because if you didn't get your fill
What was it? Tetris
Not Grandmaster
Well the last Tetris game that came out
Evolution, whatever the fuck it was called
Well it will play on
Live and it will feature
4 players offline
6 players over Live
and lots of blocks
in multicolors
and apparently a very creepy
woman announcer
Hurrah for creepy women
announcers. Boo for the fact I already
bought Tetris on the Xbox 360
and probably paid way more
for it than I should have but I guess that's my own damn
fault. I bought that. What was that Tetris
game called that was the disc version?
I don't know. Obviously it wasn't
memorable. Yet another Tetris game now on
360 is what it's called now
I mean
Tetris and Pac-Man
seriously stop making
new games or just re-releasing
your old games I guess
Going to the chatroom at chat.orangelandtrader.com
Bobby to the rescue again
with the answer about what happens to Project
Gotham 5. In fact you could say
he just owned me. I don't know
Project Gotham Racing 5 is put out by Microsoft
Game Studios. It's a Microsoft
property. They're moving it to another
developer within Microsoft Game Studios
So like I said they're moving it to
another developer much like Guitar
Hero 3 moved to a different developer
I said I got owned not you got
owned. Oh. Yeah
Yes you did. I did
That's alright. I don't play Project Gotham Racing
anyway. It's too too confusing
I like burnout. It's too sim-like
No it's just that you know the
racing games are a little different. The cars handled it
I crash into walls in Project Gotham Racing
more than any other game I play. You need to pick up flat out
Ultimate Carnage next week. I don't think about it
I'm serious. It's awesome. Play the demos
over and over and over again. Oh we'll see
Are you on their payroll?
No it's awesome. I'm talking about GameTap
Seriously. I love
the game because I played
the original flat out over
and over and over again. Playing
the ragdoll mode in it where you can just
launch the driver through the windshield
and do the high jump and stuff
I don't know. I just I like
breaking stuff and launching
drivers through windows and watching
them get hurt. Why? Same reason
I'm playing Jackass. Yeah I know it's this
theme here. You enjoy Jackass the game
you enjoy launching people through windows
I seem to remember there's that Playstation Network
game that's like a crazy guy that
does what was that called? Pain? Best
Pain or whatever? Yeah. That you were all giddy about
so you chuckle. You chuckle
like a little kid who's setting fire to things in the
back of the class. If only they had
that game
Back of the
Classroom Pyro the game coming to
Xbox Network game.
One game I enjoyed quite
a bit more than the average person and I'm not
sure why maybe just because I like Japanese
role playing games or maybe I have such
a boner for Chrono Trigger that I was able to
look past the fact that the game you know
wasn't the greatest RPG of all time but
it wasn't bad either. Blue Dragon
and one thing
that you know I was one of the negatives
I was saying about Blue Dragon is it's kind of easy
I mean if you just take the time to level
up in the very beginning of the game you're always
two steps ahead of the enemies and only
the boss fights really proved to be difficult
well guess what? Blue
Dragon has come out and said you don't think the game
is hard enough? Here's some
free download content
that will up the difficulty of the game.
You don't think the hard is game enough?
Don't worry.
What? We got covered you.
You're about to say that.
I was just
showing my translation skills
from the Japanese text original.
The ultra
hard mod gives three new
aspects to the game. New game
plus or game plus which is like
gee they had this in Chrono Trigger.
You just start the game over again with all the
stats that you had when you last ended.
But there's also now hard mode which is
twice as challenging as the normal
so I guess that means all the enemies do
twice as much damage, have twice as much
HP and impossible
impossible mode is meant
to be played with characters starting
at level 50 or higher.
So needless to say you don't want to start this
with characters that are level 1.
No word yet though if you get anything
for beating it. I would think that you should get
a special achievement or you know
a little bonus
clip or movie or something for beating
it on one of these ultra hard modes. But nope
you just get the satisfaction of
knowing you're better than everybody else at a game no one
seems to care about.
So congratulations to you.
Don't play a hard game player at Defense Force 2017.
I will say though I'm thankful
that Microsoft is putting out
or I guess I should say Microsoft because
the devs charge this. Microsoft is putting out.
Yeah Microsoft is putting out quite well
but no the developers and Mistwalker
and everybody is putting out the game
or they're putting out the content for
free. Actually I believe Microsoft
did publish it themselves. Mistwalker just developed it.
So they did decide to
charge nothing for it. So hooray for
Microsoft. Thank you for putting out.
Yes we like it when they put out.
Speaking of putting out
for the
most recent
offering from Capcom
and the Super Street Fighter 2 series
you know Turbo Remix
for matching service dot com
you know 4chan
edition
they are having
two characters confirmed
will be Cammy and M. Bison
who in the Japanese version
is Vega.
Well that's supposed to be all the same people
they're just making them all pretty.
They
do look very high def-ey.
There's some pictures on here.
Cammy with her humongous thighs.
Well people are saying her humongous
camel toe but
well that's always been Cammy.
But yeah.
Go Cammy.
Is that where she got
her name from?
I don't know.
But if you can't wait for
Super Street Fighter 2 HD
Remix
you can possibly find some
other fun games at your
local stores this week.
Including if you happen to be a fan
of basketball games
well there's going to be plenty of them
with both
NBA Live 08
NBA 2K8
and NBA 08 coming out this week
on the 2nd of October.
And of course Live
and 2K will both be on
Playstation 2, Playstation 3
the 360 and then of course Live
being on the Wii
making it the first basketball game appearance.
And of course
on the PSP as well.
And then let's see here
if you're not a fan of
basketball games then maybe you're a fan of some of the
other games from VIMVITY
including Crash of the Titans
and Spyro
or Legend of Spyro
The Eternal Night
and those are supposed to be coming out on
Playstation 2 for both and then of course
on Crash
Xbox 360
and the Wii
DS and
Game Boy Advance.
Then on PSP
a kind of crappy rip-off
of WarioWare
Hot Pixel is coming to
that system on the 2nd.
What's funny though is when they
released it over here they decided to spell out
pixel P-I-X-E-L
instead of just the PXL
as it was in other regions.
On
also most systems
Spiderman Friend or Foe
is coming out. Looks a little bit better
than Spiderman 3 and that's
going to be on Playstation 2
Playstation 3, 360, Wii
and some of the handhelds.
And let's see here
also MLB
Power Pros coming to
Playstation 2 on the Wii.
That looks kind of neat.
Also on the DS, Jackass the Game
should be coming out this week.
And on PSP
Syphon Filter. Do I want to know how to use
the touch screen in Jackass the Game
because that sounds kind of scary. I don't know but
it'll be interesting.
And then some smaller games here
maybe not a smaller game but Legend of Zelda
Phantom Hourglass is coming out this week.
And it actually might already be out
if you happen to be at the Nintendo World Store.
Other
stuff coming out on the Wii this week
Dave Mirra's BMX Challenge
which is crap.
And then of course the DS
also has Race Driver, Create and Race.
Kuru,
Poto, Cool Cool
Stars.
Krale the Treasure Adventures.
Arctic Tale. All which sound
kind of crappy.
Let's see here. Backyard Football
08. Master
Jinjin's IQ Challenge. Paws
and Claws. Dogs and Cats.
And then on the PC
of course all sorts of random
stuff including a brand new
Tycoon game because
what would it be without
a new Tycoon game almost every single
week? Rock Tour
Tycoon. Man
they're really drawn in straws now.
Scraping
the bottom of the barrel.
Sounds like fun.
Oh and flat out Ultimate Carnage on
Xbox 360 as I mentioned earlier.
Nintendo Maniac 64 says I want to see
Jackass Wii where you throw Wii
motes. Like maybe it just puts a
big target on your TV and you're encouraged to destroy it.
They've got some weird little games
in that. One of them is
the Elephant Pooh
Dive where you're diving off of a
skyscraper into a big bucket
of Elephant Pooh and then
they've got another one where
you're rolling down a
ski slope
kind of like Katamari and you're rolling
over things. They've got a bunch
of fun stuff in there. Definitely worth
a rental at least. And it's
cheap.
Well
moving on
going to the Japanese release
dates. Not a huge week in Japan
but if you've been sitting around
in Japan you've been going god damn
I want a new Dragon Ball Z
fighting game. I mean there's just
not enough Dragon Ball Z fighting games
out there on the market. Well shit you're
in luck this week because on the Nintendo Wii
Dragon Ball Z Sparkling
Meteor is coming out on the
Nintendo Wii. I believe that's on the PlayStation
too as well.
Thank god that those don't come over
at the same subtitles.
You know actually I should say this though.
Back in the day there used to be this
you know blockbuster type store but it was a
Ma and Pa store that rented video games. But they
rented import video games with a little
converter. The first Japanese video game
I ever rented was a Dragon Ball Z fighting
game on the Super Nintendo.
It was fun too because at the time we was like
oh cool this is from Japan. I don't understand
anything. You know if you're not part of the solution.
I still got the old Super Nintendo.
Oh the old Famicom? You got the Famicom?
Super Famicom. Really? Yeah. Rad. Anyhow
sorry back to Japanese release dates. On the
PlayStation 2, Bakumatsu Renka
Karyu Kenshiden is coming out.
An action game
that is probably based on an anime.
For you Bamani fans
Guitar Freaks V3 and
Drummania V3 are out in
Japan. And see I don't think they have
Guitar Hero over there and I don't think they're
getting Rock Band. So this is
what you get in Japan instead. You get
Guitar Freaks and Drummania.
Of which I have not played
V3 or V4 in the arcades
at all. I played V2.
Which was pretty much the same game.
If you will, imagine V2
but instead of a 2 there's a 4
there and you'll be pretty damn
close. Alright, alright. Fair enough.
Smartass. What if there's good
songs though? I mean you know those games
are only as good as the songs or whatever.
Forget it. Yeah. A chibi
little baseball game on the PlayStation 2
called Jikoyu Powerful
Pro Major League 2 is coming
out. It looks like if the cast of
worms start in a baseball game
that's what you get. That's MLB
Power Pros over here. Oh really?
Alright, well that shows you how much I follow
baseball games. The Crimson and Black
DS makes its way to Japan this week.
Take a look at that. Also on the Nintendo
DS. It ain't Cookin' Mama
but it's kind of close. Koharu
no DS Ushigohan
Shokuji Balance Guide
Suki. And this
what the hell do you do? It looks like a game
where you put in what you've been eating
like it shows you little pictures
of food. Yeah and it shows you
like how many grams of fat
and how many Kcals you're eating
and all that good stuff. Another thing
real quick. I think that's the smart
idea to bring something like that out over here.
There's enough people
that own DS's that would be interested in that.
That Crimson and Black DS
ain't only coming out in Japan.
Oh really?
Where else are they going to see it? Over here.
Well it's already out over here.
Well it's out over here in that bundle
but it's going to be sold by itself.
Which I mean come on
man it's just
black and red I mean really
DNA. But it's two colors! Oh my
god! Well then they should be twice
the price then obviously. Can I finish release
dates please? Sure. Thank you.
On the PSP Gundam Battle Chronicle
on the PSP
Mina no Golf Ba Vol. 3
which I believe isn't that just their hotshots
over there? Yeah. And then
Shin Sangoku Mosu
Dynasty Warriors goes into
the best hits on the PSP.
So if you're a fan of Dynasty Warriors
price cut enjoy that. That's your Japanese
release dates. Horribly butchered
pronunciations courtesy of me.
How about Europe?
Well there is some
well a little fun.
There's an hour of victory on
PC NBA 08
hour of victory comes out on the first
NBA 08 comes out on the second.
A bunch of stuff for the fifth there's
Creed 2 Liberation, Cookie
and Cream on DS
CSI 3 Dimensions of Murder
and then CSI Hard Evidence
on PC and Xbox 360
Dead and Furious on DS
Deadhead Fred on PSP
Final Fantasy Tactics The War of Lions
on PSP, Glory Days 2
Brotherhood of Men
NFL 08 and Tiger Woods PGA Tour
Great.
Alright.
Well let's see here we talked
about some 360
rumors that will probably come
true. Let's talk about some
PlayStation 3 rumors
which will also probably come true.
One of which is going to be that the
FCC has filed a
or had a filing for a brand
new PlayStation 3 model
and no word
on what it is yet but
most likely it's going to be that
40 gig system that just
that rumor won't die that one
is supposed to be coming out for
$399 or $299 depending on
who you're talking to
and apparently the
specifications for it so far it will have
Wi-Fi obviously it's going to have Bluetooth
etc. and they're identical
to the other PlayStation 3 models right
now so you know it's not going to
be like 20 gig system where it doesn't have
any Wi-Fi
or stuff like that but
still though
it's coming whether
Sony you know
admits to it or not it will be coming
soon. I bet you that you're going to
get an announcement probably any
day.
Good times.
In fact I was going to say there was
some other story that was also
kind of coinciding with the same thing
where they had one of those
it was the
Blu-ray deals
that they have going on right now for the PlayStation 3
where you buy the system
and get five Blu-ray movies. Well that
also had the same new
SKU number on there as well. So
that at least confirms that there will be a new
SKU whether it be a 48
system or God knows whether
size hard drive they're going to throw in with it
there is a new SKU coming.
Hmm
Alright.
Well, Kazurai has
commented recently on the PlayStation 3
saying the PlayStation original
price was just right. Nah nah nah
I have no regrets about releasing
this for such a high cost even if everybody
seems to have a problem with it. Well then you have
no regrets for nobody buying
it. Okay hold on that's not exactly
what he said. Okay here's a quote
quote the PS3 has been on the market less than a year
in the US and Japan and what is it less than that
in Europe? I love
that because it doesn't even know. It's difficult
right now to say who's where. Clearly
we've never started from a position of strength
and we've always had to catch up with any generation
of hardware that we've brought into the market.
You know interesting point that I think back to
the PlayStation 1 and that is kind of true
what he's saying. But I seem to
recall with the PlayStation 2 they were
kind of the big deal right
out the gate. I don't think they ever really
I mean I don't know maybe
you'd know more about Dreamcast versus PlayStation
2 Jamie but I seem to recall you know
as much as we love Sega I think Sony
was always whooping their ass from the get go weren't they?
Sadly. Yeah so
you know. But I mean
we also over here we had to
deal with the problems of coming back
from the Saturn
versus the PlayStation as you'll recall.
Over here the Saturn didn't have the proper
support to make it the
big machine like it was in Japan.
In Japan they had all of the
2D games. All of the best stuff came out
on Saturn. You know I don't know I think this is just
excuses though. I mean if you think about it their
whole thing is well we haven't been out as
long as the 360 so that's why we haven't
sold as many units.
No you still have not figured out
why you haven't sold that many units yet.
And that fact right there is scary
as it is if you can't figure out why your system
is not selling. I mean
dude it's your
fucking price. I mean that's why the
Panasonic 3DO didn't take off because
it was $700.
I mean that's what Rob was asking.
Wait quick name one game on the
3DO. 5, 4
And it had
You Don't Know Jack. I remember playing that
game. But back to what Rob asked.
I bet most people wouldn't have passed that
challenge. Sorry. I think that
the whole reason, part of the reason why the Dreamcast
didn't take off so well over here
was just coming off of the
American failure of the Saturn.
Because overseas it was
the shit. I mean
that's why I imported all my games on Saturn.
But
and you know the Dreamcast
to me had more fun
games on it than the PS2 did
but I think it was just coming off of
that failure and then
but now you know I always looked at
Microsoft has sort of taken Sega's
place as far as systems go
and then they've just turned it
right around because I honestly think that
they're looking into the
actual thing that gamers want instead of the
thing they think gamers want. You know what I mean?
If they want to catch up
they need to put out the $399 skew
and then they need to start putting out some better
games because I think with that price point being
in place people will be more likely to buy the
system, developers will be more likely
to make games for it, etc.
It's interesting you bring that up, that whole
Microsoft took Sega's place thing because then you
even put, I've thought the same thing actually
and it's kind of interesting because you even
throw that Peter Moore thing you know because he was with
the Dreamcast and then he did the, you know he's not with
Microsoft anymore but he was definitely a big part of 360
it makes it even more eerie
that whole comparison.
Anyway, we can move on
with the news now, sorry just random
sidebars. Really, can I?
Yes, actually maybe I should go to the chat and see
what's going on in chat.
I'm sorry if I mispronounced this, either
Wettu or Weetu, I think it's Weetu?
There's no A in it though. It says Dreamcast
sold really well in New Zealand but
PlayStation 2 killed it.
Misty said I never got PlayStation
2 until DDR and if I recall
correctly I got my PlayStation
2 at the same mall GameStop that I got
my little DS Lite bundle at.
BlackWolf says wasn't Tempest 2000
on the 3DO? Jaguar.
Jaguar. Was the only game worth getting on the Jaguar?
There was another one on
Jaguar. Okay, one other Jaguar game.
But
yeah, it was all about, and now you
can get Tempest 2000 on damn near
everything else. Mr. DeBucket says Peter Moore
says 9-9 of 99 is still the biggest
day in media history? Fuck Halo 3.
That's right, because the MTV
Music Awards were on 9-9 of 99
weren't they? I was sitting in line for my Dreamcast.
We can move on, please
let's move on.
That's what I was doing except for when I ran
over and bought a book and then came back and
waited in line. Wait, BlackWolf says
3DO Jaguar, same thing.
No. Compare the
controller sometime. The Jaguar
came with like a dictionary for
a controller.
You know what I still think was the most kind of
but controller there was was the ColecoVision
controller. Yeah, I was going to say it looked very
similar to ColecoVision. ColecoVision
I mean it could have been like a cell phone of the 80's
they had like a whole number pad on there.
The only game that I played on the
ColecoVision that used that number pad was
Mouse Trap. Seriously?
The Jaguar controller
reminds me of the Steel Battalion
controller. Now the Steel Battalion
controller is freaking awesome. It was one
eject button short of a Steel Battalion controller
that's what it was. Hey, I bought my husband
a Steel Battalion controller for his birthday.
Alright. Because I'm the best
wife ever. Okay, chat room please
stop derailing the show. Yes please.
Let's move on with the news.
There was a
recent FCC filing
for a 40GB PS3
and Sony isn't saying crap about
it. They are
really not saying crap about it.
I don't see any statements, no nothing.
Because
they're like, oh shit
not again.
There is no 40GB system just like
there was no PSP Slim or
no rumbling controllers.
Well
at any rate
it's there. They're not saying anything
end of story.
Or no 80GB
system.
Well I already got mine.
Why does it seem like the hard drive
is the only thing that freaking changes on that system?
Because you don't get it. Well people must not like it
because they don't have a large enough hard drive.
Well put something for me to put on the hard drive.
Bigger is better Rob. Oh well.
Well Rob, you know you can convert your videos over.
Oh wait, but there isn't really an easy way to do that.
Oh and they don't really tell you how to
Next story, I'm angry. Sorry.
I use it for putting videos on there.
I have a copy of
Kung Pao on there.
Whoop-de-freaking-do. Hey, Kung Pao
is an awesome movie. Don't talk bad about it.
Steve OdoKirk needs to fucking make a sequel.
Anyways. Somebody linked
a picture of the Jaguar controller in chat.
How is that thing supposed to, that's like an original
Xbox controller, okay.
Where you have to have like gorilla hands to be able to hold
that thing.
See, with it being that big, it makes
one sort of wonder about the
Saturn dual analog controller, but that one
is one of the single most
comfortable controllers ever. And they wonder
why the Xbox didn't sell in Japan.
I mean, you need like
three Japanese hands to hold the Xbox.
No, Rob, Rob, Rob.
I will point out to you that when they released the
Xbox in Japan, it did have a smaller controller.
Which they released here, and
Which I made Dan buy me because
I'm sorry, look at these short fingers.
You do not have gorilla hands.
You have petite little girly hands.
Alright. Anyways.
So, it's been confirmed
the price of Rock Band, and the date for Rock Band
has been announced.
Rock Band will come out on the Xbox 360
and Playstation 3 on
Black Friday. Thank you,
EA, for
$170.
And of course, that is the bundle
which is going to include both
a guitar,
a drum set,
microphone, and the game. Of course, the game
by itself will also be available
for $60 in case you
just want to play the guitar version and
own a guitar from Guitar Hero.
However, what is kind of new
is they announced that there will be a Playstation 2
version for the low, low price of
$160. You save $10.
And that is coming out on December 10th.
And of course, we'll feature these same things
as well. What I find interesting
is that they came out with a Playstation 2
version. Something tells me it's because
they like money.
You got to play Rock Band last week.
Is it worth it?
For that price? Yeah, I think so. I was going to buy it for
$200. Good. I'll come over and play yours
because I don't feel like dropping that kind of money
on a video game.
Well, hopefully you'll get a pretty decent discount.
I wish they would send me a copy for free.
I'll buy the game itself,
but I'm not going to buy $100. For a game
I'll play once, and you know it.
I'm only going to play it once, probably.
Because we don't have people
over all the time. I play
Guitar Hero 1. I don't see my roommate being somebody
where I'm going to be all like, hey, let's bust out
Rock Band and get down.
It's a party game. It's a total party game.
Speaking of Guitar Hero 2, whatever fucking happened to
their Effector pedal or something that was going to be
added later on, I
built one of those Effector pedals
and now it's for nothing.
Seriously, very disappointing.
Not that it cost me any money to do that, but
you know, still very disappointing.
Because it works, too.
Except it doesn't do anything.
Anyways,
I think it's going to be worth it.
The big thing for me, I think, is going to be to see
whether people are going to pay $170
for this game or not.
I will.
I don't know.
It's going to be big. It's definitely going to sell
very well. It's just, are people going to pay
$170 for a game?
And if so,
then we're going to see a bunch more.
I think it is going to be
a huge party game. I totally see
this is the kind of thing that people who have
big families or
people that host parties regularly
or it's going to become like the
we're going to have this at a fundraiser
or have Rock Band there. Because Guitar Hero
is already like that.
Oh, we're going to have a fundraiser.
We're going to have a bake sale slash car
wash. Guitar Hero is going to be there.
I don't know. Am I the only one that ever
notices that Guitar Hero seems to turn up at these
random charity events that you see advertised?
That's going to be Rock Band.
Well, it's cool, I guess.
I'm not knocking Rock Band.
It's just a lot of money to drop on a game.
It is.
I don't know.
Now you have me
waving on it now.
Oops. Sorry EA.
Sorry, Harmonics.
Well then let's go to the next story before
Loki changes his mind completely.
The PlayStation.com shopping service
is closing in Japan.
That's right. In December
it will be ending the site's
e-commerce services and the service
will be coming to a complete halt in February
2008. Now while at first glance
this might seem like, oh, doom and gloom
for the PlayStation, not so.
Because PlayStation.com was for
providing downloadable content for the
PlayStation 2. But as you guys all know
it's all about the PlayStation 3 now
and the PlayStation Network.
PlayStation 2 had downloadable content?
I guess in Japan, yeah. Because you get the PlayStation
points.
Well anyway, if you still have PlayStation
points you can transfer those over to your
PlayStation 3 wallet.
They always get better stuff in Japan.
Hello? Where have you been?
Where have you been?
I don't know.
Well,
for anyone who also
has been keeping up with more
of the downloadable content for PS3
especially for our European fans.
Well, I should say fans of the system.
Well,
Sony is pulling
their Gran Turismo HD concept
from the Japanese store
and it's not probably
coming out in Europe at all.
There's been no announcement.
No nothing.
They're just not getting it.
Sorry. But now
there's a Gran Turismo 5 prologue
that will be
coming out but there's no date for it
in the UK yet.
So that's kind of a bitch move I think
that they're actually getting rid of
the free version
of Gran Turismo on there
before the paid
demo I guess comes out.
Well, if you have a PS3 now
might as well download it.
Put it on your hard drive.
Honestly, what else are you going to
fill that hard drive with?
It wasn't a bad game.
I mean it's good for a demo.
I just can't see myself paying 50 bucks
I can't see myself paying 50 bucks
for Gran Turismo 5
prologue. I'm telling you
put porn on the Playstation Network
Sony will start out selling Microsoft
consoles tomorrow.
Mark my words.
Okay, don't
mark my words. Read another story.
Mark my words.
Parrish.
The fuck was that?
That sounded funny.
Do you need some fresh air, Loki?
I'm feeling fine. I have to drive from Oakland.
I'm feeling tingle fresh.
Mark my words.
You will pay for that.
By the way, kids, don't forget to buy
the Eye of Judgment. We only have to sell a million.
If you don't know what I'm talking about, listen to last week's show.
It will never happen.
Never.
Story.
So, in Europe
Playstation 3 is getting another
bundle. Not surprising
though, it's going to be bundled with Pro
Evolution Soccer 2008.
And it's coming in November.
That's all there is to say.
Yeah, it was confirmed
by Playstation France and
Well, that's logical.
You know, sports bundles are nothing
uncommon and certainly in Europe a soccer
bundle is going to sell some systems.
So, you know, makes sense.
Exactly. I mean,
remember that really crappy one that they did
for, I think it was Pro Evo
2007. It was like with
AstroTurf on the 360.
Wait, it came with AstroTurf? What?
They did like, it was an auction
thing where they were selling it.
What?
Well, ten years
Funny! Not funny.
Ten years have passed since Ultima Online
first rolled out. That's right, back in
1997 was when Ultima Online was
first unleashed upon the world.
And now EA is celebrating with a ten
years of Ultima Online celebration.
There's a brand new
Kingdom Reborn update,
which I think we reported on previously in the program.
It's free to download for the previous
subscribers through October 9th.
But, however, there's also now
the Return to Britannia campaign
that's going on. Electronic Arts
is doing a monster hunt and
prizes such as a new pendant necklace,
a whole map of Britannia that you can win,
a commemorative sculpture,
armor set, all this stuff.
The characters in game get fireworks
and ten decor tokens.
Unfortunately, I haven't played the game
so I can't tell you what those tokens do,
but maybe somebody can email us and let us know
and mail back buy more fireworks!
I was actually going to check this game out because I think
you can get a two week free trial.
Since I've been going back and forth on all these MMOs lately,
why not check out the granddaddy of all the
MMOs? I remember when I played
Ultima Online with my friend briefly,
and god, I remember who it was.
It was still long ago, but
we were complete
asses on the game and it was fun.
Did you get banned? Oh no, we were just
playing around at his
house and just running around
as our character was completely naked
yelling sausage for sale.
That's all I remember.
I think I saw that in the
barons the other day, so some things never
change, you know?
No, no, no, no, no.
Someone was walking around in one of the
towns in Ragnarok the other day going,
I got a snake mange!
Like the Adam Sandler thing.
Now they've taken that and now it's just slash dance.
Does Ultima Online have
slash dance? We don't have slash dance
I just remember it was weird because people would buy
houses and they would store their horse in
their house and I was like, why would you put a
why were we walking past a house
where I hear a horse? It was weird.
But it was because you can lock the houses, otherwise
your stuff would get stolen, I guess, or something.
I think Misty sums up my thoughts
on the Ultima Online bonus stuff.
She says, Woot explosives.
That's true, explosives are always
good incentive to come back to an
old abandoned MMO. I shouldn't say
that, actually. I guess there's still quite a few
people who play Ultima Online. I just
don't know any of them.
Oh well, perhaps some will email us.
I know a couple of people who play. Really?
Yeah.
Alright. Ask them if they're having
fun with the event or whatever. We'll have to
bring them on the show for an interview. Interview this
week, people that actually play Ultima Online. It's either
Ultima Online or Diablo. Oh, because they're so similar.
They look very similar, actually.
Some of them I just
sort of get mixed up on. Like, who plays EverQuest
anymore? We never...
To be honest, when I went out to
Pennsylvania
last year, one of the
workers at our office
that we work with out there, without saying too much about what I do
during the day, she
knew that I was into video games. I said, yeah,
at the time I was playing Final Fantasy 11.
I'm like, yeah, I play Final Fantasy 11. She's all, oh, I
tried that once, but I just can't give up EverQuest.
She's like, me and my husband play EverQuest
all the time. You haven't played EverQuest? I'm like, I watched
it once and I was bored out of my mind.
But, yeah, I've seen it.
There are people out there that still play EverQuest.
We just don't really hear much about it anymore.
It's harder to find people that are playing
EverQuest 2 because nobody wanted
to abandon their EverQuest character. I think that was one of the
biggest mistakes they made, is they should have made a way
for you can at least get some type of bonuses
for bringing your character over from EverQuest 1.
Maybe I'm just crazy, I don't know.
Anyhow,
DarkSakura, every week
she likes to surf the internet up and down and all
around and bring you her very favorite in
websites. By the way, folks,
this is the very last edition of
DarkSakura's website of the week.
Sorry to report, DarkSakura
is no longer going to be able to give you a website of the week
because pretty
much you can bet that
if the site has something to do with
pictures of cats, it's probably going to be
her website of the week. No.
I've done a bunch of cool
sites, Rob. In all seriousness,
DarkSakura's website of the week...
One had two website of the week mentions.
That's right. The Weebles.
That's right. Well, anyway, or Doctor Who.
No, there's multiple Doctor Who
sites, but I've done Weebles twice. Anyway,
DarkSakura's website of the week will be going away
in favor of DarkSakura's
Classic Game of the Week.
Well, yeah. You better pick a good one for the very first
week next week, the Classic Game of the Week. I already know what I'm
going to pick. So here it is for the very last time. And it's not
the Guardian Legend. I'm so disappointed.
No, that's too predictable.
Guardian Legend will save for down
the road, but we'll do the Classic Game of the Week. It'll be something obscure
like rainbow cotton. Alright.
Anyhow, don't give it away.
They won't want to tune in next week.
Make it a game you don't talk about a lot
on the show.
Anyhow, here it is, ladies and gentlemen,
the very last website of the week.
DarkSakura, you better be good.
The website
of the week is
speaklolcat.com
It's very easy,
very simple.
You type in something in English and it translates
it into catspeak.
What did I tell all of you?
If it has to do with lolcat, it's your
side of the week. See, I'm going to type in something right now.
Um, okay.
I don't know. I'm talking and I'm...
What are you putting in there? Rob is a big what?
Tool. Tool?
And it says Rob is huge tool.
Hahahaha
Lovely.
I'm going to post that direct link into the chatroom.
But, um, it's speaklolcat.com
And that, boys and girls, is the very last
website of the week.
End of line.
Alright, so next week, DarkSakura's classic game
of the week. Yay!
Oh, you can actually link it
with it saying Rob is a big tool.
Yep, that's why I did it.
Let me just check that out on my screen here.
Rob is huge tool.
You're a bitch.
Alright. I love you.
Wait, actually, I want to see that.
Let me go back to that site here.
Jamie is a bitch.
Rob's really good at typing with one hand.
I am. I can do a lot of things with one hand.
Jamie is bish.
Okay, where did that come from?
I think this show is in need of a break.
I think this show might actually be in need of cancellation.
But we'll have to do it for a break for now.
We'll be right back with more of Orange Lounge Radio.
Right after this, Nintendo News,
in part, we haven't even touched Nintendo yet during the show.
We'll get to all the Nintendo news in part B
and plenty more to come.
Don't worry, we'll touch Nintendo plenty when we come back.
We'll get out our wheeze when we come back.
Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights
and is podcasted to the world twice a week.
Stay tuned to our podcast feed
for the conclusion of this week's Orange Lounge Radio.