Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and released to our podcast stream
twice weekly.
To listen to the first half of this episode, visit www.orangeloungeradio.com for links
to websites with listings of past episodes.
Now the conclusion of this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio.
Welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio.
We are live on this Sunday evening, September 2nd of 2007.
Happy Labor Day weekend to those of you guys that are in the States, to those of you guys
that aren't in the States, well, happy weekend and happy Monday and hope your week is pretty
cool.
Anyhow, we're going to get right back into the gaming news this week.
Sadly, Dark Sakura is not here this week.
Labor Day weekend just happens to be our anniversary.
I think she planned it that way so she could have a three-day weekend off every year, but
oh well.
Regardless, she's not here tonight, unfortunately, but we're still here going over the gaming
news.
Shane is here filling in, although he's doing a terrible job because he's just sitting here
all night playing PSP.
I don't have a computer to look at everybody because my computer is off.
Well the thing you can look forward to is that in 40 minutes, the operator 11 thing
cuts off, so then you can use that again.
So there you go.
Hooray.
All right, let's get back into the gaming news.
Loki.
Anyways, Gran Turismo 5 Prologue.
We know it's coming out this year.
We know it looks pretty good.
What we didn't know is what exactly had in it.
Of course now they're promising that it's going to feature more than 40 cars, tracks
with reverse and alternate routes, and Gran Turismo TV, an online video channel for the
PlayStation Network.
Also we found out that it's going to be available online for purchase, and it's also going to
be available via Blu-ray, just like Warhawk.
To which I say, why don't you just finish Gran Turismo 5 instead of releasing these
half games and charging people money for them?
I mean seriously, stop making demos for Gran Turismo 5 and work on the damn game.
Well, aren't they trying to give people a reason to keep a look out for the PlayStation
3?
Yeah.
The reason is, oh yeah, we promised you Gran Turismo 5 at launch.
Oh, guess what?
It's not going to be done until next year.
So what we're going to do is we're going to use this as another exclusive title, despite
the fact that it's really kind of a demo, and we're going to throw it out there.
Oh, and by the way, you're going to purchase Gran Turismo 5 when it comes out as well,
despite the fact that it's going to have exactly the same content, plus more.
GS68 says, Gran Turismo Forever.
And Dark Tetsuya says, I don't know, Loki, Gran Turismo demos are usually more packed
than most full-blown racing games.
Yeah, but this one you have to pay for.
Those comments are coming from our chatroom, chat.orangelounge80.com.
I don't have a problem with Gran Turismo HD, which is free, but I do have a problem with
paying for Gran Turismo 5, which is only going to have 40 cars.
Here's the problem actually they're going to run into is, what if people don't really
want to buy the full Gran Turismo 5?
Now you have this Gran Turismo prologue that's just as good, you know, might get people through,
and now they're not selling tons of copies of their $60 retail game.
Uh-oh.
All right.
Well, I know Loki has no problem with this SingStar on the PlayStation 2, because Loki
loves his karaoke PS2 games, right?
Oh, yeah.
Totally.
So why does the SingStar pack, don't tell the wife about this one, or she's going to
want you to buy it?
She doesn't care.
Oh, okay.
Good.
Why doesn't she care?
I thought she loved karaoke games.
Because I'm not going to buy them.
Okay.
Did you affirm that?
Did you tell the wife about the karaoke games?
I told her I wouldn't buy them, and I told her that there was this coming out, and she's
like, so?
So what?
Yeah.
She wants to spend the money on herself.
I'll buy her SingStar PS3 if she wants, and she can record herself singing on like...
I want to come over and play that if you guys get it.
PlayStation Network and stuff.
I will not touch this game.
Yes, you will.
As I will not touch the singing portion of Rock Band.
All we have to do is to, one night when you don't drive, we have to get you to drink a
little bit, and then you'll be good.
Okay.
You were at my bachelor party.
I was near alcohol, boys.
Which, by the way, is on YouTube.
If you want to see Loki driving Mario Kart drunk, just search for Orange Lawn Radio.
It's there.
Too bad we didn't have the rest of the stuff on there, like me playing miniature golf.
Oh, that was so freaking funny.
I still have the videos for that.
Anyways though, but yeah, I was pretty sick with tons of alcohol, and they tried to get
me to sing karaoke at a bar, and I would not do it.
So I will not sing karaoke no matter how much alcohol is in me.
All right, well, damn.
Well anyway, if I could get to the story, SingStar is coming out on the PlayStation
2.
Well, it's already there, but the thing is that now there is a bundle coming out.
It's $150 US, and it's coming out with SingStar, and I'm trying to figure out which version
of SingStar it is.
SingStar Pop is coming out in November, and it's going to be a white PlayStation 2 to
perfectly match your Wii if you are so inclined.
So enjoy that.
150 bucks.
Not a bad deal for those two games.
It also, by the way, comes with a controller, a white controller, and two microphones.
So you're all set for a karaoke party with this if you're a SingStar fan.
I mean, I know some people prefer Karaoke Revolution, but it really isn't at all the
same game in the end.
It's people making asses of themselves in front of their friends, right?
Yeah.
All right.
We touched on this a little bit in part A with the whole Manhunt 2 being re-rated thing,
but Cinder Yee, Leland Yee from California, is actually on the record saying that he favors
the adults-only rating and wishes that they allowed those to be played on consoles.
Basically, you know, that there should be an adult-only rated game instead of having
the Censor games.
And I think he'd probably like to see a lot more of the mature-rated games being adult-only
because that is pretty self-explanatory.
It's for adults only.
It's not, you know, maybe some parent thinks, oh, my kid's mature enough to play this game,
you know.
Instead of that, it is pretty self-explanatory.
And I agree with him.
I think that they should have adult-only games on consoles.
I mean, consoles are for everyone.
It's not just for families.
And you know what?
So what?
If you rate it AO and, you know, Walmart and everybody does not decide to carry it, that's
the publisher's decision.
They know what they're getting into and what hurdles they're going to have to overcome
rating it AO or having a game being released rated AO.
But I think it also would give them a lot more freedom to put whatever the fuck they
want in it, which would be awesome.
It is kind of interesting that the guy's been branded as this anti-video games guy, but
I find it very interesting that he is actually supportive of, okay, the content can be out
there.
You know, I don't care if the AO content is out there, and in fact, we should have a place
for it, but just not falling in children's laps or whatever.
We need to police it so that it doesn't get in children's laps.
He basically says in the OA, the use of the ambiguous term mature, many parents are left
with a false sense of how violent an emirated game may be, and obviously, even with some
retailers as, of course, the Federal Trade Commission study suggested.
I just think, you know, I think they should do it.
I think somebody should try.
You know, it's just like they say whoever's going to win the HD DVD and Blu-ray war is
going to be whatever system gets the most porn, is going to be what decides that war.
I mean, seriously, we're not banning adult DVDs out there, and I would think that that's
a lot easier for kids to get a hold of than, you know, adult games.
But they need to get past the point that games are not just for kids.
It's an entertainment media.
It's for everybody.
It can be anything, all age ranges.
So get past that and start treating it like it is any other media.
You know, make it available to the consumers that it's appropriate for.
Alright.
Well, one game I'd like to see an AO version of someday is Silent Hill, because the game
is very sick and twisted as it is in its mature format.
Imagine if they could step up the violence even more.
You're a big fan of Silent Hill, aren't you, Mipotas?
Yes.
Would you like to see a version that's even more violent?
No.
No?
Does it scare you as it is already?
No, I don't think it's about violence in that game.
Disturbing imagery, yes.
Violence, no.
Alright.
Well, there will be plenty of disturbing imagery in Silent Hill 5.
The collective who's developing the game, as you know, it's kind of a controversial
decision that the collective is developing this, so it's being actually developed in
the US and not in Japan.
But the collective is developing this game and they are actually borrowing elements from
the Christoph Ganz version of Silent Hill, which would be the movie.
Apparently they were big fans of kind of the way that the characters moved around in the
movie.
So there will be some motion capture for the monsters in the Silent Hill 5 game.
All of the monsters.
And they are borrowing the whole night to day element that was in the movie.
Remember how in the movie it would switch from, you know, I guess you could say night
to day or good Silent Hill to bad Silent Hill, it would kind of switch?
That's going to happen in Silent Hill 5.
And now you were actually reading up a little more on Silent Hill 5.
Some article that was in a recent gaming magazine, right, Mipotas?
Yeah.
And what other details did it give about the game?
The nurses are the nurses from the movie, like, full on.
They're the ones that are attracted to light and they look exactly the same.
What was this whole thing about now the monsters will chase you?
Oh yeah, the monsters just won't, you can't just run by monsters anymore, like, apparently
they kick down doors to get to you, which is really cool.
And I don't know, I can't wait for it.
I can't wait to get some of my friends who get really scared by these games, like I'm
thinking of one in particular that cried when she was fighting one of the boss monsters
in Silent Hill 3.
Oh, that was the best thing ever.
I can't wait to get her to play this game because I'm evil and vindictive and I think
it's going to be hilarious when the monsters start kicking down doors to get to her.
Yeah, she'll throw the controller down and run into a different room and cry.
And hopefully we'll have it all up on one of these video streaming sites for you to
enjoy.
What you guys don't get about our friend, though, is, like, I'll go and pretend I'm
one of the monsters, I won't be dressed up or anything, I'll just walk like they were
and she hates it and freaks out.
So good.
pikaruno agrees, I get so scared I can't even play Silent Hill.
The first Silent Hill, I'm sure I've mentioned this before, but when I tried to play it,
I stopped it nine times at the very beginning because it was too scary.
That's just how great these games are.
Wow.
That's cool.
Asdartitsuyu in our chatroom says, what a horrible night to have a curse.
Funny.
Because it's a Castlevania reference, never mind.
I don't even get it.
Forget it.
That's all I have to say on Silent Hill.
I'm definitely looking forward to Silent Hill 5.
I looked at the same article, too.
It looks like it's going to be pretty sweet.
Actually, let me ask real quick, Shane, since you're such a big fan of the series from before,
are you looking forward to this?
I know that you were a little nervous when you heard it was going to a different developer
and it's being developed outside of Japan, but seeing kind of what they've done with
it, are you looking forward to it?
Are you still a little nervous or what?
I'm still nervous.
The screenshots are good looking, but that doesn't tell you how the game plays or if
the story is really good or if they have the elements that make it Silent Hill in the game
or not.
It could just be like, I don't know, they could have made a really nice looking, what
was that crappy game called?
The one where you were all the teenagers in the school and all the plant monsters were
obscure or something like that.
Why are you shaking your head at me a lot?
Nothing.
I'm just...
Oh, yeah.
It could be like that.
That could look really pretty, but it could be a terrible game like that game was.
So I don't know.
I hope, but...
Maybe the liquor is just starting to kick in, so I'm just nodding a little more than
usual.
Okay.
Maybe.
All right.
I'm done.
Next story.
Anywho, so one game I'm not too excited about, Loco Roco for the PS3.
It's been dated for a release in Japan on the PlayStation Network September 21st, and
no price is announced yet.
It's looks like Odeo Loco Roco Boo Boo Coco Reco or something, I don't know.
All you need to know is that...
Wait.
Loco Roco Boo Goo Coco for Coco Puff Roco Boco is what it is.
What it probably means is, they don't know that it's just an interactive screen saver.
You fuck tards and you're going to pay money for this, thinking it's a real game, and ha,
ha, we screw you over again.
That's exactly...
Loco Roco Coo Coo Boco fuck tard, is that it?
Basically, the game is an interactive screen saver.
You will be able to use the six axis to tilt Loco Rocos around, but that's about it.
So hooray!
Thank you for yet another awesome game, Sony.
You rock.
Do you think Loco Roco just jumped the shark with this?
I think it's just, why even bother calling this a game, or even have to purchase it,
if it's, you know, not even really a game.
It's just a fucking screen saver.
Well, speaking of content available on the PlayStation Network, there's something brand
new available on the PlayStation Network for those of you guys in the UK.
It's the Dirt demo.
If you want to check out the brand new game Dirt, there's a demo for you guys on the UK
marketplace, which should be interesting to note.
The US also got this demo along with other stuff, but unfortunately those you guys overseas
get the shaft yet again in terms of content available in your PlayStation 3 marketplace.
Have a nice day, but enjoy the Dirt demo.
It's a pretty looking game, but I couldn't control it at all, but it's just not my kind
of racing game.
That's just me, I guess.
Anyways, one other game that you probably won't see over in the UK also is being developed
by Homeland Security in the US.
They are developing a game, of course, I guess, I don't know, something where you, of course,
defending the United States from terrorists, and they've spent $600,000 of funding Ground
Truth.
It's a game that would, I guess, cast players in the first responders to a terrorist attack
or natural disasters.
Thank you, Homeland Security, for spending our money on a game instead of protecting
the homeland.
Is this a free download thing for PCs, or is this like a Flash game?
What the hell is this?
It's just something that's being developed.
It's not even done yet, so we don't know if it's going to be free or whatnot.
Interesting.
What do they hope to accomplish with a game like this, I wonder?
Wouldn't it be funny if the terrorists played it instead?
It would probably be to build on the success that, say, America's Army had.
I was just thinking of America's Army, and even Jonathan F. in our chat room says, America's
Army was free.
Dark Tetsuya says, Shane went there.
When do I not go there, seriously?
I guess the game is being developed by Sandia National Labs with grad students from University
of Southern California doing the graphics work.
Interesting.
So stop spending government money on this crap, seriously.
You don't need a fucking game.
You don't see the Department of Transportation saying, we want a game, or you know, God knows
what else.
They should have like a Bush PR campaign game or something.
Interesting point from an escapist in our chat room.
That may seem like an expensive game to make, but keep in mind King's Quest cost $700,000
when it first came out all those years ago.
Hmm.
Oh, great.
Isn't all that marketing?
They're going to waste a lot of money building this game, and it's going to suck.
That's awesome.
Wait, you're not trying to say King's Quest sucks, does it, because King's Quest is like
one of the greatest games ever made.
King's Quest is fucking old.
So it's old, but it's great.
Well, back in the day, $700,000 is probably a lot of money.
Nowadays production costs have gone up due to the wonderful systems and graphics that
we have and have come to love.
So back in the day, it was EGA graphics, all fucking 16 colors of wonderful goodness.
All right.
Well, this is a topic that's never fun to talk about, and I hate it when it comes up
on the show, but I think we need to bring this up one more time to bring up the clarification
piece that came out this week, and that would have to do with the really horrible tragedy
that happened at Virginia Tech earlier this year.
Many months later now, the Virginia State report, the official final report has come
out.
The Virginia Tech Massacre Review Panel has released their report, and it does show that
there is no link between video games and the murders that were committed by the culprit.
Actually, the only game that is even mentioned in the report is Sonic the Hedgehog.
Now I would fail to see where Sonic the Hedgehog is going to provoke violent gaming.
Unless he went and played the PlayStation 3 or Xbox 360 version of the game, which the
controls were horrible and could drive someone to kill people.
Anyway, there was in the report, quote, none of the video games were war games or had violent
themes.
They liked basketball and had a collection of figurines and remote-controlled cars.
So this is a big screw you to all those people that were so quick to blame video games when
this happened.
So the Jack Voldemort's of the world and Dr. Phil's and so on.
So to you folks, we dedicate a very special segment this week to you.
It's our FUs of the Week.
Loki, why don't you start us off with your FUs of the Week.
My FUs of the Week goes to the Lifetime Channel.
I don't like you, and I don't see the point.
That's it?
And to the director of that stupid movie that I had to watch today, learn how to light a
fucking movie.
Otherwise, you're going to be stuck making shit on Lifetime.
First off, I'd like to give an FU to Loki for not enjoying the greatness of his Lifetime
movies, because I love Lifetime movies.
I'd also like to give an FU to getting sick when I was traveling this week.
The only thing worse than having to travel and be gone for four days is getting sick
while you're gone and bringing that back with you.
That really stinks.
And then I guess that's it.
I can't really think of anything else this week.
So that's all my FUs.
Shane, Miklotov, whatever your name is.
Any FUs?
No.
No?
You're happy about everything?
No, but I can't think of anything to give an FU to.
Everything's perfect?
You're not angry at anything?
No.
Well, FU to you being so darn mellow.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
FU to Blue Dragon, because it sucks.
There we go.
FU to you?
You don't even...
Do you even know why you hate Blue Dragon?
Yes.
The combat is boring.
The combat is awesome.
The game is dull looking.
You're dull looking.
It looks like a generic RPG that could have been made by any company ever.
That I actually, you know, unfortunately there's not a lot that sets this apart from another
RPG except for the fact that it's on the 360 and it's pretty.
But...
The character models even look pretty bland.
The music's good.
No, because those boss fights have terrible, terrible songs.
The boss fight song's awesome.
No.
Worst game.
The boss fight song is a vocal rock song, which is pretty rad.
Don't listen to what Shane says.
No.
Listen to what I say.
No, don't.
All right.
Back to the news.
Anyways, Castlevania, the wonderful game that's gonna become a movie, yay, is now being completely
rewritten.
Yes, they've thrown out the script and are going back to the drawing boards.
Apparently, Paul W.S. Anderson, who was going to direct the movie, is not now, obviously,
and now they have a new person working on the script.
It's Ian Jeffers, who's done a screenplay for the wonderful Kevin Bacon action flick
that just got released here in the United States, Death Sentence.
Yes, you may not have seen it yet, but I'm sure that you will at some point because that's
super awesome and I know you wouldn't miss it.
So he's working on the script now.
His take on it, I guess, and of course the new director is Sylvain White, says, I was
attracted by the chance to make a dark, epic period movie that almost has an anime feel
to it.
So let's hope and pray that it doesn't suck, and unfortunately past track records of movie
games have not been...
My Magic A-Ball says, signs do not look good.
Loki, coming from the chat room here, did you like the band Deep Purple?
Do you remember the band at all, Deep Purple?
The one that did Smoke on the Water?
Yeah, no, actually I got to ask Shane this, do you know the band Deep Purple?
Yes, because Smoke on the Water.
The lead singer of Deep Purple is the guy that sings the song in Blue Dragon.
No wonder it sounds bad.
That little tidbit coming from Escapist, so there you go.
Let's talk about other movies.
Now of course there's been lots of movies this year.
You have King of Kong, which I still want to see, but I think the closest it's playing
here is San Francisco.
I'm not driving all the way out there just to see a movie, and Chasing Ghosts are some
big movies that are coming out this year, but there's another one that's coming out.
It's called Press Start.
It's not a documentary, however.
This is a quote from the little synopsis of the movie.
Zach Nimbus is a typical suburban youth and volunteer monster exterminator living peacefully
in a video game world.
It's a realm where people actually do cross rivers by jumping across alligators' heads
or being chomped to death in the attempt, and where injuries can be cured by eating
food laying around in old hallways.
Here the pleasant days are ending due to world conquest by the unspeakably evil but insecure
and telephone addicted wizard, Count Nefarious Vile.
Zach soon finds himself recruited by battle-hardened space soldier Sam, an enthusiastically bad
tempered ninja Lin Koo to join a last desperate attempt to thwart Vile's imminent victory,
but not before lampooning every video game convention that comes in their way.
So apparently this is going to be some type of little live action movie that parodies
all these other video games.
Here's the thing, though.
If you think this is some huge production that's putting this out, this movie looks
like it cost about $20 to make.
So don't be expecting a big budget production.
But hey, just because it has no budget doesn't mean it can't be good.
There is a trailer available, by the way, which you can watch on YouTube if you just
look for Press Start, the movie, there's actually a trailer, or actually looking at it in the
studio right now if you want to kind of check this out here.
Would you mind telling me what you were doing with these, hmm?
Don't forget what I did to your brother.
In a world ruled by an evil sorcerer, two rebels seek a hero foretold by an ancient
prophecy.
Who is ancient prophecy?
An ancient prophet.
This looks like that cheerleader ninjas movie.
I love LARPing.
Let's make it into a movie.
Why'd you let him hit you?
It was his turn.
On September 25th.
Batten down the hatches.
Rile up the mechanical dinosaurs.
It won't be a game.
Congratulations.
You've just leveled up.
Because it's a movie.
Did you see the graphics on that tree thing there?
That was crazy.
Those fools have no idea what horrors await them.
Thank you for warning us that the movie will suck.
Awesome.
Oh, it's going straight to DVD.
Never would have guessed that.
You never know.
It might be decent.
No, it might.
We'll try and get some of the guys from the movie on the show or something.
Where would you buy that DVD?
Like at a garage sale or something?
I guess from the website.
There's a little website.
It's straight on the website.
They're relying on a buzzword called, you know, it's like a viral marketing.
In other words, people...
Well, it's working.
We talked about it on our program and it was on a lot of major game blogs.
There was that funny part in the thing, though, about that it was his turn to attack.
I like that.
So it was like an RPG.
That was funny.
Come on, if you can sit through that Cheerleader Ninjas, I'm sure you can make it through this
movie, Loki.
There might be something about it.
Cheerleader Ninjas had nudity in it.
This might.
You never know.
That's a point.
Yeah, that's true.
There could be nudity in this movie.
Direct to DVD.
For artistic purposes.
No, they don't have the budget for nudity.
Would you really want to see any of them naked?
I don't know.
I don't think so.
What we're going to do is we're going to open up the Skype line because it's time to play
Beat the Host.
I love that song.
Let's just listen to that.
Okay.
Great.
All right.
Tonight we're going to play Beat the Host.
We're going to take our first caller on the Skype line at Orange Lounge Radio, our username
on Skype, or 1-877-GAME-OLR to play Beat the Host.
I've got to warn you, if you want to play tonight, you need to have some type of working
knowledge about music and video games or else your chances are going to be a little bit
screwed in tonight's game.
Here we go.
We're going to take our first call on the Skype line.
Again, our username is Orange Lounge Radio or 1-877-GAME-OLR.
Here we go.
We've got to call.
Hello.
Who's this?
It always gets through.
GS68.
Hi, GS68.
No, it's not Ravens Dolphin tonight.
It's GS68.
Hey, GS68.
All right.
Are you ready to play some Beat the Host tonight?
Yeah.
I'll give it a shot.
All right.
Now, how would you say your knowledge of old school or new school video game music is?
Eh.
All right.
Well, you sound very enthusiastic about your chances in tonight's Beat the Host.
Tonight you can challenge to Beat the Host.
I'm not going to let you play against Shane because he already kind of knows what's going
on tonight.
I know, but I never get to play.
He's just going to pick Matt.
Probably picks Matt anyway.
All right.
It's not even like they have to ask.
If I let you pick, you'd probably pick Matt, wouldn't you?
What would be wrong with challenging you?
Oh, you can't challenge me because I wrote the questions.
Oh, I see.
All right.
So, by process of elimination.
I'll go with Loki.
All right.
Then, Loki's going to beat the host tonight in Beat the Host, and tonight's challenge
is...
It should be called Beat the Host Named Loki.
Tonight's challenge is Put My Thing Down, Flip It, and Reverse It, is the name of tonight's
challenge.
Tonight's challenge is about who can identify the most video game music songs being played
backwards.
Okay?
Oh, God.
Now, these could be songs anywhere from an 8-bit Atari era all the way through new school
Xbox 360 and PlayStation 3 games.
Okay?
If things drag on, I will give you guys hints to help you guess the game.
Which one to get it gets the point.
All right?
So, you guys know how to play?
I'm ready.
All right.
So, you guys are going to go at the same time.
GS68, make sure you yell out your answers nice and loud so I can hear you over the music.
Okay?
And I have to leave the chat room, right?
Yes.
You do need to leave the chat room or else people are going to help you cheat, and we
can't have that.
All right.
Okay?
Is he out of chat?
Okay.
You left the chat room, GS68?
Yeah.
Okay.
Now, remember, you don't have to send me a private message or anything.
Just yell it out when you know it, because you're up against Matt in real time, okay?
Okay.
So, I'm going to keep score here, and...
There should be buzzers.
There should be, but we don't have any.
Let's go D.
Buzz.
We're a low-budget production.
Okay.
Here we go.
Here's song number one, and the first one to get it gets a point.
And remember, these are being played backwards.
Okay.
What's that, GS68?
I've heard this on the OLAR stream, but I can't put my finger on it.
Keep going.
This game was on the Dreamcast.
Seriously, you guys?
Space Shell 5.
Thank you.
Yes.
Loki got a point, finally.
Sorry.
How did you get to that?
I was...
Because it sounded to me...
It almost sounded like Tank from Cowboy Bebop, but I just started thinking about stuff that
have the same kind of pro music.
All right.
Well, again, remember, these songs are being played backwards.
To me, it sounded like a song from Loop on the Third.
Exactly.
See, it's kind of along the same lines.
All right.
Well, Loki has a point, but GS68, there's 10 songs tonight, so all is not lost.
You ready for song number two?
Yep.
All right.
Here we go.
Animal Crossing.
Ooh!
Loki's on fire!
GS68, did you even hear any of that?
Yeah.
Couldn't recognize it.
It was Animal Crossing, the little drum, tap, little quiet stuff.
Yes, it was Animal Crossing.
Good job, Loki.
You played the game way too much.
All right.
Here we go.
Here's another one.
Remember, these could be from any system, new school or old school.
Here we go.
Here's number three.
Luminous.
Oh, GS68 knew that one too.
That's right.
That was Shining from Luminous.
Damn, Loki, on fire.
That sounded so evil backwards.
It did sound like it.
You want to hear a little more?
Yeah, a little bit more.
Want to hear a little more?
Oh, now it's a little healthier.
I like it backwards.
I want an MP3 of it backwards now.
I can send you an MP3 of it backwards if you want.
That'd be cool.
All right.
GS68, it's three-nothing.
You got to make some progress here, okay?
All right.
We're pulling for you, though.
Here we go.
Here's number four.
Ready?
Yeah.
This
game was on the NES.
Master Master?
No.
Super Contra?
Contra?
No.
Ready to legend?
What'd you say?
No, it's not ready to legend.
This game had a character named Ryu.
Ninja Gaiden.
Oh, Loki got it.
Needed a couple clues to get it, but it was Ninja Gaiden.
Stage one music.
GS68, it's not looking good.
I'm sorry to say, but try to get some points on the board, okay?
We're all pulling for you, all right?
Yeah.
All right.
I'll bust Loki's kneecaps so he has a challenge in some of these later ones.
Okay, you ready?
Okay, here we go.
Here comes song number five.
You ready, GS68?
Yeah.
You can do it.
Act Freezer.
Sonic!
No.
Yes.
GS68 got one.
Wow.
I think the room...
What was that?
GS68 got one.
I think the roof came off his house.
It was Sonic.
Oh.
Oh, that's right.
Yeah.
I thought he yelled a bad word.
That is what you said, right, GS68?
Yeah.
That's what I heard, but he did it in that old...
I think it was an allusion to the old Sega commercials when he yelled it out.
He yelled, Sonic!
Or he just really wanted to win.
That was the bonus stage in Sonic.
The bonus stage music.
Yeah.
All right.
Good.
I'm so glad to see you get on the board, GS68.
All right.
Here we go into the next question.
Question number six, I believe this one is.
Here we go.
Parappa the Rapper.
Ooh.
Mere seconds splitting it up.
I could hear GS68 start to say it as Loki got it out.
It was Parappa the Rapper.
All right.
This next one's a little bit tougher, GS68.
You ready?
Ready for the next one, GS68?
Yes.
Okay.
Here we go.
This is on the 360.
And the PC.
Not that one yet.
I guess.
No.
This is a role playing game.
I don't think that's the 11th.
No.
Oblivion.
Yes.
Finally.
Jesus.
Sorry.
It took long enough.
Yes.
It was Oblivion.
All right.
Looks like Loki has six, so there's no possible way you're going to be able to win GS68, but
keep playing just for the fun of it, okay?
All right.
We're going to get through the rest of this.
Here we go.
Here comes the next one.
Contra.
No.
No, it's Castlevania.
Castlevania IV.
No.
Symphony and Night.
Castlevania III.
No.
Dracula X.
GS68.
I think he just gave up.
Castlevania II Science Quest.
Finally.
Jesus Christ.
Yes.
I didn't go through all of them.
GS68.
You should have jumped in there when his weak point was exposed.
For massive damage, you could have jumped in there with number two.
You're going to know it.
All right.
Here we go.
Here comes number nine.
Now, I'm going to say I think this was the hardest one in the whole bunch.
If either one of you can get this, props to you.
All right.
This game was also on the 360 and PC.
Fantasy Star Universe?
No.
What was that?
Final Fantasy XI?
No.
This game was the same composer who did the music to Oblivion.
Blair?
No.
The story of this game has to do with alien abduction.
Alien?
Can I guess?
What was that, GS68?
I was going to say Alien Syndrome, but I forgot that's not on the PC.
Oh, God.
I know the game, but I just can't think of the name.
This game is notable for featuring a Native American lead character.
Prey.
Yes.
GS68.
I was like, finally.
It was on the tip of my tongue.
Yes.
It's Prey.
All right.
Good job.
Good job, GS68.
I knew the game.
I just couldn't think of the name.
All right.
Let's move on.
Ready for the last one, you guys?
Yes.
Here it is.
That was Butterfly.
Yes, Loki.
All right.
That's an accident.
Wow.
GS68, you got smoked tonight, I'm sorry to say.
GG.
A score is 8 to 2.
Did you just say GG?
Yes.
GG, Loki.
GG.
Well, I'm sorry, GS68, you lost tonight, but it's our consolation prize.
We'll give you a second to plug anything you want to plug real quick.
I don't have anything to plug.
I'm sorry to hear it.
All right.
Well, thanks for playing anyway, GS68.
We appreciate it.
No problem.
All right.
Later, dude.
Good job, Loki.
You know, isn't that game unfair to the listener?
Why is that?
Because there's a time delay?
No, because when they're on Skype, it's still instantaneous.
Oh.
Yeah.
There's only the time delay if they're listening over Live 365, but they shouldn't be doing
that when they're playing that.
All right.
Looking at a chat and seeing what's going on, Zappy says, that was a hard beat the host
tonight.
Go Banjo thinks the last one was easy.
Well, if you're a DDR nerd, then the last one was easy, so there you go.
All right.
Let's get back into some gaming news.
That's it for beat the host tonight.
If you guys like those games or other games like it, send us an email, mailbag at orangehousereader.com.
We're looking for ideas for new games, by the way, so just wanted to put that out there.
All right.
Let's get back into the gaming news.
Loki, take it away.
Sorry.
Anyways, so yeah, there's some interesting stuff.
This is really interesting.
Nokia has unveiled the N-Gage gaming platform.
Now remember that they are not making any more gaming systems, but their new Nokia phones,
of course, are going to be supporting the brand new gaming platform, which looks okay.
They've got a few people on board already, including Electronic Arts, Capcom, and Viviti,
and they've got some other exclusive games as well.
It will be compatible with the Nokia models N73, N81, N93, and N95, and with more S60
models to be compatible at a later date.
The games right now, they're going to be free to demo, but will cost between 6 and 10 euros
to buy the full version and feature online play against friends or, of course, random
people via the N-Gage arena, which it kept trying to get me to walk into during E3.
The N-Gage arena at the last E3 that was a real E3 was pretty swanky.
Yeah, they actually had a really nice booth at the last E3.
Too bad it was a piece of crap product, but it was still a nice booth.
What do you think of this news?
I mean, I don't think this is so bad.
I think it's kind of neat.
I think it's much better than the N-Gage's actual system was, so there you go.
Let's move on to the next story, which is about a new PC demo, other things you can
do with your PC.
Crysis is getting a PC demo on September 25, 2007, but the one thing about that day you
should also keep in mind, that's the same day the Halo 3 comes out, so something to
keep in mind.
Well, a lot of people are anticipating this game.
It's a big first-person shooter for the PC, so if you want to take that PC versus console
gaming to a whole new level, there you have it.
Thank you to the folks behind Crysis for doing this, so funny.
Also, there is a new game, or I should say an older game, that is free now.
Command & Conquer, the Gold Edition, is free to download, and you can download it actually
off of, I believe, the official Command & Conquer website.
That's pretty awesome, and I guess they're also featuring Command & Conquer Strategy
for the month of September.
What do you mean by strategy?
Like free strategy guys or something?
Yeah.
Huh.
I guess it's an ISO image, so you'd have to burn it to a CD, but that's pretty awesome
though.
Command & Conquer is a cool game.
That's pretty cool.
Anyhow, another PC game that is free and has been free for quite a while, MapleStory, is
getting an update.
I know some of you guys out there like to play this game, MapleStory.
It's a free MMO that's available out there, and there's some brand new stuff being added
to the game.
The Mountain Village of Mulung is being added, as well as a new town called Herb Town.
Like the herbs?
Yeah, like, you know, let's go smoke a joint, man.
Or maybe not, but those are being added to MapleStory this week, so check that out.
I should also say that Mulung features a salon where players can buy new hairstyles.
That's a feature coming to WoW pretty soon, right?
Yes, I can't wait.
You love to customize hairstyles.
You know, you've been looking for a new MMO to play.
Why haven't you been playing MapleStory?
Because I've tried it before, and I thought it was a piece of crap.
Why did you think it was a piece of crap?
It was boring.
I didn't understand what I was doing, and my character was ugly.
I don't play ugly characters.
Herb Town, by the way, includes new monsters to fight, but no word yet if you can actually
score some herbs in Herb Town.
Well, following Lost Planet, and I guess Ghost Recon releasing some map packs for free, Gears
of War, the map pack that's been available so far, the Hidden Fronts map pack is going
to be available for free as well, starting in September.
Actually, tomorrow at 2am is going to be when it's going to be available, September 3rd.
You can get four maps that are included with that, including Bullet Marsh, Garden, Process,
and Subway.
So that's not bad.
Free is always good.
Hooray for free, AIDS.
I notice there's a lot of people online that aren't playing Gears of War anymore.
I wonder why that is.
I guess it's just because there's all these other Xbox 360 games capturing people's attention
now, but it seems like Gears of War was the big thing not that long ago, and now I barely
see people on my friends list playing that game anymore.
Maybe these free maps will breathe some life back into it, what do you think?
I doubt it, because they've been available for a while now, so I figured if people wanted
them they would have already bought them.
Well, now there's been a lot of stories going around about how the 60GB PlayStation 3 is
officially no more, that they completely sold out, but Sony would like you to know that
they have replenished their PlayStation 3 supply of 60GB PlayStation 3s on sonystyle.com.
That's because they were on backorder at one point, they are now back in stock, so there's
no official word if the 60GB are officially gone or not.
That actually makes sense to me, because sonystylestore, whatever it's called, is not Sony, Inc.
You know what I mean?
It's just another store, like any other GameStop or whatever, it just happens to be run by
Sony.
So of course they're going to run out, it doesn't mean the whole supply is gone.
This isn't really a whole lot of big news to me, but just to kind of stop the doom and
gloom that was going around about, oh the 60GBs are gone, they're gone forever, and
so on.
One of these days I'll buy a PlayStation 3.
One of these days.
It's alright, one of these days there'll be games for it, and I own a PS3 and I'm kind
of disappointed.
Luckily though, in October though, I'm looking forward to Ratchet and Clank.
I'm actually going to skip out on buying Lair and skip on Heavenly Sword.
Lair's been getting some crap reviews though, I'm kind of feeling bad for those guys.
I have a last minute story too about Lair, so let me ask you.
Okay, well let's open up the Skype line and then we'll get into the last minute stories.
Our Skype line is open if you want to give us a call.
Our username is on skypeorangeloungeradio.com or our phone number is 1-877-GAME-OLR, that's
1-877-GAME-OLR, or our username is on skypeorangeloungeradio.
Go ahead and give us a call.
While we wait for those calls, I'll go to Loki real quick for any last minute stories.
Real quick, you can play Lair on your PSP via remote play.
Whoo!
Gimmicky!
Wait, you can play the whole game on your PSP?
Well, most of it, because the PSP lacks, of course, a second R2 and L2 button.
Interesting.
Well let's go to the phones, we're getting some calls now, I'll come back to that in
a minute.
Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio, who's this?
You're getting a special phone call.
I've been getting a special phone call, who's this?
You're getting a special phone call, it's Jason.
Hi Jason, I knew you were Jason.
On again, off again, listen whenever possible.
But our always constant webmaster, and we appreciate you for that.
Always.
I just want to make you introduce yourself, because not all the podcast people know folks
by their voice.
What's on your mind, Jason?
I was just going to say that if anybody remembers anybody here that actually listens to all
games, they'll probably remember how much of a Wii proponent I was back in the day,
the month or so, whenever it was coming up on the show, the month or so before it came
out.
Right.
They might also remember that on the forums, I mentioned something about me having a feeling
that the Wiis might finally be generally available come springtime.
I was wrong on that one.
Hey, I saw a whole bunch of them sitting on a rack at Fry's the other day, I was finally
surprised to see, I mean there were like 20 of them in this cart, so I was surprised to
see them pretty abundant now.
Amazing that whenever I've been going to stores, whenever we drop by the electronics section
at Walmart, Target, whenever we run by Best Buy, any other electronics related store,
every time I've looked, I've never actually seen one available until today.
And so you know what happened today?
What?
We bought one.
Hooray!
I am now officially a member of the Wii 60 camp, as it were.
Wee!
Yes.
We got, I don't even remember, we got WarioWare Smooth Moves, we got Trauma Center, we got
Mario Party 8, we got Resident Evil 4 Wii, and I'm missing one, yes, that's right, the
Bust and Move 4 Wii version that the screenshots looked absolutely ridiculous, but it's probably
going to be a load of fun.
Wow, very cool.
The only thing you're missing is Metroid Prime, because that game is pretty awesome.
I was looking at that, and I really did like the DS version, with the exception that I've
always played it when I was tired, so I played so little of it, and when it comes to escaping
the planet, I'm way too tired to comprehend where I'm supposed to go, and the 3D map isn't
exactly intuitive when you're so dead tired, but I'm holding off on that for now, not to
mention we picked up a points card, so I'm going to be grabbing a few virtual console
things, and given the 360, given that, given everything else, I'm going to have more than
enough to suffice me for, well, maybe about a week, but, you know, I didn't want to buy
too many things.
And you're adding me to your friend's codes list very soon, aren't you?
Well, of course, I'm going to go through the thread and get just about everybody, probably
everybody, I'm not biased, and then I'll of course be throwing mine in there, and we'll
continue on from there.
Very cool.
Well, congratulations, I'm finally getting a Wii, so do you still, are you still as much
of a proponent for the Wii as you were nine months ago?
I've never stopped, it's just a general availability thing, coupled with money kind of thing, and
we get to thank the lovely Rai Chan for all that, because she's actually the one that
made this all possible.
She's making faces at me, saying, oh, me this, me that, yeah, you're the one that did it.
I thought I heard Rai in the background, so tell her hello from all of us here at O.M.R.
Everybody in O.M.R. says hello, and she says hello.
Hello.
Well, you kids have fun with your Wii, but not too much.
No, I'm off, well, I'm on call tomorrow, but I'm generally off as long as nothing actually
happens.
I have all paid myself to play.
All right.
Well, try to stay off while you're playing with your Wii.
I'll try my best.
All right.
Bye, Jason.
Bye, guys.
Take care.
We love Jason, because he not only hosts our website, but he's just a good kid, so we really
like hearing from Jason.
If you want to give us a call, 1-877-GAME-OLR, or our username on Skype is ORANGE LOUNGE
RADIO.
Let's go to the phones.
Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
Who's this?
GSX8 again.
You again?
Yes.
Weren't you already on this show?
Yeah, and I got hacked, sort of, by Loki.
All right.
That's the host.
Well, we've got to keep it real short to let some more people in.
So what's on your mind?
Oh.
I might get a new DS in, because my current DS is broken.
Logi said some time ago that their websites were getting hybrid DS being in custom colors.
Logi, what are some specific websites?
Some of the questions dropped.
Are you talking about websites that their DSes are coming in different colors?
There was a website that has different colors for DSes, and I can't remember.
Oh, the, like, custom dozen or whatever?
Yeah.
Yeah, I have to look.
Hold on.
Well, if he can't find it, I can tell you that, now, I know you live nowhere near New
York City, but I don't know if you can import these on eBay or what have you, but the official
Nintendo World store will do all these different types of colors that you can't get.
You know, gosh, you're a pretty penny for them.
Like, I remember being out there, and there was, like, a hot pink DS.
I swear to God, I came so close to buying it for, like, $250, though.
It was expensive.
I want a red DS myself.
Hmm.
Well, don't they have, I could have sworn I saw, not too long ago, they have the red
and black thing now in stores with Brain Age 2, don't they?
Yeah, but only the lid part is red.
Can you still find those Mario Kart DSes in there?
Those aren't lights, huh?
Yeah.
Those aren't lights.
I'm going to get a light soon if my DS, my regular DS, goes to hell.
Yeah, I still have my DS fat somewhere.
I should just give it away on the show or something, because I'm never going to use
it anymore.
But it's not a very exciting DS.
It's an old gray one.
Maybe I'll donate it to charity or something.
DS is a DS.
Okay, I found the website.
Yes.
Although they are more expensive.
It's colorwarepc.com, and they have everything from, I don't see, they used to have PSPs
and DSes, but they don't anymore.
They just have consoles.
They have PlayStation 3s, Xbox 360, and the Wii.
You can actually buy a red PlayStation 3 for an extra hundred bucks, or they have a gold
one and some other crap.
The chat room is yelling at me for thinking about donating my DS.
They want me to give it away.
You greedy bastards.
All right, GSCC, we've got to let you go to get some more calls, but thanks so much
for playing our game, and good luck on finding your red DS.
Thanks, no problem.
Bye-bye.
Well, you know what I just thought as well?
He could check Play Asia, because you can import some different colors from Japan, but
I don't think they have red DSes over there, do they?
I can't remember.
There's a lot more different colors over there, though, than there are over here.
I know that.
If there's any more calls, please call in right now, 1-877-GAME-OLR, or username on
Skype, Orange Lounge Radio.
Any other last-minute stories, Loki, while we wait?
Nope.
Just that one.
No, that's it?
Just the one about Laird?
Just the one about Laird, and that's pretty much all that I cared about.
It's been kind of a slow news week, all things considered.
I wonder if that's Labor Day or what the deal is.
Maybe.
Then there's less people listening to the show tonight than usual, probably again because
of Labor Day and all that stuff.
People are out vacationing and doing what have you.
You'll figure.
Yeah.
Well, I guess that's all the folks that wanted to call in.
Their phone's not ringing anymore.
People are just being shy.
The usual suspects are on vacation.
So, and if there's no more last-minute stories, that takes us to the end of the show.
Cry, cry.
Any final thoughts, folks?
Let's go around.
Mikkel Tod, thank you for being here, even if you didn't contribute much tonight.
We appreciate your moral support, and I'm... You okay over there?
I'm trying to... I'm doing cryptograms.
What is your late... What is your new obsession with cryptograms here?
I love them.
They're so much fun.
Is there a website that you play all these things on?
Cryptograms.org.
Is this because you're too busy now, or, I mean, now, I'm sorry, now you're too bored
because now that you won Survivor, there's nothing else to do.
I want to win another Survivor game, but I don't... Nothing's going on with it.
But you lost Pirate Master, right?
Yeah, but that's because I hated people, and I didn't want to talk to them.
At least that's what I'm going to say it is.
I don't know why else.
Hey, those of you guys that listen to this show and think it would be fun to play one
of these games online, I'm going to talk in a future edition a little more in depth about
these online games, because I think they're kind of interesting.
It's not really video game related, but I think they're really kind of different.
So I'm going to definitely talk a little more in depth about these games a little later
on when a particular game I'm thinking of is going to be recruiting soon.
I'm going to have some folks on to talk about those.
That should be interesting, right?
Yes.
Right.
And, Loki, thank you for being here as always, even if you wouldn't drink with me.
We didn't really get drunk tonight.
It's kind of sad.
I didn't drink enough.
I was nervous because of being on meds and all, and then Shane doesn't really drink ever
and you just drove, so kind of... I'm sorry if we disappointed on the alcoholic content
tonight.
I drank three of these Smirnoffs, but I'm not feeling anything.
Yeah, I don't know.
Well, your final thought, Loki?
My final thought is, I don't know, I wish there was some more news.
Oh, this is a slow week.
I'm sure things will be definitely speeding up towards the end of the year, that's for
sure, as games are released and everything.
My final thought is, this Arctic berry is probably my favorite flavor of Smirnoff Ice
yet.
I don't know what your problem is with this blueberry.
It's too berry.
It's good.
It's delicious berry is what it is.
All right.
I'm looking at chat room to see some stuff here.
Son of Dad says, final thought, Metroid Prime 3 will own my soul this week.
It really will.
It's so good.
All right.
That's it, kids.
We're out of here.
Thank you guys so much.
I know it's a little short tonight, but that's all right.
I mean, it was slow news week and Labor Day weekend and everything, but thank you guys
so much for being with us, as you always are, every week here for the Orange On The Trail
podcast.
We are an independent production, and so the only way we really keep around is from word
of mouth and for you guys telling folks about our show.
Please go leave us a happy, happy five-star review on iTunes and recommend friends to
friends in other ways, whether it be on Digg podcast or Yahoo podcast or what have you.
There's plenty of ways to get the word out.
For myself, Dark Sakura, who will be back next week, and Loki, thank you guys so much
for tuning into us, and we'll see you next week here on Orange Lounge Radio.
You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
For more information on our live and podcast program, visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com.
See you next week.