Orange Lounge Radio. Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
To join us for a live show, visit www.allgames.com, Sunday nights at 6 p.m. Pacific time.
The views and opinions expressed on Orange Lounge Radio do not necessarily reflect those of the entire staff of Orange Lounge Radio or allgames.com, but were probably right anyway.
See you next week!
Tonight on the Afterbirth, Jamie has another commitment she's got to get to early in the morning.
It's called work.
She did will us a cage match pic, so we'll be taking care of that for her.
But first, we have another edition of Secret Club.
Here's the thing about Secret Club, and this is new for all games people, so listen up, here's the thing about Secret Club.
We tell you secrets, but the thing about when you hear secrets from the first rule of Secret Club, you do not talk about Secret Club.
Meaning that if you hear it here on this program, great, you're in the know, but you don't go posting about it to websites saying,
hey, I heard it on OrangeLoungeRadio.com or I heard it on allgames.com, because we're at this point, we used to be that way where we were like, hey, you know, it makes our E penis bigger when OLR brings you the exclusive.
But then we got the smack down that one time and it's just kind of like, you know what, fuck it, we're just going to start Secret Club and start giving out secrets.
So, we have some secrets tonight in Secret Club.
I guess, yeah.
Alright, so what would you like to share in Secret Club tonight, Loki?
Okay, well, this week, I guess, we'll talk briefly, as with every year and, you know, they got to hate us, I guess, by now for this stuff.
There's stuff that always seems to come out about upcoming Konami titles and this isn't a big surprise, you know, with, you know, each year we're seeing a new release of certain games, you know, that we'd be seeing an announcement for something that hasn't quite been announced yet.
Brand new DDR game coming to the PlayStation 2, although right now the title has got me a little confused, DDRX or Dance Dance Revolution X.
I don't know what the hell that's supposed to be, but that is slated for the fall.
DDR Extreme.
I don't remember.
The X is for extreme.
Is it possibly in this, I was thinking about this this week ever since you posted Secret Club in the Secret Forum.
Is it their tenth release, maybe?
I don't think so.
Like, if you add all the games together from PlayStation 1, is it?
No, because Extreme was the eighth one and then there would have been...
Extreme 2, oh, Supernova and Supernova 2.
Yeah.
Oh, alright.
So, I don't know. Maybe they just ran out of funky titles for it, I guess.
Who knows?
And then Hottest Part 2, of course, because, you know, the first one did pretty well, so, of course, got to release another one.
AJ Mix says X is for tenth anniversary. That's a good thought.
Because 98 was the first year of DDR, hence the song.
Maybe.
There you go. There you go. Props to you, AJ.
Yeah. And then Lost in Blue coming to the Wii as well.
Lost in Blue on the Wii, so I can be bored out of my mind on the Wii too.
Yes.
Right.
And then totally on a different topic here, got some more news talking about the whole...
Remember a while back we were talking about the whole Gibson suing Activision and Harmonix for Guitar Hero?
Well, it's interesting because people were speculating, oh, it's probably over money or something like that.
I think this might clear it up.
And you'd be surprised.
This is actually... This was an email that we got from our rep at Activision, actually.
And it says, as you may know, Activision is involved in litigation with Gibson Guitar Corporation relating to the sales of Guitar Hero games.
In connection with such, Gibson has asserted to Activision that Gibson has the exclusive right to sell Guitar Hero games to music specialty stores, such as Guitar Center stores.
Although Activision does not agree with Gibson on this issue, until this issue is resolved with Gibson,
Activision is requesting that its distributors refrain from selling Guitar Hero games to any music specialty store.
So that sounds like it's over money, after all, and not some sort of patent infringement.
Well, I think we all kind of guessed that, to be honest.
I hate to say it that way, but I think we all kind of knew.
But, I mean, is this really a big surprise, brand new DDR game coming out for the PlayStation 2 this year?
I mean, what, there's like one every year anyways?
I don't know.
If that's a surprise to you, then I don't know.
Yeah, honestly, the new DDR game, no surprise at all, though the title's kind of interesting, but that Gibson thing is interesting.
You know, DDRX kind of sounds like it could be a temporary name for it, but who knows.
What I do find interesting is that there isn't anything about an Xbox 360 version.
No, there isn't. No 360 or PlayStation 3 or anything like that yet.
But, typically those games, though, if I remember last year, Supernova 2 and Hottest Party came out in September, and then the Xbox 360 one came out in November.
So it might just not be announced yet. That may be too far ahead.
I don't know. But I don't know how well they've done.
All right, now with that said, I've got to find a cage match to pick.
All right, yeah, you better look for that, because look at the cage match.
Well, thank you, everybody, for participating. Another week of secret class.
Yes, I like sharing this stuff with you guys, but I like having a job, too, so please keep it that way.
All right, so we'll see what happens.
All right, I guess at this point we do get into the cage. I was thinking I might have one more thing for secret club tonight.
You should play this thing that we posted. It's that separated at birth we fit balance board and aperture science turret.
Oh, yeah, I didn't want to do it because it was audio.
Let me see if I can get that. Let me go to the forums real quick.
It was funny.
After birth part of the show, I don't have to be as professional. Where was it here?
Here's the show role in the super secret forum. Let's see, it was we fit.
Oh, it's like the very first story in the thing that Dark Tits.
They have two little things on there.
Kind of a genius to play the first one.
All right, so what is this? There's apparently a great similarity between the Wii Fit balance board and aperture science turret.
Okay, here's what the turret sounds like.
Deploying. Target lost. Are you still there? I've been waiting.
And here's the Wii Fit balance board.
Starting up. Step on. Ready.
Three, two, one.
Measuring. Measuring. Measuring. All done.
Sounds like just another stupid Wii voice to me. I don't know. I don't know if I see the similarities.
But that's that.
Okay, I can give you one more thing for Secret Club.
Super dodge ball on virtual console at some point.
In the not too distant future.
I wouldn't see that. Why not?
Especially with River City Ransom just coming out.
Super dodge ball brawlers or something like that.
That was coming to DS at the end of next month. Makes sense.
I'm just waiting for that Wii Fit thing in that little high pitched voice to go,
Measuring. Measuring. Measuring. Still measuring. God damn you're fat.
Stop eating piggy.
Alright, let's have ourselves an OLR cage match.
The way the cage match works, three songs go in and do battle and the winning song,
well it doesn't go into rotation anymore because it's not our station,
but it does win the praise and admiration of all of our listeners
and some type of consolation prize we'll come up with in the future.
Meanwhile, let's discuss the three songs doing battle tonight.
It's last week's winner versus two new people, or songs I should say, brought in from OLR hosts.
Last week in the Orange Launch Radio Cage Match, believe it or not, I won.
And I won with a little band called Spray who was famous for the song I Am Gothic in DDR years ago.
They did a cover of the song Run With Us.
It was the theme song to the Raccoons, but they made it sound like initial, or not initial D,
Wan Gen Midnight Maximum Tune.
Like imagine mixing your favorite 80s cartoon, even though the Raccoons probably top nobody's list,
with Wan Gen Midnight Maximum Tune, and you get this song.
So it's all kinds of awesome and the chatroom voted it as their favorite too.
It's song number one tonight. It's Spray with Run With Us.
And remember, you only get a clip because it did win last week.
And you sing it in a quick sense, and it turns you down.
In the field of coming under, through your arms.
We got done with us.
We got everything you need.
Run with us.
We are free.
Come with us.
I see passion in your eyes.
That was song number one.
I'm getting ahead of myself.
The song is called Run With Us, the Michael Trend filled radio edit, technically that is,
but it's song number one on the single, which is available on iTunes.
It's awesome.
The Raccoons, Run With Us by Spray.
All right, song number two tonight is brought to you by Jamie.
Even though she's not here and sadly can't take your FUs either,
so off the table into next week.
She thought, gee, I had so much luck with mindless self-indulgence the other week.
I think I'll try it again and see if lightning strikes twice.
So she brings this song to you guys tonight.
It's called Shut Me Up, which we've managed to do tonight by her leaving early.
Shut Me Up by Mindless Self-Indulgence.
Here it is, song number two tonight.
I can't wait for you to fuck me up in a minute, minute, in a fucking minute.
I can't wait for you to fuck me up in a minute, minute, in a second.
I can't wait for you to shut me up and make me hit my bad ass.