Orange Lounge Radio
We're the hosts, Dark Sakura, Sky, and the Loco King
Tonight April 27th, 2008, the old classic game Splatterhouse is set to return
Burnout Paradise is getting patched for motorcycle riding
And are arcade ticket redemption machines a form of illegal gambling?
Orange Lounge Radio
Hello everybody out there on the internet
And welcome to another week of the program that Bobby Blackwolf had to censor three times tonight
Orange Lounge Radio, live at www.allgames.com
Every Sunday night, 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern
My name is Rob Roberts, joining me as always to talk about video games
Video gaming, gaming culture, and gamer lifestyle
My BFF in the world, Jamie Summers, Dark Sakura
Hi
How are you?
I'm tired
Tired?
Because of the sun
Tired cat is very tired?
Sleepy Jamie is sleepy
I know, it's very, we have heat issues here
Because obviously, you know, our show is based in Sacramento, California
And we're just starting to get into summer
I think it's only like 90 degrees out
And yes, even though it's late April, it's starting to get into summer
It's what, 90 degrees out?
And yeah, it's getting very hot here in the studio
And we're trying to buy more fans to help with the problem
It's only 83 outside
Hence me saying not even
Lord
No, it's 90
Oh, okay
It was 83 last time I checked
Because I was going to say, when we get into June and July
We're going to have 105
However
And I'm going to cry
However, the forecast says that it's going to be 83 on Monday
And then in the 70s, Tuesday, Wednesday, and Thursday
Huh
Well, thank you for the weather update
You know, people talk about the weather when there's nothing better to talk about
But we have video games and other things to talk about
Right, Tech Master Loki, my other BFF
Uh, yeah, how are you doing?
I'm doing fine
Good
I got a large soda today because
You knew it was going to be damn hot
It's hot
It is very hot
And I'm mad as all hell because I bought a box fan from Target
A 20-inch box fan and it's broken
And it was cracked inside the box
Like somebody else returned it
Box fans aren't very, uh, complex
You know, just switch on, go
Ugh, makes me mad
At least we have the nice oscillating fan that is doing a decent job
I think Jamie benefits more than the rest of us for that one
Yes, I do
You know what, it's not oscillating anymore
It's pointed on the back of my neck
God damn it, did that thing break too?
No, I think when I tried to turn the ionizer off
I think I stopped the oscillator too, so
It's going to keep blowing on the back of my neck
I'll fix that
I was going to go back and fix that while DarkSakura talks about her gaming week
My gaming week
And just in time with the theme music
That's what I get when I don't hit the stop button
Happens a lot here on this show
I've had a very, very, very, very busy
Lots of stuff going on week
So I haven't gotten to play much other than Ragnarok
But I'm still trying to get a ZSNES to download
So that I can play, um, uh
Seiken Densetsu 3
And Dan was supposed to bring me back Mario Kart tonight
But I'm sort of like meh about it
Because we've already had access to the game for like a week
So I'm kinda meh
Although lately, like, I really, really want to play Street Fighter Alpha 2
You just, you're going in and digging in the old classics
Are you trying to find some new classic games of the week for the future?
Well, I've actually been sort of wanting us to do our thing
Right, our thing
So I've been thinking, because we're actually going to be cleaning out the vault
Because we're getting a roommate
But I was thinking, um, once all that's set up
I wanted to bust out the Dreamcast and get on some Street Fighter 3 too
You know, as well
Good times
And, uh, third impact on Dreamcast
Alright
Well, so it sounds like there's going to be a lot of classic gaming in your future
Let's move, I know, exciting stuff
Let's move over to Loki and see if there's been a lot of classic gaming in his week
Yes, I played a classic game called Saints Row
Uh, I don't know, it's not really that classic anymore
Um, it's fun
You know, we're still, actually we downloaded a new map this week
Because we're bored with the three that they have
So we wanted the fourth one, the fourth one's okay
It's been out for, what, years now
But, you know, with the internet being blocked at our work
I had to kind of jerry-rig something in order to get to work
But, uh, that was all to just kill time until Grand Theft Auto IV
Which I, uh, sneaked an early copy of
And, um, what more do I need to see?
I've been looking for this game for, what, years now?
Since Grand Theft Auto III?
Oh, probably since, like, you know, last Grand Theft Auto
San Andreas, yeah
Okay
It's fucking awesome, I mean
It's, um, there, okay, let me just
Since the game is, you know, pretty awesome
I'll just, you know, mention my gripes of the game
I don't like the soundtrack, I think it's lame
Um, I guess I've been spoiled with, like, Vice City and Grand Theft Auto III
But I hate the radio stations in, uh, IV
I think they're crap
Um, let's see, I don't like, um
I don't know, that might be just it
Um, oh, I don't like how you can't skip the intro in the beginning of the game
Because you have to, it has to kind of boot up, I guess, a little bit
Um, before it gets into loading and stuff
You just can't bypass all that little cutscene stuff
Um, uh, oh, and I don't like the fact that I don't know any cheat codes yet
Because half the fun of Grand Theft Auto was when you didn't want to actually play through the story
As you're cheating like crazy and just getting rocket launchers and blowing everything up
I kind of miss that, but I'm sure that'll come out eventually once the game gets released
A couple questions, is the game worthy of the perfect 10 reviews it's receiving left and right?
Probably, I mean, I don't, it's not perfect
But, I mean, it's damn good, I'd say give it a 9-8 or 9-9
But nothing's perfect
Um, what is the most obscene thing you've done in the game so far?
The most obscene thing?
Like, thing that is going to shock people like Hot Coffee
Thing that is going to make Lord Voldemort
And if you haven't been listening to our show for a while
Lord Voldemort is our nickname for somebody else
A very infamous lawyer in the gaming community
What is, like, the thing you've done that would piss Lord Voldemort off more than anything?
I haven't really done that much in the game
I mean, there really hasn't been anything too controversial, I killed a guy
And we dumped his body in a river, but
I mean, well, other than the countless people that have been running over my car
Um, I would say it's a lot more realistic
So, like, you can shoot someone in the leg and they start hobbling away and stuff
Um, and also, um
Oh, I went to the strip club in there
And they have, like, you know, pretty explicit lap dances
Of course, no one's actually naked in there, but, you know, pasties or whatever
That's pretty explicit, I mean
They have, like, you can do three different lap dances
As it goes on there
And one of them has, like, two girls, like, making out on top of you
So I guess that's pretty explicit
And there's a girlfriend you get in the game in the very beginning there
And you can go in for hot coffee, I guess
But it doesn't show anything
And she actually screams, like, the weirdest things
Wait, do they actually call it hot coffee?
Yeah
And the achievement, you get the achievement for that
For warm coffee, which is funny
Um, I did see, um, in the video review from IGN
There was a scene, I'm assuming from, um
A hooker you can pick up, but it showed, like, a hooker, like, in your lap
Bouncing up and down on you in a car
So that's pretty explicit, I guess
But nothing super over the top yet
Um
Apparently, I did get four stars one time
For riding a motorcycle onto the tarmac for the airport
Apparently the police frown upon that kind of behavior
I'm like, oh crap, four stars
So, that wasn't good
Um
But overall, it's a good game
Very, um
Sometimes it can get annoying because the characters
There's a lot that uses that cell phone in the game
And a lot of characters will call you to do different missions and stuff
And if you don't answer the phone or if you don't do their mission
They, like, you have, like, a percentage of how much they like you
And that'll go down if, um, you don't do their mission
So the game doesn't let you just do the open sandbox thing?
Because one thing I loved about Grand Theft Auto was just, like, you know
I didn't even have to pay attention to the story
Not necessarily
You can do the open sandbox thing
There's actually a mode on the phone that turned it into sleep mode
And that'll turn all the, um, in-game, like, story stuff off
And then you just go and do whatever
So that's kinda cool
Um, but yeah, so, pretty much, just the radio
The stations are kinda retarded on there
You can watch TV, which is kinda funny
You have, like, fake TV shows on there
Nice
Um, and
I don't know, that's pretty much it for right now
Let's go to the chat room
chat.orangelaungeradio.com
We always invite our listeners to come join us live and participate in our program
We read chat comments, take emails, and phone calls later on in the show
First comment tonight from Sephiroth1215
After reading the soundtrack on wiki, the Grand Theft Auto IV soundtrack does look like it sucks
Too bad, cause I love the San Andreas one
But, hey, I guess, you know, the best thing about it is
Since it is on the Playstation 3 and 360 custom soundtracks, so
Uh, earlier Loki said there's no such thing as a perfect game
J-Rod says Silent Hill 1 is perfect, to me anyway
No, it's not
Well, yeah, maybe to one person
And, you know, be honest, this is, it's the perfect Grand Theft Auto, I think, for me
And I haven't even delved into, like, a lot of the online stuff yet
Because, you know
You can do custom soundtracks
So you can fix your major gripe right there
Yeah, exactly, I just didn't like, cause I mean
In 3 even, it had, like, some pretty cool stuff
Like, they had a station that was all electro music and that kind of thing
And that was really cool
And, like, in Vice City, man, all the stations were awesome there
It's just, there's a lot of music that I've never heard of in there
And I guess it's kind of cool that it's new and exclusive to the game
But at the same time, I haven't heard of it and I don't really care for it
Tigerclaw wants to know if you've explored the comedy club area of the game
I haven't gotten to a comedy club
The only thing I've gotten to right now is, like, a cabaret club
And that sucks
Cabarets shit
Do they have a burlesque show? That would be pretty awesome
Um, I don't know if they have a burlesque show
The one time I went in there, they had this really crappy magician
The second time I went in there, they had some guy rolling around on the stage
With doing some sort of western thing
Western monologue
And then, you can, um
One of the first dates you go on is bowling
So you can go bowl, which is kind of cool
They have darts, you can do billiards
They've got, um
Dance Dance Revolution
They have a game that's like, I think it's supposed to be like Qbert in there
I don't know
I gotta go for another viewpoint
Dark Sakura, any interest in Grand Theft Auto 4 at all?
No
Why not?
I just don't like those games
They're not fun to me
Is it not fun because there's no point?
They're kind of boring
Yeah?
Senseless violence not your thing?
I like senseless violence, I just think they're boring
I see
I see, I like, I agree with Loki
You gotta open up the cheat codes
Because the best part of Grand Theft Auto, at least the last one
Or I think it was Vice City I was playing that had this
There was the code that would just make the cars appear from the heavens
And you could just make like 80 cars pile up
And then fire a rocket at them and just make the biggest explosions in the world
That was my favorite part, because fire is awesome
My gaming week
You know, I kind of went and decided to go back to PSP gaming
Like, you know, I haven't been showing the PSP a lot of love here on the show with games
And after my trip recently where I was playing Final Fantasy 1
I said, I'm gonna go get Final Fantasy 2 on the PSP
So I did that, I went and got Final Fantasy 2
Which, you know, very similar to the remake of 1
It's high def, you know, pretty graphics
Fun to play
Loading times surprised me a little bit
I don't know if it's just because my PSP is old and maybe I need to get a mini
But the loading times kind of surprised me how slow they are in some points
But it didn't really detract from the experience
It's just that I noticed it, which, you know, says something there
But the other game I've actually been playing a lot more of is Patapon
I bought that game
And it really was not what I thought it was going to be
I expected it to be like a straight up music game
And certainly music is one element of it
But it was more of like a strategy type of game
I don't know how to say it
It's like a, you know, basically here's the gist of the game
For those who haven't played it is that, you know, the screen flashes in rhythm
Like you'll hear a drum beat that goes
Do, do, do
And then you hit the drums, which are the buttons on the PSP
You only get two drums to start, but you get more later on
You can, you know, hit the drums to issue commands to your little army
So you might go
Pata, pata, pata, pon
And that makes them move forward
Or you might go
Pon, pon, pata, pon
And that makes them attack the enemy
So not only are you having to think about the music
But you're having to think about, okay, what do I want to have them do next
Do I want to have them march forward
Do I want to have them attack
Do I want to have them retreat
Do I want to have them defend
You know, what do I want to have them do
So, that was kind of interesting
But, I'll tell you what
The tutorial in the game, not so great
Because it took me forever to figure out what was going on
I was like, why isn't my freaking army listening to me
And it took me like a minute to get the hang of the game
Like, I think I needed it to kind of show me a little more
Maybe I'm just stupid or old or something
But it took me a little bit to get the hang of
But then once I got in it, okay
And it's kind of cool that you can slowly build your army up
And there's that whole strategy of making the new characters
And what you want to equip them with
Or if you're feeling lazy, you just have the game auto-equip them for you
I think it's a pretty decent price for 20 bucks
It's a decent buy, so definitely check it out
It's a good price
The other game I've been playing this week is on Xbox Live Arcade
I actually bought the full version of Lost Cities
Which is the new card game
And I kind of went into it with very low expectations
Because I was thinking it was going to be another one of those games
That was just very complicated
Like, Catan
Although Catan's a great game
I just never got the hang of it
And it's just too much for me
Because I don't play a lot of those types of board games
And I don't have a lot of
I think the easiest way to learn those types of games
Is to have friends that play them
Because I think friends teaching you how to play those games
Is much easier than the Xbox trying to teach you
And so I had the hardest time trying to learn Catan
Because I didn't really play with anyone else that knew it
And so I was thinking a lot of Lost Cities, I'm probably not going to get it
But the card game is actually pretty simplistic
Yet, you know, one of those games that has a lot of depth to it
So I was kind of surprised
The only thing is, I'm not sure
You know, when all's said and done
There's not a lot of difference between Lost Cities and Uno
They're both card games
They're both, you know, they have the camera support
They both are pretty quick to play
Granted, Lost Cities has a little more of strategy
But what is it? It's a virtual deck of cards, right?
So I'm not sure why Sierra justifies the extra $5
And charges $10 for Lost Cities
Because there's nothing else there
Like, you know what, unlockable art, woohoo
You know, there's not a lot to really justify that extra price
So like if I was a brand new Xbox owner
And I wanted a card game, I'd go for Uno first
But Lost Cities isn't bad
It's just, you know, maybe a little bit overpriced
I imagine it's one of those games that's going to go on sale in six months
So we'll see what happens
But I did have fun with it
And I'm going to try to play some online matches
Although I'm sure I'll get my ass handed to me
Because I guess there is more strategy in Lost Cities
Unlike Uno
How can I describe Lost Cities real quick?
Basically, you're trying to make numerical sequences from 2 to 10
On five different colors which represent cities
And you get, if you are going to start building on a color
You have to make a 20 point investment
And you have to hope that you play enough cards
That will add up to 20 or over by the time the deck is out
Well, in addition to those, there are these multiplier cards
That you can play first
They're called investment cards
And you can double, triple, or quadruple the amount of points that you'll earn
But you're also quadrupling the amount of points that you sacrifice to open up the city
So it's kind of interesting
Katamari's Forever says in chat
Except Uno is appealing to housewives and school children
And Lost Cities is for the Uber hardcore
That may be true, but it still doesn't justify the extra price to me
You know what I mean?
It doesn't seem like there's
Essentially, they're both decks of cards as games
It's just one has a slightly more complicated rule set
That appeals to a more hardcore audience, I don't know
Act Def says Strip Uno on Xbox Live with a cam
Well, you could play Strip Lost Cities too, I guess
I'm not sure exactly what the rules for that would be
You don't need a webcam and an Xbox to play Strip Uno
That's true
You could just have a bunch of people in the house and booze and then be naked
That's probably better anyways
Real in-person naked is better
Then you can see HooHoos and HaHa's IRL
But there's some people in this world who shouldn't be naked
And those are the people playing Strip Uno on Xbox Live, probably
Yeah, but they probably don't have pictures of themselves
They're probably hired like a model
Boobies
I've got to wonder if like on XTube or Pornotube or any of those sites
If there is like a taped Strip Uno game or something that's on those sites
I don't know why I have that curious thought
But you know how I'm thinking of people using their webcams
Like on Yahoo Webcam or whatever to do nasty things
Well, why not take it one step further and upload it on the internet
For other fellow perverts to enjoy it
I'm just wondering how Strip Uno would work since it takes so long to do one game
Maybe it's like if you do a draw four then you have to remove four articles of clothing or something
That might work
Or you know, a draw two you remove two things
That could be the thing is that if you get a draw four and play it on you
Then either you draw four cards or you gotta take something off
Like it could be a choice thing
That might be interesting
That would be interesting
Not that we're encouraging people out of play
No, I don't think it should be a choice thing
I think you should just have to
Alright, anyhow, we better
Gerardo Mo's laughing my ass off
He says, Gerardo Mo says, I love Jamie's take on this
She always is here to give us a refreshing perspective from a female point of view
Boobs are great
Anyhow, that's our gaming week
Let's get into housekeeping tonight
Hey, we got the Grand Theft Auto for Xbox 360 Elite Contest still going on
And you procrastinators, contest entries are due next week
And I'm going to tell you what, we have not gotten a lot of entries
I don't know if people are just taking their time because they want to make
You know, they want to do a really, really good job
Which I can respect
So, you know, maybe they're going to wait until the last minute
But I'm telling you what, you know, it doesn't take a whole lot
And you could win a limited edition Xbox 360 Elite
And it's one of, I think, eight like rare Grand Theft Auto 4 custom paint job type systems
That was given from Gamerscore blog to All Games Radio
Let me remind you how it works
We went over it last week, but I'll say it one more time
We're going to have a bunch of people submit to us little radio things
Like, you know how Grand Theft Auto has the little radio stuff in the game?
How is it in Grand Theft Auto 4? Lots of funny parodies and things that you hear on the radio
Lots of funny commercials
Well, what we want you to do is we want you to make one of those commercials
But about Orange Lounge Radio
And for the other shows participating in this whole thing
Like, for instance, All Games Interactive
We want you to do one about them
Bobby Black Wolf, one about him
You know, Video Game Outsiders, one about them
And so on and so on for all these shows that are participating
And if you want a full list, it's available on OrangeLoungeRadio.com and AllGames.com
And yes, you can enter at more than one site
But you can only be the final qualifier for one
So we're going to pick a few that will be voted on by our audience
And the winning one that's voted on next week will be the winner
They're going to get from All Games a $25 gift certificate to the All Games store
And an All Games shirt just for qualifying for the final round
And then they're going to move on to the final round where they will compete against the final entries from all the other shows
And the community at large is going to pick their favorites
And that will be it
So one entry will win the official Xbox 360 Elite
Based on Grand Theft Auto IV from GamerScoreBlog and All Games Radio
And hey, there's also a second and third prize
I didn't talk about this last week
But second place is the Grand Theft Auto IV game for whatever system you want
And that's courtesy of Mediaspective, one of the other shows on All Games Radio
Third prize, $20 points card for your system of choice
From the Bobby Black Wolf show, the show that precedes us live here on All Games Radio
So, 23 bucks
And Loki is ineligible for the rules
So you don't have to worry about competing against him
Although he really wants it
He really wants it, but he can't have it
Maybe next time
Sorry, Loki, them's the rules
What can I say?
Alright, so if you want to send in your entries, mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com
Just use our general email address
We're separating all the entries in another folder
Or, if you don't have fancy MP3 recording stuff
But you just have a really good idea
That might be good enough to win
1-877-GAME-OLR
Whenever we're not live
Or our username on Skype, OrangeLoungeRadio
You can do that either way you want
So, there you have it
So we hope to get some more entries this week
And set people on fire
Anyway, we listened to one today
And I don't think we're going to play it tonight
We'll play it for you guys next week
We listened to one today
Somebody did it out there just for fun
Because unfortunately he lived in Europe
And unfortunately our friends overseas are ineligible
Because it's an NTSC console
He lives in Belgium to be specific
And sent us a commercial
And I'll tell you what
It was so funny
I cried, laughing
We should use it as our example
It was great
For what people should do
I know, but at the same time
I don't want 10 copies of that
For people to come up with their own original thing
Makes sense, right?
So we'll play it next week
When it's almost over
And that way you can hear
A really good one
And then we'll play the other
Qualifiers for you guys
Pretty soon
Alright
NintendoManiac64 says
Does it have to be MP3?
No, you can use AAC, Wave
Well, Wave might blow up our inbox
As long as Adobe Audition can open it
Or Winamp, we'll play it
Just try not to blow up our inbox
That's all
Alright
That's going to do it for housekeeping
If you're not already there
Join our live journal
Join our MySpace
Join our Facebook
Go to our website
OrangeLaunchRadio.com
And listen to some gaming news
Courtesy of Loki
So yes
Part of a deal that
EA had with
Milton Bradley
They will be publishing
Monopoly
For the Wii, Playstation 2, and Xbox 360
I think it's kind of funny because
EA is trying to get a
Monopoly on sports games
Oh
Karma
It's funny
Har har
I see what you did there
But apparently this is going to be
A sped up version of the original game
With some interactive minigames thrown in
And
I don't know
Doesn't really look like
There's going to be a PS3 version at all
It's Monopoly
What can I say?
That makes sense because
Monopoly never ends
So there needs to be some type of sped up version
I mean Monopoly can go
I mean Monopoly does end I suppose
But it can go on forever
I'm not even wrong
I mean if this came out on like
Xbox Live Arcade or something
I'd probably pick it up
But it's not
Like it doesn't sound like it is
Considering it's going to be on Wii and Playstation 2 as well
It really doesn't sound like it could be on Xbox Live Arcade
It could do retail versions of
I mean look at Puzzle Quest
Okay true
I mean anything's possible
But I don't know
Doesn't it seem likely that maybe that's not the route they're going?
Well it is EA
They like whoring their shit out so
I don't know
Hey maybe it'll support webcams on 360
Then you can play Strip Monopoly
How does that sound?
Good times
Not as much fun as in real life
And if you play Strip Monop-
Monop-
Monopoly you'll just get bored and pissed off at everybody else before anyone's naked
Monopoly is kind of boring after a while
Strip Monopoly would have to have like lab dances
No seriously
Because you know how you win all of your money
But you have to have the option of being able to spend it
On getting someone to get naked
Okay here's how you play Strip Monopoly
Here's my idea for Strip Monopoly
You replace the chance and community chest cards
Like you know
The kind of stuff in there was like lame
Like it was like
You win second place in a beauty contest
Collect ten dollars right
Remember that stuff
You need to replace those with x-rated things
Like
You won second place in a crotchless underpants contest
That's right
Now it's time to show your community chest
Luxury tax
Anyhow
So Monopoly's coming out on all those systems
Do you think other board games to follow
Can we strip risk in our future
Well remember I think they were talking
You know and they were also talking about making movies of these things too
So god I mean
Battleship would be pretty cool I guess
I don't know
Board games have been around forever I mean
So much you can really do that's different
It's been done like fifty times already
Gerardo says in chat
There would be cheap hotels in Strip Monopoly
You know what I would like to see as
You get houses
And then you have a by the hour motel
That you build
Yeah
You know what I would like
Oh that'd be funny Monopoly Red Light District Edition
Or something like that
I would like to see
And this is
I don't think this is Milton Bradley
But I would like to see them do a
Like Xbox Live Arcade version of Heroes Quest
Remember that game was kind of like a halfway between
Like a board game in Dungeons and Dragons
Oh yeah kind of yeah yeah
Or what was that other game
They had another game that was like something with
Volcanoes or something like that
And they had little marbles that you could roll down
And they would
Marble Madness
No it wasn't Marble Madness
I don't know
Marble Madness had things that shot balls
Let's see
What was it
Oh actdeft in chat said
Risk conquer the world without your pants
Hey they were bringing out strip DDR
That made me think of pantsless rage
Alright anyhow
Forget it
Now the chat room is just going to light up with
Strip insert board game here
It's not funny anymore
Although strip ants in your pants is kind of funny
Yeah they dump the ants in your pants
And you strip to get them out
Strip don't wake daddy
Strip hungry hungry hippo
Alright forget it
Rob
What
How about more news
Let's move on and get away from
Such a
Such
Silly
Teehee
Nudity chat
But naked is great
Let's get away from
Teehee nudity chat
And talk about violence
Woohoo
And
You gotta love
A classic violent franchise
Called Splatterhouse
You remember Splatterhouse
Yes it was for
Turbo Graphics 16
Slash PC Engine
Because the main guy
Looked like a rip off of Jason
I know
And that game goes sort of annoying sometimes
Well guess what
On the latest cover
Of EGM
They're talking about
35 different retro revivals
And right there on the cover
Splatterhouse
Sweet
So Splatterhouse apparently
Is going to be coming back
For a new
New wave
On all the next gen consoles
Not a lot else known
About the game at this time
But I suppose when this magazine
Starts floating around out there
We'll know a little bit more about it
Well
It was
The story though
Was fairly unique
From
You know
The whole
The story wasn't a rip off
Of Friday the 13th
Right it talks about
Splatterhouse has an ancient
Mayan mask that is
Strapped onto its corpse or whatever
Yeah
And he has to go save his girlfriend
So
Interesting
He's probably already dead
I wonder if it'll be like
A first person game
Probably not
Because they have the title character
Right here
But
No it's probably gonna be
Another platformer
Well we'll see what happens
More details
Butcher it
Butcher characters in the game
But don't butcher the game itself
We'll see
Speaking of butchered
Not really
For our buddies over in Europe
They've got a date for a
Super Smash Brothers Brawl
And it's going to be
June 27th
Also in addition to that
WiiWare will be out on May 20th
So
Put it in your diary
It's coming
That's what they call it there
So I'm calling it
Oh I see
Oh
I get the image of like you know
A little 12 year old girl
Who keeps her diary under her pillow
With a little hello kitty key
That opens it
We call them planners
Dear Diary
Oh okay
Yes Dear Diary
Today I pwn some noobs on Smash Brothers
I beat the shit out of them with
Princess Peach
I want a pony
The end
Dear Diary
Today I played Strip Clue
It was Miss Scarlet in the billiard room
With my
Never mind
Let's move on
More stories please
I don't know if they would consider that
Concealed weapon
But it was concealed
Let's see here
So there's a company called Shadowbane
What is wrong with this show?
That's working with
Nintendo to make an MMO
And the question is
They didn't really say what the MMO was
They were just calling it a
As yet unnamed
MMO project
But people are starting to think
Hmm
Perhaps are they developing
Animal Crossing for the Wii?
Or is it just going to be another MMO that
You know
Just wait until E3
I mean enough with the speculation
You know what I mean?
You're not going to find out any more details until E3
Obviously
Nintendo runs a very tight run ship
Where everybody's mouths are sealed
And they can't say anything about it
You know no matter who's developing it
So just wait
I think it's inevitable the game is coming eventually
But I think it would be kind of funny if
Nintendo surprised us and didn't announce the game at E3
But kind of came out of left field with something completely different
And which
No think about it
Would you really want an MMO for
Animal Crossing?
Yeah who's to say it's not a completely new IP?
You never know
Mario brother
Oh Super Mario RPG
Or Super Mario MMO RPG
I don't know about that
I don't know how you'd make that work but
Everyone's like plumber class
Or princess class
Princess class you know I'd have to play that
Or Toadstool class
I don't know
Huh maybe you're onto something
Who knows maybe you could do something like that
Copyright patentpending.com
P.S. money
Well I'm sure when the game is to be debuted
Whatever it is the secret project they're working on
One of the places that you're going to be able to see the
Clips and trailers of it first is the Everyone's Nintendo channel
You know that it had come out over in Japan
It is coming out in the US
It is confirmed this new channel is going to come out in the US
But it's just being called simply the Nintendo channel
It will come out at some point within the next month
It's coming out around the same time as WiiWare
Don't know yet if it's going to be the same day
Or if it's kind of like around that period
Here's the other interesting thing
If you play a WiiWare title
For at least an hour
And it has to be something that you actually purchased
From the channel it can't be a demo or anything like that
You will get to review the game
And I guess your reviews are posted on the Nintendo channels
But you have to
I think that's interesting that they make you play it for an hour
Before you can review it
But that's obviously a good thing
So you don't get a lot of crap in there
You know what I mean from people just hyped about the game
This game made my pants hurt!
Exactly
And anyone can read those reviews
Of course this channel is going to be free
And pretty much all the features that you've come to expect
From the Japanese version will show up in this version as well
So it's just a matter of when this is going to show up
But sometime in the next month
So that'll be pretty cool
Sooner rather than later right?
Now everyone's a critic
Nintendo's encouraging it
Well there's something else that
Nintendo themselves is going to be criticized for
What's that?
Well there was a discussion going on with Iwata
That was after they've gone through all their
You know I guess financial meeting
That they go through
Like any big company has
And he's quoted as saying that their
Projection for the year
Is not based on hardware cuts
And they are not going to need them
So translated from corporate to real English
That means
We're still making money so
Forget it we're not going to lower prices
I wouldn't think that they would lower prices anyways
They're having problems keeping enough stock
You know for this
Hardware for portables and consoles
I mean the demand's not going down for any of them
So there's no reason to lower the prices
That'd be stupid
Oh we're sold out of it people just want to buy it
They'll buy it for $700
Let's drop it to $99
Cause we don't like money
Well there's more
So far they've sold 25 million Wii
And they've sold 70 million DS's
The sales are up 73% for the financial year
With 47.7% profit
So that's not bad at all
And there's some other news that came out
They're upping their allocations
Of what they're going to be making each month
For the Wii
From 1.6 million units
Being manufactured to 2.4 million
So hopefully that will ease
You know the retailers paying out there
But I don't think it's enough
But they will conquer the world soon
Soon
Another franchise is hoping
Wait real curious before we hop on to the next story
One thing I was kind of curious about is
What about you know
We knew a couple years ago that inevitably
The Wii's were going to come out in all these different colors
Cause remember we saw the little you know prototypes
For the you know the pink Wii and the blue Wii
And what have you
Even though you know they're not going to lower the price of the Wii
Are they ever going to come out with these different modifications
Or is that something else they want to pull
Wait to pull out of the hat
I think they're going to
That's something that you want to bring out
When the demand starts to drop
Because people are like
You know it gives them another reason to buy the console
I don't think that right now
Until the demand starts dipping down a little bit
Until they start you know flattening out the demand
Versus what they've got in stock
I don't think you're going to see any of these new colors
Or price drops
Or any sort of like bundles or whatever
Cause they don't
They don't need to entice people to buy them
Cause people are already clamoring to buy these things
So
Yeah it'll be a while
Well one franchise that's making a return pretty soon
Which is pretty cool actually
Is Earthworm Jim
They're actually relaunching the franchise
They're going to be doing a brand new cartoon series
As well as some new video games
That are going to be coming to
Platforms all over the place
Including hopefully
PlayStation 2, 3
And Xbox 360 and Wii
And no word yet on
You know when this is all going to happen
But
Hopefully very soon
So we'll see some more of Earthworm Jim
Probably this year maybe
Hmm
Why do you think all of a sudden they want to bring
Bring back this one
I mean
I don't know
Why bring back Bionic Commando
Or Splatterhouse I guess huh
I guess retro is all the rage
So why not bring back Earthworm Jim
I know that game always used to crack me up
Simply for the fact that when you turned it on
Like remember the title screen
It was somebody burping the name Earthworm Jim
And it wasn't a bad game either
It was kind of cute for a Super Nintendo game
That's the system I had it on was Super Nintendo
Was that one of the games that Tommy Tallarico scored
Two of the games he's kind of famous for
Good times
Well if you have never heard of Earthworm Jim
And you've never played it
Guess what you're going to have the chance
The game is coming to the Virtual Console
Earthworm Jim and Earthworm Jim 2
Are going to be somewhat soon
There's no date yet
Going to be coming to the download service
But it's the Sega Genesis version of the game
Not the Super Nintendo version I grew up on
But the Sega Genesis version of the game
Which you know close enough
Is going to be coming to the Virtual Console
By the way just FYI
Clay Fighter and Boogerman
Are also on their way out
Both also the Genesis versions of the games
Clay Fighter is fucking awesome
Clay Fighter is pretty rad
Although it's one of those games
I don't know for me like you play it for an hour
And then the joke's old
You know what I mean
It's all about Helga with her opera attack
What about Frosty
Bad Mr. Frosty
I used to always play as the blob
That was my favorite
Awesome
Bad Mr. Frosty was great
Rama says the Genesis version has an extra level doesn't it
Not sure
Well all those games are on their way out
So soon we don't have a date
But usually when these games are announced
There's less than a month to go
So there you go
Act Deft in Chat real quick says
Tigerclaw Tommy Tallarico is working on the new Earthworm gym
Or so I heard
Rumor alert
Who are you
Well
You know especially for those of us who are
Artists who probably found this really hilarious
But you know the deal with
The Okami we cover with the IGN watermark
Oh yes the hilarity that ensued last week yes
Which is really funny because
I don't see why they bother watermarking it in the first place
When it's actually Capcom's art
So it's sort of like
Oh we're gonna put our name on it
It's ours now
No
Anyway
Because of this clusterfuck of craptitude
Capcom has released two new covers
That you can go on their website and
What
No I'm laughing because I think this is just a stupid idea sorry
I just want the covers to begin with because they're pretty
But if you go to capcom.com
Slash art redemption all one word
You can pick one of two covers
You can actually either get the original or two
Special versions that they have
One of them is a completely painted
Green background with the wolf
And a neat looking other side on the back
And the other which I personally like
It looks like some level artwork with the wolf superimposed in the front
You know where the front cover would be
And cherry blossoms
And I like that one better myself
I can't stop laughing because the site was called what
Art redemption
Redemption
Redemption for who
And I'm wondering if you don't actually have the game
If you can just get one
You never know it might make a cute little mini poster
You can
That's kinda cool
Oh I think you can
But I mean it's just funny I think the thing is silly
Because honestly how many people are gonna do that
When there's the more hilarity of
I'm doing it right now
OMG I have the uber rare watermark cover
I don't know
Or even better you just get one of those and you're like
Oh hey look there's a game spot watermark on there now
You never know
But hey free game covers
And Jamie's ordering one right now even though she doesn't have the game
Oh VS Jason SV says they don't ask for a serial number
So yes you can do it
They don't and I'm ordering one right now
Nice
Can you order two? Can you get one for the studio?
No let's you pick one
I'll have to go order one too
I'm getting the pretty one
Alright
The one with the cherry blossoms
I'll get the ugly one then for the studio
But I'm gonna let my friend know who really loves this game too
Very cool
So there's some pretty cool mods that are out there right now for Unreal Tournament 3
Although this one seems to kind of take the cake right now
Super Mario Brothers
They made a Super Mario Brothers Unreal Tournament 3 mod
And what it is basically is it's kind of like a 2D version of Unreal Tournament
But with like Super Mario Brother themed levels
So you can run around kind of like I don't know
Super Smash Unreal Tournament
Or something like that
But it is available to download off of the Epic Mega Games forums
So check out epicgames.com
Check their forums and you'll find a link to
UT2D Super Mario Beta
For the PC and Playstation 3
So that's kind of cool
I hope more games support mods and we see more things like this
So and these are things I can download on the Playstation 3?
Yeah
That's kind of neat
So what are the PC mods for Unreal Tournament 3 for the Playstation 3?
There's a great niche for the Playstation 3 right there
I kind of hope they explore more things like that with the customizations and more games
Yeah
You know I know we talked about that when this whole game first came out
But to actually see kind of the you know
Metamorphosis of that is pretty cool
And this is only scratching the surface
I mean think of all the games out there
Like using the Unreal Engine that they did total conversions for
Made a completely different game out of the whole thing
I mean you're going to see some of these come out
And then you're going to actually be able to play these on your Playstation 3
So Unreal Tournament will essentially become like
All these different games
Which is pretty awesome and definitely worth replay value
So
Hmm
Very cool
DJ Genai said I played that over at my friend's house
Good God
Alright let's do one more story here
And then we're going to get into some release dates
But this could affect a lot of different releases coming out soon
The Wii end user license agreement was recently updated
You know all that legal blah blah blah
That usually you don't even read and you just bother to click accept
You know just kind of go through it
I don't know Jamie do you read every word
On those end user license agreements
Huh
You know those things you have to click accept too
All the legal blah blah blah
I know what you mean and my reply was huh
Yeah exactly
Alright
Well the Wii just recently updated theirs
And the interesting thing about it
I mean I could read this whole thing but
You know basically the part you want to know is
Is that the Wii console and the Wii network service
Are not designed for use with any unauthorized device
Or any non-license accessory
You may not use any such device in connection with your Wii console
Or Wii network service
If you do it it's illegal avoids the warranty blah blah blah
So it's interesting that they updated this to specifically target
Unlicensed accessories
Do you think that has to do with the recent surgeons
Of all these fake Mario Kart wheel things we've seen
I don't think it has anything to do with that
I think if anything it has something to do with the Wii freeloader
Okay because I was going to say
I mean I think accessories
Peripherals it doesn't matter
Wacko tapes their Wii controller too
Exactly it's not going to hurt nothing
I see so things like the freeloader
They're trying to go after
Well that makes more sense
Hmm
I wonder if there's other types of like
Controllers out there that help you cheat at games or something
I don't know
Well not in the Wii
On the 360 they've got
Like I was telling you before the show
There's those head in the game controllers
Where they've made custom modifications
That add buttons to the bottom
They're remapping buttons and stuff like that
I need an NES advantage update
Let my NES advantage work with the Wii?
You know what
They should come out with an NES advantage controller
You know what I mean there were the official items
That had turbo buttons and crap
And even NEC got it right
With the turbo graphics and PC engine
That it had a turbo switch on there
That you could put it up to three
So I don't see what the big deal is
With cheats or anything
Remember on the NES advantage
I think it was that one
They had a slow button too
That was just the start button being hit really quick
You know what was great about that?
What?
Shooting games
Like a life force
Unless every time you hit pause
It goes doo doo doo doo doo
And then pauses or whatever
And then so if you get that
Like it doesn't work
It's horrible
You just hear that noise over and over
It worked great on like ice hockey though
That's what I remember
I still have an NES advantage out here somewhere
I know we used them in one of our photo shoots
That we did
I have one
It was fun
I also have a robot
Rob the robot
Alright well let's get to some release dates
Let's start over in the UK, shall we?
Okay
Stuff is coming out
Really only two games
On the 29th they get Grand Theft Auto 4
Yippie
And on the 2nd of May
Dream Pinball
Which I'm actually more excited about than Grand Theft Auto 4
And just a few other things
That are going to be coming out in the month of
That's pretty good is the
Pool Party
No I'm kidding
It's been listed rock band
Heading out, Death Junior
The Iron Man game
And Apollo Justice
So you have that to look forward to coming up in May
For the US
We're getting Baseball Mogul 2009 on the PC
Toy Shop on the DS
Let's Yoga on the DS
Let's Pilates on the DS
Let's not
Brain Voyage on the DS
Great Wars Nations
The Spartans on PC
And then let's see
SNK Arcade Classics Volume 1
On PSP and PlayStation 2
Then we've got Iron Man coming out on Friday
On PlayStation 2, PlayStation 3, Xbox 360
Wii, PSP, and DS
And then a couple smaller games here
Today we had Mario Kart Wii
And on Tuesday
We have Grand Theft Auto 4
But I'm sure no one's really going to be paying attention to that
And that's PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360
But what the hell is Grand Theft Auto 4?
Seriously, I haven't heard of that game ever
Never heard of it
Grand Theft Auto 4 is also coming out in Asia
That's a general release
I usually do Japanese release dates
But also some general Asia release dates
That are a much broader region
However, I am most confident that it's not any type of localized version
It's pretty much just a version of the game
From the same one the US and the rest of the world is getting
I don't know if Japan is scheduled to get a translated version of the game
They got one for the other Grand Theft Auto games, didn't they?
I think so
Maybe in the future
But they got them way late
Yeah, they got them way later
Just like, hey, same reason we have to wait forever for JRPGs to come out over here
Same kind of logic, just in reverse
So honestly, there is not a whole lot coming out
Because of the whole Grand Theft Auto thing
Even though it's not coming out in Japan
I don't get that
But there is, on the Nintendo Wii coming out in Japan
ProYaku Family Stadium is coming out
That's baseball
This is interesting
Link's crossbow training
I didn't realize we got it way before Japan
But it is just now making its way to Japan on May 1st
The Wii Zapper and Link's crossbow training
Yeah, they aren't missing much
Whenever you see the ProYaku, that's baseball
Baseball, well, who doesn't love...
Excuse me
Excuse me, ah
I'm dying
I get stuff
Live radio, Jesus
Nintendo DS, May 1st
A bunch of stuff comes out
Most of it is just peripherals
For instance, you can get a new shiny pouch
And a touch pen
In all these different colors
However, there are some games coming out as well
Emblem of Gundam is coming out
Katekyo Hitman Reborn, Fate of Heat
Comes out on the Nintendo DS as well
As Anpanman to Asobo ABC Kyoshitsu
Anpanman
Anpanman is great
He looks like bread
Well, he gets his own DS game very soon
And on the Sony PSP
Nippon no Asoko-de
I don't know if that's some type of like
Japanese traveler game
It's coming out from Sony themselves
What?
It means...
Well, Nippon's Japan
No Asoko-de
Yeah, that sounds like it would be traveling
Because it means go over there
Yeah, it looks like it's like a
It shows you
I don't know, it looks like SimCity
But it actually is showing you
Actual parts of Japan
That's weird
This one screenshot I'm looking at
Has like all these like power structures
And things
So I don't know if there's a game in here
But it definitely looks like it's using
Real roads and things
So
It looks like it could be interesting
Rob
But probably not for us
That's probably not something you want to import
I'm gonna show you what Anpanman looks like
Alright, you do that
Post me a link in chat or something
Oh
Oh, that's cute
I'm gonna link it in the chatroom
Because Anpanman's adorable
Enough cuteness, more gaming news
I want Anpanman
I wonder if they have any
Actually, Warrior Bob
Was over in Japan
Recently
And he like IMed me
So I told him I wanted an Anpanman plushie
Really?
Yeah
He asked what
Cotton game it was I was looking for
Oh
It's really cool
I thought it was very nice of him to
Make him come back on the show at some point
Well, speaking of the show
Which I should be paying more attention to
Instead of Anpanman
There's details released about
Bionic Commando's multiplayer
For anyone who is interested
Now that is
Excuse me
Only gonna be for
For a
Offline play
For Bionic Commando re-armed
But there will be
It will be presented in a zoomed out
2D sort of mode
You know
Sort of I guess like the
Playing, you know, a lot of people in
Smash Brothers is done I guess
You have Deathmatch, Last Man Standing
But
They say the defining
Object is gonna be your Bionic Arms
You'll have
You'll be able to block projectiles
Grab power-ups
You'll have
You'll have that as your only weapon
And
And then
They're also saying
Is that they've
Made this 150 megabytes
Also for this size
So
It's gonna have some stuff
It will be Live Arcade
PlayStation Network
And PC in May
Oh yeah and there's one other mode
That you have to go around without touching the floor
Hmm
I'm kind of excited to check out the new Bionic Commando game
It's gonna be good times
I should call that mode where you don't touch the floor like
Hot Lava mode
Remember playing Hot Lava in like
Kindergarten or like
Elementary school?
No
The hell's this?
It's basically you play on like playground equipment
And the ground is lava
You have one
It's like tag
But one person is like the lava monster or whatever
And they have to stay on the ground
Where everyone else is up on stuff
And you have to try to tag them and stuff
Interesting
You're really not up on elementary school
Recess games
You know what after the show let's go play Hot Lava
I know an elementary school here
Now
That would be a funny commercial for our show
Well anyways
We had better games than that
What happens when you take the video games away from the video gamers?
We took it a step further
When we used to have a game of tag
That would involve a hula hoop
And we'd throw it at each other
Because playing like
A game like Hot Lava or whatever
With a very large piece of playground equipment
You can't obviously reach up like
12 feet above you
But you can throw a hula hoop at someone's head
12 feet above you so
That was fun
We used to make up this game
That we would play because we didn't have recess
We just had an extended play period
Where we would take the hula hoops
And throw them and try to capture people
But then we would also try to like
Drag them off and tie them to the
Tither ball thing
It's like a twisted version of Pokemon
Okay apparently like everybody
Knows Hot Lava in chat
You know what I think there was
A game we played that was just like that
Except it was Sharks
I think it was Sharks or something like that
Where everything was Sharks
I want to say there was a Type A
I remember a tag game that you played on playground equipment
But it was like Sharks I think
Wait real quick I gotta say this
You know we all love those playground games
From when we were kids
I remember smear the queer did you guys play that?
No I remember a bunch of us got busted
What? A bunch of us got busted for playing that one day
It was something you played with the football
And you know whoever
Like had the football was the queer
And he had to run around
This is horrible I know
You know the way things turned out
You know
I don't wish to get smeared on a daily basis
Anymore but you know that's just
I think that's why we got in trouble for playing it
We used to play soccer ball
We would try to grab that person
And grab the ball away from him
We would put a tennis ball in a sock
And throw it at people
I'm not joking
That reminds me of that scene
In what the hell was that movie
By Kubrick the war movie
Full Metal Jacket
Where they all put the soap in the sock
And start beating the guy with it
Well the whole point of this is that
It's sort of like crazy dodge ball
If you get hit with the sock ball
Who gets to throw the sock ball
It's pretty funny
Anyways back on topic
I want to say
We never are on topic on this show dammit
They need to compile a bunch of playground
Games into a game
I think it's been done before but not very well
I want to say they need all these classes
But they need it on Xbox Live Arcade
And something like
Where everybody is competing
To be the king of the school yard
Who wouldn't play that game
I think it would be fun
They should actually do a Simon says one
That uses some sort of motion sensor
Or the wiimote
So it can tell where you're holding the wiimote
It might be fun
That would be great
Hold on
I gotta get chat comments
Rama says the game I was talking about
He says Sky that's called a blanket party
And now a highly illegal thing to do in the military
A blanket party
Hey guys let's play beach blanket bingo
Wee
So Bionic Commando
It's not coming to Virtual Console
Anytime soon
Because Nintendo doesn't want it to
And that's of course coming from
Capcom's vice president
Of strategic planning Christian
Svensson
Who basically says that it couldn't happen
It is up to
Nintendo to allow it to happen
Apparently
The thoughts are maybe they didn't like the fact that
Hitler's head explodes in the game
Or the fact that I don't know Hitler's
In the game at all
He's Mr. D
We need a fucking new
Castle Wolfenstein to come to
Xbox Live Arcade
And that would be the shit with multiplayer
Why don't they just rename him to
Smitler
I know he has another name
He was Master D
And Bionic Commando
It was Hitler
But he looked like Hitler
You know how there's some cats that look like Hitler
And there's a whole website dedicated to that
This guy looked like Hitler
Well he was in the Japanese one
Anyhow
Something that will be coming to the Nintendo Wii
If rumors are to be believed
Anyway this is a rumor
It was a tip that was sent in
To go Nintendo that Metroid Prime
Is being remade
For the Nintendo Wii
Metroid Prime 3 was already on the Nintendo Wii
But the rumor is that 1 and 2
Are being remade with all
New controls and they will all be packaged
Into one comprehensive
Metroid Prime game
Like an ultimate box set
If you will for the Nintendo Wii
Thoughts?
Yeah GameCube port getting some stuck on
Waggle controls
That sounds like the Wii
I know it just sounds like a cheap
Play for more money
That would buy it
Metroid Prime 2 the search for more money
I was just thinking that
I wonder if they would go back and add stuff to Metroid Prime 3
To kind of attract people that might already have it
Did they do that with Resident Evil 4?
How about online?
What?
Did they do it with Resident Evil 4?
Game to the Wii?
No they didn't give it online play or anything
They didn't add anything to it
That's right because they don't add anything to ports
You know what would be good Rob?
Is Metroid redone in the style of Metroid Prime?
No
Don't touch Super Metroid
Super Metroid is a god among men
I'm saying it not be
Of course the same game
But I would like to see what some of those levels
Will look like from a different perspective
Because I want the music
And everything
The only redeeming thing they could do ever
To Super Metroid is they could do it like they're doing
With Bionic Commando
And basically just
HD version of the 2D game
Yes please
That's one of my dream games
Not an official OLR dream game
Because this is not an original concept
But I would like to see
Super Metroid given the Bionic Commando
Rearmed thing and then made like
Four times as big a new game
That is like four times as big the world
It could go from planet to planet
They could do that with the Wii
If you're pushing just 2D graphics
Or whatever you can go pretty
Realistic with that stuff
I mean just do it like
Symphony of the Night or something like that
Just 2D, why do you have to do everything 3D
Everything does not have to be 3D
Rob, we need an OLR Troid
Yeah but it's not an original idea
Neither was Symphony of the Night
Unless
Unless they replace Samus with a cat
Then it's an original idea
A cat with a laser
Exactly
That would be actually, I'd play it
It should have different laser upgrades as you go through
Are you suggesting Symphony of the Laser Cat?
It wouldn't be a Symphony
It'd be more like
Orchestra of the Laser Cat?
No, cats yowl
It'd be, it wouldn't be
Operetta of the Laser Cat?
It would be
Laser Cat Operetta
Okay, it would be
Screeching matchable laser cats
Chorus, that's it, chorus
Some comments from chat
Sephiroth1215 says
Metroid Prime 1 felt a lot like Super Metroid
Okay, I disagree with that comment 100%
Because like, when I played Metroid Prime 1
For the first time
I seriously, I was like, what the fuck did they do to Metroid
And I threw the controller, like I did not like
Metroid Prime at all when I first played it
Now granted, I own Metroid Prime 3 now and it's grown
On me, the series, but like, I was so
Mad that they raped Metroid by making it a
First player game, because I was not so
Warm and friendly on the whole first person
Conversion, but when I really stepped away
And just kind of looked at it as a new series, a new game
I was more comfortable with it
But I agree, they need to bring back 2D Metroids
So J-Rod says
They need to go remake and import Eternal
Darkness, nevermind this Metroid
Nonsense, to which Sairan
Follows up with, somebody take over
Eternal Darkness is a good idea and give more games
Insanity gauges
You know, well you remember what game
It was that I really liked at E3 a few years ago
Was that Call of Cthulhu game
Where you're, what you
Used to heal yourself was morphine
And it could actually end up
Killing you anyway
Because you would end up addicted to morphine
And then you actually couldn't
Do part of the game unless you let yourself go crazy
Drug abuse the game
Nice
Some more stuff, how's that
Anyhow, so the Metroid Prime trilogy
May be on its way to Wii
But we would rather Nintendo
Just put the resources into giving us a new 2D Metroid
Of Uberness on the Wii, but we'll see
Well I'm very mad at Nintendo right now
Pissed off
Not up to F you pissed offness
But Club Nintendo
This elusive thing
This, you know
Wonderful
Organization is
Out in
Australia, not in America
For everyone
Who got their copy
Of
What game was it
It was for
Mario Kart
There was an invitation
In there with a code on it
That you could use
To use that code and get
Nintendo star points
The site is not active yet
But you can
Get started on your
Saving up I guess
Hmm
Alright
Give it Nintendo
Nintendo just needs to give it to us in America already
Stop being hoarse
I don't really know a nicer way to say it
Stop being hoarse, that's awesome
So
Earlier this week
It's not surprising because
With a big game like Grand Theft Auto 4
Obviously people are
Going to get early and leak it to the internet
As they did, but to commemorate
Such leakage
The notorious
BitTorrent site, the Pirate Bay
Is now calling themselves
Liberty Bay with you know
Niko Bellic
Of Grand Theft Auto 4
On the front page there
So that's kind of funny I guess
I love Pirate Bay so much
Wait a minute, should you be admitting that
On this program? Yes, because
I'll tell you why I love the Pirate Bay
They
Because of where their servers are located
It's not illegal
For them to have
And distribute
Their content
The torrent files Wait a minute, that's where you get your
Doctor Who fix isn't it?
Hmm
Okay, okay
Enough said
But what's funny is that all of these
Different facilities will send them letters
Of complaint and you cease and desist
And so they publish them on their front page
And make fun of them
And point out
What they're doing is
Legal in the country they're operating
From
And somewhere out there right now
Ross Steele UT is throwing something at his radio
No one has been able to shut them down
Alright
Well
But just because it's out there doesn't make it right
But it makes it awesome
And they're hilarious
And you know downloading import
TV shows is nothing
I mean I don't think that should be a big deal
Honestly
You know, if they've aired and they're gone
And you want to get them, why not?
Anyhow, especially if they're never going to air over here
You know, I think somebody ought to upload
A torrent of all this
All the old episodes of this
Or actually, they don't need to
Because all these episodes are online now
This show is fucking bad ass
I remember this show growing up
It was a show, it was hosted by this guy
I think his name was Jeff something
And he had these, I don't know, it's been a long time
Jeff, crap in the head
He had these like totally 80's
Contestants would come on the show
And they would play actual arcade games
For prizes
Now a lot of you guys remember this show
Because it was one of the first shows on G4
Back when they were actually about games
They used to show reruns of this old show
Back when this game was actually on TV
I loved watching Starrcade on G4
And then they got rid of it
It used to be on Fox 40
Look, it used to be on Fox 40
At like 10am on Saturdays
I remember when this game was
Or when this show was new
But if you want to check this out
And look at old episodes of the show
Starrcade.tv, they've posted like 15 episodes
Of the show if you want to view it
And remember the prize
Which was the big thing about it
Starrcade machine
And who didn't want that when they were a kid
Dude, I'm going to email these people
I'm going to email these people and see if we can get them on the show
You know what would be great though
Is if they were doing it
I know this was before them
But giving away the SNK machines
With the multi-card
Dan and I still want one of those
I want to get them on the show
Because you know I've got to ask that question
Will this show ever come back
Will it blend
I know, well you don't have the rights to it
You'd have to make up a new video game show
Whatever, I'd buy the rights to it
I mean really, what are they going to do, sit on the rights
It'd be called OL Arcade
No
Patent pending
Before we get to the classic game of the week
Xenocore in chat wanted to clarify something
About the whole like you know I said the import TV shows
On torrents
Xenocore says, Rob if nobody in the US had
Distribution rights for a show, it's not illegal
To share it online here, hence why
Fan subs of anime are still around
Since most fan subs stop their work
When the rights are acquired, they are pretty much
Left alone, interesting
It's done out of respect
And if anything, and this also goes back
To the argument of music and stuff
If anything those fan subs probably drive up
Interest in the actual
Anime title, then when it comes
Over here, it would probably fare a lot better
Than say, if it wasn't fan sub
Dark Tetsuya and
ActDeft in chat almost at the same time
Go OL Arcade
Instead of Starrcade
Well, definitely go
Check out some old episodes of that show and
Relive the past, because they did some great games
On there, good times, especially if
You're like under the age of 18
So you probably weren't even alive when the show
Was first on the air, you gotta go check out
Some old episodes, which you were missing
There was a time a few years ago that I had actually
Seriously considered bringing this back
As a part of our station
But, a little
Different to not get sued
There was just that one show and I can't remember
What it was
But it was, um
You'd have like a partner team
And they'd go through this trivia business
And then they'd get to run through
With these velcro jackets
Oh, I was just reading about
That show on wiki the other day
I was just reading about it, somebody in chat will say it
It's not Nick Arcade, it's something else
This predates Nick Arcade
Somebody in chat will say it
But I used to watch
That show
All the freaking time, and I so wanted
To be on it
Video Power
Credit to Rama
And there was
Also GameProTV
Do you know that GameProTV was filmed right here
In Sacramento? Was it? Yes
I want to
I want to say I read something
That they used the Sacramento studios
That it was actually produced by the folks
With the NBC station around here
Well, I, um
I liked that one because that was
The show that
First introduced me to a concept
That they never really did anything with
That I thought was great
And I would love to see games actually do this crap
And that was the save card for the Neo Geo
Where you could play in the arcade
Save your data on the card
And go play it on your Neo Geo system at home
If you had the game
You could kind of
I mean to do that with like F-Zero
Type things, you remember that? Yeah
I know, it's a little shady, but
But I think that bringing back that sort of
Format for a game would encourage people
To purchase the
Home version too
If anything, it would drive sales, I would hope
You know what, I'm going to take back what I said earlier
By GameProTV, because it says on IMDB
They filmed it in Los Angeles, maybe it was just that
They did a couple one-off shows, but I want to
I swear I read something, or maybe I'm getting it
Mixed up with another popular gaming show around the time
So, my bad
Alright, well, we're awfully reminiscent
About classics right now
What a perfect time for us to bring in
Dark Sakura's classic game of the week
It's a chance for us to pay
Respect to our elders a little bit
The elder games, that is
Dark Sakura's going to sift through her massive archive
And pick a game to share with us tonight
Dark Sakura, what have you picked
For the masses tonight? I have picked
Rival Schools, United by Fate
And I want to play the intro music
Wait, you want to play the intro music
Or you want to play the... No, I want to
Play some of the intro music for everybody
Because this has the best intro
Okay, well, give me a minute, because I got to pull up the intro
Tell them a little bit about the game, then we'll have the intro music
Well, it's a fighting game, and it's put out by Capcom
And I love this game so much
And the name in Japan was
Ishiritsu Justice Gakuen
Which means Private Justice High School
And you have
Different students that go to different schools
Hold on, intro music
Let's talk a little more about this game
Oh, well, the other music I picked is my favorite level music
The version of this that we had in rotation for a little while
Was the one I ripped off of my Playstation disc back in the day
So
It was
Basically
It was a 3D fighter
And you had a partner
But there were actually several students that would go out to the same school
Well
It was basically, there were students
Going missing from the different schools
And the students would get together
And try to find the people who had gone missing
And in the arcade there were
Less characters
That actually brought in
Two of the
Actually one of them was
One of the characters that had been missing
And the other one was one of the teachers
But they brought those into the home version as well
But the game also had Sakura in it
As a
Sort of hidden slash helper character
Who went to a different school
But was friends with some of the other
Students
So it was pretty cool
You would also have
Each person would have their own special attack
But you could save up
Your energy
And do a team attack
Where they would work together
There were some of them who had buff attacks
Where the cheerleader
Oh god
She's so annoying
But she'd come up and cheer people on
Five power bars
Filled up, something like that
Or Hinata would come out
And you know
Grab your hands and go, you can do it, you can do it
And you'd get back some of your life
Stuff like that
Or other people would just have attacks
It was very very cool
Very bizarre
It's definitely
It was very popular
But I still sort of think it's more one of the niche fighters
In my opinion
There were also
Different counter moves that you could do
You know
In some cases you could block
Some certain special moves
In a certain way
You'd actually have attack cancels
Where you could
If you timed your hit just the right way
You could cancel out the other person's attack
And then both of them would cancel out
But if you are already taking some damage
It wouldn't decrease any of it
In Japan
It came out with an extra disc
That was called
Nekketsu Seishuniki
Which had a bunch of minigames on it
And we got the minigame disc
Except for the biggest notable difference
About it was removing the dating sim mode
The dating sim mode
Nice
Was actually where you were a student
And you went through a full year of school
And you made friends with the characters
And you did all this other stuff
And then
Based on who you made better friends with
Determined what moves you would get
So um
When your school year was over
You could play your character
In versus mode
And the moves were like I said
They're based on who you were better buddies with
And um
That was taken out although I did
And I spent 90 bucks on this thing
Because I wanted it so much
They released
A version 2 that had
The Nekketsu Seishuniki mode 2
That had a more in depth dating mode
And had a DDR sort of minigame in it
Sort of
It was like a dance off mode in the middle of high school
It was so crazy
But um
I also remembered that
The funniest thing about me playing through this
Because I knew less Japanese then
Than I know now
Was one of the characters asking me
When your birthday was and then when you came to your birthday
We would bring you presents
Nice
It was cool, it was really cool
And there was an actual sequel
Which was Moru Justice Gakuen
Which we got as
Rival schools too
Pretty much
They had
They actually had a customized character mode
But it was a board game
It was actually pretty funny
And you had bitch fight mode
Is what I call it where you do the little slappy hand fight
But the characters in the game
There was Batsu, Hinata, Kyousuke, Hayato
Ron
Her attacks were using a camera
There was Shoma who used a baseball bat
Natsu who was a volleyball player
Roberto who was a soccer player
Nagare who was a swimmer
All of his attacks were so stupid
He wore a speedo and goggles to attack
It was just so many good characters in the game
It's one of my favorites ever
Yes
I was really good at it
Although my favorite character is the second one
Who is that?
That would be this girl
Who kicks a whole bunch of ass
I don't know why I just
Picked that over me
Oh, Zaki
She wears a really long version
Of the school uniform
Wears a mask and fights with a chain
She's really fun