[SPEAKER_18]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and released to our podcast stream twice weekly To listen to the first half of this episode visit www.orangeloungeradio.com for links to websites with listings of past episodes Now the conclusion of this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_02]: Welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio on this April 6th of 2008.
[SPEAKER_02]: We are live here on our stream for the last time on Live 365.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is the last piece of live programming.
[SPEAKER_02]: But for you people that download and listen to our podcast every week faithfully, not a darn thing is going to change for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: But we do invite you all to come on and listen to a live show, participate in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_02]: The new place to do it will be www.allgames.com starting on Sunday the 13th.
[SPEAKER_02]: But meanwhile, we still have some of this week's news to take care of, so let's kick off this week's news for Part B with Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it's no surprise, with DualShock 3 being released here any time now, that they're going to be pulling the plug on the 6-axis.
[SPEAKER_05]: Basically throwing motors in those old 6-axis controllers that they have lying around and putting a new shell on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So yeah, if you're looking for a rumble-less controller, you're going to be out of luck.
[SPEAKER_05]: However, though, if you want to get with the times and actually have a controller with that last-gen rumble technology in there, then feel free to head to the store probably now and go pick one up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rostelia T says, That sucks.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like the six-axis.
[SPEAKER_02]: That comment from chat.orangelongeradio.com So...
[SPEAKER_02]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, good thing or bad thing about this?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it just kind of sucks because it's going to cost so much money to replace now.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I guess new console owners won't really care.
[SPEAKER_05]: I kind of anticipated this was going to happen, so I already sold back two of my controllers.
[SPEAKER_05]: And so I just have two more now that I just have to replace.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the thing is, though, now I think you're going to be fucked if you try to trade them in like GameStop or something like that because no one's going to want them.
[SPEAKER_05]: The value has gone down big time on that.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_02]: No future games are going to support them, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, they will.
[SPEAKER_05]: It just won't have Rumble, probably.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Rumble will be disabled.
[SPEAKER_05]: Gotcha.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, that's not the only thing Sony is doing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sony is shutting down the PS2 and PSP gaming servers for some of the online games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some games are no longer going to work after June 30th.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, here's the weird thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: One of the games on the list is Amplitude, but I thought that game already went down.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, some of these games, I think, are already gone.
[SPEAKER_02]: JackX, Lemmings, PS2, MyStreet, Syphon, Filter, OmegaStrain, TwistedMetalBlackOnline, Everybody's Golf, PSP, Lemmings, WorldTourSoccer2
[SPEAKER_02]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: But Twisted Metal Black Online kind of sucks, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's no offline mode for that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, well, those servers are bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wonder if somehow old news didn't leak through as new news this week, and we're getting fooled, too, because I swear that Amplitude thing is like a year old.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it's supposed to happen on June 30th.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: PSP, I've never heard a PSP game shutting their server down, so that element's new for sure, so.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe some wires got crossed, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe it was Frequency that was getting shut down last time.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, Frequency was never online.
[SPEAKER_02]: I miss Amplitude, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was a great game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wish they'd make a sequel.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wish that my computer wasn't being messed up right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are you having problems connecting to the network?
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, there it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: For some reason, what happens is that, and this is just with my crappy laptop, is that I'll have several different Firefox windows open, and then one of them will suddenly vanish.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: Cagney, Davis, Eastwood
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess, so far that just looks like it's alphabetical, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: If there's one called Cagney, there has to be one called Lacey, come on.
[SPEAKER_06]: That'll be when they get to L. Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: So they're saying that these patches are going to be coming out over the year.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, that's good, they're going to keep the game fresh.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's one of those games I played a lot for two days, and I'm just kind of collecting dust right now, which is too bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: I finished Saints Row, so that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Someday, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some other cool stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: This may be cool if you're into Gran Turismo.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or if you have, perhaps, I don't know, a younger sibling that you're trying to get into Gran Turismo.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently, there's a game that they were talking about a while back called Gran Turismo for Boys.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was going to be a kid-friendly game for kids.
[SPEAKER_05]: Grand Turismo 5, The Standalone Game
[SPEAKER_05]: and of course when they were first announcing Gran Turismo 4 Boys it was revealed in November 2004 by Yakumuchi and kind of the way the hook pre-teens on cars I guess kind of like Hot Wheels or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: How exactly do you do that?
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, is it just that the cars are a little more silly, or what?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if it's a little more silly.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe, like, easier to tune, or something like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe they walk them through on how to tune the cars.
[SPEAKER_02]: I need that mode.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't do all that stuff in those games.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's too much... That's why those types of games like Gran Turismo 4s aren't really for me, because there's too much of that car shop stuff that I'm not really into.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, not like Crazy Taxi.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just push the pedal and go, and try to drive into people.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have you seen that new game?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's supposed to be coming out in a couple weeks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh,
[SPEAKER_05]: Emergency Mayhem, Emergency Vehicles
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe you can do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Throw the body into the dumpster.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would throw my passenger in the fire.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: And so they're saying, the team at MadDoc Software is extremely talented.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bringing them within the Rockstar Games family will enhance our core technology and further support our commitment to creating progressive and innovative gaming experiences.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, another merger.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the sound of the corporate suck-up.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the last game they worked on was the Bully Scholarship Edition.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, port.
[SPEAKER_02]: And a broken one at that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gotcha, so it could be that more games are going to get ported.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe that Grand Theft Auto on DS isn't so incorrect.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, I'm down for Grand Theft Auto game on DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you see that rumor about it earlier this week?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's a misprint.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I do too.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, something like that, they couldn't really put Grand Theft Auto 4 on the DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: Unless it was top-down, which would be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, so now we're going to get into another segment here on the program and we like to do this every week.
[SPEAKER_02]: And this segment isn't going away or changing at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: We still continue to ask you guys to email us every week with whatever feedback you have for the program.
[SPEAKER_10]: We do?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, we do.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like it or not.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, and we call it our mailbag.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if you want to send us some emails, mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com is the place to send them.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura dives into the mailbag every week and picks out a few of her favorite emails to read here on the air.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's what you do, because you're going to do it right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or else.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or else you go in that dumpster.
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fire.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, he knows Rob doesn't sing the intro for me anymore.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe on all games I will.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_02]: On the fuck show I will.
[SPEAKER_02]: He didn't sing the mailbag intro, I thought it was very... That was the Let's Ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it was Let's Ask Orange Lounge, which we haven't done in a long time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why don't we?
[SPEAKER_06]: We should do one... For our Skype segment, let it be that.
[SPEAKER_02]: You mean no Skype calls tonight?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, let them call in on Skype, but have it be Ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_02]: But they get to ask a question and that's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: If they do anything else, we hang up on them.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, I love that idea.
[SPEAKER_02]: So tonight's Skype segment is Let's Ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_02]: You call in, ask a question, that's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: You try to deviate the call, we hang up on you.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was wondering what your thoughts are on crappy MMOs, such as RuneScape, or that's pretty much the only crappy MMO I've played.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, it's not that bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just full of grinding, so I guess the true question of mine is, what are your thoughts on RuneScape?
[SPEAKER_06]: I've never played it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also, whenever I see, let's have tea screen name, I always think it says, let's shave tea.
[SPEAKER_06]: But that doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_02]: How would you shave tea?
[SPEAKER_06]: Tea leaves, maybe you shave them with a razor.
[SPEAKER_02]: You and your logic.
[SPEAKER_06]: So keep up the great work, SkyDarkSakura and Loki, and I can't wait for the next podcast.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's from...
[SPEAKER_06]: Someone who didn't put their name on here.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's for person.
[SPEAKER_02]: RuneScape, the only thing about it, I'm looking at some articles about it on Wikipedia.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks a little dated to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've never played it, but it's free, and free is always a good thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, free is not always a good thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess that's true.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was Yaris.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yaris.
[SPEAKER_02]: But this looks better than Yaris.
[SPEAKER_02]: At least you can customize your equipment.
[SPEAKER_02]: The characters look kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently there's 150 different RuneScape servers throughout the world.
[SPEAKER_02]: It started in 2003.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, no, I might have to check it out.
[SPEAKER_02]: It might be fun.
[SPEAKER_20]: It's RuneScape.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck RuneScape.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why fuck RuneScape?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, so you obviously know this game.
[SPEAKER_02]: What do you think of RuneScape?
[SPEAKER_02]: You get what you pay for.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why don't you like it?
[SPEAKER_20]: It's slow, it's clunky, it's a grind fest, and it has one of the worst communities I have ever seen in a game, ever.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it looks like it's set in the universe of Paperboy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Based on that screenshot, it does a little bit, huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: Paperboy the MMO, that's pretty rad.
[SPEAKER_06]: That would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'd play it.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: and then you go to the Crystal Castles and you're done.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: Next email!
Okay!
[SPEAKER_06]: Jeez, Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: Jeez.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like ordering the next email.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think I'm going to do that from now on.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to order the emails.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, watch me shove this ferret up your ass.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ew.
[SPEAKER_06]: This comes from... No, I love the ferret.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wouldn't do that to the ferret.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a new segment.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't think of an introduction to my email except for holy crap.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm a bit scared about what happened to Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hope you feel better and that it wasn't anything too serious.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I feel better.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you want to do something for me, just cross your fingers, cross your toes, pray if that's what you're into or what have you.
[SPEAKER_08]: And sacrifice chickens to your god.
[SPEAKER_02]: Light a candle or something that it doesn't come back and that it goes away.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because honestly, that's the most scary thing about it is that I still have a little bit of those pains and I'm hoping it's just on its way out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't worry, Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: We can help you.
[SPEAKER_05]: We've played plenty of Trauma Center.
[SPEAKER_05]: We know what to do.
[SPEAKER_06]: Remember, video games teach you about real life and shit, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Uh-huh, uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, oh, hey, it's addressed to me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ride and Rock Online 2, Gate of the World private servers are up.
[SPEAKER_06]: The one I play on is euphro2.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's E-U-P-H-R-O-2.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: It runs off Korean beta software, and only basic things are translated, menus and such.
[SPEAKER_06]: The soundtrack is also much better than the first Ragnarok.
[SPEAKER_06]: The game is also completely different from the first as it runs in 3D, and you can change classes whenever you want, as long as your job level is over 5.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the game runs surprisingly a lot like World of Warcraft by interface and battle system.
[SPEAKER_06]: The private server has two servers, a test that's 100-100-100 rate, and a main server, I don't know what rates, assuming it has rates as their RO1 server, 3-3-3.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, that's from SakuraMax, and it says, waiting for something amazing to happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm surprised you're not all over Ragnarok 2 if it's out there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not until I find translated copy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like fully translated.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, I'm going to look into this one tonight actually.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sounds like soon though.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to look into this one because I'm very interested and I've read up a lot on Ragnarok 2 already.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I tried to get into the official beta but I didn't have a Korean social security number.
[SPEAKER_02]: By the way, Cheeseburger sent me a private message commenting on RuneScape.
[SPEAKER_02]: He said, I played and one time someone was following me asking me for sex.
[SPEAKER_01]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_02]: I should be playing this game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sounds like fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, can I continue?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Next email.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, OLR.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have been listening since episode 245, which I don't know which one that is.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just wanted to tell you how rad your podcast, your postcast is, it says.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have laughed so many times listening to you guys, and my ears do burn when you mention anything to do with Australia.
[SPEAKER_06]: Last year, Loki mentioned a mobile game called The Coolest Girl in School, co-created by Champagne for the Ladies.
[SPEAKER_06]: I actually worked next door to Champagne for the Ladies doing freelance game artwork.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki referred to it as GTA for Girls, LOL.
[SPEAKER_06]: Keep up the good work, pixel poison.
[SPEAKER_06]: And this is from Australia.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's someone from Australia, so that's cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm glad we didn't offend all of our Australian listeners when we were... It wasn't a couple weeks ago, we just totally...
[SPEAKER_02]: Somebody asked us what the capital of Australia was.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't remember what the hell happened.
[SPEAKER_06]: You asked me and I didn't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: So whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not Sydney.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember that much.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's all right.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know my world capitals that well.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know Australia, but that's because I'm part Australia.
[SPEAKER_06]: They said that there's a two-year-old on YouTube naming off capitals of countries and all the states in the United States.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: He's going to grow up to be a crack whore.
[SPEAKER_06]: And he's two years old.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are you smarter than a two year old?
[SPEAKER_02]: Probably not.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lord of the Rings-ish Epic
[SPEAKER_02]: But they'd have to put some money and some star power and some writing and all that good stuff and some special effects into it.
[SPEAKER_02]: What do you think, Rice Princess, being the big Zelda fan you are, do you think that they could actually make a movie out of Zelda?
[SPEAKER_08]: Of course they can.
[SPEAKER_08]: They can make a movie out of anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, that's true.
[SPEAKER_08]: They do sometimes, like, not well, but yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, the trailer, like I said, it was okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, for what it was, an April Fool's joke, it was good.
[SPEAKER_08]: For like a real movie, no, I wouldn't watch it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: They should do an animated one.
[SPEAKER_02]: That'd be cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's a crazy idea I've always had.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think the Sci-Fi Network, you know how they sometimes do those random miniseries?
[SPEAKER_02]: Like they did the Wizard of Oz thing not that long ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they're kind of low budget, but they're decent, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Like a Lifetime movie?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I think they should do like a miniseries adapting one of the Final Fantasy games.
[SPEAKER_02]: It sure is boring around here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, Squeenix would never ever let them do it, but I don't know, they should.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because The Spirits Within sure as hell wasn't a Final Fantasy movie.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was a good movie, it just wasn't Final Fantasy.
[SPEAKER_02]: SSJ100 Matt would like to remind us they did make a movie out of Good Burger, so why not a movie for Legend of Zelda?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a good point.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, I'm going to keep going, alright?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Next email.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is from J-Rod.
[SPEAKER_06]: Woohoo!
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: June.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's coming out in June.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll get it if it has a custom mode in it, like a creator wrestler, because it's actually the only fun thing I like about those games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I didn't know this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sagan Chat says, in response to my Sci-Fi Network comment earlier, you do know that Sci-Fi was in plans to make a Myst miniseries.
[SPEAKER_02]: I did not know that, but that would be kind of rad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Missed Online was interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm kind of sad to see it go, but it took a lot of manpower to run that game, I think.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Missed Online was creepy.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was one of the creepiest MMOs I ever played.
[SPEAKER_02]: It made me think, what if Silent Hill was an MMO?
[SPEAKER_02]: It would be like this.
[SPEAKER_06]: That would be beautiful.
[SPEAKER_06]: But then you'd have to take a psychological exam so it could bring up monsters based on things out of your own psyche.
[SPEAKER_02]: RossDLUT would like to point out that Midway's website also lists the game being Summer 08.
[SPEAKER_02]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Can I read the next email?
[SPEAKER_02]: Next email!
[SPEAKER_06]: It's freaking long, but I'm going to read it anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: and this email was sent by DidYouLoseASock.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I didn't.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm wearing both of them.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't either.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're in the house.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not wearing them now.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm barefoot.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm naked.
[SPEAKER_06]: My feet are naked.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Next email.
[SPEAKER_06]: I went to an advanced private screening of the movie Postal by Yui Bull based off of the video game of the same name.
[SPEAKER_06]: Easily one of the worst films I have ever seen.
[SPEAKER_06]: EWI was at the screening and he is actually cool in real life.
[SPEAKER_06]: Before showing the film he talked about the reasons he made it and wanted to make a film that he would like himself and did not care what critics or other people would think about it and that's what he got.
[SPEAKER_06]: He also commented on how the Will Ferrell and Adam Sandler movies are all the same and they keep making them over and over again.
[SPEAKER_06]: and about how the film 10,000 BC critics hated it 9% on Rotten Tomatoes yet it made over 200 million worldwide because the money put into the advertisements for the movie.
[SPEAKER_06]: He also talked about how he is not the only one to do poor adaptations and pointed to the films Elektra and Catwoman.
[SPEAKER_06]: Amen to that.
[SPEAKER_06]: He talked about a few other problems with films in the film industry.
[SPEAKER_06]: All the points he made were really great but his film still sucked in the end.
[SPEAKER_06]: Every religion and race is made fun of in this film.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was like a live-action South Park with crude humor and morals throughout.
[SPEAKER_06]: Would the film have actually been good if everything was replaced with South Park characters?
[SPEAKER_06]: Probably, but then again, I think anything would be really funny if it was replaced by South Park characters.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is this film worth seeing?
[SPEAKER_06]: It was so bad that some might find it good.
[SPEAKER_06]: I might suggest this film over all those stupid spoof movies like Superhero Movie and Meet the Spartans.
[SPEAKER_06]: Iwi Bull in the past has boxed critics
[SPEAKER_06]: who would not like his films.
[SPEAKER_06]: So after the film got over, of course, I did not like it, so I asked him to fake punch me for a photo, which he did and was a good sport about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Where I saw the film was a small private screening room that Ebert and Roper and other media people used to view films.
[SPEAKER_06]: No major reporters were there, only smaller media outlets because of the status of the film.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was an amazing place and better than the film itself.
[SPEAKER_06]: Spoiler warning!
[SPEAKER_06]: Should I?
[SPEAKER_06]: No one's going to see it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, no one's going to see it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to see it, but that's fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Reduce the volume on your iPod for about 15 seconds if you don't want to hear the spoiler.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now.
[SPEAKER_06]: The only slightly funny part in this film where Yui will place himself as a stereotypical German dressed in lederhosen.
[SPEAKER_06]: In the film, he talks about how his films were funded by Nazi gold and then fights the creator of Postal because he was mad at Yui for ruining his game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I give credit to someone who can make fun of themselves, and I think he included the picture.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm trying to pull it up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, we did.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good picture.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a MySpace photo right there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wait, I got punched in the face by UE Bowl.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, you should get that on a shirt.
[SPEAKER_02]: You should actually print that on a shirt and say, I got punched in the face by UE Bowl.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki is Tingle or Uwe Bolle is not in the film industry anymore.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think you have a better chance of getting him to leave the film industry than me to dress up as Tingle.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, snap.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because at least signatures don't cost anything.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_05]: True that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Last email.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, OLR.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm a loyal podcast listener and wanted to tell you how much I like your show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Your show makes me happy and Loki's runs always make me laugh.
[SPEAKER_06]: In fact, you guys make me laugh so much that I've gotten used to awkward stares in public.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for making such a great show and please keep it up.
[SPEAKER_06]: And this is from Able2Think.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's more.
[SPEAKER_06]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, I know how much you love Treasure, so I thought I'd let you know that the bleach fighting game on DS is made by them.
[SPEAKER_06]: P.P.S.
[SPEAKER_06]: An interesting question.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'd like to hear your answers.
[SPEAKER_06]: a woman while at the funeral of her mother met a man who she did not know she thought he was amazing she believed him to be her dream partner so much that she fell in love with him right then and there but never asked for his phone number or address and could not find him after the funeral a few days later she killed her sister so the question what was the woman's motive for killing her sister now think about it why would you think that she would kill her sister I don't know do I care
[SPEAKER_02]: Dr. Phil made her do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry, I wasn't listening.
[SPEAKER_08]: So she can see the guy again?
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Answer.
[SPEAKER_06]: She was hoping the man would appear again at her sister's funeral.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you answer this correctly, you think like a psychopath.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I've heard that thing before.
[SPEAKER_06]: This was a test used by a famous American psychologist to test if someone has the same mentality as a killer.
[SPEAKER_06]: Several incarcerated serial killers took part in the test and all answered the question correctly.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you didn't answer the question correctly, good for you.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you gave the correct answer, please let me know so I can keep an eye on you.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then they're interviewing someone.
[SPEAKER_05]: So what was the motive?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then they stabbed him in the face.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let me tell you about my mother.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ba-dum-bum.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or you could just be good at logical deduction.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, you don't have to think like a psychopath.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can just think it out.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was last email, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, that was the last email.
[SPEAKER_02]: By the way, kids, we have a list list coming up tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Things Live 365 could do to get us to stay.
[SPEAKER_02]: I need everybody in studio to do a list of three things.
[SPEAKER_02]: But there's too many.
[SPEAKER_02]: We only can only do five.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I figured that much.
[SPEAKER_02]: So Irene and Nathan, you guys can combine a list.
[SPEAKER_02]: So think a list of three things.
[SPEAKER_02]: Things Live 365 could do to get us to stay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Does anybody need cards to write things down?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I built cards.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would like a card, Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's a card.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you have a pen or a pencil?
[SPEAKER_02]: You can borrow mine, but you've got to give it to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, we have a pencil.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Never mind, but thank you very much, Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is great radio, by the way.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm trying to fill time.
[SPEAKER_08]: Back to the news, please.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I know I'm super excited this is finally launched, but guess what?
[SPEAKER_05]: Engage is back, bitches.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Engage application has finally launched.
[SPEAKER_05]: and it is compatible with Nokia's N81, N81 8GB, N82, N95, and N95 8GB phones.
[SPEAKER_05]: And there are five games right now currently available for it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Brain Challenge, System Rush Evolution, and World Series of Poker and I guess two other ones.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then all the other games, or all the games I guess offer free trials and then can be purchased straight from a computer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Chirp, chirp, chirp, chirp
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean it is the end gauge.
[SPEAKER_02]: Quick poll.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to do a quick poll and chat right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just want you guys to answer with yes or no.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you care about the N-Gage?
[SPEAKER_02]: Chat room, answer now.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll do this next story.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you care about the N-Gage?
[SPEAKER_08]: That is the whole chat room.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Spoken on behalf of them.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just going to see while I read this next story.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is something people might care about.
[SPEAKER_02]: Saints Row 2 is coming out on August 26th.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are you excited about this, Loki?
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Xbox 360 and PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: This was announced at the THQ Gamers Day, which was in San Francisco earlier this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which we didn't get invited to, those fuckers.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, we never do.
[SPEAKER_02]: There is a Saints Row 2 website now up and running.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's at saintsrow.com, not saintsrow2.com, but saintsrow.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the timing of it is between Grand Theft Auto 4 and Christmas, so it's a pretty good time.
[SPEAKER_02]: So there you have it, Saints Row 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: with Uncle Gary talking about different aspects of the game that are new to Saints Row 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, of course, for those who aren't aware, Uncle Gary is Gary Busey.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: But there are some new things, especially if you've been reading any of the previews on there.
[SPEAKER_05]: There are sticky satchel charges that you can throw on people and detonate them remotely.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then you can actually throw people in this game.
[SPEAKER_05]: And there's different taunts you can do, including...
[SPEAKER_05]: I believe you can teabag someone in this game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lovely.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's the results of our quick poll.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you care about the end gauge?
[SPEAKER_02]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hell no.
[SPEAKER_02]: Vader.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kinda.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: The what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, it's a no.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: BlackWolfClarifies is kinda saying, some of the games I saw for the new N-Gage platform had some neat ideas, so kinda.
[SPEAKER_02]: And lastly, Mayusatsuma says, the only N-Gage I care about was the one from Star Trek The Next Generation.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, God, why?
[SPEAKER_02]: You love that show, Jack.
[SPEAKER_02]: Chat comment of the night, I love it.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's my favorite.
[SPEAKER_02]: You win.
[SPEAKER_02]: So there you have it, the results of the quick poll.
[SPEAKER_10]: I answered the poll too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Live radio is awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: What did you say, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_02]: Padme, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, look.
[SPEAKER_02]: Next story, please, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh yeah, it would help if I actually could find it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, there we go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Gran Turismo PSP.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, some people do.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's actually delayed until 2009.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: It should be noted that it's actually called Duke Nukem Forever's Gran Turismo for the PSP.
[SPEAKER_06]: I call it, you know, you've got prologue, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, it's funny, though, because they were showing this thing off like, I want to see before the PSP came out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wasn't it one of the things that they were saying, hey, yeah, it's going to be so awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I thought they were talking about Ridge Racer, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: Didn't happen.
[SPEAKER_05]: IGN It happens to the best of us.
[SPEAKER_05]: IGN had a few things.
[SPEAKER_05]: First, their story about a game called Skate It coming out for the DS and the Wii.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right, that's a version of the game put out by EA that will be coming to the Nintendo platforms.
[SPEAKER_05]: No word on when exactly it will be coming out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course, the information was very brief, but they did say that they were talking about using, of course, the Wii Remote...
[SPEAKER_05]: And you know what's better than spoiling one game?
[SPEAKER_02]: Spoiling two games because IGN did the same damn thing with an upcoming Batman game.
[SPEAKER_02]: The story was pulled.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was not a lot of details on the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was pretty much, I guess, just a generic kind of blank page that just indicated there was a Batman game coming.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you could probably put two and two together and figure that it was a...
[SPEAKER_02]: Dark Knight Adaptation.
[SPEAKER_02]: And keep in mind, Pandemic is the company that made Destroy All Humans and Mercenaries.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Pandemic was the company that was slated to make this Batman game.
[SPEAKER_02]: So what do you think of that?
[SPEAKER_02]: The folks making Destroy All Humans making Batman.
[SPEAKER_05]: It could be okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Destroy All Humans has kind of been lost its edge since the first game.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's lost its edge.
[SPEAKER_05]: But Mercenaries 2 looks fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: I had a friend that worked on that.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's interesting though, here's what they had, actually someone had copied this from the NeoGAF forums.
[SPEAKER_05]: It said,
[SPEAKER_05]: And now we know it's happening for sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: Elevation Partners, who were owners of Pandemic and Bioware until the EA purchase, had gained the video game rights to the franchise.
[SPEAKER_05]: We rumored last year that EA would publish the title, but now EA owns the aforementioned companies, and the publishing aspect was a given.
[SPEAKER_05]: Unfortunately, we don't have any specific platform, a release date, or even an official title, but given EA's history, we would expect a game to be called The Dark Knight, released this July alongside the film.
[SPEAKER_05]: and to hit just about every platform known to humankind I can tell you right now it's probably not coming out in July I was going to say it seems a bit late but if they are developing something like that it could also come out around the release of the movie on DVD that's what I'm thinking more DVD Blu-ray time
[SPEAKER_05]: E.A.
[SPEAKER_05]: actually did the last Batman game, I think.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: So, it makes sense.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some of the Batman games really kick ass.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, the old school Batman on the NES was one of the best games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, that was fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was one of the best games on the NES.
[SPEAKER_08]: Heck yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Batman Returns was kind of wonky.
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't play it.
[SPEAKER_02]: The first Batman was pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: So.
[SPEAKER_08]: Again.
[SPEAKER_02]: There are good movie adaptation games once in a great, great while.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, list list coming up.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hope you guys have your list soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's coming right up after one more story, which is Jamie's story.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: Samsung is bringing different games out for their smartphones and one of them is Second Life.
[SPEAKER_06]: So basically they're actually showing it the CTIA wireless thing that was going on where you can access it using the smartphones and talk through a text and SMS.
[SPEAKER_06]: So they said that they want to launch it in the second half of this year.
[SPEAKER_02]: All righty.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be interesting, though, if you can have that crack with you.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Furry's Portable is what it is, right, Drew?
[SPEAKER_02]: Furry's Portable.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, here's the deal, guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to play a little game we have been playing since our first couple episodes here on Live365 right on down to the very last episode on Live365.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a segment we call Listless.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tonight's list list, the topic is things Live365 could do to get us to stay.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's been a little while since we've done list lists, it's at least been a few months.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some of our games only show up once every few months.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's the deal, the way it works is that we're going to go around the room and each person is going to name their top three, one at a time, things that Live365 could do to get us to stay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Has everybody done with their list?
[SPEAKER_02]: If anyone is still in need of suggestions, chat room, you can try to influence us now.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you have a good idea for things Life 365 could do to get us to stay, start posting those suggestions in chat now.
[SPEAKER_02]: And maybe a host or a guest will pick up on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But then, after the list is made, so we'll get a big list that has 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 10, 15 things on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then we're going to go around and we each take one thing off the list.
[SPEAKER_02]: We vote something off the list.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's off the island, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: No more.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's off the list, and then the chat room will take that list of then 10 and vote on their favorite, and we will come up with the definitive list!
[SPEAKER_02]: of things Life 365 could do to get us to stay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Participating tonight, DarkSakura, myself, Loki, Drew, and so that we don't have too many people, Bryce Princess and Silent Nathan.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that's going to be his new name, like Silent Bob, Silent Nathan, are going to be combined as one person because they're a couple and you can do that to couples.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh my God, that's so cute.
[SPEAKER_02]: What do you think of that, Silent Nathan?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what I thought.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just giving him a hard time.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's because his girlfriend hogs the mic.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: What do you mean?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't hog the mic.
[SPEAKER_08]: You shut up now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's start off the list.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll start tonight with Drew.
[SPEAKER_02]: What is your number three thing that Live 365 could do to get us to stay?
[SPEAKER_02]: Ferret radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: All ferret, all the time.
[SPEAKER_02]: AllFerret Radio, AllFerret all the time.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if I've ever fucking listened to that, but it might work.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, AllFerret Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rice Princess and Silent Nathan, your number three pick.
[SPEAKER_04]: Provide the studio, via Irene, a unicorn.
[SPEAKER_22]: Provide the studio a unicorn.
[SPEAKER_22]: Via Irene.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, that's the important part of House of Beetle.
[SPEAKER_22]: I like that idea.
[SPEAKER_22]: I think a unicorn would be fun.
[SPEAKER_22]: It would be great.
[SPEAKER_22]: I think that would give me a stay.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'd stay with Life 365 if they gave me a unicorn.
[SPEAKER_08]: And leave like six months later.
[SPEAKER_08]: Once you have the unicorn.
[SPEAKER_22]: Do I have to feed it?
[SPEAKER_22]: I hope they provide food, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm pretty sure unicorns are self-sufficient.
[SPEAKER_08]: Unicorns eat children.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, see?
[SPEAKER_08]: We've got millions of them here.
[SPEAKER_22]: All right.
[SPEAKER_22]: Let's see what happens.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm just curious what Bobby Blackwolf thinks of this whole segment.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm seeing if he suggested anything because, you know, it could change.
[SPEAKER_02]: We may have to pull out of the deal.
[SPEAKER_02]: If Live365 is able to provide a unicorn, we might have to pull out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, let's see what some of the other things are on the list.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, we'll go to you next.
[SPEAKER_02]: Number three, your number three pick.
[SPEAKER_06]: Pay for me to relocate to England.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just you?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, me and the people of my choice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, sorry, I'm slow.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm typing as we do this here, so it takes me a minute.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry, filler.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Irene, sing.
[SPEAKER_02]: When we need a little filler, you're going to sing, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: I can dance, I can sing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, that's why we have the theme music, too, so there's something to listen to.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, your number three pick.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would like Ken Kutaragi's heart on a platter.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kalima!
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry, we can't do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're out of platters.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's sick.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're sick.
[SPEAKER_02]: I bet you got that serial killer question right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ken Kutaragi's heart on a platter.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lawsuit in the air.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sue Live 365.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't sue us.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Obviously, he's joking.
[SPEAKER_08]: Obviously.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I love what the chat room suggests.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to read that later after what we get here.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: My number three thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: The number three thing Live 365 could do to get us to stay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Force Compile to reform and make a sequel to The Guardian Legend.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_06]: Dot com.
[SPEAKER_02]: If Live 365 wants us to stay, they will force compile to get back together and make a sequel to The Guardian Legend.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: At gunpoint, however they have to do it, but that's the only way we're staying.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_02]: The number two way...
[SPEAKER_20]: Make tuner software that doesn't suck.
[SPEAKER_20]: Radio 365, I'm looking at you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why do you think that I was using the SAM2 broadcaster?
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Irene and Silent Nathan, what is the number three, I'm sorry, number two thing that Live365 could do to get us to stay?
[SPEAKER_03]: Blowjobs for everyone.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was my number one answer.
[SPEAKER_02]: My number one was blow me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now I'm going to have to change that, you asshole.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's okay, I'm stealing a great one from chat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, you're number two.
[SPEAKER_06]: My number two?
[SPEAKER_06]: That would be to pay me $100,000 a year to do Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: by me I mean us each and guests get like $5,000 a visit they get royalties
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess that kind of is the same thing as what she said.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is that a reference?
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, here's mine, here's mine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Pay us $200,000 a year to do Orsandria.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was actually my original number three.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm serious.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lovely.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, so we have pay $100,000 a year to do Orsandria, immediately followed by pay $200,000 a year to do Orsandria.
[SPEAKER_02]: Beautiful.
[SPEAKER_02]: Number two thing from my list that Live365 could do to get us to stay...
[SPEAKER_02]: Heal my pancreas.
[SPEAKER_02]: They could do that with a unicorn.
[SPEAKER_06]: We need to play you the Weird Al song over and over and over again until your pancreas go, okay, fine!
[SPEAKER_02]: Heal my pancreas, the number two thing that Light365 could do to get us to stay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, yeah, DarkSakura, heal please.
[SPEAKER_06]: Give Jamie a cookie.
[SPEAKER_02]: How about give Jamie pastrami?
[SPEAKER_06]: I like pastrami better.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, give Jamie a pastrami cookie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rice Princess and Silent Nathan, did you come to a consensus?
[SPEAKER_02]: What is your number one thing that Life is Survived could do to get you to stay?
[SPEAKER_04]: This is a complete consensus between me and Irene.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go back in time and make Rob not retarded so that he'll vote for Chrono Trigger.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: referencing tonight's bonus segment we were talking about OLR March Madness just so the podcast listeners know I cast the deciding vote between Super Metroid and Chrono Trigger so alright I have to shorten that though for the sake of pencil space to put make Rob vote for Chrono Trigger no you don't you can type that all out Rob you leave that intact Mr. Rob hold on you better sing
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, your number one thing on the list.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not a damn thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: They done fucked up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good answer.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that's our winner right there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not a damn thing they've done.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bucked up is DarkSakura's number one answer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, your number one answer.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was going to go with George Foreman Full Cow Grilling Machine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, you mean the PS3?
[SPEAKER_05]: This isn't my choice, and I'm sure this is for the chairman, because I sure as hell wouldn't want to see this happen, but purchase one million copies of The Eye of Judgment.
[SPEAKER_06]: Somebody check this man for a fever.
[SPEAKER_02]: God damn it, that's the one I was going to steal, you ass.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, then put in George Foreign Folk.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, grilling machine.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it's too late.
[SPEAKER_02]: You said purchase one million copies of Eye of Judgment is Loki's number one.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, so if Life is Five purchases one million copies of Eye of Judgment, then we'll stay.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we'll have much LOL with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, my number one.
[SPEAKER_02]: My number one would be the thing that Life is Five could do to get us to stay...
[SPEAKER_02]: Buy us a George Foreman full cow grilling machine There you go
[SPEAKER_02]: If you might remember from the... I think the last time we did this was for the Consumer Electronics Show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Things we most want to see at Consumer Electronics Show.
[SPEAKER_02]: And one of the answers was, buy us a George Foreman... I'm sorry, the answer was, a George Foreman full cow grilling machine that actually grills the entire cow.
[SPEAKER_02]: All Ferret Radio, Provide a Unicorn via Irene, Pay for DarkSakura and the people of her choice to go to England, Ken Kutaragi's Heart on a Platter, Force a sequel to The Guardian Legend, Make tuner software that doesn't suck,
[SPEAKER_02]: Blowjobs for everyone Pay $100,000 a year to do OLR Pay $200,000 a year to do OLR Heal Rob's pancreas Give Jamie a cookie
[SPEAKER_02]: Go back in time and make Rob not retarded and vote for Chrono Trigger.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not a damn thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: They done fucked up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Purchase one million copies of Eye of Judgment and buy us a George Foreman full cow grilling machine.
[SPEAKER_22]: Damn it, this is hard.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is a good list.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought this would be kind of a dumb segment tonight, but we did a good job.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you really have to remove...
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the game, sorry to say.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, we're going to start with the same order.
[SPEAKER_02]: Drew Nami, we'll start with you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which one of these items is not worthy of the list?
[SPEAKER_02]: The $100,000 a year.
[SPEAKER_02]: I knew someone had to do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pay $100,000 a year to do OLR is off the list.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, Rice Princess and Silent Nathan, which of these is not worthy of the list?
[SPEAKER_04]: Pay $200,000 a year.
[SPEAKER_02]: Damn, throw the baby out with a bathwater.
[SPEAKER_20]: Do you not like money or something?
[SPEAKER_20]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: I put it in there that it's paying $5,000 each minute.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nathan's more interested in blowjobs for everyone, alright?
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, who's next?
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, which of these is not worthy of the list?
[SPEAKER_06]: All ferret radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: All ferret radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because we have that anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, which of these is not worthy of the list?
[SPEAKER_05]: I know this is going to sound weird, but blowjobs for everyone, because who knows who's giving those blowjobs?
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, that could be some scary shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, have you ever watched Cat House Girls?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: It could be some scary stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: It could be Air Force Amy.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_02]: My turn, we have Provide a Unicorn, Pay for DarkSakura to go to England, Ken Kudaragi's Heart on a Platter, Force a Sequel of Guardian Legend, Make Tuner Software Doesn't Suck, Heal Rob's Pancreas, Give Jamie a Cookie, Go Back in Time, Make Me Vote for Chrono Trigger, Not a Damn Thing, Purchase 1,000,000 Copies of I, Judgment, and Buy Us George Foreman Full Cow Grilling Machine.
[SPEAKER_02]: The one I deem not worthy of the list, Ken Kudaragi's Heart on a Platter.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because that's kind of sick.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here is the list that you in chat can vote for.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're going to send me, Sky, a private message in chat with your top two in order.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's important because your first pick actually gets two votes, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: Here is the list as it stands.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm about to paste a big thing in chat, so brace yourselves.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_06]: As Rob gets kicked from chat.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I won't get kicked.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, here we go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here is the list as it stands.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hope that doesn't win because that's kind of easy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Make it win, people!
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't even realize that came out this week, but that was one of the days I was in the hospital, so I must have missed it.
[SPEAKER_08]: So do you get all the Mr. Peabody and stuff, too?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, Mr. Peabody, Sherman, they're all in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Really?
[SPEAKER_06]: I have to tell you a bit of trivia, though, about the Data East machine.
[SPEAKER_06]: The picture of the Wayback Machine, right next to it is the DeLorean from Back to the Future on the playfield.
[SPEAKER_02]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to have to check that out.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't realize that had come out.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I do have Pinball FX and I would like some more tables for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'm definitely going to check that out.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'm glad we do this show because I missed a lot of gaming news while I was out.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, let's move on with the gaming news.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've got to start tallying some votes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, that would be my turn, wouldn't it?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, there is talk about a game called Velociraptor Safari coming out to the iPhone.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: As much as I appreciate iPhone gaming, you know, and what they're doing with it, I don't think I would find it in my heart to play Velociraptor Safari.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fuck that shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bring us Jumbo Safari.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you haven't played Velociraptor Safari, then it's fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is it?
[SPEAKER_06]: How fun is it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you get to kill them?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, you have a giant spiky chain.
[SPEAKER_06]: I will kill Velociraptor.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have a spiky chain that you catch the Velociraptor with and you have to pull him through a portal type thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is like Jumbo Safari.
[SPEAKER_06]: with Velociraptors.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's actually a web game, of course, and what they did is made the client compatible with the iPhones.
[SPEAKER_05]: No cost to you, which is awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, maybe I'll have to give it a go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm too busy listening to American Idol on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, there are some new developments now in the world of PS3 piracy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Unfortunately, there is now a PS3 backup launcher.
[SPEAKER_05]: The problem is, though, it's still in alpha, and it only works on PS3 dev stations.
[SPEAKER_05]: But what it allows you to do is boot PS3 games from the hard drive, boot games from a DVD or Blu-ray disc drive,
[SPEAKER_05]: Copy original PS3 games from said optical drive to the hard drive and patch executables on some games to run from the hard drive.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a matter of time, I guess, before this becomes as vulnerable as, say, the PSP, which isn't good.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I can imagine, though, that a lot of people probably wouldn't want to copy a 50 gig game to their hard drive.
[SPEAKER_05]: That would probably suck.
[SPEAKER_05]: So...
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry, I'm in the middle of tallying votes.
[SPEAKER_02]: We had a lot of votes tonight, by the way.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you want to vote, this is your last chance to vote in tonight's listless.
[SPEAKER_02]: Things Live 365 could do to get us to stay.
[SPEAKER_02]: One more story before we get to some last-minute stories.
[SPEAKER_02]: I figured this would be an appropriate story since OLR is always dedicated to giving you the current in gaming news and staying on top of what's going on in the scene.
[SPEAKER_02]: There are new prototypes for the Atari 7800.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can actually download them, the ROMs, you can get them at AtariAge.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a game called Sirius.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a side-scrolling shooter that's kind of like R-Type and Gradius.
[SPEAKER_02]: For the 7800, it's not bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Plutos is a vertically scrolling shooter.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not quite as ambitious as Sirius, according to the poster at LostLevels.org where this is found, but it's still not bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Rampart, which apparently is some type of port of the arcade game that I quite enjoyed Rampart back when... Yeah, remember that game?
[SPEAKER_02]: They ported it to a lot of systems.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently there was a prototype for the 7800 that never quite got off the ground.
[SPEAKER_02]: So there you have it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I actually have a couple 5200 prototypes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actual cartridges or just ROMs?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, the remakes like that that they did.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have a couple of them.
[SPEAKER_02]: I always wanted to pick up one of those flashback consoles.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think they're kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: I might still pick one up.
[SPEAKER_02]: But they don't have Activision games in there, do they?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to get made fun of by Irene for this, but I don't care.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think they have an Activision one.
[SPEAKER_02]: My favorite Atari 2600 game of all time, well, there's two.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pitfall 2 is the first, but the other one is Kaboom.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why would I make fun of you?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because you make fun of me for everything.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ask Orange Lounge Ask Orange Lounge
[SPEAKER_05]: Hooray!
[SPEAKER_05]: Somebody, for some reason, I don't know why, but there's a picture on Xbox 360 Fanboy of a Master Chief My Little Pony that someone made, and it's kind of weird looking.
[SPEAKER_08]: That creeps me out.
[SPEAKER_05]: It gives me nightmares.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's very creepy.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's also some videos on Xbox 360 Fanboy of the new download content for...
[SPEAKER_05]: Burnout Paradise, actually, and that's also available on the developer's website, CriterionGames.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: They have a thing on there for that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's also, this was another one of the April Fool's jokes that was out there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Super PP Brothers, it was from ThinkGeek.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: They did, like, the thing that would, the Wii remote would kind of fit into this, almost like a jockstrap or, like, panty thing that you would put on and
[SPEAKER_05]: GameRadar.com
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, Mario 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then they also have Paper Bowser World, Paper Bowser World, Operation Grom.
[SPEAKER_05]: Those are two full games that are done kind of similar to Super Paper Mario.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then Neo Sonic Universe, which looks kind of cool, kind of a brand new side-scrolling Sonic game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course, the Metroid 2 remake, which now has a playable demo work-in-progress demo
[SPEAKER_05]: and then finally Chrono Resurrection which of course you may remember got cancelled it was the full 3D remake of Chrono Trigger and I think which should be added to the list they have that new Mario game that someone was making that was a mashup of Halo, Mega Man and all that stuff that should probably be added to the list but if you go check out the article which is on Dig right now and it's also on GamesRadar.com they have links to most of the games that you can download of course not Chrono Resurrection because
[SPEAKER_05]: Only the devs get to play that one.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then I got to import this game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Momo World War 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like chicks in, Nazi chicks in bikinis or something done anime style.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sexy Nazi anime girl game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know, that sounds pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, guys, ready to figure out who won tonight's listless segment?
[SPEAKER_06]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, let's reveal the winners tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Things Live3CC5 could do to get us to stay the definitive list.
[SPEAKER_02]: As voted by you, the chatters created by us, the hosts and guests.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here it is, the number three thing that Live3CC5 could do to get us to stay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Provide us a unicorn via Irene.
[SPEAKER_08]: Number three?
[SPEAKER_08]: Unicorns can do anything.
[SPEAKER_08]: That should have been number one.
[SPEAKER_08]: It would have made all the other dreams come true, but I won't mope.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: At number two, we have a tie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Number two, buy us a George Foreman full cow grilling machine is more important than the unicorn.
[SPEAKER_02]: How about a George Foreman unicorn grilling machine?
[SPEAKER_10]: No!
[SPEAKER_02]: and Not A Damn Thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: They done fucked up.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was number two.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was surprised too.
[SPEAKER_02]: But then I looked at what was number one and I wasn't surprised at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: The number one thing that Live 365 could do to get us to stay?
[SPEAKER_02]: Purchase one million copies of The Eye of Judgment.
[SPEAKER_08]: Big surprise.
[SPEAKER_20]: And settle this bet once and for all.
[SPEAKER_20]: You do realize, of course, that Jamie does not get a cookie now.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's okay, I can't have a cookie.
[SPEAKER_20]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, um, let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Heal Rob's pancreas would have been fourth, and then give Jamie a cookie would have been fifth.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't want a cookie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: When I come up here to do this show the day after my birthday, I want banana pudding.
[SPEAKER_02]: Isn't it nice to want... Or carrot cake.
[SPEAKER_06]: Those are my demands.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: This is Rob's...
[SPEAKER_02]: And yes, what would you like to say?
[SPEAKER_10]: I would like to say that I am very sick because my pancreas hurts.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyways, it's Extifer.
[SPEAKER_09]: How's it going?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god, Extifer?
[SPEAKER_02]: Fine, even though you're an asshole.
[SPEAKER_02]: So what's up, Extifer?
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, I'm doing pretty well, and you?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, my pancreas hurts a little bit, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Aw.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_09]: You should stop letting Irene punch you in the pancreas.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to do that, actually.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, that's never going to happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: Extifer, you used to do a show here on our station, our little network here on Live3CC5, and we already canceled your show once, and now we're leaving from Live3CC5 altogether.
[SPEAKER_02]: Does that make you sad?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, actually.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_09]: I was really, you know, sad when I couldn't do the show anymore because I live in another city now and it's hard, you know, for me to get over there to do any type of programming anyway.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, I mean, we kind of ended, I mean, at least with me, it kind of ended a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_09]: But, yeah, it does make me sad that we don't have the opportunity to do it again, I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it kind of sucks.
[SPEAKER_09]: Unless they're...
[SPEAKER_02]: What did you think of tonight's list list, though, with the ways that Live 365 could get us to stay?
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you agree, or is there something else that you would have put on the list?
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, I'm all for the cow and the George Farman grill.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sounds good, huh?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, actually... I'm like, you know, get me a cow, put it on the grill.
[SPEAKER_09]: I am like, you know, meat central.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's all I can think about.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did he just say, I am Meat Central?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think he did.
[SPEAKER_02]: He did.
[SPEAKER_08]: He said, I am Meat Central.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I am Meat Central.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is my connection breaking up?
[SPEAKER_09]: Because I feel like the connection's breaking up.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it's just a little laggy, but that's okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to wrap up because we want to get to some real calls.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, snap.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm a fake call.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I just wanted to ask you real quickly, do you have any parting words?
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's not that we won't ever have you on all games, our new home, but do you have any parting words for Live365?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I'm about ready to go bleach my asshole, so that's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, have a good one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bye, Extifer.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, have a good synchronous.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, you too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bye Christopher, I mean, Xtofer, we love you.
[SPEAKER_08]: And your asshole.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what we should have put on the list.
[SPEAKER_02]: Live 365 has to bleach Xtofer's asshole.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh god.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god, no.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ew.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bleach.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's the deal for tonight's Skype line.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to open it up, but with some boundaries tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tonight, you can state your name, and you get to ask us a question.
[SPEAKER_02]: But if you try to do anything else, like you start ranting about Jack Voldemort or whatever, then you're getting cut off.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because tonight, we want to bring back for one last time on Live 365, Ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_02]: You ready, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_02]: This is for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Legend of the Doctor
[SPEAKER_02]: State your question, Legend of Zaku.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, basically, I know it's been like five and a half years and everything, but do you have any regrets?
[SPEAKER_12]: Any regrets at all of the journey you've taken so far?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll start with DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ladies first.
[SPEAKER_06]: I regret letting Andrew tell jokes.
[SPEAKER_20]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_20]: I regret it too.
[SPEAKER_05]: I regret ever doing an impression of Tingle's voice.
[SPEAKER_05]: Laughter
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm surprised you didn't say I regret ever buying karaoke revolution.
[SPEAKER_02]: Too late.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rice Princess, Drew, anything?
[SPEAKER_08]: I regret nothing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow, that's really freaking loud.
[SPEAKER_02]: Drew?
[SPEAKER_02]: If you say I regret... That's more than the question.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hearts.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's the thing, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: The only thing I regret, I'm going to be honest, not doing this sooner.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi, caller, state your name A lone vacationer
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello, LoneVacationer.
[SPEAKER_02]: State your question, please.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, Rob, I was wondering why you had to be so retarded for Metroid instead of Chrono Trigger.
[SPEAKER_02]: The sad thing is the podcast listeners aren't going to get this because they didn't hear the bonus segment tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: I voted for Super Metroid because I believe it to be the greatest video game of all time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Look, as much as I love Chrono Trigger, I loved the Final Fantasy series just a little bit more.
[SPEAKER_02]: The battles got annoying to me in Chrono Trigger.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know what it was, but it did have a good story.
[SPEAKER_02]: I respect Chrono Trigger as a game, but as far as Super Metroid, it was the music, it was the fact that it was a game that you could sit down and beat in one sitting, but it felt like there was so much you could do.
[SPEAKER_02]: You could play it where you collect everything, you could play it where you explore everything, you could play it to speed beat it, and all of those things were accessible to a normal person.
[SPEAKER_02]: Usually it takes a hobbyist to speed play through a game and stuff, but just with the items and everything, it's just a game I remember very much in my memory.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, there you have it.
[SPEAKER_02]: See, the caller knew not to say anything else because that would be more than a question.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, let's get to another call here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_02]: State your name.
[SPEAKER_02]: The name is Ranma.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello, Ranma, and please state your question.
[SPEAKER_16]: My question is to everyone, your greatest or favorite moment on Live365?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh shit, this is going to be a hard one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god, there's so much.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you can't say it though because that would be more than a question, but you could private message it to me in chat and I might read it.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, what was your favorite moment in all of Life 365's history?
[SPEAKER_06]: Leaving it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Episode 69, The Whole Thing
[SPEAKER_20]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_20]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did I delete it on accident?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, God, I did not.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, Rob, how could you?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, you did.
[SPEAKER_08]: That would be terrible.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, briefly explain for the listeners what that was about, Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: What happened?
[SPEAKER_05]: So we got nominated for most unlikely to hear on, like, terrestrial radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hold on, let me see if this is it.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, that's something else.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why do I have a Kylie Minogue song in there?
[SPEAKER_05]: God, I'm gay.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Tom Brokaw on the West Coast, Fixing the Word Bukkake
[SPEAKER_02]: This is actually a clip from Howard Stern, but it was so funny here on the show when they played it.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's not right.
[SPEAKER_13]: That ain't right.
[SPEAKER_13]: People on the West Coast got gypped of hearing Bukkake.
[SPEAKER_13]: And in this report out of Moscow tonight, two Russian planes carrying a total of more than 100 people crashed almost simultaneously today.
[SPEAKER_13]: The first crash happened in Bukkake, about 110 miles south of Moscow.
[SPEAKER_08]: He said Bukkake.
[SPEAKER_02]: That clip was courtesy of the Howard Stern Show, but that Bukkake thing, I swear to God, gave us like a month worth of stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Gaming Radio, So Uncensored,
[SPEAKER_21]: and even Tom Brokaw could get a job with us.
[SPEAKER_21]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh my god!
[SPEAKER_21]: You just talked over it, you stupid bitch!
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh my god!
[SPEAKER_21]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's hilarious.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was more than a question, sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: You should play all of the old promos or buffers or whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, you can't.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I mean, you could string them in a sequence or something.
[SPEAKER_20]: Some of them are stupid.
[SPEAKER_08]: I love them.
[SPEAKER_08]: Some of them are so stupid.
[SPEAKER_08]: They were like the ketchup.
[SPEAKER_20]: I still have the nori, nori, nori promo.
[SPEAKER_20]: That never aired.
[SPEAKER_20]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_20]: That's old school.
[SPEAKER_20]: I'll send it to you later.
[SPEAKER_20]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: My favorite moment in Orange Lounge Radio history was the drunk show where Jamie drank so much tequila she lied in my bed face down after consuming an entire box of waffles.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wasn't face down.
[SPEAKER_02]: And had me delivering waffles to her.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I was running up the wall yelling, I'm in the Matrix, I'm in the Matrix.
[SPEAKER_06]: And how sober was I by the end of the show?
[SPEAKER_05]: We can't forget Super Bacon either.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I wonder why my pancreas is fucked.
[SPEAKER_06]: The deep fried rice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember when we did peep jousting?
[SPEAKER_02]: Peep Wars!
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that was actually on a Wednesday night show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically you take two marshmallow peeps and you put toothpicks in them and then put them in the microwave and it's peep jousting because they get really big in the microwave and then eventually one slaughters the other.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's so fucking hilarious.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Good time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: State your name.
GS68.
[SPEAKER_02]: GS68.
[SPEAKER_02]: And what is your question for tonight on Ask Orange Lounge?
[SPEAKER_11]: Any progress on the Faname panel?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: Shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's more than a question.
[SPEAKER_05]: And if I remember correctly, that's Memorial Day weekend, which is the first weekend in May?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Last weekend in May.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let me know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nelly with me, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_00]: I have actually a very favorite moment in live 365 history.
[SPEAKER_02]: You better phrase it as a question or you're in trouble.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is Jeopardy, bitch.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you remember when Loki sang Oops I Did It Again?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't remember it, but I sort of remember vaguely doing something that wasn't funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was still pretty damn funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: How much do you charge for autographed Xbox 360 faceplates, and what's your favorite dish at the Olive Garden?
[SPEAKER_02]: That was a two-part question, you little bastard.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll let it slide.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_02]: How much do we charge for an autographed Xbox 360 faceplate?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't see why we wouldn't charge anything more than the cost of the faceplate plus shipping.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, we're not out to make a profit on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you want one, which I hear you do, we'll work something out.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've got some extra faceplates.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: You want to just give them one?
[SPEAKER_06]: We need to airbrush it white and then autograph it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I have no extra white ones because I bought other ones.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, we'll figure something out, Osfer.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then the other question, I like this one.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's your favorite dish at the Olive Garden?
[SPEAKER_06]: The breadsticks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mine was the, what did they call it, pasta rustica or something like that?
[SPEAKER_02]: And they got rid of it, those assholes.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then I like the Tuscan chicken.
[SPEAKER_02]: They got rid of that, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: What a bunch of fuckers.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm mad at all of them right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rob's not allowed to tell anybody he likes anything at the Olive Garden.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't eat them anymore anyway, at least for the next month while I'm on this.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm rather plain, so I always get the spaghetti with meat sauce.
[SPEAKER_02]: You are boring.
[SPEAKER_02]: I always used to get the shrimp scampi.
[SPEAKER_02]: Folksenbach?
[SPEAKER_02]: Shrimp scampi?
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, I really like the risotto.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's the name of that chicken dish on our first or third date or something that I got?
[SPEAKER_08]: Like,
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know, some chicken dish with pasta.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I also like their zuppa, whatever the hell's in it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, the white one with sausage and potatoes.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's really good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, God, my pancreas hurts just thinking about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, thanks for the question, caller.
[SPEAKER_02]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll figure something out about that faceplate.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, Skype line's still open.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't see any need to close.
[SPEAKER_02]: See, the calls are so short tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Caller, please state your name.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's SSJ100, Matt.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello, and please state your question.
[SPEAKER_18]: My question is, what would be your dream interview to have on the show?
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, your dream interview.
[SPEAKER_02]: Akira Yamaoka.
[SPEAKER_05]: We talked to him.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, we didn't have him on the show, but we've seen him in person.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right, you narrowly missed it.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's right, because somebody wanted to go interview somebody and lost the recording of the damn interview.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll throw a curveball at you in just a minute.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll tell you why, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Drew, what would be your dream interview to see us interview?
[SPEAKER_02]: Freeze Pop.
[SPEAKER_02]: We had one guy on the show, remember?
[SPEAKER_02]: All of them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here in studio performing a la Mo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: A la Mo.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rice Princess.
[SPEAKER_08]: Christian Bale naked in front of me.
[SPEAKER_20]: You're asking too much.
[SPEAKER_20]: Via a unicorn.
[SPEAKER_08]: Via a unicorn.
[SPEAKER_08]: And there won't be a lot of talking.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just going to say this.
[SPEAKER_02]: My dream interview would be Morgan Webb.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because...
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd have a field day.
[SPEAKER_20]: You better have a damn good reason.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would have a field day.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_05]: I gotta stop you real quick.
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: They posted an old video clip of her.
[SPEAKER_05]: She was on the Tyra Bank.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bye, caller.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for the question.
[SPEAKER_05]: She was actually on the Tyra Bank show one time and spouting off some, like, three...
[SPEAKER_05]: Three different types of gamers and what you can learn from your guy based on the types of games he played.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that was so retarded.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, the chat room is yelling at me.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't want the interview because I think it's going to be... Let me ask her some questions in public.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's all I want.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: You forgot Nathan.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry, Nathan.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't have anything to say.
[SPEAKER_10]: Damn it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh!
[SPEAKER_02]: He's so emotional.
[SPEAKER_02]: Caller, state your name.
[SPEAKER_17]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi, caller, what is your name?
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, um, Gold Banjo here.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hello, Gold.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was wondering, seeing as how you're at, like, an internet radio show and all, I'm wondering if anybody's ever, like, threatened you or stalked you or something?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow, threatened us or stalked us.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a good one.
[SPEAKER_02]: No one stalked you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, I don't remember anyone.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wait, who?
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, God!
[SPEAKER_07]: Did he?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: There was a person that was borderline stalking me.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm listening to what you're saying now.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think we've ever really had anything beyond that, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that was more just kind of like a silly internet prank.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not that that's acceptable.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not.
[SPEAKER_02]: But nobody's ever threatened us with death or anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, we're not famous.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll threaten you with death if you don't change your vote.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi, callers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Please state your name.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yo, what's up?
[SPEAKER_12]: This is Ross Steel, UT.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello, Ross Steel, UT.
[SPEAKER_02]: And please state your question.
[SPEAKER_18]: How many blind monkeys do you think it took for Ubisoft to come up with the name HAWX?
[SPEAKER_02]: One for each letter.
[SPEAKER_02]: Four.
[SPEAKER_05]: Only one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because you have to understand, Hawks is edgy because they have an X instead of a KS.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're thinking 90s now.
[SPEAKER_22]: It took 90 monkeys?
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow, that's extreme.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're laughing too much, and that's more than a question.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, but just kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: But we've got to free up the line.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: I like this.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is like a condensed... It's great.
[SPEAKER_02]: Look how many people were getting in tonight for the last... Okay, we still got... I know there's still people trying to get in, so I'm waiting.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, here we go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Another call.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello, caller.
[SPEAKER_02]: Please state your name.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello, this is your favorite Swede, AK River.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why did you start out in Live 365 in the first place?
[SPEAKER_02]: Go figure it comes from someone not from America.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why did we start on Life 365 in the first place?
[SPEAKER_02]: I have my answer.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if anyone else wants to contribute.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was easy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, two reasons.
[SPEAKER_02]: A, it was easy.
[SPEAKER_02]: www.DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: We didn't talk about that very much
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see if we get some more.
[SPEAKER_02]: 1-877-GAME-OLR How many more times?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god, this segment's going long.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's alright, it's the last.
[SPEAKER_02]: We got a little time, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: You guys are okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, Jamie's starting to get a little restless.
[SPEAKER_02]: We gotta wind down soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, hello caller, please state your name.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello, hi caller, please state your name.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is Misty.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, hello, Misty!
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm glad to hear from Misty.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, Misty, I know you probably went waiting forever to get in, but please state your question.
[SPEAKER_01]: If I were to win the lottery and bribe all of your bosses with however much they needed, would you people fucking come to ASEN?
[SPEAKER_01]: I want to.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have been... Sweetie, I love you.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, no, no, this is Misty.
[SPEAKER_02]: I really, really want to go to Ace and I've been bringing this up since last year.
[SPEAKER_06]: We need to get our asses to Chicago and go to a convention.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I actually need to finish one of my costumes to actually be able to wear it there.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I also want to go hang out in Artist Alley with Megzi and Chris because they're going to be there this year too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Honestly, I would be going this year if it wasn't for my medical issues.
[SPEAKER_02]: I really was considering going this year and making it happen, but my medical issues have made me think twice about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's very unfortunate.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: If a miracle pulls through in the next week, I might reconsider.
[SPEAKER_02]: But right now I have to say no.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, any chance in hell you'd go to ASIN?
[SPEAKER_02]: Even if she won the lottery and paid for it for you?
[SPEAKER_02]: Even if she won the lottery, my wife... I can't go because my wife can't stay home alone.
[SPEAKER_06]: Can I represent us at ASIN?
[SPEAKER_02]: If you can go, sure, go for it.
[SPEAKER_06]: If someone pays my way, I'll go to ASIN.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for the call.
[SPEAKER_02]: Everyone give Misty a kiss.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bye, Misty.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, fun fact from Bobby Blackwolf.
[SPEAKER_02]: All Games Radio was on Live 365 in one of its incarnations.
[SPEAKER_02]: In fact, they used to give people the link to OLR to test the Live 365 player.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, you know... Isn't it funny how things come full circle?
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, maybe one more.
[SPEAKER_02]: One more.
[SPEAKER_02]: 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wanted to get Misty in because I know she doesn't get to listen live much and...
[SPEAKER_06]: That's why I gave Misty the pass.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because she's special.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a girl thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Admit it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_02]: One more.
[SPEAKER_02]: Last call, last question.
[SPEAKER_02]: Guess what?
[SPEAKER_02]: You're the last one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Please state your name.
[SPEAKER_02]: E.T.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello, DT.
[SPEAKER_02]: First off, we all need to tip our hat to Dark Tetsuya for a moment and praise him for the work he's done for our station because he's been listening here since episode one.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's been a longtime supporter.
[SPEAKER_02]: He writes website articles for our front page even when the damn thing is deader than a doornail.
[SPEAKER_02]: He has updated the OLR wiki with articles.
[SPEAKER_02]: He keeps things posted on the forum.
[SPEAKER_02]: Please, everybody, let's give Dark Tetsuya a round of applause for the hard work he's done for our station.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkTetsuya, please...
[SPEAKER_02]: The last question of the night for Last Scorn's Lounge.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, let me set this up.
[SPEAKER_17]: As you know, she... Go ahead.
[SPEAKER_17]: She is planning on coming to California in October.
[SPEAKER_17]: Wouldn't there be a chance of getting her on the show somehow?
[SPEAKER_02]: Is she going to be here on a Sunday?
[SPEAKER_17]: Her and I.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think I'll have to find out Wow
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's been a dream of mine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, damn, that's a lot of calls tonight and I think it's time to wrap things up.
[SPEAKER_02]: We already did last minute stories.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god, we missed one thing though.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was supposed to do it after the list list tonight and I completely glossed over it.
[SPEAKER_02]: What segment did I forget, boys and girls?
[SPEAKER_02]: What segment did we forget?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, the FU's of the week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, I gotta get the music.
[SPEAKER_02]: Holy crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wouldn't that be hilarious?
[SPEAKER_06]: This entire show's been an FU to Life 365.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, hold on really quickly, because I've got to set this up here.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you may hear just a moment of silence.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, I'll let the music play for a little bit.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let the music play.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here it is, the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, start us off.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fuck you, Live365 Loki Fuck you, Live365 Drew Fuck you, Live365 Rice Princess Fuck you, Live365 Silent Nathan And my F.U.
[SPEAKER_03]: of the week F.U.
[SPEAKER_02]: Live365 For upping your rates and using scare tactics to motivate it And F.U.
[SPEAKER_02]: the R.I.A.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, for starting the whole damn thing in the first place.
[SPEAKER_02]: And honestly, this all goes back to you assholes forgetting our names.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, actually, I got to say in seriousness, we have met some good people at Live365.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember Betty, she was a real sweetheart.
[SPEAKER_02]: There are some great people.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I got speakers.
[SPEAKER_02]: When we say F you, we mean to the corporate decisions that were made there and not necessarily the people.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just want to get that out there because in our five and a half years, we have interacted with a lot of great people and other broadcasters that we've met through Live 365.
[SPEAKER_02]: So please don't misappropriate our angst.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: So anyhow, that brings us to the very last part where we give our final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_02]: Silent Nathan, any final thoughts?
[SPEAKER_02]: Rice Princess, your final thoughts?
[SPEAKER_02]: Drew, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_02]: Indignation.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_05]: My final thought is I need to play some more games other than Saints Row.
[SPEAKER_05]: Although I may go back to Saints Row to finish the activities.
[SPEAKER_05]: Gotta get them achievement points.
[SPEAKER_02]: My FU of the week... I'm sorry, not my FU of the week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it goes back to my pancreas, honestly, but my final thought is I really don't want it to flare up again and end up in the hospital.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hate to sound like a baby in a hypochondriac, but keep your fingers crossed for me, kid.
[SPEAKER_02]: The ferret is next.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ferret, your final thought, please.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, Dark... All right, shut up.
[SPEAKER_02]: You had two final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dark Sakura, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_06]: Reject false icons.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's going to do it for Orange Lounge Radio, the last live program here on our network on Live 365.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you to all that have supported us since May 23rd.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: All you guys on the forums, all you guys on LiveJournal, Myspace, Facebook, and everybody that downloads this show, thank you for five and a half years.
[SPEAKER_02]: It has been fun on our own stream, but the party ain't over, and we look forward to the next chapter of Orange Laundry.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was a really big chapter one.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is like War and Peace right here.
[SPEAKER_02]: We look forward to the next chapter of OLR when we combine forces with All Games Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: and come together to make the Voltron of independent gaming podcasting.
[SPEAKER_02]: And remember, if you like what you hear, tell a couple friends about Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's word of mouth that helps make everything go around and brings more listeners to us so that we can slowly take over the world.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, can I rant anymore?
[SPEAKER_02]: Or is that it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Are we done?
[SPEAKER_02]: Are we out of here?
[SPEAKER_06]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're done.
[SPEAKER_02]: Goodbye, Life365.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_15]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_15]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_15]: For more information on our live and podcast programs, visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com See you next week!