[SPEAKER_01]: Tonight, April 20th, 2008, Rock Band is set to get its first full albums, Soul Calibur the original is headed to Xbox Live Arcade, and did a recent video game release borrow its box art from the internet?
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello everybody out there on the internet and welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: We are that podcast on the internet dedicated to video games, video gaming, gaming culture, and the gamer lifestyle.
[SPEAKER_02]: My name is Rob Roberts and joining me as always, say hello to the one and only DarkSakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_02]: And how are you, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm a little tired.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry to hear about the tiredness.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can tell you're quiet and you seem like your energy is depleted a little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, happy late birthday to you, Miss Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know this weekend was your birthday and I guess you're just too exhausted from all the partying, huh?
[SPEAKER_05]: I went to San Francisco for Sakura Matsuri and I was very sad because it was so windy that all the blossoms had been blown off of the trees except for a few.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh no.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I did a lot of shopping and they changed Kinokuniya.
[SPEAKER_05]: That has a whole anime, manga stuff section downstairs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's where all the fanboys were, but that's also where all the Copic markers and deleter pads were, so I had to go down there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I noticed you brought back a video game magazine all in Japanese.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks like Famitsu magazine.
[SPEAKER_05]: I brought back last month's issue of Famitsu.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I brought back the first issue of the Blue Dragon manga, which is interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I was thumbing through it and I'm like, this looks to have nothing in common with the video games.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not done by Toriyama.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I brought back a bunch of comics.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cool, cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know she's getting a lot of belated happy birthdays in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you, everybody else in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_02]: And if you want to join us, chat.orangeloungeradio.com is the place to be.
[SPEAKER_02]: Even though we do tape live on all games radio, we do use a separate chat room still, our old chat room.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's chat.orangeloungeradio.com, or if you're already on the Game Search Network, it's channel Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I got pie today, but I haven't eaten any of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Birthday pie instead of birthday cake?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because my boss baked me a cake on Friday.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, not on Friday, but she brought me carrot cake, homemade carrot cake.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because carrot cake is my favorite cake.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: She baked me a cake.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm so happy.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's even better than giving you a cookie is baking you a cake.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I got pie today.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: What kind of pie?
[SPEAKER_05]: I did eat a lot of cookies, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: I had samosas.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love samosas.
[SPEAKER_05]: I ate them, they were cold too, and had Mars Bars eggs, and Nestle Black Magic eggs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, you gotta stop talking, I miss all these foods ever since I had to go on the low-fat diet thanks to the pancreas.
[SPEAKER_05]: Pie is good for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's full of vitamin banana.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's move over and say hello to Techmaster Loki, who also joins us every week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_02]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm doing good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Any cookies or pie in your day?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you have an exciting weekend?
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you have anything fun?
[SPEAKER_00]: I waited two hours to eat at Joe's Crab Shack yesterday, I guess.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, that's not fun.
[SPEAKER_00]: Two hours?
[SPEAKER_00]: Two hours.
[SPEAKER_00]: That must have been some damn good seafood.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, it's just we were damn patient.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's really popular here, though, in Sacramento, though, because it's on the river.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was Saturday night.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was during Dinner Rush, and they had prom people there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: People are dumb.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was out of town for four days.
[SPEAKER_02]: I missed Jamie's birthday, sadly.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was completely out of town since Thursday.
[SPEAKER_02]: I did my yearly pilgrimage out to the middle of nowhere, also known as Mendocino, which is up on the north coast of California.
[SPEAKER_02]: Part of it's a vacation from life, but it's also a vacation from the internets and everything because there's no phone connection out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's no internet.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's no nothing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just the beach, hot tub.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good times, except for the food poisoning I got that kept me in bed all day Saturday.
[SPEAKER_02]: That kind of sucked.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh well, I did end up playing some video games, so I'll talk about that in a minute, right after we get to DarkSakura's Gaming Week.
[SPEAKER_02]: How was your Gaming Week?
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, it wasn't, well, other than Ragnarok, but I bought Famitsu and Blue Dragon Manga, and we were supposed to hook up the Dreamcast.
[SPEAKER_05]: We had talked about hooking up the Dreamcast so that I could play a couple of things that I've been sort of having an itch to, but instead I downloaded ZSNES today.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ssj100Matt says, you ate at the Crab Shack on Passover?
[SPEAKER_05]: Fired.
[SPEAKER_02]: Somebody who didn't change their name, OilArmyRecruit2559 says, Always with the Ragnacrack.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, and your point is?
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you ever sign up for the number two?
[SPEAKER_05]: Solid Goomba, by the way.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you ever sign up for the number two?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I'm going to wait until they have more than just menus translated.
[SPEAKER_02]: To get some of the bugs worked out from the early releases?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, because I'd actually like to be able to do the quests, and I don't read Korean.
[SPEAKER_05]: I, amazingly enough, know how Korean is read, you know, how the characters are arranged, but I do not actually read any Korean.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nobody's perfect.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, let's move on over to Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Was there any Korean in your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, then what was there?
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't think.
[SPEAKER_00]: Um...
[SPEAKER_00]: I played Omega 5, actually.
[SPEAKER_00]: I was downloading some Xbox Live Arcade games.
[SPEAKER_00]: I downloaded Ikaruga, but I never got the chance to play it.
[SPEAKER_00]: I did play... Actually, I played the demo of... What was it?
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_02]: What was the new release this week?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I was out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rocky and Bullwinkle and... Oh, that's right, the minigame thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wanted to check that out.
[SPEAKER_02]: I gotta catch up.
[SPEAKER_00]: I heard that sucked, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm actually kind of excited there's another game out there that uses the webcam, other than Totem Ball.
[SPEAKER_02]: Totem Ball and what, Uno?
[SPEAKER_00]: Really, we shouldn't be encouraging them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, fine, whatever.
[SPEAKER_00]: Um, so, yeah, I played Omega 5.
[SPEAKER_00]: That was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's just really hard, but that's kind of shooters for you, I guess.
[SPEAKER_00]: Um, I played lots of Mario Kart, and it's kind of, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: I guess it's just like the other Mario Karts.
[SPEAKER_00]: I still really hate the fact that you can't do...
[SPEAKER_00]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_00]: More Saints Row, yes.
[SPEAKER_00]: I played multiplayer, but then I realized something.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know why I haven't realized it before, but I just found a code in the game that actually makes this game totally different and a lot fun in just the weirdest way.
[SPEAKER_00]: I couldn't stop giggling the entire time I was playing this.
[SPEAKER_00]: The code is the evil cars code, and it makes all the cars in the game try to hunt you down and kill you.
[SPEAKER_00]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_00]: And so you'll be running around or something.
[SPEAKER_00]: All of a sudden, this car comes from nowhere, just flying through the air just at your head, where they'll be backing up towards you.
[SPEAKER_00]: And so I made it kind of a goal to run from one end of the map to the next.
[SPEAKER_00]: and it's fun and in fact I think I might actually do a little video for YouTube or something like that just something funny with you know that whole thing in there because it's hilarious because you'll be hiding in like a little ditch or something all of a sudden all these cars fly over your head and stuff trying to kill you
[SPEAKER_02]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: As I was going to say, it would be fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: That could be a fun multiplayer game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who can live longer being chased stocked by the cars?
[SPEAKER_00]: What I've been doing, like I said, I put in the infinite ammo code, the infinite sprint, and just go crazy.
[SPEAKER_00]: Just run.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's pretty hard.
[SPEAKER_00]: Especially when you get onto the freeway and stuff and there's trucks coming after you and cars are exploding because they keep running into each other.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: SSJ100 Matt and Chad is chiming in with Death Race 3000, which he wants to point out is being remade.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is that the one where you get stalked by cars?
[SPEAKER_02]: Death Race?
[SPEAKER_00]: No, that's the one that's just like Carmageddon.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, I know the one you're thinking about.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's a Stephen King movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was Carrie!
[SPEAKER_02]: No, Carrie was the... Christine!
[SPEAKER_00]: Carrie was the prom queen.
[SPEAKER_05]: Christine was the one about the Plymouth Fury.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, there's another one I was thinking of where the cars were alive.
[SPEAKER_00]: And remember they had that big rig with the clown face on the front?
[SPEAKER_02]: It?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, that wasn't it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Forget it.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't remember what it's called.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not that important.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm sure someone in chat will know, though.
[SPEAKER_00]: But, yeah, it's cool, though.
[SPEAKER_00]: The code just, you know, I guess a little bit more life for this next few weeks until Grand Theft Auto 4 comes out.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you've been extending the life of Saints Row for quite some time.
[SPEAKER_00]: You're one of the only people I know that still just...
[SPEAKER_02]: doesn't shut up about this game, ever.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's a great game.
[SPEAKER_00]: I already have my Saints Row 2 pre-ordered, so I can't wait to play that too.
[SPEAKER_00]: Everyone's always pro-Saints Row or pro-Grand Theft Auto and hating on the other ones.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't understand why you can't like both.
[SPEAKER_00]: I love both games just equally.
[SPEAKER_00]: They're good in different ways.
[SPEAKER_00]: Grand Theft Auto tends to be more realistic, where Saints Row is just absolutely batshit crazy with all sorts of stuff that you wouldn't be able to do in real life.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's just great.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, chat.orangealtrader.com, some comments.
[SPEAKER_02]: In response to the Vision Cam, VXJSNXV says, Rayman's Raving Rabbids on the 360 use the Vision Cam.
[SPEAKER_02]: Unless, of course, you're talking about Arcade Consoling.
[SPEAKER_00]: And Brad from PodCulture, Maximum Overdrive was the name of the movie with the cars there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nice work.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was going to say about Rayman's Raving Rabbids.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was already worn out from the Wii version.
[SPEAKER_02]: I never even bothered with the 360 version because I was already kind of... It's dirt cheap now because that game didn't sell for crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, aren't they making a sequel though?
[SPEAKER_00]: They already made a sequel, Rayman's Raving Rabbids 2.
[SPEAKER_00]: They came out on the Wii last year around the holiday.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently I slept through it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, you didn't miss much.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's what I hear.
[SPEAKER_00]: But they didn't do one for the 360 because the 360 one didn't sell at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: Frisbee wants to know, can you use a vision cam on the computer?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, you can, actually.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's software available on Microsoft's website, but there's no audio with it, and the quality's not great.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually considered using it for our Justin TV feed, which is taping our show over at justintv.com, but the quality's not that great.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, that's why we don't use it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it does work.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is a USB camera.
[SPEAKER_02]: My gaming week, believe it or not, even though I was out of town for four days, I did get the opportunity to play something new because what is going into the wilderness with ten of your friends staying in a cabin and not bringing along some party video game?
[SPEAKER_02]: And I got to check out for the first time SingStar on the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we've talked about this game an awful lot on the show, but I've always been more of a karaoke revolution player.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the games I've had.
[SPEAKER_02]: But we did get to check out SingStar and
[SPEAKER_02]: The friend of ours had a variety.
[SPEAKER_02]: He had SingStar 80s, SingStar Pop, and SingStar Amped.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I guess one kind of cool thing is that you could switch back and forth between the games without having to turn the whole dang thing off and on.
[SPEAKER_02]: You just pop in another disc and it loads the 30 songs from that disc.
[SPEAKER_02]: Each game has about 30 songs.
[SPEAKER_02]: SingStar was kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was more impressed with it than I thought I would be.
[SPEAKER_02]: The only kind of bitches I have is that I didn't like the pitch gauging quite as much as I do in Karaoke Revolution.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, you can only see your pitch as you sing.
[SPEAKER_02]: You don't see it...
[SPEAKER_02]: Any time you're saying something into the mic, like you do in Karaoke Revolution, you really kind of have to play both games to know what I'm talking about.
[SPEAKER_02]: But if you play Karaoke Revolution, any time you make a sound, that arrow shows up on the line to show you where you're at.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whereas in SingStar, you don't see it until you're already singing.
[SPEAKER_02]: But one thing I did like about SingStar is that it had pretty much all the real music videos in the background as you're playing, which is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like SingStar Pop has Aha Take On Me, so you know we had to play that just to see the video, because, I mean...
[SPEAKER_02]: What was the last time you saw Aha take on me, the video?
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's got to be years and years ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some of our listeners are probably too young to even remember this video.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: About four days ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: On YouTube or something?
[SPEAKER_02]: I hadn't seen it in years.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the one hit lender song.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, but still.
[SPEAKER_02]: SSJ100 Matt says Rob in a cabin in the woods with SingStar horror movie plotline anyone?
[SPEAKER_02]: kinda it could have been but I there was a lot of songs I sang and had a pretty recognizable song list I actually think I might want to pick this game up on Playstation 3 although only as a party game I mean you know how there's those video games that really only work when you have friends over SingStar is definitely one of those games maybe maybe
[SPEAKER_00]: Because why get a PlayStation 3 for this crappy game?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I'm not going to get it just for that, but I like the fact that there's the music videos, the actual music videos in the background, and the way it's put together is nice.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know you just want it so you can film yourself and put yourself on that fake YouTube thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hell no, hell no, because our listeners will find a way to exploit it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not going to subject myself to that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Can you imagine me getting on there singing Like a Prayer?
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what happened last time I sang Like a Prayer karaoke?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it's been like 10 years and I haven't lived it down, so not gonna happen, sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or if it is, it's set to private or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that, and I played on the PSP, because William brought his PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: He was playing the shit out of Puzzle Quest most of the time.
[SPEAKER_02]: I played more Final Fantasy while I was sick yesterday, because I got food poisoning or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was sick all day yesterday.
[SPEAKER_02]: One or two?
[SPEAKER_02]: One.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's the old school upgraded one on PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know I've talked about it on the show before a while back, but man, the graphics are just beautiful on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's one thing the PSP does have going for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Even though it has that little screen and everything, the graphics are high def and gorgeous.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's one thing I really like about the PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I kind of want to go and get Final Fantasy 2 so I can play that on my PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then if I want to borrow Final Fantasy 1, I will.
[SPEAKER_00]: I didn't get into the 2.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was...
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's just different.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, that's going to do it for our gaming week.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if you want to join in and chime in on our gaming weeks or the news for tonight, you can join our chat room, chat.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: In the meantime, we do have some housekeeping for you guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: One thing that kind of made me sad, you know we have the Orange Lounge Radio Wiki at orangeloungeradio.wikia.com and that is growing and growing and the people, the listeners that have been contributing to that are doing an awesome job.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_02]: The bad news isn't about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: The bad news is about Wikipedia, the main site, you know, wikipedia.org.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know how Orange Lounge Radio had an article on there?
[SPEAKER_02]: It got zapped.
[SPEAKER_02]: Somebody deleted it.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's the thing I don't get.
[SPEAKER_02]: I always thought that articles, when they got deleted from Wikipedia, had to go through a review phase for articles pended for deletion or whatever, and people are supposed to review it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nuh-uh.
[SPEAKER_02]: When I looked in the deletion log, this guy named ClockworkSoul just nuked it.
[SPEAKER_02]: He must be some admin on there.
[SPEAKER_02]: He just nuked it, and it said, Web content does not indicate important significance.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Without any debate or argument, this guy just kind of did it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And now you know who to go after.
[SPEAKER_02]: Probably the first show to use Skype.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a part of me that thinks we were the first online show to use Skype, and I think I have the post to back that up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not to toot our horn too much, but I think there are things we have accomplished that make it somewhat notable.
[SPEAKER_05]: What about the other websites referred to on there that are still there?
[SPEAKER_02]: First site to use a PSP-based website?
[SPEAKER_02]: First gaming thing to have a PSP spinoff site?
[SPEAKER_02]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: So let's just put it back up.
[SPEAKER_00]: First and least updated.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but I would just say if you guys are going to go back and recreate it, you just might want to source some things.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you know some of our news stories are on YouTube, whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh well, we'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_02]: Regardless, we do have the Orange Laundry Wiki, which is like ten times better anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: And nobody can delete that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: See if we care.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: Our communities, we have MySpace.com slash Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have our Facebook community, the Oil Army, our Live Journal community at Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_02]: Join us if you are on any of those communities.
[SPEAKER_02]: Speaking of community, the All Games community has banded together for this.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: A limited edition Xbox 360 Elite based on Grand Theft Auto 4 is being given away.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now we have to correct something that was said last week's show.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is not one of the 500.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the bad news.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is not one of the 500 like uber limited edition things that Mark Echo got one of and we were making fun of him.
[SPEAKER_02]: Where the other 499 went, we have no idea.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the good news is it's one of eight.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is one of eight Xboxes being prepared with the whole customization specifically for community websites as a Grand Theft Auto promotion.
[SPEAKER_02]: Allgames.com has one and Orange Launch Radio is coming together with a bunch of all game shows including All Games Interactive, Dead Pixel Live, Bobby Blackwolf Show, Super Happy Funtime Show, Electric Sisterhood, Mediaspective, Chatterbox Video Game Radio, Video Game Outsiders, Ultimate Quest, Video Game Show and Platformation all coming together to give away this Xbox 360 Elite.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, if you want to win this, you can.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because here's how it's going to work.
[SPEAKER_02]: Each one of those affiliates I just named is going to send one finalist to the final round.
[SPEAKER_02]: And here's how it works.
[SPEAKER_02]: Every show is doing the same giveaway.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's going to happen is that... Okay, you know how like Grand Theft Auto, one of the big things in it is the radio stations that play?
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, you know, Grand Theft Auto, huge on the soundtracks, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, the last one had what, like a four-disc soundtrack?
[SPEAKER_02]: And they play all these songs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well...
[SPEAKER_02]: Amidst the songs are fake DJs.
[SPEAKER_02]: And people tell me all the time I sound like that one DJ in Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_02]: What the hell is his name?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, Laszlo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently I sound like him.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if that's true or not.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't hear it, but I guess other people do.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you know how Grand Theft Auto has those DJs and stuff?
[SPEAKER_02]: They have little commercials and fake DJ things.
[SPEAKER_02]: We want you to be that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's how it works.
[SPEAKER_02]: You are going to submit a sound clip.
[SPEAKER_02]: It can't be any longer than two minutes and it has to be in the style of a Grand Theft Auto 4 radio station commercial.
[SPEAKER_02]: It can be a spoof ad, a segment, it can be a little song and dance, whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: It has to somehow relate to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, that's the only thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: It can be one of our in-jokes, and if you don't know any in-jokes, go check the wiki.
[SPEAKER_02]: It can just say our name in it somewhere, whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: It just has to somehow relate to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: We will pick our favorites, like maybe our top five favorites.
[SPEAKER_02]: The community will vote on the winner, which will then go on to the final round at allgames.com to win one of these eight rare 360s.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's like, what, two minutes worth of voiceover?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: for possibly an Xbox 360 Elite, one of eight being made in the world.
[SPEAKER_02]: So there you have it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So the contest starts tonight, and if you have an MP3 you would like to submit to us, you can send that on in.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can either send it to mailbag at orangelaunchradio.com, or we will set up a special page on our forums where you can send those in.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll pick our favorites.
[SPEAKER_02]: The community will then vote on the winner, and then what happens is that the winning bumper goes to All Games Radio
[SPEAKER_02]: and All Games Radio will choose the ultimate winner out of those.
[SPEAKER_02]: But hey, the good news is just for winning from us, you get an All Games t-shirt and a $25 gift certificate to shop.allgames.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: They sell video games, so that's like half off a video game right there.
[SPEAKER_02]: So go for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Submission starts tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have to have these in by May 4th at midnight Pacific time.
[SPEAKER_02]: No late entries accepted.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know many of you listen to several shows on allgames.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: you can submit multiple entries per multiple shows but keep in mind you'll probably have to do different bumpers because you know since we're making you have something related to Orange Lounge Radio for example Electric Sista Hood would probably want something relating to their show and so on and so on
[SPEAKER_02]: we have the right to play your submission on our show blah blah blah if one person should win multiple contests a coin flip determines the winner open to North American residents only I'm sorry US and Canada only it's an NTSC console so we can't give it to Europe those are the rules sorry Europe
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, we can't really give it to anybody else because it's going to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Unfortunately, cast and crew of the participating affiliate shows are not eligible.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry, Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: And last but not least, no copywritten materials permitted in the entry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Parody is fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can't use, like, if you want to play Welcome to the Jungle, you have to, like, sing it yourself or something or, you know, Welcome to the Radio or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have to sing a makeup thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: So there you have it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actdeft is asking, what about Mexico?
[SPEAKER_02]: I will have to ask the official judges about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that counts as North America.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that's okay, but I will get the final ruling on that shortly.
[SPEAKER_02]: Decisions of the judges are final.
[SPEAKER_02]: No bitching.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you like the full list of rules, they are available on forums.allgames.com and we'll be posting them on our site soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's like, what, like $500 prize right there?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's nice stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's prizes for second and third place too, but if I told you that tonight, I'd have nothing to tell you about next week when we plug the contest again.
[SPEAKER_02]: So get working on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: A two-minute commercial parody.
[SPEAKER_02]: Orange Lounge Radio, anything that would happen in one of those little radio bits in the Grand Theft Auto game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Be creative.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, if you want, if you don't have a fancy recording studio set up in your place, you can also leave it on our Skype line, 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_02]: When we're not live, you can call in and leave a bumper there.
[SPEAKER_02]: So don't say you don't have many different ways to send this in.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's all futile anyways because, like I said and stated again, the console's going to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Even though you're ineligible.
[SPEAKER_00]: Even though I'm ineligible.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hell, I'm not even entering and it's going to me.
[SPEAKER_00]: So...
[SPEAKER_00]: Marvel vs. Capcom
[SPEAKER_00]: SubZero Staring Down Batman Midways Gamer Day
[SPEAKER_00]: and they were showing off a trailer featuring Sub-Zero fighting Batman.
[SPEAKER_00]: And the game itself, I don't know, I'm not a huge Mortal Kombat fan, but flying through the air while punching each other or falling, it's kind of hokey, but that's just my opinion, you know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: It made me think of the more recent Dead or Alive games.
[SPEAKER_00]: All I gotta say is, I hope they have villains in there as well, other than just... Because I think it would be pretty badass if they had a cool version of Joker in there.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay, that might be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: It might also be in horrible taste, though, to play a fatality on the Joker.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay, shut up.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay, fucking Jack Nicklaus is still alive.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who cares if, you know... Jack Nicklaus was a golf player.
[SPEAKER_02]: You mean Jack Nicholson?
[SPEAKER_00]: Nicholson, whatever.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hey, little did you know, Jack Nicklaus was actually Joker at one time.
[SPEAKER_00]: And then Jack Nicholson... It's just... All these things you don't know about movies, Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: Look, I said this on Bobby's show when we were doing our little tease before we went live tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: The thing is that obviously this game is not going to have fatalities because it's going for a teen rating or whatever, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: But...
[SPEAKER_02]: and people are like, oh my god, I can't believe it.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's a Mortal Kombat game without fatalities?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of sacrilegious to be able to perform a fatality on Wonder Woman.
[SPEAKER_02]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or on Batman.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, you can't decapitate Batman.
[SPEAKER_02]: You just can't.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can break Batman's back.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can do a friendship on Batman all you want.
[SPEAKER_02]: In fact, that might be kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can break his back.
[SPEAKER_05]: That would be hilarious because that's what happened to him.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think they should be mature.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_00]: Stop pussying out, DC.
[SPEAKER_00]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_02]: Somebody said in chat earlier you could kill Superman but he'd just come back.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just sacrilegious.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't ask me why.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just something about seeing your childhood hero get decapitated as all kinds of wrong.
[SPEAKER_00]: Now, here's a question for you.
[SPEAKER_00]: Can you think of any game whatsoever that's had Superman in it that's been any good?
[SPEAKER_02]: Superman on the Atari 2600 when I was five years old was the shit.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay, well that doesn't count.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_02]: You said name a Superman video game that was good.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay, I was thinking, I don't know, within this decade.
[SPEAKER_04]: There was that Justice League game.
[SPEAKER_00]: That wasn't very good.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was better than the straight Superman games.
[SPEAKER_00]: All the games that Superman has ever touched, crap.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_00]: This isn't going to be very good.
[SPEAKER_00]: And it's Superman's fault.
[SPEAKER_00]: He should have stayed dead like a good superhero.
[SPEAKER_02]: Instead of a fatality, I'm thinking the game will have nudalities where the characters are forced to don their own underoos.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess that wouldn't get a teen rating, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hope the Wonder Twins are in it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, all I can say is this is going to come out and be yet another mediocre Mortal Kombat game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Am I the only one that actually enjoys Mortal Kombat's combat system?
[SPEAKER_02]: I kind of liked how you could switch between the fighting styles and the weapons.
[SPEAKER_00]: I actually kind of enjoy the Mortal Kombat games, not just for the fatalities.
[SPEAKER_00]: If I'm to be fair, though, I don't like Street Fighter either, so, you know.
[SPEAKER_00]: I like the fact that everything was hand-drawn stuff in Marvel vs. Capcom.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hell, if they wanted to do a 2D fighter with the Mortal Kombat characters all hand-drawn, and not really Mortal Kombat style, but kind of ripping off SNK or Capcom,
[SPEAKER_00]: DC Comics Marvel vs. DC Fighter Marvel vs. DC Fighter
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, let's read comments from chat room.
[SPEAKER_02]: SSJ100, Matt wants to point out, there was a good Superman arcade game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ranma says, mind you, Mortal Kombat vs. DC idea has been around since Marvel vs. Capcom, which is funny because I know it's been brought up on this show before.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to say this whole thing was in rumor state a couple months ago, and we joked about it then.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ranma continues, and as much as I'm not too thrilled about not having fatalities, Mortal Kombat vs. DC does not need it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, the fandom will be pissed off, but the DC fandom is bigger than the Mortal Kombat fandom,
[SPEAKER_00]: Here's what's going to happen.
[SPEAKER_00]: This game is going to be in development right now.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's scheduled out for the fall.
[SPEAKER_00]: What movie is coming out this summer?
[SPEAKER_00]: The Dark Knight.
[SPEAKER_00]: What movie is going to probably be out on DVD in the fall?
[SPEAKER_00]: Here's where the whoring begins.
[SPEAKER_00]: They're just going to put this out at the same time as the fucking Dark Knight movie, and they're just going to try to sell some more copies on a mediocre game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pardon my ignorance, I don't follow comic books, but is Iron Man DC or Marvel?
[SPEAKER_00]: Marvel.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, never mind.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's not related.
[SPEAKER_02]: because I was going to say there's the Iron Man movie coming out too, but I guess that's old.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's Marvel.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's Marvel whoring.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ah, that's why I asked.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm getting the Iron Man game too.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's Sega whoring Marvel characters like that and the Incredible Hulk.
[SPEAKER_00]: Both games which look good, but I think are going to be mediocre.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I think the last comic book I bought when I was maybe seven years old was Uncle Scrooge and Huey, Dewey, and Louie.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have comics right here.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: Best comic book game ever.
[SPEAKER_05]: DuckTales was a pretty awesome comic book game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Comics.
[SPEAKER_00]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_00]: X-Men.
[SPEAKER_00]: Is that what a comic looks like?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a graphic novel.
[SPEAKER_00]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's an older one, too.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's what adults have to read nowadays because you can't read comics.
[SPEAKER_00]: You have to read graphic novels.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hell no.
[SPEAKER_05]: I still buy comics.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got to ask this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Instapoll in chat.
[SPEAKER_02]: There is a greater comic book game than DuckTales.
[SPEAKER_02]: Y or N?
[SPEAKER_02]: Meanwhile, we'll see what the Instapoll results are in a minute.
[SPEAKER_02]: By the way, Tigerclaw wants to add this.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think this is in our show role anywhere, but speaking of Mortal Kombat, I don't know if you heard this, the actor who was Liu Kang in the Mortal Kombat movie, Robin Shu, he is going to be Jen in the new Street Fighter movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: So there's that crossover there for Mortal Kombat and Street Fighter that one of the actors is going to be.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's very loose, Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, a little bit.
[SPEAKER_00]: and little does he realize what kind of, you know, crap he is walking into.
[SPEAKER_00]: Do we not forget Raul Julia and what happened to him in the last Street Fighter movie?
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, the Soul keeps burning on July 29th.
[SPEAKER_02]: Soul Calibur is coming to Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry, not on that day.
[SPEAKER_02]: Something else will come out that day.
[SPEAKER_02]: On Xbox Live Arcade, though, sometime this summer, Soul Calibur is going to be coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be old school because it's the Dreamcast version that's actually coming to Xbox Live Arcade, not the arcade version of Soul Calibur.
[SPEAKER_05]: It better have the Japanese voices in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because my man was Maxi.
[SPEAKER_02]: It will have arcade training and survival modes in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that was revealed at Namco's Gamers Day.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is not the arcade version.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is the Dreamcast version.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now the question is, will it have to squeeze into that 150 megabyte limit or not?
[SPEAKER_03]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's going to be pretty rad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Especially if they're up the graphics to HD and all that other good stuff they usually do.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's going to be pretty rad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't you think, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that would be fairly pretty.
[SPEAKER_05]: Soul Calibur is also, remember, the game that gave us Rod Calibur.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now we just, well, that's the next question.
[SPEAKER_02]: Will we be able to use other interesting control devices on the Xbox 360?
[SPEAKER_05]: See, there isn't a fishing rod controller for that.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, but there's the Scenic controller.
[SPEAKER_05]: That would be cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: We should have a contest.
[SPEAKER_00]: The rock band drums.
[SPEAKER_00]: Guitar caliber.
[SPEAKER_05]: We want guitar caliber.
[SPEAKER_05]: I played Soul Calibur with my DDR pads.
[SPEAKER_05]: My first DDR I owned was the Dreamcast DDR.
[SPEAKER_05]: The only analog button on there was the Konami logo to put it into SSR.
[SPEAKER_02]: and the question being asked in our chat room by none other than Bobby Blackwolf.
[SPEAKER_02]: In other words, will it blend?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a very good question, will it blend?
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's the results of our quick poll and then we'll get to more Soul Calibur news courtesy of Jamie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Quick poll was, is there a comic book game better than DuckTales?
[SPEAKER_02]: Here are the results.
[SPEAKER_02]: N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, N, Y, X-Men Mutant Apocalypse.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's all about maximum carnage.
[SPEAKER_02]: I missed that one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Y, Superman 64.
[SPEAKER_02]: X-Men Arcade is a close second.
[SPEAKER_02]: N, Y, Marvel Super Heroes vs. Street Fighters.
[SPEAKER_02]: N, N, DuckTales freaking rocked.
[SPEAKER_02]: Y, X-Men Arcade.
[SPEAKER_05]: The X-Men arcade game was really, really good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Looks like the majority do believe DuckTales is the greatest comic book game ever made, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: That kind of surprises me.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't count DuckTales as a comic book game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think of the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: There wasn't a DuckTales comic book until I think six months after the show had already been out for a while.
[SPEAKER_05]: So technically it was based off of... That question is actually invalid.
[SPEAKER_02]: So our entire poll was a crock of shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: The entire poll wasn't just a crock of shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was a crock of compost.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, then why don't you take us back to reality, Miss Summers?
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, but I prefer unreality.
[SPEAKER_05]: So how about more Soul Calibur news?
[SPEAKER_05]: Soul Calibur 4 is going to be out on July 29th and there will be a regular and a premium edition.
[SPEAKER_05]: What you talk about, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_05]: Soul Calibur 3 was awesome.
[SPEAKER_00]: Drew, you could make, was it the Pope, or was it the Pope character they made, or was that in Moral Combat?
[SPEAKER_02]: The Pope was in Soul Calibur 3.
[SPEAKER_00]: So Tansel's Pope.
[SPEAKER_05]: I had a lot of friends actually make custom characters for that.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was the only thing I wanted, and I don't know if this one's going to have any customized.
[SPEAKER_00]: The Special Edition, I think, was going to have some sort of thing for that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, anyway, you're going to get your choices of different characters like Darth Vader and Yoda and a bunch of other people.
[SPEAKER_05]: And no spawn.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's okay, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: But...
[SPEAKER_05]: is of course different versions are going to have different characters like the Playstation 3 one will have Darth Vader, Xbox 360 one will have Yoda but there are but like you were saying the premium edition is going to have the extra customization content and a tournament kit and that will retail for $79.99
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, Quandary.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm getting my stimulus check, like we all are, hopefully, pretty soon, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm thinking, hmm, $600.
[SPEAKER_02]: Perfect amount to finally take the splurge and buy my damn PlayStation 3, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because you know there's going to be all this crap around Christmas time I'm going to want, including home, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: So here's the thing, is that... Here's where I'm stuck, is that I don't know whether to get Soul Calibur 3 for the PlayStation 3 or Xbox, because I do think Vader is cooler than Yoda, so I kind of want the PlayStation 3 version based on that alone, but...
[SPEAKER_02]: I know on Xbox Live, the online is going to have to be better on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there's going to be more people and there's achievements and so on.
[SPEAKER_02]: So what do I do?
[SPEAKER_02]: I know you guys are both buy in your console ownings.
[SPEAKER_02]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_02]: Xbox 360 or PlayStation 3?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to put the same question in chat.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's another mini quick poll.
[SPEAKER_02]: Only for those of you guys that own both systems, which one are you getting Soul Calibur 3 on and why, if you're buying it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Or Soul Calibur 4, what the hell?
[SPEAKER_02]: Soul Calibur 4 and why?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm thinking that we'll probably go with the Xbox 360 edition just because Yoda is comical fighting.
[SPEAKER_05]: But again, it's like you said, there's going to be more content out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Plus, I also think that the Xbox 360 controller is just a little more comfortable for a fighting game.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's just me.
[SPEAKER_00]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_00]: I wouldn't buy a system for that game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not going to buy the system for the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want the system for other stuff, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I'm just saying, if I'm going to have the system anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wouldn't buy the system until Home comes out.
[SPEAKER_00]: Trust me.
[SPEAKER_00]: Because who knows?
[SPEAKER_00]: Seriously, this summer, they may be trying to drive sales.
[SPEAKER_00]: They may drop the price again.
[SPEAKER_00]: Let me confess.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm eyeing the whole gray metal MGS4 bundle.
[SPEAKER_00]: Alright, good luck finding that.
[SPEAKER_00]: I would say, you know, I guess I could be sort of biased towards the 360, but only because you should really look at the game more than just one character, and I know that Darth Vader's cool and all, but if you want to play Darth Vader kicking ass, just buy Force Unleashed when that comes out.
[SPEAKER_00]: But, um...
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: Really, how much did you... Well, I guess, you know, Soul Calibur 2, I mean, Link was pretty popular and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: See, exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, you had to have Soul Calibur 2 on the GameCube because of Link.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hands down.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: We actually have all of those.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, let's look at the chat room, what they thought.
[SPEAKER_02]: J-Rod says, PlayStation 3 equals Vader.
[SPEAKER_02]: Vader greater than all.
[SPEAKER_02]: Black Wolf says, I'm getting the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, I have both because of Vader.
[SPEAKER_02]: J-Rod says, the only way to get more people on PlayStation Network is to buy the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: J-Rod says, Soul Calibur 4 is PlayStation 3 for me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: HitStun says you have to have Yoda versus Vader.
[SPEAKER_02]: Queltipo says 360, fuck Vader.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sephiroth1215 says the PlayStation 3 version is better for Vader and the control is much better for Soul Calibur.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jrod answered the question like five times.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's throwing me off.
[SPEAKER_02]: FootyMonster said if I get it, I'm going to go 360 because that's what I own.
[SPEAKER_02]: Plus, Yoda greater than Vader.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, I said it, bitches.
[SPEAKER_02]: And RawSteelUT says stop hating the PlayStation 3, Loki.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't hate the PS3, it's just, once again, they've got the achievement system built in already.
[SPEAKER_00]: I have more friends that are on the 360.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'll be getting exclusive games for the PS3 when those come out, just right now, if there's a game coming out on both platforms, I'm going to get it on the 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: And who's to say, like Bobby said before, who's to say that they could possibly, you know, add these as download content later on for the other systems?
[SPEAKER_02]: True.
[SPEAKER_02]: You never know.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, you know, that could be all for naught.
[SPEAKER_00]: And of course, why would they pass up the opportunity to whore out themselves a little bit and sell the characters for an extra five bucks on top of the game?
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, I could see them doing that.
[SPEAKER_00]: Especially now that we have download content available.
[SPEAKER_02]: Time will tell.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would see them, not so much the Vader-Yoda thing, but maybe bringing back classic Soul Calibur characters who maybe don't make the cut for Soul Calibur 4 or always were intended to be downloadables or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: This should be a special mode.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or what do you want to bet?
[SPEAKER_02]: If this custom creator thing is in it, that's where your download content is going to be.
[SPEAKER_02]: Download new pants.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the special mode should be the Kill Voldo mode.
[SPEAKER_02]: Again and again and again?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Again.
[SPEAKER_02]: Replace the punching bag mode with just Voldo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_02]: New game.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, one thing that you may be able to download content on for Soul Calibur 4 would be the brand new PlayStation Store.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_00]: This week, after a brief
[SPEAKER_00]: A bit of downtime.
[SPEAKER_00]: They finally brought back the PlayStation Store with its new features and stuff.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's a lot easier to browse.
[SPEAKER_00]: And then finally kind of caught up on all the content that 360 owners have had for a while including still live for Rock Band and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_00]: So definitely worth checking out.
[SPEAKER_00]: Also coming along with that is the brand new firmware 2.30 and that's live as well and
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's supposed to be enhancing DTS HD and Master High Resolution Audio.
[SPEAKER_00]: It looks a lot better.
[SPEAKER_00]: I didn't really care for the old PlayStation Store too much.
[SPEAKER_00]: I still wish that those prepaid cards are out there because that would be pretty nice so I could buy some with store credit instead of having to pony up real money for PlayStation money.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you have yet to buy anything from the new store?
[SPEAKER_00]: Uh, not yet from the new store.
[SPEAKER_00]: To be honest, I haven't plugged in my PlayStation 3 in quite a while.
[SPEAKER_00]: What?
[SPEAKER_00]: You're not helping to cure cancer even?
[SPEAKER_00]: No.
[SPEAKER_00]: Fuck cancer.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, one thing that I'm kind of surprised you haven't jumped out and downloaded, although, then again, it is kind of expensive, Gran Turismo 5 Prologue.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is now on the PSN store.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's 1.9 gigabytes to download it.
[SPEAKER_02]: 40 bucks if you want to download this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Buy the full game.
[SPEAKER_00]: At least you get a case with it.
[SPEAKER_00]: And if you stop playing it later on, you can sell it for, you know, money.
[SPEAKER_02]: The weird thing is that the intro video and the ending videos don't come with the game when you download it, but you can download them later to view, which is kind of strange.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can only get the ending video, of course, after you've beaten Gran Turismo.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a whole documentary as well, Beyond the Apex, which is apparently only on the Blu-ray version of the game, so I guess if you want a documentary, you have that as well.
[SPEAKER_00]: But seriously though, that's the only thing I could see.
[SPEAKER_00]: I know why they offered these games available to download, but if they're offering a disc version of it, I don't understand why people don't buy the disc version of the game since that's the thing.
[SPEAKER_00]: You may get tired of playing this game later on, or say for example, you want to sell it off before Gran Turismo 5 comes out.
[SPEAKER_00]: You can't do that with the download version.
[SPEAKER_00]: You have to
[SPEAKER_02]: I can think of maybe two reasons.
[SPEAKER_02]: One, convenience, especially for those that may live in the middle of nowhere where it's harder to get to a store.
[SPEAKER_02]: Your only option is like Walmart, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Two, no sales tax in some places.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if, because I know on Nintendo, if you live in California, you don't get charged sales tax on Wii Points.
[SPEAKER_02]: Same thing with Xbox.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I don't think on PlayStation, which uses real money, I don't think you get charged sales tax.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay, great.
[SPEAKER_00]: So you save a few bucks there.
[SPEAKER_00]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm just saying, though, wouldn't you rather have a case and all that stuff for it?
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: If a game came out on the Xbox Live Arcade and I had a choice of downloading it or buying it in a store, I'd buy it in a store.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's just me, I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: What about the PopCap game?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I guess those didn't come out until way later, too.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, they didn't come out until way later.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: RossDLUT is pointing out in chat, Rob, the middle of nowhere isn't going to have broadband.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess that's kind of true.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, yes and no.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think broadband's really spreading out more and more, especially as, isn't satellite in some form starting to support like a broadband-esque type of connection?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, and really, really middle of nowhere, there's always going to be a Walmart around.
[SPEAKER_00]: They pop up like Starbucks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, maybe a bad excuse, but I don't know, just trying to think.
[SPEAKER_02]: Obviously somebody's buying it or they wouldn't be putting it out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: True.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, see, I like what they did with Warhawk.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, originally they had it where you can buy the version in stores and it came with a Bluetooth headset.
[SPEAKER_00]: And that was how they kind of, you know, you can do this and get all this extra stuff or if you don't want to buy that, you can just download the version of the game.
[SPEAKER_00]: Then later on they came out with the version that's just the game only, but...
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know, it's still... I would rather buy it on disc, I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, you mentioned you and the husband got this game this week, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: I keep wanting to say Grand Theft Auto, Gran Turismo.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, Dan was playing quite a bit of it, and he had his cousin over playing it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't really watch it, because you know me, I don't really give a crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: Was it pretty?
[SPEAKER_05]: I said I didn't watch any of it, because I didn't give a crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought maybe Elise glanced at it once or twice.
[SPEAKER_05]: I looked a little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was pretty.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, see, that's what I was looking for.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you guys actually go get the box version or did you download it?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that Dan bought it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: He probably gets a discount anyway because of the whole game store connection thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Makes sense.
[SPEAKER_05]: But he was pretty happy about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, he was like... I was like, so why do you... And I straight out asked him, I was like, why did you want to pay money for a glorified demo?
[SPEAKER_05]: And he's like, well, honestly, I look at this as more of a part A, you know, sort of thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, the game comes out...
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't.
[SPEAKER_02]: PSP is still hot shit in Japan
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know why, but it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right now, in order of systems sold, number 6 is the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: PlayStation 2 is after that.
[SPEAKER_05]: PlayStation 3 is after that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wii is after that by quite a bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let me actually just go back and give the numbers.
[SPEAKER_05]: So...
[SPEAKER_05]: Xbox 360 is at $1,147 PlayStation 2 is $6,834 PlayStation 3 is $8,232 Wii is $46,296 The DS $47,158 and PSP at $85,721 if that's going to put it into perspective as far as what was sold in the past week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_05]: so just PSPs really got it now and actually I was looking through a couple of back issues of Famitsu when I was at Kinokuniya and there were plenty of PSP ads just in terms of ads there were just more and you know there's actually a couple of full just PSP only magazines so I thought that was kind of interesting Loki any thoughts on why the PSP is really taking off in Japan all of a sudden?
[SPEAKER_00]: Monster Hunter hmm
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: They like the Monster Hunter.
[SPEAKER_00]: Maybe Monster Hunter on PS3.
[SPEAKER_00]: That'd be pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_00]: Could be.
[SPEAKER_00]: Thanks for watching, and I'll see you next time.
[SPEAKER_02]: No fanboy, no siree.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not over there.
[SPEAKER_00]: Not at all.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hey, I just know a great game when I see it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not by a saw.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are you excited that it's gone gold?
[SPEAKER_02]: This means like no more delays.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's really going to happen.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's coming.
[SPEAKER_02]: What is it?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's only like a week away, right?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's the date?
[SPEAKER_02]: April 29th.
[SPEAKER_00]: See, the thing is though is I'm... Are you going to make it to the show that week?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, well, there's a few reasons.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm going to Vegas that week, actually.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_00]: To go train a certain large shoe company on how to sell games.
[SPEAKER_00]: Wait, a large shoe company?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: On how to sell games?
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: A certain website begins with Z. Okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_00]: And ends with Epos.
[SPEAKER_00]: Don't hold back.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, yeah, I get to go to Vegas.
[SPEAKER_00]: I was actually thinking about...
[SPEAKER_00]: Bringing my 360 with me to play, you know, during... Because I'm going for a day.
[SPEAKER_00]: We're actually training them on, like, different... Kind of giving them, like, the games 101 type shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sure there... I'm sure we have... I know we have listeners in Vegas.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sure there's some out there who would be like, Loki, come over.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll play.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll buy pizza and beer.
[SPEAKER_02]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_00]: But here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_00]: My boss reminded me.
[SPEAKER_00]: He's all, you know, there's going to be 360s there.
[SPEAKER_00]: So you can just bring Grand Theft Auto with you.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm like, I know, but I want to bring it...
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know if I should bring it on the plane
[SPEAKER_02]: This game rules.
[SPEAKER_02]: This game sucks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Your controller's kind of big.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think we have anything in your size.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Another series that people are pretty into.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who likes their survival horror?
[SPEAKER_05]: Me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you like the game Siren?
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: July 24th is the day it's supposed to come out, but a demo is supposed to be out very, very soon in Japan, so if you were a fan of Siren.
[SPEAKER_02]: To which Jrod in chat says, Siren is absolutely terrible.
[SPEAKER_02]: Avoid it at all costs.
[SPEAKER_00]: And they also have a big, like, Siren in the game that sounds just like the one from Silent Hill as well.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't want to say rip-off because the game, I think, was out before Silent Hill, so...
[SPEAKER_02]: Queltipo says, hooray for Siren.
[SPEAKER_02]: When nothing you do makes much sense, you just have to do it anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, what if they go back and fix all the problems and make the graphics even prettier?
[SPEAKER_02]: Would that make this game worth owning?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hey, you know, nothing's going to hurt having another survivor horror game out there.
[SPEAKER_00]: There really isn't that many.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but then you just have to keep reminding yourself, Silent Hill 5 this year.
[SPEAKER_02]: Silent Hill 5 this year.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, you hope it's this year.
[SPEAKER_00]: I hope.
[SPEAKER_02]: It better be.
[SPEAKER_02]: Especially after seeing the little preview clips for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm so freaking excited.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's bonerific.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if I'd go that far.
[SPEAKER_05]: I couldn't find the article.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: How about some different gaming news then?
[SPEAKER_05]: How about some Rock Band?
[SPEAKER_02]: Alrighty, I'll take it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, Harmonix is going to have up a downloadable album for Rock Band that's going to be available next week.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's called Screaming for Vengeance by Judas Priest.
[SPEAKER_05]: It has 10 tracks that will cost $15.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's both for PS3 and Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: Each of the songs will be $2 a piece.
[SPEAKER_05]: Later on, coming in May, there will be an album by The Cars and then Doolittle by The Pixies.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Pixies are cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it looks like they're just still working on trying to get those out.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that's kind of a neat idea.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they said, though, that they were supposed to have The Who have a first downloadable album, but they said that that's going to be later on.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's very interesting that they're going this download album route, especially in a day and age where, you know, I don't know, this is probably a bit of a controversial statement, but where music seems to be getting away from the albums.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, sad but true.
[SPEAKER_02]: We live in this iTunes world now where it's very easy to buy the one song that you like, and a lot of people don't ever take the time to listen to the entire album.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I find it kind of interesting the rock band is kind of going this route where they're standing behind the albums in a way, you know?
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess when you think about, well, in the classics, that's when the albums were really albums.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe it's not so surprising.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you know, and I also think that it's sad that we really don't have albums as a big format anymore just because from an artistic point of view, keep in mind what all went into making an album, you know, with your cover and everything and you had all the publishing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that actually is sort of a...
[SPEAKER_05]: A neat thing as far as its nostalgic value.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_02]: Looking at chat comments.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hitstuns in chat.orangelunchradio.com says, When I download stuff, I get the whole album.
[SPEAKER_02]: J-Rod says, Rock band needs more modern metal.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actdeft says, I'm an iTunes boy living in an iTunes world.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sephiroth1215 says, I'm waiting for Nevermind to come out.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll get the whole album for that.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be classic, classic rock, especially for this generation.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, that early 90s stuff is really the defining classic rock.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're getting old.
[SPEAKER_02]: We ain't getting any younger.
[SPEAKER_02]: But hey, while we age, we have a lot of new games and things coming out around the world to look forward to, so let's do some release dates.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes, this week, actually, there's going to be something pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, about a week from now, there'll be something pretty cool, because it's going to be coming out on Sunday.
[SPEAKER_00]: Mario Kart Wii, finally coming out in the U.S., so you can take a look at that.
[SPEAKER_00]: Very good game.
[SPEAKER_00]: Let's see, other things coming out other than Mario Kart Wii...
[SPEAKER_00]: There is a game actually also on the Wii, little known, Heavenly Guardian.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's a pretty cheap game, and it's kind of like a side-scroller shooter game, so that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's also NBA Ballers Chosen One, which is coming out this week on PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360, kind of a one-on-one, two-on-two basketball game.
[SPEAKER_00]: Let's see, there's also...
[SPEAKER_00]: RiverKingMysticValley
[SPEAKER_00]: and that's like a fishing game, fishing RPG.
[SPEAKER_00]: I guess it's what Harvest Moon is to farming, this is to fishing.
[SPEAKER_00]: Battle of the Bands coming out on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's that music game that doesn't require instruments but you have different mashups of music genres in there.
[SPEAKER_00]: This is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: Wild Earth African Safari.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's the Pokemon Snap type of game that's for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's the Africa before Africa.
[SPEAKER_00]: The World Ends With You James Bond
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that came up on last week's show.
[SPEAKER_02]: We were talking about The World Ends With You.
[SPEAKER_02]: James Bond.
[SPEAKER_02]: This totally sounds like a Bond.
[SPEAKER_00]: This game you may want to skip.
[SPEAKER_00]: Target Terror by Konami.
[SPEAKER_00]: Apparently one of the ugliest games for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_00]: This is a game that came out of the arcades circa 1990s with wonderful mocap technology.
[SPEAKER_00]: Kind of think of like Area 51 and Maximum Force type things.
[SPEAKER_00]: Chameleon on PSP Shin Megami Tensei Persona 3 FES Dream Pinball 3D
[SPEAKER_00]: Lineage 2, Call of Duty 4, and I believe that's actually it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yep, that is it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jonathan F. in chat just said something I've been wondering about for the longest time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fantasy Star Universe, Ambition of the Illuminous, Max Attack G begins, I guess, this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Play the old PSO stages in PSU.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's like the whole reason I downloaded Ambition of the Illuminous, not realizing they weren't there yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, God, I hope you can do that at low level.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hope I don't have to level, like, 100 to play them.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I will if I have to.
[SPEAKER_02]: I miss caves that much.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who doesn't miss caves and those damn little plants that kept paralyzing you all the time?
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow, traveling to Japan and looking at some of the releases over there.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you're a war fan, hey, Xbox 360 is where it's at this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: On April 24th, Frontline's Fuel of War and Tom Clancy's Rainbow Six Vegas 2 both come out in Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if you like those war shooting tech games, you might have fun with that.
[SPEAKER_02]: In PlayStation 3, Senjo no Valkyria comes out as well from Sega this week in Japan, as well as another version of Rainbow Six Vegas, except that's just a price reduction on the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Trying to figure out what this Valkyrie game is here.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's actually a game that we're getting over here in the fall.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a turn-based RPG.
[SPEAKER_02]: It combines strategy with action, and you proceed in the game like it's a history book.
[SPEAKER_05]: Valkyrie Profile
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's like you make history.
[SPEAKER_02]: That sounds kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, coming out on other systems, going over to the Nintendo Wii coming out this week, the white GameCube controller we talked about last week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also coming out, Osuji Sentai Clean Keeper.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_00]: That's like a weird Captain Planet thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wait, hold on.
[SPEAKER_02]: The fairy mentions that there is a queen of pollution in school seeking to bring the school down by dirtying it and the only way to stop her is to form the Clean Keeper Squad by rescuing all the cleaning fairies and finding the girls who can see and bond with these fairies.
[SPEAKER_00]: This game sounds badass.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think you have to capture girls and clean them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Osuji Sentai Clean Keeper H2O Edelbloom
[SPEAKER_02]: Prism Arc Awake also comes out.
[SPEAKER_02]: And lots of other games get price reductions.
[SPEAKER_02]: Furayaki, Everybody's Golf 4, and Rim Runners gets a price reduction.
[SPEAKER_02]: I swear to God, that's the name of a game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rim Rummers.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're so immature.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: Days of Memories 2, Ako de Pon, Ikisama Horiyuki, Puzzle Mate, Summon Night,
[SPEAKER_02]: This is a big week for DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yataman DS, Bikiriori Dokiri Daisukisen de Koron.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's sort of part of the charm of this segment is getting to hear me butcher such Japanese names.
[SPEAKER_02]: How about PSP?
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see real quick if there's anything on PSP to match the amount of stuff coming out on DS this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, there is quite a bit this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: A lot of it's movies.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like I Am Legend you can finally pick up.
[SPEAKER_02]: SNK Arcade Classics Volume 1 makes its way to Asia.
[SPEAKER_02]: How about Vampire Chronicle gets a price reduction?
[SPEAKER_02]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's release dates for Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's move over to Europe.
[SPEAKER_05]: NBA Ballers, Chosen One on the 25th for Xbox 360, Nitro Bike on PS2, Turok, PDC World Championship, Dart 2008, SingStar Summer Party, Wii Fit, that's good, and Grand Theft Auto 4 on the 29th.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Barf!
[SPEAKER_00]: On the Genesis, we get a cool RPG, Fancy Star 3 Generations of Doom.
[SPEAKER_00]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: But they do have as downloadable content as we found out this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: The five bonus songs on the Wii are just download songs from the other systems.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dirty Little Secret by the All-American Rejects, Don't Look Back in Anger by Oasis, Rome by the B-52s, Rockaway Beach by the Ramones, and you don't have to turn out the red light for Roxanne by the police.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good songs!
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually own two of those five as download songs, and I don't even own that many songs.
[SPEAKER_02]: But...
[SPEAKER_02]: A little bit disappointing to some that they are just simply download songs from the other systems, but they will be right there on the Wii disc to offset the fact that you won't be able to download anything else for now, for a while.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, we've got a whole bunch of downloadable content for the week.
[SPEAKER_05]: For Xbox Live Arcade, Rocky and Bullwinkle for 800 points, Battlezone for 400 points, Demo Zone, Xbox Live Marketplace, Universal War, Earth Assault, and Condemned 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's not for Germany.
[SPEAKER_05]: Game Content, Samurai Warriors 2 Extreme Legends Expansion, 2400 Microsoft Points, Halo 3 Legendary Map Pack, and a theme that goes with it, 800 points, and Kanan Lynch the Dope Bag for free.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's actually...
[SPEAKER_05]: in the UK, sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: For US, we have a lot of stuff for Karaoke Revolution Presents American Idol, Rock Band Saints of Los Angeles by Motley Crue, Call Me by Blondie, Simple Man by Lynyrd Skynyrd, Message in a Bottle by The Police.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have a classic rock pack that has Call Me, Simple Man, and Message in a Bottle, and a video for No Country for Old Men.
[SPEAKER_05]: for the PlayStation Store.
[SPEAKER_05]: Again, this is in the UK.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sega Superstars Tennis.
[SPEAKER_05]: For content, there's Warhawk Broken Mirror Pack, Super Stardust HD Solo Add-On, Guitar Hero 3 Dropkick Murphy Song Pack, which is free.
[SPEAKER_05]: Layer Deadly Dragons Pack for free, Metal Gear Online Beta Client for free.
[SPEAKER_05]: For the US, there's Gran Turismo 5 Prologue, which is 40 bucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have UEFA Euro 2008 as a demo.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then we also have the Warhawk Broken Mirror Pack, Booster Combo Broken Mirror and Omega Dawn.
[SPEAKER_05]: Super Stardust HD Solo add-on, Laird, Deadly Dragons Pack, Rock Band Downloads, Still Alive, Sprode by Freeze Pop, Shake by Count Zero, Rock Rebellion by Ben Camero, the Harmonix Pack, which is Sprode, Shake, and Rock Rebellion, Call Me, Simple Man, Message in a Bottle, and the Classic Rock Pack.
[SPEAKER_05]: For Virtual Console in the UK, they got Phantasy Star 3 Generations of Doom, which is a Mega Drive game for 800 Wii Points.
[SPEAKER_05]: In US and Canada, we got Phantasy Zone for Master System,
[SPEAKER_05]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_05]: And MegaTurrican.
[SPEAKER_05]: For PC, a demo of Kung Fu Panda came out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whatever Kung Fu Panda is.
[SPEAKER_00]: Sounds pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_00]: Kung Fu Panda?
[SPEAKER_00]: That's based on the Jack Black film, I think.
[SPEAKER_05]: Steam brought out Rainbow Six Vegas 2 Trackmania United which gives free access to Trackmania United Forever and Trackmania United Forever was also free well the Trackmania United was 40 bucks Metabolite Ultimate Collection Juice 2 Hot Import Nights, Exo Cubes Essential Collection Heroes of Might and Magic 5 that be all are
[SPEAKER_02]: Damn you, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now I have Message in a Bottle stuck in my head.
[SPEAKER_02]: Message in a Bottle.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is my favorite police song ever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ever.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the ferret agrees too.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was not Message in a Bottle.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was gibberish.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was gibberish and a ferret.
[SPEAKER_00]: Alright, so we know that Mario Kart is already out now in Japan and Europe.
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_00]: and it's another, not really a game but a UMD video Bokudaki no Kajitsu and that actually translates to Only My Fruit and it's an erotic like hentai UMD video or game or something so that's kind of funny erotic PSP game beats out Mario Kart Wii if only they had more jubblies in Mario Kart Wii maybe
[SPEAKER_02]: Nintendo is, uh, sending out an SOS about right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Seriously, how to get beaten by porn.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, is this like something that's really, really popular in Japan or something?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, Akihabara.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wait, but this is only one store's chart, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: This isn't like the whole country's chart.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is Akihabara.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, so maybe it's a little bit much to say that OMG, Mario Kart Wii gets its butt kicked by porn in the entirety of Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it's just one store.
[SPEAKER_02]: And maybe this is the only store where you can buy this particular game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sort of like how here, you know, Walmarts and Targets don't carry certain games, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, maybe.
[SPEAKER_00]: If they only carried more porn games, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, it's only announced for Japan right now, but if this sells over in Japan, I don't see why they wouldn't bring this over here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like I said, Resident Evil 4, we didn't do too bad, so why the hell not?
[SPEAKER_02]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, there has been an ESRB game rating released because of blood and fantasy violence, and it's set for something on the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can we guess what that is?
[SPEAKER_02]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_05]: Castlevania Order of Ecclesia All games have fantasy violence But the best ones have real violence
[SPEAKER_05]: None of them have real violence.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's all fantasy.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's all you perceiving one character beating up another, but it's just fucking data.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what, though?
[SPEAKER_02]: Whattheyplay.com Snap will have real violence.
[SPEAKER_05]: But will it blend?
[SPEAKER_02]: We hope.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know if it'll blend since it's an idea.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't think you can get ideas into a blender.
[SPEAKER_00]: Just yet.
[SPEAKER_00]: Maybe a new blender with idea blending capabilities.
[SPEAKER_00]: You never know.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know if this will blend.
[SPEAKER_00]: It may blend on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_00]: But apparently Namco has announced another, yes, there is actually another already, cheerleader game for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's called Wii Cheer.
[SPEAKER_00]: It features...
[SPEAKER_00]: and cartoony cheerleaders jumping around and stuff.
[SPEAKER_00]: And you apparently use the game, each one of your pom-poms, I guess, in the game is actually a Wii remote.
[SPEAKER_00]: So you use two Wii remotes and kind of think like a Wii version of yet another cheering game, Oh and Done, or Elite Beat Agents.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's kind of like that is how you play the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would be interested in this if they had just called it Bring It On, the game.
[SPEAKER_00]: and it forces you to use spirit fingers spirit fingers that movie was was incredible I don't know that's the only way you're allowed to finish that sentence don't get me wrong this is this is like I guess a cool idea for girls because um the video the trailer showed girls playing this game why's it gotta be an only a girl game huh
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, because they showed little girls playing the game.
[SPEAKER_00]: Do you want to play a game that little girls play?
[SPEAKER_00]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: This is kind of... I don't think I can play this game.
[SPEAKER_00]: I would feel dirty playing this game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, I got to look at some of this trailer.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, little girls dancing and happy.
[SPEAKER_02]: This makes horrible radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: They butcher the songs, by the way.
[SPEAKER_02]: So they're probably going to be all horrible cover versions.
[SPEAKER_02]: Create your own cheerleader.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jamie, custom mode.
[SPEAKER_02]: Look at that.
[SPEAKER_02]: You like that, don't you?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'd probably make a cheerleader.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll end the torture for our chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Killer or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: They look like they're all having fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what games are all about, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because they're paid to look like they're having fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: What was the game called again?
[SPEAKER_02]: We cheer.
[SPEAKER_05]: We cheer.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just like we ski.
[SPEAKER_02]: We starve ourselves to fit in the outfit.
[SPEAKER_00]: They do kind of look like they have starved themselves.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're children.
[SPEAKER_02]: Be nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're children on TV.
[SPEAKER_00]: Then they'll have the, you know, we need to get to Dallas, the WDS Dallas sequel for the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fireboma says Sky sold as soon as he hears that song.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is a good song.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who doesn't like that song?
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't it feel good?
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually am really annoyed by that song.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, poop on you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry, Debbie Downer.
[SPEAKER_02]: Channel Z says they show a boy playing at the end of the WeCheer video.
[SPEAKER_05]: Boys can be cheerleaders.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_02]: Smart boys are cheerleaders.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know why?
[SPEAKER_02]: Why?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because they get to put their hands up the girls' skirts all day long.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Touche.
[SPEAKER_02]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: How can you respond to that?
[SPEAKER_02]: You can't.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you saw Bring It On, you'd know this.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was the gay cheerleader who was, you know, cheerleading because he was gay.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then there was the cheerleader who was, you know, just there to hit on all the women.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, that's the thing.
[SPEAKER_00]: He can hit on all the women, but he ain't going to get any of them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's look at another game here.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Okami on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the funny thing about Okami on the Wii is that...
[SPEAKER_02]: I.G.N.
[SPEAKER_02]: In other words, Capcom lifted the IGN art from the website or whatever to make the Wii box art for Okami.
[SPEAKER_00]: Isn't that funny?
[SPEAKER_02]: They stole their own artwork from a website.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that's really funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_02]: and apparently it's legit.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can go look at a box for this game and it's there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if they'll be able to fix it at one point but at some point later but apparently the press releases that have gone out already have this on there.
[SPEAKER_02]: People have confirmed it.
[SPEAKER_02]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Frisbee in chat says Capcom googled their own box art.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently they did.
[SPEAKER_02]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Someone's getting fired.
[SPEAKER_02]: Someone totally got fired.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ha ha ha.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, we're about ready to take a break here and go from Part A to Part B, but first, it just would not be an Orange Launch Radio Part A if we did not pay tribute to video game classics.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we do that with a little segment here on the show called our Classic Video Game of the Week.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura goes through her vast archives of video games and picks out one classic for you all to pay respect to.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's it going to be this week, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_02]: Strider.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bitches better recognize.
[SPEAKER_05]: And unfortunately, the only copy of the first level that I could find was the Genesis version.
[SPEAKER_05]: However, this was one of the first of their eight meg titles that they brought out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, you can't start it past where the music was.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wait, do I need to start at the very beginning?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah!
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, right there.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is classic.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, um, this is the game that actually in Japan was called Strider Yu-Yu, and it gave us the character from Marvel vs. Capcom, but basically it's a platformer, and it's actually very interesting because all of the in-between areas...
[SPEAKER_05]: are basically the characters speaking their native languages, but they're speaking them to each other and can apparently understand everybody else.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess they have translators in the future like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you go through different levels, and the first one starts off, you have to fight this guy called Grandmaster Mayo, and you're going through different areas, like you start off in the Soviet Union, the next one is, I think the next level is in Siberia,
[SPEAKER_05]: You have the Amazon Rainforest, you've got a big platform in space, and actually this is my favorite level to do because as you're going through that, you are on the ground and then gravity reverses and you're in other areas and then you have to fight this thing that you move in a circle around.
[SPEAKER_05]: But his weapon is called a cipher, which is like a swinging tonfa-style blade, but as you get power-ups, it'll extend further, and he'll get his little mechanical animal buddies to help him out, like a falcon, and a big saber-toothed tiger, and his little things that... Okay, I don't think they actually got names until Marvel vs. Capcom came out, but the little tiny things were called Ouroboros, but that was also one of the bosses of the game, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, okay, the stages in this was, um, St.
[SPEAKER_05]: Petersburg, um, the Siberian Wilderness, the Aerial Battleship, um, Amazon, and, um, the Third Moon.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was just a really kind of an epic sort of game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, the thing about the, um, in-between areas is that, like, um...
[SPEAKER_05]: For example, after you fight, there's the area where you fight three girls as the bosses, and one of them is Pompu, who was also one of the helper characters in Marvel vs. Capcom, but she speaks Chinese.
[SPEAKER_05]: The bounty hunter guy speaks English.
[SPEAKER_05]: I see they didn't do it on the...
[SPEAKER_05]: on the Genesis one, the arcade one.
[SPEAKER_05]: It also, there were other versions that came out, like the one that we were listening to was the Genesis one, but it's been on the Amiga, the Amstrad CPC, Atari ST, Commodore 64, ZX Spectrum, and there's been a Master System version and a Sharp X68000 version.
[SPEAKER_05]: There was...
[SPEAKER_05]: We actually have a burn of this, the version that was going to be Super Graphics CD.
[SPEAKER_05]: We actually have a copy of the proto for it, but we don't have the arcade card to play it with.
[SPEAKER_05]: I will tell people that there is a Nintendo version.
[SPEAKER_05]: However, just to let people know, that was actually based off of the Strider comics that came out in Japan and is not anything like...
[SPEAKER_02]: It's very interesting because when I, you know, I didn't have a Genesis growing up, we only had a Nintendo, but I do remember Strider on the Nintendo, and I love that game, but it is completely different than this game.
[SPEAKER_02]: This game is more of like a platformer, whereas Strider on the NES was a bit more like adventure.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it was a bit more Bionic Commando, and that fucking triangle jump made me want to kill people.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, I mean, it's so interesting that you have both games that were Strider, yet they were so completely freaking different.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is very interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, part of the reason with this was they were actually going to leave out the, um, as far as I'm aware, now this is coming from my husband, and for anyone who kept up on older video game sites, my husband used to run one called Neo Strider Strider Zone.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I did all, I, you know, fixed all of his graphics on it for him.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, um...
[SPEAKER_05]: Dan is full of Strider trivia.
[SPEAKER_05]: When they were first going to bring it out on Genesis slash Mega Drive, there wasn't enough memory to accommodate the full game.
[SPEAKER_05]: They were going to leave out the Amazon level and ended up just creating their 8MB cartridges to...
[SPEAKER_05]: And I have to say, it's pretty damn close to arcade perfect.
[SPEAKER_05]: Journey from Darkness, Strider Returns
[SPEAKER_05]: and, um, a lot, it plays basically just like Striders, a lot of the same type of game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, it did get a really good sequel called Strider 2, which was really freaking good, um, but that'll be touched on at a later date.
[SPEAKER_02]: So Strider 2 is different than Strider Returns?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, Strider Returns was more of a... It was just awful.
[SPEAKER_05]: In fact, the story that it brought up was actually retconned because of Strider 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: The real Strider 2 that came out.
[SPEAKER_05]: and the one that came out was, I think, a worthy sequel.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, that's the Amazon level.
[SPEAKER_05]: When you fight the girls that... This is someone doing a speedrun of the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: They use the emulator cheats, though, but it's a speedrun in seven and a half minutes.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's fighting the half-naked Amazon ladies.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hot.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, well, there you have it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Your classic game of the week, Strider, for the arcade and the Genesis or Mega Drive, whatever region you happen to live in.
[SPEAKER_02]: Check it out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Respect the Classics.
[SPEAKER_05]: that had the NES version of Strider, Bionic Commando, and Mighty Final Fight.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's also another way that people can check it out.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, very cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: And besides that, Mighty Final Fight is just fun, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it's kind of silly fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's basically chibi Final Fight.
[SPEAKER_02]: At least it had Guy in it, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: It did, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's why I had Final Fight Guy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, we're going to go ahead and take a break here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Plenty more to come in Part B tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to talk about some more Grand Theft Auto news.
[SPEAKER_02]: Can you believe it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Lots of stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Talking about Bionic Commando rearmed a little bit as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: And somebody dared to say that Wii games look like crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who would have thought?
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll talk all about that in Part B right after a quick break.
[SPEAKER_02]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and is podcast to the world twice a week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Stay tuned to our podcast feed for the conclusion of this week's Orange Lounge Radio.