[SPEAKER_06]: Tonight, we say goodbye to Live365, we say hello to AllGames.com, and as always, we make fun of the latest in gaming news.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hello everybody and welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: We are that podcast on the internet dedicated to video games, video gaming, gaming culture, and the gamer lifestyle.
[SPEAKER_06]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_06]: Joining me as always, say hello to the one and only DarkSakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_06]: How are you doing?
[SPEAKER_01]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm doing okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good.
[SPEAKER_06]: Say hello as well to TechMasterLoki.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_06]: How are you doing?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm doing okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm glad to hear you're okay and not crappy
[SPEAKER_06]: And no one's here.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't want to say goodbye.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know what I want to say?
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_01]: Fuck you!
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I sent the official cancellation notice today, so there's no turning back now.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a done deal.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're bastards.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: They shouldn't have upped the rates.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, oh well.
[SPEAKER_06]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_06]: Dark Tetsuya Episode 1
[SPEAKER_06]: Ragnarokan
[SPEAKER_01]: As usual, and we have started working on cleaning up the pinball machines because Dan's having a pinball party next Sunday.
[SPEAKER_06]: That sounds like fun, a pinball party, huh?
[SPEAKER_01]: We're having a bunch of people over the house, it's like everybody wants to meet you.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's like, well, too bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: What exactly happens at a pinball party?
[SPEAKER_01]: Pizza and pinball.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: That sounds pretty good.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then people talk about their collections and stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's just like, look how pretty my pinball tables are.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are people actually going to bring pinball tables over?
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, I was going to say they're not very portable.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, but we have plenty, I think.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, here's my question.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you going to have not just the pinball machines, but maybe like Pinball FX on the TV on Xbox Live?
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what you can do on Life 365?
[SPEAKER_06]: Shit, you can do shit.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was going to suggest that he hook up the Nintendo and put in Pinbot.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ah, there you go.
[SPEAKER_01]: and maybe we can hook up the TurboGrafx and put in Devil's Crush.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, good idea.
[SPEAKER_01]: And he picked up one of those classic collections too, like the whatever super awesome of pinball.
[SPEAKER_01]: And to ShadowScyler, I play on Essence RO, but you won't ever find me.
[SPEAKER_01]: I haven't made the guild yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: How about Sonic Spinball?
[SPEAKER_01]: I could do that.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've got Sonic Spinball.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because that was a very strange pinball game.
[SPEAKER_01]: it reminded me of that part of Casino Night where I'd get stuck and get pissed off
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, which server do you Ragnarok on?
[SPEAKER_01]: That's what I answered.
[SPEAKER_01]: I said that I play on the Essence server.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sorry, I was on crack.
[SPEAKER_06]: Kanti says, how many pinball machines does DarkSakura have?
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, now I have to think about which ones are actually mine because we're holding some for some people.
[SPEAKER_01]: So the ones that we're holding is a Brite of Pinbot, an Indiana Jones that Dan is shopping out.
[SPEAKER_01]: We are holding a Back to the Future and a Black Knight, not Black Knight 2000.
[SPEAKER_01]: I wish I had that one.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then...
[SPEAKER_01]: Star Trek The Next Generation, No Fear, Twilight Zone, Simpsons Pinball Party, Creature from the Black Lagoon, and my machine, World Cup Soccer 94.
[SPEAKER_01]: Did I say Twilight Zone?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, we have Twilight Zone.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: It seems like things have changed a lot since the last time even I was over there.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's crazy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, so Loki, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_06]: As he sits down, ready to go.
[SPEAKER_07]: My gaming week was pretty brief.
[SPEAKER_07]: I played pretty much just Saints Row this entire week, I think.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it's finished now, so that's good.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, well, I'm still not 100% in the game because I have to do all the damn activities, and some of them are fucking impossible, but
[SPEAKER_07]: As far as the story goes, I'm done.
[SPEAKER_07]: Never knew what the ending was anyway, so.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I'm glad I'm done so I can start Saints Row 2 when that comes out and Grand Theft Auto 4 and all that fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow, that's a relatively short week for you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I played a lot of Saints Row.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, we played the death matches during lunch.
[SPEAKER_07]: I had a funny moment where I was driving on the sky in Saints Row because the game is a little glitchy sometimes.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that was fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: And...
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know, that's about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's stupid, but funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: One of those stupid, funny things.
[SPEAKER_06]: So obviously, don't take that too seriously.
[SPEAKER_06]: The game takes a minute and a half to beat.
[SPEAKER_06]: Besides that, really not a lot.
[SPEAKER_06]: I played Mr. Driller for like 10 minutes.
[SPEAKER_06]: The new one on Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, yeah, I was a little bit disappointed.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was kind of like, I wonder what version they ported because I was surprised to see, and maybe it's just because it's the mechanics of the game or whatever, but I was surprised to see that the playing field was only a really small portion of the screen.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know if maybe that's to support the multiplayer or what have you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did you get to play online?
[SPEAKER_06]: Which is probably a lot more fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I'm completely basing my judgment off the demo.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't play a lot of games this week, but I have a valid excuse.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll talk about this real quick because a lot of people have been asking.
[SPEAKER_06]: The reason why Part B went up on Saturday this week, which is extremely late for Part B to go up.
[SPEAKER_06]: We tried to get it up on Wednesday, like Thursday at the absolute latest.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've got something going on.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was in the hospital for three days this week, and it was mentioned on OrangeLunchRadio.com, you probably saw that, and obviously I'm here, so I'm fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know how much I've mentioned it on the live show, but I've been having abdominal pains on and off for the past three weeks.
[SPEAKER_06]: and finally it kind of reached a head on Wednesday.
[SPEAKER_06]: I got woken up by some horrendous chest pain and it was like alien is going to pop out of my chest bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I finally just went to the ER.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was kind of getting the run around from my doctors.
[SPEAKER_06]: They had diagnosed me with pancreatitis but didn't seem to be doing much about it and finally I had to go to the hospital.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that's where I spent about three days pretty much because what I had was acute pancreatitis.
[SPEAKER_06]: Basically, my pancreas is fucked up and it was producing too much of a certain chemical and it makes it really painful to eat fatty foods.
[SPEAKER_06]: It most commonly happens, funny enough, it most commonly happens in luscious, people who drink a lot, alcoholics.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like 80% of the cases are alcoholics.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, while I enjoy the occasional beverage and I talk about it here on this program, I would say drinking one, maybe two drinks a week does not make me an alcoholic.
[SPEAKER_06]: So alcohol didn't cause it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And being fat didn't cause it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought that maybe the fact that I ate out a lot and all that stuff might have caused me to go to the hospital, but that wasn't it either.
[SPEAKER_06]: My triglycerides were too low for that to be the case.
[SPEAKER_06]: So...
[SPEAKER_06]: That was not the case either.
[SPEAKER_06]: So they don't know what caused it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And now the thing is that, and I don't want to be into too much of a downer syndrome or whatever, but folks have been asking.
[SPEAKER_06]: The weird thing is that they did a CAT scan, they did an MRI and all this shit on me in the hospital.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have some type of cyst on my pancreas, apparently, and
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank God it's not cancer, says the doctor.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I don't mean to bring the show down, but that's basically where I was all week, and since folks have been asking, that's what's up.
[SPEAKER_06]: I find the toughest part of all of it is, A, the fact that I didn't do anything to cause it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's one of those cases where really they don't know what caused it.
[SPEAKER_06]: They think it could be an allergy to the medication I took, although if that's the case, I will be one of the first documented cases of that kind of allergy, like ever, to this antibiotic I took.
[SPEAKER_01]: They also say that stress is a cause.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm not that stressed out, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: Things are pretty good in my life right now, all things considered.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sure, the Life 365 thing sucks, but it's not going to cause me to go to the hospital bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_06]: So I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's really bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, yeah, my only thing is I'm always afraid it's going to come back.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I've lost a crazy amount of weight.
[SPEAKER_06]: In the past month, I've lost 21 pounds.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, to put it, and you probably notice if you're on Justin.TV because my pants, like, won't stay on.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's kind of sexy.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, I'll stop being such a downer now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey guys, coming in clearly I hope?
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Introduce yourself.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Drew Nami, of course.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's Drew Nami.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you were here episode one, weren't you?
[SPEAKER_05]: I was not here episode one.
[SPEAKER_06]: But you were listening episode one, and now you're here for the last show on Live 365.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, not the last, last show.
[SPEAKER_05]: I remember episode one, I was listening from New York.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ah.
[SPEAKER_06]: So how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to get that mic a little closer to you while you talk about your gaming week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, you move a little closer.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know what happened to Irene, so we'll wait for her later.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I've been on my wild methadone.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's so exciting about the most recent Guild Wars expansion?
[SPEAKER_05]: and you get a whole bunch of new missions, new skills, basically new everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it all leads into... Yeah, they're still saying you're really quiet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Go ahead and just pick up the mic.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just hold it away.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's away from your mouth.
[SPEAKER_06]: Live radio, folks.
[SPEAKER_06]: It happens.
[SPEAKER_01]: Did you play on April 1st?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, did you play on April 1st and everyone was a stick figure?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I played on April 1st.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I think the reason why it wasn't picking me up was because the mic was off.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, how convenient!
[SPEAKER_05]: That might have been the problem.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, but it's on now.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're good.
[SPEAKER_06]: So anything else in your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_05]: I've actually been participating in one of the X-Fire events for Grand Chase.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently there's still an open beta and they want people to test it out, so they're doing in-game contests and such.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's kind of like Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_05]: meets MapleStory, if you can even ponder that as possible.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you going to miss Live 365?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I am going to miss Live 365.
[SPEAKER_06]: What are you going to miss most about it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Pretty much listening to 24-7 Station while playing WoW, but both of those are going to be gone.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're ditching WoW too?
[SPEAKER_05]: I stopped playing WoW back in October.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, in favor of Guild Wars?
[SPEAKER_05]: In favor of having money.
[SPEAKER_06]: I ran out of money.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ah, I gotcha.
[SPEAKER_06]: WoW is one of the, you know, WoW is an expensive habit.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll probably join back up with the new expansion, but... There are ways to play for free.
[SPEAKER_05]: There are ways to play for free, but they all suck.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hacksaw servers.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't imagine they're fun at all.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not that, but yeah, there are ways to pay for free.
[SPEAKER_07]: Lays 2600.
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: You could steal prepaid cards from the store.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, on the 2600.
[SPEAKER_05]: On the 2600.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, you... No, I hate April Fools.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can move in a total of eight directions.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I meant in the latest magazine of the 2600.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, 2600 magazine.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, that 2600.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, not the Atari 2600.
[SPEAKER_07]: I thought you were talking about this stupid prank.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, it's something that has to do with PayPal and crap, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: Interesting, but you have to do it every time you play it, so that's annoying.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love, though, that you have the Horde symbol on your laptop.
[SPEAKER_06]: That always makes me giddy.
[SPEAKER_05]: I dug this up from some of my old stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: I never expected you had a laptop by the time I got this.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hope they can see that on Justin TV, our little... All right, awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, turn that mic off when we're not using it, because it makes a lot of clicky-clicky noises.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, what the hell?
[SPEAKER_06]: My mic is on crack.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, well, I think that's going to do it for everybody's gaming week.
[SPEAKER_06]: So let's talk a little bit about housekeeping.
[SPEAKER_06]: Really, the only thing on deck is that there is the all games move pending.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's going to start on April the 13th.
[SPEAKER_06]: Love this, by the way.
[SPEAKER_06]: Allgames.com is rolling out the red carpet for us.
[SPEAKER_06]: We love them.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're being great.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's actually a little countdown clock on allgames.com that says it counts down the days and hours and minutes until OLR comes exclusively to their station.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to be great.
[SPEAKER_06]: So look for us there.
[SPEAKER_06]: The plug will be pulled on Live 365 on the 12th.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll be taking the horse out to the barn and shooting it on Saturday.
[SPEAKER_01]: They will become glue.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know we make fun of it here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Even some folks in chat were commenting earlier like, boy, they sure sound like they're going to miss the 24-7 feed.
[SPEAKER_06]: We are.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to miss it.
[SPEAKER_06]: But at the same time, you know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's kind of like one of the songs in the pre-show tonight, which had a very tongue-in-cheek theme tonight if you were listening to our little pre-show music.
[SPEAKER_06]: A change will do you good.
[SPEAKER_06]: So this is going to be something new for us.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to be fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that's that.
[SPEAKER_06]: uh Zappy says will there be punch at the plug pulling punch and pat punch and pat but not alcoholic punch because I don't want to go back to the hospital with more pancreatitis please not that
[SPEAKER_06]: So we're excited though about AllGames.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: I still don't have the final word for you on Travis and DMN and all that, but if I had a Magic 8-Ball and I shook it, it would say Outlook looks good.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're probably going to come over a little later than us, but we'll be there on Sunday the 13th.
[SPEAKER_06]: Excited.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Enough housekeeping.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's get into gaming news that we can taunt and make fun of.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, so this is pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's been rumored to be happening, but finally official now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sam and Max are coming to the Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, of course, it's being brought to us in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_07]: by Dreamcatcher and, of course, the Adventure Company.
[SPEAKER_07]: And in Europe, Joe Wood, of course, is publishing it there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not really any word on what exactly it will include.
[SPEAKER_07]: Probably, you know, a lot of the episodes that we saw on the PC...
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't know if maybe it's a compilation of Season 1, maybe something like Season 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe it's even like... No, it's not going to have download content on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's pretty awesome, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, glad to be able to play some Salmon Max since I don't use GameTap.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or want to buy software.
[SPEAKER_06]: And so that's going to be going to WiiWare?
[SPEAKER_07]: I think that's actually going to be going to the Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, so it's not WiiWare.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I remember there was a rumor a while back that it was going to go to WiiWare.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess they could do it that way, but I don't think they would.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it'd just be, you know, maybe like the first season or something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that would be, I mean, if they package all the games together into like one, because the games themselves are only like three to four hours long, but if they package, you know, the entire first season, which was like eight episodes, I want to say?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't remember off the top of my head.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe they could do the first and second season or something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: That would be good.
[SPEAKER_06]: That would be a great deal because that would be, you know, you'd probably have like at least 15 episodes all together in one place.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that would be a pretty good deal.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought I had it turned on and pointed at me.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm probably going to play it, if I don't have to buy it.
[SPEAKER_06]: BlackWolf says the first season is 6 episodes and the second season is 5 episodes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Still, that's not a bad deal.
[SPEAKER_06]: for 11 episodes.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's going to be a 30-40 hour game.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the size of most games.
[SPEAKER_06]: That'll be a good deal.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is also going to be a good deal.
[SPEAKER_06]: It would be a Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_06]: Brawl sequel.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's also kind of a duh.
[SPEAKER_06]: but at the same time, it would be interesting if a Brawl sequel came to the Wii because if you think about the previous Nintendo consoles, they only had one Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_06]: game apiece.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nintendo 64 had that Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_06]: game, which I want to say was originally developed for the Super Nintendo but was brought over to the 64 when the console life switched up a little bit.
[SPEAKER_06]: and then the GameCube had one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now the Wii has its one.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it would be kind of weird if there was a second one on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think Nintendo plans to move away from the Wii anytime soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it would be kind of interesting if we got a sequel.
[SPEAKER_06]: What is the basis for this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, Nintendo is, in one of their latest surveys, they do these surveys all the time on their website, they're asking a question about how likely would you be to buy a sequel to Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_06]: Brawl on a scale of 1 to 7?
[SPEAKER_06]: One being I wouldn't buy it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Seven being I'd buy it in a heartbeat.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sure most people are saying seven, seven, seven.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know many people who wouldn't say seven.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it would be interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: What else can they do with Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_06]: Brawl?
[SPEAKER_06]: A DS version?
[SPEAKER_06]: Ah, there you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: I bet that's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I bet that's exactly what they're going to do.
[SPEAKER_06]: I bet it'll be a DS version.
[SPEAKER_06]: You think if there was a DS version it would be just a dumbed down same version you kind of have on the Wii now?
[SPEAKER_06]: Or do you think they'd...
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually take the time to make something kind of new, maybe with some more DS-centric characters.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, keep in mind the DS is basically a handheld Nintendo 64.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess that's true.
[SPEAKER_01]: So it'd probably be more like a throwback to the old Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_07]: True.
[SPEAKER_07]: Of course they're going to whore this out, but I don't think it's going to come anytime soon.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it'll be at least maybe a year or two off if they're going to do something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Jaded in chat says the PictoChat level where you can draw your own pics.
[SPEAKER_06]: That might be kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: I bet the online seems to work a little better on the DS than it does on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: I bet online would work better.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I guess.
[SPEAKER_01]: The PictoChat level would be full of like cocks or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: No doubt.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not too confident with Nintendo and their online.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ross Steel UT says I say we bring back the Virtual Boy with Smash Brothers.
[SPEAKER_01]: No!
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: I do not want a migraine.
[SPEAKER_01]: Unless it's a playable character, that'd be cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would not mind the migraine.
[SPEAKER_07]: They should do a Super Nintendo version of Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_07]: That'd be cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's gone.
[SPEAKER_07]: The system's like dead and gone.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's as dead as this station.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bring it on to the DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do all 2D.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would believe that a Smash Brothers would come to DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do a Smash Brothers game in the Marvel vs. Capcom 2 engine or something like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Arcade Smash Brothers.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe that'll be the thing is they'll get third parties on board.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: But regardless, I'm sure this survey is a no-brainer.
[SPEAKER_06]: It depends on who they're surveying.
[SPEAKER_07]: If they surveyed us, I'm sure we'd all be saying... Why do you waste money on a freaking survey like that?
[SPEAKER_07]: Would a sequel sell for a really popular game?
[SPEAKER_07]: I have no idea.
[SPEAKER_05]: In other news, water is indeed wet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, and Jamie, just think of the Virtual Boy possibilities.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can have the Teleroboxer stage.
[SPEAKER_01]: No.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_01]: The migraines are not worth it.
[SPEAKER_01]: My Virtual Boy is sealed in foam in a plastic case, never to be opened again.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want to play Virtual Boy.
[SPEAKER_06]: I haven't played one in years.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was like 12.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'll bring it next week.
[SPEAKER_06]: I played one at Blockbuster once.
[SPEAKER_01]: We have one of the ones that Blockbuster was selling.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's why we have the nice hard case and everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: Can we hook up Virtual Boy to Justin.TV somehow?
[SPEAKER_05]: Have the headache cam?
[SPEAKER_05]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_05]: It wouldn't be easy, but you could do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: That might be fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, I say we should have some type of competition with the Virtual Boy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like who can play the longest without having a seizure?
[SPEAKER_06]: Throwing up?
[SPEAKER_06]: Or throwing up?
[SPEAKER_06]: and Cheeseburger in chat asks the definitive question, if Chuck Norris was in Brawl, what would be his final smash?
[SPEAKER_06]: Overused joke.
[SPEAKER_01]: Don't you know that that hand is actually Chuck Norris' hand?
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's move on to the next story, please, before the Chuck Norris choice.
[SPEAKER_06]: God, you guys are chinging to me.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, you know, there is actually, for anybody who has been waiting, and I know lots of people have for Mario Kart Wii, there's going to be a really awesome launch ready for it at midnight on the verge of the 26th to the 27th.
[SPEAKER_01]: And guess where it's going to be?
[SPEAKER_06]: My pants.
[SPEAKER_01]: No.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sam's Club!
[SPEAKER_06]: Because no one knows how to get down like Sam's Club.
[SPEAKER_01]: You can go to Sam's Club and they'll even have
[SPEAKER_01]: 15 Wii consoles on hand.
[SPEAKER_06]: Will they have the ladies serving the samples of the little teeny weenies?
[SPEAKER_01]: Dude, I would go just for that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Would they forget to mention those 15 Wii consoles are being sold together in like a giant family pack of Wiis?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, it's the Wii plus like 50 controllers and shitty games and a box of Froot Loops.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Sam's Club actually realized that they're not a club and they're just a store.
[SPEAKER_01]: And a two-gallon container of mayonnaise.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because, you know, when you think video games, you think Sam's Club.
[SPEAKER_01]: I bought the Vio at Sam's Club.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's my question.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's all Sam's Clubs that are doing this or is it just a few?
[SPEAKER_01]: It's saying... It's not actually saying a few.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's just saying Sam's Club.
[SPEAKER_06]: We should party down at Sam's Club.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's what I'm thinking.
[SPEAKER_06]: If it is at every Sam's Club, we go to the Sam's Club out in freaking Roseville, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: because Roseville knows how to get down.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a lot of retired people out in Roseville.
[SPEAKER_06]: What we'll do, we'll go there and we'll dress to the nine.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll dress in party hats and boas.
[SPEAKER_06]: We have those hats, the little Mario hats that Ranma gave us some time ago.
[SPEAKER_06]: We can wear our little hats.
[SPEAKER_06]: It'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: Count me in.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: If they're doing it, we've got to do that.
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_01]: I'll just have my copy the day it comes out.
[SPEAKER_06]: You don't want to go party at Sam's Club?
[SPEAKER_01]: Come home with Smash Brothers.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dude, two gallons of mayonnaise, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_01]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_01]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, are you down with the Sam's Club party?
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll probably already have the game by the time the thing launches.
[SPEAKER_06]: God, you people are no fun at all.
[SPEAKER_06]: You don't go for the game.
[SPEAKER_01]: I stood in line for a Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: How can I get excited about Sam's Club?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the point.
[SPEAKER_01]: We took our lawn chairs and sat in line for our Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll probably go there and be like, sorry, we're not doing the launch party, and be like, crap.
[SPEAKER_05]: I will go, and you know why, because I have nothing better to do.
[SPEAKER_06]: Will anyone go party at Sam's Club with me?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, if you don't want to go to Sam's Club to get Mario Kart, maybe you want to go to Japan to get Trauma Center 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's right, the game is actually being slated for the DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's coming back.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess the second opinion wasn't really a sequel then.
[SPEAKER_07]: But Trauma Center 2, and I guess the sequel has Dr. Stiles and Nurse Angie tackling the effects of the unanswered mysteries of the guilt virus from the prequel.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Trauma Center is one of those games where I swear it's one of those blink and you miss it kind of games, but it's a quote, an epic story that once aired on the station and on the nightly news here and locally.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's so much fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: Trauma Center is so much fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: I like making them die.
[SPEAKER_06]: I do too.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I love the whole bringing him back to life.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Wii controls in that game are really cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: When you have to do the whole... Defibrillator.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, the defibrillator.
[SPEAKER_06]: You have to push into the screen, onto the body.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's really funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like Trauma Center.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would think you of all people, Loki, would, like, Trauma Center would be one of your favorites.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I liked it better when it was called Life and Death and came out, like, early, early, early PCs back when they had Windows 3.1.
[SPEAKER_07]: Life or Death was hardcore.
[SPEAKER_07]: And everybody, and the only, like, surgeries you'd do would be removing appendixes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh my god, Life or Death was hardcore, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, if you screwed up in that game, you were killing patients left and right.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was a very hard game.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's why it's called Life and Death, and not Life and maybe... They should have called it Life but Mostly Death.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because that's what that game was.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was like, I'm going to scribble with the scalpel.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you have to, like, read all this stuff before you go and do the surgeries.
[SPEAKER_07]: But we didn't like to read.
[SPEAKER_07]: We just wanted the scalpel.
[SPEAKER_01]: In Trauma Center, you... Calteepa makes the best suggestion.
[SPEAKER_06]: In chat?
[SPEAKER_06]: What did he say?
[SPEAKER_01]: Psychological Trauma Center.
[SPEAKER_06]: That would be kind of rad.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what else is going to be... What?
[SPEAKER_07]: I was going to say, oh, no, I have to repair your daddy left you or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dr. Dennis Leary Shut the fuck up by Dr. Dennis Leary
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, look, let's move on to games I definitely want.
[SPEAKER_06]: I do want Trauma Center 2, but I definitely, definitely want this.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was actually surprised to hear that Final Fantasy 4 was not already confirmed for North America, but then again, this is Squeenix we're talking about.
[SPEAKER_06]: But apparently this week, Final Fantasy 4 director Takashi Tokita did confirm that Final Fantasy 4 is being localized for North America.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was in the latest issue of Nintendo Power.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, wait, scratch that.
[SPEAKER_06]: He didn't actually confirm the localization, but, I mean, there was English language screenshots in the article.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's on the cover of the freaking magazine.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's safe to say the game's coming out over here.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's safe to say the game's coming out here.
[SPEAKER_07]: I wouldn't know it or anything.
[SPEAKER_06]: Would you know about when the game is coming out here by chance?
[SPEAKER_07]: I would say it's coming out around here...
[SPEAKER_06]: In time for my birthday?
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: God damn it!
[SPEAKER_01]: I can't get you what I was going to get you for your birthday.
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course, I don't remember when your birthday is, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_06]: June 26th.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't forget it.
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not going to be out for my birthday?
[SPEAKER_06]: Will it be out in July?
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_06]: Can we play Hot and Cold?
[SPEAKER_06]: Is it July 15th?
[SPEAKER_06]: Warm.
[SPEAKER_06]: July 17th.
[SPEAKER_06]: Warmer.
[SPEAKER_06]: July 19th.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, still warm.
[SPEAKER_06]: July 18th.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's a Tuesday?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Pulling up a calendar.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is how we get Loki to tell us secrets now.
[SPEAKER_06]: July 22nd.
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: July 15th.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are they putting it on a Sunday or something?
[SPEAKER_06]: July 20th.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, further.
[SPEAKER_06]: Forget it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's close to August.
[SPEAKER_06]: July 29th.
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: God.
[SPEAKER_06]: July 27th.
[SPEAKER_07]: Right now, it's at the end of July.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's not the only game coming over here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, what else?
[SPEAKER_07]: Uh, just another game Is it Chrono Trigger?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not Chrono Trigger Is it Chrono Trigger?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's another DS game that's already in Japan right now That I'm showing you the title for Can I please say that on air?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, go ahead Dragon Quest V Yeah Wait, what?
[SPEAKER_06]: Dragon Quest V That's apparently getting localized as well Excuse me for a second Should be fun
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you just squee in your pants?
[SPEAKER_06]: What the hell was that noise?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I just squeed into the mic.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, there's another game coming out, too, the same day as Final Fantasy 4, but it's not for the DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's actually a 360 RPG that's by Square Enix, although it's got the weirdest title ever, Infinite Undiscovery, so that should be coming around the same time.
[SPEAKER_07]: But a lot of stuff could move, so...
[SPEAKER_06]: Dragon Quest V, Final Fantasy IV in July
[SPEAKER_07]: That's not a Square Enix game.
[SPEAKER_01]: That was Nintendo themselves.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that was Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bastard Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what I call them now for not bringing that over here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, they did.
[SPEAKER_02]: It came out over there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why not here?
[SPEAKER_02]: What's up with that, Nintendo?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because the same people that own Nintendo own Life 365.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to take a detour for a minute to say hello to Rice Princess, who showed up 39 minutes late.
[SPEAKER_06]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm good and late, how about you?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Awesome, I got you a present.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, then I forgive you for being late.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ooh, ooh, is that it for me?
[SPEAKER_03]: This is it for you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, that looks so pretty.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's kind of random.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is, but they were on sale, and I'm like, oh, they have penguins, I'll be like it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Floor mats for the car with penguins on them, they're so cute.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow, woohoo, yay.
[SPEAKER_03]: I accept your gift.
[SPEAKER_03]: Woohoo, in lieu of being late.
[SPEAKER_01]: Your offering pleases Kitty.
[SPEAKER_06]: It smells like new car.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, that's weird.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I have to say one other thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I got a Captain Crunch malt from Carl's Jr.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is so fucking, I mean, flipping good.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, we can cuss.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fucking good.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's free radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my god, it's so yummy.
[SPEAKER_03]: What are they going to do?
[SPEAKER_03]: Cancel us?
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, you cannot be on our station anymore.
[SPEAKER_03]: But yeah, it's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_03]: So yeah, okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think we should try to set some sort of Guinness Book of World Records for the most time fuck has occurred in a podcast.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Fuck Show
[SPEAKER_03]: Yay, we'll lose all of our listeners in one shot.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll do it South Park style.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll have one of those little click counters in the corner of the Justin TV feed.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll do it, we'll do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bobby, fuck show, why you're in?
[SPEAKER_06]: Bobby's in chat right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also say hello to Nathan, who's here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_06]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_06]: I am fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: Was the Captain Crunch milkshake flippin' fantastic?
[SPEAKER_06]: It was.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was?
[SPEAKER_06]: Glad to hear it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't drink it or it might kill me.
[SPEAKER_06]: I still haven't had it yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I have to stay away from high-fat foods for a month.
[SPEAKER_06]: But if they had Captain Crunch Jell-O, I'd be all over that shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll make you.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_01]: Rob, you should have a smoothie.
[SPEAKER_06]: Black Wolf says, why?
[SPEAKER_06]: So, fuck show it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: So what night is that?
[SPEAKER_06]: It wouldn't be April 13th, it would be the 20th.
[SPEAKER_01]: It would be the show the day after my birthday.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, fuck, I'm in.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that's a great idea because I'm going to be gone most of that week.
[SPEAKER_01]: You're going to come for my birthday stuff, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't, I'm going to be out of town.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll figure something out.
[SPEAKER_06]: It'll be our late April... Oh my God, the show is on 420.
[SPEAKER_06]: It has to be a fuck show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Enough about the fuck show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Jamie, brownies?
[SPEAKER_06]: Irene had enough time to go to the bathroom and back and we're still talking about the fuck show.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to be on 420.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is it going to be like a really slow, mellow fuck show?
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, hey, man.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it'll be... No, it'll be... Here's the deal.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think this is the rule.
[SPEAKER_06]: These are the rules for the fuck show.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, wait, wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: 420 is marijuana day.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not...
[SPEAKER_03]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who can work the word into the show?
[SPEAKER_03]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft
[SPEAKER_01]: is Final Fantasy Fables Chocobo's Dungeon will be coming out in the summer over here and it's happy and makes me go squee and it'll be $39.99.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's about time.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's essentially the game that was on the DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like already.
[SPEAKER_07]: So we're getting a DS port on the Wii now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I think it may be remade a little bit.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, Wii is like the porting system.
[SPEAKER_06]: First it was all our PS2 games get ported with Waggle.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now we're getting DS games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I guess that's nothing new.
[SPEAKER_06]: We had Cookin' Mama.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's cute and it goes quee.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you going to buy the game just because the Chocobo goes, Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: I am.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, will you hack the game so the Chocobo goes, Fuck.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I don't know how to do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, so it's been recently discovered that Konami has trademarked a new name for a Castlevania game.
[SPEAKER_07]: The title of the game, which is assumed to be for the DS, is Castlevania Order of... Man, I can't even pronounce the rest.
[SPEAKER_07]: It looks like Ecclesia.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ecclesia, yeah, that's right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Order of Ecclesia.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that a musical term?
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought all the Castlevania games had to have music in them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh yeah, Portrait of Runa.
[SPEAKER_01]: Has to be something artsy and this one's more like logic.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ecclesia.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Not making up words.
[SPEAKER_07]: I suspect that this game will have someone in the Belmont family fighting a vampire, probably Dracula, and there will be whips of some sort and possibly magic and hearts and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, hold on.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm using my mind reading techniques right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Something tells me
[SPEAKER_06]: This game will have holy water as a weapon.
[SPEAKER_07]: And crosses.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, and crosses.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe daggers.
[SPEAKER_06]: And an axe.
[SPEAKER_06]: One of the characters will have a whip.
[SPEAKER_06]: Stop giving your nonsense.
[SPEAKER_06]: You heard it here first, I'm telling you.
[SPEAKER_03]: When are they going to have a Castlevania game where you fight the Belmonts?
[SPEAKER_02]: They have had one, Symphony of the Nights.
[SPEAKER_02]: You fight the Belmonts?
[SPEAKER_02]: You fight Richter?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wasn't that at the second castle?
[SPEAKER_02]: Sort of, but he's not like the main boss.
[SPEAKER_03]: He is unless you go do the thing where you have to go fight Shaft.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, he is the main boss.
[SPEAKER_03]: Totally, if you're not wearing the sunglasses.
[SPEAKER_01]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's the only time he actually is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then there's Arya of Sorrow.
[SPEAKER_01]: I didn't play that one.
[SPEAKER_04]: He is a boss, though.
[SPEAKER_01]: Richter is awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: I like his Ryu look and Rondo blood.
[SPEAKER_03]: All of them!
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, because you always fight Dracula or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like, come on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or Castlevania.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dracula fucks up the Belmont family reunion.
[SPEAKER_07]: DS.
[SPEAKER_06]: Aw yeah, Dracula's gonna fuck you up.
[SPEAKER_06]: I haven't really been into the Castlevania series on the DS.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't like the 3D Castlevanias.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, they're okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like what, 64?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, like Lament of Innocence.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Curse of Darkness.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like my 2D Castlevania.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I understand that.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, despite whatever it is they're putting out on the DS, it's working because Nintendo is supreme when it comes to Japanese hardware and software sales.
[SPEAKER_06]: And this is per the latest issue of Famitsu Magazine.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Nintendo DS and the Wii have sold 6.3 and 3.7 million units.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's 6.3 million for the DS, 3.7 for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Wii Fit is selling like crazy in Japan, 1.76 million units.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nintendo has the top five spots in software.
[SPEAKER_06]: Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_06]: Brawl, and Pokemon Mystery Dungeon.
[SPEAKER_06]: Those are the top five games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't hate on Pokemon.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't hate.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hate as much as I want.
[SPEAKER_07]: Pokemon Mystery Dungeon doesn't really count because it's two games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, that's true.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a little bit of cheating, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Cheaters.
[SPEAKER_06]: Poke-cheaters.
[SPEAKER_06]: Cheater-mons.
[SPEAKER_08]: Cheater.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, so yeah, Nintendo's making a lot of money in Japan.
[SPEAKER_06]: Go, Fig.
[SPEAKER_01]: What else is new?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: You tell me what else is new.
[SPEAKER_01]: This has to do with old stuff for something new.
[SPEAKER_01]: There has been a fact sheet released for details on Mario Kart Wii, and for anyone who's wanting to play with their classic controller or the GameCube controller, it has been said that certain moves will not be able to be used with those controllers.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like snaking?
[SPEAKER_06]: I say hooray.
[SPEAKER_01]: It doesn't say specifically.
[SPEAKER_06]: They took snaking out of the game altogether.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think we talked about that last week.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's good.
[SPEAKER_01]: But it's basically saying that by using the Wiimote and Nunchuck together you're supposed to have full playability in the game but those people are going to have an advantage over the people using the older controller schemes.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have a feeling that it's not so bad as people are making it out to be.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think
[SPEAKER_07]: It'll probably be because I think you can do different little tricks and stuff, not just one trick when you're doing jumps to get boosts and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: So you probably will be able to do one trick on the GameCube or Classic Controller or something like that, and then the people at the Wii can use the controller to do different tricks using the motion controls.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because, I mean, with that controller turned sideways or something, I mean, there's definitely not...
[SPEAKER_07]: That many buttons to use, and so a lot of it's motion control, so I don't see why they couldn't translate that stuff into button presses.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just sheer laziness.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you think the game's going to control as well with a classic controller anyway?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because it seems to me like this game is going to be calibrated for that motion control that an analog stick can't quite replicate.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_07]: I still think it'll be fine with the classic controller.
[SPEAKER_07]: I played Brawl with the classic controller, and I plan on playing this game.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it's different.
[SPEAKER_06]: Brawl doesn't rely on motion so much.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, but I mean, I plan on playing this game with the classic controller, and if that doesn't work, there's always the remote nunchuck, which you can just use the analog stick on that, and then...
[SPEAKER_07]: Some of the motion controls with the remote Because that's not gimped on it But I don't think it's going to be a big deal And the fact that they would do that to try to force people to buy their stupid You know, possibly use their stupid steering wheel controller or something like that I think it's kind of lame Besides, that steering wheel is going to give them problems We'll see I'm looking forward to the game nevertheless It's going to control a lot differently, that's for sure But as long as it's better than Double Dash
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, this is kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a homemade game for the Nintendo system.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a game called Glider.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's made by a company called RetroZone.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess it's a remake, I think, of a game that came out on the Mac or something like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: But the interesting thing about it is the game will have download content.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it's not as easy as it sounds.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not just like something you can pop into...
[SPEAKER_07]: You actually have to reflash the cart, and it requires a $70 accessory to do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wow, what a bargain.
[SPEAKER_07]: But you can get new levels and stuff, and that same accessory will let you dump ROMs and crap like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it's just still kind of neat to see them actually, first off, making new games, and secondly, allowing you to add new levels to it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Aren't there still new games for the Nintendo being made in countries like Taiwan and stuff?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because didn't we see a version of one of the Tekken games?
[SPEAKER_06]: Like get an NES port or something recently?
[SPEAKER_07]: I've seen some weird stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, and those RPGs I've been seeing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like Final Fantasy VII ported to the NES and that stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then there's also one that I saw, which is Contra III ported to the NES.
[SPEAKER_07]: That Titanic game?
[SPEAKER_07]: That looked like tons of fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, so I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's...
[SPEAKER_07]: It's interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hell, they're still making like Vectrex games and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's always a fan of something somewhere.
[SPEAKER_06]: Would you play a game based off Titanic on the NES?
[SPEAKER_01]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: Even though Leonardo DiCaprio dies?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, if you are interested in playing this game Glider, you can find it on the website RetroUSB.com
[SPEAKER_07]: It's, I believe, like $50, no, $42.
[SPEAKER_07]: Currently, it's on back order, but coming out early April.
[SPEAKER_07]: The only bad thing about it is it's black and white.
[SPEAKER_07]: I really do think it came out originally on a Mac.
[SPEAKER_07]: The game, I guess, is from 1989.
[SPEAKER_07]: But what's cool, though, is it comes with a cardboard box, pretty manual, just like the old NES games.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, of course, there's the black dust sleeve and that kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's region-free.
[SPEAKER_06]: Airball
[SPEAKER_07]: Sudoku, yay.
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: I said Sudoku, yay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sudoku?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's...
[SPEAKER_06]: Turok
[SPEAKER_06]: is coming out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you pre-order your copy?
[SPEAKER_03]: I did, yes, and then I named my kid after Turok.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was great.
[SPEAKER_03]: Poor kid.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wonder if he gets teased.
[SPEAKER_03]: What grade would he be in now?
[SPEAKER_03]: Still in elementary school?
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: The kid that was named Turok.
[SPEAKER_03]: You don't remember that contest?
[SPEAKER_03]: They got paid a million dollars to name their kid Turok?
[SPEAKER_03]: You host a video game show and you do not know this?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't remember old news.
[SPEAKER_03]: It ain't that old.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's like, I don't know, 10 years old or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: By the way, we apologize that our audio is so fucked up in studio tonight, but something about that microphone that they're using in the back is really sensitive.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll talk like right here.
[SPEAKER_06]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a perfect level.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wonderful.
[SPEAKER_06]: Live radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Back to Japan.
[SPEAKER_06]: Coming out on the Nintendo Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mario Kart Wii makes its way out on April the 10th, as well as Karas Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's not Kid Akaris, that's K-A-R-O-U-S.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then Neo Geo Stick 2 comes out as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not sure if that's a joystick.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, it's just a joystick.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought it was actually a game for a minute.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like a stick figure game where you kind of think like Stick Fighter.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, Stick Fighter, exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: The PlayStation 2 Battle of Sunrise comes out.
[SPEAKER_06]: from Sunrise Interactive.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I wonder if it's like the employees fight each other.
[SPEAKER_07]: That would be cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: That would be actually kind of a rad game.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, this looks like... What kind of game does this look like?
[SPEAKER_06]: It looks kind of like one of those robot fighting games that you see quite a bit of in Japan.
[SPEAKER_06]: It looks like it's got a tech element to it as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: That must be the gist of it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Probably some type of tech game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also coming out in Japan on the Nintendo DS...
[SPEAKER_06]: Oshiri, Kajiri, Mushi, no, Rhythm Lesson DS comes out from Sega.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wait, did you say the first word was... Oshiri, Kajiri, Mushi.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oshiri, I'm probably just mispronouncing it because I horribly do that.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it's a music game.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like learn how to dance like these scary looking critters with flowers coming out of their heads on the cover of the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe they're saying like,
[SPEAKER_03]: Move Your Butt, Rhythm Dancing, whatever it's called.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_06]: So if you live in Japan and you've got no rhythm, hope is on the way.
[SPEAKER_06]: On the PSP, the only game coming out on the 10th, Nanpure and Okake Puzzle 10,000 Mon.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's just a Sudoku game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that's what they call it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yay, Sudoku.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, shut up.
[SPEAKER_03]: You shut up.
[SPEAKER_07]: How many Sudoku games do they have in the Simple series?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just nuts.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's silly because you can just play it for free online.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know why you'd buy a game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to remember that, though, that Oshiri means butt.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, JustinTV, want me to show my Oshiri?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, please don't proposition that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would have to see it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my god, Glenn.
[SPEAKER_03]: When did he get here?
[SPEAKER_03]: Nobody knows who Glenn is.
[SPEAKER_06]: Never mind.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nobody knows that joke outside of well.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I kind of regret saying that.
[SPEAKER_01]: According to Alpha Canonogram, it's a butt-biting bug game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sounds like fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: And no, I'm not going to show my butt on the Justin TV cam because some sick asshole would highlight it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I'm not going to do that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's move on with other release dates, please.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: How about some for the UK?
[SPEAKER_06]: How about it?
[SPEAKER_01]: A bunch of stuff on the 11th.
[SPEAKER_01]: We have Phoenix Wright, Ace Attorney, Trials and Tribulations, Soldier of Fortune Payback, the History Channel Battle for the Pacific on a bunch of systems, Assassin's Creed, Altair's Chronicles, Assassin's Creed Director's Cut Edition, Draglade, Mario Kart Wii,
[SPEAKER_01]: Sam and Max Episode 205, What's New, Beelzebub I think that's a funny name, although I still won't play the game UEFA Euro 2008, Victorious Boxers Challenge So you can punch people in the face Sounds like fun That does sound like fun I want to punch people in the face Well, Drew's right there Hi, come here so I can punch you Is that it?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes
[SPEAKER_07]: Yay, crap!
[SPEAKER_07]: My favorite.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_07]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: What the hell is wrong with us?
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, make some games that aren't stupid.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dude, they should make a game called Furries.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, they shouldn't.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know you would at least rent it, just to see what it's about.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I would not waste my money.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's called Second Life.
[SPEAKER_03]: It totally is.
[SPEAKER_07]: The orange box is going to be broken up this week, so we have Half-Life 2, the episode pack, which I believe is episode 1 and 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: Then we've also got Portal coming out on PC.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then finally, of course, Team Fortress 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: and on the Wii, Minicopter Adventure Flight.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a game where you can play around with a RC helicopter.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's also Summer Sports Paradise Island.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a Wii game with lawn darts, which are illegal, I guess, in the United States.
[SPEAKER_06]: Lawn Darts are illegal here?
[SPEAKER_06]: Dude, we had those growing up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, they're illegal now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ooh, I'm reporting you to Hot Dog.
[SPEAKER_07]: You don't know Hot Dog.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also on the Wii and PlayStation 2, Baroque is coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: On PlayStation 2, Arcana Heart, which is that all-girl anime fighting game from Atlus.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hot.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, Fatal Fury Battle Archives Vol. 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: Coming out on PlayStation 2 for $14.99.
[SPEAKER_07]: On PC, we have Overclocked, A History of Violence, Assassin's Creed, and finally, oh, let's see here, Sam & Max Episode 205, What's New Beelzebub, will be coming out on GameTap and PC.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I guess Civil War Mysteries as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey!
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: We make fun on this show.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I think that's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And there's, as we mentioned, I think a few weeks ago, Ikaruga's rumor will be coming out this week on Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hopefully that's not broken.
[SPEAKER_06]: And hopefully it isn't a shitty port, because that'll make me cry.
[SPEAKER_01]: Where is my radiant silver gun?
[SPEAKER_06]: Uh, questions, or comments from chatroom.
[SPEAKER_06]: Qualtipo says, the furry game would be rated D for drama.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I guess there's a lot of drama in the furry scene.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would know.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're kidding.
[SPEAKER_06]: Uh...
[SPEAKER_06]: Catamaris Forever, Arcana Heart, Eleven Girl Fighters, Girl on Girl Action ManBearPig, CosplayersHateFurries
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't know there was this rivalry between cosplayers and furries.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like Pirates and Ninjas.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dude, that should be a fighting game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess one kind of drama hates the other kind of drama.
[SPEAKER_06]: Cosplayers versus furries.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would buy that.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's like Pirates versus Ninja.
[SPEAKER_06]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh yeah?
[SPEAKER_01]: Cowboys.
[SPEAKER_06]: and SSGL100 Matt says, no, no, no, everyone hates furries.
[SPEAKER_06]: Aw, poor furries.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not poor furries.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're completely cognizant of what they're doing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dude, I would love... Okay, so what are the ideas for games we've had?
[SPEAKER_06]: We've had laser cats.
[SPEAKER_06]: We've had... What else do we have on a previous show?
[SPEAKER_06]: We need to write these things down.
[SPEAKER_06]: You do.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or put them on the wiki or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: Something.
[SPEAKER_07]: Damn it.
[SPEAKER_07]: But now we have... Wasn't there something that had to do with paper?
[SPEAKER_06]: It was one of those games, yeah, because there was a game for DS coming out that you could just play on paper.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was like Pictionary or something on the DS.
[SPEAKER_06]: I remember talking about that in a previous show.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was something you could play with a pen and paper.
[SPEAKER_06]: And now I want to add this to the list.
[SPEAKER_06]: Cosplayers vs. Furries.
[SPEAKER_06]: An epic fighting battle.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rob's voice, the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, no, scratch that from the list.
[SPEAKER_06]: That wouldn't sell.
[SPEAKER_06]: LOL, that was the name of the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: There was a game on the DS called LOL, and it was something you could just play with a fucking piece of paper and a pen.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, that's right, because the whole premise of that game was to get people to laugh or something like that, and they would vote on which drawing is the funniest or something like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, that's it, that's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, it's called pen and paper.
[SPEAKER_06]: Can somebody please add that to the wiki?
[SPEAKER_06]: Can our wiki gods like AJ Mix or DarkTetsui or somebody, can our wiki gods add a page of our great ideas?
[SPEAKER_06]: And be sure to put on the bottom, patent pending.
[SPEAKER_07]: GameStop.com is down GameStop.com is down GameStop.com is down
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, please.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: So if that's it for the US releases... I think it is at least.
[SPEAKER_06]: How did release dates turn into cosplayers versus furries?
[SPEAKER_03]: You did it.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was your fault, Rob.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's all my fault.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was an April Fool's joke.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, it's actually not the first anymore.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I'm trying to transition into talking about some of the April Fool's Day pranks from around the web.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you know I've got to start with this.
[SPEAKER_06]: This week we had so many April Fool's Day pranks because everyone gets in on it, except for Orange Lounge Radio this year.
[SPEAKER_06]: We didn't do an April Fool's Day prank because we had depressing news.
[SPEAKER_06]: So the holiday was kind of ruined for us.
[SPEAKER_06]: However, the IGN trailer for The Legend of Zelda movie.
[SPEAKER_06]: What the fuck?
[SPEAKER_06]: Somebody spent like thousands of dollars on that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you see that trailer?
[SPEAKER_03]: I did see that trailer.
[SPEAKER_06]: Didn't it make you like want to like come?
[SPEAKER_03]: Not at all.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was actually pretty well done.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some of it was hokey, but it looked like a sci-fi movie to me.
[SPEAKER_06]: What do you expect?
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, it's not much on the trailer.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, if they put a decent budget behind it and maybe had a good writer or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't believe for a minute it was real because it didn't have a single star in it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And a movie like Zelda would at least have a star in it somewhere.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like Ian McKellen playing the old man that says, it's tough out there to go alone.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here, take this or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: But he'd say it in his voice.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's dangerous to go alone.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's dangerous.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sean Connery, it's dangerous to go along.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't do impressions.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, you can't, so you should stop.
[SPEAKER_06]: But there would be at least one famous person.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's why this thing couldn't be real and the CGI was a little hokey.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I thought it was pretty amazing.
[SPEAKER_06]: The work that they did do.
[SPEAKER_06]: For an April Fool's joke, it was awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, they put a lot of effort into it for an April Fool's joke, but I wouldn't.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, did you see the Making Of trailer?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because they did that shit in July of last year.
[SPEAKER_03]: They did a Making Of trailer of a trailer.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, well, they had like a Making Of little snippet thing that was released the day after that shows you like how they did it.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I didn't check.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, oh, it's April 2nd.
[SPEAKER_03]: Time to check and see if there's something following up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is this better?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: The date was July.
[SPEAKER_06]: They did that in July.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the only thing I cared about in there was, like, when did they do it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I wanted to hear them say, like, why they did it.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it was July when they were putting it all together.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was just kind of surprised at that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, good job.
[SPEAKER_06]: But Loki, I noticed there was no Tingle in the movie, so there's still hope.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I don't think that there was Tingle in the first game either.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_06]: They can work it in.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, they can't.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, they can, but I'm not playing him.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, the legend of me.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Legend of Me The Legend of Me Other April Fool's jokes from around the web Microsoft actually put together their own little thing like they were announcing all these devices that were going to come out such as the retro Xbox 360 that had a wood finish on it and the retro controller and I thought the hilarious part I like how Microsoft can kind of make fun of themselves because the retro controller had like 100 buttons on it it looked like a typewriter it was kind of funny and then they announced like a virtual headset and my favorite was Xbox Live the board game
[SPEAKER_06]: That was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_06]: What else did we have?
[SPEAKER_06]: Kotaku did Cake Kaku for a day or something like that, not Bukkake, but Cake Kaku or something like that for a whole day where they were nothing but gaming cakes, which was actually kind of funny because they do cover a lot of gaming cakes on that blog, or at least they did in the past year.
[SPEAKER_06]: What else was there?
[SPEAKER_06]: Somebody announced My Little Pony for Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, don't forget WoW.
[SPEAKER_06]: StarCraft 2 Torrin Marines
[SPEAKER_05]: They were beefy.
[SPEAKER_01]: I still like the Guild Wars thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: I thought that was cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Lord of the Rings on mine had giant chickens that you had to fight.
[SPEAKER_03]: But nobody cares because it's Lord of the Rings on mine.
[SPEAKER_06]: And actually, speaking of Guild Wars, the Guild Wars wiki and the WoW wiki switched places for a day.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you tried to go to WoW wiki and it was giving you Guild War quests.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then vice versa.
[SPEAKER_07]: Brilliant.
[SPEAKER_07]: And there was also the Konami Ubisoft one where they had Altair in Metal Gear Solid 4.
[SPEAKER_07]: and they did like an actual video from in-game and stuff with all that going on and what other ones oh Dark Tetsuya says Shang Long in Street Fighter 4 yeah just gonna say that that was funny I don't know there's oh Bungie did one where they're showing like the Xbox Halo 3 stats you know how like show a little light or whatever where people are playing Halo 3 and apparently it made you know their little cartoon Halo head thing on there
[SPEAKER_07]: Creativity from around the web Did anyone fall for a prank?
[SPEAKER_07]: Chatters, did any of you fall for a prank?
[SPEAKER_06]: I got my boss to fall for a prank.
[SPEAKER_06]: My work review was on April 1st.
[SPEAKER_01]: And so I was thinking that there was going to be all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I went in and I was like, well, before we start the meeting, I have to tell you something really, really important.
[SPEAKER_01]: And this is bad news for you.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's really good news for me.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I've been offered a job at the Beau Ravage in Biloxi, Mississippi as their massage therapist for some sort of reopening thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I'm going to be moving in three weeks.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I did it completely deadpan.
[SPEAKER_01]: And she just got quiet and looked at me and said, I'm happy for you.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I was like, well, thank you.
[SPEAKER_01]: And also, I just completely fooled you.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is at my annual review.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_01]: But she said that they all got her by... She calls in to check on us every morning and that they said that nobody else showed up.
[SPEAKER_06]: The only April Fool's prank I played is I went to our guild forum for WoW.
[SPEAKER_06]: I went to the guild forum and I posted a post that says why I quit the guild last night to go back to Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then you open it up and it says, yeah, right, April Fool's.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's clever, Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know, it was great.
[SPEAKER_05]: The worst part is, some of us actually believe you.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_01]: What about all the Rickrolling stuff that was going on?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, God, Rickrolling is so old.
[SPEAKER_01]: However, there was a clever one that was linked to me of the Muppets.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, that one.
[SPEAKER_01]: And that was cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: The best Rickroll was not Beaker, but it was not GameFAQs, which was evil.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it was actually Chris Perillo of Locker Gnome from the Screensavers announcing his last video podcast.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because apparently he had a fight with his woman.
[SPEAKER_05]: His woman.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's always the woman.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry, I just... He looks away, freeze frame, never gonna give you up, starts playing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm like, oh god.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think my favorite April Fool's joke other than the Zelda thing had to have been...
[SPEAKER_07]: and I know it was a little late for April Fools but the release of Mr. Driller and they're online.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's so funny because it doesn't work.
[SPEAKER_07]: I fooled all those people because it's Mr. Driller online and the online portion doesn't work.
[SPEAKER_06]: You remember Mo who was here a few weeks ago who did a cover of Still Alive?
[SPEAKER_06]: Remember that?
[SPEAKER_06]: She actually has a cover of Never Gonna Give You Up on YouTube and that's how we found her actually.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's how Jake found her to begin with and they call it chick-rolling.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you want to link that YouTube.
[SPEAKER_06]: So there it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not making that up.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a cover of her doing Never Gonna Give You Up.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's quite good.
[SPEAKER_03]: So April Fool's, I guess it's about fooling people, obviously.
[SPEAKER_03]: And yeah, the Zelda thing was pretty good, but I kind of like things that make me laugh on April Fool's Day.
[SPEAKER_03]: And definitely the Molten Core console thing just made me crack up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Blizzard does good jobs every year with April Fools.
[SPEAKER_06]: They do good jobs.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's move on with news because we want to wrap this segment up.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, I have our downloadable content stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yay, stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: Xbox Live Arcade, Mr. Driller Online, 800 Microsoft points.
[SPEAKER_06]: April Fools, game doesn't work.
[SPEAKER_01]: Xbox Live Marketplace, Army of Two, Football Manager 2008.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is UK, sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_01]: Some of it's over here.
[SPEAKER_01]: Game Content, Call of Duty 4, Variety Map Pack, Two Worlds, Curse of Souls, Pinball FX, Rocky and Bullwinkle Table Guess what?
[SPEAKER_01]: I owned one!
[SPEAKER_01]: For reals!
[SPEAKER_01]: So ha ha.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's how I got my World Cup Soccer.
[SPEAKER_01]: A whole bunch of Karaoke Revolution, American Idol stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_06]: I gotta get that game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: themes, MrDrillerOnline, FIFA Street 3, Brazil, England, France, Italy, Germany, Mexico, Spain, USA, Australia, pictures, Major League Gaming, GotFrag, Major League Gaming, Game Battles, Turok Creatures, Turok Whiskey Company, Wolf Pack, Variety, MrDrillerOnline, War Shit, Call of Duty 4, Nick Busby, Ink Blots, Number 2, Rainbow Six Vegas 2, Elite Pack, PSN, nothing.
[SPEAKER_01]: Virtual Console in Europe, Yoshi's Cookie.
[SPEAKER_01]: In the U.S., we got Cruisin', and we got Wonder Boy, which we've talked about.
[SPEAKER_01]: For the Metabolite thing, there's Imprinium Romanum, Buku Dominoes, and Rayman Raving Rabbids, and Sins of the Solar Empire as a PC demo is out.
[SPEAKER_01]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's the hilarious thing about the Mr. Driller Online theme, is that when you download it on Xbox 360, what the theme is, is just a bunch of red X's.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's see, I was going to say also...
[SPEAKER_07]: PlayStation Network is not going to have much for the next few weeks anyway since they're revamping their store and in the meantime not putting anything up there.
[SPEAKER_07]: So if you want your free still live like you get in Xbox 360 you're going to have to wait until the 17th.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that sucks.
[SPEAKER_07]: Another game though that you're going to have to wait even longer for is The Force Unleashed which was originally going to be a July game but now it's been pushed all the way to September 16th where it's hopefully going to stay.
[SPEAKER_07]: This week though they had some videos showing off
[SPEAKER_07]: The different versions of the game, which I guess each game is getting their own exclusive things.
[SPEAKER_07]: For example, the PlayStation 2 and PSP titles will be getting some exclusive storylines and stuff like that in the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: In the 360 and PS3 versions, you of course get kick-ass graphics and physics.
[SPEAKER_07]: In the Wii version, they actually have a battle mode where you can fight different people
[SPEAKER_07]: and also like, you know, Wiimote, Lightsaber Combat and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I believe also the PSP version has some like legacy storyline modes that you can play through five different storylines through the six episodes of the movie.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it looks like a pretty awesome game.
[SPEAKER_07]: And like I said, September 16th is when we can see that in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you excited about The Force Unleashed?
[SPEAKER_07]: I actually am.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm thinking about picking that up for the 360.
[SPEAKER_06]: Star Wars games are usually pretty good.
[SPEAKER_01]: I like Lego Star Wars.
[SPEAKER_06]: So go figure.
[SPEAKER_06]: We have people trying to connect to Live 365 right now and it's not letting them in.
[SPEAKER_00]: Those are bastards.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not going to miss this place at all.
[SPEAKER_06]: The more I think about it, we should have done this a year ago.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rooster Teeth.
[SPEAKER_06]: You might not know that name, but you definitely know Red vs. Blue, something that they've put together for years and years, but they obviously... They also did The Stranger Hood.
[SPEAKER_06]: Right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, now they're going to do something called Reconstruction.
[SPEAKER_06]: They put out a trailer, a little teaser video that's available on YouTube if you search for Reconstruction, Rooster Teeth.
[SPEAKER_06]: You'll find it... What I find interesting about it, though, it's a little bit more serious.
[SPEAKER_06]: At least the trailer had a more serious tone, so...
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess they're getting away from the funny stuff and maybe doing something a little more serious.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know about that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, every series that they've done has been funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess that's true.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, maybe, I don't know, but it would be interesting if they took the different direction.
[SPEAKER_06]: It would be interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe it'll be a dramedy, like Ally McBeal was drama but funny, well, to some.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, that's debatable.
[SPEAKER_06]: I never really found it funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: Neither did anybody else.
[SPEAKER_03]: I never watched it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, snap.
[SPEAKER_01]: She was too skeleton-like.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that's every time I look at it.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: No more TV critic.
[SPEAKER_06]: Back to gaming news.
[SPEAKER_01]: Remember when we were talking about the contest for Puzzle Quest, the add-on getting a name?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, I do.
[SPEAKER_01]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that the name of the new expansion?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, that's the name.
[SPEAKER_01]: Try to spell it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyway, they got 500 plus suggestions.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's it?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's actually kind of sad.
[SPEAKER_06]: Only 500?
[SPEAKER_01]: I know, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: And in the end they got Revenge of the Plague Lord.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was hoping they would pick Puzzle Quest 1.5 to search for more money.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's Spaceballs 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ah, yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's actually kind of a dumb title.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: It doesn't make me go OMG 1.
[SPEAKER_01]: The Runner's Up.
[SPEAKER_01]: with Sorceress of Malbec and the Scourge of Antharg.
[SPEAKER_06]: Those are much cooler names.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think I knew an ogre in a D&D game named Antharg.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like they threw the alphabet into Will It Blend and they got those names.
[SPEAKER_01]: Say that again.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Sorceress of Elbec?
[SPEAKER_06]: What was that?
[SPEAKER_01]: Malbec.
[SPEAKER_01]: Malbec and the Scourge of Antharg.
[SPEAKER_06]: Antharg.
[SPEAKER_01]: Did you actually watch any of those yet?
[SPEAKER_06]: Will It Blend is pretty good.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, I watched the one where they blended a Guitar Hero controller.
[SPEAKER_01]: I liked the one where they blended the iPhone.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: I liked the one where they exposed a hobo in that.
[SPEAKER_06]: April Fool's.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, there's a game that is on Xbox Live Arcade that everybody loves.
[SPEAKER_07]: and, well, they're going to be loving the sequel, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's Geometry Wars Retro Evolved 2, and it is coming to Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, at least that's where we would assume it's going.
[SPEAKER_07]: And this comes to us from the Australian Classifications Board, the OFLC, which has just raided the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, you know, kind of like the MPA, not the MPA, but the ESRB here.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: What do you think they're going to change in this game, though?
[SPEAKER_06]: I kind of like the Wii version.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Wii version was good.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, that would be a pretty kick-ass download game.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, I mean, then again, it's the game that's on the Wii, so I don't think they could do the same thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, like, I didn't know there was a lot else they could do to Geometry Wars, but that Wii game was pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Add some new animes, maybe, or something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Different weapons.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe they'll have, like, co-op or competitive mode or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: That would be a big change, because they didn't have that in the first one.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, we're going to play this song.
[SPEAKER_06]: Long-time listeners of our show recognize that song as Happy Wedding, which is going to introduce a new segment in the show this week called Nerds Got Married.
[SPEAKER_06]: Whenever there's a wedding of note that we want to highlight on the show, we're going to say Nerds Got Married.
[SPEAKER_06]: So this week in Nerds Got Married, a listener of Orange Lounge Radio actually got married.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Viva Pinata guy!
[SPEAKER_06]: Remember the Viva Pinata guy?
[SPEAKER_06]: He's actually a listener of the program.
[SPEAKER_06]: He commented on our MySpace.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think he was mad because we were poking fun at the story, even though that's what we do here.
[SPEAKER_06]: But the Viva Pinata guy got married.
[SPEAKER_06]: You might remember in Viva Pinata, he did the diamond sending thing and did a little note in the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they had the wedding, and they did it on a cruise ship.
[SPEAKER_06]: and they actually had little Viva Pinata creatures on their wedding cake.
[SPEAKER_06]: So congratulations to David and Jen.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you want to see more about the wedding, it's all on David's YouTube channel, which is available at, what's his username?
[SPEAKER_06]: Gearscast.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's G-E-A-R-S-C-A-S-T.
[SPEAKER_06]: He must also be a big Gears Award player.
[SPEAKER_06]: So there you have it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nerds got married.
[SPEAKER_06]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_01]: It also hurts my heart that this is classic now.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, DarkSakura, what did you pick for the kids this week?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's your classic game of the week, something they must check out.
[SPEAKER_01]: I picked pure awesomeness.
[SPEAKER_01]: I picked Crazy Taxi.
[SPEAKER_01]: 100 gas.
[SPEAKER_06]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, this is the best, like, one of the best games ever.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey, hey, hey, it's time to make some crazy money.
[SPEAKER_01]: Are you ready?
[SPEAKER_00]: Here we go!
[SPEAKER_06]: That's not the same song I remember.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, well, it had Bad Religion and Off the Line.
[SPEAKER_01]: Gotcha.
[SPEAKER_01]: But yeah, it's basically, not only is it a clever type of beat-the-clock sort of driving game, you can do different kinds of stunts in there to increase your fare.
[SPEAKER_01]: You have to play for a better rating.
[SPEAKER_01]: I remember playing in the arcade until I got an S-class license and I was so freaking happy.
[SPEAKER_01]: But the game also is a clever advertising technique for Pizza Hut, Fila, Tower Records, which actually I guess it wasn't so clever for Tower Records, Levi's Store, and Kentucky Fried Chicken.
[SPEAKER_01]: They all had massive product placement in that game.
[SPEAKER_01]: But you had four different drivers.
[SPEAKER_01]: You had your balanced driver, you had your fast one, you've got your best control, and then you had your heavy cab that can
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_00]: The songs from Bad Religion and Offspring from Bad Religion have been released at 10 and 2010, then the Master of the Gearing.
[SPEAKER_00]: And Offspring knows all I want to enjoy the world and lay down the line.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what it was.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: I remember that song.
[SPEAKER_06]: That song, like, I can't hear that song on the radio and not think of this game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, let me forward a little bit.
Thanks.
Take me to Pizza Hut.
[SPEAKER_00]: Take me to Pizza Hut.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love this game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I actually think this is one of the better driving games.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not so fond of it on the Dreamcast as I am in the arcades.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, for me, that's the home for this game, was an arcade game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Although I will give props to the Dreamcast version, because it had the missions, and it had the extra stuff in it.
[SPEAKER_06]: The missions were hard, though.
[SPEAKER_01]: The missions were actually pretty cool, so I'm just going to bring that up.
[SPEAKER_01]: You actually... It trains you to do different stuff in the game, is what the missions are there for.
[SPEAKER_01]: So showing you how to do, like, uh...
[SPEAKER_01]: I actually thought the later ones that had some of the interesting ones like the super long jump and everything that was kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is one of my favorite games ever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Irene, were you a fan of Crazy Taxi?
[SPEAKER_06]: I never played it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Really?
[SPEAKER_06]: Really.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a really fun game, actually.
[SPEAKER_06]: I should try it.
[SPEAKER_06]: For a driving game, it's a lot, it's just different.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not just, you know, like NASCAR, vroom, vroom, vroom around in a circle.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: You race the clock and get crazy money.
[SPEAKER_06]: You guys get crazy money.
[SPEAKER_03]: Take people to Pizza Hut.
[SPEAKER_03]: How could you not like that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I'll have to try it sometime.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's actually available on GameTap, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know I whore that a lot, but hey, they got free games on there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I guess free, free, but...
[SPEAKER_01]: Is it like on the later ones, how they had it where you could play, where you could have multiple people in your car, too, and do different deliveries to different places?
[SPEAKER_06]: Rostio UT says, funny that Pizza Hut isn't Pizza Hut anymore, they're Pasta Hut now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did they have to change that in later games or something, maybe?
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, in the game?
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wasn't that an April Fool's joke?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, perhaps.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, they're Wing Street now, or whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tiger Claw mentions in the game you can't run over people, sadly.
[SPEAKER_06]: Any attempt, they always run out of the way.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm talking about running into cars.
[SPEAKER_01]: You can run into cars.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love Crazy Taxi.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know, me too.
[SPEAKER_01]: I want to make some crazy money, Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I got a dollar.
[SPEAKER_01]: I owe you a dollar.
[SPEAKER_01]: You should just keep it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow, that's going to do it for Part A of our podcast, but there's plenty more to come for this, our last week on Live 365.
[SPEAKER_06]: Coming up in Part B, we're going to play a game that we started here on Live 365.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, this game dates all the way back to a show I did on college radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: So this game has survived for 10 years.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to play it one last time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, not last time, but one more time tonight here on Live 365, and then we'll bring it over to all games in a few weeks.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to play Listless tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: and the topic for tonight's list list so folks can start thinking about what they want to do here in studio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Things that Live365 could do to get us to stay.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is the topic of tonight's list list.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you guys think about that and we will cover that in part B of our podcast.
[SPEAKER_06]: But until then, a break.
[SPEAKER_06]: See you then.
[SPEAKER_06]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and is podcasted to the world twice a week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Stay tuned to our podcast feed for the conclusion of this week's Orange Lounge Radio.