[SPEAKER_01]: Orange Lounge Radio will be closing after April 12th.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thanks to all who have supported us in our five and a half years of broadcasting.
[SPEAKER_01]: On April 13th, please join us in our future projects at our new home.
[SPEAKER_00]: Live365.com
Like a shooting star
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey, you're listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: It is the end, guys.
[SPEAKER_01]: 30 minutes before we officially pull the plug on Orange Lounge Radio and five and a half years of memories on Live 365.
[SPEAKER_01]: But no tears, no crying, damn it.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's no crying in internet radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: because the future begins at allgames.com this Sunday.
[SPEAKER_01]: The new chapter of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: But we take a look back at some of the important things that have happened over the past five years.
[SPEAKER_01]: And you've got to love this guy.
[SPEAKER_01]: He was one of the first very accessible people on... Oh, actually, we're going to take a quick little detour here.
[SPEAKER_01]: Somebody's calling me a little early here.
[SPEAKER_01]: We're going to go sky blind.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hello, are you there?
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hello, how are you, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_07]: Tired.
[SPEAKER_07]: Been all day at Ikea.
[SPEAKER_01]: How was Ikea?
[SPEAKER_01]: What were you going shopping for at Ikea?
[SPEAKER_07]: It was Swedish.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was very Swedish?
[SPEAKER_01]: Were you going for meatballs or what?
[SPEAKER_07]: We actually had meatballs and then I saw the herring and decided that it was disgusting.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I bought shelves.
[SPEAKER_01]: What are you going to be organizing later?
[SPEAKER_07]: The computer room.
[SPEAKER_01]: Fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a wreck.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sounds like fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a freaking wreck.
[SPEAKER_01]: a freaking wreck well hey we're at the end Jamie this is 30 minutes before we pull the plug on the station and it's all over are you sad?
[SPEAKER_07]: no
[SPEAKER_01]: Me neither, really.
[SPEAKER_01]: We have a few people joining us.
[SPEAKER_01]: The chat is filled up a little bit, chat.orangelandrady.com.
[SPEAKER_01]: We have a handful of people here.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is really the loyalists we have here tonight, the people that have been with us through thick and thin, through five and a half years.
[SPEAKER_01]: Do you have anything you want to say to those people as we say goodbye tonight?
[SPEAKER_07]: To our listeners?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like fire.
[SPEAKER_01]: Always have and always will.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I can hang out on the phone for a little while.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, sounds... We're going to ignite our flame pit and char some malum flush.
[SPEAKER_01]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sounds awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, hey, since you're on the phone, I'm going to play a song just for you, okay?
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is a game.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm doing things a little bit out of order here, but that's okay, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was going to play something else.
[SPEAKER_01]: We'll do this song.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is a song from a game, and this is a little bit newer, but this is a game that Jamie is just – she hasn't really shut up about in the past year because she just loves this game so much, and it's Portal.
[SPEAKER_01]: Portal.
[SPEAKER_01]: His other stuff is pretty quirky too.
[SPEAKER_01]: This was a triumph I'm making a note here, huge success It's hard to overstate my satisfaction Aperture science
[SPEAKER_04]: We do what we must because we can For the good of all of us Except the ones who are dead But there's no sense crying over every mistake You just keep on trying till you run out of cake And the science gets done
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm being so sincere right now Even though you broke my heart and killed me And tore me to pieces And blew every piece into a pile As they burned it hurt because I was so happy for you Now these points of data make a beautiful
[SPEAKER_03]: I think I'd prefer to stay inside Maybe you'll find someone else to help
[SPEAKER_04]: What was the joke?
[SPEAKER_04]: Haha, bad chance.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, this cake is great, it's so delicious and moist.
[SPEAKER_04]: Look at me, still talking when there's science to do.
[SPEAKER_03]: When I look up there it makes me glad I'm not you.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've experimented too long, there is
[SPEAKER_01]: That's Jonathan Coulton here with Still Alive on OLR, the final little live show when we're going to be pulling the plug on OLR in 23 minutes.
[SPEAKER_01]: Jamie's joining us by phone.
[SPEAKER_01]: You still there, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_01]: No.
[SPEAKER_01]: You're half dead.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey, you want to hear the latest in the Live 365 drama?
[SPEAKER_01]: This is hilarious.
[SPEAKER_01]: I tried to send them an account.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh my god, it's so hard to cancel your account with them, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: So you have to send them an email in order to cancel the account because they have no handy dandy thing on the web.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I sent them an email like on Monday, hasn't been responded to.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sent them an email like second request Thursday or Friday, still hasn't been responded to.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I'm just like, great.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're going to try to charge my card tomorrow, but aha, I'm one step ahead of them.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm going to call the bank tomorrow and put a stop pay on anything they try to do.
[SPEAKER_01]: So things are going to get ugly.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, you've already paid for the service, and if you're going to try to do those, you should just cut it off anyway, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Exactly, that's the thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't have 85 bucks or whatever much they're going to try to charge us for another month.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't want to be here another month.
[SPEAKER_01]: We're ready for the future, dang it.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's so crap.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know, it's such crap.
[SPEAKER_07]: The crap is the best word for it.
[SPEAKER_01]: How did we put up with this for five years?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because we were lazy.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, yeah, something like that.
[SPEAKER_01]: We're super lazy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nothing is...
[SPEAKER_07]: Nothing is as motivating as being forced into it.
[SPEAKER_01]: True, very true.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think it's kind of part of the thing we're learning here throughout this transition.
[SPEAKER_01]: But the future of OLR is going to be very exciting.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, I got to play with the all-grit game stream yesterday.
[SPEAKER_01]: I got to hijack it for a little bit.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was lots of fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: The quality is really good.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think it's going to be a good time.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I've got news.
[SPEAKER_01]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_07]: They've brought up a blog for that Street Fighter movie.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, the blog was, I guess, overloaded because of a lot of heavy web traffic.
[SPEAKER_07]: But they've got it back up now.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's at streetfightermovie.net.
[SPEAKER_01]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Street Fighter, The Legend of Chun-Li, which means I'm not going to watch it because she's my least favorite character.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll watch it if Kylie's in it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Even if she has a cameo or is on the soundtrack, I'll still watch it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: It'd be awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm sure we'll talk more about that on tomorrow night's show.
[SPEAKER_01]: Also on tomorrow night's show, I just taped it not even 20 minutes ago.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's the reason why we started a little bit after 7 tonight.
[SPEAKER_01]: Farbs, the man who wrote Rom Check Fail is going to be on tomorrow night's show.
[SPEAKER_01]: I thought we were going to do the one that we discussed because I found it
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, no, no, that'll be the next to last song.
[SPEAKER_01]: But then it occurred to me that there really is only one song we can go out with.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's really only one song.
[SPEAKER_01]: But that'll be the next to last song.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: See, even I'm keeping Jamie in suspense here, but you will approve.
[SPEAKER_01]: Trust me, you'll approve.
[SPEAKER_07]: I will?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, you will.
[SPEAKER_07]: Will you tell me off air?
[SPEAKER_01]: You better.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm going to stick you with a spork.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, if you join chat or something, I'll tell you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: I actually don't have IRC on this computer yet.
[SPEAKER_01]: Dang you.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm going to download it I hate that client I'm downloading it
[SPEAKER_01]: He actually came on the show and did an interview and he was a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: So we're going to play one of his remixes right now.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's Middyhead's smack mix of Jelly Kiss.
[SPEAKER_01]: We'll be back with more at the end.
[SPEAKER_01]: We don't know a lot.
[SPEAKER_01]: Jerry Kiss here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey, you know, one of the first big whoop-dee-doo deal shows we ever had on Orange Lounge Radio, do you remember when we got to premiere a brand new DDR song before anybody else did, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, I do.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, it was, and I'm thinking not even like, we did it for some of the Xbox games a couple years ago, but even way, way, way before that, because we had buddies at Konami, we got to premiere the DDR version of Your Rain, you remember that?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I do.
[SPEAKER_01]: That it is.
[SPEAKER_01]: I will never forget how we teased everybody with like little bits and pieces and clips of that song for like three hours and people actually stayed to hear the whole damn thing because they're awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know, that was really cool
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey, you're in chat.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey, then you can see everybody there, chat.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey, while you say hello to people in chat, I thought since Loki's not on the phone tonight, we need to tip our hat at the one and only Loki somehow.
[SPEAKER_01]: Little known fact about Loki, he actually was not a full-time show host when the show started.
[SPEAKER_01]: He did not join full-time until episode 20, and Jamie and I made the decision to anoint him as a host of the program because...
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, he just never went away.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, he came to every single program, but he was very passionate and obviously has done a lot, a lot, a lot, a lot, a lot of great work for OLR over the years and is just as much a part of the station as the rest of us.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I got to play a Loki remix because he's a very talented remixer.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is probably one of the most famous remixes he did over the years.
[SPEAKER_01]: So you ready for this?
[SPEAKER_01]: This is Don't Play Nice, the Zodiac Mix by Loki and Verbilicious.
[SPEAKER_01]: Ooh, then don't answer your iPhone when you hear this, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_06]: Checking if the DJ's hot, I'm just chillin'
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, let's switch it up.
[SPEAKER_01]: Loki versus Verbalicious with Don't Play Nice, the Zodiac mix.
[SPEAKER_01]: 11 minutes till the plug gets pulled.
[SPEAKER_01]: We don't have a lot of time, but hey, you know, Orange Lounge Radio started as a, you know, DDR, 2DX, Beatmania, Parappa, you know, all those music games.
[SPEAKER_01]: We started as a station like that.
[SPEAKER_01]: We all came together, DarkSakura, myself, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_01]: We all met playing DDR at the local arcade.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, literally, that is how Orange Lounge Radio started.
[SPEAKER_01]: Do you remember the first time we met, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_07]: I do, actually.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wasn't it over in Milpitas?
[SPEAKER_01]: It was.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was the day we all went to go play Para Para Paradise together.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, and so Siege was there and doing his thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's right, raving to the beat.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, Jamie, what would you say is your favorite DDR song of all freaking time?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'd have to actually say the brilliant T.O.G.,
[SPEAKER_01]: Brilliant2U OG.
[SPEAKER_01]: Shit, I had something else queued up.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_01]: I can find it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know I have it.
[SPEAKER_01]: What is it about Brilliant2U OG that makes it your very fave?
[SPEAKER_01]: Because I'm going to do a block here of the host's favorite DDR song because I know Loki's and I'll play mine too.
[SPEAKER_07]: I had Love by Sonic Dream.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, no.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love, I adore that song, but it wasn't my favorite DDR song.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's all good.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think I have OG Remix queued up somewhere here.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just gotta dig for it a little bit.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not a problem.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just thought that it was different, you know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I thought that I liked the mix itself, and the steps were a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's one of the first harder songs I've done.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh my gosh, I do not have B4U Orchestra Groove.
[SPEAKER_01]: How is that?
[SPEAKER_01]: I have, like, the entire DDR Freak Radio playlist from back in the day, and somehow I don't have B4U Orchestra Groove.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, let me see.
[SPEAKER_01]: How is that?
[SPEAKER_07]: I have it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I might have it.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, I have the third mix.
[SPEAKER_01]: Wasn't it on third mix?
[SPEAKER_07]: Good money, DDR...
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm looking in my portable drive now.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, then we'll do mine and Loki's first while we dig for that so we don't have a lot of time.
[SPEAKER_07]: I wouldn't object to you playing Love.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright, then we might play Love just in the interest of time and everyone will just know for the record that Rob screwed up.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey, what better way to end OLR than me screwing up?
[SPEAKER_01]: Here it is, Love by Sonic Dream.
[SPEAKER_01]: One of Jamie's favorite DDR songs.
[SPEAKER_01]: One of them.
I believe in
[SPEAKER_01]: Here comes my favorite DDR song of all time and it's from a home version.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'm pretty sure this song is Matt's favorite DDR song.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright, it's almost that time.
[SPEAKER_01]: We're like four minutes from the end, or about five minutes.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm going to go a little bit over, but Jamie, it's just about over.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know what else to say.
[SPEAKER_01]: What, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_07]: I just said yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: I thought you said Rob.
[SPEAKER_01]: I thought you were going to do the Rob, Rob, Rob thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_01]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, we... What?
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: We promise.
[SPEAKER_01]: I hate you.
[SPEAKER_01]: I hate you so much.
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know what, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_01]: It's time for you to get the F out of Life 365.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, we swore that this was going to be our last song, and it's not.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's actually our next-to-last song in Live Through CC5, but it's very fitting for the end of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's 2 Live Crew with one of their classics.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, here it is.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anything else you want to say about this song, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_07]: I were just...
[SPEAKER_07]: I have memories of this song from my freshman year of high school.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll put it that way.
[SPEAKER_01]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: And we dedicate this to all the OLR listeners who have stuck with us for five years through thick and thin, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: We dedicate it to all of you and hope you'll be able to recover from the message in this song.
[SPEAKER_01]: Here it is, 2 Life Crew.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's my house, and if you don't like it, get the fuck out.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's my house.
Go!
[SPEAKER_02]: If you like it, get the fuck out!
[SPEAKER_02]: Get the fuck out my house!
[SPEAKER_02]: You missed me, bitch!
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: That would be fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sorry, the chat was correct to me.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's supposed to be 9 Pacific, which would be midnight Eastern.
[SPEAKER_01]: I want to be moved out by midnight Eastern, which is only about an hour away, and I have dinner planned.
[SPEAKER_01]: So this is it, the last song.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm going to introduce it here in just a moment.
[SPEAKER_01]: But Jamie, do you have any last things you want to say?
[SPEAKER_07]: A couple things.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_07]: Number one, Live365, fuck you for giving in to the...
[SPEAKER_07]: whole RIAA scare tactic bullshit going on.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's the number one thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Number two, I really like hamburgers.
[SPEAKER_07]: And number three, cinnamon buns from Ikea are really, really, really tasty and smell really, really, really good, but they're really, really bad for you.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the very final thing is reject false icons.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have something, a new one.
[SPEAKER_07]: This has been my catchphrase for life.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nothing changes until you make it change.
[SPEAKER_01]: That is true.
[SPEAKER_01]: Very true.
[SPEAKER_01]: And now we're making it change.
[SPEAKER_01]: We're going to change tomorrow is when it all starts.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is kind of sad.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's a sad moment.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's happy and it's sad.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_01]: I feel bad for all the folks that have really supported us over five and a half years of internet radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know the music and all that stuff is going away, but obviously the show is still going to be there.
[SPEAKER_01]: We're still going to be there.
[SPEAKER_01]: The community is still going to be there.
[SPEAKER_01]: The Oil Army is still going to be there.
[SPEAKER_01]: Nothing is really going away except our stream.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, Rob.
[SPEAKER_01]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_07]: We're starting over.
[SPEAKER_01]: We are starting over.
[SPEAKER_01]: Indeed.
[SPEAKER_01]: True words.
[SPEAKER_01]: So that's it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just want to say thank you to everybody in chat right now.
[SPEAKER_01]: Everybody who couldn't be here tonight but wanted to be.
[SPEAKER_01]: Everybody that supported us for five and a half years and please continue to support us in the future.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's going to bring us to the last song.
[SPEAKER_01]: And Jamie, do you want me to hang up or just keep you on through this?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll stay on.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is what's going to happen, folks.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm going to play the last song, which, you know, after thinking long and hard, we wanted to pick one song that really just encompassed everything that Orange Lounge Radio in the past five and a half years.
[SPEAKER_01]: If you could just sum it up into one song, this is it.
[SPEAKER_01]: So we're going to play this, and then that's it.
[SPEAKER_01]: You're going to hear silence, and then you're going to hear the stream get cut, and that's the end.
[SPEAKER_01]: So...
[SPEAKER_01]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Any last, last, last things, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_01]: Because this is really it.
[SPEAKER_01]: We're not saying anything after the song.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's over.
[SPEAKER_01]: The plug's getting pulled.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess out with the old and with the new.
[SPEAKER_01]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_01]: So here it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: Abba-solutely?
[SPEAKER_01]: Abba-solutely.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know that herring roe I was talking about earlier?
[SPEAKER_07]: The brand is Abba.
[SPEAKER_01]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: So you have tangents.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's us.
[SPEAKER_01]: You will keep going on with randomness as long as I let you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, I will.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, play the damn song.
[SPEAKER_01]: Group hug and chat, everybody.
[SPEAKER_01]: Here it is, the last song and then the plug getting pulled.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thank you from myself, DarkSakura, Loki, everybody.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thank you for your support of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: We are starting over.
[SPEAKER_01]: We'll see you tomorrow night at allgames.com.
[SPEAKER_01]: Good night, everybody.
[SPEAKER_03]: and more.