Orange Lounge Radio
Who's the host?
Dark Sakura
Sky and Loki
Tonight, March 13th, 2011
Microsoft shatters sales records
EA bans a player from Dragon Age 2 unintentionally
And despite what's happened to Guitar Hero, could Dance Hero be a reality?
Orange Lounge Radio
Hello my friends out there on the internet and welcome back to another week of Orange Lounge Radio
It's the show where every gamer has a voice
We do tape live every Sunday night at 6 o'clock Pacific
Right after the Bobby Black Wolf show at AllGames.com
www.AllGames.com
My name is Rob Roberts, I'll be joining you over the next few hours with my co-host
Not here tonight, sadly
The one and only Dark Sakura, Jamie Summers
She is out of town, don't feel too bad for her though
She's on her way to Disneyland
So, you know, how can you feel sorry for her when she's going to the happiest freaking place on earth
And we're stuck here doing the show in her place
Oh well
Anyhow, so she might be joining us a little later for a call, we'll see
But joining us here, as always, say hello at least to tech master, Loki is here
Yes I am
Yes, how you doing, Loki?
I'm doing great
Awesome, good to hear it
Everything going well with the baby and all that good stuff?
Yes
Good, good
Alright, and joining us tonight, since unfortunately Dark Sakura is not here
We do have a third host sitting in the studio with us
And he hasn't been on the show in quite some time
But say hello everybody to Matt2
Well hello Rob number one
How are you doing Matt2?
I'm doing well yourself
I'm pretty good, I feel like we just had this conversation
It seems like deja vu, but you know, we're not in the matrix or anything so it can't be
Yeah, for the podcast listeners, this is take two of the live show because we had a little screw up
But just pretend I didn't ask you these questions just five minutes ago
Anyhow, Matt2 hasn't been here in about two years and five studios ago
No, we've had like five studios throughout all of OLR
You were in the last one that we did
So it's been a little while
But some of the folks that listen to Hoard House, my Warcraft show, might know you as Grandpa Warcraft
Yes, that's right, I am the Deckard Cain of your show
Yes
Alright, so what types of video games do you play?
Just tell us, I'll ask you about your gaming weekend a little bit
But generally, what types of video games do you like to play? What consoles do you own?
It's mainly MMOs for the moment and a lot of iOS games
I'm playing a lot of games on the iPhone 4 and soon my iPad 2 if it ever gets here
But I own a 360 and I'm still debating on whether getting a Kinect
But my console history goes way back to Atari 5200 and every NES system
And then made the transition to PC games when games like Descent and Duke Nukem 3D were uber back in the day
So is that really where you like to game the most, just PC?
It kind of fell into PC. I got the 360 because of Halo
I was definitely a fan of the Halo series until recently
And other first-person shooters
Oh, you say that a little stinging like, I did not like a certain Halo game that really ruined it for me
Is that what's going on?
Well, I bought Reach and I beat it on hard, not legendary, within the first few hours
I went, oh, this is going to be focusing on the multiplayer side, isn't it?
And sure enough it does
Which I'm an okay fan of
But I do like a lot of story
And I was really disappointed in how quick the first person went through
But, you know, there's other first-person shooters out there, Call of Duty, Gears of War, things like that
But for the time being it's 360, debating on the Kinect
And a lot of Warcraft on the PC and iOS 4 games
You do anything else on the PC besides Warcraft?
Not as of recent, I tried Star Trek Online
Jamie Summers convinced me to give it a try
As a huge, huge, huge Trekkie
All your WoW characters are named after Star Trek characters
They used to be
I thought you had one named like, B'Elanna
And I'm like, I know who that is
I was the other guy that watched Voyager
When I first started Warcraft, all my characters were named after obscure Star Trek characters
Not Picard and Riker, because that's just too pretentious
And those names are taken in five minutes
Yeah, I'm sure they are
I went Neelix, Kes, B'Elanna, Darmok
If you remember the Darmok
Who liked Kes?
Well, I never leveled her up
She's a rogue sitting there collecting dust, obviously
And now they're all Latin names
Because now I'm Alliance
And it's much more formal on that side of the...
Ho ho
Yeah, exactly
PC games-wise, Fable, I played a lot of Fable back in the day
Awesome
And stuff like that
Alright, so it sounds like you've played quite a variety of different things
I try to
Do you do the iOS stuff now?
That's where gaming seems to be going in some ways
I do
At least it's casual
I confess I downloaded Angry Birds Seasons today
Because I figured it's appropriate
It's St. Patrick's Day on Thursday
They play Irish music in the background
And there's shamrocks everywhere
And pots of gold if you hit, you get bonus points
So yeah, that's my new diction
I did download, reluctantly, or regretfully, Mega Man 2
And it doesn't work when you don't have an actual tactile controller
Don't get me started
I know, and I listened to your podcast about it and it made sense
But I love Mega Man
It's a huge, huge favorite series of mine
So I wanted to get it because I'm a supporter
And I can't even get through the air stage because I can't
When they play the buttons, so
Well, they have those little things, like stickers that you can put on your iPad
Or, you know, iPods or whatever
To create tactile controls for the touchpad stuff
I might invest in that with my iPad 2
Because little buttons like on my phone and you gotta take them off and put them back on
I don't know
They actually have some pretty sweet ones
There's ones that were through, like, ThinkGeek or whatever
They had actual, looks like an arcade joystick that plugs on there
Which is kind of cool
And then they had some that just kind of stick to the side suction cup wise
But apparently they're pretty decent
I mean, but really they just need to come out with something better
So yeah, when it comes to the iPhone 4
And what my iPhone 4 and iOS games is kind of my main focus right now
I'm not on WoW or the PC games
They're good bathroom games
I find the, like, Cut the Rope is a great potty game, actually
For cutting the rope?
Yes
For pinching the loaf?
Wow
Out on the ice tour coming soon
Anyhow, speaking of St. Patrick's Day, since you brought up St. Patrick's Day
You were kind enough
I like this, when we invite you to the show you do bribe us a little bit
Well, yeah
I brought this gigantic beer in a green, like, can thing
It is green, I didn't think of that
It's imported from Canadian
I love Canadian
I know, yeah, we love Canadian
America's hat
America's big, liberal, loving hat
It's America's suburb
Anyhow, no, obviously I'm just giving them a hard time
But, so I'm gonna drink this beer
Since you drove tonight, I can drink a beer
That's right
I'm gonna get drunk in Jamie's house when she's not here
Yay!
I brought her for Loki
Then I'm gonna go pass out in the vault
Yeah, but I have to drive and I don't like beer, so, sorry
So, anyway, let's start the celebrating a little early
There you go
Oh, I was so hoping that would explode in your face
Hey, that's not nice
It would ruin his microphone
It would ruin the microphone and the keyboard
Now, the audience
I have to do a third take
No, the audience doesn't know is it's not your average, you know, Budweiser 12 ounce can of beer
It's 18
It's a 40
No, it's not a 40
It's 18 ounces, I believe, or 20
And it's a Pilsner with a mild aftertaste and it's very hoppy
What do you think, Rob?
Not bad for beer
Okay, good
But I can drink one of these
You know, usually I don't screw around with beer
You don't?
No, I'm just like, let's fill the glass with vodka, splash of cranberry, I'm good
And a twist of lime
Yeah
But after one of those, Rob, I do get a little tipsy, so I can only imagine what the drive home
My driving you home is gonna be like in a couple hours
Well, look, this will be, I guess you could say in some ways, my gift to the listeners
You know what, it's been, it's been a crazy week in the world
It has been a crazy week in the world and, you know, I realize some people play video games to escape
Sometimes the crazy things that are going on in the world
And I like this show to kind of be like that too
That, you know, if we can give you a few lulls tonight to take your mind off of some of the not so lullsy things going on in the world
Then I think mission accomplished
Sounds like a plan
So
Share some
Alright, let's talk about our gaming weeks
And the type of video games that you've been playing this week
Since we do always start off the show that way
Loki, how was your gaming week? What have you been playing?
I didn't play much
I played Grand Theft Auto at work
I played Naughty Bear for like a few minutes
Which the game is really low budget
But it's kind of funny because they have this like British guy who, you know, yells out these, you know, different things like
De-fluffication!
You know, it's just like, it's so weird
It's just a weird, weird game
De-fluffication sounds like something you could go to prison for
I know
But yeah, it's a weird, really low budget game
They're doing a game of the year edition that's coming out in May
So if you want to, you know, pick it up later on I guess you could
But honestly it's really low budget
But it's kind of fun, I guess
Because I mean the whole game feels like a really kiddie game but you're just brutally murdering these teddy bears
It's just not bloody enough though, that's the only downside to it
And then mainly just working on Grand Theft Auto edits at home
And I finally finished, I think, some of the stuff that I got to burn my new discs that we're going to be playing at work now
Which is incredibly bloody now because I made the blood effects really huge
But it serves two purposes
Needs more blood!
It serves two purposes. One, people are always saying, well, you know, I swear I hit you with those, you know, the minigun or something like that
And I'm like, no you didn't
Well this way you'll know if you hit somebody because the blood effect is just so huge that you'll see that bullet spray from, you know, pretty far away
And because it looks fucking awesome
Because you shoot somebody and it's just hilarious because it's just all this blood everywhere
Um, I'm trying to think of one else
Is there ever enough blood for you, Loki?
Yeah, I mean, I don't know, it's just fun to see what I can do with the game
On a completely random note since you're talking about blood and all of this stuff
One of these things that I saw this week that, um, I think she needs her own video game
You know the rap artist Lil' Kim?
She has a new album out called Black Friday
And I don't know if you've seen the album cover but it's very like Kill Bill with blood splattering everywhere
And there's this little decapitated pink wig that's on the ground on the album cover
That I think is supposed to symbolize Nicki Minaj and their little feud, I don't know
But, um, I'm thinking she should have her own video game
I don't know, there's something about Lil' Kim
No, I don't think so
What, you wouldn't play a Lil' Kim video game?
No, I would not play a Lil' Kim video game
Why is that?
Because, I, I'm sorry, she, what, she thinks she's some sort of sexy samurai there?
I'm sorry, that does not happen
She's got big ol' boobies
Oh, oh, well in that case she has all the requirements to fill, you know, the samurai position
Big tits, done
You're a samurai now
If there were a video game called Big Titted Samurai, you would check it out
You would at least kind of look, you would pick up the box and look at the back
I would look at that, but, you know, I'm just saying though, it
Only goes rated M
It, it's just, it's stupid
It's stupid, it's stupid that artists have feuds
No one cares
Oh no, this artist doesn't like this artist
Oh no, who cares, it's just
Westside rap and East Coast rap
Oh god, so stupid
Yeah, you're all gangsters, oh my god
Oh, such the feud
Alright, sorry to derail the conversation
But I don't know, when you were talking about Gran Todano and blood splattering everywhere
I was thinking about that album cover I saw and I was like
I would play her in a game
Yes, exactly, I agree with Kitsune
I would play a Robogatia video game
I'd play anything from that company because
Robogatia's really weird
As, you know
And by the way
Many of the other movies that they put out
Since I'm very rude and the second take made me derail a little bit
I forgot to introduce the chat room tonight
Chat.OrangeOnTrady.com
If you are listening live at All Games Radio on this Sunday, March the 13th
You should hop on over to our chat room and join us live
Chat.OrangeOnTrady.com
And besides, a big-tit samurai game, that's just basically, you know, the last Ninja Gaiden game
Couldn't they just take, was Dead or Alive 4
And all those big-titty characters and give them swords
And they already got the basic code down for that
That's kind of Soul Calibur
Or Soul Calibur
Well, they already kind of did that though
With the last Ninja Gaiden game, they had, you know
Bonus characters from Dead or Alive
And from the other, you know, DS, Dragon Sword game
And that kind of stuff, but
Once again, you know, I don't think we should really give
A rap star a video game
Have we not learned from 50 Cent?
Really, I mean, Blood in the Sand was amazing
I do give you the fact that it is so ridiculous
That it is awesome, but
I just don't think Lil' Kim has that same appeal
Well, rap stars have their own game, isn't it?
Rap star, rap hero
Which is not a bad game
It really isn't
A lot of people want to pass it off, it's like
Oh, I don't like rap, but if you look at it as a game
They invested more in, especially coming from Konami
Or what, I'm sure somebody else did it and they published it
But coming from that kind of that same family
If you look at that next to like DDR
Which has been recycled so many times
Or the Karaoke Revolution games
It's like, wow, they're the only ones that are like
Really doing something new and exciting as Def Jam rap stars
With their community features
That's really amazing that they have all that
And they didn't put in anything else
Hey, we have this cool dancing game that has camera support
That we, you know, people dance in front of a camera
Could we have community support for that?
Nope, sorry, that would be forward thinking, of course
Or, you know, how about
Now's the time, seriously, Guitar Freaks, you know, Drummania
Maybe you give it another go and not make a crappy game this time
No, no, let it be, let it be
Put it out to pasture
Moo
Alright
Oh, I bet we'll get another Guitar Hero game
We'll see
They're looking at you like
The money's there
They're just waiting for, you know
They've milked the cow dry
They just have to wait for it to melt to come back
So you're not saying like we're gonna have a new Guitar Hero game
Like this year or next year
Because, no, they announced it's done
This year
But you think there'll be that renaissance
In like three years' time
They've announced, they didn't say that they've dissolved the franchise completely
They said there's no Guitar Hero, no Tony Hawk game this year
Okay, alright
That's very tinfoil hat of you, but we'll see
Oh, come on
They think money's there
I mean, we were talking with Bobby beforehand
You know, and it's gonna be a story we're gonna be covering later on
Talking about a trademark that they had
A long time ago, I remember with Drum Villain and Dance Hero
And everyone was like, oh no
Here they go, copying DDR
Well, you know what, I mean, seriously
They're just like, okay, what's Homarnax doing that seems profitable
I would like to see what that whole Guitar Villain idea was all about
Unless that was, I always envisioned that that was just to protect someone else from doing it
That'd be dumb
I mean, but anyways
They're basically just gonna look at whatever
Homarnax is doing that's profitable
Then they're gonna copy it
I mean, that's...
What's gonna happen? I mean, seriously
If Rockman 3 continues to be profitable
I mean, granted the game didn't sell as well as
You know, maybe 2 did, but
Once again, they have a lot of download content
It's not really market
You can't really look at the game sales
And say, oh, this game, you know, the series is dead
It's just, I think their download content is doing really well
But, once again though
The dance games are doing really well now
Like Just Dance and Dance Central and stuff like that
So, of course they're gonna be like
We have this completely original idea that we're gonna put out
And you're gonna buy it because it's part of the hero franchise
You know, our wonderful hero franchise that we support greatly
No, we didn't kill off the hero franchise
We're bringing it back with dance hero
I think Matt's got some angst left over from last week
No, it's just...
It's just so retarded
They're so two-faced
Oh, the music industry, music genre's dead
It's so dead
Oh, but here's our dance game
It's part of the music genre, right?
No, it's a different music genre
We were talking about the other music genre
They'll do whatever, you know, has money behind it
If they can make money doing it, they're gonna do it
Just like there's gonna be another Call of Duty game
Because it's Call of Duty
It makes money
Somewhere in there we were talking about Loki's gaming week
And I get the feeling he's done
So, Matt, too, do you want to share your gaming week?
What you've been playing?
I'm afraid
No, my gaming week
Again, I do play Warcraft semi-regularly
I'm in class right now
So that inhibits some things
I've got different characters I work on there
I'm part of a guild with some IRL friends
So that helps pass the time with WoW
Gaming week, Angry Birds is really addicting
I'm going through all of them
Trying to get three stars and everything
For me, it's all about the physics
The math behind it, I get the right angle
And the right, I don't know
You know what, I feel for him
I don't want to cut the rope, but I do
No, I'm sorry
I understand the physics part of it
And that's kind of cool and stuff
I promise I only play when I poop
I do not play when I poop
Sometimes I play in bed
I tried to give
I have played in bed, actually
I have tried to give Angry Birds
I gave Angry Birds a try
This is one of the games I bought
Everybody likes it, so I'm going to buy it
It's 99 cents, what the hell
I didn't play it for the longest time
I actually played it
It's okay, but I just
I don't see how everybody's so obsessed about this game
If it was Scorched Earth
There's no discussion
And that has physics
And angle calculation and all that fun stuff
And tanks
See, that's what Angry Birds needs
If you played Angry Birds
And they released an ad
Every time you killed a pig, it would explode bloody
Would you then play it?
No, I wouldn't, because it's a cheap cash-in
Just like all these holiday add-ons are cheap cash-in
What if the pig exploded
And then bacon comes out the USB slot
On your phone?
Okay, really it's alright
Keep your protein to yourself
I forgot to mention it because it wasn't really part of my gaming week
But I made bacon ice cream this week
Eww
It's actually breakfast ice cream
Breakfast ice cream?
Well, it's because there's waffle cone in there
And maple syrup
Bacon waffles
Did you cover it in chocolate butter?
That's something you'd order at IHOP
Where you can get dessert for breakfast
Seriously, that French toast that's fucking stuffed with cream cheese
That is not breakfast
I had chicken and waffles for breakfast today
That's better than bacon-flavored ice cream
Uh, actually
Anyways, think about getting chicken and waffles at IHOP
Don't. It's alright
But it's not good
I mean, it's not like
Mmm, that's really yummy
I'm full now
Somewhere in here was Angry Birds and IOS
And now we're talking about frying the birds
You said bacon! This is all your fault
You did say bacon
Okay, so I did make bacon ice cream
I think I put too much bacon in it
And I know how- Nonsense!
Exactly, nonsense
But it's just
You have to really be in the mood for bacon ice cream
Because if you're eating it
It's ice cream-y and then all of a sudden salty
And it's just like
Huh? Why is there salt in there?
I mean, it's a little strange
My wife likes it actually, though
She likes the bacon ice cream
She is a horrible Jew
Horrible
Nah, I'm just kidding. You know I love her
Anyhow, so yeah, Angry Birds, right?
Yeah, it's a lot of
IOS games on my iPhone 4
And again, as I mentioned, I'm getting an iPad 2
Hopefully by week's end
I don't want to wait in lines and get it
So I ordered it online
Once I have that, it'll sync in and play Angry Birds
And huge, huge, uh
What's that? 9.7 inch- Angry Birds HD
HD, well, it's not Retina display, unfortunately
It's HD because it's in the 9.7 inch
Diagonal screen, whatever
Holy crap, that's a game that's really gonna utilize HD graphics
Hell yeah
You see those pigs' beady eyes winking at you
Aside from that, I
The pig is saying no
To see you know
The last thing I'm thinking about picking up
And hopefully you're fourth guest in the chat room at
chat.orangeloudradia.com
Yeah, so you have been listening for a little while
I think you've been slipping into this role very easily
I've been thinking about picking up Dragon Age 2
I had original Dragon Age, I downloaded a lot of the
DLC content
I like the DLC content
I was disappointed that it was very out of
chronological order
Once you pass the game, you download some DLC
It pretty much says, oh, just pretend that you didn't
You know, end the game and
This is extra stuff
But I'm curious about Dragon Age 2
Getting reviews, I'm hearing mostly good
But I defer to your chat room if anyone's
Bought it, I appreciate your opinions
And I might be picking up that and
Detoxing from WoW for a bit
And then going over to my Xbox
And of course, you know what
The best part about any new Dragon
Age game coming out is of course going to be
Gay sex scene!
Yay! Gay sex scene in Dragon
Age! Hooray!
Let's talk you more penis
Here's what I have a problem with Bioware
There's such fucking teases
There's no nudity, and there's definitely
No sex scenes
They just kind of like, jump on the bed
I'm looking for this
See, look at that, that's tongue right there
That was some tongue, some big gay kissing
Yes, there's
Woman on woman and man on woman
Whatever you want, it's all there
If we can have boobs in God of War, why can't we have boobs
In, you know, Dragon Age, or Mass Effect
Because it just wouldn't be classy
Oh, who cares!
I thought it was classy
I would rather die than spend a moment
Not here with you
Well then fine, they need to consult with Hugh Hefner
To make a classy, you know
Topless woman game, okay
I mean, seriously
I don't understand why they can't do this
And you know what, they can do full frontal for guys on there
They did it in Grand Theft Auto
In, you know, the Lost in Damned expansion
So, if they can do it classy there
Then why can't they
But the important thing is classy
Classy, topless women
I'm trying to think of a classy penis
And I don't think there really is one
Oh, why yes, Guinevere
This tea tastes rather lovely
Yes, I'm quite enjoying
This little tea and crumpets that we're having today
Oh, but I seem to have lost my bra
Have you seen my bra?
That would be the game that Loki wants to play
Classy, topless women
That sounds very boring
They only have swords
That would conclude my gaming week because we're moving on to another topic
That I think is probably a different podcast
Right, then
Moving on, my gaming week
A lot of the same old stuff, Warcraft
You Don't Know Jack and a lot of those fun games
But I did play one new game this week that I wanted to talk about
And if you've been listening over the past couple of weeks
You know I've been very excited about Torchlight
Coming out on Xbox Live Arcade
Torchlight
Was kind of an indie, it's a startup
Studio, some of the folks that used to be
Blizzard are a part of this studio
They put together Torchlight
And it was on Steam a couple of years ago
And it's been the subject of some of their
$10 sales
I think at one point you might have been able to get the game for $5
But in a nutshell, Torchlight
Is very much inspired by Diablo 2
And obviously we've gone through a huge drought
There hasn't been a Diablo game in many
Many years, the last Diablo game was
What, 99? 2000?
Yes, there's one coming out
But that doesn't help me now
So Torchlight was really there to fill the void
If you like those dungeon crawling games
Where you kind of get the items
And socket the items, have your talent trees, all that stuff
The one thing it lacked
Unfortunately, multiplayer
Multiplayer was lacking in the game
But it is a $10 game
At some point, $20 I think is the most you're going to pay for Torchlight
I think if you buy it at retail
Which is still pretty good value considering
I think they still charge $30 for Diablo 2
In the battle chest all these years later
So it's not a bad deal
Randomly generated dungeons and all that good stuff
Never the same game twice, woohoo
So finally they ported this thing to Xbox Live Arcade
And they've had to make some changes with the game
And that kind of had a lot of people nervous
Because the dungeon crawly games are usually very reliant on point and click
And these style of games I kind of throw all the way back to
I don't know if you remember this on the PC
A very, very old PC game called Rogue
Did you ever play Rogue way back in the day?
Diablo's clearly inspired by this game
From way back in the day
And I want to say, isn't NetHack a derivative of that too?
I think, or am I crazy?
I don't know, something I was reading about, I haven't played that one
I just remember Rogue back in the Commodore 64
They're all kind of like this
So it was very interesting to kind of see that style of game now on the Xbox
Because this isn't really the type of game we see a lot on Xbox I think
It's not an action-y game like Tomb Raider
It's not an intense role-playing game like Final Fantasy
It's kind of somewhere in between
So it's neat to see something like this on Xbox
But they had to change some things
There's less pointy and clicking
You attack with the X button
Your menus are totally different now
Because you don't really have the bag that you have everything in
It's just straight up, you have 50 slots and different tabs
It's really weird to navigate
It's a little overwhelming at first
And I've got to be honest
Torchlight's biggest drawback for me on the Xbox 360 is
What they had to do to convert it to console I think in some ways
The text is very small
So if you don't have a big TV
You might be in a little bit of trouble
There's some framerate issues and it's noticeable
When I was going through some of the dungeons
There's a lot of enemies on the screen at once
And you're trying to do some attacks
It just seems like the framerate really drops
And then suddenly everything's dead which is cool
But not the smoothness that I came to expect on the PC
And just the weird, having so many buttons
To send your pet to town you have to bring up your menu
With start, hit the back button to bring up the pet menu
And then hit the Y button to send him to town
There's a lot to it which I understand
That's what they have to do to make a PC game work on the Xbox 360
With minimal loss
You don't want the game to lose anything
And the good news is it doesn't
It's still got that same kind of feel to it
But unfortunately these few drawbacks
Make it really hard for me to recommend on the 360
When I know most 360 owners own a PC
So my point is
If you have this game on the PC already
I think you're good
Like you really only need this if you insist
Like I've got to have something to play on the TV
Or I really want to have this on console
I want to go for the achievements
Those are all really good reasons I suppose
But I would say if you've never played the game before
And you're kind of trying to decide
Do I want to play this?
Go check out the PC demo
Not the Xbox 360 one
Because I think the PC demo is a little bit better representative
Of what Torchlight really is
So that would be my recommendation
But it's not a bad game
I just feel like it lost a little something
When it came over from the PC
The PC version is
Excuse me, really superior
So check that out on the PC
If you must, if you don't have a computer
Good enough or something
I guess you could always use the Xbox 360 one as a substitute
It's not bad
It's just not, again, that same level as the PC
So that was pretty much my gaming week
So let's talk a little bit about housekeeping
Not a whole lot in housekeeping I want to talk about right now
I want to talk about something after this first story here
But I will say, of course, our Twitter
Twitter.com slash O-L-R if you want to add us on Twitter
Or you can always add us on Facebook as well
Facebook.com slash OrangeLoungeRadio
A good way to always follow us
And we'll see what the latest and greatest is about our show
Forgot to mention my gaming week
Since I'm not really playing it yet
But it will be tomorrow
I'm getting a Japanese 3DS
So that's coming tomorrow
Nice, what made you decide to take the plunge and get the Japanese 3DS?
Because I like everything early
Even his ice cream for breakfast
I have a problem with needing to have things early
I'm getting a Japanese 3DS with Nintendogs
And then Ridge Racer
Only because Pilotwings wasn't out yet
Otherwise I would have gotten Pilotwings
We have to bring that to the studio next week
I got to see one a while ago
But I want to see what that finished product looks like
I'm sure Jamie would love to check it out too
It would be fun too if they have good import games later on
Because sometimes Japan gets stuff before we do
Like Smash Brothers and stuff
And I'm still getting a US one when that comes out
With Street Fighter 4
Because you have an addiction
It's so funny too
Because just last week you were all
Last week was a really good Loki hatin' on Nintendo show
And now he's sitting here going
Yeah, I'm buying 2DS, 3DS's
It's just really funny
Hey, I never said I wasn't buying the 3DS
No, I know, I know
It just makes you mad that they don't reach their full potential
Exactly
I don't have a problem with Nintendo as far as making hardware and stuff
I just have a problem with them not
Yeah, like you said, reaching their full potential
Remaking games, come on
These Nintendo 64 ports to the 3DS
That's just some cheap shit right there
I'm going into our chatroom
At chat.oransonshady.com
Darktoygak says
Loki is going to make 3D porn on it, no doubt
No, I'm not
Let's see
Yeah, what's the old adage about new hardware coming out?
Time to penis?
Is the whole like, how long before somebody tries to put their penis on it?
BlackWolf in our chatroom says
Loki bought Nintendogs, he's part of the problem
You are part of the problem
I am part of the problem
But, okay
Here's why I bought Nintendogs, okay
And this is a completely weird reasoning for
Cats, that's the reason I wanted
Well, not the cats too
I have a cat that's already annoying
No, the reason I bought Nintendogs plus cats
Is because I think that shows off the 3D pretty well
And this is something I'm really going to be kind of showing to my co-workers
To kind of say, hey look, check out the thing
Oh, research purposes
Yes
I mean, I
Yeah, whatever
Alright, fair enough
It was, okay, it was either that or Professor Layton
Because I can't read Japanese so that's not going to do me any good
Or there's like some
Cube puzzle game, no thanks
And then the rest of the games are coming out over here anyways
Once again, it would have been
If they had pilot wings, I would have bought pilot wings
I will get pilot wings when it comes out in the US
Alright
Alright, well we'll be hearing more about the 3DS next week then for sure
Yes, absolutely
Awesome
Alright, well let's get into the news tonight
And Loki's going to start us off with some news
And like I mentioned a minute ago
A lot of stuff going on in the world
And some of it reaching into video games for all of us
Yeah, of course
You may have heard that there were some major earthquakes in Japan
And tsunamis and all that fun stuff
That caused a lot of damage
And because of that, they're having issues with being able to keep the power up
And so they're asking companies to conserve power
And bring back their services once that power has been restored fully
So because of that, Square Enix has decided to shut off the servers for Final Fantasy XIV and Final Fantasy XI
For at least one week
And also other companies affected by this as well
Well, Konami, they're shutting off the servers for Metal Gear Online
Which, to be honest, until I read that, I forgot that Metal Gear Online even existed
So yeah, I'm sure lots of people are playing that
So yeah, those are the two companies so far that are included
Part of that, who knows what other companies will be having that
That's still pretty big though
Yeah, because you're talking about two major MMOs, for better or for worse
I mean, I know we've given Final Fantasy XIV a hard time on the show
One major MMO, one major pile of crap
But you and I spent many years on Final Fantasy XI and it still certainly has its fans
So that's kind of not something we hear a lot in the gaming world
Where it's like an MMO literally gets put on hold because of real life
And it's just kind of, there's an old adage, especially in Warcraft
And I'm sure the other MMOs have this too, is that RL greater than wow or whatever your game of choice is
And I think that especially is kind of what's coming into play this week
And I can't see how really anyone can complain about this
I'm curious if they're going to shut down for that week if they're going to issue credits to all those customers for that week
Because it's on their bad and their decision to shut it down
I think they're going to, I think they're going to do a free month or something like that
I think they will, and I think I read somewhere it is confirmed they're going to gift them the month of April
I think that's awfully generous
I honestly, in a situation like this, I really don't think they would necessarily owe them anything
I think most people would understand but you would always have that one person
And I'm sure all of us have probably seen the pictures and the damage that we have
And definitely take a moment to look at that
But I don't, my gut tells me the extensive damage they have
One week, them shutting down, I think it's going to be the first of many weeks
Or rotating weeks off
Yeah
So just maybe time to take the games offline for a little while
Or maybe something else you could consider doing is seeing what you can do to help
And that was kind of the other thing I wanted to make sure I mentioned at some point tonight
Obviously we've all seen what's been going on in Japan
And it's just, there are no words
There are no words for what is happening and what we're seeing on the television
And I just, I couldn't imagine that scale of what a tsunami can do
So I really would challenge you, all our listeners
We've been doing this show for nine plus years
Never once have we ever asked you for money
Tonight I'm going to ask you for money
And I'm going to say, you need to buy one less game this month
Or one less arcade game, Xbox Live arcade game
Or maybe not pay for an MMO for a month
Take the money that you're saving on Final Fantasy XI or Final Fantasy XIV
And go to redcross.org
And please make a donation
Everybody should try to do at least ten dollars
If all the OLR listeners could donate ten dollars
It's still a little bit for what they're really going to need in the big picture
But it's a start
And just whatever you guys can give would be so appreciated
So please consider cutting back on a game this month
And giving money to an organization that's going to need it to help a lot of people
So redcross.org is where you can go to donate
And there's many, you can do texts on your phone
I know a lot of people get our show on the iTunes store
There's a big little link there in the iTunes store
It says donate and you can donate and 100% of the proceeds go directly
But you know what, why don't you go look at the horse's mouth redcross.org
And see what you can do to help
Because even if you're strapped for cash
There's probably a lot of other volunteer types of things you could do to help
And that would all go a long way as well
So I needed to get that out there
I know I talked about our show being an escape
But there is the reality that there's people that need help
So alright
Anyhow, let's move on with some other gaming news
And this has to do with the Microsoft Kinect
A lot of big news this week about the Kinect and some of the sales figures
Some reports coming out there that 10 million Kinect units have been sold
That is from Aaron Greenberg who is one of the executives at Xbox
Wrote a tweet
And apparently this is so fast and so reaching
That Guinness World Records actually went out and said that the Kinect is the fastest selling consumer electronic device of all time
133,000 plus units each day for the first 60 days
That's faster than the iPhone or the iPad
That's really surprising to me
Because I thought with all this iPad-a-balloo last year and everything
I would have thought for sure the iPad sold faster
But I guess not
Congratulations to Microsoft for that
But seriously, Guinness, you need to find some different types of records to put in your book
Look for some tall people or people that are fat or people that can eat dog food or something like that
I don't know, just not consumer electronics
Seriously, the gamer edition of the Guinness World Records is just retarded
It's just the most popular character
It's like ugh
Well look, something else to follow that up with is that Microsoft also apparently had the biggest non-holiday month ever
February 2011 they sold over half a million Xbox 360s
535,000 to be exact
The biggest non-holiday month ever
27% up over last year
That's pretty significant because nothing is really coming out for them
And it's all this Kinect momentum
Because obviously it's these bundles with the Kinect and Kinect adventures
And now that people are starting to play them at friends' houses and see them on shows
And hear about it in school and so forth
I think the word is really starting to spread about this
And I think that's what's kind of keeping it going
So, very interesting
Not hearing a lot about the move
From what I understand though, Sony didn't have a bad month
I think Sony sold quite a few units too
They're getting closer to Nintendo
Nintendo's about to slip into third place
Which is really big news
Nintendo is not even going to slip into third place
They're in first place
I believe they sold more 360s than we used last month, didn't they?
Yeah, last month
But overall, they're in first place
They've got a lot of catching up to do before they're in third place
Honestly though, I think
With the move, it's kind of funny because
From a retail standpoint
They're treating it like there's still shortages on the move stuff
Which makes no sense
Because there's no demand for the move stuff
At all
And yet, the stuff is hard to get
For some reason
But, yeah
They're doing some stuff with the move now
That people are actually interested in
You'd be surprised, like the SOCOM4
And Killzone 3 stuff
With their stupid move gun
That they have
People are actually interested in that
And it's just
I guess it seems really stupid
But the actual peripherals that they've made for it
Aren't just like
Shells
Like the Zapper
These are actual things that do have
Integrated buttons and triggers and stuff like that
That aren't just
Ok, I pull this trigger and it
Pulls a lever that pushes this button
It's not anything like that
It's actual
Some special stuff that they're adding to these
So it's a little bit better
I think to play a first person shooter that way
But people are interested
So that may help
I am so curious about
This year's E3 and where the Kinect goes
So, props to Sony though
For at least allowing
The move to be supported by
Their big tent pole
Titles that they're putting out
Because the Kinect, not really having that
You have the Kinect games and that's it
You're not going to see Kinect support for Gears of War
At least not Gears of War 3
Maybe some spinoff or something like that
And Halo
I'm sure there's going to be some sort of spinoff Halo game
But not real
We didn't see any Kinect
Kinect support for
I don't even know what the next Microsoft title is
Because they haven't really announced anything
Actually, that's funny
Yeah, there are no first priority
Microsoft titles right now for a while
Probably the fourth quarter
We're not seeing anything like
The question of the Fable or something like that
There's no Kinect support for that stuff
So, they haven't really
Embraced it yet, I guess
I mean, they have their first party Kinect games
That they made, but there's no
Core games that are a part of that
Again, E3 I think is going to
Really be telling as to what their
Strategic direction is for
Phase 2 of the software
And possibly integrating that into their core lineup
Especially, didn't we have a story a couple weeks ago
About the whole Halo remake happening
That now the rumor is it could be Kinect
Halo Kinect or whatever
Well, I don't think, once again
I mean, they should have it be optional
Obviously, and then the other thing
Is I think they should have a couple different levels
That you go with it where
Not necessarily everything is motion controlled
But maybe head tracking, once again
I think head tracking added to a
First person shooter is just no brainer
You should be doing this anyways
For having that
Part Kinect enabled, you don't need to be running around
With Kinect for everything, just do that
It shouldn't be mass arm flailing
All over the place, that's what I fear
But it might be kind of cool, you have the controller
Or whatever, and maybe to lob a bomb
Or something, you would throw your hand up
Or something, like lob a bomb
Something very subtle
Where you're not breaking out of that
Controller thing, but I don't know
I just would not want mass arm flail
Like some Wii games are
I can see someone lobbing their controller by accident
Like a real grenade, hitting their flat screen TV
I don't design the games
I'm just trying to come up with ideas
Once again though, head tracking would be
Head tracking is pretty cool
You can implement that pretty easily
And once again
It doesn't interfere with playing a game
If you don't want to move your head around
Fine, then don't
Or you can just turn that off
That kind of support would be awesome
There's a ton of first person shooters coming out
I mean, come on
Seriously, you should be able to do that
They've got to find a way to keep reinventing
Or adding to FPS
At least for me, the allure
Has kind of died away, like I mentioned earlier with Halo
Even Medal of Honor
And stuff like that
It died for me after Quake 2
I'm like, they just don't make them
Actually, I take that back, because Quake 3 I love
They don't make them like they used to
True, the last PC first person shooter
I played was actually Jedi Knight 2
From what?
The mid 90s?
I play lightsaber, that was awesome
I only play a lot of first person shooters on
Console or PC
Especially not PC, because I cannot stand keyboard, mouse
No, no thanks
I will take an Xbox 360 controller any day
And yeah, I know
That's not really good when it comes to
Playing multiplayer online
But I don't play multiplayer online, so it doesn't matter
But yeah, the last game I played was
Crysis
With the Xbox 360 controller, it was awesome
So I do plan on picking up Crysis 2 when it comes out on consoles
Screw the PC, I don't want to upgrade my PC again
To play fucking Crysis, I already built
The PC for that, that's enough
I do need to upgrade my graphics card
So they're old
We'll be good thinking about it
Thinking forward with Kinect
It's an unknown game that maybe people don't remember
PsyOps came out for Xbox while back
You gain telekinesis power
It can move things with your mind
It was a puzzle, first person shooter
Third person, if you readjust the bit of things
I can see that having a lot of fun with Kinect
You move your arm to move a box out of the way
Then you go back to your controller and shoot things
You could throw a box at enemies
And knock them around
That'd be pretty freaking amazing
How about an Xbox Live Arcade game that's
Kinect enabled called Slap-a-Bitch
And what you would do is
You walk around with the controller or whatever
And then you can just reach out and slap a bitch
It's other people that are on
The Kinect
It's like Halo, but it's slapping
Well they have a game like that for the Android
I believe, OS
You could just sneak up behind somebody
Well they have something like that for the Android OS
And it's not as content controlled as
The app store for iPhone and Apple
It's simpler
It's booty smack or booty slap
And you actually tap the phone or you slide your finger across
Your Android device and you
And you slap a bitch on her ass
So we're getting there
We're getting there, but we're not there yet for the Kinect
Once they released that development kit
I should say
Once they released that development kit for the indie marketplace
There will be a slap a bitch
I guarantee it
Slap a ho, slap a bitch, slap a baby, it'll be all good
Slap that ass
We're so bad
Alright moving on, how about some more gaming news
I'm going over to Matt too tonight
Sure, so keeping with the whole Microsoft
Company discussion
Turns out those codes
On the back of your Microsoft Live cards
Actually have a pattern to them
So a group of smart hackers
Decided to look at those codes
Take some old Xbox Live points cards
And Xbox Gold trial codes
And they figured out an algorithm
That actually allows them to
Anticipate the rest of the strings
By doing so they started to exploit
Microsoft for Microsoft points
And in doing so, and of course you post
These things on forums so everyone can do it
They bled Microsoft
For an estimated one million dollars worth of points
Space bucks
One million space bucks
So of course Microsoft
Caught on to this and pulled the codes online
But as I was reviewing
Some of the news
Tossed a question to me, the algorithm
Is still enforced to the cards on
Walmart and Target walls
I'm not understanding
Because they pull these codes that were posted online
But aren't they still sitting on shelves?
Correct, so my thinking
My thoughts were when I was reading this
That's great you pulled the codes
But the existing codes on store shelves are still
The same algorithm or maybe a set of algorithms
Yeah there might be several algorithms
And so they must be in their
New batch of product for that
They've got to be redoing the algorithm
I wonder if there will be a recall
Maybe the algorithm, because I'm sure
These codes
Probably not just tell
That it's a Microsoft code, but it probably
Actually tells Microsoft where the card was bought
I would imagine the GameStop chain
Probably all has similar digits
In the beginning or something like that
But whatever algorithm was cracked
Is probably tied to one particular retail chain
And beyond points
I might sound like an idiot to the folks that did this
Because I don't profess to know how you crack an algorithm
These aren't necessarily the 1600 point cards
These are the 160 Microsoft point cards
That you get with some games
Right, the actual point value is 160
So we're not talking a lot
But they're able to refresh and then
Regenerate the algorithm and keep going
And even they were able to find the code
For bringing in props to Halo Reach and things like that
So instead of digital tchotchkes and SpaceBucks
They were able to figure out the codes
Darktoygak has a really good question
Don't these things have to be activated?
Like when you buy the cards at the store
I always thought once they scan on the barcode
Then they're active or whatever
It's just a piece of cardboard
That has a code underneath it
That's what makes me wonder
I can understand
They did these 160 point cards
Those things
But if they started doing 1600 point cards
There'd be no way for them to track that
How would they even be able to figure out
Which ones are sold and stuff
I'm sure those codes link to some type of serial number
Some type of, not product key
Some type of way to
If Microsoft is smart
And we hope that they are
They've got to have some type of inventory tracking methodology
They generate so many codes
To so many locations
I could swear that you have to activate them at the register
Before they run
Because otherwise how easy is it to steal those cards?
Okay, well actually it wasn't from cards
From what I'm looking up here real quick
It's actually from a website that was
Generating these codes
Kind of like a promotion thing
So they figured out that you can go to this website
Because really you're only supposed to be able to go there once
You can go to this website, change part of this URL
That's in there
And you can see if
The code's working or not
And then
Basically
You keep
The code is located
But again the algorithm stays
And if there are existing cards
I don't know
I always figure there's a pattern to it
But someone found the exploit and they shared it with the community
And let them for about a million bucks
I gotta be honest
This news kind of sucks for Microsoft
But I'm kind of surprised it didn't happen sooner
That's true
Considering how long those types of cards have been around
I'm surprised
I guess it wasn't the cards
To really rip the hole open
To get these points
But I'm really surprised it didn't happen sooner
And I wonder if other gaming companies
Or consoles like this
I wonder if they are taking stock
In this
And how they procure their point cards and stuff
I'm really wondering what effect this might have
On digital distribution down the line
I mean granted this is just one little
Well it's not really little
But it's one thing that happened
And maybe it wasn't the cards after all
But you have to think about
What does digital distribution mean to our company
And you've seen the expansion happening
Kind of a GameStop where now
One of their walls is no longer game
Boxes but it's those plastic cards
For Playstation Network and so forth
So you gotta kind of be wondering
If people are able to exploit that system
Is digital download
As smart of an idea as we all thought?
Or does it need some time to get more secure?
Out of a little harder if they were exploiting
Those Facebook gift cards you can buy in the store
For your true SpaceX
There's no value in that
I'm curious if even one of those is sold yet
So that's been reported that Microsoft
This week they started renting movies on Facebook
Oh lord
Yeah that's true
That's something else for people to spend their SpaceX on
Give credit cards over to
Ironically enough the first movie that they started renting
Was The Dark Knight right?
The Batman movie with Heath Ledger
And all I could think of in my mind was
And here we go
Maybe that was the joke
I don't know
So I will be avoiding that part of Facebook
I don't want them to have my credit card information
That's for damn sure
So yeah a million bucks has been bled dry
From the coffers of Microsoft
Quickly in their lesson and have to start changing
Their strategy on how to
Deal with codes perhaps
Be interesting to see the ramifications
Of this six months from now
Well they can figure out who uses those codes
So they're gonna punish them
They'll be taken out back and flogged
Publicly
Drop the hammer or cut the rope
Yes they'll be
Cutting the rope
Let's move on
Well as rumored the new firmware for the
PlayStation 3 has come out
With cloud saves
So yes now you can actually
Save your games
If you're a PlayStation Plus subscriber
I was just about to ask, I'm like nah you have to be
PlayStation Plus for that right?
So you can
Save some games
Or your game saves online
And also apparently
According to one of the PlayStation 3 hackers
It has
Resecured the PlayStation 3
For now
Cause obviously the
Keys are still in there but they've just
Moved them to someplace else
And they have another key in place
So for now
It's been secured but
It's just a matter of time
Really you can't
Even calling it re-secured
That just doomed it for failure
Right there
Just say nope still broken
Nothing to see here
Keep on moving
But it's hack proof Loki
This new firmware is hacker proof
Nobody will hack it
Nothing is hacker proof
And no one's bothering to even
Well here's the thing though
The firmware right now because you can
Spoof it anyway so you can still
Connect to the PlayStation Network if you really want to
But
Whatever
Is cloud saving something that interests anyone in this room?
I do think it's kind of neat
Because you know like
If I go to visit friends like in the bay area
You know or something I could
Connect to the cloud I guess and get my game saves
Especially for things like
I own this on the 360
So maybe it's a moot point but you don't know Jack
Like you remember when I was reviewing the game
I talked about you really want to make sure that save file
Goes with you otherwise you're going to be recycling games
Because of the dumb way
You have only five episodes at a time
Able to lock or whatever
If you don't take that game save with you you're going to end up
Recycling games very quickly and that
So the cloud save would be very useful for that
Because I don't always think to copy my save file to a card
And so on
I was going to say thumb drives are fucking cheap
I mean why would I spend money
On PlayStation Plus
I have two jump drives right here
Both of these cost me less than ten dollars
I mean why would I
And those are eight gigs
Why would I even waste my time
I think the cap was 150
I don't know if it's 150 saves
Or if it's 150 megabytes
I can't remember what it was
The honest thing I can say is that sometimes you just don't know
When you're going to need a game save file
I have never ever
Gone to a person's house and go damn
I really wish I had my game save with me
Especially not for the PS3
Because people that now have a PS3
That I go to their houses
Regularly
I know one person
Alright
Well I feel the same way about cloud saving with
The whole rock band guitar hero things
Because I go to one of my buddy's houses
Who has played rock band extensively
And unlocked a lot of the games
I come back to my house and I haven't
Finished those parts of the tour to unlock the songs to play
So cloud saving would make a lot of sense
When you do the all unlock
That would be cheating Rob
Here's the other problem too with the cloud saving thing
Don't you have to put your profile on their system anyways?
I mean you can't just dump the save off the internet
Well with Xbox
Yeah it is profile centric
That's true
Here's a better idea
This is great and this will cost you
No money so fuck Playstation Plus
You take that game save
It's not very big
Email it to yourself
Boom it's on the cloud
Don't need to fucking pay them for shit
You want that download that save anywhere
Download the save just go to a PC
Download it
But your friends don't have a PC I don't believe you
Because everybody has a PC nowadays
Seriously
Why am I going to pay
Boom it's on the cloud
And he pointed up
In the studio he pointed up towards the cloud
Just in case we didn't know
Boom headshot on the cloud
Alright
Gameguru in our chat
Says my USB drive is bigger than the cloud
Hot
Google mail
Gmail bigger than the cloud
7.8 gigs right
And you know
If I remember correctly
I believe you can download stuff
Through the web browser on
The
Playstation 3 I think
I'm not sure what you can download if it's just
Images and stuff like that to save to your system
But you may very well be able to download game
Saves
Now here's a point from Spaznator PC
Can't wait to hear your response to this in our chat room
Low key most saves can be copied
To jump drives external hard drives
But some are copy locked
In those occasions cloud saving comes in handy
And then the only person
Or the only people you can blame
For that would be Sony for being dicks
But maybe
For a Playstation Plus member they'll give you the keys
To unlock that save
Oh yeah how generous of them
I can have access to my saves
Oh thank you great master
I mean it's like
What the hell
Sorry no you can't have your saved data
But you can pay for the privilege
To access that data
Last week was Nintendo this week is Sony
I know you gotta love Loki
One week it'll be Apple then it's Nintendo
Now this week it's Sony
Angry angsty
Man against iOS and iPad
And iPhone stuff
But he still is in many ways
No I hate Apple
The only reason he has that is he got it for free through a work
No you have to understand I hate Apple
Because their computers are shit
They're overpriced shit
And that's all it is
Who thought it was a fucking genius idea to have
No ports whatsoever other than
One USB slot that's awesome
That's awesomely stupid
I mean
But people buy that for like two grand
When you can spend two grand on laptops
I can get two fucking nice laptops
For that same kind of price
But people go oh my god new Apple product
I gotta go buy it
That's where I have my problems
I'm still giving props for the
The iPhone because it probably is the best
Smartphone out there right now
And even like the iPod touch
Because it's probably the best
MP3 player out there
It's not my really MP3 player
It's an iPhone without the phone
But
I'll be damned if I buy a fucking
Apple computer
Fuck that
Seriously that is a waste
You might as well just set fire to your money
Because you'd be doing yourself
A great injustice to buy
An Apple computer
Oh Loki
I think in a new segment Loki's angst
That's the show
But that's not a segment
And I still don't get the iPad
I don't get it
I guess it's better than having a
Netbook maybe
But
I can't put it in my pocket what good is that for me
I'm using mine, I'm planning a career in real estate
I'm using it to take pictures of listings and homes
And video so I'm putting it to a business use
Ok so yeah that's fine
And I'll be able to watch porn on it
Hey that's a frame device that has a screen
I don't play the slideshow of porn
Versus the slideshow of listings
You better have a big thing of Windex to clean that iPad with
But um
Anyway so
No no I just
Of course everybody's now putting out tablet
Right
That worked really well back in the 90's
Because everybody wants to touch something
I remember when tablet PC
Fuck I remember when my uncle worked for like
Wacom and they were making tablet PC's
Yeah that's old school shit
Oh my god you have to use a stylus
On this
Alright anyway let's move on
To some other stories going on here
And this is a follow up to something we were talking about
Last week remember that scandalous game
We Dare
Yes that was the one that's kind of like Truth or Dare
I guess but it was going to be a video game on the Wii
And the trailer video featured spanking
Which I guess was one of the mini games
Well guess what happened
Thanks to the magic of the internet I guess somebody
Realized maybe um
This game isn't really suitable for the
12 plus rating that it originally got
And yes Ubisoft
Just spoke to the Daily Telegraph
This week saying following the public
Reaction to the 12 plus rating of
We Dare Ubisoft has made the decision
Not to sell the game in the United
Kingdom so uh
This means that the game will not be sold anymore
In the UK they will have to import it
From some place where this game will be
Sold um
I don't know where that's going to end up being
Canada or Australia
Or what?
It's stupid that they're even doing that
How about download it on the internet because that's probably going to be the easiest place to get it sadly
I don't usually advocate piracy but
It's just a
Fucking game I mean seriously
First off the situation that
They posed in the stupid trailer made
No sense anyways there's first off never
Going to be two hot girls playing a game with you
And they're not going to go make out because they
Started playing you know a fucking
Wii game you know what's going to do that
Lots of alcohol
Lots of yeah that's really all you need
Lots of alcohol you know and
And uh slutty chicks
And then they'll go and make out and stuff
A Wii game is not going to get them to do that
It will not get you you know laid
Um
And I trust you if you bought this game
You'd be very bored because who the hell
Are you going to play this with?
I mean seriously you're going to invite your friends over and play this
Play against the computer?
Play against the computer I mean
You want to fucking you know
I'm sorry Dave I cannot let you spank me
So they're not they're not selling it in the UK
Were they not selling Twister in the UK?
They're not selling bottles in the UK because I mean
That's all you need too for like fucking you know
Uh
Was it an erotic night with your friends or something
Like that I mean I just don't under
This just proves that the UK
Is possibly more prudish than the Americans
No they're just as prudish because we're not selling it over here either so
By the way
Just real quick uh also
Ubisoft got a stern warning
From the Europeans rating board
Peggy um not Bundy
But P-E-G-I Peggy
Uh asking Ubisoft to basically
Remove the We Dare ads from the internet
Oh yeah because once something hits the internet
It can totally be erased you guys
Whatever you know what I think it can
Try to find anything
From uh being Bobby Brown on the internet
You can't
It just doesn't exist I have an icon of Whitney Houston
Saying kiss my ass
No you do I have looked
I have scoured the internet trying to find those episodes
For my wife because that would be like
They never released it on DVD?
No she filed lawsuits to block that
It never came out on DVD
Really? Yes oh man
That would be worth a lot if anyone's got that on VHS
That was an amazing fucking show
We need to send Sam Flynn to break into the headquarters
Of Bravo or whatever fucking network or air that show
And steal the master tapes because seriously
That was an amazing piece of television
It was awesome
Anyhow speaking of Bobby
Uh Black Wolf is in the chat room
Saying please tell me you have in your show
Role the guy who actually recorded himself
Playing the game showing how tame it really is
Of course I don't
But I believe it
I believe it's not as bad as that commercial makes it look
We saw you know the actual gameplay
I'm sure it's on YouTube somewhere
It's just
It's just a ploy to get people
To buy that game because they're like oh it's so dirty
No it's crap
Okay it's Ubisoft
This is the same company that puts out you know
Uh the pets games
Or the imagine games
You know or you know all that stuff
Imagine sex party
I mean that's basically what this is
Well unfortunately I couldn't find
The We Dare gameplay but I did find
A trailer for We Dare Island
Oh he's cute
Oh she's spinning a tie
In slow motion
Or is that a bra? I can't tell from back here
Ah yes
So the ladies are on the couch
Giggling at the boys and they're one pseudo stripping
And they're dancing and they're having a gay old time
The question is though
Is it going in reverse?
Oh oh now the girls spanking
The girls are laughing I think it is going in reverse
God I love YouTube
I'm gonna link that in the chat
That's more like XTube going on right there
Alright
MrBlackWolf is giving me the appropriate link
That we should be looking at here
If the game doesn't have full frontal it's not We Dare
I mean seriously
We can check it out
There's us being all adventurous
Ooh I want that dress
You do huh? Yes
Okay
Oh these guys are sassy
You really like this song?
Yes
How can you not like this song?
I guess it's okay but I'm just sick of hearing it
I'm sick of hearing you
Not to mention it's a cover
I guess they're just dancing it's kind of like Just Dance
Is that it?
Alright I'm bored of that video already
What is that on Farmhouse media 3000
It has that little YouTube clip we were just playing
Anyhow
Let's move on
Matt2 what do you have for us?
Some more news so looks like that
If you play Dragon Age 2 and you
Have some angst and you want to get unleashed
In the forums watch what you say because
If you call EA the devil
You might actually get shut off
So a player actually posted online
On their forums and
For whatever reason reference
EA called them the devil you can have your opinion
About that and
EA not liking this bad PR
Decided to temporarily
Suspend the player's account on the
Forums because that's not
Unusual when you play WoW or other online
If you go off and say some naughty things
They'll do that but someone flipped the other master
Switch and temporarily
Suspended this guy's account for three days
So when he loaded the game and
Played the game could not
Actually play it all because he called
The exact quote from
The forums was
Quote have you sold your souls to
The EA devil?
Really?
At Banfurth
It's the Activision devil by the way
Exactly
But the other part of it too
That's not so bad
If you've seen and read other forums
It's like don't come into my house and then call me
The devil
So here's the thing
We strictly enforce the community against profanity
There's no profane
El Diablo here
It's a bad term
But there really isn't anything profane about it
It's just really kind of a nasty, spun comment
So of course
EA was like oh our bad, sorry about that
And they apologized as a glitch between
Suspending the user account for
Forums versus suspending the full blown
Account for the game
They have since apologized to the player
And moved on after some gamer backlash
Isn't that ironic?
They had to come back and apologize, sorry
We're the devil and Banjuu
And Rob and I have posted and read
Some of the WoW forms and things like that
And there's some pretty angsty 12 year olds on there
But this is pretty bad
I kind of wish Blizzard did this
Like read the forum posts and was like
Oops, sorry we banned you
My bad
Be careful what you say on the...
We need to take that Ragnarok Online approach
You want to talk bad about our game? We ban you
You can't play the game anymore
How do you like that?
It just proves that you better watch or see on the internet
And this is obviously a mistake
This is not what happens if you were to
Call EA the devil or go off with profane language on their website
So
Just something kind of funny
But it just shows how much control
Video game distributors do have
They can flip a switch and you're gone
Or you're banned or you're suspended
That's right, so you guys think twice next time
About calling EA the devil
Call them dirty come guzzlers instead
Hot
Let's travel the world and look at some release dates
Let's start with the US, Loki
This week's not a lot of stuff coming out
We got a few budget games and then
Some decent stuff
So starting off with the budget games
Maximum Racing Dragonstock and Maximum Racing
GP Classic Racing
These are very budget games coming out for the Wii
Let's see
God's Eater Burst
Coming out on PSP this week
From D3
Looks pretty awesome
Jakandia and the Timeless Land
This is a game that's very similar to
30 Second Hero
So I believe this is the one that actually lets you
Pick how much time you have
And then you can play the game for that long
And then of course
On the Wii, Trackmania Build to Race
Awesome game on the PC
So I'm sure it would be pretty good on the Wii
Homefront
The big game for this week
On Playstation 3, Xbox 360, and PC
Kind of
The first that we'll see
Of the Just Dance series
But a little bit of a spin-off
Dance on Broadway coming into Playstation 3
For the move
Also on Playstation 3
Yakuza 4
With less stuff changed this time
From the Japanese version
Artun Liko
Is it just me or was that kind of a fast turnaround this time?
It was a pretty fast turnaround
Artun Liko Koga
Nel of Arseal
On Playstation 3 this week as well
Let's see
Also
Playstation 3, Xbox 360
And I believe the Wii
Top Spin 4
Coming out this week as well
And then
Surprisingly enough
The Xbox 360 version of this got cancelled
But Warriors Legend of Troy
It's a
Trojan version of Dynasty Warriors
So check that out
And then finally
We've got another Ubisoft
Fitness game
Fit in 6 on the Wii and Playstation 3
Of course Playstation 3
With move support there
It's kind of like their answer to the Arseal fitness
Since that never came out on other systems
Other than the 360
That's
That's it for this week
Yes, that's it
Alright, I'm gonna move on to Japanese release dates
I do realize things going on
Could have an effect on this
On the Xbox 360
Dragon Age Origins Awakening
That would be the expansion to the original Dragon Age
It's gonna be out on March 17th
Going on to the Playstation 3
And checking out some of the releases there
Yakuza
I'm sorry, that's a US release
Motorstorm 3 Apocalypse
Comes out in Japan
As well as the Dragon Age Origins expansion
Ryu Ga Gotoku of the End
Comes out in Japan as well
I'm not sure what that
Game is, it's from Sega
And it's related to the Yakuza universe
But I think it's a bit more of the action adventure
Type of game, so there you go
Let's see
Coming out on some other systems
Want to see the Wii real quick
If there's anything coming out there
I don't believe so
No, nothing this week because of course
Nintendo's focused on the 3DS
And the recent launch that happened there
So you can check out Steel Diver this week in Japan
And Tom Clancy's Splinter Cell 3D
Is on the 3DS this week in Japan
And lastly
On the PSP
We have
Where to go
No, I guess
Is there anything on the PSP this week?
Doesn't look like it
For some reason I'm not able to find the dates on my list
There we go, never mind, there it is
The Little Battlers is the big release
On the PSP this week
Little Battlers
Is a game from level 5
It's an RPG coming out over there
Looks like you battle these
Little kind of polygonal
Types of things, it looks a little bit
Valkyria profile to me
Kind of mixed with traditional RPG mechanics
So that could be kind of neat
So there you go, that's it for Japanese releases
What about the UK?
Alright, so from our friends across the pond
Coming out on Ides of March
Is Total War Shotgun 2
Coming out on PC
And then for releases on the 18th Friday
We have Assassin's Creed Brotherhood on PC
We also have coming up God's Eater Burst
On the PSP
I'm just intrigued by the title
Homefront is coming out on the 360
PS3 and PC
Also again on Friday the 18th
MotoGP coming out
Also on Friday, PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360 versions
Motorstorm Apocalypse coming out on the PS3
Okimada and Chisaki Taio
See, I could do Chinese
Japanese pretty well, huh?
I was worried about any
I was worried about any type of Japanese releases
I had in my read tonight
Coming out on DS
Also Topspin 4 for 360, PS3 and Wii
Coming out
And finally Yakuza 4 is mentioned before
Coming out on the 18th for PS3
I remember buying Topspin
Original for 360 and was not a fan
It made me frustrated
I did not like the original Topspin game
It was on 360 either
That's it this week for the UK
Alright
Just a few more news stories for you guys
And then we're going to get to the classic game of the week
But first, something from Loki
I'm sorry, I'm very distracted right now
What was that?
They finally released the Grand Theft Auto 4 texture editor
Remember the one that got ripped off for Trend to Buy?
Yeah, someone finally released it
All the things I can do
It's just so mind boggling
Anyways, let's talk about Pokmon
Apparently
There was a rumor
And of course, you know there's always rumors for the stuff coming from Twitter
Back when this whole disaster
Went down in Japan
That the Pokmon creator died
That would have been tragic
Except it's not true
Basically
The company tweeted back
They said, false
Pokmon company and Game Freak is fine
So
No one's dead
Some people are sick
That's all
Sick
Maybe
It was a very unfortunate case
A mistaken identity or mistranslation
But unfortunately
That probably was not the case
Sick people
Alright, moving on
One other news story for you guys
Free Realms
I don't know if you've ever checked this game out
It's a casual MMO
The weird thing is it's free to play
It's coming out on the Playstation 3
The funny thing is
It's coming out very soon
March 29th
It was originally on the PC
And now it's going to be a free to play casual MMO
On the Playstation Network
So it's not like DC Universe Online
Which is kind of the other big MMO on Playstation 3 right now
Free Realms
Is going to be different
They say that they did take some things
From DC Universe Online, Sony Online Entertainment
Of course in developing this
But basically
This is kind of something basically new
They had to port the rendering over from the
Old engine from the PC
The PS3 version unfortunately
Will be independent of the PC version
You will not be able to play with your friends
On the PC version
Being able to link the accounts unfortunately isn't possible
So it'll be interesting to see how this
Works on the Playstation 3
Again it's a free to play MMO
So I would assume that means on the PS3
It's going to be that way as well
Maybe it's one of those things that's only open to Playstation Plus though
I don't know
No word on that yet
So we'll see when the game comes out in just a couple weeks
Alright for now
It's that time of the show where we like to take a trip down memory lane
And look at the classic game of the week
Every week here on the show
Dark Soccer likes to step into the vault of classic gaming
And pull out a game that she thinks you guys should be checking out this week
Unfortunately she's not here this week
So we all decided to run into the vault
And knock everything over
And let everything kind of pile up on the floor
In one big pile
We jumped on in, pulled one game out
And this is what we got
After we smashed everything with the hammer
And locked me in the vault for 24 hours
No I'm kidding
We decided since Matt 2 was good enough to step in
And fill in for Jamie tonight
Why doesn't he get to pick the classic game of the week
What did you pick for the classic game of the week?
Well I'll never presume to take over for Jamie
But I'm honored to do this segment here
So after being locked in the vault for 24 hours
And a dog pile ensued
I sifted through it and found
This little gem on Super Nintendo
One of my favorites
Actraiser
And Actraiser was produced
And distributed back in 1990
So 20 years ago
Oh my god I'm so old
Exclusive for Super Nintendo at the time
It was put out by Enix then
Now Squeenix as we know it
And the whole idea of this game was
It was two fold
You were a platform side scrolling
Action as well as
City building almost like RTS
And the whole premise was that
You were god, or a god I should say
And you would have to run around
And kill stuff and defend the land
You then also
Once you completed the level which was
Again very basic side scrolling levels here
You would then turn into an angel
And fly around and protect the city
From other monsters
And you could see his butt
You could definitely see his ass
You fly around in an angel form
And help defend the city
You would also have to do things like
Help crops grow by being god
You'd have to make it rain on the crops
And lightning to burn bushes
So your city could grow and things like that
At the time when I was playing it
I really enjoyed the music from the game
The gameplay is pretty straight forward on the platform side
And the angel
Side scrolling or RTS side
But
So anywho, a little bit more background about the game
Again the idea that you were a god or a master
And you take the form of
The overseer in a cloud
Not cloud saves, but just cloud
And then when your citizens call upon you to help defend the land
You would beam on down
To the world and take over
In a humanoid form
The funny part is
There was an Actraiser 2
Really a prequel to the game
But a lot of religious subtext
Was discovered about it
People were concerned about the game
Because in the Japanese text for this prequel
They actually called the main character god
And the villain of the game Satan
So here we are talking about the devil again tonight Rob
But it was a very
It was a very
Engaging game because again it had two
Parts to it, you had to again defend the city
And build your cities
If you didn't do these certain tasks
Your citizens would die and you would lose the game
One of my favorites
It later came out for Virtual Console
And also released on
Mobile phone devices
So this is out there to play
And I don't know
I just really enjoyed the music from this game
So your classic video game of the week
Is Actraiser
On Super Nintendo and Virtual Console and Mobile Phone
An excellent fucking choice
And I remember when
Matt too told me what game he wanted to do for the classic game of the week
I was like no Jamie had to have picked that at some point
Well I asked her about it. I was like go check the wiki
Jamie picked that right
And it hadn't been picked yet
Well I checked the wiki just to be certain
And then I sent her a message
And said hey these are the three games I
Would like to review
And these are on the wiki that I want to run past you
She goes oh I totally had Actraiser on my list to do
So yeah go ahead and take that
I also gave two other suggestions to Rob
I told him one of them
I think he was impressed on how far back
My video gaming experience went
Do you remember the game I told you?
But Congo Bongo?
I totally remember that game from the Atari 5200
But anywho
So Actraiser
Is definitely a great game. Check it out
Let's not take attention away from Actraiser
Because this game is amazing
It's definitely in my top 10 video games ever
The sequel doesn't hold a candle to it
And it actually bankrupt the series I think
That's too bad
Like Enix made so many good freaking games
On the Super Nintendo
I'm not even talking about Dragon Quest, Dragon Warrior
That series. I'm talking about
The Illusion of Gaia
And that whole series
That was in Soul Blazer
I think was one of the other games
That whole series was awesome
And of course they were the ones that did Busta Move
depending on what country you were in
That was all Enix
And a lot of that has disappeared since the Square merger
Which is unfortunate
One of the most graphic things about this game was
Whenever you had to warp down to the world to defend it
The screen would spin around
And it was just high-tech
And it made you feel like you were falling
Into the earth
So as your citizens
Gain power-ups and learn smarter
They can learn how to build better
Buildings and better crops
And things like that
It definitely had a SimCities
And a platform feel to it
Definitely check it out
Thank you to the week for the Super Nintendo from Enix
Actraiser
And for heaven's sake, at least just listen to this soundtrack
Because it's one of the greatest soundtracks ever
I believe it's Yoko Kanno who did the soundtrack to that
Who's um, just
No, no, what am I saying?
She sang a song
For like Evangelion or something
Yuzo Koshiro did the music to that
And he did
He did a DDR song back in the day
I believe he's the same guy that does Wangan Midnight
Maximum Tune, Streets of Rage
Lots of great stuff
So, very cool
Alright, that's going to do it for this Part A of Orange Lounge Radio
But fear not, there's plenty more of
OLR to come when we get back
Including the mailbag, your tweets
So get those in please, your Twitters
Twitter.com slash OLR to get in your tweets
And of course, more news, we're going to talk about those
Dance Hero rumors, some games being
Cancelled at Sony, and what's going to
Happen to NBA Jam
We'll find out after this, a quick break with more
Of Orange Lounge Radio
Welcome back everybody to Orange Lounge Radio
We are live tonight with the
405th episode of our show
On this March 13th of 2011
We are live at All Games Radio
As we are every Sunday night at 6 o'clock Pacific
9 o'clock Eastern, right after the Bobby Black Wolf show
Obviously, it's been a crazy week
And if you are just joining us
I did make a plea in Part A
And I'll say it again, please, please, please
For those folks in Japan
That have had to go through such a
Crazy, horrific thing going on
Right now, please consider donating to the
Red Cross, you can go to
Redcross.org, I'm really
Encouraging all of our listeners to part with
$10, it's not that much
That's like less than the cost of one month
Of an MMO, that's an Xbox Live Arcade game
You can go without this week
And put the money to where it's really, really
Needed right now, anyhow
Moving on, we're gonna get back into some gaming news
And some rapid fire news, and your Twitter
All the tweets at twitter.com
Slash o-l-r, we'll read those on the show here in
Just a minute, so get those in, this is your last chance
Also, I gotta do a plug
For the spin-off shows, unfortunately Dark
Sakura's not here tonight, but she does do a
Fun little show with Mara & Marvel
And Dan Shadow, it's called Comic Insanity
But that's with no I, it's
Comic N-sanity, and you can find
That on Twitter, or you can also find it at
Infamous.net, again, just the letter
N, Infamous.net
If you like World of Warcraft, check out my
Spin-off show with X-Defer, the best little
Horde house in Azeroth, also known
As Horde House for short
And all of that coming
To a new website also this week
That I'll be able to give out, and I'm very excited
So that's all on its way to being done
In the meantime,
Some rapid fire news, some quick stories
For you guys, let's start with Loki
According to the
New issue of the French gaming magazine
Joystick, Bethesda's next
Game in their, well, next
Announced game is gonna be Prey 2
That's right, the sequel to the
First person shooter game that came out from
3D Realms and 2K games
Wow. Of course, 3D Realms is no
Longer around, and you know
Bethesda was purchased by
ZeniMax
Which snatched up the
Company ID software
So it makes perfect sense that they're gonna be putting out
Shooter games
No word exactly on when that's coming out
But probably something that we'll be
Hearing more about during E3 this year
I'm kind of surprised that Prey is getting a sequel
Because the first one didn't really do too hot
I mean, it was a good game
Especially for dummies
Like, it was a first person shooter for dummies
Because you can never die in Prey, and that's one of the things
I really liked about it, because I suck at first person shooters
The story was pretty good too
Even though it totally cut off abruptly
Like, you play in the game and then it's over
It was weird
For a sequel
Yeah, kind of like that
But not really
Without the journey
This is kind of a neat little Easter egg
I guess for the Google Chrome browser
If you're using it
There's actually a piece of JavaScript
You can paste into the Chrome's
Address
And when you do that
It activates a hack which reloads a page
And basically allows you to
Roll around a ball
A katamari ball, to be exact
And pick up all the words
And images on the screen like you would a katamari
Awesome
And you can find this piece of code
At kathack.com
That's K-A-T
Hack.com
And check it out
It's kind of a neat one
Does it play the music too?
I don't think it does
But thanks to the advent of
The MP3
You would provide your own soundtrack
For your web page rolling up
Adventures
It's just not the same
And then finally
There's a company out of
San Francisco that wants to make your life
The RPG
So basically it's life
But it's you
It's coming from a company called
Green Goose
And basically what it is
Is this package that you get
It's packaged with a water bottle
Toothbrush and vitamin container
And it says the Green Goose
Logs how many times a week
That you say for example
Pick up their toothbrush or whatever
Awarding them points each time that they do
There's sensors on the bottles
And on the toothbrush for tracking
As well as a credit card size
Pedometer that communicates with the
Base station that's attached
To a broadband router
The points that the player earns
Will
Not really do anything
But it's meant
To encourage a healthy
Lifestyle I guess
And clean teeth
Okie dokie
I don't know
Neat
This is something I can see them selling
At a dentist office or something like that
I remember all those toothbrushing
Games and stuff that you could play on
With the Atari 2600 and Commodore 64
That were supposed to like you know
Teach the good habits and all that
It would be kind of funny
Like a life of the game or something like that
Well they kind of have that
Like in the 3DS where you earn points for walking
Or shaking
The 3DS
And you award the same points
For walking or throttling something
Alright
Let's move on here to some
Other news about the Legend of
Zelda the Ocarina of Time 3D
There is some
New things that are supposed to be in there
It's not just a direct port
Of the 64 version
The 3DS version is supposed to have some other
Stuff and this is in an interview that
Happened with Miyamoto
Talking about the 3DS version of Ocarina
Of Time. Apparently they've set up a new system
Where when you use the A, B and X, Y
Buttons there's also some special buttons in the
Touch screen that you can use to switch
Between the items right away
Between maps and menus and so forth
Also one other
Little teaser that's there
From Satoru Iwata says
Of course the Nintendo 3DS version of
Ocarina of Time is crammed with interesting
Things that weren't in the Nintendo 64 version
But we'll wait to talk about those
To the release
By the way
Quick follow up from SX in our chat room on the
Katamari Damacy add-in. It does play the music
Just so you know
Well that's good to know. That's coming from our chat
Some rumors about Grand Theft Auto 5
Is the code name Rush
That could be what's going on
I guess that's some casting
Details that were done on a Google search
Apparently there's this project called Rush
And it has to do with Grand Theft Auto 5
Rush is tied to Take-Two Interactive
They own Rockstar Games
Apparently it's a video game
Set in the Los Angeles area
So maybe they've gone from New York to L.A.
Who knows but that is apparently
Some of the rumors about the game
Some of the casting that is in the game
There's a 38 year old FBI agent
In grape shape
A 25 year old young Mexican-American
FBI agent
23 year old moron
White trash hillbilly named Clyde
And so on and so on
So lots of parts that they're casting for
That's either going to be a Grand Theft Auto game
Which I can only hope
Or it's going to be a sequel to Midnight
Club L.A.
And lastly, Valve is going to be
Bridging Portal and Portal 2
With some type of surprise
We don't exactly know what that is
But that was from
Coming out of PAX East
Something that will tie the story
Of the interim time between Portal and Portal 2
Is that a comic book?
Is that an arcade game?
Is that YouTube?
Who knows?
Apparently something will be coming to tie
The two worlds together in the future
So we'll see
Matt 2?
This is Strong by Trapped
That's just half of what's in that pack
These are all those angsty
Boy frat bands that you like
Yes, this is good music, Rob
It sounds like men with vaginas
When I hear it
I'm sure a lot of our listeners
Are like, you're an asshole, Rob
You like Lady Gaga
I heard she did a great song
That copied Madonna's song
Weren't you in the middle of some news?
Yes sir, let me continue
So check that out if you're into rock music
Other stories that are coming up
There it goes
Torchlight
Rob talked about this in his gaming week
He's tried Torchlight, it mimics Diablo 2
And all that's great
But it was cancelled in Japan
Due to text bugs
And due to translation delays
So basically Torchlight was there
It was set to launch in the Xbox Live Arcade
And when it came down to it
It was just abruptly cancelled
Due to some various
It's a weird reason to cancel a game
It's a very weird reason
Various reasons to go back and forth
There must have been a dirty word
In mistranslation or something
I don't know, there was a lot of debate
Whether it was a bug or a text issue
Everyone was pointing at each other's fingers
But basically it was quoted saying
We're not privy to the decision making process
But it was due to bugs in the translation
Because the game has never been translated
To Japanese
Since there was no existing Japanese version
Of the game, the complexity of a new translation
Combined with the randomly generated naming
Scheme for Torchlight
Made it beyond the scope of the project
You would think that if they were going to release something
In two different countries
And countries had different languages
They would include that in the scope of the project
It still just seems so abrupt
Too hard, I don't want to do this
I don't understand!
Google Translate won't work for this game
Rob, you made a point that the text
On the screen was awfully small
Yeah, maybe you couldn't read it
So maybe the Japanese videography of the characters
Didn't look right
So who knows
Maybe look for that in the future if they figure out how to translate it
Or maybe that's just wah wah wah
So, unfortunately no Torchlight
For the Xbox Live
For the Japanese version
And
I really don't want to have to share this news
Because the first iteration of this was
Just so horrible
There's work that a new
Doom movie is coming out
Yes
We all remember in 2005 The Rock
Dwayne Johnson
Did a
Wonderful version of Doom
In an attempt to
Do a movie on the first person shooter that
Got us in the early 90s
But there's a reboot in the works
That's going to completely ignore Dwayne Johnson's
First version, thank god
And of course, like everything else
In this frickin' time and day
It'll be in 3D
Oh, of course
Will we have scenes with a gun in 3D?
Probably
Was that in the first movie?
It wasn't in 3D, but the perspective
You were running around for parts
The scene with a gun swinging back and forth
Like you were in the video game
I would be okay with this if they just
Took Doom 3D
Sorry, I'm just looking real quick
I'm trying to bring back some memories here
Oh god, please don't
I saw this on
USA Network or TNT or something like that
I think they cut out all the violence
Oh, they did, and the swearing
Swearing in violence would have made it better
Yeah, it was just bad
Doom is waiting
So there's no release date, there's no nothing
It's just in the preliminary works and it's just
A new project in the early stages
Yay, another Hollywood reboot, just what we needed
And in 3D, can't forget it's in 3D
We've run out of ideas, completely
Exactly, so
Time to remake crap
Look for that, hopefully, in the near future
Yeah, can't wait
There will be no hopefully looking forward to
Much anticipation, alright
I promised someone we'd do a quick phone call here
At this point in the show, so we're gonna make a phone call real quick
And try to get this all taken care of
I hope it's going through
I'm kind of relying on Skype tonight
And sometimes it can be a little
There we go, one ringy dingy
Two ringy dingys
Hopefully there's an answer, that might be quite embarrassing
What?
Hi, is this Dark Sakura?
Yes, this is
How are you, did you make it to Disneyland in one piece?
Well we're not at Disneyland yet
We're going tomorrow, but we
We made it to the hotel room
You're in that area, right?
I can look out of the window
And see the parking structure
There you go, now
Aren't you down there because you get to hang out with the official
OLR lesbians this week, or at least one of them?
Well both of them on Tuesday
We're going to Goofy's Kitchen together
Yay, well be sure to tell them
We all said hi and everything
Well, you know, I was gonna try to
Unfortunately it didn't work out, I was gonna have you plug
Your spin-off show, but I already did that for you
The whole comic insanity
But do you want to tell us anything about your gaming week?
Or anything maybe you've been doing to pass the time in the car?
Like on the iOS games?
Well, I played a little solitaire
Mostly I was vlogging
And just singing along with us
Some classic rock that happened to come on
Awesome
On a CD that I made so I knew it was on there
And played some Marvel vs Capcom 3 during the week
Nice
Wow
Looking forward to the new characters to be
Paid to unlock?
Well we're getting Shima Grass
Jill's not worth it
So I gotta say Matt 2 is doing a
Pretty good job filling in tonight
His classic game of the week was very well received
But he totally set the vault
On fire and I
Just want to apologize for that in advance
That everything is on fire
You realize Dan's going to
Castrate you before he kills you right?
All of you
Dan scares Matt 2
Although I
Did admit
The vault wasn't
On fire it was a small
Ember burning and you
Overreacted and luckily they had a dry
Chem fire extinguisher under the sink and I put it out
He was putting his cigarette out in there
And I'm kidding I'm totally kidding
We haven't even gone in there
I know I know
Matt 2 brought me beer tonight and not you
Ha
Okay
It wasn't true oh well for our fashion list
One of the hosts was slightly intoxicated
I offered it to Loki
In disbelief and then said err
And handed it to Rob so
Alright so we're about to
We're about to get into Twitter topics but is there
Anything you want to say to the listeners tonight?
I have the best husband ever
Why is that?
I just do
He's pretty cool
He's okay
Because he's awesome
And he likes
The pita sandwiches at the place you took me to
This week and that was pretty awesome alright
That's what we had for breakfast
Oh no I just kicked
Shermie on accident I'm sorry Shermie
Did you notice what I did for you?
I washed her
Bed so it would not stink
For you
That is a big cat
I washed her
I washed her butt for you
Thank you that's so kind
Because it would not stink
Because her butt stinks
The great lengths you go to for
Okay so we
Got to get back into video gaming news but I
Wanted you to at least be able to say hello to the
Listeners so anything else before I let you go?
Listeners?
Why do I care? No hi
Hi everybody
I'm at Disneyland and you're not
You guys stay safe have tons of fun
At the park tomorrow tell the OLR lesbians
We said hi and Marissa too
If you end up seeing her and
Marissa has a disease
Aww how sad
She's in bed with cold chills
And running fever disease
Aww sorry to hear it
So everyone send Marissa happy thoughts because we
Love Marissa
Alright well you have fun take care
Until then we said hey
Will do bye
And we only stole one game
Okay it better be Gyromite
We've got like three of them
Okay bye
She totally just gave us permission to steal
Gyromite sweet alright
Is there Robbie back there too?
There might be I don't know
Alright let's get to some Twitter topics
I've been messing around but I wanted
You know she wanted to come on the show at some point
Let's go to the tweets twitter.com slash
OLR
Every week you guys send us your tweets and we sometimes
Read them on the show it just depends like if we feel
Like it or not I don't know alright
No I'm kidding um
Spazinator starts us off tonight sending us some tweets
There is a few new
Free videos on the PSN Video Store
Excuse me I have like
Beer burps tonight it's not good for radio
Uh huh
Listen to this happy music while I cough up beer
Pets
Alright
Anyways Spazinator says there's a few new free
Videos on the PSN Video Store such as
A rental of Ghost Rider and a few TV shows
And he actually linked us to a
Blog post I guess Sony
Is now actually blogging about this stuff
And some of the free movies there's some
Anime episodes so like right now
Full Metal Alchemist Brother and Afro
Samurai are free right now
Next week FLCL and
Trigun, Death Note, Kakaishi
Naruto Shippuden
and Vampire Knight, Inuyasha
Bleach, lots of free
Shit right now on PlayStation
Network so check that out also
Uh yeah they're blogging all about that on the official
PlayStation Blog so
Poor Spazinator's gonna have to find something else to talk about
On the show if I could just log into the PlayStation
Blog and see the video releases now
I'm kidding
Alright
Moving on a few folks talking
To us from PAX East hopefully someone will
Call in when we get to the calls
Let's see ActDeaf wants to tell us about a new
Rhythm game coming to PlayStation Network
Called Dyad
Who was shown at PAX East
Linking us to a little trailer here
On YouTube hold on let me uh
Let me stop the cute music here
You're like zooming down this tunnel
It's kinda like a Wipeout HD
Mixed with uh
Oh what was that frickin game
Audio Surf on uh
Steam
That's what this looks like to me
It's cute
I'm not sure how that's a music game
I like it, it's like Chiptunes or something
Is the music, I wonder if that's the whole deal
I will have to wait and see
If that's the whole deal
I will have to research more about that
A little later
Moving on to some more tweets
Reddertainment tweeting us saying
It's good to see Square issuing refunds
Over the Final Fantasy XI outage
Treats their customers better than the airlines
Would in the same situation
Oh snap good point, very good point
Tigerclaw wants to bring this up
AT&T is going to be introducing a bandwidth cap
For DSL and U-verse customers
This May
Comcast folks have been dealing with this for some time
But apparently now there is going to be
A 150GB monthly usage cap
For DSL customers and 250GB
Cap for U-verse users
Starting on May 2
AT&T users from now through March 31
Are going to start receiving notices
Informing them of the change
In the company's terms of service
There will also be overage charges
If you go over
I guess it's $10 for every 50GB
Over the 150 or 250GB limit
That's actually not bad
Because Comcast has been doing this for a few months now
And they threaten to pull your coverage all together
If you go over the 250GB cap
It takes a lot to get over
It takes a lot to get over 250GB
I was looking at my usage, I think in the month of January
I used 18GB
And I play a lot of WoW y'all
I play a lot of WoW
I've never gone over 250GB
And I download a lot of
Porn
Not ISO's at all
None of that
Never do that
But I could see with more and more
Streaming HD movies
Streaming HD movies is a couple gigs
So if you watch a
Streaming HD movie every day
You might hit this cap
It's a little bit unfortunate
Unlimited does not mean unlimited
Don't get me started on net neutrality
Oh my god
Can you believe if they started
Charging an extra $10 for Netflix
At the top of what you already pay for Netflix
It's ridiculous
They'll just find a way around it
Now they said
The whole net neutrality thing
They can throttle bandwidth on different things
Because they have the right to do that now
Cable companies are going to destroy themselves
With all this crap
Just watch
It's going to make piracy worse
All the net neutrality stuff
Is going to make it worse
I'm telling you
Just look at the behavior
Of the internet
And if you don't think that charging people extra money
To access certain services is going to encourage people
To get around that gate
Or for new services to start up to offer
The same stuff in less legitimate ways
Just you wait
Tigerclaw
Sends us another tweet about
Voice acting in Portal 2
Announced at PAX
JK Simmons will be doing a voice
In Portal 2
That is Juno's dad
And from Spiderman
J. Jonah Jameson
JK Simmons will be doing this
Cave Johnson is the character
The president and founder of Aperture Science
That's a pretty big role
There you go
That'll be fun
Was that demo at PAX East for Portal 2?
That's pretty awesome if it was
Probably one of those behind closed doors things
Which is a little silly
Apparently a pro wrestler
Was one of the first to
Pitch a perfect MLB 2K11 game
Yeah here's the deal
Did you know that they're doing this
Contest right now for MLB 2K11
I saw a commercial for this the other day
If you are the first to pitch a perfect game
You can win a million dollars
By being the first to
Pitch a perfect in this game
Kinda interesting
Perfect starting April 1st
Meaning that Mana
Who did this Michael Mana is the
Professional
Wrestler known as Stevie Richards
He posted the video on YouTube
But unfortunately this doesn't start
Until April 1st so the win doesn't actually
Count and it's supposed to be harder than it was
Last year because you can't
I think you have to actually use the
Legitimate rosters for players that are
Current up to that date
You can't just power load
Your team or whatever
Like they did last year so
It should be slightly harder
So it may take like
Two days instead of one day
And lastly a tweet from
Blue Swim saying Dead or Alive
Announced for the
3DS that there is going to be some
DLC
So yes some DLC coming to the 3DS
And it's going to be
Let's see the series boss characters
Alpha 152, Alpha Kasumi
Genra and Tengu
I'm sorry they are not DLC they are just going to be
A game which is pretty cool
However free downloadable content
28 additional costumes
Going to be free Cheerleader, Leifang
Ninja Outfit, Ayana
And so on and so on
La Mera Posa in a white cat outfit
Indeed
More information available in
Famitsu Magazine which broke the news
This week that's pretty awesome
That's going to do it for tweets
Twitter.com slash OLR if you want to show us your tweets
Next time
Let's go back into some news
Yes
So
I don't know
I kind of
Ranted about this a little bit in the beginning
But
Really Dance Hero
Apparently you know there were
Trademarks registered a while back
I remember we were talking about like a Tar villain
And Dance Hero and stuff like that
Oh no they are going to do something like DVR
Well now apparently
There's some more
Info regarding it
Apparently they are saying that
There are some artists
Working with
Activision on the franchise
Timbaland, J Sean
The Prodigy and Afrojack all have
Songs I guess that are
Going to be in this
It's
I don't know I mean I guess I could
See them doing something similar like this
Like Dance Central because it's
You know made money
It's what's popular right now
And
I guess
This is coming from I want to say
Some sort of
Like licensing
Thing or something I'm trying to see here real quick
I seem to remember some time
Ago we saw Activision licensing
These things and we weren't sure what they were for
Wasn't some of it for DJ Hero
But then some of it never really was explained
Yeah
Basically they're saying
The songs that are licensed so far
2012 by J Sean
Featuring Nicki Minaj
Out of Space by The Prodigy
The Way I Are by Timbaland
Take Over Control by Afrojack
Yeah
I don't know what they're going to really do with this
I assume it's going to be something similar
Like Just Dance or
Dance Central
Trying to cash in
Thanks I hope
I hope they ruin this
Genre as well
Haven't you done enough
Bad
Interesting comment from Game Guru in our chatroom saying
I don't think Activision is following Dance Central
They are following Just Dance
Okay
Those aren't that different
Well they aren't
But I also kind of see the point that
He might be making there with the whole
Kind of the style of the games
And the way they control
Is a little bit different
I guarantee this is probably going to be coming out in the fall
This year
Because they're going to have to have something to fill
I mean what if they really announced
That they're going to be putting out this year
Call of Duty
My question is how is it going to be different
Because otherwise they're just setting themselves up for the same
Goddamn situation
That got Guitar Hero canned
If they come out at E3 and announce
This fucking game
They need to say and here's how it's different
You better acknowledge your competition
And tell us why it's better
Otherwise, fuck off
For real
Our new Guitar Hero game is different because now it has drums
And singing
I don't care what it is
You know Harmonix is bringing Dance Central 2 to E3 this year
You know it
That's got to be their thing that they're working on now
You know that's going to be shown
So if you can walk down the hall
And see Activision in their little game
They better be prepared to say
This is how our game is different
Otherwise I do not give a fuck
And you better bet your ass that Ubisoft is bringing Just Dance
To the other consoles this year as well
I mean that thing sold out like crazy
On the Wii
Of course they're going to be bringing it to the connect and the move
So they've already got right there two competitors
For this genre
And whatever Konami is going to just
Randomly show too
Could be involved in there too
Dance Masters exactly sold millions
But you never know, Konami, bless their hearts
They're still trying
They got DDR
And props to them though for at least trying Dance Masters
What I consider a very Japanese game
You know what, you're right
Dance Masters is very
Different from Dance Central
It really is
You're not really looking deep
At the music game if you pass them both off
As the same game
Because Dance Masters does function very different
The thing that's kind of frustrating about it
Is the fact that it's so hard to really kind of
Get into, you know what I mean
It's just like
I guess it's very much like Para where you just
Do it
And that's it
If they had a little bit more structure
If they had like an actual tutorial or something
To it, it might be better
But hey, you know, sequel
That'd be kind of cool
Alright well Sony Europe
Has actually cancelled some games
Some of these were dance games
Like maybe SingStar, I don't know
But unfortunately, I doubt that by the way
I'm just trolling
But Sony Computer Entertainment Europe
Has mentioned to the staffs at Studio Liverpool
London Studio, Evolution Studios
That they are going to be streamlining
And closing various projects
To move the development to other
Higher priority first party offerings
So we're not talking layoffs or anything
We're just talking about these little games you are making
Yeah, no, no, you need to come
But streamlining could lead to layoffs
Streamlines of corporate work for layoffs
We don't know yet
The publisher went on to say
Quote, with the incredibly strong list of
Exclusive first party titles coming up both
This year and in the near future
Resources should be reallocated to enhance those projects
Closer to completion
Maybe they're trying to rush to meet Christmas, I don't know
Sony exclusives?
Yeah, so who knows
Sony didn't say what projects were affected
They didn't say anything about layoffs
They did reiterate there is no impact
In the role that the first party studios play
It's just, I guess, moving the resources around
Maybe they didn't like that LittleBigPlanet 2
Didn't make Christmas because maybe it impacted
Sales, I bet it did
So maybe they're really stretching
To make Christmas this year and they're really just
Bringing it home on some of the first party games
They're really going to put it all behind
Which I could understand that
And you know, there are some games
When's that Twisted Metal game supposed to come out?
Is it this holiday? So they're going to show that again
At E3, is it?
They have a lot of stuff coming out
I mean, that's for sure
It's pre-packed first quarter for them
And second quarter's starting off pretty strong
I mean, they've got
First quarter so far, they've had LittleBigPlanet 2
They're going to be having
Killzone 3
DC Universe
And PlayStation Move Heroes
Will be coming out
Possibly
Sorcery
I think the Eco and Shadow of the Colossus
Collection, although both of those
I think may have been delayed
And then second quarter so far
They've got SOCOM 4
Motorstorm Apocalypse
Infamous 2
I mean, I wouldn't say
They're definitely putting out their releases
So who knows
I don't know what they're
Uncharted 3
They have for the fourth quarter
Resistance 3
And then
I guess
Twisted Metal, possibly
I wouldn't be surprised if that wouldn't be quarter one of next year
Alright
Well, let's move on with a couple more stories
We'll get to the mailbag here in just a moment
But first, Matt2
Alright, so for those who are
fans of NBA GM
Your time with that game might be coming
to an end
So EA Sports is kind of
Going out here and saying there will be no more
Roster updates or any type of post
Release support for NBA Jam
So it's kind of the
Up and coming news that
NBA Jam is coming to
Coming to an end
EA has been quoted here
The priority for Jam on the 360
PS3 was to deliver HD graphics and online
Play to round out the
Great gameplay that defines the franchise
For us to include roster and
Title update possibilities
Would have been a sacrifice of quality
In those key areas and thus made the difficult decision
Not to include them
So with NBA Jam
And their post game
Releases as well as roster updates looks like the
The franchise is coming to an end
This franchise was so badly
Mismanaged from the beginning and it's really
Sad because it was this whole like
Okay, it's only going to come out on the Wii
No, just kidding, it's coming on the Playstation 3
And the 360 but we're not going to do the
Obvious arcade thing and no, it's only
Going to be an exclusive
With this sub-par basketball game
To try and get it to sell extra copies
Oh fuck, this basketball game really sucks
It's getting cancelled, well shit, now we better
Charge like $60 before this, I mean
This franchise was horribly
Mismanaged from the start
Shame on whoever ran this thing
I mean, I guess they were trying to think of something outside
The box, but you fucked up
Yeah, the marketing project manager on this
Was streamlined, probably out the door
You know what, I hate to say it
But they kind of deserve it
This was a horribly
Mismanaged franchise, this game should have been huge
And it should have been on arcade
Or it should have been a budget title
If this game had been $30, it would have sold
Millions of people would have it
But of course, you know, classic sport games
Like their Madden franchise will still continue to get roster updates
And support, because that thing is still on fire
And it's got a huge following
For the Madden series, so
They literally had to bring this game up
They had to bump this from a B title
To an A title to fill in the gap
Of a game that was so fucking terrible
They had to can it
This game was set up to fail
Absolutely set up to fail
The time and energy spent to not release it
Is definitely a hit in the bottom line
So for those fans of NBA Jam
Looks like
Whatever last copy you have
To own or to rent
Is the last iteration you're going to have
Sell the franchise to someone who knows what to do with it
Seriously
Konami? You never know
I remember playing Double Dribble back in the day
Which was pretty sweet
We did Blades of Steel, was that Konami as well?
Konami knows how to do some pretty sweet sport games
They're winning 11s
I mean, unfortunately, soccer is not
Big here in the US
But it's huge everywhere else
And that's a huge franchise
I just remember playing that game, Blades of Steel
The only time that it had
Speech in an 8-bit NES game
And Ten Yard Rush
Ten Yard Dash
Ten Yard Rush was the first Nintendo title
That was another classic
But anyway, NBA Jam
Coming to an end
Well, we don't know if it's dead
They're stopping the roster
They're not going to support NBA Jam
It doesn't necessarily mean the death of it
But it's
If I had a Magic 8-Ball, it would say Outlook not good
Yeah
Definitely
My gut says it's coming to an abrupt end
Sorry to the fans of that game
Spaznator in our chatroom at
chat.orangelaundry.com says
If NBA Jam was either Xbox Live Arcade or PSN
I'd snatch it up in a heartbeat, but no such luck
I would have done the same thing
Lots of people would
Where did NBA Jam get its start?
In the arcade
Even if they had just buffed up
The old version with new rosters
I would have been all over that
I guess maybe the troubling part is
Getting the rosters to match the
Look and feel of the players
Exploited heads and all that
If you download something
It's an awful lot of content to recreate
Visually to someone's exploited head
I don't know, it's sad
But it's another sporting game that's kind of done
TigerKlon, our chatroom says
Sell the franchise to Activision? They'll end up releasing
New NBA Jams every year
At least they'll get maintained, right?
We'll see
Alright, moving on with some more news
Um
I don't know
We talked a little bit about this
How there was a temporary injunction
Where
LG won against Sony
And they got some of the PlayStation 3
Shipments held
In Europe
Sony actually won
Overall
This was due to a patent dispute
And now
I guess
They're saying that all the C's PlayStations
Have been released
So um
That was quick, and it actually
Only took about a day in the courts
To settle everything
Well that was fast
After all that news about like, oh my god
It's gonna be a shortage of PlayStation 3
Nope, it's done
And then on top of all that
And here we stop
And then on top of all that, LG had to pay legal fees
And they got laughed out of court
And also they're saying that for each day
If LG failed to comply
It would be fine
The rate of 200,000 euros
Ouch
Which is still a buck and a half each
That's a lot of money
That's $275,000 in
US dollars
I think we might
We might actually have some audio from the
Proceedings of the trial, let's see here
Ah god dammit
Somebody bombing on YouTube
Never mind
I think I did a little bit
I was trying to find a clip here
Let me see if I can find this
Um
Okay I think we have a clip here from
The trials proceedings here
Let's see if we can get this out here
What kind of a reliable car are you gonna get
For $1,000?
And I'm asking you, why didn't you
Finish paying your brother for the car?
Well judge, what I'm trying to say is
That bitch scares me
Fucking love Judge Judy
She's amazing
Did you see the episode with, um
She's doing her usual, you know
Killing people with her eyes and her nose
And someone lit up a cigarette
In the audience
Not a plaintiff or defendant but an actual audience member
Just chilling in the back
And she's there going off in her
Diablo fire, spewing
You want to smell smoke?
I smell smoke
And some guy in the back
Actually pretty well dressed, looked like in a suit
Damn courtroom
So what kind of cigarette on TV on Judge Judy
How random is that
She still scares me
I'm trying to see if I can find that in this
It's not on YouTube
It was a random episode that I just had me watching
When I was, you know
There is this one though
What kind of cigarettes did you buy?
Marlboro Reds
It's my hearing or his speech
I'm not sure
I think he smoked a certain type of cigarette
I don't think I've ever seen the bailiff get sassy
Did you hear that? No, it's his speech
The bailiff was getting a little sassy
I think he smoked a certain type of cigarette before
Going to court
Anyhow, moving on
There is no overturning this ruling
If you want to sell your Gameboy
Advanced craft to GameStop
You better do it quick
They're going to stop buying all of this in April
So I think right now
They will buy a Gameboy Advance
For maybe like 20 bucks
But come April
They will not be buying them anymore
April 2nd supposedly is the date that's all happening
You can probably blame
The 3DS for this
Because now everything's kind of kicked back at Generations
So there you go
There's no new Advanced games
Being sold, this isn't really a big surprise anyway
Although I will say
I thought some GameStops still kind of specialized
In selling old shit
Like usually in a big city there's at least one GameStop
That does kind of still carry the old shit
Like the stockpile of NES games
I've seen regular GameBoy games for sale
At GameStop
Are GameStops franchise or corporate owned?
Corporate? Corporate
But it doesn't mean that you can't
Put your GBA up on eBay
Oh yeah
There's GBA and there's indie stores as well
Which by the way the one by my house closed
Yeah there used to be an indie store by my house
It closed
I know, sad
Anyhow
Let's go to the mailbag
Every week you guys send us emails at
Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com
And we like to pick a few of our favorites
And read them here live on air
Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com
A very thin emailbag this week
I'm very disappointed in all of you
Because Loki doesn't look at me during the show
So anyway, he's too into his
Grand Theft Auto hacking thing
Which by the way doesn't seem to be working too well
So we've got one email
This week that I'm going to read for you guys
But it's a good one because it's from Belgium
Ja? Ja
So this is an email from Belgium
Hello good folks at OLR
My TV is about to die on me
I'll have to buy a new one in the near future
Can you give me any advice on what makes a good TV for gaming
And watching DVDs on a 360
And watching analog cable TV
How much milliseconds is good for gaming
Contrast, etc.
You already seem to know
What you're looking for because the delay
Is what you're going to want for gaming
And the refresh rate on the screen
I believe for PC monitors
You don't want to go any higher than 4
Most monitors now are like 2
And I think the TVs are the same way aren't they?
2 millisecond refresh
Something like that
Here's how nerdy I am
I use TV as my monitor from my office
For my PC computer
Playing WoW on that thing is pretty fucking amazing
It is slightly orgasmic
And videos are nice on it too
But definitely look at refresh rates
Definitely look at megahertz
Refresh rate as well
60 or 120
High refresh is also preferred as well
And keep in mind that the
Cheapie TVs right now
Only go as high as 720p in HD
So definitely look at the pixelage
On the TV. Mine only goes as high as
1080i because I bought an HDTV
Kind of on the cheap when HD technology
Was still newish so they cut back
Kind of that way
So double check that
Don't forget to look
At the obvious because sometimes
They will kind of brush that over
To cut a couple hundred dollars. If it's cheap
There's probably a reason. Always remember that
Definitely 1080p and refresh
Rates are probably your two
Pieces of information you want to hold up
People will tell you though you can't tell the difference
Between 1080p and 1080i
I kind of beg to differ. I think I can see it a little bit
Especially in Blu-rays is where I can see it
And also HDMI cables
Get the gold plated ones if you can
There's a better strength to that
At least I've noticed
Spaznator PC in our chat room says
Vizio is supposedly coming out with a
$300 3D HDTV this year
See, something's got to be wrong with it
Although I don't know. My main TV is Vizio
And I've been relatively happy with it
For the fact that it doesn't do 1080p
Well, I have to look at
I paid only $700 for it
Several years ago when HDTV
Was still kind of new-ish
So I can't complain too much
My TV monitor in my room is an
LG 46 inch
I forget the model number
It's amazing. While on it plays very well
It serves well
For monitor use and all that
Don't skip
On those two parts
The resolution and the refresh rate
Well, moving on with our email from Belgium
There's more to it
Also, I ripped the ligaments of my ankle a month ago
During a soccer game
Yes, sports are healthy
Because of this, I'm unable to play any game on Kinect
It made me think of the many disabled people
Who cannot play movement controlled games
Because of their condition
When the future of gaming really is Kinect
Move, Wii, or whatever will be next
I hope there will be a proper alternative
For them to play games
I think we've mentioned on the show before
Gaming can't always 100% be
These technologies
It's nice to have
But it shouldn't always be a necessity
I think there will always be
Something for that core gamer
Who just wants that controller in their hand
To play an RPG or a shoot-em-up
Whatever it is
A good mix is a good thing
Or maybe even games that take
Disabilities into consideration
Would be a great thing
There's many ways a person can be disabled
And you can't always think of everything
But it's always good to see game companies
Be at least considerate
Especially the big ones
Definitely
Well, thanks again for making the show every week
You guys are awesome
Greetings from Fabrice, Belgium
Thank you very much
Sounds like Febreze
Not Febreze, I believe is the name
I wonder if we can send the studio some waffles
Chocolate
Chocolate waffles with chicken
And fries, oh my god, Belgian fries
Oh my god
Road trip
No, there's a place in New York City I went to once
And there was this restaurant in New York City
That just sold nothing but Belgian
Like the French fry type thing
But like the Belgian big ones
And like 20 different kinds of dips for the fries
That's the only damn thing this store sold
Packed, packed, wall to wall
There's actually a place like that in old Sacramento
Is there really?
There's a lot of toppings or dips
Why has my fat ass not been to this place?
It sounds amazing
Because old Sacramento is touristy and we live here and we don't go there
I guess
I've been to old SAC before, it's weird
They're like Spanish with jalapenos and nacho cheese
And they go to France
They've got like blue cheese on them and crap like that
The only problem I have, I can't believe this email is leading to talk about French fries
But whatever, it's orange on the studio, deal with it
The thing is that those restaurants
Usually like the fries with the dips
Half of them are always mayo based
Nope, those are out
I won't do mayo based things
French fries with mayonnaise, disgusting
Anything with mayonnaise, disgusting
If you've known me for any length of time
I hate, hate mayonnaise
Good to know
I won't be making any type of chicken salad for you for lunch
Or put a honey mustard dip in it or something
That's not frickin' mayonnaise
Anyhow
Aw, the chat room's all, you guys are making me hungry
Sorry
Alright, well I guess maybe
The hunger might lead to a little bit of angst
Cause I know when I don't eat, I get mad
So, uh, it's time for the FUs of the week
Moji, start us off tonight
Uh, fuck you too
The stupid Grant Without a Texture editor
It's out there
But it doesn't seem to do anything
Working or whatever
Hate that crap
And then, uh
Yeah, that's basically it
Screw that
I waited all this time and it doesn't open anything
Well, I'm sure there's something wrong
Or it's bugging or something, but I'll figure it out
Uh, Matt2?
Uh, I'm gonna give you
Fuck you to midterms, I've got two of them this week
And, uh
Yeah, not looking forward to finishing those
FU2 income taxes, I'll have to be
Finishing those up here soon so I can
Mail the check to Uncle Sam and
Governor Brown, although it's really good
To not say Governorator anymore
I will yield to that
Um, and FU2Loki's
Texture editor thing that I don't understand
That he seems pretty angsty about
Um, FU to natural disasters
Um, because
FU Mother Nature
Uh, seriously, because, um, yeah, it's just
Oh my gosh, I'm really glad that everybody I know
Is kinda safe, but unfortunately I know like
Thousands of people aren't safe, and that's just
It's just really hard to read
Because that could really happen anywhere
So I just, ugh, very sad
So anyway, um
There's an FU to that, and I would also say
FU to, um, money
I don't have enough of it
I never do
Banks have a lot of issues, kind of go in
And ask for it nicely
Well, if you put one of those Richard Nixon masks over your face
Yes, and offer them a chocolate gun
Maybe I could get some money
And then they'll give it to you magically
Although the pursuing, um,
Might go to jail for many years for that
The tie-in's something that Loki does often
If you get five stars after that bank chase
You're fucked
Alright, couple more stories for you guys
Then we're gonna open up the Skype line
At 1877 Game OLR
Our username on Skype is OrangeLoungeRadio
That's not opened yet, but it will be in a moment
Yes, um, in case you're wondering why Activision
Does what Activision does
They pull out year after year
It's because they're only encouraged by people
That buy those games
And this isn't gonna help
If you're hoping for the Call of Duty franchise
To go away
Call of Duty Black Ops is the
US's best selling game ever
It has beaten everything
In only about four months
And, uh,
That includes also
The sales of Wii Play
Which Nintendo claims is around 13 million copies
I thought this was a down economy
Oh my gosh
13 million copies of Wii Play
Is way too many of that freaking game
But even, oh my gosh
See, I don't really play the Call of Duty games
I can't really hate on them
I've seen them played
I understand why dudes like them
But not a series I personally get into
So this is now the best selling game of all time?
All time
Oh my gosh, that's crazy
It really is
Halo
They sold 5.6 million units day one
Bigger than WoW?
I guess so
Bigger than everything
Well, are you counting subscription based
Or are you counting true sales of the original and expansions?
Well, I don't think you get to combine original and expansions
I think you just have to count original, I suppose
Yeah, but still
It's pretty hot
Alright, one more story for you guys
And it has to do with rumors
What a freaking shock
That the rumors are already starting about an
Xbox 720 and a Wii 2 announcement
At E3
Well, it has to do
And here's where they're coming from
It has to do with some tech demos
That Epic is showing about the next gen graphics
Because their whole Unreal
Engine upgrade and all that
The Guardian in the UK
Is reporting that there is going to be
A Wii 2 that will include a Blu-ray
Drive, a quad-core
processor, and a built-in LED projector
The projector will display
gameplay. Isn't this
Weren't these the early rumors of the revolution
That the 3D was going to be projected
Although, funny enough
Isn't it funny that we did end up getting
3D from Nintendo, it just wasn't
The Wii, it was the 3DS
The Guardian should not be a source for
Anything when it comes to, like, consoles
Duh, there's gonna
Sequel to successful console?
Really? There's gonna be
A new console for Nintendo?
Woah, I do not see that coming at all
I love this too, it's also the
Right time because Nintendo does
Console announcements every five years
The Nintendo 64 in
96, the GameCube
In 2001, and the Wii
In 2006, so surely
Loki, surely the time is
Right for Wii 2
You know, we didn't become the
Super game analysts of the world
For nothing, so let me just tell you
How it's actually done, The Guardian
First off
They're trying to extend their console
Cycles now because, well
It sucks making a new console
Every few years, and honestly, you know
Technology does get better, but I mean
Graphics-wise, what are you gonna really push now?
And they don't really care about graphics
Because they're Nintendo
And that would make the price
Of their console go up quite a bit
Now, not to say that we're not gonna
See another Nintendo console
That's the Wii, you know, we may see something
Like we were saying before, that's kind of a
Next step, like, um, you know
Like people are saying the Wii HD
Or something that may be a little bit
More souped up, is it gonna have an
LCD projector in it?
Probably not, because that's
That's stupid, I mean
That's just kind of weird
It's just ridiculous
Why would I need a projector on my console?
Project things onto my naked body
That's a horrible, horrible thought
I have no words
Mario could jump up and down on my wang
That's one platform-based game right there
Oh my god, can you think about the YouTubes
That are gonna come from a projected Wii game
I mean, it's not like it's that hard
To hook up a console to a projector
I mean, you can walk into Fry's and buy a projector
My buddy's done it before with an Xbox original
He had Mario jump on his wang?
No, he's hooking up an L
He took an LCD projector
And respective cables and components
And was able to project the image
Of the game on a blank wall
But that's because we had to take down posters
So a projector is gonna need space
Blank canvas to work on
It's not gonna happen
No, that's dumb
I'm sorry
No, they're not gonna do that
And a quad-core processor
Or something like that
Really? Really?
A quad-core processor?
Is that what you think
The fastest thing is out there?
I mean, shit
The fucking 360 has more cores than that
Nintendo's main release
I think this year is not the Wii 2
Or the Wii Squared, it is the 3DS
And that's what they're gonna stick to
They don't need to
They don't need to even think about a new console
Until their system starts becoming number one
The Wii is still popular
It's releasing decent games
They're still playing it
The 3DS is gonna continue that
Now the thought is, of course, that they may want to try to get the jump
On the next generation
Because the 360 did have that jump
And they did pretty well
I don't know
They're just not gonna do some sort of Blu-ray
Crazy
They don't need to
For one, Sony owns Blu-rays
That'd be kinda weird
Well, I still think that the next-gen consoles
Especially on the 360
Or you're gonna see something that's not a DVD drive
They have to because of the capacity
Yeah, because you just can't
Did they always say
Never to use projectors with games
It was always the first line in the various instruction manuals
Yeah, because of burn-in
But that's just old-school projectors
And even still
You're not gonna want to do that
Because old-school projectors
Nowadays, there's still some latency for that
But no
Why would you even have a fucking projector
On a console? That makes no sense
Like I said
To project Mario onto my naked body
It's seriously some guy making a story
The cell tabloid
The guardian
Spaznator in our chatroom says
Sky, that's a mental picture I seriously didn't need
Thank you
Is it possible to bleach a mental picture out of one's mind?
Yes, just pour the bleach into your ears
I don't know, let me ask you here
Hold on
And now I present a little bit of Mario
Jumping on my wang
Hold on, let's see if I can
Project Mario here
Jumping on my wang
Really don't
Ow!
Did he jump on a ball?
That was like the shittiest NES rip of a game
It really was
No, but seriously
If they're gonna do something with their next
Or Wii
The next Wii or whatever
It's gonna be just kind of an HD upgrade
I don't even think it would need to be necessarily
On
You know, non-DVD
Platform, because right now
Fuck, they are not even really using dual layer
There's like two games that use dual layer DVDs
For the Wii
There's no real need to do that
In order for the Wii to be competitive
Like for like, you need to
Throw in blu-ray capacity and some type of
Body-sensing motion device
Because that's what the two consoles have right now
As Rob Giggles, like a little school girl
So, what is the Wii
Squared to, whatever
Maybe it's not a projector, maybe it's like a
A wang
Well, then they're already on par with
Their competition, they'd have to exceed
Their competition
Now, this is getting off of Star Trek for me
But if they did some type of holography or hologram
Or something like that instead of a projection
Then they'd have something, but again, what would you use it for?
No, it's The Guardian
They're not really newsworthy
It's entertaining, although if they named the Xbox
Second iteration the 720
Really?
No, it's what everybody wants to call it
They're gonna call it something cool and hip
Well, I'll tell you what an awesome name would be, The Bacon
They just call it The Xbox Bacon
Who doesn't love bacon?
Want to come over and play with bacon? Fuck yeah!
I don't know if they should really call
The sequel of a console that had issues with heat
Baking
Not a good thing
They called a
The most popular console in America right now
Is called The Wii
That's what little girls do when they sit on the toilet
They Wii
I remember the commercials when it came out
Those two creepy HD guys would come up
We would like to play? I'm like, whoa
This game's for pedophiles or something like that
This console's a little bit weird
And then it was motion controlled
And hilarity ensued
What would you call the red ring of death
On a console called bacon?
I don't know, there's got to be some type of
Joke there someplace, it's not coming to me
There would never be a ring or red
On any Microsoft console
Going forward
A Jewish Xbox
This Xbox is kosher
It's made by Jewish monks
I tease because I love, come on people
I guess I could say something about
There is job postings at Microsoft
Looking for hardware engineers
To quote, define and deliver next
Generation console architectures
Well, no shit they're making a new Xbox
Doesn't mean it's coming out of E3 this year
These things are going to be like
Four years out, you know, it'll be a while
So
Do you think Apple is rumored to
Release some type of a gaming console?
That's a lot of buzz in the whole Apple world
What I think they're going to do is
Yes, it's called the iPad
The gaming console, come on people
That's retarded, first off
Oh goody, I get to plug an HDMI cable
Into my iPad and be tethered to my TV
No thanks
Oh, and I'm sure that
Cable cost you $40 to make
Fuckers
Oh, my mistake, $30
Well that totally makes sense, a piece of cable
That's like a few
Feet long, what, like six
Six feet?
I remember the size, it was $29.99 for the
HD adapter thing to send
And 1080p
From the pad
To a compatible
TV
So I'm going to credit AkumaJP in our chatroom for this comment
But perhaps this could be the sequel to
The Nintendo Wii, could be this
Sitting on the toilet
She's an awfully jolly lady
Wait, best part's coming out
Flushing? Yep
You're joking right, I've never seen this before
Here comes the punchline
Wait for it
Sitting on the toilet
Yeah, FLUSH!
The Nintendo Flush, this year at E3.
It's videos like that that keep me gay.
Rob, why do you do this to me? I thought we were friends.
It was the chatters! The chatters said it!
But you played it!
It's every gamer has a voice, even that lady.
Now she's one of those challenge people that probably couldn't use the Kinect.
Yeah, the Kinect.
Because she'd be sitting on the toilet and have minimal body movement for the Kinect.
Oh lord.
I have to go home and favorite that now.
It's pretty awesome.
Spread it around.
You gotta admit.
I was trying to find the 8-bit remix of that song to prove that she plays video games, but I don't know.
I guess it's not on YouTube anymore. Whatever.
Anyhow, I guess we can open up the Skype line now and take some calls.
1-877-GAMO-L-R. Our username on Skype is OrangeLoungeRadio.
Give us a call. We'll talk about whatever it is you want to talk about tonight.
Hopefully it's gaming-related, but if you want to talk about sitting on the toilet, then more power to you.
So the phones are open right now. Let's take some calls.
We'd rather you didn't talk about sitting on the toilet.
That's true. So let's go to some calls.
Hi, you're on OrangeLoungeRadio. Who's this?
This is that one, Akke Ripper from Sweden.
What's up, Akke Ripper? I haven't heard from you in a while. How you doing?
Yeah, well, I have been away. Oh, no, I haven't been away. I've just been sleeping like when you're on.
Unfortunately.
No worries. What's on your mind tonight?
What was I going to say? Well, I could talk about Dragon Age 2, which I have already finished.
Ah, what do you think?
It's marvelous.
Once again, to the minor story behind it, well, I got it on Wednesday, and I got it pretty early because it locked up.
It was unlocked at midnight to Thursday, my time.
So what is it? At 3 o'clock Wednesday, your time, I think it is, and got unlocked.
And like 40 or 50 hours later, I beat it. It was quite nice, really. It's thumbs up.
Do you recommend it?
I do recommend it highly.
How was the lovemaking?
It was quite nice, I do say.
It was quite nice, from what I see.
It's a nice.
It's quite a nice.
But here's the other thing though. Since really I almost, but here's the other thing.
Well, I did make love to one of the characters, but here's the other thing though.
Since really, really, really, these love scenes in both Mass Effect and Dragon Age Origins and Origins 1 is awkward beyond fucking awkward.
It's like, I don't even want to see, I close my eyes.
No! No! Really? Really? What the hell?
Just no, no.
This is the best video game review we've ever had on this show.
I'm glad to be here, present for this.
But other than that, it really is a kick-ass game.
Unfortunately a bit shorter than the first Origins, but it's on par with Mass Effect 2.
And maybe even longer than Mass Effect 2 on second thought.
Well, I would say really bi. And most of the, and also, it really makes up for one of the, yeah, how the fuck will they continue this?
Even though, one of the comments that I found on Twitter is that the whole story in Dragon Age 2 is like a origin story, if that makes sense.
Overall, yeah, so thumbs up.
Also, Tactics Orger has finally been released, and that's quite funny.
Also, on side notes, as usual, I play as a girl character, because I don't, because here's the other thing though.
I don't even like playing as a male character, because, well, hello, I'm one of those trannies, whatever, that's not, that, if I even would choose.
I don't even want to be a man, and I don't want to be a girl, either.
That doesn't even necessarily have anything to do with it though, because I like to play, like all of my characters in World of Warcraft are women,
and that's just because people are nicer to you, because they think you have big boobs sitting there behind the monitor.
I just, it's totally like selfish reasons, like, you know.
Yeah, well, in a way. Also, in a kind of way, there are, I should point out also, I play, as usual, I play, I was on the difficulty settings of casual,
which means that I, in one way, breezed it through, and was all like, yeah, yeah, whatever.
But here's the other thing though, even though if you play on casual, you will actually have minor problems on two places though.
Which I did have problems on two places, but after all I did some thoughts on two things, and was like, yeah, it's not that hard, really.
But it will be kind of hard in some places.
Well, I don't blame you for playing on the easiest level. I've been playing Torchlight on the easiest level, because I just want to, you know, jam through the game and kind of see everything that's there.
But, you know, sometimes you just want to kind of take in the story, or in some cases, get straight to the lovemaking.
Yeah, but also, since I've seen the ending to Dragon Age 2, it makes me actually want to replay origins, so my warden can make love to a certain character,
so to set up certain things in Origins 2.
You have to go back and get the right characters to fall in love so that the lovemaking can continue in 2 now.
Or the STDs.
Yeah, can you pass the STDs from one game to another? Alright, forget it.
Alright, Ate Ripper, to be quite honest, I don't ever want this call to end, but I've got people...
Yeah, also, before I go, there has been released a new trailer for apparently two expansions on Sims games.
Ah, yes.
One apparently animal expansion for the console version, and then we have, like, what is it, Sims 3 Pets or something, and then you have some Sims 3 Generations, which is apparently for the PC version.
Unfortunately, though, there has been no signs of weather effects, which is a bit sad, because I do want weather effects.
But here's the other thing, though. It makes interesting, because, well, raising kids in Sims is quite fun, and with this expansion, it will expand that.
Do you think there will be a Sims 4 anytime soon?
Not likely. Not that it seems so.
Also, side note, they don't say any date for the Generations 1, but for the animal expansion on console, it's at November 2011.
Alright.
So, um...
Yeah.
Alright. Well, Ate Ripper, I gotta let you go so I can get to some of the calls, because I got people from PAX East that are just dying to get through.
Yeah, well...
Honestly, you need to have a video game review podcast. You need to think about it.
Oh, well, well. Oh, well.
Later on! Take care, buddy!
Yeah, later.
Bye.
Where is he from again?
Sweden.
I'm going to Sweden.
You know, and here's the thing. He hasn't called us in quite a long time, because, you know, it's like, freaking what? Like, they're eight, nine hours ahead of us right now?
At least nine.
I don't know how Daylight Savings kind of plays that. So it's like four or five o'clock in the morning over there right now, so I can't blame him for not staying up every week to listen to OLR.
Word.
God damn, that was worth it. Alright, that was worth the wait.
Alright, I'm going to do a rare outbound call, because I promised these guys they could get through, and it's about PAX East, so I want to do this call real quick if I can.
Sorry to those folks trying to get through right now, but I did promise this call, because I want to talk to at least one person that went to PAX East this week.
We'll do some more incoming calls in a minute. Just hold on. Hold on, guys.
By the way, a question in the chatroom if I've played Mortal Kombat. Hey, hey, it's Rob from Orange Lounge Radio.
Hey, it's Rob from Orange Lounge Radio, who's this?
Hey, it's DJ Rama S and DDR Dollar Bill.
Hey, you guys. Some of our regular callers here at Orange Lounge Radio, but I know you guys went to PAX East, right?
Yeah.
So fucking tell us about it. What happened? What'd you see?
It was great, but Rob, before we continue, there's one thing you need to know.
What?
Yeah. The anime title, FLCL, is called Fully Coolie.
Oh, my bad. I'm just, I'm not, you know, cultured enough to know these things. I'm sorry.
I knew that.
It's okay, we forgive you.
Alright.
I've learned something here on the show tonight. Tell me about PAX East already. I don't care about that damn anime.
Okay, Rob.
Yes.
I played the 3DS.
It's fucking awesome. Yes.
Even though, okay, let me ask this question now, because I've been, you know, I said ever since E3, I was like, dude, the minute you play one, it will sell you one.
Like, it almost violates that golden rule of gaming, that the system is only as good as the games that are on it, because seriously, does it even matter that the games are subpar right now?
Nope. Doesn't matter at all.
It's the technology, right? The first time you see it, it's kind of, did you do that thing where you looked at it and then you went, whoa, whoa, this is like real.
Yeah. And the funny thing is, back where I used to live, when I used to get my monthly bus passes, they actually had a 3D effect similar to the 3DS screen, so I was automatically used to it.
Right. So what did you get to play on it?
The Legend of Zelda, the Ocarina of Time.
And what did you think?
It was great. Now, here's something, I don't know if you've covered it, because the stream was dropping for us as we were traveling, but when you play with, when you grab the slingshot, you can actually move the 3DS around for targeting in the game.
Oh, see, these are some of like the new features from this entire game.
Oh, well, that's it. I have to totally buy this rehash of a 64 game, because they have motion controls now.
Oh.
It's different.
Damn, Loki. Who put the hater in your tree today, man? Dang, oh.
He's been hating for a couple of weeks now. It's all right. But yet, did you hear the part where he's ordered both a Japanese and an American 3DS?
I don't blame him because of region locking, so you know.
Yeah. So, what else was there? I heard Children of Eden was there, and I hear it's like amazing. Did you guys play it?
I didn't, but Alpha Kanabran, he was like, it was amazing. Yeah.
And that look was like fucking orgasm.
I want to know more about it. Well, how did the show compare to last year?
It was, in a way, kind of felt like last year was a little bit better, but on the same token, it was just oh so much to see, you know?
Yeah.
It was like, Exo Hall was twice as large, tabletop gaming was twice as huge, you know?
Wow.
And it was a lot more, and Marvel vs. Capcom 3, the number one horned out game at this con.
Of course.
Of course. Of course everybody's going to be playing that. Did you check out the classic gaming room while you were there?
Yeah, I got in there for a little bit. It had all of your favorite games in there, too.
Awesome. What about panels? Did you spend any time going to a panel or anything?
I went to the video game music panels. I went to one about OC Remix, where two of the composers did live the opening to Final Fantasy VI.
Oh, that's hot.
Yeah.
Was that as awesome as it sounds?
Say what?
Much better. I recorded it. Instead of getting a chance, I'm going to throw it up on YouTube.
Nice. Very cool. Alright, so what was the best thing about PAX East altogether?
Oh, man. That's a lot.
That's a lot. I mean, I went just for two things. The 3DS and Duke Nukem Forever. Got my play. It was great.
What was the demo for Duke Nukem Forever like?
What was what?
It was fucking win. I mean, you start out in a football field punching people so you get the weapon and you start blowing shit up.
Was there titties?
Real life titties, yes. Oh, yeah.
Wait, are we talking about Duke Nukem Forever still, or are we talking about like you just saw titties in the expo hall, like randomly?
I'm talking about the booth babes, my brother. The booth babes.
Of course, the booth babes. Nice.
Well, anything else you want to get out about PAX East before I get to more calls?
It was fun. It's worth it to come because as we were hanging out Saturday night, the way it was laid out, it was like not really stressful.
This kind of revitalizes the reason why I go to conventions and also there was no appointment per se set up for demos.
You could email them and they will email you back if you want a time to come in to check out particular products and games.
But even though I was pressed, you had to wait just like everybody else except on Saturday where you're allowed in an hour early.
Alright, that's cool. That's cool. I'm glad to hear it because we were getting a little worried on some of the things we heard, but I guess they were just rumors.
Last I could have heard was not exactly true. That's the problem.
Alright. Well, one other thing I want to ask. Did you guys catch, what was the last Omegathon game this year? I haven't heard yet.
We couldn't do that because we had to drop off Misty and Alpha Kinanagram at the train station and the airports.
Aw, bummer. Alright. Well, maybe somebody in chat will yell it out. I'm sure it's going to hit the internet somewhere.
O-L-R invasion next year.
Next year, PAX East 2012, O-L-R-Con. It's going to be you, me, Dark Sakura, Loki, TDR Dollar Bill, Misty, Alpha Kinanagram, Zaku, the whole crew.
We're getting a suite. We're getting some alcohol. We're bringing the 360s. We're going to jury rig the TV. We're going to get our gaming on.
And boobs. Hell yeah.
Alright. Well, you guys have fun. Be safe on your drive back and thanks for letting me bug you even though you're on the show every week anyway, Rama.
Hahahaha. Love you too, man.
Later, DDR Dollar Bill. Drive safe. I said later, DDR Dollar Bill too. Drive safe, you guys. Later.
Awesome. Let's get some more calls.
Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio. Who's this? It's Zaku here. Hey, Zaku, buddy. What's on your mind?
Yup. I, too, also went to PAX with Adam. Awesome. Also known as Rama.
I mean, yeah, sure, it was my first PAX, but at least I was able to pull off a decent trip to Boston.
Even though it was like, the way I see it is, what the fuck?
It's all good. What did you think of PAX East? What did you play?
Yeah, I mean, I did try to partake in most of the things on the show floor, but the lines were too long.
There was no way I was going to spend two hours waiting to see what's inside the LA Nor booth, let alone the Battlefield 3 one.
By the way, just quickly, I know Adam for a fact that he endured whatever he did to see the 3DS, but it was almost E3-like.
Where the lines would just stretch literally around the booth.
That's the only turn off, and I guess it's part of the fact that PAX is pretty much like a poor man's E3.
Was there just too damn many people?
Pretty much. Compared to all the other cons I've been to, even the ones I've been to in the Javits Center in New York, this was by far one of the largest I've ever been to.
Well, the East Coast sadly doesn't get a lot, so I'm not surprised at all that everybody comes in.
PAX does fill that void for folks that can't actually make it out to E3, so it's creating that whole experience, that experience itself, without having to go on the other side of the country.
But more to my point, I did cosplay on Saturday, and I'm just trying to upload the picture I took personally.
I mean, I post for several pictures, some for media, but I didn't make Kotaku's roll. But I'll upload mine.
Well, let me ask you quickly, I want to take it back to the games a little bit. Even though the lines were long, I'm assuming you got your hands on some things, right?
Yeah, some. I wouldn't say a lot, but it's like, I was just hanging, you know, just going from some booths.
What did you play that's worth talking about right now?
Oh man, I can't even think off the top of my head. Homefront. Homefront, yeah.
And how was that?
Pretty much, that's definitely one thing I'm going to buy on Tuesday. Well, for PC that is, but the 360 version is just as good.
That was what I was able to get my hands on without having to wait hours in line.
Most of the major titles there, they were, you know, it's like, you're going to spend hours just going through two or three of them, and that's going to cut into most of your day on the show floor.
Did you get to do any other of the sights and sounds of E3 that wasn't just the...
Yeah, I went to the harmonics panel.
Oh, how was that?
Saturday. It was pretty good, I mean, you know, I managed that.
Did they comment on the whole sale from MTV and all that?
No, it was just like, well, what they did was like a reverse Q&A where they actually, you know, where the panel asked questions to, you know, the fans that lined up to speak.
So, I was basically asked a question on, you know, how to deal with like asshole, you know, fans that complain about some of the most obvious and like unrealistic things about the game.
And so I had to, you know, I was basically asked my opinion on those, you know, on that particular subject.
What did you say?
So, I managed to relate it to the DDR scene, well, my local DDR scene, and I pretty much like got a pretty good ovation out of it.
Props to you, buddy.
I know, if it was recorded live, I'm pretty sure my comment was up there.
You know, if the panel, you know, mentions a military zombie, that was me.
So, are you going back to PAX next year?
Yeah, I mean, this time I have to stay in, you know, I have to stay in the hotel right next to the con, but yeah, I'll definitely do it.
It's just that I may have to like go, I may have to take that day off, you know, that Friday off just to get my hands on the show early.
I'd take a whole week off to go to E3, although I'm probably not going this year, but yeah, it's a lot, so.
Alright, well, Zacko, buddy, I'm gonna let you go so we can get more calls, but I'm glad to hear you had a good time at the show, even if you can get your hands on all the good stuff.
Sounds like you found a few gems in there somewhere, so.
Yep, sure did.
Alright, well, hopefully, see you next year.
Definitely.
Alright, later.
Bye.
I need to make a whole to-do of it and just go out to the East Coast.
You're a fan of New York City, right, Matt, too?
I know you love to go out to New York City and all that.
Absolutely.
We have a lot of listeners out in New York City, and I've gone out there a couple times and done like meetups, and we had some nice like Dave and Buster's fun, and did some random things out in the city, it's cool.
Yeah, New York is good, and it's expensive.
We'll go to PAX East next year, don't you want to go to Boston and play some games?
Baston?
I have never been to Baston before, to walk in the park.
Baston is fun.
I went to Baston, I went with somebody who went to college there, say did some schooling there, so he knew the area pretty well, and we had fun.
Boston's actually on one of my lists of cities to see in the East, but yeah, New York is a lot of fun.
1877 Game OLR, or a username on Skype is OrangeLawninsRadio, what the hell, we usually only do three, but I'm feeling generous tonight, let's do one more call.
While we wait for a call, oh, call's coming in right now, I guess we'll go to it. Hi, you're on OrangeLawninsRadio, who's this?
Hi, this is Baston here.
Hey buddy, what's on your mind?
Just to be different this week, rather than talking about videos, I'll be touching on MMOs this time.
Alright, MMOs.
Yeah, specifically two of them, DC Universe Online and Final Fantasy XI, mainly because you guys kind of touched on them earlier.
Well, one thing that wasn't mentioned that is kind of interesting is that supposedly, at least with DC Universe Online, sometime within the near future, I think within the next month or two, there's going to be a digital download version appearing on the PSN store.
And I had heard of that, that they're going to do a full digital download, which wouldn't be too unrealistic. I mean, Xbox 360 does something similar already with some of the games, and I believe PlayStation has a handful of games you can buy.
I want to say one of them was day and date of Street Release.
World of Warcraft's latest expansion was full digital download as well, which was awesome.
Hell, PC thrives on digital download. Hello Steam. I mean, Steam is like PC gaming right now. It's a big chunk of it, so I'm kind of not surprised all PS3 is going in that direction.
DC Universe Online is a Sony online entertainment, so it's another branch of the same company, same family, so not surprised at all by that news, but neat.
Yeah, well, some doing that has its ups and downs depending on how you look at it. On one hand, yeah, there's the convenience factor, no doubt about that.
At least with the beta that went on, granted, it was beta not the full retail releases, obviously there's going to be differences, but at least with the beta, that was a pretty freaking huge file.
I mean, it was like, what, ballpark figure of 15 gigabytes?
It was huge.
Yeah, and even if you got a pretty hefty hard drive inside your system, there's still a good chunk of your hard drive dedicated to one game, but hopefully most PS3 owners have already, at least at $1.40, already upgraded their hard drive at least once.
So what did you want to say on Final Fantasy XIV?
Well, actually 11, not 14.
Oops, sorry, 11.
Yeah, well, you know how you were mentioning that, at least temporarily speaking, that they're going to be shutting down the servers for the game because of the recent earthquake?
Right.
Well, just prior to that earthquake hitting, they had made an announcement that they're already going to be consolidating some of the servers.
Uh oh, that's usually the sign for the MMO that things are going downhill, but you know what though, come on, Final Fantasy XI's had a good run, and Sony did kind of probably siphon some of the players with a release of 14, kind of cannibalized 11 a little bit.
Yeah, well, I hate to mention a rival podcast, but this is where I got the information from.
There's a podcast that's dedicated to Final Fantasy XI called Limit Break Radio, and they had a very small podcast, their most recent entry for that show on their website.
The main host had mentioned that the first time they consolidate the servers, there was a need for it, then yeah, they could see what they did, but the second round of consolidation of servers, they don't see what the logic behind that was because once this new round of consolidation goes through,
the servers would probably actually be overpopulated, and for those trying to do the end game kind of thing, it's going to be a lot more difficult for those people because the competition for the mobs and...
They might be worried that they're going to hemorrhage more users because of some of the other MMOs that are out, just with Rift and DC Universe and so on, maybe they're just worried, they're kind of being proactive, I suppose.
Well, it's kind of sad to see Final Fantasy XI going this route for the reasons that you just mentioned, because it's kind of foreboding.
Granted, I haven't played the game in a year or two now because of financial reasons, but I was always hoping that eventually once I was able to, I could get back into the game because I love the game so much.
There'll always be at least one server up, it's a Final Fantasy game, it'll never die completely. I want to ask you real quick before I let you go, since you brought up MMOs and I know you're big on Sony products and Sony fanboy and all that, and you like free things, what do you think about the announcement of Free Realms coming to PlayStation 3?
Well, I really haven't formed an opinion as of yet, because obviously I haven't played Free Realms, either on PS3 because it hasn't come out yet for it, and I just got my computer not even two months ago and it just barely runs some games, albeit poorly.
So, until I actually play something, I can't really form a decent opinion about it, but I'm willing to at least give it a try.
I'll tell you what, once I give it a try, let's say for a multitude, I'll either send an email or call in and essentially give a mini review of it. That way I can be a little bit more fair and balanced about it.
Alright, we'll be looking to hear from you.
Alright, but for now we're going to let you go so we can wrap up the show, but have a good one buddy!
Yep, you too, take care.
Alright, later!
Alright, that's going to do it for the Skype line tonight, thank you guys so much for calling, sorry to those who didn't get through, if you didn't get through tonight, you can always send us an email, our mailbag had like one email in it tonight you guys, mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com, type out your thoughts and we'll read them next week on the show.
But for now, last minute stories, I forgot to ask Loki, we had some back to back calls tonight, Loki did you have any last minute stories?
Not too much actually, this is kind of stupid, you know, same thing with DJ Hero, I care about that, I don't really care about this.
But Guitar Hero, hey look, there's more DLC coming out, now I know we said that we weren't going to put anything out because we're done with that series, but the phones asked for it so we're putting out more DLC.
Well thank you for graciously giving us DLC for your game that you've decided to discontinue, whatever.
Anyway, so those tracks coming to Guitar Hero Warriors of Rock, they're from the artist Trapped, and you get modern...
Didn't you read this earlier in the show?
I already did.
Sorry!
We were trying to design textures for GTA.
I was the only one, Matt.
I didn't read the story with any angst, so I was trying to do a little bit of journalistic...
It's still stupid though because they say, oh well we're just continuing the series, ah just kidding we're going to put it out because the fans want it.
Who listens to the fans?
Um, there's apparently the guy that Dan Fortin from Midway, who's now a part of NetherRealm I guess, you may remember him as the Toasty guy.
He's coming back in the new Mortal Kombat game.
Toasty!
Yes.
Alright.
Well, that's going to do it, I guess if that's it for the last minute stories.
I believe it is.
Another episode of Orange Launch Radio has come to a close, but not before we say goodnight to everybody.
Starting off with Matt too, thank you for being here tonight and filling in for Dark Sakura.
Thanks for the invite, I appreciate it.
You did a good job with the news tonight.
Well, thank you very much.
Alright, so we'll have to have you back again sometime.
Hopefully not to fill in for someone.
Exactly.
Maybe just to be the fourth wheel at another point.
Fifth, you've got the chat room.
That's true, we do have the chat room.
Always present fourth guest on the show.
I'll be the spare tire.
The fifth wheel.
I'll be the spare tire in the back.
Excellent.
I'll be the junk in your trunk.
Well, we'll see you again, don't wait two years before coming back.
Do you have any final thoughts for our listeners?
Um, Nutrisystem sucks.
Although it's working, it sucks.
I did have dinner tonight consisting of Buffalo Wing Pretzel Bites and macaroni and cheese in a cup.
Delicious.
Yes.
Not.
I'm going to go eat something else when I get home.
Final thoughts?
No, really great to be here.
Hopefully I'll be invited back on your other podcast in the future so I can be the Deckard Cain of your show and stay a while and listen.
Of course.
But no, thank you for having me.
Look, it was a pleasure seeing you and I will work on my angst next time.
And thanks for the beer.
Did it work?
Maybe.
I've got two more at home.
Awesome.
Alright, I want to say a final thought, headaches suck.
Beer doesn't make headaches better either.
It's too bad.
Loki, your final thought tonight?
I am tracking my 3DS.
It's coming out of Oakland right now so I will have that tomorrow for sure.
Alright.
It must get stolen first.
Unless the plane crashes or they lose it.
Or it doesn't get stolen in Oakland.
Alright, that's going to do it for another episode of Orange Launch Radio.
Thank you guys so much for downloading and listening to our show.
We really appreciate it.
You know, we don't ask for anything to do this show except tonight we do ask you to
donate at least $10 to the Red Cross for a game and donate to those in need this week.
It's very important.
However, outside of that, the way you can help promote this show and continue what we
do here, just tell a friend.
Tell a friend about the show.
Even if you like, I don't know who to tell about the show, leave a nice 5 star review
on iTunes or wherever it is you found this podcast at.
Forums.
I actually get the little emails from Google and see people talk about it on forums and
I just really appreciate you guys that say nice things about the show.
It doesn't go unnoticed.
I really appreciate it.
So, until next time, we'll be back with Dark Soccer to do it all again next week.
I hope you all have a wonderful night and until then, bye bye.
Be safe this week.
You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
To join us for a live show, visit www.allgames.com Sunday nights at 6 pm Pacific time.
The views and opinions expressed on Orange Lounge Radio do not necessarily reflect those
of the entire staff of Orange Lounge Radio or allgames.com, but we're probably right
anyway.
See you next week.