Orange Lounge Radio
Who's the host?
Dark Sakura
Sky and Loki
Tonight, March 20th, 2011
Some big games get delayed
The NES classic River City Ransom will soon have a sequel
And could a Silent Hill game be on the way to Xbox Live Arcade?
Orange Lounge Radio
Hello my friends out there on the internet
And welcome back to another week of Orange Lounge Radio
It's the show where every gamer has a voice
And we are here live with episode number 406
On this March the 20th of 2011
My name is Rob Roberts, I'll be joining you over the next few hours
When my awesome co-hosts say hello to the one and only
Dark Sakura, or Jamie Summers
I beat your butt at Pinball Effects
It's Pinball Effects on what? PS3?
Xbox
You were literally showing me this while the opening was going
So I didn't have time to process this
Because I just found the picture
Yes, I'm putting it up on our thing
Oh gee, thank you
No, it's the icons, because I think it's cute
Your icon's like, sad face
Mine's like, one!
Oh wait, it's not Xbox 360, the FX2 or whatever, the new one?
Well we don't have FX2, we just have FX
But it's got samples of the FX tables
But we'll get into that in my gaming week
I was going to say, at some point, I don't want to spoil the gaming week
But you should get the FX2, because the shell is free
No, I totally want, I totally want
Oh yeah, go for it
Alright, also joining us tonight, say hello
As he does every week, to the one and only tech master, Loki!
Hi
How are you, Loki?
Good
Awesome
And Loki's brought some new toys to the show tonight
That he's been showing off
Yes
You want to tell our listeners about what you've brought to the studio?
I brought a 3DS from Japan
I'm not privy enough to get one of the US ones early
I am going to be getting one on time, though
Nice
With Street Fighter, because that's the bundle I picked
And then, Motor Store Apocalypse
I got review code for that because
Because Sony loves me so much
Or because I bought it off eBay
Nice
Photographic evidence now on orangerealgeradio.com
Yes, I noticed you've been taking pictures over and over there
And you've been uploading them to orangerealgeradio.com
I actually took a picture on the 3DS of myself
So I can see myself in 3D
Because looking in the mirror obviously isn't good enough
I wanted to see what I would look like on a 3DS in the picture
But unfortunately I can't upload that
You can
Oh, can you?
But it's a format that only 3D devices can read
It's like an ITG
It's some sort of weird format
But it's for 3D devices
So it wouldn't do me any good to upload it to orangerealgeradio.com
Because no one would see it
You wouldn't be able to see it unless you have
Like a 3DS
Or maybe some of those special cameras
Or the phones or whatever that can view 3D stuff
Or maybe a 3D TV
I don't know if you can view pictures on a 3D TV
I would not want to blow up that picture to the size of a 50 inch television
No, look at my crap
I noticed the resolution on the cameras
They're VJ cameras
It's really just a gimmicky thing right now
But like 10 year olds will have a field day with it
I'm having a field day with it
Are you really?
I have to admit I was nosy
The first thing I did before I took a picture of myself
Is I looked at everything you were taking pictures of
And it's this cat
Oh it's the cat
Oh look more pictures of the cat
Here's a picture of his desk at work
Oh and here's the cat again
Well she was there at the time
That's why I took a picture of her
She's so exploited
It works really well with stuff that has a lot of depth in it
Because if you just take a picture of
I took a picture of triple baked pizza
Thankfully my nose is gigantic
So there's a lot of depth there
You can actually almost
The photo that I took of the game while I was playing it
You can actually almost see the 3D in it
It's actually kind of neat
Almost
You can actually see the layers in the image
Is what you can see
Eventually it'll be kind of cool
Because maybe you can download the pictures
Through the web browser
When it comes out in May
That's awesome
Um
Yeah it's been pretty fun to play with
I've got Nintendogs
But I haven't played Nintendogs
It's mainly just the show off
Because no one really cares about 3D
Although Ridge Racer does look pretty cool in 3D
So I could have just stuck with that game
But I wanted more than one game
I picked Nintendogs
Because whatever
May would help justify to the wife
The cost of everything
It's like oh I'll get you Nintendogs
She wouldn't, no
She doesn't care
She thought Nintendogs was dumb to begin with
I thought Nintendogs was dumb
But I had to see what it looked like in 3D
And it looks pretty cool, very fuzzy
They are very fuzzy
And my whole row, they're just treating them like they're real dogs
Oh the puppies are here
It's our official puppies
Okay
I would play Nintendogs
Maybe that one won't make me feel completely
Violently ill to my stomach
I used to play it for like 15 minutes
I used to play it for 15 minutes
During my break at work
And then I would forget about my puppies
And they would run away
Are you gonna get one at launch?
I might have to wait a little bit
Yeah it's probably fine
There's only one game
Other than
Street Fighter
That I'm getting with the US one
And Street Fighter is kind of like eh
It was either, well the three options I had were
Street Fighter, Samurai Warriors
Which eh, don't care about Samurai Warriors
And uh
I'm trying to think of the other one
I don't remember
Madden or something like that
I don't want Madden
So I picked Street Fighter
And then I'll probably pick up Pilotwings
Because I want to play Pilotwings
Yeah I would play Pilotwings
That looks fun, otherwise I'll probably wait for the Kid at Gris game
But, yeah Kid at Gris looks awesome
But Pilotwings, I'm very disappointed
There's only three types of
Things
Well the Super Nintendo one was maybe four
I guess, wow that's kind of sad
Oh yeah because they keep forgetting
Every fifth stage was like
This random shoot em up that you would have
So it was actually like a fifth
Well they have that kind of stuff in there
Hang gliding, jet pack
Sky diving
There's another one
By plane
And then the shoot em up stages
But I mean come on
If you can pull off four on a Super Nintendo
I think you can maybe pull off
More than that, I mean come on
Let's be honest here
The geometry for the levels and stuff like that
You're using WooHoo Island or whatever
From Wii Sports Resort
You have the island, the 3D object created
I keep forgetting that WooHoo Island is like a character now
Oh it's dumb
It's a character
It's a character no one cares about
It's an island, big deal
You know someone can make an island
Especially with the level of graphics
That they're putting in there, I mean come on
This is the type of stuff that you would have seen in
Prop Cycle, hell Prop Cycle had
More detail to it than this stuff
But it's just
That, I mean, right there
Oh you don't have to create the island
Which is kind of a major part of Pilotwings
So you have to model the planes
And weather vehicles and stuff
And then you have to place your markers around
Stuff like that and code the rest of the game
It didn't seem to me that that would have been
A lot of work
You know what I mean?
Sorry I'm just checking out some gameplay video of Pilotwings
And remembering how freaking awesome this game was on Super Nintendo
When it first came out, like seriously
And now that I look at it I'm like
Gosh, the basics for this
I mean it's really just a very
Simple graphic of the island
With the mode 7 trick
But it just
I remember this game was the shit when it came out
Yeah and you know what
I bet you anything that they're going to re-release this
On the virtual console for that
And I will bet you anything they will code
A new emulator for it that everything that has
Goddamn mode 7 is going to be in 3D
And all the parallax
Stuff that was in there, you know, different layers
Sprite layers and stuff like that
Will be offset in certain distances
That's what's going to happen
Well they said it was going to be as simple as anything that had a Z-axis
Would be, you know, able to be
Made in 3D
Kind of neat
In the chat room, the ever present fourth guest
On our show chat.orangeloungeradio.com
Big thanks to those of you guys
That like to show up every week and I love this
Chat, these comments here
BlackWolf, our old pal that does the show before us here at All Games Radio
The Bobby BlackWolf show
He starts at 5 o'clock Pacific when we start at 6
And yes, I'm leaving the pilot wings
Gameplay going because I'm just, I'm being nostalgic
BlackWolf says, fact, Dead Island
Also takes place on Wuhu Island
If only
And GameGuru says
Wuhu Island as a fighter for
Super Smash Brothers 4
There you go
Anyhow
It'll be a stage
Alright, so what else did you bring to the show with you?
You brought a Playstation 3, right?
I brought a MotorStorm
Apocalypse
And it's all sorts of awesome
It's basically
You're racing through the city that's
Been destroyed by an earthquake
Among other natural disasters
And so now you're
Basically racing through that
And then at the same time they've got
A little bit of a storyline going on where there's this
Corporation that basically
Wants you and these crazy
Homeless people out of the city and the crazy
Homeless people are throwing molotovs at you during the
Races
So while you're racing in some of the later
Stages after they've established this
They're shooting at you with guns
So you have to dodge guns
You have to dodge molotovs
You have to dodge falling everything
Like there's just
All sorts of crazy stuff
All of a sudden there's a track where I was racing on a bridge
And this air raid
Siren goes off and all of a sudden
The bridge starts shaking and starts collapsing
Right as I'm racing through it
And that was all sorts of
Cool and then
There's another stage where I was racing on a motorcycle
Then all of a sudden this building just collapses
Right next to me
It was awesome
It was an incredibly good time
Seriously, probably my favorite one out of the series
So why did you bring the PS3 with you?
You want to show it off a little later during the show or something?
Because I'm gonna play it
Instead of paying attention to the show
Oh I'm paying attention to the show, I'm multitasking
When the calls start coming in
It's just like, I'll let Rob talk to the callers
And I'll sit here and play Motorstar
I can't help it if they're not interesting
Well didn't you think, I thought some of those comments
Was very interesting before we had a Dead Island
Taking place on Wuhu Island
As a fighter for Super Smash Bros. 4
And I was kind of thinking like
You know, there could be a trailer that's out there
And it's like
Pilot wings meets zombies
On Wuhu Island
And it's very awesome
Just like that trailer
Which by the way I hated that trailer
I just want to throw that out there
I don't think I ever talked about it on the show but I hated that trailer
I really hated that Dead Island trailer
I thought it was artsy and everything
But like, I just
I really didn't like it
I guess I can get into the reasons why later
Remind me later, I'll talk about it
But for now we always like to start off our show
With how was your gaming week
So Dark Sakura, how was your gaming week?
It was eventful, I just played
Some Ridge Racer on the
3DS
And my eyes hurt
I played
Pinball FX, which I talked about earlier
And uh
I played a lot of Pinball FX
Actually, just sitting there all night and I updated
My avatar
And I played that
Game with the big
Stupid dragon
You know, where you click the button and they run
And you press, you know, the buttons
And they do stuff
And the chicks have horns, that type of thing
World of Warcraft
Oh okay, I was like, what?
And I like the discussion that we all
Got into yesterday
About what the Dark Stalkers characters would be
If they were characters in World of Warcraft
So we were trying to
Figure out if you wanted to make like
Victor, would he be a drawn eye
Or whatever, so it was kind of funny
That's it, I'm gonna go get some dinner now
Awesome, enjoy the noms
Uh, well, Loki
I know we've heard a little bit about 3DS
And MotorStorm, but anything else in your gaming week you wanna talk about?
Um, yeah, sure
Um, other than
MotorStorm and
Well, let's see, MotorStorm
You know, I already talked about how awesome it was
Uh, the 3DS played
Ridge Racer, and that's Ridge Racer
I mean, it's, they didn't really change anything
Too much
Um, played some of the
Um, games that are
Kind of packed in with the 3DS, like the
Um, what is that
Face Invaders game, which is kind of funny
I took, I took basically
What was the equivalent of the
Drunken Mario Kart picture
With, uh, the camera
So that was fun, I was shooting my face
And then, um, I actually tried some of the
Cards, and you can, there's one
Where you're shooting targets with a
Arrow, so that was kind of cool
And then, um, other stuff
I actually downloaded, um
On the IOS re-rave
So I was playing a little bit of that
And that's pretty cool, I dug it
I was pissed off for a while though, and I still
Kind of am a little bit pissed off about it
Pretty high scores, I'm like, why aren't they
Appearing on the high score table
Didn't realize I had to register for, like, a login
Or something like that for their thing
So after I did that, it reset all my high scores
Thanks
Wah, wah, wah, that's what you get for not
Signing up for the first place
Well, they didn't make it, they didn't say, in order to have
Your scores posted to the site, you need to register
It just says log in and register
How else is it going to know who you are?
Well, I thought I would just take my name
I'm sorry, did I throw logic into this equation?
Yeah, exactly
I'm sorry, Loki, I'll never do that again
So I played that
I dug some of the songs in there, of course
A lot of Kyle Worden music in there
So if you're a fan of In the Groove, you'll probably
Dig that
What else did I play?
Grand Theft Auto
Pretty much
Yeah, that was pretty much it
And there were some random IOS games
I played
Just going through some of my games
I downloaded to see, well, hey
I haven't played this yet, let me try this out
And see if it's any good or not
A lot of them weren't, so I just ended up deleting them
There was one I played
I think it was called Hyper Missile or something like that
That was pretty cool
Yeah, but mainly
Mainly Motorstorm, I've been playing a lot of that
Actually
I'm really hyped about that game
Awesome
Alright
Anything else or is that it?
That's it
Alright, I'll talk about my gaming week
Mostly a lot of the same stuff I've played in the past
So not a whole lot of new stuff
The usual wow
Torchlight a little bit on XBLA
Even though playing Torchlight
On Xbox Live makes me want to go back
And play it on the PC more
You can go chew on that one for a little bit
And some of the other stuff
But I did check out a few new things
One of them that Loki already mentioned
Because obviously as a music game fan
There's definitely the roots there
It's kind of a mix between
Elite Beat Agents meets
DJ Max Technica meets
In the Groove
And I wasn't sure if I was going to dig it at first
Because
Obviously this show has been on a long time
And way back in the day
We used to be exclusively about music games
And we would talk for three hours about
The DDR scene and a lot of what was going on
And at the time
One of the things that was going on in the DDR scene
Was the game In the Groove that came out
And it's no secret
I was never really a huge fan of the In the Groove games
It's funny because
In retrospect
I think I appreciate what they were trying
To do a lot more now
Than what I did then
Because especially coming so far
Now and seeing everything that's happened
Where I don't think Konami ever truly had faith
In that series
I can appreciate what they were trying to do
In retrospect, but just at the time
It really felt cheap to me
And I was really longing for more
DDR. Anyway, sorry for the
Tangent, but just to give you the mindset
I was coming in here. I was coming in here thinking
I don't know if I'm going to really dig this because I was not
Really ever a big fan of In the Groove
But I gotta say, I enjoyed
ReRave. It's cool
It's $2 to download
Not a whole lot of songs come
With it for free
I right away downloaded a song pack
That was free
So I couldn't tell you exactly how many songs you get initially
It must only be like 2 or 3
It was 3
There was a song pack of about another 4 or 5 songs you get for free
And then of course
It wants to charge you more money
To get extra song packs
Song pack 1, song pack 2
With a bunch of songs that are very similar
To what you hear in the default packs
Not a lot of name recognition in those packs
You're not exactly going to get Lady Gaga
Rihanna type of stuff
There's one of them, I actually bought all the packs
Did you?
I wanted some actual songs to play
And I was in a let me buy some stuff mood
But I played
Some songs, once again I don't recognize the artist
But there's one of those songs from
One of the Geico commercials was in there
Oh geez, really?
I wouldn't recognize the artist, but that makes sense
So I mean, ok, whatever, cool
And a lot of the music games on
I'm sorry, Xbox Live
IOS are set up the same way
And DDR itself
Being one of them, there's a DDR-S game
That comes with no songs and everything you have to buy
And song packs, so
This is nothing new, the model
But as far as the 7 songs that come with it or so
I've been playing most of them, and I enjoy the songs
They're pretty good, and the gameplay is
Pretty slick, actually
I like the whole turning power
Power dials or whatever
And you hit them right at the top
And very similar to Elite Beat Angels or Technica
You tap things on the screen
In time with the song
Right when the power, imagine like a power
Symbol on your computer that slowly turns
From a 6 o'clock position to a 12 o'clock position
And you're supposed to tap it
Right when it's at the 12 o'clock position
But some of them are hold
Some of them have multi-taps
Some of them you drag around the screen
You know, different little tricks that kind of go with it
And yeah, I enjoyed it
It was really fun on the harder songs
And the harder levels
Even with Game Center
And their own little system
As Loki was talking about earlier
For saving scores
So it's pretty slick what they've done
That's kind of what I walked away from the game with
Is that this is a pretty slick IOS game
So yeah, if you're a fan of music games
You definitely want to check this out
I mean, it's 2 bucks
It's not a bad deal
It's unfortunate there's no demo or anything
So that people can see what it is first
But there's videos online
So yeah, re-rave on the IOS
The other game I checked out this week
This is a demo
I don't like to review games based off the demo
But this is one very high-profile game
I've had a lot of anticipation going for
And that's Mortal Kombat
The demo's now out on PlayStation Network for everybody
You don't have to just be a plus subscriber
Regular or a plus can now get the demo on PS3
So I spent a little time with that
Just to see if it was going to be as awesome as I was hoping
I don't want to say I didn't like it
Because I did
But I felt it was lacking
And granted, it was a demo
It's supposed to be lacking
It was only bare bones
But when you get that mode
That's you know
Fighter versus fighter
That's still kind of the core part of the game
And I don't know, it just wasn't as
Action-packed as I was hoping
And as fast-paced as I remember the Mortal Kombat games being
However, I am saying that
Very open-mindedly
Because I realize again, it's a demo
I was playing it single-player
And I think Mortal Kombat really
Best shines in multiplayer modes
So I'm totally not being fair
When I'm saying that right now
But that was my honest-to-god reaction as I walked away from it
Going, gosh
I was hoping I'd have more fun with that
But the fatalities did make me laugh a lot
Like a little girl
And the trailer that showed the upcoming ones
Like there's one where you push some guy's face into a subway train
And it hits all the windows as the subway goes by
And that made me laugh
Because Mortal Kombat is kind of dopey
Because you like people getting their faces ripped off by a subway train
It was funny because Alan called me out on it
And he's like, I don't get it
You hate the Saw movies
But you giggle at this stuff
Yeah, but there's different
There's a very clear difference
There's a difference with like, okay you must torture yourself
For my amusement
And there's a difference between like
Ha ha, your face is gonna get ripped off
Ha ha
The Saw movies are trying to be real
And teach these moral lessons
Through these really sick things
That I don't like
But Mortal Kombat is basically one step above a cartoon
It's about the nether realm
It's not real
Do you want to play a game?
You forgot to feed your cat
Now I'm gonna feed you to a tiger
Those are the Saw movies to me
Exactly
She was fine, I fed her later on
Why do I have to get eaten by a tiger?
That doesn't seem fair at all
I will say what I did like
I'm not trying to
Gosh, I'm gonna bring on the hate mail
I did like about Mortal Kombat
That I was able to pick it right up
And it just felt like playing Mortal Kombat 2
In like Street Fighter 4 style graphics
And that part was pretty awesome
Like being able to select Mileena
And just remember that Tord Tord
Low kick was the little drop
Cool things like that, really easy to get back into
So that same sort of learning curve
Where you were able to kind of slip right into
Street Fighter 4
From Street Fighter 2
I think a lot of people are gonna find with this new Mortal Kombat
So I probably will still pick up the full version of the game
Even though I walked away from the demo going
I just
I don't know, there's something
But I think online play
And multiplayer play
And a lot of the other modes when the game's fleshed out
Will make up for that
But I have to be honest
I'm not gonna lie just for the sake of hype
Anyway, so check out the demo
See if you had the same reaction
I talked to a friend of mine who felt the same way I did
Very excited about the game after playing the demo
Went, I don't know
Wasn't what I remember
But anyway
There you go, those are the games I played this week
So chat.orangelandsrated.com
If you want to join us in our chat room
Tigerclaw in our chat room says
Sky, the fatality that looks the most funny
Is the one showing Liu Kang getting hit by a taxi
Oh yeah, that was
That was pretty funny too
And I like the x-ray attack stuff
I mean that stuff was funny
I hope there's more of them in the regular game
Like not just one x-ray attack for every character
Because I think some of those might get old quick
But I cracked up at some of them
They were pretty funny
So
There you go
A lot of the same old moves coming back
Johnny Cage can punch people in the balls still
So in fact he likes to do it over and over again
I think he has an issue
Anyway, let's move on
Some housekeeping for tonight
Our Twitter, you can join us on Twitter
Twitter.com.olr, all the updates for what's going on with the show
Also our Facebook
At facebook.com.orangeloungeradio
Otherwise we have no planned shows off
Or trips were taken or anything
So every Sunday night in the near future
At All Games Radio, www.allgames.com
6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern
Is where you can hear us live
So, yes ma'am
I have an arcade report
Disneyland
Oh yeah, that's right, you were gone last week because you were at Disneyland
Yes
Did you have fun?
I had a great time
Did you do the Toy Story Midway Mania?
We totally did
It's like a giant video game, I love it
Dan totally kicked my ass, but I kicked his butt at AstroBusters
The Starcade
Is actually now also
The home of Star Trader
Because they've closed down the Star Trader
And Star Tours for the revamp
I saw when they had shut down
Star Tours
But the Star Trader is also being redone
Right, well to get all the new merchandise I'm sure
So, well that and they sort of
Would have to go through there to take care of the hallway
If they need to redo the hallway
So, um
It's now kind of half the arcade
It used to be, literally
Interesting
That's my arcade report
You didn't play anything there
It's expensive
What? Oh, I know
Because Electronica doesn't go under the week
And they had said that it was gonna during spring break
And then they didn't
Is Captain EO back already?
Yes, it's the original 77mm film
With grain and everything
It's showing it's age
The cheeseball 3D
That was not great
Here's the summary of Captain EO
Is that
Michael Jackson flies through space with a bunch of Muppets
Lands on the Borg homeworld
And turns all the Borg
Into extras from Xanadu
Ruled by Angelica Houston
The end
And it's awesome
But am I not right?
No, that's a pretty good way of summarizing it
The end
I'm gonna be sad when they get rid of that finally
Because you know it's not
There's gonna come a time when they're finally gonna have to get rid of Captain EO again
For a new movie
It better not be Honey I Shrunk the Audience again
Because that movie was terrible
Let's actually get into some other video game news
No Captain EO game to talk about this week
But maybe some other video games
So we'll start off with Loki tonight
There's been a few games delayed from Japan
Not necessarily because of the whole tsunami earthquake thing
But you could probably attribute some of that to it
Starting off
Warriors Legends of Troy
On Xbox 360 and PS3
And Dead or Alive Dimensions
Both coming from Tecmo Koe
Those have been delayed
And won't make their scheduled release dates
Of March 24th and March 31st
Honestly not a big surprise
Dead or Alive Dimensions
Has been delayed a few times already
For the US
And Warriors Legends of Troy
Not even coming out on the 360 in the US
That's been delayed indefinitely
So I'm not surprised one bit
And that was prior to the whole earthquake thing
So
Take that for what it will
And then on top of all that
Of course this is a little bit too
Various reasons why they're delaying some of this stuff
Yakuza of the End
Motorstorm Apocalypse
And
Disaster Report 4
Well Disaster Report 4 has been cancelled
From Sega
Which
You know a game about wandering around in a
You know a city that has
Undergone some you know traumatic disaster
Might not be the most sensitive thing to put out
In a country
Unfortunately the game was a disaster
Honestly it probably was
Because Disaster Report games have not been very good
They were very budget
But Motorstorm Apocalypse obviously
The content based on that
I don't really understand
I mean I understand
You know the people might be
It's not like you're racing through Tokyo
Or something like that
Or racing through parts of Japan that are being destroyed
This is like it looks like San Francisco
So eh
Well you know people are being hyper sensitive
About it but I
I sort of get it because
When you put down multi millions of dollars
On these projects you have to release them
Just right you know
And right now you've got an entire
Country that probably doesn't want to be thinking about
The apocalypse you know what I mean
So for
It just I can see where
People would be concerned it's in bad taste
But nuclear boy Rob
That's a whole other thing though
You're talking about the little YouTube thing
He needs something to distract him from having to poop
And then
Well the other thing is
Not only did they announce it was going to be delayed in Japan
But Motorstorm Apocalypse also got delayed in Europe
And then later on in the US
I don't understand why
Because the game is done but
Eh whatever okay
You're delaying it
That's fine
But eh
Again if your game comes out the wrong week
It might get destroyed like Blur
I would say a lot of the big reason Blur
Didn't do well is it came out the wrong week
But it was coming out the perfect time
I mean granted it's coming out around the same time
As another Sony game So Com 4
But I don't really think those would compete
With each other too much
It was coming out in the month where there was essentially nothing
This time it's not the other releases
Yeah but I mean I can understand delaying it
In Japan but people in the US
You know they're not going to be like
Oh well that's just insensitive
It's not Japan for one
It's just completely
You know it looks like San Francisco
In fact I would probably
Be willing to bet it's based off
San Francisco because San Francisco
Kind of known for earthquakes so
You know that's not a stretch
And you know the
Actually I'm going
To say it is goddamn San Francisco
Because you know having played some of the
Tracks and stuff it looks like San Francisco
There is a Sony office right outside San Francisco
So it wouldn't surprise me at all
You know so I mean
I don't understand delaying it there
Or in Europe
But okay whatever you know
They want to wait and release it in May
Or something where it's packed full of
Releases and fine
I really think that they should just
Keep it with the April 12th release date
It was perfect there was nothing else coming out
It was just
You know
Well are we talking maybe it'll just be a couple weeks
Maybe, maybe a couple weeks
But really a couple weeks
That's going to put it out in a lot of
You know because let me put it this way
You've got MX vs ATV Alive coming out in about a month
After it was originally coming out
So if you wait a little bit longer
You're going to have another off-road racing game
Granted both of them are completely different from each other
But they're still both
Kind of in the same genre
I just think it's kind of a mistake to move it
It should have really come out at that time
Because it would have been perfect
There's nothing else coming out
Um
It's awesome so seriously pick it up
When it does come out
Because it's all sorts of awesome
I'm going into the chat room
At chat.orangetonstrader.com
Bobby Blackwolf in our chat says
Actually yes people in the US find things insensitive
They bash the event
Because it did an episode this week
About a nuclear power plant being threatened
And everyone was like how dare NBC air this
Oh god
You know what they need to just stop
Listening to those people
Because I mean
I'm going to boycott your show
I'm not going to watch it next week
But I'll catch it on DVR
Well there's been a lot of
I mean I'm just playing the devil's advocate here
I also think people are maybe blowing this out of proportion
People are dumb
On the west coast and you know this as well as I do
There's been a lot of talk
Like the news is dominated with this talk about
Could the radiation from the power plant in Japan
Get to the west coast
I need to get my tin foil hat
Because they're going to spin it any way they can
To make it sound like it's terrible
Just like you know they were saying oh my god
The plant's going to melt down
It's a matter of minutes you know
Oh actually no
Everything's back to normal again
Oh but it's going to kill us all
Nuclear rain
You know fallout
Scary
Vote Republican or this will happen
I mean seriously they just blow it way out
Because what else are they going to talk about
Charlie Sheen I mean seriously
They've got to talk about something
Get you to watch the news
Look I
We've got to be careful how we tread here
Because I think to some extent it is a very
Frightful thing
If this was all going on
Like I know they shut it down years ago
No don't get me wrong
It is a frightening thing
But what's going on
There and what the reporting is going on
There is completely different
I am honestly going to say
It's a lot like nuclear boy
I'm sorry those who haven't seen it
The worst that's going to happen is they're going to have
To evacuate Fukushima
And then
Fish are going to be
Sick you can't go fishing near there
Plants are going to be radiated
You're going to have to deal with this for probably the next
7 to 10 years
I think is what it takes for
Nuclear radiation to be cleaned out of
Land and our technology is a lot better
Than it was you know around say
Chernobyl
Think about that
Right now they're in a position
To do that and keep in mind this was
A place that was designed
To go against a 7.5
Earthquake
Which was to date
The biggest I think that Japan had seen
So
Something like this coming up and having
Everything still pretty much
Hold intact with just a few problems
That has to say something
Pretty amazing for you know
The level of
Of care and
You know thought that went into the construction
Of these places
You know and also should make everybody
In Sacramento shut up about us having
Nuclear power here
Because we don't have earthquakes
Shut up
Well I got the perfect location for a nuclear power plant
Where the old one was?
No
Where the kings normally play because they suck
So you know what
Well they're leaving anyway
And hey we can still hold count
Aren't we a video game show I think we got a little off track
Well but
I think that my point is made that everyone should watch
Nuclear Boy because it's great
You know all we have to worry about
Is just mutated dolphins
Rising up you know to enslave humanity
That's really what it comes down to
Now you're making light of a terrible situation
Knock it off alright
It's not terrible that those dolphins
Are so smart it's terrible that they're using it for
Evil ok? Let's talk about something
That's definitely
Fiction let's get away from the real world stuff and get to
A land of fiction and one of our favorite fictional places
Silent Hill
Of course Silent Hill is
At least a one time awesome video game series
That's kind of slipped into a
Ok yeah I really like
This series because I used to like it
Silent Hill we're experimenting with
New weather patterns now
So anyhow here's the deal
Apparently Silent Hill is going to have a release
On Xbox Live if rumors are to be
Believed and here's where the rumors are coming from
It's an interview with the Italian based
Xbox 360 magazine and it's from
The art director for Silent Hill
Downpour saying quote
At the moment there will be no
Multiplayer modes in Silent Hill Downpour
Konami is investigating
A separate chapter devoted entirely
To the multiplayer now
He went on in this interview to say that he doesn't
Know any details but it's supposed to be
Xbox Live Arcade and quote
That most players have to survive in the
Town of Silent Hill
Now I kind of look at this and go that's
That's silent hill cash in
Well Silent Hill was always supposed
To be a very single
Player experience like I don't see this
Turning into a shoot em up
Type of thing like I don't really see it as a
Bang bang you know kill the others
Really? It would be kind of cool
If like one person could be pyramid head
Really? And everybody else is trying to run away
You don't see it as a bonus points for you know
Manic and rape You don't see it as a bang bang
Shoot em up game but yet Konami does
Because they released an iOS game that was
Basically that and they released an arcade game
That's basically that so they
Apparently do see it as a shoot em up Well but
Not like shoot other people you're shooting
The creatures of Silent Hill or whatever I don't see
Where the multiplayer element comes on that's my point
But then there's a part of me that also pictures
Like a very Left 4 Dead kind of game
That actually could be kind of awesome
Like and maybe it's like don't take
Left 4 Dead literally but maybe some type of
Like cooperative survival
Game where maybe everybody
Helps each other in a certain way
To survive the town of Silent
Hill that might be kind of cool
I don't know That would be neat
And I think like a Left 4 Dead style game
Would be in demand like right now because Left 4 Dead
Was very popular there was the original
There was a sequel we haven't heard anything about a third
So maybe
Silent Hill could kind of release a game like that
I don't know that's I mean when you talk multiplayer
Silent Hill like I just I really hope
It isn't blue pyramid head versus red pyramid
Head that would be ridiculous and dumb
So it's It's like spy versus spy with
Pyramid head Yes that would be hideous
So either it's got to be like a
Co-op survival or it's got to
Be one versus
Everybody which now the
More I kind of say that out loud I think that's kind of dumb
Too so I really hope it's more like the
Co-op survival that could be kind of rad actually
Can you imagine like having to figure out puzzles
With multiple people that'd be kind of fun Nothing
Would get done I can think of something like
Oh crap Pyramid head's coming
Push someone in
His path Exactly
Sacrifice dark Sakura
Hey be like bitch
Please smack
Alright
Anyhow yeah we'll see what develops
With that I would imagine if this
Is true if big if remember this
Is a rumor because it's coming from an
Italian magazine from the art director
Like I'm not saying that
You know that small time stuff but you know
Again it is it does
Say it sound a little bit like I have this cousin
Who's a camera man on you know the new
Superman movie and he told me that Art directors
Are pretty big Yeah I know
But still Dude it has
Art director in the title Alright anyhow
Hey just take it with a grain of salt
That's all I'm saying don't be disappointed if this game doesn't happen
I would love to be an art director of a magazine
Or if it isn't good
I would love to be an art director Anyway
Well maybe you should when this guy gets
Fired for leaking all the details about the game
You should apply for his job
I don't want to move to Italy
Alright moving on dark Sakura
What do you have for us Well
Apparently the
Zynga people
They Zynga sucks
I'm sorry
His name is Brian Reynolds
And he said that Xbox Live
Is too small for them
To bother with
For Farmville
That means my mother won't be getting an Xbox anytime soon
They're basically saying
It's too small of a demographic
He says that most of his friends have
Smartphones and computers
But not too many of them have an Xbox 360
That's because your friends suck
He's an idiot
I actually
Kinda get what he said
There are way more people on
Facebook than there are on Xbox Live
Fact But let's look at
Hard cold numbers okay first of all
There are 23 million members
On Xbox Live as of February
In January Facebook had
600 million users
And Farmville had 62 million
Active since September of last year
So basically
What he's saying is he doesn't like money
I don't see how it would be
That difficult
I mean really
But he's like no it's not gonna be worth
Our time for just these people
Okay if you don't want more addicts fine
Exactly he's basically saying
Well why would we put it on
Xbox Live or
The Playstation network or something like that
They have less people than they have on Facebook
Duh! It's called expanding your demographic
You already have it on Facebook
You already have it on smartphones
That's why you would put it on a console because you don't
Have it there yet
Here's what he said
Basically the worry
Is the social experience
Basically the social experience is going to be
A very small number so that the amount of
Social capital that is there will not be very
High so basically you're not gonna have
People doing the microtransactions
Yeah and I think that
Is more what this boils down to
I think you know
It's a little bit comparing the
Apples to oranges and what's going on with these
Comparisons yes there are zillions more
People on Facebook than Xbox Live
But you have to remember that the Zynga games thrive
On this very specific business model
Where they are free to play with the
Purchasable enhancements that's not the way
That Xbox works
To some level yes you can enhance
Certain Xbox Live arcade games with
Extra things but you're always putting some money
Down up front to play the games
I would question sure you might have hundreds of
Millions of people playing FarmVille on Facebook
But how many of them are actually paying for it
You know and it's probably
A pretty damn scary number
When you know a lot of us kind of sit here and
Don't understand FarmVille
But again I think the types
Of games that you have come to
Know on Facebook and mobile phones are not
Necessarily the same types of games that are
On Xbox Live Arcade
It's just kind of like
I don't know by the way you know
The percentage is using those
I'm just going to use those numbers as a basis
The percentage of people on Facebook
That play FarmVille
4%
Tiny
Tiny tiny
So I mean if I
Were this guy I'd be looking to find ways
To get more revenue in
I'd be adjusting the business model do like
XBLA version of FarmVille
Or my thought why does it
Have to be FarmVille or something based
Off of it. If your games are so damn addicting
Rise to the challenge
And create a game that you could get away
With charging $15 for
You know there are
I can't believe I'm about to say this
But there are some things you can appreciate about FarmVille
And
Like it keeps my mother from preaching at me
That's like saying there are some things you can appreciate about Hitler
No
I am not going to go there period
Other than
Volkswagen and the Autobahn
Alright look
My thing is that like
The thing about
Now I'm totally lost
I feel sick
I feel a little sick now
The thing about FarmVille is that
It kind of gets your friends
Even though it might not be us
The people that are the quote unquote
Hardcore gamers
It gets our moms
And our relatives and people
To be playing a
Multiplayer game together
Very easily
And maybe there's a way they could bring
That multiplayer effort
To the Xbox Live place
Which in turn could maybe enhance
Xbox Live but I don't think that necessarily
Has to be just fucking FarmVille
No. There's plenty of other games they could rip
Off
Right? I'm just still
Kind of feeling ill from
Orange Lounge
Making people throw up in their mouths
Daily
Making my stomach flip flop and I just ate
I feel ill
Going to chat.orangeloungeradio.com
Spazinator told me to bite my tongue
Black Wolf says that would require that they actually
Make something original
Defective Candy says
Every time we sell one of those Facebook game cards
Where I work I die a little on the inside
Alright
You're just feeding the beast
Let's move on
Loki
Take us to some completely different news please
This is completely different
They're actually working on a
Transformers MMO
And it's being developed by the people behind
The browser based
MMO RuneScape
And I guess they've worked out a deal with Hasbro
And the game is set to be released in
North America, Europe, Latin America, Australia
And New Zealand sometime in 2012
And they said that
The title will be a dynamic
And action packed game
No word on which
Transformers universe
It will be based on
But that is interesting
Let's hope it's not the Michael Bay
Transformers universe although you know that would be
Action packed
Apparently Asia is
Also getting its own Transformers
MMO from
Net Dragon
And that's slated to roll out
I guess later this year
That's interesting
Be popular
People like Transformers
I don't know the MMO space is a little bit crowded right now
I don't know if it will be able to kind of
Get its way in there
If it was free to play that would be pretty cool
Hopefully they don't have the expectation bar very high
That's all I'm saying
The MMO space is a very tough nut
To crack right now
And if it's not free to play
It has to triple be that much better
And judging from the
Transformer games that have been on the consoles
The last one was alright
And the next one is supposed to be okay
Because it's from the same people as the last one
So hopefully
I'll try to keep an open mind
But I mean
We all know that third movie is going to be terrible
I realize they're all
Now admitting like wow the second movie
Was really bad but you know the third movie
Is going to be even worse
That last move
If I'm wrong then I'm wrong hooray
But I'm just not getting my hopes up
That's all
Hey let's talk about music games
Ubisoft is going to be putting out a new game
It's called Rocksmith
It's a rhythm game that uses real guitars
Wait a minute
That worked before
Isn't that a train that left the station quite some time ago
Alrighty well whatever
It's called Rocksmith is the game
Some of the artists that will be in the game
David Bowie, Interpol, The Rolling Stones
Pretty solid song list
Right there so far
You can use any electric guitar
That you might just happen to have
So we're not talking about buying a cheap
Plastic peripheral it's using
An existing electric guitar
So that's neat I guess
Not sure exactly how this all works
Just yet as to how it's going to identify
From any guitar but I would imagine
Some type of audio
Pitch sensing peripheral kind of similar
To how it detects when you're singing
What pitch you're singing at
It would probably plug into it like you'd plug it in
Like you'd plug it into an amp
So there is a trailer out there right now
It's supposed to be coming out the second half of the year
So I imagine that we'll be hearing
More about this at E3
Okay how are we going to use less
I was going to try and play it
Yeah but I wanted to play the trailer but a stupid commercial
For those goddamn bears
That talk about toilet paper
We had actually talked about this before
It was actually a game in development called Guitar Rising
Oh yeah
But that never really came out
And then Ubisoft bought it
Yeah it shows a guitar plugged into
The Xbox
There's got to be some little adapter
Thingy or something
It looks like an amp plugged to USB
Yeah it's similar to what you use with the
Um
Karaoke mics
I'm sure it's got to be something just like that
So
I was trying to
Look at the commercial here
Yeah somebody plugged it in there
A little electric guitar
Again it doesn't really show me anything about the game
It's just hey dude is tuning his guitar
Getting ready to jam
Man there's so many terrible commercials for games out there
Nice guitar
Alright let's move on Dark Soccer
Well it's been 22 years in the making
Da da da
There will be a sequel to River City Ransom
Yay
Or as it was known in Europe, Street Gangs
Or I really like the Japanese name
Hot Blooded Downtown Story
Nice
It's so hot
The Japanese developer Miracle Kids
Is trying to
Actually got a bunch of the original development team
Back together
And they are going to be doing a console version
In the summer with a PC release
In 2012
So the console version is this summer
The PC one will be out next year
And
They're also
Got
Downtown Smash
Dodgeball
Which for us was Super Dodgeball
Which is on Xbox Live
Indie games
So
Yay
If you still want to play the old school one
Get it on Virtual Consoles
500 points
And to this day my favorite version is still the PC Engine one
This is news I want to be excited about
But I'm just really worried
A lot of time has gone by
And this can either be a retro
Revival that's done very awesomely
Or very terribly
I always worry it's going to end up in the
Second one there
I think the man who rearmed
Did the whole 8-bit retro thing extremely well
But I don't know
The second one apparently wasn't that great
A lot of the stuff that's retro too
Is sometimes better left in the past
That's all I'm saying
We'll see as soon as we start to see
Some screenshots and some actual gameplay
But I guess it's kind of cool that that's coming back
I mean that was a game I really liked
Hopefully it kind of comes back as an arcade title
I don't know if I'd want to pay $60
For a new River City Ransom game
But I don't suspect it's going to be
Something for Xbox Live Arcade
Remember when they re-did
Final Fight
Did they?
Yeah it was
Final Fight for
It was for the Xbox and Playstation 2
Oh it was awful
I do not have that
Oh yeah I do remember that
That was terrible
The last great one was Final Fight Guy
Actually Final Fight CD
That was a good version
What was Final Fight CD on?
Is that Sega?
Guess who has it?
Well I'm sure you guys do somewhere in that vault
Crazy stuff
Alright let's move on with some release dates
We're going to travel around the world and check out what's coming out soon
For your favorite console, Loki
Lots of stuff this week
Some re-releases and stuff
Raven Rabbids Party Collection
It's a collection of Raven Rabbids
1 and 2 and TV Party
Mayhem 3D on Playstation 3
And on Xbox 360
It's a demolition derby type game
TrackMania Build to Race
on the Wii
Awesome racing games
Check it out
Tomb Raider Trilogy
Re-release or HD versions
Of the last three
Tomb Raider games
And of course the last one was really on PS3
So it's a re-release event
Crysis 2 on PC
PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360 this week
Chikandia
The Timeless Land
This is a sequel
I guess spiritual successor to
32nd Hero
That's on PSP
PlayStation Move Heroes
Coming out on PS3
Disidea
Duidisium
Or Duidisium
I went for that the first time
That is a game
That is coming out on PSP this week
So if you want a little bit of a
Sequel to the
Disidea
Naruto Shippuden Kizuna Drive
That's on PSP
And of course
This is going to be a huge week
Because it also happens to be the week
One week from today to be exact
When the 3DS launches
So we have lots of 3DS games
Ridge Racer 3D
Tom Clancy's Ghost Recon Shadow
I believe it's Shadow Wars
That's on the 3DS as well
Asphalt 3D
Lego Star Wars 3
The Clone Wars
That's on pretty much everything
PlayStation 3, Xbox 360
Wii, DS, 3DS
PC and PSP
Combat of the Giants
Dinosaurs
That's on the 3DS
Rayman 3D
That's of course on the 3DS
Umm
Let's see what else we've got here
Pro Evolution Soccer 2011
On 3DS
Nintendo Plus Cats
Golden Retriever
Toy Poodle
French Bulldog
Pilot Wings Resort
Steel Diver
Samurai Warriors Chronicles
The Sims 3
Super Monkey Ball 3D
And umm
Bust A Move Universe
Super Street Fighter 4
3D
And Madden NFL Football
All on the 3DS this week
And of course
One week from today
Frisbee in our chat room is going
Name of game 3D
Name of game 3DS
That's what they're all called
Pretty much right?
Alright
Let's move on to
Japan and look at the Japanese release
Dates coming out this week on the Xbox
360 on March 24th
Arkania Gothic 4
Crysis 2
A game called Escatos is coming out this week
This is like an old school shooter
Type game that's been revamped basically
Or I should say it's inspired by old school shooters
And it's like you know
In like 3D
It's basically another shmup
But it looks like it has some more retro based modes
So if you're into like old school shooters
I think they're going for you with this game
Fighters Uncaged also this week as well as
Otomedius Excellent comes out this week
So lots and lots of
Shooting fun games this week
Going over to the Playstation 3
And looking at what's coming out over there
We have Crysis 2 there as well
Gachinko Heroes
Pro Yaku Spirits
2011 comes out this week as well
From Konami
It's baseball
And moving on to the
Nintendo Wii
Ikine no Yoru
Rune Factory Frontier
Gets a price reduction so does Tales of Graces
And that's really it for the Nintendo Wii this week
On the Nintendo 3DS
In Japan this week
Of course it's time for a Gundam game on 3DS
Gundam the 3D Battle comes out this week
As well as Rabbids Time Travel
And The Sims 3
All make their way out in 3D
On the Japanese 3DS this week
And lastly going over to the
PSP to look at the releases there
Huge week
I almost want to import this
But I know I won't be able to read it
Final Fantasy IV The Complete Collection makes its way out on the Sony PSP
Just give it another month
I'm so excited for this
I dust off the PSP, get my charger, get ready to go
So excited for this
Also an interesting game called Are You Alice?
Comes out this week on the Sony PSP
It's set based in the
Was it the
Brady Bunch universe?
No it is not based in the Brady Bunch universe
Actually it looks very much like a
I don't know how to explain this
Like a very like old time
Think of like that Castlevania
Sort of flair
I mean it's not like vampires
But definitely the costumes kind of remind me of that
Sort of story
It's an adventure game
On the PSP
I don't know if that's something
That's coming out over here
I don't think so
I don't know if it's based on the anime or what the deal is
Are You Alice?
At least it wasn't Are You Jimmy Ray
Because I hated that song
Remember the 90s?
Alright how about the UK?
Dark Sakura
Well in the UK we have
A crap ton of stuff
Starting on the
22nd we have Swarm
On the 23rd Battle of Los Angeles
And IL-2's
Sturmovik Cliffs of Dover
That's very British
On the 25th we have Combat of Giants
Dinosaurs 3D, Crysis 2
Dead or Alive Dimensions
Dissidia, Duodecium
Final Fantasy
Dynasty Warriors 7, Hello Kitty Seasons, Lego Star Wars 3
The Clone Wars
Nintendo 3DS of course
Pro Evolution Soccer, Street Fighter 4 3DS
Where's the rest of the list?
Super Street Fighter 4 3D
Super Street Fighter 4 3D Edition
The Sims Medieval
Splinter Cell Chaos Theory
Asphalt GT 3DS
I already said Lego Star Wars 3
Nintendo X Plus Cats, Pilotwings Resort
Rayman 3D, Ridge Racer 3DS
Samurai Warriors Chronicles
Super Monkey Ball 3D
The Sims 3DS, Tom Clancy's Ghost Recon
Islands of Wakfu
That's later
That's on the 30th, nevermind
K done
So excited to be finished with those release dates
Alright just a couple more stories for you guys
Then we got the classic game of the week
A trip down memory lane
With a classic video game coming up in just a little bit
But first, two more stories for you guys
Yeah we got some news about the NGP
Or what's codenamed the NGP
From Sony
They're saying that the
games will be downloadable day and date with the
retail releases
So you'll be able to either buy
the cartridge that these are going to be on
or download them from the Playstation Network store
All of them? Or just the Sony ones?
Well they're saying all of them
But here's kind of an
interesting thing though if you think about it
That sounds
good in theory
Until you realize one thing
There's no onboard storage on the NGP
So
Where the hell am I supposed to put these games that
you're having me download? Oh I have to buy your
proprietary memory unit
Oh how wonderful
I have to buy a fucking memory card
to do that. How about this? I'll just buy the
retail game. Man that
sounds good. Because you know what I could do with that
retail game? When I don't want to play it anymore
I can sell it back
Because I'm sure you're not going to have any sort of
price break or anything like that on there
So
Unless they come out
cheaper because I'm not buying
all the packaged goods that go along
with the game
I'm not interested, sorry
And then on top of that
there's a rumor regarding the price of the system
Apparently
Sony Europe put out
a survey. I guess this is
tying in with Ubisoft
It was
Some survey
conducted by a
research firm and sponsored by
Ubisoft. They're saying that
the retail price of the Sony NGP is expected
to be around $350
How likely
would you be
How likely would you be
to purchase the NGP now that
you know the retail price?
They're saying that's the premium model with 3G
The next question is
How about the one without 3G
which will be considerably lower at
$250?
That's fucking expensive
both ways and I know that the reason
that they're saying, oh well $350
we're competing with the iPad and those
tablet devices but
because you're a handheld
gaming console
I know you may want to think that you're a computer
or think that you're a tablet or something like that
but the truth of the matter is
you're not, you're a game console
so your price is too damn high
$250 should be the topic
I don't even think that these
prices that we're hearing about mean anything
I don't think Sony knows what they're charging for this thing yet
I really don't
I mean, a week before
E3 I believe this rumor right now
doesn't mean squat
We'll see
I wouldn't be surprised
if they go and try to charge $350
but here's the thing, it'll be $350
retail but
because these are gonna have
3G, they're gonna be tied with some sort of
data plan and get it for a lot cheaper
than that because you're gonna be signing a contract
or to your contract or something like that
so that's where it's gonna make
sense for people to pick up the 3G
Not necessarily though, you don't have to sign a contract for
an iPad
an iPhone, yes, but an iPad, no
you don't sign a contract for those
Well then how do you get the 3G?
You buy it with the 3G enabled and then you buy a separate data plan
but they don't subsidize the cost of those machines
at all
because I believe the data can be through
either, and correct me if I'm wrong chatters
but I'm pretty sure it's either to AT&T
or Verizon
and now we have this big huge news today
that AT&T has gobbled up T-Mobile
or at least will be over the next 12 months
assuming the government approves of the acquisition
or what have you, so that's just gonna be
even more, you know, that's one
less carrier out of the sea
It'll be interesting to see what happens
A lot of people on my Twitter
are not happy about that acquisition by the way
Apparently a lot more T-Mobile customers than I realized out there
who don't want to switch
Well they have some pretty good budget plans
That's okay, I'm already with AT&T
I know, I've never had a problem with AT&T, but some people really hate them
But then again, I don't live in a huge city
It seems like everybody I know that hates AT&T
lives in a huge city
I have better luck with AT&T here than anything else
and I have no trouble
when I travel, so
Well, we'll see
Alright, anyhow
More stuff, and this is on a completely different
kind of note, you know, obviously last week
we spent a little time talking about how
you guys can help, what's going on
in Japan and the really unfortunate
tragedy that's happened over there and
a lot of the gaming world now coming on board
to do some really cool things for the
disaster relief over in Japan
I don't even have time to name it all
but here's some of the ones that caught my eye
Squeenix
is just flat out donating money
There's no buy this game for whatever
cost or donate through the
Nope, they are just straight out giving
100 million yen to the relief
effort, they are also collecting
donations from employees throughout the world
and they are also going to be getting donations
through select Squeenix
online services and the amusement
facilities that Taito operates in
Japan, so very cool what
Square Enix, or as we always call them on the show
Squeenix is doing
This weekend, PopCap is donating
the sales of their IOS games
that means iPhone and iPad games
to the Red Cross, so they
donate 100% of the sales of
the games this weekend
March 19th and 20th, so those listening
live, today is the last day to do it, those that are
listening on the podcast, you missed it
but all the money will be donated to the Red Cross
and they
are saying in a statement that they
recently opened an office in Tokyo
and while the Japan based employees are safe
and uninjured, we understand countless
others in Japan need food, shelter
and medical attention, given that Plants vs.
Zombies reached number one on the iPhone and iPad
sales charts in Japan, it seemed like
the most appropriate game to feature in the
fundraising campaign, so if you don't already
own the game, now is the perfect
excuse to get it, so very cool
Also
just a lot of other things
games purchased on Direct2
Drive, the company will donate a dollar
each game to Disaster Relief
Bungie is currently selling
a little band, the little
armbands that kind of remind me of the
Livestrong, I'm sure everybody has seen those, these blue
ones, Japan Quake Relief
2011, those proceeds go
directly to the Red Cross
Also, I don't know if you guys saw this, if you
logged into the Playstation at all
there is a link right in the
Playstation store that I think also
comes up in the What's New, you can just
donate money right from your
Playstation, very similar to what they got
going on in iTunes right now, so you can just
donate right the funds that are in the Playstation
wallet, or just donate through the
Playstation, so if you
don't know how else to donate, that's
one way you can do it, and there you go
So
Awesome, and that's not even all of
them, there's lots of other great things going on out
there in the gaming world of people
donating money, and you know, as I said
last week, please, anybody
if you listen to this show
I really think in lieu of giving us
money, which we don't ever ask you for
really would hope you would donate what you
can to the relief efforts going on
in Japan, and even if you're like
I don't have any money, I've got zero cents
donate time
would even be helpful at this point, the Red
Cross can use help all over
during this very unfortunate
time. Alright
let's take a minute to switch gears
here and take a trip down memory lane
in a segment we do here on the show every week
called the Classic Game of the
Week, Dark Sakura's gonna step
into the vault and find a game that she just
loves more than anything
in the world, and say
kids, you better be playing this game this week
or I'm gonna beat you up
So Dark Sakura, what is the Classic Game of the Week?
I
well I apparently love a lot of games
then if that's the story
the game of the week is
Strider 2
or known as Strider Here U2
which is the
official sequel to
the first Strider game
and I'm bringing up a
YouTube right now, sorry I'm a little delayed here
but here you go
here's a little bit of the
gameplay
the music too, the music's pretty good
actually I really like the first level of the music
anyway
it really is
not a sequel to
the NES one, I'm just saying
because the NES one is actually a retelling
of the manga
the Strider 2 the manga
so this one
is basically set 2000 years
after the events of the original game
and
the Grand Master has returned to life
and so has Strider Here U
so
he's going through different levels
it's actually 2D sprites
over 3D backgrounds
but it's the same as the original
it pretty much plays the same
you've got three action buttons
he has all of his
old moves like walking, jumping, crouching
sliding, climbing walls and ceilings
and he's got a dash
now by pressing
left or right twice
and a double jump, basically you press jump
in midair and a backwards somersault done while sliding
and then he can
do a thrust jump off of a wall
if he's holding onto a wall
and he's got like
extra slash moves
and all kinds of different moves, he's got like a boost
if he's got a boost item
so he can shoot, you know
out of his plasma, out of his cypher
so it's pretty cool
and this one actually has a few
throwbacks as far as health
you know, replenishments
you can extend your life bar
you have a cypher extension, other boosts
and then you can get
different things
in the game, you can get the
Yasuchi and the Sakji symbol
from Vulgus and the Zenny coins from
Black Tiger and Forgotten Worlds, I love that game
anyway
so you've got five stages
each of them
gives you a little breakdown beforehand
we have an appearance of
Tonpuu in here, cause she was so cool
and
it was
it was pretty awesome
you've got the first three
on Earth, Hong Kong, Germany
and Antarctica
and that was Hong Kong, of course the one that
Tonpuu is in, and then the last two
are in space, you have the flying
battleship Balrog and
Third Moon, which are both
locations in the original game
the home version did come out
in 2000 on the Playstation
and I've got both
versions, I believe, the Japanese and the US
one
it actually comes with two discs
on the first disc is Strider 2
and the second disc is the original
coin-op version of Strider
so that's pretty neat
but a labeling error on the American one has
both discs labeled as Strider
so we used to have to guess
so if you finish the games and
do all the achievements on the same memory card
you get a secret level called Strider 2
Mission Zero, it's a waterfall stage
and then if you
complete all of the missions you get
Strider Hyun as
a playable character
he has two cyphers and is pretty hardcore
and awesome
and that is actually my favorite person
to play through the damn game with is
just like, I've got two of these suckers
and I'm bad
and he like, I think he can throw one like a boomerang
if I'm right
anyway, um, so yeah
really really hot, this was
I mean, the game is
really cool, it's kind of, if you
if you're, I guess a veteran of it
then it might seem like it's
a little short and a little
huh? but there was so much
coolness in it that it's just a
fun game, I mean I could sit down and
play through it in a couple hours, it's just a
fun game, so
that is my game of the week
Strider 2
alright, good time
the arcade game
also on the Playstation 1
classic video game of the week
hardcore
okay chat room, why are you
bothering with Deadpool?
there's 50 million
Deadpool titles out, ugh
Deadpool's jumped the shark
I'm sorry, he's only good at Marvel vs Capcom 3
really?
not a fan anymore, huh?
no, okay, I love the character
and I think he was fine in
Cable and Deadpool
great series, and then they ended it
but now Deadpool's in like
eight titles, seriously?
I think it's eight
and it's like, dude, too much Deadpool
too much of a funny thing
is annoying, sorry
Strider 2, awesome game, go play it
and underappreciated
highly underappreciated
alright, well we're going to take a quick break guys
we'll be back with more of Orange Launch Radio
we have some rapid fire news tonight
of course Twitter topics is your last chance to get those in
at twitter.com slash OLR
get those in right now so we can read them in a little bit
we're going to talk a little more about the censorship
of Mortal Kombat in Australia
we'll talk about some legal battles and
a possible sequel to the King of Kong movie
maybe?
yep, it might be happening
so we'll talk about that when we come back in just a little bit
with more of Orange Lounge Radio
welcome back everybody to Orange Lounge Radio
we are live on this Sunday evening
March the 20th of 2011
with the 406th episode
of our show
we're about to get into the twitter topics
but first, some rapid fire news
until we plug the side projects
that we have
or whatever you want to call them
DarkSakura, you have another little podcast you do?
yes, and if anyone listened to my rant
at the end of part A, this is a rant you'll hear
all the time on the show
do Comic Insanity
you can download the podcast
at Infamous
N-F-A-M-O-U-S dot net
and we basically, it is me
and Mar and Marvel, and you have something
hanging from your shoe, nevermind it's your shoelace
well that has happened, yes
it's just a little weird
and Dan Shadow
and we basically
talk comics, we talk about what's coming out
what's on our pool list
we have one that we read every week
and next week we are going to have
hopefully a special guest
so you'll just have to tune in and listen
but we go live every Tuesday
awesome
if you enjoy the World of Warcraft
or even if you don't, you just like to hear people talk
about it and tell dick and fart jokes along the way
you should definitely check out
The Best Little Horde House in Azeroth, it's a show that
Extfer and I do all about World of Warcraft
brand new website just launched today
www.hordehouse.com
for all the information, H-O-R-D-E
H-O-U-S-E, for all the information
and you can download it right there
alright, there you go
so let's get into some rapid fire news
quick news stories about what is going on
in the gaming world that we just don't have a lot of time for
otherwise, Loki
if you're in the UK, you'll be treated
to some little big Planet 2
download content coming in May
this is kind of a little bit different than the normal stuff
that they put out, they're actually doing
what they call a teacher pack
and it's being developed by Media Molecule
it's to be packed with demonstrations
of the national
curriculum and it's based
in game levels that other
teachers have made
and I guess this pack will also feature
Playstation Move functionality as well
which is pretty cool
you know, I didn't get to play
Little Big Planet when I was
in school, well
all we had was these kids today
Number Munchers and
DDR machines in their PE classrooms
and now Little
Big Planet teaching a history
you should grow up on Number Munchers
and Oregon Trail
like we did
and then of course
this is kind of neat
more download content coming
to DJ Hero 2
this new
I guess, pack is called the
Indie Hip Hop Mix Pack
and features the
artists, well let's see
here's some of the mixes here
My World Premiere
by Charisma and
Peanut Butter Wolf mixed with
The Red Instrumental which is by
Jlib
Party Hard by The Perceptionists featuring
Guru and Kamu Tau
mixed with
Ghost Rider
by RJD2
and then The Best Day
by Atmosphere remixed
by FSG
and those are available
probably right now actually
for
$8 or
640 Microsoft
points or $300 each
or yeah, $300
points each on
the WiiWare store
premium for those download
content packs on the WiiWare
and then of course some more music
game download content
Dance Central getting some more
tracks
not as much as I was hoping, you know, be put out by
Harmonix but I guess maybe it takes a little longer
to get some dance routines put out
Fat Boy Slim Weapon of Choice
awesome song
Gwen Stefani with Hollaback Girl
Carrie Hilston
with Turning Me On
and Paula Abdul with Straight Up
those are available for $3 per track
or 240 Microsoft points
that's a lot of
download content there
it's good to see that game is still getting supported with
download content, better support than a lot of games
I haven't gotten to play it in a long time
but I really want to go back to it
oh, that was another thing, I forgot to mention
a really late part of my game week
I played U-Star 2
what the hell's that?
U-Star is like
karaoke for movie scenes, you read
lines and it puts you
into the movie like a green screen
that sounds horrible, actually it sounds like
something I've seen at Disney's California
Adventure, where you can like
it's set up like Ursula from
the Little Mermaids
and you can reenact scenes
over where Turtle Talk with Crush is
that whole thing, yep, you can reenact scenes from
your favorite movies
it is a terrible game
the interface is just absolutely terrible
oh my god, my co-worker though
was doing lines from like
300 and stuff like that
and
THIS IS CAKETOWN
and just the way he was doing it
though, it was like
Igor from
Frankenstein or something like that
and just this really weird voice
he did the whole thing
it was hilarious, and the game has
the worst framing ever
we had the camera set up on a table
and it would zoom in or zoom
out too much
depending on the scene, so there's
one scene that you could do, it was kind of
an ad-lib thing, it was like the moon
or something, like moon surface, and all it had
was his head
his head was on the screen
it's a terrible game
it's funny, it sounds like something you'd buy
for like one night of LOLs and then it's over
I'll probably wait for it to drop in price
it is pretty funny though, for like a drunken party game
ok, there you go
some other quickfire news here
Red Faction Battlegrounds has a release date
it's going to be April 5th
and it will be out for $9.99
on the Playstation
that's also 800 Microsoft Points
but here's the thing, if you're in the Playstation Plus
thing, before March 25th
so this week
you can get the game for FREE
so this is more incentive for you to sign up
for the Playstation Plus membership, free stuff
so yeah, that's Red Faction Battlegrounds
also, I found this kind of interesting
GameStop is now selling
500GB Playstation 3s
but they don't really make
500GB Playstation 3s, so how do they do it?
well, it's a refurbished deal
they sell refurbished Playstation 3s
and they call them premium
refurbished Playstation 3s supercharged
they come with a 500GB
Western Digital Scorpio Blue
hard drive
and a bunch of peripherals and things come with it too
so here's the deal
you can buy one of these for $400
it comes with a Playstation 3 slim
with the new hard drive
a special supercharged console skin
that reminds you how awesome GameStop is
for getting this for you
a one year warranty on it
and then I guess a media hub with a remote
increasing the number of USB slots
also an HDMI cable
so
I gotta say, it's an interesting
little spin on the whole
used game stuff
there's some people that really like to shop around
for used only things to get a deal on it
and even though I don't necessarily
know if you're getting a deal with this
you are getting a lot of
extra stuff that a lot of people
kinda have to buy anyway
like the HDMI cable and so forth
I don't know guys, I have an 80GB
hard drive on my Playstation 3
and I still haven't hit the limit yet, knock on wood
but I also don't download a lot of movies
I'm not Spazinator, Spazinator calls in every week
talking about some video he's downloaded
like I don't have that many movies
I have a 500GB hard drive in mine
do you really, but you redid it yourself right?
yeah I did it myself because I had 20 in there
oh my gosh, yeah
I can see
mine's only 80, I haven't filled it up yet, knock on wood
um
yeah I guess if you're
used to paying a lot of money for
HDMI cables it's a good deal
but
it's an interesting way
to make the used Playstation 3
business kinda interesting
like it's kinda creative
to just get the hard drive and put the new ones
in there at the GameStop level
well I think also too, and I'm not sure
if GameStop have this problem, but
Sony was oh so wonderful
and decided, hey you know what
we're having shortages on the old systems
so
you place a bunch of orders for it and they don't come in forever
and then oh hey we're gonna
we're gonna send a bunch of them to you
you get them, oh by the way we're releasing
new SKU, suckas
and so you're left with a bunch of systems that
oh by the way we didn't price protect those so
they're gonna come out at the same price and you're
stuck with these old systems that nobody wants
haha suckers, so
if they did that to GameStop
which is very unlikely because they're GameStop
but let's just for all
you know sakes and purposes
say they did, and
what are they gonna do with all these old systems? Well they can buy
a bunch of hard drives for cheap, upgrade them
sell off
the old hard drives I guess if they want to
and sell them
for a premium and make money
off the system and the accessories
bundle with it
and it becomes a unique
item for them because there are no 500
gigabyte PS3s
Togak in our chat room is commenting on the size
of your hard drive saying that's a lot of porn Loki
no no no
I stream my porn, that was actually for
for rips
of games but I
my system's all legit now
I unmodified it because
I want to play MotorStorm
and
you know it's just
it was the right thing to do
whatever, once again remember we
got into it a couple weeks ago
about how there wasn't really
much I wanted to play on there, well MotorStorm was
one of the games I wanted to play but
I'm not missing much
or anything
Alright one more story I've got, we'll go over to
Jamie, this is about a Wipeout
Kinect game and you might
be kind of looking going wait a minute I thought
Wipeout was a Sony franchise, why is it coming out
on the Kinect? Because it's not that
Wipeout, no no we're talking about the
ABC reality show that
is kind of like a Japanese game
show I guess for American audiences it's
Wipeout the game show
it has a Kinect game coming out
this summer
you might remember this game was already
released on the Wii and the DS
I'm sure it was pretty terrible
now they talk about how there
are infamous big balls
and I assume they're not talking about genitalia
but these actual giant balls that people bounce
I've never watched this show it just looks
idiotic to me but I guess
a lot of people really like it but people bounce
on giant balls like it's a pinball machine
or something so this game
Wipeout will have more than 30 obstacles
you will run, duck
dodge and of course Wipeout
and they go on
this quote about everyone who watches the show
wishes they could try the obstacle course and now
this is their chance!
Is it like Takeshi's Castle?
It's sort of like Takeshi's Castle but
like really dumbed down. Kind of what I get from
looking at it yeah but I've never
and like I'm a reality TV
whore okay I watch a lot of crap
that I deservingly
deserve to be made fun of for watching
like Big Brother come on
but I don't watch Wipeout
like I'm not going to stoop that low
Well remember how they like it's basically
it took all these Japanese game shows and just
gutted the soul out of them
like that show
Hole in the Wall the one that was the funny Japanese
game show that was a segment on Ellen
and that's where it should have stayed like
it's funny for two minutes and that's it
no it was actually well it may have been a segment
but it was originally a Japanese game show
and you know
that's funny because they're just
playing it for fun they're not doing it for prizes
but you know of course us
Americans don't want to watch anything that's for
fun it's got to be for money
because who cares about fun
so they
had that and then they totally like fucked it up
they just it's like
it's just like you know American Iron Chef
you know they just
gutted all the soul of that show
out of it and then the
it's Iron Chef at least it has Alton Brown
it does have Alton Brown
and at least it wasn't as terrible as the original
American Iron Chef although William Shatner
hosting
I don't hate that I think he
would be just as over the top as Chairman Kaga
exactly he would be just as over the top
but this like fictional cousin
or something like that is retarded
now he's on a hideous
TV
sitcom on CVS
based off a Twitter account
what?
oh yeah William Shatner he's been on a show for like a year called
TJ Hooker
Shit My Dad Says
you know I've actually thought about starting
a Twitter account for Shit My
Wife Asked Me About
might be kind of long
it's just weird
there's some funny stuff like
what was it the other day she was
I'm trying to remember one of the questions because it was just like
really? that's so weird
um
oh I don't even remember now
it was so strange
it was funnier in your head wasn't it?
it was funnier in my head
no but I do say funny stuff now to her and then she
posts it on Facebook like she was asking me about
so how do you spell
how do you spell desert?
or was it dessert or something like that I'm like
well the way you remember it is
you know you want more dessert than you want desert
so you know
dessert has two S's and desert has one
so what about the desert something
I'm like and what if you need to spell
deseret because you're a Mormon
and so I'm like
listen that's the way I learned how to spell
um desert
so if you don't like it you can
shut the hell up
or you can go to hell
so she wrote that on Facebook
good times
but she asked me weird shit all the time
like all these
random questions about things
it's the job of a wife to ask her husband
really bizarre things
what are some of the bizarre things you asked Dan?
Dan!
what's the bizarre stuff I ask you?
he says he doesn't know
she keeps asking me questions about mythological creatures
and stuff she's like
you know what's this look like? I'm like I don't know
stupid thingy
it's just something
that happens
is that something that happens like when you get married
because like you know
Alan doesn't really ask me stupid shit
it's no
it's like if you've got
someone who's got a really kind of
wandering mind
every so often the weirdest questions will pop up
and when you hit that comfort level
they'll just ask you
like
and typically it tends to be
I've noticed the wife
or the girlfriend
or
I guess
and every so often
just the most random questions but because I feel
so comfortable around my husband
I'll just blurt them on out
like you know
I don't know
it just occurs to me
this whole thing was funnier in your guys'
head like it seems like a big in-joke or something
but thank god I'm not a lesbian
I wonder how it would be
amongst lesbians
if they would both annoy the crap out of each other
with annoying questions
I think it's just written into the
female chromosome
alright let's move on
speaking of the female chromosome
Dark Soccer give us a few more stories here and then we'll get to Twitter topics
okay well
here you go
Rock Band! And this should make
my very good friend happy because she
likes Billy Joel and I do not
but it's the Billy Joel
piano challenge
it has I go to extremes
Miami 2017
seeing the lights go on on Broadway
my life
which was the theme from Booze and Buddies
I used to watch that show
prelude angry young man
and scenes from Italian restaurant and she's always
a woman and there are also
for some of these pro guitar
bass expansions available for another 80
Microsoft points the entire pack will be
800 Microsoft points or 1000 Wii points
or 10 bucks
you know what
I'm good I don't really
do not like Billy Joel
I don't know Billy Joel was like kind of one of those things
that was better left in the movies
if it's a piano pack why don't they freakin put
piano man in it
okay wait I think that might already be out
maybe? okay well then fine
that piano man was in there already
yeah this might be like a second time
that's how much I like Billy Joel I didn't look
that's like the only song he does that I like
I like the song
Philadelphia even though the movie is really sad
I...
next story
okay more rock band stuff
yay
guess what song's gonna be in it
the bed and shooter song
yay cause they're climbing in your video games
playing your guitars
playing your bass
and playing your keyboards
cause they're playing everyone out there
and it's the long version
god I fucking hope they put
Friday out next
you know what
I'm gonna tell you the same thing that I told
our friend Melody
do not buy that song on iTunes
too late
I really wanted her to reach
number one cause it would be funny
I've lost all respect
well pfft
this is the reason why?
because
no talent rich kids
do not need the dollar that is
better spent on Jolly Ranchers
the end
I'm on a diet
yeah
you want a girl scout cookie?
you know what I've got some
I don't want to get it
don't blame a little girl with a dream
blame the music production company
it's the same thing I said when the music
could have been a dollar closer to getting
that music production company to make you a song
I know
this girl
I'm just jealous cause I don't have a song
she's way auto tuned and you can tell
she can't sing
she did, they interviewed her on
Good Morning America and they made her sing a few bars
of America the Beautiful
was she the best singer I've ever heard? no
but was she talented?
she's 13!
anyway why are we arguing about this?
I'm not talented and I can't sing
why is this guy famous?
would you pay this guy a dollar to play this song
on a rock band?
cause this one's funny
well Friday's funny
Friday's just sad
it's only funny with the video, with the girl with the braces
I would pay a dollar to pay
or to play
Night Man
from It's Always Sunny
alright anyhow
got a man coming in and raping
somebody? is that it or is there another one?
no there's another one
Marvel Vs. Capcom 3
Shuma Gorath
and Jill Download Content
are...
Shuma Gorath
downloadable content
is delayed
it was gonna be 400 Microsoft points
which is 5 bucks each
but now they don't really know why
it was gonna be out on March 15th
but it's been pushed back
I don't know when, but it's pushed back
which is no great loss because it's crap Jill
and not fun Jill
how does one delay something that's already on the disk?
yeah, I don't know
that's a very good question actually
I forgot where the key was
to unlock this
ah crap
the keys fell on the couch
ah down the drain
got to get a string and a magnet
I don't know why that's really funny
but I'm just imagining Capcom
putting out this press release
sorry guys we had to delay the Capcom
Marvel Vs. Capcom 3 downloads content
we're trying to find a string and a magnet right now
to find the unlock key
so please bear with us
and thank you for your patience
we appreciate our fans
love Capcom
yes we appreciate you enough
for you to
pay for our download content
I mean, pay the unlock content
Twitter Topics!
twitter.com slash o-l-r
going to a tweet coming up first
from Defective Candy
let me turn down the little song there
in the background
Defective Candy is sending us a tweet about
Augmented Reality makes the 3DS bigger than Gigantor
what is this?
this is a link from
Candinator
sending us this story here
about the 3DS had launched some time ago
and
let's see
it's about, you have to remember
I'm reading these for the first time thanks to Twitter
I guess it has to do with the AR tech
oh I see
some folks have made a super sized version
of the 3DS pack-in Augmented Reality
card all for the sake of
giving Kobe's Lonely Lifesize
Tetsujin 28 Ghost statue some company
and as you see in the video below
he does need a friend, it may well be a me
I gotta see this video, what is going on
oh I see they have this big statue that they did
oh
I see, so what they did
instead of having the guy
stand on the mat to take the picture
they got this gigantic version
of it to put the statue on
I see what they did
they took the little pack-in Augmented Reality
thing, put it under the statue
dude
and now he's
in the 3DS Augmented Reality game
haha
it's kind of funny I like that
sorry that probably made for terrible radio
but hey you tweeted it, alright moving on
to another Twitter from SilverSonic1534
sending us another
really good story about helping
the folks out in Japan for the
disaster relief, a rare
Nintendo DS it was signed by a bunch of Nintendo
veterans and it was auctioned off
this week, let's see
it was a
Mario Kart DS promo
system and it was signed by
Miyamoto, Koji Kondo
the Zelda chief, Eiji
Onomura, Charles Martinet
Martin Lung who does the piano
stuff for Video Games
Live
all of that was autographed
by all those people and they sold
it, I'm not sure exactly how much they
went for, let me look, let me see on eBay real quick
ooh it hasn't sold
yet, it's got 16 hours left
$2,500
sorry $2,550
$2,550
is what it's at right now
so if you want to check that out
more tweets coming at us
from TigerClaw
PSP based Augmented
Reality game, what is it with all the
Augmented Reality games tonight, that's popular
that's right yeah, this is
turning school into an adventure worth
writing about
an imaginary worlds project
using the system with the AR software
you design fantasy landscapes
at school by finding art online
and matching it with scannable codes that were
hidden around the school
they then took camera equipped systems around
the school and embarked on quests
finding items to defeat monsters and writing
about the experience afterwards, that actually sounds
kind of awesome, I'd like to see something like that
on an even bigger scale
I don't know, like Amazing Race
but for real
anyhow, Amazingly Real Race
Amazingly Real Race on PSP
apparently the program went over
very well, very enthusiastic response to that
the kids were well behaved
and cooperated when they took part
kind of neat, I like that idea
remember
I don't know why, but you know what this reminds you
remember when you were in grade
school and you'd go on a tour of a
historical building, you'd have to put on those
big headphones and as you walked
under certain places you would hear the
stuff in the headphones, like it was all based off radios
well imagine now
if you could use these augmented reality devices
to scan in the certain codes at places
and you would read a little bit about what it is
you know, you're at, or what the importance
of the location is, I don't know, so this reminds
me of to some extent, I can see that
kind of neat, anyhow
one other tweet here from TigerClaw
AMD has made a statement
that DirectX is holding back the graphics
performance on the PC
links us to a story from Gamasutra here
via our Twitter
a quote here from
AMD
GPU division worldwide developer
relations manager Richard Huddy
quote, it's funny, we often have at least
ten times as much horsepower as an
Xbox 360 or a Playstation 3
in a high end graphics card
yet it's very clear that the games don't
look ten times as good
to a significant extent, that's because
one way or another, for good reasons and bad
mostly good, DirectX is getting in the way
so
so mostly good, but
yeah, but I guess maybe that's because
I'm gonna bitch about something, it's mostly
for the good of the game, but
but we can't do it
isn't the Xbox 360 all based off
a version of that? I mean wasn't the original name of the
Xbox the direct Xbox?
no, that's stupid
I thought that's where this whole thing came from
no, it's basically
the Xbox 360
like the Xbox 360
is running on a modified version of
DirectX 9 that has some of the
features of DirectX 10 in it
but
it's basically DirectX 9
alright
and one more tweet here from
gamergirl saying, which do you think is better
Torchlight PC version or Torchlight
Xbox Live version
and what do you find fun about the game as a whole?
I would say the PC version
is much better and the reason for that is
that they tried to cram too much into the Xbox
Live one and unfortunately it suffers
from some frame rate issues and just a really
awkward interface, I mean
for a dungeon crawler, collect a bunch of items
games, it doesn't work
too well on Xbox, I mean if for whatever
reason you hate gaming on the PC
then the Xbox is an okay substitute
I've played far worse games on
Xbox Live, but I just think between the two, the PC
version is superior. What do I like about the
game? Well, did you ever play Diablo
2? Because if you like that, that's why
I like Torchlight, because it's like a newer version
of that, but otherwise I like the fact
that the dungeons are always randomly generated
and there's something about that exploring
and collecting, you know, kind of like
that slow grind of improving your character
and completing quests, kind of like
a little bit like an RPG but with
much more action in it, I think that's
kind of what draws me to the game is that, you know, there's
definitely that exploration and you can't
really spoil it, like there can't be a strategy
guide for how to explore level
3, because level 3 is always different
it's random for each person that plays it
and I think that's part of the charm of it
Alright, I'm letting in one more tweet
here from SSJ100Matt saying
Someone took My Little Pony
and mixed it with the Starcraft 2
trailer and sends us a link to
something on YouTube called Ponycraft
I'm not sure what to do
This is not My Little Pony
It's like Noose. Did they redo My Little Pony
a couple of years ago or something?
They might have
This is not the one from the games
That's really not going to make
sense to me at most
Yeah, it's like a new My Little Pony
Might have a lot of vengeance
Somebody has far too much time
on their hands, that's all I'm going to say
Whatever, if that's the
project you want to be famous for, then cool
Alright, that's pretty hilarious
It's interesting
I've seen weirder things on YouTube, I guess
Nuclear Boy
I have not seen Nuclear Boy
And what is, ok
It's a great way to describe it to children
And I'm not up to date on all my
astrological stuff that's going on right now
or astronomical, I guess
Yeah, astronomical
But what the fuck is the super moon that they keep
seeing fucking tweets about and shit
Something about the moon being closer in orbit
I believe
It was supposed to be gigantic in the sky last night
but we wouldn't know because it's been raining
for like nine fucking days straight here
so the clouds have been blocking the sky
So you missed something, but you didn't
You would have had to drive that way
There's a picture of it
from Washington, DC
The super moon
See, there it is big
Oh, that's dumb
That's not big at all
But the moon's really big, Loki
It's a super moon
And since it's over Los Angeles
it's orange with a big rip across it
like an Evangelion or something
Seriously
Now I can see that
Alright, let's move on
Twitter topics are done, so back into the news
Loki, what have you got for us
Yeah, so
Super moon
This has been kind of a thing
that's been going on with Australia for the
longest time
Take violent game, ban it
because hey, you know what, we don't have anything
that's, you know, for adults
So, too bad
So apparently, Mortal Kombat
they appealed
the
failure to rate
the game
because it was not classified as
R15, and instead
their appeal was rejected
So, now
unless changes are
made, they cannot release it in
Australia
So that kind of sucks
And it will ban the title from
official retail distribution
And, of course
One of our other games is Extremely
Disappointed
That's always the comment, we're extremely disappointed
I'd be like, we're fucking pissed
That would be my fucking press statement
right there, fuck them in their asses
We're pissed
And they were
saying, praising thousands
of Mortal Kombat fans in Australia
and around the world who have voiced their support
during the appeal process
Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah
Really? Are you surprised?
I mean, they banned games with lesser
crap in there
Not to say that this will always
be the case, in fact, they're actually
pressing the
I guess the Australian
federal government
They're hoping to have
a consensus on the R18
game rating creation
Which is stupid
This is all government run anyways
But, whatever
Of course
The
MA-15 Plus
that the
country already has for mature games
is not good enough for
some of these, so adding the
restricted R18 Plus rating
will allow them to release some of these
more mature games
into the country
They said
I foreshadow that there is
if there's not consensus around
this issue, the Commonwealth will certainly
be considering other options because we
cannot continue to have an outdated
classification system that's actually
in my view, causing harm to young people
It just seems, I mean, the Saw movies aren't
banned there, right? I don't think so
What I saw in this game was no worse than Saw
I mean, I'm always gonna use that
as my defense. Those goddamn Saw movies
are terrible! Well, I don't understand how they always
rate games as, well, it's interactive
so it's more violent. No,
I don't think so. I think it's less
violent. If you think about it, I mean
the content in these games
like, for example
Grand Theft Auto, you can run people
over and they, you know, blood
sprays and stuff like that, you can set people on fire
all that stuff, but it's nowhere near as graphic
as you see it depicted in movies
I mean,
it's just way worse. It's cartoony
almost. And I mean
really
at what age are we gonna, like
finally let teenagers
you know, be able
to decide for themselves what's
reality and what's fantasy
because if they don't know that a game is
not real
then there's more, you know, serious
problems with them than
them playing a violent game
I'm fine with them taking violence
out of video games completely. Like, they could
just strip every video game out there of violence
as long as we could get ample nudity in its
place. That's what I'm saying.
Let's get some boobs. Nudity is even
worse. Like, it's like, oh my god, you know
there's a little bit of nudity in this game
oh, banned. Oh, but violence, we
can, you know, we can
drill holes in this guy's head
while he's, you know, still alive
but as soon as you wanna fuck one of those
holes, oh, banned.
Wow.
Well, speaking
of legal troubles
you might remember that Activision
had filed a suit against
Electronic Arts and the former
heads of Infinity Ward
well, in California, it was ruled this
week that the lawsuit filed by
Activision against the former Infinity Ward
studio heads, Vince Zampanella
and Jason West, it will be able to
proceed. EA wanted to have
the case dismissed
but unfortunately, the judge
felt differently. They decided
there is enough evidence that the case can go on to trial.
EA's options now
at this point, they can still request a summary
judgment that way
you know, it could all be rejected
but if that doesn't happen, then the case can
go to trial in May of this year.
It's gonna be interesting. Or it will get settled
out of court before then because that's what always seems to
happen. Has a video game case ever gone to trial?
Don't they always get settled out of court?
I don't think I've ever seen one go to trial.
I'm talking about one
between companies. I'm not talking about
some crazed asshole
played an Xbox and decided to do something
stupid. That's not a true
game lawsuit. That's just an idiot doing something
idiotic. I'm talking about
an actual two companies
suing each other. Does it ever not
get settled? Because they
usually end up having to pay less
by not going to court.
Or at least they have the illusion of this.
It's all just a giant game of chicken.
Chicken!
Alright.
So let's move on, DarkSakura.
Well.
Hold on.
Okay.
No, I cannot hold on any longer.
Because I pulled up the mailbag instead
of the story. Oops.
So,
I'm sure people remember me having
spoken of the King of Kong, right?
And it was the
video
of Steve Weeby and Billy
Mitchell.
Mitchell, yes. I'm sorry. He's a jerk.
Mitchell!
Trying to compete for the
top scorer on Donkey Kong. Well, now
we've got a new
documentary out called
Dr. Kong.
And this
is about
Dr. Chien, who is a
plastic surgeon, who
beat Steve Weeby's
record, reset record,
by hitting
1,090,400
points on Donkey Kong.
So,
there actually is a website about it.
You can go to
DrKongTheMovie.com
and...
Can I play the trailer here?
Play it, sure. It's kind of interesting, actually.
I don't know why. It's funny.
Here we go. So we see scenes of the
plastic surgery going on.
Establishing shots of
yes, this dude is a surgeon.
I'm copying this to the chat room, by the way. Sure.
And then you see him playing some Donkey Kong.
And he has a Donkey Kong machine.
I was feeling one of the people at Twin Galaxies
and when he found out I was a plastic surgeon, he was like
should you be out getting laid?
Like, why are you playing Donkey Kong?
I was like, I'm playing Donkey Kong so I can't get laid.
Wait a minute.
He's playing Donkey Kong
so he can't get laid?
Like, I don't get that. He's a plastic surgeon.
He makes girls' boobies bigger all day long.
That's what plastic surgeons do, right?
All they do is boob jobs, right?
Well, chin jobs
and lipo. Never
reconstructive surgeries after accidents, though.
No.
Just boob jobs. I don't need that.
So he works on boobies all day
but he plays
Donkey Kong to get laid.
I'm not sure I see the logic there
but let's continue.
I kind of like, I don't know, fame
I guess, or glory. I don't know.
Congratulations!
Paul, this guy's the guy that beat the world
that just beat the Donkey Kong.
Now that you have the world record
you have to quit playing.
Do you tell Mozart to stop composing music?
What?
That was the trailer. Do you tell Mozart
to stop composing music?
So is that the big question that's gonna be
answered in the movie? Like, does he get laid?
No.
No, he does not get laid.
Aw, what a downer.
And to...
He sounds like William.
Stop it!
Oh my god, Rob.
You are so red in the face right now.
Cause I'm mad that he dared bring that up
on this program.
You're a dick.
At least he sounds more educated.
He doesn't sound...
Next story!
Oh, put the 3DS down.
Loki, put the 3DS down
before I shove it up your ass.
Oh, fine.
Our next story.
Let's talk a little bit about Minecraft.
Yes, Minecraft.
Minecraft, they're going the route of
Nintendogs.
And you're gonna get
your own
I guess, domesticated wolf
Canines.
And...
You'll be able to walk around with them
and whatnot.
And then of course, later on, they're gonna be
adding achievements as well. That's the next thing.
But for right now,
they are working on
pet wolves.
Neat, I guess.
I don't know if they really
would do much. I mean, can you train them to
attack things?
I don't know.
I have a friend who has pet wolves.
Like real ones? Yes.
Just hanging out in the backyard?
A couple of them are half-wolves and one of them is full.
Here in SAC?
Yeah.
They're domesticated.
Kind of neat. I don't know.
They're kind of cool-looking.
These Minecraft ones are far more adorable.
That's all I'm saying. They are pretty adorable.
Is he gonna punch that wolf?
Oh, he's gonna beat it with a... No?
Punch? What is that?
What does that even have in his hand?
Looks like a stub.
Maybe it's like a stick to play fetch.
I still have yet to play
Minecraft. I feel so uncool and uneducated.
Yeah.
I kind of feel the same way.
You're so kind to me tonight.
Now he's punching a...
Oh, he punched a cow in the ass
and then the wolves are
attacking the cow.
Nice.
So you can stick your wolves on...
on other things.
So I guess you can now release the hounds.
That's neat.
Alright.
What happens if you punch the dog?
They probably get angry.
They bite your nuts off.
Is Minecraft like an MMO?
You can play with other people.
So you can visit other people's worlds and stuff?
That's kind of cool.
I really need to try this damn game already.
I don't know why I've been so lazy.
Oh, the dog's showing hearts.
He likes you.
He gave him a bone.
You try to hump, you're like...
The dog's on fire.
That's not good.
Cause the dog's stupid and standing over the fire.
Oh good. I've got people in chat. Defective Candy.
Don't feel bad. I've never played Minecraft either.
And SilverSonic. I've never played Minecraft either.
I will make it my mission this week to play Minecraft.
At some point. I promise.
I couldn't get into it. I didn't like it.
Really? What about it didn't you like?
It's just kind of a pain in the ass.
I think it's just you don't know where to start with it.
It's like...
I tried and I just honestly
I couldn't get into it and it just wasn't fun to me.
But it's like the big thing in gaming right now.
It's like Minecraft and Angry Birds.
Yeah, and if
you know everybody
if the biggest thing in gaming was for everyone to play
their Nintendo 3DS
while walking towards the end of a broken bridge.
Guess what?
I'll be playing PSP in my house.
Alright, moving on.
The Kodoo Game Lab.
I don't see a lot of coverage on this.
But it's out there and about.
Microsoft did release this.
It's a game creation utility.
It just came out this past week.
It's a free software suite.
And it's doing a game design
competition to sort of
kick off the whole Kodoo Game Lab.
It's called the Kodoo Cup 2011.
It's for
students aged 9 to 17.
Oh great, the target age group of our show.
Divided into
two age groups within the 9 to 17 bracket.
You will use the software
to design your game.
It's submitted by May 10th.
Prizes. $5,000 awards
for both individuals and schools.
A trip to New York City. Laptop connect
bundles. And a Zune HD.
Which is amazing because didn't we also have a story
this week that the Zune got
axed?
Gotta get rid of them somehow.
Maybe they'll have like 5,000 Zune HD's
as runner up prizes trying to get rid of
their Overstock.
That's too bad.
What I like
about this is the screenshot I'm looking at
of the Kodoo Game Lab. Somebody has designed
the lost numbers as a computer chip.
The 4, 8, 15, eh forget it.
Anyhow, so if you
are between 9 and 17 and you want to win money
or a, you know, Zune cause they're
so popular, check that out.
Meanwhile, let's go to the Mailbag.
Every week Dark Sakura reads
the emails that you guys send us at
mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com
So, why don't
Dark Sakura, why don't you
put on your surgical gloves, get ready
to jump in there and do some plastic surgery
on the mailbag. Ew, it's squishy.
Ok, first
Like a boob. No, not like a boob.
Like putting your finger
up a butt or something.
Anyway, hello OLR, it's your
friendly neighborhood spazzinator. Seeing as
the OLR mailbag has been a wee bit
on the light side as of late, I thought
it might be
a good'em idea
G-O-O-D-M, idea to
send an email rather than a tweet for
a change of pace. I found a little
something of note that bears mentioning seeing as it
relates to a subject you folks touched on
last week. Must be why I wasn't here.
With the recent events
in Japan in mind, SCEA's
arrangement to relay donations to the Red Cross
from one's PSN
wallet. As of the time I typed this
there's a spot on the game's side of the PSN
store, the first icon you see once you enter the new
pieces section, that allow you to make donations
of 2, 5, 10, 25, and
50 dollars
in US funds. I imagine
that you could make multiple
donations and mix and match amounts as well.
Although I can't say for sure that
I don't have access to the stores in other regions
I'd imagine there's similar setups in other regions'
PSN stores as well. In case
either of you, in case
either one of you or a fellow listener is asking
albeit to oneself,
something along the lines of, so
here's my point, this makes things that
much easier to donate to a cause if you feel
so inclined, but may not necessarily
have a PayPal or bank account, etc.
Such is the case with me, but I digress.
I'm not sure if Microsoft
will be doing a similar setup
in the Xbox, the
XBL marketplace, but if
I were betting man, the odds are in favor of it.
So in short, if you would like to donate and think
you can do without a rock band song, or if not
more, and you're on PSN
anyways, why not make a donation through the PSN stores?
Whispers, psss.
Besides, then you can honestly claim
that gaming does actually do some good
in the fact that it would just really piss off certain
ex-lawyer from Florida.
XD colon minus
P. I have not
heard about that guy in a very long time.
That certain ex-lawyer from Florida.
And that makes me happy that he
has not been in the news in a very long time.
That's one of the best things
to come out of this email, honestly. I bet he's
sitting on attack going, ow, there's attack.
Damn gamers.
Damn you gamers.
And you get a cute little theme.
And also to keep in mind
whenever you make a donation to
charity, get a receipt of it.
You can write it off on your taxes.
If you are, of course,
of tax paying age.
Just saying.
So you get a kickback. Not bad.
Also save all your school receipts.
Okay, I would close this
email with a clever quip or something, but frankly
my brain is fried due to lack of sleep.
And the word is lack of
sleep. And I can't think of
anything currently, so I'll just say this.
If you happen to have a PSN account with some
spare money on it, please
at symbol, at least consider donating.
And I just think
that because everything else is so flawlessly
done and the grammar is so awesome.
You can see the tiredness
coming through. I can see the tiredness.
And I'm like, I do that same crap when
I'm tired. So I was like,
okay, but some of them made me laugh.
I like good'em.
Good'em. Good'em. I'm gonna use that
word good'em. Don't know what it means,
but it's good'em. All good'em.
Mm-mm, good'em.
Crunchy- crunchy-um. Crunch'ems.
There should be a serial called good'em.
Okay, last email.
I'm- Nooooo.
AHHHHHHH
AHHH
Rob.
Apparently the last email was from the Tasmanian devil.
Rob. Rob. Rob what? Rob what?
Rob. Rob. What?
AHHHHHH
AHHH
Dinoboat fire.
No.
I'm writing about two things.
One, Test Drive Unlimited 2
has finally patched
and now does multiplayer events. If you put
it down because of the locked out bugs,
you can play it again. They serve
this up by installing the enticing
memory- sorry, the enticing
update named mandatory 1.
Two,
why hasn't us lately been
talking about how great the iOS devices
play games being DS killers
or the death of the consoles? That is
total bullshit. The iOS touch
screen is only better for certain types
of games. Nintendo's 3DS is
poised to sell like hotcakes and I believe it will.
As for consoles, as long as
they are configuration
controlled, they will always be popular.
I just believe that it's Apple,
Apple's fanboys, and Sony that are trying to
cast doubt on Nintendo's business.
I agree.
Yes. And I think I've said that on the show before
is that the Apple stuff,
the device itself,
not all games work on it.
And a lot of the ports, they show
being bad ports.
But some of the original stuff works out okay, like that
re-rave game we were talking about earlier. I mean, that was
designed for a touch screen. It works.
And it works pretty good. I'm sorry,
pretty good-um. Alright.
Pretty well, actually. Any other
emails tonight? Pretty well. Well-um.
Well-um.
No, that's it, Rob. Alright,
mailbag at orangelaundry.com
if you want to send us an email to possibly
maybe read on
next week's show. Maybe.
But for now, some angst
in the segment we call FUs of the Week.
Um.
FU.
This is sort of an FU to jury
duty. I mean, I know it's my civic
duty and actually I kind of want to be on a
case, but right now
I don't have to go in tomorrow, so I'm very happy.
You should reschedule yours
for May 9th, because that's the night device.
Okay.
Well, I actually am going to have to reschedule
mine for after school because I can't have anything.
And here's my FU.
FU to the damn light cycle
that I'm having to model
in Maya.
I've gotten the tail of it done
finally, but I'm
having a hell of a time with a curve.
I can't
get Maya installed on my computer, so
it's pissing me off.
And I don't really feel like going to hang
out at the Mac Lab all day using the Mac Lab
to try to get it to work.
So Maya can bite my butt.
Yeah.
I'm probably
gonna not get an A in this class.
I kind of don't care. I just
want to pass it.
Because guess who's graduating this semester.
That would be me!
Okay, I'm done.
I'm just reminded of a scene with some
strangers with candy. I got a D!
You know what?
What?
I have not gotten a D at all.
What about an F?
The only reason I got an F
is because I dropped the class and they didn't
register me on the books that I dropped it.
F for fantastic work.
F for
fuck this place!
Um...
I would say probably F you to
um...
a few colds
and having
my son have a cold
because he's really cranky. And F you
the tape gun that attacked my finger
earlier this week. I now have
I have multiple cuts on my finger.
Did it jump up and bite you?
Something like that. I have
one, two, three. That looks painful. My god.
That wasn't that painful. But yeah, there's
like five. Imagine if you
cut yourself with
not necessarily a piece of paper but like
maybe like a knife
just like a small cut
but five of those
really close together. That's basically
the tape gun for you. And it did that
on two fingers.
It hurt for a little bit but no more than that paper
cut. It looked really bad though.
That was fun.
That's it.
My F you goes to Loki
for bringing up my ex on the program.
On live internet radio. Thank you Loki.
But really though
my F you goes to
tacos because they are amazing and
addicting and I really want one right now.
Like just a taco sounds great.
Just saying.
You know Rob, we had pesto chicken
you could have some. That's alright.
I'm craving the really fatty Jim Boy's ground beef
tacos. Parmesan cheese
on the crust. Delicious.
Alright.
Moving on with some more news and then
the Skype line at 1877 game OLR.
But not yet. We have some more news stories
real quick. Loki. Yes.
And you know I don't know this
is kind of
interesting.
But you know
this kind of ties in with announcements of announcements.
But there is a rumor
right now that there's I guess
an Hitman ARG
that's going on right now.
That's leading up
to the announcement of a new Hitman game
at E3.
That series is still around?
Yes it's apparently still around.
I guess it's
right now they're saying
that
I'm trying to see where it's coming from.
It started with an ad
from Faircount Media Group
in a catalog at Sundance Film Festival
depicting a box of
the
Hitman series brand donuts
with a barcode ending in 47.
And then it says I guess
when a Hitman forum user tracked down
the agency responsible for the ad
and emailed them he received a
response from an account saying
you're on the right track.
And then they gave him a new image showing a pair
of black gloves that appears
to be a game script
and another barcode ending in 47
and some other random numbers and blah blah blah blah blah.
Whatever. Okay so it's a
stupid ARG leading up to
the announcement of Hitman.
Great.
Oldest have to wait until E3.
Oh surprise.
I love announcements about announcements.
My favorite thing in the gaming industry.
In seven days
we will be announcing
an announcement about a game coming out in 14 months.
You don't
make it so damn obvious
what it's going to be.
You have to make it completely
weird and off the wall.
And then people are like oh.
There will be a trailer announcing
this announcement.
Moving on. One other quick story
for you guys. It has to do with the game
Doodle Jump. Have you ever heard of Doodle Jump?
Dan plays Doodle Jump all the time.
I have never heard of this game but apparently
it sold 10 million copies
between iPhone and Android.
What is Doodle Jump then DarkSira?
You'd have that little dude
on the picture. It's like
you just turn it and he jumps from platform
to platform and you just have to keep him going forward.
Oh okay so you don't actually doodle in the game.
I don't think so. Interesting. I haven't played it.
I've just seen Dan play it. Well they've sold 10 million
copies. I think you can
make your own characters by doodling.
And funny enough this is the perfect
kind of last story for tonight to kind of go
with that story that came up earlier about how
Zynga is like we don't want to do our game on
Xbox because Xbox is too
small. Well what's the announcement?
Yep Doodle Jump is going to be coming out for
Xbox 360.
Lima
Skye who is the creative
person behind the game
Doodle Jump said that
they reached 10 million of their milestone.
They've also said that they are going to
be bringing the game to Xbox Live
Arcade and the Kinect controller
for Microsoft. They
also want to release a multiplayer update
to the iPhone version. They want to do an
iPad version and of course
merchandise, t-shirts, stickers,
buttons, yay!
Can't wait.
So even though some people
want to hate on Xbox 360 because
it's too small, some
people think it might be a good
place for their game. At least the Doodle Jump
people think so.
So that's it for the news tonight. Let's
go to the Skype line. We're going to open up the phone
lines right now. 1-877-GAMELR
or our username on Skype is
OrangeLoungeRadio if you'd like to give us a call.
In the meantime while we wait for some calls
maybe Loki has a last minute story or five.
Yeah, actually I do
and let's see
this was kind of cool. I saw this earlier today.
We talk a lot
about Kinect hacks and stuff like that
but this one's a little different.
It's a Kinect hack working on a PS3
and basically
it's somebody using the Kinect
to play Killzone 3
and it's
quite a workaround.
Apparently it allows
you also, I guess, to navigate the cross media bar
and
then
I'm assuming
if it's tied
in with some sort of
hack, you probably
have to have a custom firmware or something like that
in order to get it to work. In fact, yeah, it looks
like here
oh wow, there's lots of stuff here.
Hold that thought.
Hi, you're on OrangeLoungeRadio. Who's this?
This is DJ Blaziken.
DJ Blaziken.
What's on your mind, buddy?
Not much other than
I think it was last week or something
Parasite Eve came out for PlayStation Network
and I finally picked it up.
It did. I saw that on the list when I was going to get the
Mortal Kombat demo. I saw that scrolling by
and I was like, oh shit, yeah, I heard that that was
coming out. So, what'd you think?
I thought it was actually pretty
darn well. It works a little
bit awkward and really blocky
on my 20 inch
TV and 1080p, but
looks really good though on the
PSP Go.
And this is a little
thing for all the listeners who might have the
PSP Go that probably didn't know this
or ever figured it out.
You can actually sync your PlayStation
3 controller to it
via the Bluetooth
and makes it a little bit
easier to play
if
you're at a death or something
and you just don't like the
whole control scheme of that.
But, oh my god.
I mean
for years I just saw the trailer
and
that blew my mind.
It still blows my mind
now, looking at the visuals
even though now we're in the HD age
it still just goes
to show
Square
puts a lot of effort into just maxing
out the potential of whatever system
they're working on. Everything from
the original NES
now. I think we've seen it.
It's max.
The thing about Parasite Eve, they did make a second
game, but they never really made a third.
I do know there's third birthday, but
that was years later obviously.
Do you think
it's best that some games don't get
sequels? Or do you think that
really good games deserve sequels?
I think really good games
especially like this, I don't know how much
notoriety it got, but
it seems like a game
for a potential of sequels.
I remember it
being a pretty big deal back in the day because
it was one of the first Square games to come out after
Final Fantasy VII from what I remember.
Now granted my memory's a little fuzzy because
I'm really fucking old, but it's something like that.
Yeah, I saw one of those PlayStation
magazine demo discs
and, oh my
god, even though at the time
my mom wouldn't let me play rated M games back then
and two, I just didn't have
the cash to get it.
So, and now that
I am of age and
have the cash, I was just like,
heck, I'll get this.
That's right. I'm mature now.
I'm gonna play all the mature rated games I want.
And, you know what, it's
I don't know what, I
gotta praise Square because
we have probably the best
I mean, I may sound like a little bit
of a Square fanboy, but
who hasn't been
ever.
They always just seem to come out with
games with a really great story arc
that connects you with the characters
and makes you feel like
an emotional
attachment to them almost didn't.
It's just like,
whoa.
Going to our chat
I will admit,
if this has ever happened to any of you guys,
that a game ending ever made you cry,
it would've had to
been the first Kingdom Hearts
ending when
Kyrie and Source split apart
on two different lands. OMG spoilers.
I could never beat
Kingdom Hearts.
It was hard.
It was hard, but
worth the grind. Yeah, yeah, that's true.
If you reached the ending,
it was a pretty sad ending.
It just brought tears to my
eyes. I was like, no!
Go back!
It's okay, try to keep your emotions in check
on the show, buddy. Have you played
through Parasite Eve yet?
I've gotten up
to probably the first
boss battle so far,
and I'm just getting my ass
hated to be like
that, and so I'm trying to look at
walkthroughs and possible online
strategy guides to figure out
any ways to beat it.
The good news is with those older games,
there's a ton of them out there, so that's a good thing.
Yeah, which there's a lot more
help with it.
I'm just trying to figure out,
because I have the PS3 Slim right now,
basically,
would it be
worse...
I don't know if any of us remember
Blingcast for the Dreamcast.
I have them all.
Okay,
basically, what would you think,
because with the PlayStation Move controllers
being thrown in the way of Wii remotes,
if with the jailbroken
PS3, someone comes out with a Wii
emulator that does HD
support for the PS3
Wii games?
It would be difficult because
remember, emulators take a lot more horsepower
to run than the actual consoles
themselves, so even right
now running a Nintendo 64
emulator on a PS3, while
possible,
that's pretty much maxing out
the resources right now.
The PlayStation 3 has to emulate the fuckin' PS2
first, and I'm not talking about the
old school first generation consoles,
because they had the extra chip, which is why they were so
expensive, but I find it very
odd that we still have seen nothing about
PlayStation 2 emulation on PlayStation 3
outside of that very, very first
generation of consoles.
Maybe it wasn't a firmware patch
that we just never really figured
No, you would have
trumpets and fanfare and
confetti everywhere if that were to happen, and honestly,
I wouldn't expect it to be as easy
as putting your discs in. I think those sick
bastards will make you pay for the games
all over again. But I
can hope not. I sure hope not.
I might just get a PlayStation
2 again if that, if it doesn't
work. Just so
I can have BeatMania
with most of the Beemani
titles, really, because
I mean, I have the Rock Band keyboard, and it's
making me miss Keyboard Mania, because that was
at my arcade.
They traded
they got rid of it
I don't know why, that along with pop and music
they used to have that.
They had just got all the Beemani games here
at Family Fun Center, but
they traded them all in for random
stuff, and only
once we have wrapped the Link's
Para. Rest in peace
the arcades I remember. Alright, Blazekin
I gotta let you go so we can get our calls.
Arcade Infinity RIP
That was just sad watching the
video. Alright, we're gonna go Para40 right now.
Alright, Blazekin I gotta let you go to get
more calls. Have a good one buddy.
Alright, peace out. Bye.
Alright.
1877 GameOLR
username on Skype is OrangeLoungeRadio
Anything else low-key while we're waiting for
another call?
Um
I don't really have too
much. I was gonna talk, there was some
other developments with the
whole Playstation
hacking stuff
and the whole court case, everything. I believe
they, was it the
judge okayed Sony to get the
basically
people that have
donated money from California
into
the GeoHot thing. They've
gotten access to those records
and then um also
they're trying to find
a software development
kit manual
on his computer because
in the manual it has like
if you need help support and you're in the
US territories call this number because he's
basically saying that he was unaware that
Sony was in California or something like
that and they're trying to find a way to link it to him
that he knew that they're in California
to which I say, who the fuck
reads the manual for something like that
and I don't think it's
actually on his system. I think he used
open um
open source stuff to create
his hacks so
it may be a
stretch but it seems like they're really trying to
grab at straws here. Alright we got
another call coming in so let's go to it. Hi you're on
Orange Launch Radio. Who's this?
Hey how's it going? This is SSJ100 Matt. Hello
SSJ100 Matt. What's going on buddy?
Hello hello
Doing good. I just wanted to call
and get my late PAX East report.
You're late. PAX East was
so last week. Are you
calling in to talk about PAX East 2012?
The internet line looks like 100 years.
Alright no I'm kidding. What's up? Obviously
you're probably on the way home or something so we'll
give it a buy. Did you have a good time?
Yeah I definitely had a good time. You know what
I liked it a lot more than
last year's. Oh of course because
I wasn't there. Yeah well
Hey don't agree with that asshole.
I'm just kidding.
So what was better
about it than last year?
You know what? It was the bigger
conventions that really made a difference
and I think
a lot more people were able to work with
the larger space.
Tabletop gaming was
big.
I mean
the spacing of the
boots were good. People weren't hidden
behind other boots.
You know you're able to see everyone
so everyone got plenty
of traffic I think and
there were a lot more
there was a lot more
newer stuff there I guess.
They got to play on the 3DS. They got to play
Duke Nukem Forever
and
the one game that I really liked
Child of Eden
Oh yeah the
spiritual successor of sorts to Res
sure. Yeah and
you know what I think you guys
will certainly enjoy it. I'm actually considering
a Kinect because of that game.
How does it work? Is it really
like Res but you use your hands
to kind of highlight things? Is that kind of what the deal is?
It's pretty much that way
and you know what it's weird because
there's two different ways of shooting.
Use your left hand to shoot
to highlight over and then push forward
to shoot the missiles.
And then you can use your right hand
to shoot the gun regularly.
Interesting.
So you switch off
during the gameplay which is really interesting.
And it's really interesting that it's able to
capture that
with limited problems but
but you know the other thing I really liked
at PAX East was
the classic arcade run.
They had a lot more stuff
I'm sure you remember last year
it was kind of set up like Flynn's
arcade where you had Journey music playing
and
last year I remember
last year I remember it was just a room full of
consoles and you could kind of check out whatever game you wanted to
play and do it all that way
but they kind of took it, kicked it up a notch
this year with the bigger space.
Well yeah well I'll say that but I'm also
talking about the arcade room where they had
the arcade machines all set up.
Oh yeah, the one that was next door to the console room.
Yes, yes I remember.
Yeah.
You know they had a lot more
I think they doubled the amount of arcade games there.
Oh nice. And they also had a couple of
guys from
Twin Galaxies trying to beat high scores live.
Nice! Oh man
that was one of my favorite spots at PAX East.
Yeah.
So that was really interesting so
I had a lot of fun there
and you know it was kind of to the point because you know
not too many people went up there to play stuff.
Everyone was downstairs on the Xbox floor
so you know I was able to play
all the arcade games I wanted to.
Nice.
Very cool.
What do you hope that they bring next year to PAX?
What's an improvement they need to make for next
year's PAX?
I think you know
that
as much as it was a great
plan, the
panels themselves weren't, I didn't really
find to enjoy.
The thing was most of the panels
were about networking.
A lot of stuff you would kind of see at GDC.
I mean I'm not really
into getting into the business. I mean I'm just
you know a gamer. I don't play.
I don't make games.
But you know they had a lot of panels like that and you know
it's a great idea and I think they should keep that but you know
there was you know
very limited stuff that
about games
you know
gaming itself I guess. So maybe they need to
diversify the panel lineup a little bit more.
Or maybe have more rooms.
There was only one panel they went to
and that was the Xbox Live
enforcement.
Oh yeah I saw a clip of that one online. That looked kind of
interesting actually. Where they were showing
how they could ban
people. Like they basically just run through
giant columns of names and highlight
all the colors. It was interesting.
Yeah. Kind of neat.
Alright well I am hoping I
can go out to PAX East next year but
you know it's a plane ticket
so the cost of gas has to come down but we'll see.
It's in April
next year. During Passover in the west.
Oh no.
No no. Get this. It starts on
my birthday this year. Does it
really? Yep. Interesting.
Well no Passover. Well I was going to say
it would be funny if PAX East was around that same time
next year. No cake.
I'll eat cake on the day before.
Space it out a little more from like
You should come to PAX East.
You know what if I could afford it or if
a bunch of people wanted to get together and put
the money together and send me a plane
ticket. Although
Japan disaster relief is kind of
important right now. More important. I know.
But I'm saying if you got
ten people
to put twenty bucks together
that's half a plane ticket. Just saying.
That's just wasted twenty dollars. No I'm kidding.
Alright no but I
Hopefully things will get better
next year financially and economically
and we can evaluate that for next year.
I really want to go to PAX West
this year to be honest. I really want to go.
But I just don't know if I can. We'll see.
Alright. Well enough
coulda woulda shoulda wanna
hopefully talk. I'm gonna go ahead and let you go
when I'm out to get a few more calls but
thanks for the report. And Child of Eden I definitely
have my eye on that one. I want to play out when it comes out.
Absolutely. Alright. Take care
buddy. Take it easy guys. Alright later.
1877 Game OLR.
Our username on Skype is OrangeLoungeRadio
while we wait for some more calls.
Loki anything else?
Um
Not really. I don't know.
I don't remember if we talked
too much about Angry Birds and
how much they've sold.
Freaking tweet! Argh! Angry Birds.
That's my impression. I don't understand the
Angry Birds obsession. I don't either.
The game's alright.
It's okay but I mean it's
there's more fun games out there.
I think it's really the price point
that sold so many copies of that.
I don't understand the whole movie franchising thing.
I don't understand the
just the whole obsession with it.
People are dumb.
That's what I've really come to understand is
this whole new casual gaming
market out there. Your moms and
you know other
relatives or whatever they're playing these casual
games. Oh no they're hardcore now.
Oh I'm sorry. They're hardcore
according to Zynga. Zynga you're stupid.
They're not hardcore
and I'm sorry I think that they're kind of
they're not dumb
necessarily but their
expectations are a lot lower
compared to everybody else. I don't know.
Whatever.
Alright sorry I didn't mean to have
dead air there but I wanted to remind the folks in chat
because there's sometimes a bit of a delay.
Last call for Skype call is 1-877-GAMO-LR
or our username on Skype is orangeontradios
so folks in chat want us to go to DragonCon
in Atlanta. I totally
totally totally want to go to that.
See I don't know if there'd be enough for me
there. I mean I would go to hang with
people and that would really
be it for me. It was kind of like
when I went to that anime con in Chicago
the AsenCon that I did a little panel at.
I want to get an Asen too. I had a good
time hanging with people
but the con itself was
just kind of like woop over my head. We need to see about getting in for
Fanime. I mean we need to talk to our people.
Yeah. Alright we got another call coming
up so let's take it. Hi you're on Orangeontradios. Who's this?
Hi this is
Spazenator. Hey buddy how you doing Spazenator?
Pretty good you.
Two quick
items.
One question and one comment.
The comment first
sorry about the typos and all that
in my email. I'm just
giving a hard time. She just gives everybody shit
don't worry about it. I give people I like a hard time.
It's called love.
Yeah I know.
Now
as far as my question
now seeing that Microsoft
is basically doing away with the
Zune
now are they going to
ax the video marketplace
as well on Xbox Live
or is that going to stick around?
That was around before the Zune.
When did the Zune come out? The Zune came out about a year
after Xbox was out and I seem to recall that
video marketplace was going pretty early
so no I mean if they can still
sell movies on there they're going to do it.
Even though the Zune's
going away don't forget they still have the Windows
mobile phones and I think that's really kind of where they're
focusing. I mean think about it.
A lot of the marketplace
for the iOS
is centered around the iPhone.
I mean granted you have your
iPads and you have your iPod
touches still but I think the
iPhone claims a pretty fair share
of that market so I think
the Zune fading out is more
Microsoft kind of aligning itself.
Instead of doing a Zune phone
now they have this Windows 7 phone or whatever it is.
So no you're not
going to see the movie stuff go away.
God how could you? Especially with like
Netflix,
Hulu they've announced for the end of the year
and all this other stuff.
Yeah it's only going to be
more.
Yeah I was just
kind of curious because now that
I got a computer and I use
the Zune marketplace
on my computer I'm just going to use
a whole lot more now.
You'll probably see it get
rebranded as like you know
the Windows Mobile or
it'll get rebranded. They'll probably
walk away from that Zune name.
But it'll still be there.
Oh alright.
Thanks for taking my call.
Definitely appreciate it. No problem buddy.
Have a good one.
Later.
Wow that was a neat call. Hey I got a question
and he answered it and he's like okay bye.
I like that.
Alright so since that call was so fast we'll go ahead and do
one more call. Hi you're on Orange Launch Radio. Who's this?
Hi guys.
Can you guys hear me? We can. Who's this?
Hi it's DDR Dollar Bill.
Hey DDR Dollar Bill. How you doing?
Hey doing alright man.
Just figured I just want to make it quick
because I don't want to waste you know
take too long. Just want to give my
presence on PAX East. Hey you're late.
No that's alright. You were driving in the car
last week right? Yes I was.
Okay well you didn't get to talk because you were probably driving
so what did you think of PAX East?
I enjoyed
it heavily.
My favorite part was
not exactly was something that not many
people really understood.
It wasn't really the games. It wasn't really
the panels.
It was the actual fact that I
actually got to interview some of the developers.
Oh.
So just being close and getting
to interact with people that are usually
behind closed doors at trade shows.
Exactly.
Okay.
Who were some of the developers you got to talk to?
I got to talk with one guy from Microsoft
who was developing
the upcoming Firepaw Wrestling release
on Xbox Live Arcade.
I was
really interested because
Firepaw Wrestling, I don't know how many
people know this but it's like a really old
school wrestling game that
was hailed heavily because you know.
I've actually got a couple of the
Firepaw Wrestling games.
What's that? I've never heard of it.
We've got the Dreamcast one that had the Virtua Fighter characters
in it.
Oh. You mean the All Japan
featuring Virtua.
They had a wolf in it. Yeah.
Yeah and the Giant Gram series.
Yeah but I think we've got one of the
Firepaw.
I think the Dreamcast
yeah D it's called.
Yeah.
This one actually uses your avatars
as wrestlers.
Oh that's pretty sweet.
Oh yeah and from what I was told
you actually have to develop
the moves from the beginning.
So you start off at level 1
and you basically keep fighting and the more levels you get
the more moves you get.
And the moves
from what I've seen so far they seem kind of
more arcade-ish
not so much like the current
wrestling games like SmackDown vs. Ball
and all that.
But I think if
it works well I think it would actually be a nice hit.
Especially since it's used to your avatars
and whatnot.
So you liked
getting close to the developers and it's funny
because on a previous call SJ100Matt was talking
about the panels were a little
much on the side of how to get into the
business. Did you find
that same thing to be true or did you kind of like
that?
I found that
to be the same thing and to be quite honest
I actually liked it because
it actually showed me
a side of gaming I've never really
explored. Like the developing
side. You just discovered
a whole new side of yourself you never knew was
there before.
Oh yeah
considering how much video I was doing, yeah.
Nice.
You know I remember when I went to PAX the first year
PAX Prime one of the games they were showing was Warhammer
and it was pretty cool. The Warhammer Online
one, the WoW killer that
didn't really end up killing WoW. But it was
cool to be able to kind of like as one of the guys
I was playing the game and he just came up and was talking to me about it
it was really cool. Like I
like that when folks will just kind of walk up
and talk to you about the product. You know E3 is a lot
of that too. Unfortunately
a lot of the big boosts will kind of
turn their nose up at you but the
littler companies, man they
they'll practically drag you into their
boosts to talk about whatever it is they're putting out so
I always kind of like that, getting to talk to folks
just about what they really love
doing. A lot of people
a lot of people that are really into the game
industry really love what they're doing. It's pretty cool.
I had two more interviews like that
I had one with the one developer
from Lord of the Rings
the MMORPG
Yeah which
I'm actually going to probably take a shot at it
one day since it's free
and another one which
I actually might pay for because
it was really interesting was like
I'm going to get the name wrong
but it's called iRacing
it was like a racing simulator type
kind of like Gran Turismo for the PC
and you
had pretty much you had to play against
real players not computer
AI
and I was actually sitting down
with the driving wheel with the voice feedback
and everything
after about maybe 10 minutes of driving
and I had to stop because I wanted
to do other things
I actually felt my body going
forward like the whole inertia
Oh wow
Yeah I was like wow
I was like
slowly walking away like
That sounds like my first time with a 3DS
but
I had to turn that 3DS off I couldn't see
I was
half blind when I tried it
it was just too much headache
It was interesting to hear different people's reactions
I'm so curious to see what's going to happen when that thing comes out
for the public
I know like Best Buy already has a demo unit out
Oh yeah I heard a lot of places are getting
the demo units so they're pretty easy to
get your hands on now I mean they're out Sunday
this is not something that's coming out like 6 months from now
it's out like soon so
Yeah I'll probably pick it up later
but one last thing though about 3D
real quick
I also saw the Nvidia 3D cards
and
for some reason 3DS
and most 3D TVs
I can't really use the 3D because it makes me dizzy
Right
But when I was trying out Warcraft
in 3D
on 3 screens
no problems
whatsoever
I can only imagine what that must be like
that must be insane that's too much wow
did I really say that?
that's too much wow
Oh Rob that's not such a thing
I cannot believe that just came out of your mouth
that's why I said it
that I've hosted this show with for 9 years
that's why I said it Rob
it's crazy it's called irony
it's crazy
I just like the 3D it's like wow I can actually see it
the first sign of the end of the world coming
in 2012 was when Dark Sakura
admitted to liking Warcraft that was like the first
sign alright anyhow
DDR.com I gotta let you go so we wrap up the show
but thanks so much for your call buddy
and glad to hear you had fun at PAX East
see you next year later I hope
I hope
I really would like to do PAX West this year
I'm hoping I can save the money fast enough cause Seattle's not that far
that's the good news I could drive
to Seattle I mean
it would be a pain in the ass but I could do it
Dark Sakura's pretty much driven to Seattle
I mean granted the town she
goes to is in a different corner of Washington
but it's about the same length when all
said and done right? well it's
it was like a 17 hour drive to get to Prosser
so I would imagine tack
on another 4 to that to get to Seattle?
no because you can get to Portland in
10 and Seattle's another
3 to 4 from Portland but that's
just a straight shot up 5 so
to get to where you're going you have to go through more
we went I think in the 93 yeah
you gotta go through weird no Seattle's
just a straight shot up 5
but see my ride's
quite a bit longer and we actually
didn't go through that part of Oregon we
stopped in like Bend you know what
Dark Sakura we should rent I already
know Loki's not going to come because the baby you
and I should rent a van
we're doing it go up to Pat
I can't promise you money money money
I know I need money
alright we'll see more to
develop in the future let me just do one
more check with Loki on any last minute stories
and then we're going to wrap up the show nah
you just want to
get out of here and play more Motorstorm
yeah I won't
get to play more Motorstorm at home
I could I mean
it's just you know a TV and stuff
yeah alright
well we're going to go ahead and start to wrap up tonight's show
but first we have to go around and get
everybody's final thoughts
Loki well I guess we'll start with you tonight
you have a final thought for listeners I will be
playing lots of Motorstorm at work though that's
for sure it's such an awesome
game and
Dark Sakura your final thought tonight
we
have Girl Scout cookies and I am going
to be wonderful and not eat one
my final
thought is I will happily eat that Girl Scout
cookie on your behalf but what
I really want is a taco a taco
Girl Scout cookie
just
Rob what me
also I need
to go on a diet that's
it for another week of Orange Lawns Radio thank you guys
so much for listening to our show we really
appreciate the support you guys give us every
week when you tune in we hope you guys all
have a wonderful week enjoy the 3DS
those of you guys are going to run out and get it on Sunday
we'll be back to talk about that and much
more next week I'm sure Loki you're getting
yours right on Sunday right so you can show us an American
one next week no it's not on Sunday
I ordered mine from GameStop
yeah I know but hey knowing the game
industry and how it works they're getting the largest portion
of those systems yep
so I ordered a bundle off their website
so it'll be shipped to me so I'll have it
not Sunday
but the next week I don't really care because
I already have a 3DS but yeah I mean it's
be nice to see the American versions
of stuff and the different games that are out here
so yeah
alright well that's going to do it so next week we'll be back to talk
3DS and so much more whatever else is going on in
gaming with you guys on the show where every
gamer has a voice Orange Lawns Radio
remember if you like the show please leave us
a nice review on iTunes or tell two friends
about the show help us spread the word because
word of mouth is all we got for advertising
we'll be back next week to do it all again have a good week
be right anyway
I'll see you guys next week