[SPEAKER_02]: Tonight, March 6, 2011, the PlayStation 3 stops shipping in one country, GameStop becomes the target of a class action lawsuit, and Microsoft clears up some old gamer tags.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hello my friends out there on the interwebs and welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is that show about video games.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's the show that brings every gamer a voice as we have over the past nine years.
[SPEAKER_06]: We do tape live Sunday nights at All Games Radio, www.allgames.com, right after the Bobby Blackwolf Show.
[SPEAKER_06]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll be joining you over the next few hours with my co-hosts.
[SPEAKER_06]: Say hello to the one and only Dark Sakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_06]: Shimei.
[SPEAKER_06]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_06]: Shemazel.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are we the Laverne and Shirley opening?
[SPEAKER_07]: This will be showing up on our photo feed shortly.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because today's alcoholism is brought to you by Chimay, which is tasty.
[SPEAKER_06]: Uh-oh, you're not drinking during the show again, because last week, oh boy, that was a rough show.
[SPEAKER_07]: Watch me.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm drinking.
[SPEAKER_06]: Say hello and welcome back.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki is back with us tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_06]: How are you doing?
[SPEAKER_06]: You feeling better?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: We told all the listeners why you were gone.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry if you want to keep it a secret.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I don't.
[SPEAKER_06]: We figured you'd tweet about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's fine.
[SPEAKER_07]: I told him that we played a song in Tribute.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's right, we did play Living with a Hernia on our way out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently it was something, I don't know, I guess it was something I had for a long time or something, but on Tuesday last week, all of a sudden, my innie became an outie, and it's like, oh, this kind of hurts.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why is this hurting?
[SPEAKER_04]: So I went to the doctor.
[SPEAKER_04]: The doctor said, hey, you better go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here, I'm going to make an appointment with the surgeon right now so you can go get checked out.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then I went to the surgeon's office, and they're like,
[SPEAKER_04]: We can take care of this right now if you want.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm like, all right.
[SPEAKER_04]: So they did that, and it hurt like a bitch for, well, during the operation.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, operations tend to hurt.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did they put you under?
[SPEAKER_04]: Nope, it's local, and that felt weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I bet.
[SPEAKER_04]: But then, no, then it's just like really stiff and sore for a couple days.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just want to point out they don't knock you out for a vasectomy either if you want to.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure that would.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've heard.
[SPEAKER_04]: That probably wouldn't have hurt as bad as, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not even really hurting, it's weird stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Imagine someone putting their finger into your belly button underneath and then pulling muscle down or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's kind of the feeling.
[SPEAKER_06]: The synchronized sounds of barfing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or the feeling of someone electrocuting fat or something on you and popping and then smelling that fat burning.
[SPEAKER_04]: Once in a while we do talk about video games, I promise.
[SPEAKER_04]: But no, I'm feeling better.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wait, did they turn the fat into bacon?
[SPEAKER_04]: They did not.
[SPEAKER_04]: It does not smell like bacon.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not even... Human flesh smells like chicken burning.
[SPEAKER_04]: It does not smell like chicken burning.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not pleasant.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's not pleasant to feel it burning either.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, well, look, all this gross medical talk house aside, hopefully you had a chance to play a lot of games while you were recovering.
[SPEAKER_04]: and so forth.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was an umbilical hernia.
[SPEAKER_04]: As long as I can remember, my belly button feels weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: It felt like there was a tube on the other side or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: You never had a baby to lift before.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't even know if it was that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is your intestines hooked up to the wrong space?
[SPEAKER_04]: Basically, what happens with hernia is sometimes fat or tissue can get trapped inside of it, and then the circulation gets cut off and it dies.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that's what started to happen with some of that, so that's why it started hurting.
[SPEAKER_04]: So they had to get rid of that so that it wouldn't turn into gangrene or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: I gotta go to our chatroom at chat.orangeloungeradio.com let me read you some of the comments in our chatroom right now we are live at chat.orangeloungeradio.com OMFG Loki stop can't Loki just talk about Grand Theft Auto or Earth Defense Force instead Orange Lounge Trauma Center
[SPEAKER_04]: Talk about both of those.
[SPEAKER_04]: I saw the new little trailer or like behind the scenes, or not really a trailer, it was like a behind the scenes thing or a preview of Earth Defense.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's so awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know how to follow that up, but I guess we'll... No, I'm fine now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Technically, I'm not supposed to be lifting anything or doing anything, but I feel fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: And so I've been lifting my son and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just not like, you know... It's because you're secretly a cyborg.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not going to go, you know, try to get more cat litter or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like a 30-pound... It's basically, if it hurts, stop doing it.
[SPEAKER_06]: uh well you were missed last week Loki but our aim's improving now that you're within targeting range because last week seriously we had a drunk Jamie we had the Oscars girl I was tipsy we had a drunk Jamie and then Mystique came in middle of the show and I don't even know what happened I did pretty good on my Oscar picks I think I haven't got a chance to be back to my work but I hope I won something that'd be kind of cool
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_06]: I played well.
[SPEAKER_07]: Damn you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Addict.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dealer.
[SPEAKER_07]: I joined the Horde House Guild and made a death knight because I did not want to start from one.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the interesting thing about having a new guild.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, my spinoff show, Horde House with Extover, has an official guild now.
[SPEAKER_06]: And all the details are on the last show.
[SPEAKER_06]: On the Goober server.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, on what WowWiki calls a server full of bad players.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we had to roll there.
[SPEAKER_06]: We had to roll there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Had to do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: But everything's starting from scratch.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's been very weird.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've run into nothing but assholes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Really?
[SPEAKER_07]: Except for us.
[SPEAKER_07]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_07]: There was one nice person who wanted to group with me, but I'm like, I don't want to play with you.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's just been MMOs for you?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, today I went in either room because I wanted to play Marvel vs. Capcom 3 and Dan was playing through Shinobi.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I sit down with my sleeping bag because it's really warm.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because I was super cold.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I sat with my sleeping bag and I fell asleep to Shinobi and woke up to Ikaruga.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I guess that counts that I can sleep to video games.
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently at some point Dan beat it because I opened my eyes and saw the ending and I was like, whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I think that's about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_06]: And then we were talking about Rygar, the arcade game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, not the NES game that most everybody remembers.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was also an arcade game.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I was talking about the Tidal Arcade Classics that is on Xbox, the old school one.
[SPEAKER_06]: It has Rygar, it has Tecmo Bowl, a bunch of other stuff in it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, like, I've been really wanting to play that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't get to it today, but, like, ever since our little conversation this morning, I've been dying to go back and play some Rygar.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's been like an old school arcade day.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is, I think, one of the backwards compatible games.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's why I know I can play it.
[SPEAKER_07]: That came up in our discussion today.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, because I don't think Dan knew that it was backwards compatible and is one of the few.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't think he checked.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think Taito had like the Rainbow Islands and Bubble Bobble.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't remember what was in that collection.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was years ago that I first got it but now it's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Parasol Stars.
[SPEAKER_06]: A lot of those arcade games kind of get recycled and they want to charge you five, ten bucks a piece for them.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love Parasol Stars.
[SPEAKER_07]: I found a copy of Parasol Stars for a PC Engine and they wanted like a bunch of money for it which was retarded.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which was stupid.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry if I offended some retarded people out there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was trying to see if I could find the Taito Arcade Classics page, but I can't find it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's an older game, so it's probably harder to find.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I don't want to hear anything about Pokemans.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you jealous?
[SPEAKER_07]: I've already heard about Pokemans from when Shane was playing through Pokemans.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's all old news.
[SPEAKER_06]: I find it fascinating how many people are going to get Pokemon Black and White on the 3DS even though you can play it on a DS Lite but because the launch lineup for 3DS is not as strong as it could have been there's a lot of people that want to use Pokemon to kind of fill in the gap Pokemon fans are pretty rabid so it's a big day for a lot of people Dan has announced that we are waiting for Star Fox to get our 3DS and I want Kid Icarus
[SPEAKER_06]: GameDevStory GameDevStory GameDevStory GameDevStory
[SPEAKER_04]: and so you can develop games and stuff like that and I'm just kicking ass at it and it's kind of funny though because
[SPEAKER_04]: It takes place during pre-Nintendo and stuff like that, but there's all these different systems with different names that are supposed to be those consoles, like the Nintendo IES or the Neon Geon, stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have my company, Orange Lounge, here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me go over some of the past products that we have put out and that have sold well.
[SPEAKER_04]: And of course, everything is really inappropriate, so that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: One of our first games, Two Girls, One Cup, sold 847,000 units.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, that's early on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pokemans, we put out a game called Pokemans, sold 2.7 million units.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some of the other more popular games, Fucked Your Mom, 4 million units, Pokemon 3, 11 million, You Is Stupid, which is our You Don't Know Jack game.
[SPEAKER_04]: and then of course I ripped off other things obviously since Nintendo doesn't exist so we have Mario RPG as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pokemon Online, 54 million copies.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then of course our last music game DDR, Olarmy, 46 million.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's on our console, the glory hole, because they happen to be watching the soup at the time.
[SPEAKER_04]: And our console is kicking the PlayStation's ass.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: I gotta do a quick correction, so I apologize.
[SPEAKER_06]: I blended my companies together.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Rygar and Tecmo Bowl, of course, are in the Tecmo Classic Arcade Collection, not Taito.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry, a very similar sounding in my arcade classic knowledge failed me for a moment, but there's Tecmo Classic Arcade.
[SPEAKER_06]: That is the one that is backwards compatible.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bomb Jack, Rygar, Tecmo Bowl, Solomon's Key, lots of awesome ones.
[SPEAKER_06]: There is a separate game called Tidal Legends.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't remember if this one was backwards compatible, but this was the one that had like the Bubble Bobble, Space Invaders, Elevator Action, New Zealand Story, and some of those games.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, oops!
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm getting old, sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: And these games are how many years old?
[SPEAKER_04]: And funny enough, Frisbee, uh, Fucked Your Mom, the sequel, Fucked Your Dad, that is actually the sequel, so, uh, pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, you know, but the game, it's all, like, done in pixel art, and it's, um, it's pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: You basically, you hire people, fire people, you train them, that you can, uh, eventually get, like, uh, you can go to E3, or, I think they call it Game Dex, it's like, uh, Comdex, um,
[SPEAKER_06]: SSJ100 Matt wants to know what theyplay.com Snap is selling.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's an old school by the way.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't have that game yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: We may have to develop that game.
[SPEAKER_04]: But we just put out Call of Duty and sold 7 million units in the first week.
[SPEAKER_06]: And don't forget my dream game for the Xbox Live Indie Arcade would be Granny's Got a Gun.
[SPEAKER_06]: Granny's Got a Gun.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's the Golden Girls with machine guns.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, and it's great though because you can see what your console, how it's doing and stuff in the marketplace.
[SPEAKER_04]: They even have the Virtual Boy.
[SPEAKER_04]: and all the console stuff since we kind of know what's going on with the game industry and everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like, okay, here comes the virtual kid.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a 3D handheld or 3D portable.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think I'll be developing on that because I think it's going away really fast.
[SPEAKER_04]: And sure enough, it goes away really fast.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just like the other ones.
[SPEAKER_04]: Instead of the Saturn, it's the Uranus.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yeah, it's pretty fun Definitely worth picking up Game Dev Story And they have the new one They don't have it over here yet But they have some spa sim They have the spa sim over here Which is kind of dumb But they have a game store It's called the Game Dealer And you play like a GameStop type thing It's a similar game, Dev Story I've heard about that But yeah, definitely, Game Dev Story Check it out, it's awesome Alright
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, and then other things.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course, of course.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wouldn't be a week on OLR without Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_06]: In fact, was that what you were playing a minute ago that was in like debug mode or something where you had the flying ice cream truck?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, that was the PC version.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm working on mod stuff for it because I've edited the water and everything to create this kind of a hydro thunder type track thing in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm building, I've done the water part of it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Called Ice Cream Thunder.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Jack in the Box Jack in the Box
[SPEAKER_04]: No, but you can... Some other map edit stuff I was working on, I was doing some tweaks to the physics of the bus and the ambulance, and so now I can clear Central Park with a ramp, which is awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: That bus moves fast.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: They need to bring back something like hard drive and modernize it with more stunts.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, I guess you could say, well, like, Burnout or whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that would technically be... Well, yeah, I mean, like, I understand.
[SPEAKER_04]: As far as, like, that game Stunts, I guess that would be Trackmania.
[SPEAKER_04]: It would be kind of similar to Stunts.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah, Trackmania.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, you know, as far as, like, a simulation racing game like that, I don't think they have that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, but hey, you know, EA, Need for Speed, you know, maybe some Need for Speed stunt game or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_06]: A lot of the same stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: I haven't really invested a lot in new games lately.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was tempted the other day, though, man.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Dreamcast Collection with Space Channel 5 Part 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: Crazy Taxi and Sonic Adventure, which are already out on Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I didn't because I figured the game I really, really want, it'll come out on Xbox Live Arcade eventually.
[SPEAKER_06]: And if I really, really, really wanted to play it, I could probably just borrow, you know, Alan's copy or Jamie's copy or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: So...
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll just wait a little longer for some choo-choo in Space Channel 5 Part 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: As far as games I actually did play, went back, today I was feeling really old school for some reason.
[SPEAKER_06]: I went back and played Bionic Commando Rearmed because I was going through my Xbox games because I bought a lot of arcade games back in the day and I was like,
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, you can't forget.
[SPEAKER_06]: Especially for you folks who are just now getting Xbox 360s.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think sometimes you can get a little bit distracted by all the arcade games that are out there now.
[SPEAKER_06]: But seriously, there's a lot of old school stuff that's really pretty good out on Xbox Live Marketplace.
[SPEAKER_06]: So do your research because...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, as far as other games I played this week, I did check out the demo for one new game, Beyond Good and Evil HD, which is of course the big Xbox Live title that came out this week, which made a lot of people really excited because the original game has lots and lots and lots of fans, and
[SPEAKER_06]: Let me admit something to you guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: I never really played the original.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know, I know it was like a huge game, had its fans on PC, PS2.
[SPEAKER_06]: Again, I think the original kind of came out during a time where I wasn't, either I was way too hardcore into the music games where I was missing a lot of this stuff, or I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just, you know, there's not enough time in the day to play everything, so I missed this the first time around.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I checked it out this time, and I at least played through the demo, and I was left wanting to get the full version.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: So having not played the original, I can't sit here and profess to know a lot about what they upgraded, but I will tell you it was widescreen.
[SPEAKER_06]: It definitely seemed like there was a lot of water effects that seemed to be somewhat new, and everything seemed to be very, very smooth.
[SPEAKER_06]: It did kind of look like an up-resed PlayStation 2 game, but that's okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, I hear a lot of people are really drawn to this game because of the story, and I know this game really throws you in right away.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: having to play the first 30 minutes or so in the demo was nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I will check out more of that if I don't get too distracted by Torchlight next week because that is the Xbox Live game I am waiting for.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love the PC one.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm so excited to see how it translates to console.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm really worried I'm getting my expectations way too high that I'm going to be just left disappointed next week.
[SPEAKER_06]: But hopefully I can fit in Beyond Good and Evil HD too.
[SPEAKER_07]: According to GameGuru, Space Channel 5 is on Steam.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, it did.
[SPEAKER_06]: It came out, I believe, over the weekend on Steam.
[SPEAKER_06]: It just kind of suddenly showed up.
[SPEAKER_06]: So yeah, if you want to check that out on the PC, that'd be cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, so that was pretty much it for my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Those two games and some of the usual stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: WoW and some other PC games and so forth.
[SPEAKER_06]: Super Meat Boy, getting frustrated.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tried some of those new levels that we were talking about a couple weeks ago on the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Couldn't even beat one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Couldn't even beat stage one on some of those really hard ones.
[SPEAKER_06]: Disgusting.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's get into some housekeeping and then we will get into the gaming news for tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not a lot to say for housekeeping except DarkSakura sadly will not be joining us next week, but there will still be an OLR.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki and I will be here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Perhaps a guest host.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_07]: I will be in a car.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, you're going far away.
[SPEAKER_07]: Far, far away.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hope you have fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't go too far that you can't come back.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because we can go one week, but I don't know about two weeks.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not be back.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Join us on Twitter, twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can join us on Facebook, facebook.com slash Orange Laundry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Speaking of Twitter, I'm peeking at it a little early tonight, and I thought this was a really funny tweet from Defective Candy sent us a tweet.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know I'm getting to Twitter early, so shoot me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Introducing OLR to seven of my friends tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're partying it up with some old school Unreal LAN partying and tuning in.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, shout out to you guys at the LAN party.
[SPEAKER_06]: That sounds pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Kicking it old school with Unreal.
[SPEAKER_06]: Back in the day, this might be a little more even old school than Unreal, but back in the day we used to get together and play Quake.
[SPEAKER_06]: That used to be kind of the big thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is like way before MMOs and all that.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'd get together and play Quake like online.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was just a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: My first LAN was Duke Nukem 3D.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh yeah?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I used to do that on the modem, the dial-up thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: Duke Nukem and Command & Conquer Red Alert were fun over the modem.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, I hope you guys are having fun and thanks for spreading the word of the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: I appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, let's get to the news.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Loki's going to start us off tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Much busier week than last week, that's for sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it helps to have stuff going on and conferences and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_04]: We did talk about this a little bit, that it was a possibility, especially with LG suing Sony over the Blu-ray technology.
[SPEAKER_04]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: I only know what that's supposed to do for 10 days.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently, the consoles collected are temporarily being held in Dutch warehouses until the case moves forward.
[SPEAKER_04]: But right now, they're expected to...
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess retailers are expected to have enough PS3s the last 2 or 3 weeks so you may not necessarily see any shortages or something like that you may if this case goes further and they end up winning everything because somebody's going to have to pay them some money
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you think maybe that's just what's going to ultimately happen, is that this all gets settled out of court to stop this from happening?
[SPEAKER_06]: It all depends.
[SPEAKER_04]: 90% of the game lawsuit stories end up settled out of court.
[SPEAKER_04]: It all depends whether they feel they're in the right or not.
[SPEAKER_04]: If Sony knows that they have no chance at winning this, then they probably won't fight it, but...
[SPEAKER_04]: If they think that they're in the right and they don't need to pay them any royalties or whatever, they're going to fight it because it saves them money if they don't have to pay these royalties on every single console shipped.
[SPEAKER_06]: How damaging is this to Sony, do you think?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I look at this and go, well, if they can't ship it to stores, are stores still okay for a little bit because stores have what's on hand?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just a shortage for 10 days.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's no big deal.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not like the PlayStation 3 has a must-have game coming out this week or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: People deal with shortages on stuff for a lot longer than 10 days.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, look at the Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's just fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: I doubt this will make any sort of impact.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just everybody likes reporting on this stuff because, ha-ha, Sony's getting their taste of legal battles since they're suing GeoHot and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, it's just...
[SPEAKER_04]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can't say this is so much a patent troll thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, this is not.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, well we'll see what comes of this.
[SPEAKER_06]: The legal team at Sony working overtime these next couple weeks for sure.
[SPEAKER_06]: Big, big gaming news and kind of always divisive when I talk about Apple.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Apple did announce the iPad 2 is coming out March 11th and you bet this is gaming news because...
[SPEAKER_06]: A lot of folks are gaming on the Apple these days with the iPhone and the iOS.
[SPEAKER_06]: Big, big system.
[SPEAKER_06]: Controversial, too, if you want to get into the whole fact that they charge very little for the games on the iPhone.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some people have a problem with that, as we learned at GDC this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: but I digress iPad 2 was announced this week it is coming out on March 11th it will cost you anywhere between $629 and $829 if you want a unit with 3G lowest you can go though is $499 if you want the Wi-Fi Wi-Fi only up to $699 just throwing it out there too if you wanted to get the original iPad those are now sliced in price by $100 so those are now out as well
[SPEAKER_06]: Some of the big things that are supposed to be coming out with the iPad 2, it's not just the fancy colors, but of particular interest is this cable that will allow you to hook up the iPad to your television and get the output in 1080p display, which is making a lot of people very excited.
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course, streaming movies that are on the device makes it very easy to bypass the Apple TV and so forth in order to do that.
[SPEAKER_06]: But a lot of people also wondering, could this have some feature for games going with it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Where you could use the cord to have the iPad as a control device for something on your TV?
[SPEAKER_04]: Angry Birds HD No, I mean, who wants to be tethered to a TV?
[SPEAKER_04]: Unless they have some sort of wireless thing, it's not
[SPEAKER_06]: Which quite frankly I'm surprised they don't through the whole Apple TV thing They may later on They can stream stuff through Apple TV and it could be something that comes through iOS later on We did have the story last week or two weeks ago about the whole people were playing PS3 games through the iOS was a whole thing that had been set up The technology is getting there and that has nothing to do with Apple themselves That was kind of a
[SPEAKER_06]: Filed in the Hack and Crack bin
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but that's a little in the reverse.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's not necessarily... I mean, playing PlayStation 1 emulated games, that's through the actual system that's running that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But streaming stuff from the PlayStation 3, though, that's a little bit different.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's just streaming video.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I mean, I'm sure that the... Obviously, since the iPad 2 is a dual-core system, I'm sure it can handle streaming stuff, but...
[SPEAKER_04]: As far as the Apple TV goes, that thing is just like an Intel Atom little box.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think it has enough oomph to do 1080p.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's capped at 720p because I think that's what iTunes is.
[SPEAKER_06]: The ones that are out there now, yeah, 720p.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let me throw this question out there to you guys here in studio and the chat room at chat.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's been a lot of talk this week with this news and in the game blogs and so forth about the 3DS, which we'll get into some of that news in a little while, and the iPad 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_06]: What do you guys kind of think?
[SPEAKER_06]: Does the 3DS really have to worry about iPad 2 or vice versa?
[SPEAKER_06]: Or do these things kind of coexist and neither really has to really worry about the other?
[SPEAKER_06]: So why are they dogging on each other?
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's the latter, but you know how companies are.
[SPEAKER_07]: They like to look for drama where there isn't.
[SPEAKER_07]: And on top of that, the rivalry is only good for both of them.
[SPEAKER_07]: Establishing some type of farcical rivalry.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Unfortunately, Nintendo will never be able to compete with Apple as far as their online marketplace goes because their online marketplace is open.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's an open marketplace for all these developers to basically create these games, submit them, get approval, and then they are up on the marketplace really quickly.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's why you get like...
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, but see, that's what Nintendo needs, because, unfortunately, you're never gonna be able to compete the level with these guys if you're just releasing, like, three games a week, you know, on that.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, I'm sorry, but, you know, the virtual console stuff...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Cut the Rope, the stuff that's really good on iOS, of which there isn't much, but there are some really, really good games on there.
[SPEAKER_04]: There are good games on the iOS platform, and it's just some of these games that people just decide that they like.
[SPEAKER_04]: Angry Birds, I don't think is a great game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a game that's popular.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, Sam's Frustrating Game is what it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the public disagrees.
[SPEAKER_06]: Public's dumb.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's selling very well.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think it's all that either.
[SPEAKER_06]: I prefer Cut the Rope.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I can say, okay, it's selling like... But exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you know what, though?
[SPEAKER_04]: I wouldn't be surprised.
[SPEAKER_04]: And there's no reason why they can't have Angry Birds on the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right now, on the DSi.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why can't they have Angry Birds on there?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it should be able to run.
[SPEAKER_04]: PSP has it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was a download game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It didn't... I mean, it came out way later.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, I mean...
[SPEAKER_04]: That's even the problem with the PSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: Their little online stuff, it's so closed that they just can't get games fast enough.
[SPEAKER_04]: They need to really open it up.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I think the closest thing to the App Store is probably the Xbox Indie games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because your lease is there, you're seeing a lot of games coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Granted, a lot of them are crap, but that's the same with the App Store.
[SPEAKER_04]: A lot of it is crap.
[SPEAKER_04]: But if you open it up...
[SPEAKER_04]: A lot more stuff comes out.
[SPEAKER_04]: And yeah, you're going to get a lot of crappy games, but you're also going to get a lot of good games.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if you're smart and know how to highlight those good games and know how to push that platform forward, then that is good for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: The problem with Nintendo, though, is if they do that and they start pushing that platform forward...
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's going to want to pay $50 for a game?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because then they can just get some really quality games for like 99 cents or a few bucks instead of $50.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why should I pay $50 for a 3DS game like Zelda?
[SPEAKER_00]: Because it's 3D!
[SPEAKER_00]: So what if it's 3D?
[SPEAKER_04]: It doesn't mean that those digital download games aren't 3D.
[SPEAKER_04]: They could easily program for 3D.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just like there's going to be indie games that are going to support the Kinect eventually once they open it up for everybody.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why should I have to pay that kind of money?
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's what they're complaining about.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're complaining about the fact that they think that these games are devaluing their games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, why do you think that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because obviously if you think your games are so much better...
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's go to comments from our chat room.
[SPEAKER_06]: Chat.OrangeLawnTrader.com for some comments.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkTitsuya says, I think Nintendo's just jealous because they can't keep releasing all new hardware after a year the way Apple seems to.
[SPEAKER_06]: They don't need to.
[SPEAKER_06]: They do, but they do.
[SPEAKER_06]: The DS Lite, the DS Lite in new colors, the DSi.
[SPEAKER_06]: The XL.
[SPEAKER_06]: As of lately, I would say they have been doing something new every year.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, the XL.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: But see, that's even retarded too, because what's the point of making the system larger?
[SPEAKER_04]: How is this supposed to drive sales for you guys?
[SPEAKER_04]: I never understood that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's make a portable system larger now.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: Why?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just like, oh, let's make the Game Boy Micro.
[SPEAKER_06]: GameGuru says Nintendo pretty much dumped every game they do own on the virtual console.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or at least, well, every game they could dump.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess maybe a dig at EarthBound, because the whole trouble's there.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're not thinking...
[SPEAKER_04]: The problem is they're a few steps behind when it comes to embracing online.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're not where these first party companies are.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're not supporting download content as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why aren't there downloadable tracks for Mario Kart?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's stupid simple.
[SPEAKER_04]: You could easily just put out all... Because the Wii can't handle it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I know it can.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Wii can handle it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But see, the problem with the Wii, though, is because they, you know...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: So if it's that easy, open it up like Mod Nation Racers.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my god, you've got a community of people that are excited about a game.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can even start charging for some download content, different tools and stuff that you can put in there like LittleBigPlanet.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can make money off this.
[SPEAKER_04]: The problem is they need to change their stupid business model in order for it to work.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry, but I just don't see them ever embracing online like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let me ask you this and then kind of try to close to this thought because I want to come, believe it or not, I want to come back to the Wii thing later in the show because I have another question about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: But let me ask this.
[SPEAKER_06]: You say they need to change their business model, but at the same time, numbers say they have the number one console in America, period.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, so why do they need to change their business model?
[SPEAKER_06]: They're number one.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hate it.
[SPEAKER_06]: You hate it.
[SPEAKER_06]: We all hate it, but they are number one for right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, that's the problem.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a cocky attitude though.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you say, oh, but we're number one, we can do whatever the hell we want.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's great until Apple decides to put out a console and then they have this app store and you can download all these games for 99 cents.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or let's just say that they're iPad prices and it's like two bucks a game or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry, but a lot of people, there are a lot of good games out there that are on these marketplaces, even like the Android marketplace and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not everybody really wants you to spend the kind of development time that it costs for a $50 game.
[SPEAKER_04]: For example, a perfect example...
[SPEAKER_04]: Excite Truck.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love that game.
[SPEAKER_04]: That game is awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: All they needed to do was release download content for it or a sequel that had basically the same style of gameplay, just more track.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not Excite Bots.
[SPEAKER_04]: Excite Bots was... I don't even know what the hell they were doing.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I know Nintendo was behind that kind of crap.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, you know what would be better?
[SPEAKER_04]: If we made some more minigames in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: It does not belong... Minigames do not belong in a racing game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's really, really stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: All they had to do was download content.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they could have still made some money on top of that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Games like that, even if they have download content, do not devalue their sequels when they come out.
[SPEAKER_04]: So what if there's good download content for that?
[SPEAKER_04]: People will be more willing to buy the next game because they know they're going to be supporting download content on top of that.
[SPEAKER_04]: or hell, you can put out the game for a cheaper cost and then have in-game downloads or something like that you can add to it and increase value that way.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's just so many ways that they could do it but they don't want to because you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: People don't download games.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what they think.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I think Apple would disagree with you on that.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, let me ask this question.
[SPEAKER_06]: How do you kind of feel about Nintendo right now?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I do notice you're looking at eBay on your computer looking for 3DSs right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a part of you that must... There's something Nintendo's doing right for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I just get every console, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: That doesn't even necessarily... And I was just looking to see if anybody's actually offering up a Japanese system for a decent price.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry, but even though $350 is a good price for a Japanese console, and it is in California, although his reserve price is probably $500, so screw that.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know me, I like getting stuff early.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways, but no, I'm not actually going to probably buy that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will buy a 3DS when it comes out because I think it's a cool technology, but I got to be honest, the launch lineup is very disappointing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm like sitting there going, looking at the tiles coming out, I'm like, well, I'll pick up Pilotwings because that looks fun, but it's like, and then Nintendo's like, but we have Steel Diver.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a 2D submarine game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, you know, that's neat, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or like, you know, hey, we have Nintendogs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Arf, arf, and cats.
[SPEAKER_04]: Meow, meow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nintendogs and cats.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or, hey, hey, hey, we've got Ocarina of Time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, I was reading the news articles.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, my God, Master Quest is in Ocarina of Time for the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's so amazing.
[SPEAKER_06]: GameGuru says, your Mario Kart example doesn't work.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nintendo only makes one Mario Kart per system.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm talking about other consoles though.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is even bad now as far as the trend goes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember before with Mario Kart for the GameCube I think was the first one they did?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like, oh look, we've got some of the older tracks in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: A little bit of retro nostalgia there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Game Boy Advance Super Nintendo Nostalgia
[SPEAKER_04]: and now all of them do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Half the tracks are all old tracks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Come on, man.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's lazy right there.
[SPEAKER_06]: You have to admit, Rainbow Road's pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have Rainbow... But yeah, I understand it's really sweet, but there's a new Rainbow Road in every game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not necessary to put in one of the...
[SPEAKER_04]: Mario Circuit Tracks from the Game Boy Advance and my 3DS version or something like that they just have such potential a track editor would be so awesome but they'll never do it because they're afraid that people will
[SPEAKER_06]: Drive Mario into a fire repeatedly over and over again
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: Come on, people.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mario Kart's a cool game and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even your Mario games are fun or Zelda or whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: But if you throw in some sort of community aspect to it, people get really excited about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think that's going to speak a lot louder than...
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh hey, we put out a Mario Kart game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I know you're going to put out a Mario Kart game on the 3S.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're also going to put out a Mario Kart game on the next console you put out.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, that's dumb.
[SPEAKER_04]: In a Zelda game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, we know that's coming.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'd be dumb to think otherwise.
[SPEAKER_04]: But they have such potential, they just really are squandering it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura's been waiting to talk about her next story.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've given up.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm looking at Monday through Friday.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: More to come later though.
[SPEAKER_06]: We haven't finished the Nintendo news yet and I've got another killer question for Loki in a little bit here on the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: GameStop has yet another class action lawsuit.
[SPEAKER_07]: We've gotten a lot of money from GameStop because of employee stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: And apparently now people should be getting more... Anyone who's bought anything ever from GameStop, actually, that used their credit card to buy it, should be getting their $5.
[SPEAKER_07]: because apparently they acquire additional personal information including the cardholder's physical residential address by pairing the personal identification information with the cardholder's name obtained from the credit card.
[SPEAKER_07]: So basically, you swipe your card, they get all your info.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not saying what they're doing with it, but they're supposedly doing it against your knowledge.
[SPEAKER_07]: But here's the thing, everywhere that you use your credit card does that without your knowledge.
[SPEAKER_07]: So this is me, we're going to have class action lawsuits against the grocery store and the porn shop and...
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think it's necessarily that I think it's more because you have to put in all your personal info for like trades or whatever that they're basically saying okay this person here's this person and this person paid here's their name okay we're going to link their card number to this address now which is not good especially if that information just kind of gets leaked out I'm sure those GameStop employees are very trustworthy as far as you know
[SPEAKER_04]: Minimum wage, that has a lot of trust built into it.
[SPEAKER_06]: They kind of should have some people's addresses on file, though, for the people that like to sell back stolen games.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's the point, too, is that I think that it's a good idea.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, I don't see any problem with it as long as they're not selling it, and if you're on the opt-out list, then they can't.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um...
[SPEAKER_07]: Identity theft sucks and so forth.
[SPEAKER_07]: This isn't something that... Unless someone actually breaks into a database that all of their stuff is uploaded to and steals the information directly out of the database, I don't think that there's much of a problem.
[SPEAKER_06]: William Murderface in our chatroom says, so GameStop wants to troll me?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know how to react.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ranma in our chatroom says, I hate when I swipe my card.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some terminals require your zip code and you can't continue your transaction without it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Isn't that a credit card protection thing?
[SPEAKER_06]: Like at Chevron, a gas station, I don't know if those are everywhere.
[SPEAKER_06]: But at Chevron, when I do the swipe, it always makes me put in my zip code because that's how it knows that I'm... Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently it's illegal, but I still don't see what the big deal is.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because it's not like they can actually go out and sell your information without your permission.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or they have to let you know that they're doing it.
[SPEAKER_07]: If this is just something that automatically pops up, especially if they need to do consumer tracking, I don't see what the big problem is.
[SPEAKER_07]: I really don't.
[SPEAKER_07]: Even... I mean, I really... I think that people are just being paranoid.
[SPEAKER_07]: Really.
[SPEAKER_07]: So if you want to get your $5, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's all you're going to get.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe $1.50.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the other thing with these class action lawsuits is that, well, you know, even though you might go, eh, GameStop's getting sued, likely they'll settle out of court because that's the way these things tend to go.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, you know, it'll be like $2 to those that send in a form that swear on an affidavit that their privacy was breached or whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, it'll be interesting to see how that goes.
[SPEAKER_06]: So...
[SPEAKER_06]: Marisa Congusto in our chatroom says, gas stations are allowed to do this because they do not store it for marketing.
[SPEAKER_06]: We just discussed this in Business Law the other day.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't think that they keep it for marketing either.
[SPEAKER_07]: Really?
[SPEAKER_07]: We bought stuff at GameStop and never gotten offers and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I've never been spammed by them or what have you.
[SPEAKER_07]: We only ever got coupons and stuff when we had a subscription to Game Informer and it came with our magazine.
[SPEAKER_06]: I am spammed by them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you?
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you sign up for their little card though?
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe that's why.
[SPEAKER_04]: I signed up for their card, and then I get two emails from them every week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I told them, like, I'm on your mailing list twice.
[SPEAKER_04]: You need to take me off there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Never happened.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then I also get, oh, hey, you know, you can get this special, you know, this is for GameStop people only.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a special survey thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: You go fill out surveys and you get cash.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like, stop bothering me with that crap.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ram on our chatroom says, when I swipe my CC to refill my MetroCard, it asks for verification that I get, but not when I'm in Kmart.
[SPEAKER_06]: It asks every single time.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's not credit card protecting.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're pulling for where people live.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, Kohl's does that, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: They always ask your zip code.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is actually illegal to ask that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's for demographic information.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's still legal to ask that.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's actually a... I never said it wasn't.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can't you just say no?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, you can say no.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then they don't... You can tell them you don't want to give it, and that can't stop them from...
[SPEAKER_06]: Most of those people that are working there anyway will just be like, alright, whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: What they'll do, they'll just put in a different zip code.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what I bet most of them do.
[SPEAKER_06]: You tell them no, they just make up a zip code.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know that's what's happening.
[SPEAKER_06]: Most of the people on the front lines like that don't care.
[SPEAKER_06]: I sometimes feel bad for them because then they're the ones that take the brunt of all this hatred towards the collecting and so forth.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_06]: More news.
[SPEAKER_06]: Release dates coming up with Classic Game of the Week as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: So this is interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: BurgerTime HD, or as I like to call it, BurgerTime Galaxy, because that's certainly what it looks like.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's being developed, I guess, by Monkey Paw Games.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's coming out on PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, Wii, and PC, I'm guessing as part of their digital platforms, PlayStation Network, Xbox Live, WiiWare.
[SPEAKER_04]: and they're introducing new monsters or I guess carrots, apple cores, hot peppers, oversized monsters and other fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: They actually had some video online of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Looks interesting though.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can actually play it multiplayer, split screen, which is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yeah, it definitely looks like BurgerTime Galaxy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: I do love me some BurgerTime, the old school 80s machine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you see the video of it?
[SPEAKER_06]: I haven't actually watched it yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is it on YouTube?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can pull it up here real quick for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: We need to be more prepared.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let me see if I can find it here on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_04]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: BurgerTime HD level complete gameplay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's take a look at this here.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just got to make sure there's no commercial.
[SPEAKER_06]: Holy moly.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like running around this 3D-looking circle thing, like all the levels have been changed into this giant cylinder.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a very different look for the game, but it's kind of the same damn game.
[SPEAKER_06]: At least at first glance.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, there's this co-op thing going on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, it's not the same game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: I do see where you're getting BurgerTime Galaxy, absolutely.
[SPEAKER_06]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_06]: That looks like it could be interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll have to look at the demo for that when that comes out.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was an old school 80s game I really liked.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm curious how the co-op works.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's something else.
[SPEAKER_06]: You guys want to see it?
[SPEAKER_06]: I just typed BurgerTimeHD into YouTube.
[SPEAKER_06]: It came right up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, speaking of guilty pleasure games, this is one of my biggest guilty pleasure games ever and it's been so long since I've played one of these games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mortal Kombat.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mortal Kombat 9 or really it's the reboot, just Mortal Kombat is coming out soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_06]: Next week, March 8th, by the time some of you guys hear this, here's the catch.
[SPEAKER_06]: You've got to be a PlayStation Plus member because they are the ones that are getting the demo first.
[SPEAKER_06]: You'll be able to play a Scorpion, Sub-Zero, Mileena, and Johnny Cage in the Living Forest or the Fire Pit.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: Most fighting game demos only have two characters, so it's kind of neat that they have four.
[SPEAKER_06]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: One or two players.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm imagining not online, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: The other cool news is that not just the demo on March 8th for PlayStation Plus, but everybody will get it March 15th.
[SPEAKER_06]: So if you're like, I don't really want to sign up for PlayStation Plus, you can just wait one more week and you'll be able to get it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I should say this though.
[SPEAKER_06]: That is only on PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_06]: They do not have a firm date for when Xbox Live is getting it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just later.
[SPEAKER_06]: Could be a lot closer to the game's release in that regard.
[SPEAKER_06]: Very curious about that.
[SPEAKER_06]: by the way also a small follow-up on Mortal Kombat 9 I don't know if you guys heard but it was banned in Australia because they refused to rate the game and when they refuse to rate a game that basically means that the game is banned well the publishers behind Mortal Kombat they are appealing this decision we'll see just how far they get with it so
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see before the game's release.
[SPEAKER_06]: Either way, it's probably going to end up getting delayed in Australia.
[SPEAKER_06]: Probably a lot of people just going to import the damn thing from somewhere else.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll probably be out there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Even though that's supposed to be illegal as well, I don't see them exactly banging down doors because people got bootleg copies of Mortal Kombat.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if it has to be bootleg, I'm sure that you can just import it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Most of those games are region free.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't mean like actual bootlegs.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean like, you know, PlayStation 3 is region free.
[SPEAKER_06]: So there'll probably be lots of people just...
[SPEAKER_06]: Hitting up Amazon or something, getting a friend in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_06]: to buy it and then ship it to him.
[SPEAKER_06]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, also, on Mortal Kombat, one other thing, I remember reading a story about this this week, I wanted to throw this out there, is that there's this whole challenge mode in it, too, and I remember watching a video for it on YouTube, and they were all talking all excited about this, where, I guess, like, 300 levels, and they say you get something super special if you get all the way to the end, I'm assuming you unlock a bonus character or something, that's just my assumption, but it's like all these cool modifiers, like, there's some modifiers, like, Headless Kombat, where you fight with no head, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: kind of reminds me of some old tacky fighting games upside down mode where the image is flipped upside down and that's how you have to play I just thought it was kind of funny so 300 levels though that might be overkill I don't know about that that's going to take a serious investment to get through but we'll see
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_07]: Does that make sense?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because I think I might have drunk a little too much Chimay and it's baffling me.
[SPEAKER_06]: It actually kind of does.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a lot of people that wait to buy a use to just save the $5 because it's cheaper.
[SPEAKER_06]: I could see this.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's some people that sell back their games fast too.
[SPEAKER_06]: I picked up Tron Evolution maybe a week after it was out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now I realize why someone sold it back so quick.
[SPEAKER_06]: But some games you can get pretty quick that way.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, ones they already have on...
[SPEAKER_06]: Wait, wait, oh, Dan, you gotta say that on the air.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hold on, Dan.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's that, Dan?
[SPEAKER_01]: GameCrazy fucking did that for free.
[SPEAKER_06]: How so?
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, you just could put your name on a list?
[SPEAKER_01]: Like, you could come in and say, hey, can you give me a call when this game comes in used?
[SPEAKER_01]: And they did it.
[SPEAKER_01]: But they went out of business.
[SPEAKER_06]: And why did they go out of business?
[SPEAKER_01]: Because Hollywood Entertainment sucked.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sorry to hear it.
[SPEAKER_07]: At any rate, some of the games on the list already are Crysis 2, Homefront Dragon Age 2, Shift 2 Unleashed, and Tiger Woods PGA Tour 12.
[SPEAKER_07]: So yeah, you can pay five pounds and save a game that's not out yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which we'll just go to show you, game stores will take your five dollars for anything.
[SPEAKER_07]: Someone probably had that copy, or when it comes out, they probably got that copy, said this game sucks, and, you know, spanked over it or something, and then took it back, and then you get the spank version.
[SPEAKER_07]: You get it christened with the love of another man.
[SPEAKER_06]: Be careful, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: This could be one of those games that you can't sell back, like DC Universe Online, One Unique Key.
[SPEAKER_06]: So be careful what you pre-order used.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think they've got a specific list for it.
[SPEAKER_06]: GameGuru in our chatroom says, oh great, GameStop is going to push pre-orders of used games now?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh no, no, no, this is Game in the UK.
[SPEAKER_06]: However, you know if it does well for them, it'll just get copied by everybody else.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, anyhow, let's travel around the world and look at some release dates and games that are coming out real soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, actually, today, Pokemon Black and White came out, so that's pretty exciting if you're a fan of the Pokemans.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which there are some real rabid fans of Pokemon out there that are over the age of 30.
[SPEAKER_04]: As on the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: This week I actually have a new Kinect game, U-Star 2 in the movies.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember U-Star was that camera green screen system that they were selling on TV that only worked with PC at one point.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wasn't there already a crappy game like that on 360 that had the vision camera like you in the movies or something?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that was a little different though.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was more of like you're doing mini games and then it puts you into the game or the movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: It makes a little short film.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is actually, it's like karaoke for movie lines.
[SPEAKER_04]: Basically, you recite movie lines and you can play different people in there and it will actually kind of...
[SPEAKER_04]: Crop the actor or actress out of the scene and it'll put you in their place.
[SPEAKER_04]: And so you can get scored for accuracy and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's neat, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: And there's certainly not a lot of Kinect games coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's on PlayStation 3 with Move support.
[SPEAKER_04]: You do need the PlayStation Eye camera, though, if you want to play that.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then, of course, on Xbox 360 for the Kinect.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dragon Age 2 PC, Playstation 3, Xbox 360 Wii, The One Million Dollar Pyramid
[SPEAKER_04]: Another TV show game.
[SPEAKER_04]: A couple MLB games this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: MLB 2011 The Show.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's on PlayStation 2, PS3, and the PlayStation Portable.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, MLB 2K11 on PS2, PS3, Xbox 360, Wii, DS, and PSP, I believe.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pets Bunnies Bunch on Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess it's gearing up for Easter.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um...
[SPEAKER_04]: What the hell is this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Beastly Frantic Photo?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think this is some sort of stupid application that ties into that crappy movie Beastly.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was going to say, there was a movie with Vanessa Hutchins that came out called Beastly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I think that's what this is.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have not heard of that, but that's kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yep, I think it's some sort of photo game, and it looks like crap.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's Vanessa Hudgens' Snap?
[SPEAKER_04]: It might be.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, they have a trailer for the movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't really care about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is Beastly like a knockoff of Twilight?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, it's a retelling of Beauty and the Beast.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: A modern day retelling of the fairy tale but not with the underground community The guy is suddenly turned ugly by some witch girl and he has to stay in his expensive penthouse
[SPEAKER_06]: Be Our Guest
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, just like how, you know, Little Red Riding Hood, I don't remember werewolves being in Little Red Riding Hood.
[SPEAKER_04]: I could be, it's been a while since I heard Little Red Riding Hood, but I don't remember werewolves being in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I don't think emo people were in there as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now they're making emo Snow White too.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, come on, the original Little Red Riding Hood, she gets eaten by the wolf and gets digested and dies.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: As should those types of movies.
[SPEAKER_04]: Atari's Greatest Hits Vol.
[SPEAKER_04]: 2 on Nintendo DS coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Phantom Brave, Heroes of the Hermuda Triangle for the PSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not the Bermuda, the Hermuda.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hermuda, like hermaphrodite.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also...
[SPEAKER_04]: What else we got here?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sims 3, Barnacle Bay on PC, in case you want to get your pirate on.
[SPEAKER_04]: For the Sims 3 there.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then some crappy Wii games, Maximum Racing, GP Classic Racing, and Maximum Racing, Dragon Sox.
[SPEAKER_04]: And just don't even bother, seriously.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then, because...
[SPEAKER_04]: and I gotta go on the rant mode about this but I'm sorry but like here we go just because Nintendo is so gracious for everybody for a limited time and this is the last time that they're reprinting this game from the Super Nintendo Super Mario All-Stars will be coming out one week from today
[SPEAKER_04]: The Limited Edition, oh my god, limited, going on eBay for $80 because, oh my god, I've never played a game that was on the Super Nintendo on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is coming out once again on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: Get it now before it goes away forever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Seriously, if you buy this, you're stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: You are stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just spend the money on the virtual console.
[SPEAKER_04]: Better yet, just buy the freaking Super Nintendo and the original game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, you don't need this limited soundtrack and a little art book.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just think your rants are funnier with Mario Brothers music in the background.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yeah, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what we have coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: But seriously though, they are taking you guys for fools.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, $30 for a Super Nintendo game.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's next, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to have like Game Boy Advance, you know, Mario Land or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're going to put no new color in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're not going to do shit to it.
[SPEAKER_06]: In fact, they're not even going to change, you know... Aren't all those going to be coming on the 3DS?
[SPEAKER_06]: The virtual console, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're not doing shit to them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nothing at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they're going to charge tons of money for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what you can buy a Game Boy for nowadays?
[SPEAKER_04]: Probably $30 including that stupid... Probably even less than that.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can probably find them dirt cheap at a garage sale.
[SPEAKER_04]: People don't even know what they are.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're trying to get rid of them.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't feed the beast.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a very beastly week in U.S.
[SPEAKER_04]: releases, apparently.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're just encouraging them.
[SPEAKER_04]: The message that you're sending loud and clear to Nintendo is, we like your old shit, please bring it back and charge us a lot of money for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all that they're doing.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: People are dumb because they're like, oh, Mario must buy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mario must buy.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, they can put out like,
[SPEAKER_04]: Mario teaches brain surgery or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mario's a wonderful douche.
People would buy it because it's got Mario in it.
You got it!
[SPEAKER_06]: The Mario!
[SPEAKER_06]: and novel thing that's been ported.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's been on the PS2, Windows, PSP, all this stuff before.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is coming out on the Xbox 360 as well now with some extra stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's, I guess, I don't even know if it's like an interactive anime or anything, but who knows?
[SPEAKER_06]: So yeah, that is coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Probably nothing that'll ever see the light of day over here, I gotta be honest.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I have heard something about an English translation patch on some of the other versions for those that are into it.
[SPEAKER_06]: On the PlayStation 3 coming out this week, there's an all-new console coming out in Japan this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it is a satin silver model.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not sure what is coming out to kind of drive the sales of that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know that Heavy Rain is getting a price reduction over there, and there is Shin Sangoku Musou 6 comes out this week as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's from Koei.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is this Dynasty Warriors 6?
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that what this is?
[SPEAKER_06]: and Rurouni Kenshin.
[SPEAKER_06]: Meiji, Kenkaku, Ramatan, Saisen comes out from Namco Bandai this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: What the crap are they doing another Kenshin game for?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because the public demands it?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: But there you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: That does it for your Japanese releases.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, for the UK, we have a few things.
[SPEAKER_07]: On the 9th is Torchlight.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then on the 11th, we have Brunswick Pro Bowling.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dragon Age 2, Homefront, and U-Star 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's move on with some more news and then the Classic Game of the Week is just up ahead.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh boy, can't wait for this next story.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, take it away.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, actually, just to go back real quick about my complaining about All-Stars.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, seriously, this is Nintendo we're talking about here.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's such a step backwards with this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Look at Smash Bros., once again.
[SPEAKER_04]: Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_04]: Brawl.
[SPEAKER_04]: Perfect example.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's how you treat a franchise as far as nostalgia purposes.
[SPEAKER_04]: They had demos for virtual console games on there for some of the old stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Animal Crossing is seriously one of the best games that's come out in the past 10 years.
[SPEAKER_06]: Honestly, it really is.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're talking the original.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not any of the sequel.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not any of them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not any of the re-releases.
[SPEAKER_06]: But the original is one of my favorite games to have come out in the past 10 years.
[SPEAKER_06]: Easily.
[SPEAKER_04]: Another perfect example, I might add, of a game that Nintendo has done absolutely nothing with.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Absolutely nothing with from game to game.
[SPEAKER_04]: How much really have they changed from each sequel?
[SPEAKER_04]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's basically the same damn game presented in a slightly different way.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I mean very slight.
[SPEAKER_04]: And most of the times, it's not a good way.
[SPEAKER_04]: Come on, we're seriously, we're just encouraging this crap.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, you got some Nintendo news to report for us, Loki?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways, so, we've got some interesting stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, this is all from Game Developers Conference.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're talking a little bit about the 3DS and some neat stuff, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, I mean, once again, you can't read too much into this because...
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, for example, the first part we have here, apparently the 3DS will have access to 10,000 AT&T Wi-Fi hotspots by late May.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why not at launch?
[SPEAKER_04]: Eh, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: But whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Late May.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, that's neat that they're embracing... Is that like all the airports?
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's gotta be like some restaurants have them.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Where do you find AT&T Wi-Fi hotspots?
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess just
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, but I know that when they're selling you on their internet and stuff, but you get access to all these for free as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Big whoop.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that how they're going to deliver the patches without asking?
[SPEAKER_06]: If you take your 3DS out in public, it finds an AT&T Wi-Fi hotspot, all of a sudden, whoop, patch.
[SPEAKER_04]: They don't, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have to agree to apply the patches.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: it's their way of saying we don't have 3GS but you'll be able to get online in public at all these places that's what it says to me and then of course the 3DS Virtual Console is basically getting all the portable platforms on top of I believe Game Boy and Game Boy Color they're getting Game Gear and
[SPEAKER_04]: and TurboGrafx-16 games because it's funny because TurboGrafx-16 played the actual console games on the handheld so you're going to be getting those games.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've got one of those.
[SPEAKER_07]: Turbo Express.
[SPEAKER_06]: How funny this whole NGP joke with the Neo Geo pocket comes forward.
[SPEAKER_06]: Never mind because TurboGrafx, not a Neo Geo.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fail.
[SPEAKER_06]: But
[SPEAKER_04]: But maybe in the future, who knows And I understand it's coming late May Why stop there?
[SPEAKER_04]: Why stop there?
[SPEAKER_04]: You have a virtual console You have virtual console stuff already out there For like Nintendo, Super Nintendo stuff Don't tell me this system can't play Nintendo games Or Genesis games Or Sega Master System games Once again This could be an open marketplace Like the iOS platforms Or Steam or something like that Where you can have a bunch of games on there
[SPEAKER_04]: Right for the picking so people can go, oh my god, I love playing the original Mario Brothers or I love playing Mario Kart 64 or something like that on my Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to take it with me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh damn, I have to buy it again.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, that's okay because I love Nintendo and I'll buy whatever they put out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Such a missed opportunity.
[SPEAKER_04]: They only have these portable games coming out for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's so frustrating that they could easily do this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nope, nope, sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're not going to do that right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whoa, but we may announce it later on, and people will be so grateful that we've allowed them to repurchase our game again.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ha, ha, ha.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, yeah, that will be coming out later on.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, it's just so frustrating because they're just dumb and yeah, late May, so if you buy your system when it comes out at launch, just know that you're not going to actually have access to their little service to purchase virtual console games nice
[SPEAKER_04]: and then also they're saying via the system update you're going to get some other online features that they were touting.
[SPEAKER_04]: The DSiWare service of course, the ability to transfer DSiWare games from the DSi or DSiXL to your system.
[SPEAKER_04]: The web browser and of course the eShop which will include the whole virtual console stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: So let me get this straight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Your console's not done.
[SPEAKER_04]: because that's what it sounds like to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: You don't have one of the advertised features, web browser and all that stuff, at launch.
[SPEAKER_04]: So your console's not done.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not ready.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're releasing it too early is what it sounds like.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that might explain why you don't have enough games out for it because you want to push this thing out to pad your fiscal year numbers.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because it's coming out at the very end of the month.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, I definitely think it's that.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think that they did the exact same thing with, um... Well, they did the exact same thing with the Wii, because they had, remember, the web browser, I believe, didn't come out right away.
[SPEAKER_04]: It got released later on.
[SPEAKER_04]: It wasn't, you know, too later on.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, we're only talking, like, you know, a month or two for this online shop thing, but...
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just, if they had it ready to go at launch, they could be making so much.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's time wasted and money lost because they could be selling a bunch of stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the fact that they're just like,
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, you know, we're just not going to put virtual console games on there because... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know why they're not putting actual virtual console stuff that's on there for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why don't they put Nintendo games or Super Nintendo games?
[SPEAKER_04]: They have all this stuff already done.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's already ready to go.
[SPEAKER_04]: And maybe they have to convert it over to something special or redo it for the 3DS, maybe.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're talking, like, emulators here.
[SPEAKER_04]: It can't be that difficult to port this stuff over.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: If the homebrew community can do it on the Game Boy Advance and the Nintendo DS, and this thing does support Nintendo DS games, it should be able to do this.
[SPEAKER_04]: It should have no problem doing this whatsoever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Unless they're going to do something cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because they said that, oh hey, we're going to release...
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, fuck.
[SPEAKER_04]: They may have all sucked, but still though, I mean, there's a lot of games that they release on the virtual console that did suck, but it's still a lot of people haven't gotten a chance to play them because that console is out for such a short amount of time.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then lastly, apparently all DSi, or almost all DSiWare games will be available at the 3DS eShop launch, and of course they have some limits as far as the transfers and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: It says, of course, we've got virtual console games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything that's rendered in 3D, converted into 3D, is called a 3D classic.
[SPEAKER_04]: So they're going to have some converted games, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it said that, I guess, downloadable games will be under the eShop banner.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're saying that...
[SPEAKER_04]: Pretty much the whole DSiWare lineup will be available at launch.
[SPEAKER_04]: There may be a few exceptions, but the majority of all the games will come over.
[SPEAKER_04]: A few games are being left off the 3DS's eShop for undisclosed reasons.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, they're saying it's not the number of transferred games.
[SPEAKER_04]: It would be the same... They're saying that the transfer feature will be coming in late May.
[SPEAKER_04]: And...
[SPEAKER_04]: they didn't say it would be the same game the number of times you can transfer it from device to device so if you build up a large category of DSiWare games you won't be penalized just how many times you can move it move that same group of games there'll be a limit on so I guess they're not saying the amount of games there's not going to be a limit on the amount of games you can move over but how many times you can move it so that's that's it hmm and
[SPEAKER_04]: if they were nice which they're not they would also allow you to do that same kind of transfer thing with the Wii and the virtual console stuff that you download but they're not to be fair I mean what Microsoft allows you to transfer it once a year and I don't even know Sony's thing aren't Sony's pretty locked down aren't they
[SPEAKER_04]: um you can transfer actually you can transfer quite a few times because they have people sharing stuff remember you can do it like five times that's right and that's per game um I I don't know it's
[SPEAKER_04]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, it is what it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's going to be a lot of disappointing stuff, I think, as far as how they support their online stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's unfortunately just... They could be making a lot more money than they are.
[SPEAKER_04]: If that's really what they're concerned about and making people happy and stuff, they could do it really easy.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're just not.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, well, let's move on from all the 3DS talk.
[SPEAKER_06]: Although, I am still excited about the 3D video, but I think you make a point.
[SPEAKER_06]: They gotta let you share it.
[SPEAKER_06]: But here's something that a lot of people are also very excited about.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, that feature alone makes the device worth a lot more than...
[SPEAKER_06]: And maybe that's why they're trying to rush it out, too, is because they want to get ahead of a lot of those cameras that are out there on the marketplace that are very expensive right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're trying to maybe get the jump on that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Cheap alternative.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow, I want to mention this because a lot of folks are excited about this.
[SPEAKER_06]: The game Catherine, which is coming out overseas, it is also coming out in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_06]: Summer of 2011 it is coming out this summer.
[SPEAKER_06]: PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a preview site already up.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can pre-order the game on Amazon.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: but give it time I'm sure that's details they want to keep under wraps until a little close to the release date but some folks still very excited about the release of that game alright since that game is coming out in a couple months let's talk about something that's coming out a long time ago it's the classic game of the week we like to take a trip down memory lane and talk about a classic video game that's been out for years and years and it's something that maybe you should be checking out
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura is going to step into the vault and find a game.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, what is the classic game of the week?
[SPEAKER_07]: Classic game of the week is Willow.
[SPEAKER_07]: And before people say, you've done Willow before, this is a different Willow.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is the side-scrolling arcade version of Willow.
[SPEAKER_06]: So not the NES RPG game many people remember that you have done before.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is the arcade version.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it was released by Capcom in the arcade and it's freaking hard.
[SPEAKER_07]: So basically this one's platformer.
[SPEAKER_07]: and it has six stages where Willow gets to go kick some butt and sometimes you can play Mad Mardigan and you basically it's typical platformer left or right to move press the A button to use a weapon you can
[SPEAKER_07]: Hold it down and fire charge shots, you've got magic power gauge, you have a B button to jump, and you can go up ledges and do all kinds of stuff, you can climb down them, and you can open chests, and you can get gold and buy items from the Owl Mage, and buy all kinds of stuff, including a life pack, a 1-up, and information.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, um, it's pretty hard.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love the music in it, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: Can you play a little bit of that, Rob?
[SPEAKER_07]: Isn't that good?
[SPEAKER_07]: Neat.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was a really pretty game, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the only version that was out was the arcade one.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was a CPS1 game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Pretty much you could fight a giant rat.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is unlike the NES version, which was an adventure RPG.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which is weird, because Capcom did them both.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, well, I think that Capcom was notorious for bringing out different versions of games that were one thing in the arcade, but did them different for the NES.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what this game looks a lot like is Magic Sword, actually.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I'm really surprised I've never played this before.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because there's a lot, like just watching this, there's a lot in common with Magic Sword.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is very interesting to me.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just that whole side-scrolling thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, it's really gorgeous.
[SPEAKER_07]: You've got all the story elements.
[SPEAKER_07]: You even have the monsters from the movie.
[SPEAKER_07]: And pretty cool cinematic areas.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's just gorgeous artwork in it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And basically, like in the first... Ah, scary-looking Val Kilmer, sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ah!
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, his weapon is kind of like the cipher from Strider, but it can be charged up and increases range and potency.
[SPEAKER_07]: Basically, you can also buy swords when you stop in the shop.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, uh, it's just really cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Although he's got, like, very pretty boy-looking features when you play with him.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mad Mardigan, that is.
[SPEAKER_07]: Very, very brown hair.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Willow just looks adorable.
[SPEAKER_07]: But yeah, it's a fun game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Pretty tough, but lots of fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, there it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: The classic video game of the week for the arcades, not the NES.
[SPEAKER_06]: Willow.
[SPEAKER_06]: A very Magic Sword-esque kind of game, but with a bitchin' movie franchise behind it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Although, I gotta admit, I always like the video game way better than I like the movie.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's just me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, anyhow, we're going to take a break, but don't go anywhere.
[SPEAKER_06]: There is plenty more of Orange Lounge Radio to come.
[SPEAKER_06]: When we come back for Part B, we're going to be talking about dev kits for the Kinect.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, it could be really happening.
[SPEAKER_06]: Gamertags being freed up and a classic, classic PC game making its way to the iOS system.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we're going to talk all about that when we come back from a break here with more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Welcome back everybody to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: We are live on this Sunday, March the 6th of 2011 for the 404th episode of our podcast.
[SPEAKER_06]: We 404'd.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was going to say we didn't make enough 404 jokes in the opening, but yes, it is episode 404.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura and myself work on.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you like Orange Launch Radio, you might just like these shows too.
[SPEAKER_07]: We have Comic Insanity, which goes live every Tuesday at Infamous.net.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's N-F-A-M-O-U-S dot net.
[SPEAKER_07]: We are awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's me and Mar and Marvel and Dan Shadow.
[SPEAKER_07]: And we're pretty geeky and pretty comic-y.
[SPEAKER_07]: And we're pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Insanity?
[SPEAKER_07]: The Insanity's there too.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: And some Infamy along with it and some other in stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: and The Best Little Horde House in Azeroth is all things World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not taped live anywhere right now but we do put out a pretty fun podcast on Thursdays-ish and you can look that up online at The Best Little Horde House in Azeroth in iTunes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just search for Horde House and it'll come right up or whatever your preferred finder of podcasts is.
[SPEAKER_06]: There is a website coming very soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm hoping next week we'll have more details on that.
[SPEAKER_06]: We have the early workings underway.
[SPEAKER_06]: Very exciting.
[SPEAKER_06]: And now an official guild for this show as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: So check that out.
[SPEAKER_06]: This week's show, by the way, was particularly off-color and explicit.
[SPEAKER_06]: So now's a great time to check it out at the best little hoard house in Azeroth.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki has a show called Raising a Baby.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although it's not really a show.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just what he does.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wouldn't have a show even if I didn't have a baby.
[SPEAKER_04]: Been there, tried that, don't think so.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I've said it before, it's a crime how undervalued your mix show was because you were pretty good at it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh well, some things are just not meant to be.
[SPEAKER_06]: It took too damn long.
[SPEAKER_06]: What is meant to be?
[SPEAKER_06]: More gaming news and Twitter topics very soon on the Twitters.
[SPEAKER_06]: But first, some rapid news, Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, of course, we knew the Gears of War 3 beta was coming soon, thanks to Bulletstorm.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bulletstorm players will actually get access to the Gears of War 3 beta on April 18th.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then, of course, if you don't have Bulletstorm, you can also get into the beta if you've pre-ordered Gears of War 3 from GameStop.
[SPEAKER_04]: Those players will be able to get in a week later on April 25th.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, of course, you know, multiplayer beta, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: Gears of War 3 Beta Tester Medal
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, you get the Thrashball Cole, which is the fictional sport that's in Gears of War.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you get the variant skin for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: The gold-plated Retro Lancer, possible if you complete a bunch of levels in that, 90 matches.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a lot of matches.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Flaming Hammerburst, if you complete one match by Sunday, April 24th.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, the Flaming Lancer by one match during the week of April 25th.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Flaming Sawed-Off Shotgun, one match during the week of May 2nd.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the Flaming Nasher Shotgun during the next week, May 9th.
[SPEAKER_07]: What isn't flaming?
[SPEAKER_04]: Not much.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not me.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's coming soon, and check it out if you haven't yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: I am so excited to get my next issue of Game Informer.
[SPEAKER_04]: The cover game, of course, is Saints Row III.
[SPEAKER_04]: God, I love that game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Saints Row, seriously, you know, what Grand Theft Auto used to be as far as, you know, over the top and ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not that I don't, you know...
[SPEAKER_04]: Not that I dislike Grand Theft Auto 4 because I've made it over top and ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_04]: But Saints Row is awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that is coming out on Xbox 360, PlayStation 3, and PC this holiday.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the game looks awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, the cover or whatever that they have looks awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: And apparently the game is going to be taking place I guess in Stillwater still.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also...
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess there's this gang called the Syndicated Criminal Organization that has contacts in different parts of the world and they're saying that it ultimately propels you into a new city that hosts the most outlandish gameplay scenarios ever seen.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they're saying, judging by the cover here, nine-way free-fall gun battle from a plane.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do respect the fact that they have System Link.
[SPEAKER_04]: or Hasselhoff.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then finally, the Panasonic Jungle is not going to be coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was kind of an ambitious idea.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was an ambitious idea for a portable handheld MMO system.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just... Oh, the MMO thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nobody understood that anyway, so that's fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just not feasible.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know...
[SPEAKER_04]: Why don't they just say, nobody got it?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not a thing that, it's not that nobody got it, I think.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just, I don't know if we'd be able to run a lot of the popular MMOs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, that wouldn't be able to run World of Warcraft, for sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, they're saying, oh, it would have been able to, you know, use titles like Stellar Down, Battlestar Galactica, and RuneScape.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's really Battlestar Galactica.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Rift, it's all about Rift right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I mean, so, it just doesn't have enough oomph to be able to, you know, work.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can you imagine, though, if they ported World of Warcraft to, like, the iPad?
[SPEAKER_04]: It won't happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: It won't happen, but I'm just saying something of that caliber to something like that would be ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_07]: We would have people just moving into their bathrooms.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: They have that, like... There's some pretty complex MMOs that are on iOS.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's the one?
[SPEAKER_06]: Legends or whatever it's called.
[SPEAKER_06]: Play Legends?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_06]: Super Mega Neo Climax Super Mega Neo Climax
[SPEAKER_06]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_06]: ModNation Racers has reached a milestone this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Two million user-created items.
[SPEAKER_06]: Plenty more download content on the way, according to the PlayStation blog, including a parts pack that's already available on the PlayStation Store.
[SPEAKER_06]: More track packs to make new tracks.
[SPEAKER_06]: Western and pirate-themed.
[SPEAKER_06]: More career DLC coming as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: The party is not stopping at ModNation Racers.
[SPEAKER_06]: Two million user-created items.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mario Kart Wii Zero.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's pretty crazy.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: PlayStation Home was announced that it's upgraded to version 1.5 and some of the new features that are coming out in 1.5 of the home client.
[SPEAKER_06]: Games that run within home
[SPEAKER_06]: There's already kind of some of these, but they're trying to take it kind of up to the next step with low lag, real time multiplayer gaming, allowing more first person shooters, racing games and so forth.
[SPEAKER_06]: A demo was shown for Sodium 2 Project Velocity that shows some of this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, you gotta admit, Sodium was one of the more interesting things that happened with Home.
[SPEAKER_06]: I realize it's stretching it, but it was interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's a sad... That's, you know, what's the big thing about Home.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, but they say now it looks like Wipeout HD.
[SPEAKER_06]: And to that I go, oh, now that's interesting because Wipeout HD is kind of badass.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I... If that is true, that you're going to see more stuff like that in Home...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, here's some news from a game developers conference.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ninja Gaiden 3!
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, wait, didn't we already have a Ninja Gaiden 3?
[SPEAKER_07]: Wasn't it on NES?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, but this time it doesn't involve Ancient Kingdoms or whatever the subtitle was.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Ancient Warships, whatever it was.
[SPEAKER_07]: This one has a bloody Ryu on it, so that should be really, really hot.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, really, really cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then we have the Rock Band releases, which a friend of mine who was completely nuts over Depeche Mode is all happy with this.
[SPEAKER_07]: We have the Depeche Mode pack that has Never Let Me Down Again and Personal Jesus and Policy of Truth.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then I Will Possess Your Heart by Death Cab for Cutie.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wish they had more Exciter stuff in there because that album was awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: And last but never least, we have more news for Marvel vs. Capcom 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: We have the dates for Jill, Valentine, and Shuma Garath.
[SPEAKER_07]: They will be on March 15th for Xbox Live, 400 points a pop.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then on March 16th for the PS3.
[SPEAKER_07]: You gotta wait on PS3, ha ha ha ha.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you heard that right.
[SPEAKER_04]: For people that aren't familiar with Microsoft Space Dollars.
[SPEAKER_04]: $5 a character.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you, Capcom.
[SPEAKER_04]: You suck.
[SPEAKER_04]: $5 a character.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm gonna get Jill.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pay to unlock content.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it is pay to unlock content.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's on the disc already.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you, Capcom.
[SPEAKER_04]: You suck balls.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're just mad at everyone tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, seriously.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, we put it on there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, but we're dicks.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: You need to say something nice about a video game company to balance all this hatred coming out of you tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Marvel vs. Capcom 3 is an awesome game, but they're dicks for charging $5 a character.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry, it's stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, characters should be like $2 at the most.
[SPEAKER_04]: And especially stuff that's not on the disc.
[SPEAKER_04]: This stuff is already on the disc.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're just being dicks.
[SPEAKER_04]: They didn't even spend the time to apparently polish it up.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's no actual storylines or whatever for them.
[SPEAKER_04]: They didn't do any cutscenes for them.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're just assholes.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all they are.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if you buy them, you're supporting assholes, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: So just keep that in mind.
[SPEAKER_06]: SSJ100 Matt in our chatroom says Deadpool better make Jill sandwich jokes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a good point.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you think Deadpool should make a Jill sandwich joke?
[SPEAKER_07]: No doubt he probably would if silently.
[SPEAKER_07]: Does he ever do anything silently?
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, let's get to the Twitter and read some of the topics that you guys sent to us tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Twitter.com slash OLR is the place you can send us tweets and we read them live.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not all of them though.
[SPEAKER_06]: but most of them Spazinator PSN sends us an FYI about the PSN video store there's currently a free anime pilot Hikaru no Go and a movie rental Stranger Than Fiction on the PSN video store yeah I heard PSN was like giving away more movies you know not that these are all movies like people are lining up to see but hey it's free Stranger Than Fiction wasn't terrible yeah if you like free stuff why not there you go
[SPEAKER_06]: SilverSonic1534 is sending us a tweet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you see this video?
[SPEAKER_06]: It shows some of Super Mario 3DS screenshots.
[SPEAKER_06]: It looks to be a game like Super Mario Bros.
3.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then follows that up with a correction.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not looking like Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_06]: 3, but apparently it's going to have some of the powers that were on Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_06]: 3 on the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Send us a Twitter link to an IGN video.
[SPEAKER_06]: That I guess is kind of showing... I don't want to watch all these talking heads.
[SPEAKER_06]: All they did was show the stupid... It looks like they're comparing it to Mario Galaxy.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I heard about how the raccoon tail was visible in the little logo that they teased.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, and they're kind of showing this a little bit in the video.
[SPEAKER_06]: So...
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I'm sure, you know, people, one thing they do love about Mario is all these little, like, powers, like the raccoon and, please, the Tanooki suit.
[SPEAKER_06]: That would be amazing if they brought that back.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, that's kind of one of the things that made Mario Galaxy fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want this shoe.
[SPEAKER_06]: The bee suit was awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sure some of that stuff, it's all going to be anything that tickles your retro bone and gets you to drop 40, 50 bucks on the games.
[SPEAKER_04]: And by the way, all of that information that was from IGN right there was all speculation because all they showed was the stupid logo.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, it's going to be Mario 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's speculate on what it's going to look like.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think it... Of course, it's going to look like they're successful Mario games, but 3D.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it's not that hard to figure out, I don't think.
[SPEAKER_06]: Am I crazy?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, going to Actdeft, who sends us a little twit pic.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's a collection of little Pokey dolls.
[SPEAKER_06]: He showed us his Pokemans live on air.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_06]: But the question that goes with this, do you collect a video game paraphernalia or have a collection besides the vault?
[SPEAKER_07]: Will we put it all in the vault?
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess this might be more of a question for Loki and myself, IDK.
[SPEAKER_07]: You guys go ahead and answer that because it's a stupid question.
[SPEAKER_06]: To be honest... Hey, now there's no such thing as a stupid question.
[SPEAKER_07]: I said for me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, for you.
[SPEAKER_06]: For me, I gotta be honest, not really.
[SPEAKER_06]: For a while, I seemed like I had an Xbox Live Arcade collection going on because I was downloading everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I don't really collect.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't buy games just because they're rare.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't really have a lot of autograph things or collectibles.
[SPEAKER_06]: I rarely if ever buy limited editions I think the last like limited edition I remember buying was that Final Fantasy 12 at GameStop that had like the extra little frills I mean it's got to be a really big game I don't even buy collector's edition of Warcraft exception I did buy collector's editions of Burning Crusade and Wrath of the Lich King but it was at a charity event it was at the first Doom Loud I did buy those so and so that's for different reasons and I ended up giving away the Burning Crusade one to my friend for Christmas so different thing
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, you a collector?
[SPEAKER_04]: I am not a collector of anything, but I have like, you know, I get tchotchkes sometimes, so I have a bunch of stuff at my desk at work.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've got like, well, I used to collect Gundam models, but then I bought...
[SPEAKER_04]: Pretty much all of them.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's still fun every now and then.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do have, for the last Samurai Warriors game, I think, Samurai Warriors 3, they have these little mini figurines.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have almost a whole collection of those because we got a bunch of boxes of them, and so I opened all of them to try to create a whole collection.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm missing one, though, I think.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's the other thing I should say about why I don't collect.
[SPEAKER_06]: I got hoarding tendencies as it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: If I really was a rabid collector, it would be really bad, you guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I can't.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't get rid of the stuff I have.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have my Japanese copy of Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_04]: at my desk sitting there since I don't need the Japanese version anymore, the real version.
[SPEAKER_04]: And what else did I have that's really weird?
[SPEAKER_04]: Um...
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a poster for the Atari Pac-Man.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want it for a penny on eBay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: But nothing to the scale of DarkSakura's vault.
[SPEAKER_06]: That is a whole little special level all on its own.
[SPEAKER_07]: Some of our stuff that we've gotten that we've really looked into is just sort of like...
[SPEAKER_07]: It'll be there and we'll see it and it's cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, we've gotten all kinds of neat collector stuff, you know, through Dan getting some swag from the local reps and, you know, going to conventions and things.
[SPEAKER_07]: I still think the coolest, one of the coolest things we got was the Goemon doll because we bought our Twilight Zone pinball game from the guy who owned Working Designs and he just gave one to Dan.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: on the wall and just stuff we've looked into.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, sometimes this stuff just falls in our lap.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not like we're trying to collect it on purpose.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then Dan says from the other room, and some of it we spent stupid money on.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, well, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_06]: A couple tweets coming to us from Tigerclaw.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tigerclaw linking us to this story.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess a quote from Cliffy B., Cliff Blazinski.
[SPEAKER_06]: Merry gamers, don't date them.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to read verbatim this article from Joystick with a Q. Proper credit to them because I was tweeted this story and didn't have a chance to skim things in advance for the relevant stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: In a candid talk during the Game Developers Conference on Thursday, Epic Games Design Director Cliff Pazinski advised attendees to have an educated gut and to be cognizant of the value of marketing and long-term relationships with customers.
[SPEAKER_06]: He encapsulated his talk in the Power Creative, a project member who is unique, valuable, and visibly tied to the game's identity.
[SPEAKER_06]: This could be anyone.
[SPEAKER_06]: I see.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's more like he's not saying that in the literal sense, like Merry Gamers.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's saying kind of, you know, be...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: According to Blazinski, the market only tolerates games that land on the far end of the spectrum between freemium snack games and big budget games like Gears of War.
[SPEAKER_06]: I believe the middle class game is dead.
[SPEAKER_06]: The power creative understands how to engage fans over a long period of time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Make gamers marry your game, not just date it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Again, if you want to read the rest of that story, it's on JoystickWithACue.com as tweeted to us tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do game developers, some of them, need to work on the relationship with the fan and that whole idea of marry your audience and don't just take them out on one night stands?
[SPEAKER_06]: Or do you think that whole little comparison is way out of... You need to satisfy your market.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you don't satisfy them, they'll leave.
[SPEAKER_07]: They'll leave you for other developers who love them longer and harder.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mega Man Universe Mega Man Universe
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow, another tweet to us from Tigerclaw, a link to a story on Kotaku about the social game developers rant.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, I did hear about this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently, there was a panel at Game Developers Conference where a bunch of the folks that develop for these social game companies like Zynga and Playdom and all this, they basically got up and said, Hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: Stop picking on us.
[SPEAKER_06]: Screw you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: they also did a little mini game where the developers were encouraged I'm sorry the people attending the panels were encouraged to collect coins and whoever could get the most coins got to do a rant of their own which is kind of funny because it's like that's kind of like how a social game would actually work so ha so there you go is that it for tweets oh no one last tweet from blue swim orange lounge foodio question which is better Cadbury cream eggs or marshmallow peeps also welcome back Loki
[SPEAKER_07]: Cadbury cream eggs and marshmallows are disgusting.
[SPEAKER_06]: I actually disagree.
[SPEAKER_06]: Marshmallow peeps because they can joust in the microwave.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Cadbury cream eggs are too much.
[SPEAKER_06]: If I'm going to eat a Cadbury cream egg, it needs to be one of those little mini ones.
[SPEAKER_06]: The big ones are too much, too rich.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what's fantastic?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's going to Touch of Britain and getting the Mars eggs.
[SPEAKER_07]: Those are fantastic.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or the orange cream eggs.
[SPEAKER_06]: I still kind of prefer marshmallow peeps personally.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not a big fan of either one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cream eggs, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's it for tweets.
[SPEAKER_06]: Twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_06]: In the meantime, let's get back into some other video game news before we get to the mailbag, the FUs, and of course, your phone calls.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: So this is kind of neat and kind of along the lines of stuff that
[SPEAKER_04]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: ISU which stands for the interfaces you and of course it's SoftConnect's 3D gesture recognition software development kit now available for qualified developers and they can license it for free.
[SPEAKER_04]: It says it's going to work with all 3D depth sensing devices, which includes support for the Kinect.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I guess it's a strictly non-commercial software development kit.
[SPEAKER_04]: And a commercial version, of course, can be purchased from them as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it says there's going to be different ones actually coming out from it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Evoluce, PrimeSense, and of course, Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, neat to see that there's going to be some... I'm actually, I'd be kind of curious to see what the first, like, real retail game that comes out that supports Kinect.
[SPEAKER_04]: That'd be kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then, of course, not to be outdone by that, PlayStation, the PlayStation Move, I should say,
[SPEAKER_04]: They actually have some tools as well to be able to program stuff that supports the PlayStation, iCamera, and the Move controllers.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's called MoveMe and it's a software tool that's going to be using the PlayStation Move technology to create unique applications.
[SPEAKER_04]: and, of course, it's coming soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're saying that MoveMe is going to be a downloadable application for the PS3 that allows researchers, students, hobbyists, developers, or anyone to build the ability to develop for the PlayStation Move.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they said they want to see what innovative applications programs can create using the PlayStation Move controller, the PS3 system, and the PlayStation Eye camera and the PC.
[SPEAKER_04]: So...
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently, it's going to be available on the PlayStation Network this spring, but people that are interested will be able to apply for it as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can go to, I believe, usplaystation.com slash ps3 slash playstation-move slash move-me and check that out.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you think will ultimately come of this?
Oh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe some applications or whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think they're... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a lot of stuff that they could do with the PlayStation that they're not.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, remember a long time ago they were showing some of the stuff, even what they could do with the PlayStation Eye camera.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, they're all, hey, look, we made a combat game.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it was the developers for the PlayStation Eye stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: They were showing, hey, look, we can make a combat game where you draw your...
[SPEAKER_04]: and tanks that you use and you can scan them in and play a game with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: They did all those cool tech demos but never released them.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like, you know, you could have done something cool with that but no.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you see more like bite-sized applications coming maybe to the PlayStation Network?
[SPEAKER_04]: They should.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, that was the whole point with like even on the PSP how they have the PlayStation Network on the PSP and they have the PSP minis and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was supposed to be more of like those bite-sized applications.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm hoping...
[SPEAKER_04]: and so on and so forth.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: Xbox Live has been around quite a while.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's been around since about 2002.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: They're not saying what meets the qualifications for dead.
[SPEAKER_06]: I am assuming that ones that were used on the old Xbox, because old Xbox Live is gone, that never migrated to a 360 account.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm assuming that's what qualifies, but it's a huge assumption.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think part of what definitely falls into this, people that change their name, their old name would still be unavailable.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I think a lot of that is kind of getting moved permanently.
[SPEAKER_06]: so uh also it's stressed on here uh the process will take time to complete they will will not be able to tell you when a gamer tag that you want is available you should always check back regularly because they are reviving gamer tags daily you can go into the xbox channel and change gamer tag to see if the gamer tag you want is available I tried to get Major Nelson but it was taken hmm
[SPEAKER_06]: so there you go I did notice though one name I would be interested in changing to was available so who knows I'm not sure how I feel about $10 just to change my gamer tag but you never know we'll see anything's possible
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's move on with some more stories, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, today's other story is Metal Cthulhu.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_07]: Another World.
[SPEAKER_07]: You remember this game?
[SPEAKER_07]: It came out in the 90s.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh my god, I do remember that game.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was epic when it came out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, it actually first came out in 1991.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was a cinematic sci-fi side-scroller.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's going to be brought up to date to come out for iPhone and iPad.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's being ported by Dotemu.
[SPEAKER_07]: They haven't said anything about new features, but they're saying that they want it to be the best experience on iOS.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry, I'm looking at a video on YouTube of this game being played, actually.
[SPEAKER_06]: Taking me back a little bit, let me skip ahead.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is somebody playing it on an Amiga.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, it really is a pretty game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, it was great.
[SPEAKER_07]: And this is supposed to be just a big old update.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they're also working on an Ubisoft game called From Dust that's going to be out on PC and PSN and Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dude, another world.
[SPEAKER_06]: This game was kind of like a souped-up version of Prince of Persia, but, like, that's really... It's like Prince of Persia in space, but with epic cutscenes involved.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Kind of a little flashback, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Running away from a killer bear.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, this game was so epic when it came out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wasn't, like, Out of This World or something like that?
[SPEAKER_06]: It was called...
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, in the US it was called Out of This World.
[SPEAKER_07]: Another World was the UK release.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yet I still know it by that name.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_06]: very cool Salacious Pop in our chatroom says that game is fucking amazing but it's hard as fuck I have no idea how you can play it without tactile controls and I got the HD version they put out like four years ago I didn't realize they'd done a remake already and damn good point it's cool that they're putting it out again and nostalgia and all that on the iOS but again no joystick means hard game is very very hard so I don't know we'll see
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow, let's move on with a few more stories.
[SPEAKER_06]: The mailbag is coming up as well as the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_04]: so they've got some cool stuff coming to OnLive some of the things that they announced at Game Developers Conference that they're going to be offering to developers that want to put their games on to the platform they're saying voice chat game invites for multiplayer games the ability to directly upload brag clips to YouTube and then also achievements which they're guessing is going to be stuff derived from console versions
[SPEAKER_04]: If they want to put up an old retro game or something like that and add achievements to it, they can.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, they're going to allow developers to let their game support wireless controllers when played on mobile devices such as the iPad, iPhone, or Android-powered phones or tablets.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really, they need some controllers for some of those devices.
[SPEAKER_06]: True.
[SPEAKER_06]: So...
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, they're doing alright, I think.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think they're making progress, and it's definitely been, you know, it works, so... I think it's worked a lot better than anybody thought it would.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think a lot of people wrote this thing off when it first came out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Before it came out, really.
[SPEAKER_06]: So...
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, we'll see what continues with that.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's neat that they're still going with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That type of device, though, how they have the micro-console and stuff like that, if they can do MMOs on that, that's how you would get a device like the Jungle, where it would basically be something that runs on a server at some company or whatever, like World of Warcraft or something like that, and you have your controls on there, and it's very limited, but you don't need to have the powerhouse of...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: DJ Maxx
[SPEAKER_06]: And the music's pretty popular amongst the crowd, but usually there's not a real legitimate anyway way to get the music outside of Korea.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, guess what?
[SPEAKER_06]: Starting in March, it was announced, Pentavision has announced that the soundtracks for DJ Maxx are going to be published on iTunes.
[SPEAKER_06]: three albums followed by a new album every week I guess until they get caught up because that's a lot of albums but there have been quite a few DJ Max games at this point so fans of that series are going to be very happy that they get their nice CD quality sound out of iTunes that'll be pretty cool if they didn't already get it through other means from the Korean albums that's pretty cool you know iTunes has been doing a lot of different Japanese pop artists like the really big names like Ayumi and Goct and
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I bought an Ayumi song on there not that long ago.
[SPEAKER_07]: I got a Larkin CL album a while back.
[SPEAKER_06]: They also do a lot of video game soundtracks.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's interesting to me that they don't have a gaming section in their store.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe I missed it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think there is a soundtracks section, so maybe it's buried in there and I've just missed it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: DJ Maxx
[SPEAKER_06]: Loom
[SPEAKER_07]: Loom.
[SPEAKER_07]: Didn't they?
[SPEAKER_06]: They did something.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess it was a hack.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loom's on Steam.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh yeah, it's on Steam.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to say it was like a hack for the iOS or something, of course.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know I got Loom on Steam.
[SPEAKER_06]: Somebody wants to hack the old LucasArts stuff for that.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, I actually have a copy of Loom for PC.
[SPEAKER_07]: I bought it on eBay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because I love that game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hardly remember how to play it because of all the chords and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I remember some of the chords and I do them way too early.
[SPEAKER_07]: But Loom would be fun on Steam.
[SPEAKER_04]: Scorched Earth.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, man.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's been years since I played Scorched Earth.
[SPEAKER_06]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_07]: What about Phantasmagoria?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's not outside the realm of possibility.
[SPEAKER_06]: There was a news on that not that long ago.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know they brought out the seventh guest, which I know it's a completely different company, but for some reason these go together in my mind.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they were talking about the 11th hour, and I want to say around that same time we had heard something about Phantasmagoria.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that would be pretty cool if that were to come out for iOS.
[SPEAKER_06]: The point and click games would lend themselves much better to the iOS system.
[SPEAKER_06]: So maybe like Kyrandia would be awesome if we could get that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Obviously, I've got to say King's Quest would be kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_06]: And there was the whole Flash versions that got shut down, so we know it's kind of possible.
[SPEAKER_07]: Good old games.
[SPEAKER_07]: Had a Phantasmagoria for digital download.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe that's why we reported on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe you have the SCUMM emulators though for jailbroken devices.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you know me, I'd like to see more classic Commodore 64 games show up outside of just the emulator.
[SPEAKER_06]: There is the emulator that's available but it keeps going up and down and up and down.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't even know if it's still on the store right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: They also have there's some other emulator that was out there that was
[SPEAKER_06]: iDOS was an emulator.
[SPEAKER_06]: I had Duke Nukem and all that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have it on my phone, but it's pulled from the store now.
[SPEAKER_06]: iDOS.
[SPEAKER_04]: There was another one.
[SPEAKER_04]: I did get the, they finally leaked that out too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember that Minecraft client that got uploaded for just a little brief millisecond or whatever?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I finally found that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I don't have a Minecraft account, so I can't play it yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, well, let's get to the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_06]: You guys send your emails to mailbag at orangelaundry.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura picks a few of her favorites and reads them live on air.
[SPEAKER_07]: The first email is actually directed towards me.
[SPEAKER_07]: It says, Hello, I heard last week that DarkSakura is going to Faname Con.
[SPEAKER_07]: I will be going this year as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: How about an OLR meetup at the convention?
[SPEAKER_07]: Hope to see you, Sakura.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jinai.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, if everything works out, I'm not making any, like, supreme promises or anything because, honestly, I miss cosplaying and I think I wouldn't mind doing it again.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, um, we definitely need to see about getting our panel.
[SPEAKER_06]: That would be... Might be a little late for that.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're almost into... Oh, we're at, like, mid-March...
[SPEAKER_06]: If we could swing it, yeah, I'd love to do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll probably be here that weekend.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll bring the dolls again.
[SPEAKER_07]: The scary, creepy dolls.
[SPEAKER_07]: Next email.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, OLR, how would you feel if Konami gave the DDR series a reboot on the Kinect?
[SPEAKER_07]: The game would feature songs from DDR's history and songs found in the charts today, and it would also feature an online mode where players can compete in dance battles or form their own dance groups and choreograph their own dances.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think, unfortunately, Konami's already kind of screwed the pooch with that because Dance Masters is kind of that.
[SPEAKER_06]: At least it's a lot of the old DDR songs, but in that whole Para slash Dance Central-esque kind of format.
[SPEAKER_06]: And there's a demo available now on Xbox 360 if you want to see what this game's all about.
[SPEAKER_06]: But yeah, I...
[SPEAKER_06]: I think you have some good ideas, but the weird thing is, I don't know, did he say with a dance mat and Kinect?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it just says Kinect.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, guess what?
[SPEAKER_04]: If you want to use a Kinect, though, with DDR, the upcoming DDR game, Dance Dance Revolution, because, you know, they made it just... We covered last week where there's a hack for it that they're trying to...
[SPEAKER_04]: No, that's Step Mania, but I'm talking about the actual Dance Dance Revolution.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember the one that came out on PS3 with Move support and then on the Wii as well?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it's coming out in April on Xbox 360 and it uses the Xbox Vision Camera.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which is now also technically the Kinect, but you can do crap with that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But seriously, we don't need to give Konami reasons to make more gimmicky crap for Dan Says Revolution.
[SPEAKER_04]: They just need to stick to the core mechanics and improve on that, or just basically do what they were doing back years ago, and they would be fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: But they're trying...
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know what they're doing anymore.
[SPEAKER_06]: They need to just reform Konami Hawaii and give them the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's really the only thing that would get me super interested in DDR again.
[SPEAKER_04]: Put me in charge.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will make you a game that's going to be perfect.
[SPEAKER_06]: More emails?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, there was actually more to this email.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, my bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: Finally, it would be great if you guys would give my video game blog a quick plug on the show, which I will be happy to do.
[SPEAKER_06]: No!
[SPEAKER_06]: That'll be $50.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hush.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here's the link.
[SPEAKER_07]: PlayStationUK.wordpress.com Thanks, Liam.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, Liam.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would like to know Liam's thoughts on the whole LG lawsuit that we covered at the top of the show, since that is affecting the UK.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe it's on his blog.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, we'll have to just go there later.
[SPEAKER_07]: And maybe look later.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, next email.
[SPEAKER_07]: Greetings, OLR.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is your neighborhood turtle again.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've included a link you guys should check out concerning Unreal Engine 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: Looking at the screen caps plus the previews of Crysis 2 and Battlefield 3, I'm incredibly impressed, mostly with the lighting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Being a graphics whore, all these next-gen games look very promising.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love pretty things.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why else did I sit through the first 13 hours of Final Fantasy XIII?
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, really.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, the lighting is really tremendous.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's amazing.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, Unreal Engine, the last one, was amazing enough.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sure the new one's just going to be even more of an improvement.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to be great.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think that's four.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's just the new updates that they did for three.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, my gosh.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought this was the new engine.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, that's just the tweaks that they did for three, I think.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's a pretty crazy poly count these things are running, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think they have Unreal Remember the next one's Rage, I thought
[SPEAKER_04]: from, was it Epic Rage?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I know Rage is the next big engine.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, yeah, I don't think that's Unreal 4.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's just tweaks to the three, if I remember correctly.
[SPEAKER_06]: I also want to see what crazy, like, non-shooting things come out of the engine.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because, you know, like, we've been getting some really random things in the Unreal Engine.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, there was a few role-playing games from Square that were done in the engine.
[SPEAKER_06]: Was it Last Remnant that was in Unreal?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: Last tournament was?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I've been looking at this, and this is kind of funny since I've been taking my 3D class.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just, now that I actually understand the physics behind some of this, it's pretty cool seeing, you know, what happens by layer.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just amazing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, I'm going to share this picture with the chat room because this is a really good example.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's the one of the dude's face where they start with the, it's basically just a demo of the subsurface scattering.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's really cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're also showing how cool smoking is.
[SPEAKER_07]: Honestly, a falling cigarette is a good showing of lighting and physics in action.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because that was clearly part of their demo.
[SPEAKER_04]: and it also shows that Epic has set the release Falling Cigarette the game after Gears of War 3 and I can't be any more excited than I am possibly right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Next email.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cigarettes will fall.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fall of 2012.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi guys.
[SPEAKER_07]: Since the website won't let me post this because it's too long I figured I'd just email it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh good.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura loves long emails.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: Her saying that about a game is not something I've seen every day.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wouldn't I be hearing every day?
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, in fact, I think this is the third game ever she's been that impressed.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, of course, I went through the rest of the demo, even showing her how much customization was involved in creating her character and following the storylines and how they can branch off.
[SPEAKER_07]: After the full demo, I found that while the controls aren't as good as I'd like them to be, they're far better than the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_07]: For me, any game that causes a casual person to stop and take notice wins more in my book than something that's designed for hardcore fans.
[SPEAKER_07]: Again, another topic for another day.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, why the PS3 over Xbox?
[SPEAKER_07]: Besides control, the download content comes with it instead of having to buy it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Besides, it's very rare that a game does better on PS3 for me than the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_07]: And to end it, her final thought after I turned off the demo, sure beats Halo.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think that sealed the deal.
[SPEAKER_07]: sometimes having the audience there while playing a game is more fun than playing it alone well you won't be on this week but we'll catch you guys later oh no well won't be on this week but we'll catch you guys later and that was from Mantis Knight that's another one of those games you know it's funny because I brought up Beyond Good and Evil earlier in the show and it's one of those games like everybody played and loved and I'm just now catching up on it yeah put Mass Effect in that same bin it's funny
[SPEAKER_07]: Last email.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, OLR gang, ACHP here.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know a lot of people who listen to this show probably want to work in games.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know I do.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I thought I'd share some advice.
[SPEAKER_07]: Meet people who make games.
[SPEAKER_07]: While not being able to afford the $1,000 pass to get into Game Developers Conference this weekend, I was able to squeeze myself into some post-hours events.
[SPEAKER_07]: And let me tell you, it is probably the best thing I have ever done for my professional career.
[SPEAKER_07]: You'd be surprised at how willing people are to chat and network with complete strangers who don't even work in the industry.
[SPEAKER_07]: at a random party for a company I've never heard of I was able to meet the business developer managers for Q Entertainment met a guy who knew a guy who was there with a recruiter who's now helping me find placement as an entry-level programmer so if you want to get your foot in the door and haven't booked a ticket for PAX do it if you and if you have go look up your favorite company
[SPEAKER_07]: Go look up if your favorite company is doing any meet and greet type of activities.
[SPEAKER_07]: You may be glad you did.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hope this helps someone.
[SPEAKER_07]: ACHP P.S.
[SPEAKER_07]: Game developers are definitely the most socially awkward people ever.
[SPEAKER_07]: With an open bar and go-go dancers on the tables, they are just idly chatting or playing on their phone.
[SPEAKER_07]: I lulled.
[SPEAKER_07]: P.P.S.
[SPEAKER_07]: I wrote this on my Android phone, again to prove that you can write grammatically correct and properly spelled and punctuated words without a keyboard or autocorrect.
[SPEAKER_07]: Cheers.
[SPEAKER_06]: You said to be very patient.
[SPEAKER_06]: But yeah, I agree.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some of the best parts, at least about E3, which is one I was going to pretty regularly for a while, some of the best part is networking.
[SPEAKER_06]: So yeah, absolutely.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you're going to be going to any of those shows, just don't be shy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just say hi to people.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can tell when somebody doesn't want to talk to you or if you're bugging somebody or what have you, you know.
[SPEAKER_06]: But most of the times at these expos, people kind of, you know, they want to be social.
[SPEAKER_06]: They want to hang out.
[SPEAKER_06]: They want to talk their game.
[SPEAKER_06]: So good email.
[SPEAKER_06]: Was that it?
[SPEAKER_06]: That was it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Excuse me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Chat.OrangeLoungeRadio.com if you want to chat.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you want to send us emails, mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: SSJ100Matt throws in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_06]: There are a ton of networking panels at PAX East this year.
[SPEAKER_06]: So coming up.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would like to know how the networking is at PAX East for those of you guys that are going.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to know how you guys, you know, if you find people or what you discover.
[SPEAKER_06]: So let us know.
[SPEAKER_06]: In the meantime, we need to stop being so nice talking about all this networking and hand-holding and partying.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's time to get angsty with the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would like to give a big fuck you to the Library of Congress, more specifically their website, in trying to help my client copyright his book.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not letting me do the regular copyright submission.
[SPEAKER_07]: It wants me to do the pre-registration submission, which actually isn't even necessary to do.
[SPEAKER_07]: Online registration is $35.
[SPEAKER_07]: Pre-registration is $150.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, what do you think we want to do?
[SPEAKER_07]: Especially since I've made sure that the book is fully the way it needs to be.
[SPEAKER_07]: Everything's ready.
[SPEAKER_07]: We've got a publisher.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, just frustrations.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, bite my butt, Library of Congress.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_04]: F you to Dominic's New York Pizza and Italian Deli for not realizing that Philly Cheesesteak has cheese on it and giving me a sandwich that does not have cheese on it and it wasn't that great so I have to throw it away but yes next time I will not be buying the Philly Cheesesteak sandwich from you because you have omitted cheese although my wife does like the clam pizza
[SPEAKER_04]: Not my thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: And my FU goes to those big Belgian waffles for being so yummy and delicious and very fattening.
[SPEAKER_06]: F you to food for making me fat.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's my F you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, just a couple more news stories for you guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then the Skype line at 1-877-GAME-OLR Username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're not ready for that just yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: We have a couple more stories for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Capcom would like to remind you that Street Fighter 2 has turned 20.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's been 20 years since the game was released in arcades in 1991.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's seen six arcade iterations and of course a ton of ports, cross consoles, PCs, and
[SPEAKER_04]: and definitely one of the top arcade games out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: They are still assholes though for charging $5 for download content for Marvel vs. Capcom 3 I'd like to add.
[SPEAKER_06]: But happy birthday Street Fighter and your 20 different iterations to go with those 20 years, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Pretty soon Street Fighter 4 will have just as many.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which is one of the more interesting launch games on the 3DS, might I add.
[SPEAKER_06]: A game that I played, what, a year and a half ago?
[SPEAKER_06]: Two years ago for the first time?
[SPEAKER_04]: You know Dead or Alive is not a launch game anymore?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a launch window game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry, that's not a launch game.
[SPEAKER_04]: A launch game is a game that comes out day one.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is a launch game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'd even give you a week or two after that.
[SPEAKER_04]: A game that comes out two months after that is not a launch game.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is a launch window game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, my launch window is four years after the console comes out.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a launch game.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's Nintendo for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Way to spin that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, we don't have a lot of games on our system.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that's okay because we considered the launch four years after it comes out.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, Angry Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's move on to another story.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is about Steam and Steam possibly invading your television.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's a quote from Doug Lombardi, the Vice President of Marketing for Valve, from earlier this week in preparation for Game Developers Conference.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, uh...
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not necessarily there's going to be some type of little hookup kit or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's that they're talking about actually putting your PC games on the television, a big picture mode, and I guess a controller-friendly version when you want to play on your TV.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: more plans were announced to Game Developers Conference this past week but you know I think a lot of you are just going to wait and get Portal 2 on the consoles if you don't already have it planned on the PC not to disrespect those that do their gaming on the PCs because there will certainly be a lot of people buying it there or I don't know I got to admit that PlayStation 3 deal where you get it in both places looks awesome where you buy Portal 2 on the PlayStation 3 and then you get the Steam copy on PC for free I think that's how you got to do it
[SPEAKER_06]: Microsoft's going to be hurting to sell copies of that.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, we're going to open up the Skype line at 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Skype line is open right now for you guys to give us a call.
[SPEAKER_06]: While we wait for some calls, Loki, do you have any last minute stories for us?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm trying to think what we haven't covered yet other than my hatred for what Nintendo's doing with the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, there was some new hackers, well, not really hackers, but stuff that's going on with the whole George Hotz thing and being sued.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently, there's some drama over the third-party company that Sony, or I should say the law, the court has going through his hard drives.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently, Sony's trying to get a copy of the hard drive for themselves.
[SPEAKER_04]: and even though a third party is supposed to be the only ones looking at the hard drive basically but somebody wants to know what's on there and possibly the steel information it sounds like or maybe manipulating the system a little bit so people are kind of up in arms about that I don't know
[SPEAKER_04]: This is kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, the NGP, I guess the games, of course, they're coming on kind of a cartridge or memory card type device.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're going to be coming on two and four gigabyte cards with room for game saves and patches because the actual system will not have any onboard storage, or at least that's what the thought is.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that kind of one of the ways you're trying to get around all the hacking?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think it's going to work because the way I'm thinking it now what are you going to save your downloaded games to then?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because obviously they're going to have some sort of online market or something like that and I know it has a second memory card slot for stuff like that so I mean it might be a way to get around it but I mean it didn't work for the Nintendo DS Are they trying to do it maybe because it's a non-standard format or something?
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, maybe just to make it, you know, easy, but I'm sure that's gotta be some sort of, um, you know, it's partly probably anti-piracy.
[SPEAKER_06]: and then again the phone number 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio if you want to get through tonight I would advise calling now because the way these things go is I say the number like 20 times and nobody ever calls and then suddenly just at the last minute like everybody calls at once and then I say well we've taken enough calls so I'm just saying get in early
[SPEAKER_04]: Microsoft has gone the route of Spore, where you can basically take your avatars now, you can create poses or whatever with them, and you can get jumbo wall prints of your avatar.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you want to put yourself up on the wall, you can get a 16GB Zune with your avatar on it, etched in, or a $60 figurine of your avatar.
[SPEAKER_04]: and of course the wall print is going to cost you $150 so that better be damn big and the zoom will cost you $170 figuring $60 that would be kind of neat to have at my desk not the wall print, that's retarded that's going to cost you a bit of money though, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_04]: yeah, I'd probably wait I'd want to see what these things look like in the size, because I'm not going to pay $60 for a 3 inch statue, it better be something pretty significant alright, we've got calls coming in, so let's go to it hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio, who's this?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, this is Spazinator.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, Spazinator, what's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, I'm just calling in about the whole home thing that you were mentioning earlier.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, about the whole upgrades in home where they're going to have more built-in stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: What do you think of all that?
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, I'm probably in the minority here on this, but my whole opinion is kind of like kind of goes along the lines of who cares?
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean,
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, you kind of sort of touched on it a little bit to a degree, but when you said, you know, when are they going to do anything with the clubhouses?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, I mean, you know, there's so much they could be doing with home to make it a little bit more interesting.
[SPEAKER_00]: Like, if you look right, well, it's kind of hard to...
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, talk about something like you're really looking at, but you know how the one wall behind the stage is supposed to be like a video screen in Clubhouse?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, they could be doing something with the video screen, like you guys could be showing off...
[SPEAKER_06]: some of the videos that you guys have made for Orange Lounge I will tell you this much the minute that Sony allows us to put some type of video on that monitor I'll do something exclusive video content wise that won't even be on YouTube we will only put it in Sony Home but I'm not going to hold my breath my camera is still in a box because I don't see that happening yeah you could there's always that and also um
[SPEAKER_00]: Now with our own private spaces, whether it be the log caping space or the default one, whatever you happen to have, they could sell virtual jukeboxes and virtual TVs.
[SPEAKER_00]: They'll allow you to stream all the MP3s that you got on your PS3's hard drive or
[SPEAKER_00]: The video content that you add to the video servers or what have you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Although I'm with you to a point here, Spazinator, I got to ask this question.
[SPEAKER_06]: I got to play devil's advocate and ask this question.
[SPEAKER_06]: Since the PlayStation 3 is a gaming system, why not have enhancements to the gaming mechanisms within home and making the gaming within home better?
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, there's that too.
[SPEAKER_00]: I can certainly see your point.
[SPEAKER_00]: But, you know, perhaps Bobby Blackwood loves to point out from time to time, I'm really heavily into the whole PlayStation 3, more so than my 360.
[SPEAKER_00]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: Your 360 handle, I'm not going to give away your 360 handle, but it has PSN in it, and that always cracks me up that PSN is in your 360 handle.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, well, my point being, you know, you would think, you know, with that being said, you know, I would be all over home like here on the gorilla.
[SPEAKER_00]: But the thing is, I really haven't touched home in God knows how long.
[SPEAKER_00]: And the last time I, the only reason I even bothered with home the last time is because, uh,
[SPEAKER_00]: and all games community said the invite to join them at home.
[SPEAKER_00]: That was about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's nothing to do in there but dance with furries right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: But hopefully Sodium 2 will bring people back if not at least for a day while everybody's curious and checks it out, right?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: But, you know, if they implemented some of the ideas that I just thrown out, you know, I would be using home left and right, you know.
[SPEAKER_00]: But, you know, until then, you know,
[SPEAKER_00]: The only reason I would even consider using it is I would have to be bored out of my mind, like borderline comatose bored, you know?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, maybe you need to go to Game Developers Conference and tell them your ideas.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, Spaz, we're going to let you go to get some more calls, but thank you so much for the call, buddy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, sure.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_06]: You too.
[SPEAKER_06]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or use the name on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: By the way, screen filled up with phone calls while Spaz was on the line.
[SPEAKER_06]: What did I tell you?
[SPEAKER_06]: I tell you, the minute one person tries to call, then everybody's going to try to call.
[SPEAKER_06]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is open now.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see if somebody gets through.
[SPEAKER_06]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or I use name on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Any other last minute stories that we have?
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki's looking for stuff for after the show, so I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess, is that it?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I've got stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Battle LA is becoming a game that's going to be downloadable on PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, and PC.
[SPEAKER_04]: Being developed by Konami, so I guess that's needed.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a movie game, so wait and expect.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hopefully that'll be coming out soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, next month.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right in time for the movie, I guess, considering it comes out in a week.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is being developed by the people that did Timeshift, Saber Interactive.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yay, we got more calls coming in.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yay, let's go to the phones.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, you're on Orange Sounds Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, it's Ron.
[SPEAKER_06]: How are you guys doing tonight?
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course, because when I say get through now, you know how to get through the system and beat everybody else.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, you've got some type of psychic prowess.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know what it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a blessing and a curse.
[SPEAKER_06]: A blessing for you, a curse for us.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_06]: Funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: First thing, I just want to say, Loki, welcome back.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm glad you're feeling much better.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: You got it.
[SPEAKER_06]: But don't ever talk like that in the opening of the show ever again, am I right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's right, I do remember that.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Special Dance Pad, and both I do remember that Oh yeah, those were selling for crazy money for a while And then, what happened?
[SPEAKER_06]: Reprint?
[SPEAKER_04]: Even more recent than that, the Wii System Everyone was like, oh hey, we can't make enough of these They're just so hard to put together Such advanced technology that's been around since the GameCube How do we do it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, like I'm supposed to believe there was a shortage on those that wasn't on purpose.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sure, whatever you say, Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll believe you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, what do you think about the 3DS?
[SPEAKER_03]: I really want one, but to be perfectly honest, I think I'm going to do what SSJ100Matt said.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wait a while.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll just see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Man, that's good advice.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, you asking about all this Nintendo stuff, though, reminded me.
[SPEAKER_06]: I had a big question I was going to ask Loki in Part A when we were doing all the 3DS stories.
[SPEAKER_06]: He was so ranty, I got completely sidetracked.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I'm going to ask it now with you on the line, Robin.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's just making up for last week, so yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's got to do double duty this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: But no, I want to ask this question because this is a serious question.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is one I was talking the other day with some people about is...
[SPEAKER_06]: What's the Wii going to give us this year?
[SPEAKER_06]: Nintendo at E3 this year, we know they're going to announce a Mario game for 3DS.
[SPEAKER_06]: Duh!
[SPEAKER_06]: We know they'll be talking about the other 3DS titles throughout Christmas.
[SPEAKER_06]: What have they got going on the Wii right now?
[SPEAKER_04]: Skyward Sword, that's about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they're dragging that shit out as long as possible.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is it possible, not to sound fanboy-esque here, but is it possible that Zelda was pushed back because this is the year they're going to announce a Wii HD?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: And not a Wii 2, but a Wii HD.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, this is exactly what happened to the last Metroid Other M. They announced it way too damn early.
[SPEAKER_04]: It gets delayed forever.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just like the Metroid Prime Trilogy.
[SPEAKER_04]: they're just pushing shit back longer and longer and they keep announcing stuff well into it much in advance just so they have something to fill up their E3 press conference with because I mean seriously if they cut out all the stuff that's supposed to be coming out this year I mean well they announced Skyward Sword and that was a big part of their thing and I bet you right now it's going to be a big part of their press conference you know coming soon and I'm sure there'll be a Just Dance 3 that they can always
[SPEAKER_04]: X-Differ play a whole lot of Pikmin?
[SPEAKER_06]: I think so I don't know, there's a part of me that feels like now is the time for Nintendo to come out and say it's gotta be next year if not this year, it's got to be next year because the 3DS will be standard by then and they've gotta come out and say okay, here's the next Wii but I don't think it would be the Wii 2 so much as it would be comparing the DS to the DS Lite If it's the Wii 2, is it the Wii Wii?
[SPEAKER_07]: Shut up Maybe it's the Weed
[SPEAKER_04]: VD Sure
[SPEAKER_06]: And why wouldn't it?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, because one thing that Nintendo has done pretty well is the whole back, well, I guess really it's only been on the one series of games, backwards compatibility with the Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: Every GameCube game is playable on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I mean, for the portable systems, it's been pretty good.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because the DS had the Game Boy Advance.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Game Boy Advance had the Game Boy.
[SPEAKER_06]: When you were doing cartridge formats, you kind of couldn't.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I get that.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: and that's why they're not going to embrace that type of mentality because why should they put out a new console that has better graphics on it people don't care and according to them people don't care and really they're just going to be releasing quality games same reason with the whole online argument is like they don't care people don't care about online
[SPEAKER_04]: We too would be weenie in Japanese
Get it?
[SPEAKER_06]: That name will never get old.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: You make a good point.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe this will be the year we finally fucking get F-Zero on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: How about that?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, not gonna happen.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_06]: God, Loki!
[SPEAKER_04]: You're ruining everything!
[SPEAKER_04]: No, you have to understand.
[SPEAKER_04]: What you're gonna get is you're gonna get New Super Mario Bros.
2.
[SPEAKER_04]: No!
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just gonna have some different levels and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: What a goddamn F-Zero game!
[SPEAKER_03]: Wait, I can go for New Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_03]: 2, but if Nintendo re-releases Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_03]: 64 for the 3DS, I will nerd rage.
[SPEAKER_06]: Look, despite all the hatred, all the vicious, vile hatred that Loki's been throwing at Nintendo this entire show, I am telling you, if Reggie comes out at E3 and announces the Wii HD with F-Zero as a launch title, I will jump on stage and do something very naughty.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would not buy it.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's gonna snog him.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would not buy it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a Wii that's gathering dust because I don't play it and there's nothing I want to play on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I could play New Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_04]: on it or Mario Galaxy 2 or something like that, but I haven't even finished Galaxy, so I don't know why I'd want to play Mario Galaxy 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just...
[SPEAKER_04]: The only thing that interests me, and this is going back to once again what they could have done right with Mario Kart, is the modded tracks for Mario Kart.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because that sounds interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ooh, new tracks for Mario Kart.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can go play that game again.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's to stop them?
[SPEAKER_04]: Seriously, what is to stop them other than the fact that they probably didn't program DLC into Mario Kart?
[SPEAKER_04]: But let's just imagine a world where they are forward thinking and actually did that.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's to stop them from saying, hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Instead of putting out a new Mario Kart game, we're just going to have this $10 expansion that's going to add 16 new tracks to the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: People would be damn excited about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: But they're not going to do that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Does this mean you can borrow your President Cat?
[SPEAKER_04]: This is such a forward-thinking company that they're like, oh!
[SPEAKER_04]: Patches to games?
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't need that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Games are perfect when they come out.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's never going to be glitches that we'll need to fix.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, let's just not even bother putting a system in there for that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you hear that David Jaffe, completely random tangent, did you hear that David Jaffe was out there at a Game Developers Conference and I was reading some article about he said that companies should be limited to only three patches in a calendar year and they should not be allowed to patch a game until at least six weeks after release.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, because you know what all that's going to do?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's just going to leave a broken game for longer.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know what he's thinking.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's thinking, oh, if we limited them to this, then they have to make sure the game is working and spend extra time.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, they don't give a shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: They'll just wait longer for it to be fixed.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all that's going to create.
[SPEAKER_04]: And he should shut the hell up and just make his Twisted Metals and God of Wars and be done with it because his crappy Calling All Cars game was terrible.
[SPEAKER_04]: And he talks too much, and he's seriously annoying.
[SPEAKER_03]: Damn, Loki, won't you switch to decaf?
[SPEAKER_04]: He was saying, like, the Wii's terrible.
[SPEAKER_04]: And all of a sudden, oh, hey, you know, maybe we should develop games for the Wii because it's popular.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, so wishy-washy.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, no, seriously, that's a dumb idea with limiting people to patches and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think even some companies... I want to say it's either Microsoft or Sony charges companies for putting out patches or title updates for their games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to say it's probably Microsoft that does that.
[SPEAKER_07]: They like them to put out... So...
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just don't think it's a good idea.
[SPEAKER_04]: What they should do though is if games are buggy, they should have some sort of, I don't know, penalize the developers somehow for putting out buggy games.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have to figure out a system to do that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Make it more expensive to patch?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, because once again, it just leaves broken games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Look at Activision, Black Ops and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a lot of stuff that's just broken with that game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It took them forever to patch that stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just...
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, Ranma, thanks for sitting on the line while Loki bitches.
[SPEAKER_06]: Appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm glad to do my dutiful duty as a proud member of the OL Army.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's going to be so much Nintendo fanboy hate mail this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't wait.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, Ranma, thank you, as always, for your call.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have a good one, buddy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Later.
[SPEAKER_06]: Too bad Loki took up all your time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: I've had friends tell me the best part of the show is when Loki gets mad at something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, no, it's just annoying.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just honesty.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just how it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Game companies nowadays know that they don't have to put out a perfect game.
[SPEAKER_04]: They can just release it buggy.
[SPEAKER_04]: They get a few more sales out there because they don't have to wait for development.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then they patch it later on when they let people basically test it out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why should they hire beta testers when they can go ahead and have the public test it out?
[SPEAKER_04]: They figure out what all the bugs are, read their forums or whatever, go fix those bugs, and then...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: That's how the game industry works.
[SPEAKER_04]: Unfortunately, since now these games can be patched on the fly, there's less focus on putting out a game that's not buggy from the beginning.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, well that's going to do it for the Skype line tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks to those of you guys who got through.
[SPEAKER_06]: To those who didn't get through, call sooner next time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Probably could have fit in another call or two if we had some sooner.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, but for now we're going to go ahead and close the skyline.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you do want to elaborate on some thoughts, though, or you want to respond to Loki, mailbag at orangelonestrater.com is a great place to do it, or on our Twitter at twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_06]: But for now, it's getting to be about 9 o'clock Pacific, midnight on the East Coast.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's probably about time we start to wrap up the show with some final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let me check in, though, real quick.
[SPEAKER_06]: Any other last-minute stories we want to throw in before we wrap up the show?
[SPEAKER_06]: Um...
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll have a lot of fun stuff coming from PAX East and I expect those of you guys that are at PAX East next week, I want phone calls.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is kind of neat, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: Infamous 2 is going to let you create your own missions.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's something.
[SPEAKER_04]: It doesn't even have to be a Mario Kart type game.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can just have a game where you just create your own levels and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: People eat that shit up now.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what the trend is nowadays.
[SPEAKER_04]: Play, share, create.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sony gets it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Somewhat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hope sucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can't be right all the time.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's go around and get everybody's final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm getting worried.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki might need to get some Eidol here pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm just giving you a hard time.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dismanstrating.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's manstrating all over the place.
[SPEAKER_07]: Copyright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: One more last thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, please.
[SPEAKER_04]: By all means.
[SPEAKER_04]: And this is just a rumor, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a rumor that Strider and Frank West are coming as download content.
[SPEAKER_04]: Those will be $5 each, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you, Capcom.
[SPEAKER_07]: I will pay $5 for Strider to hear you.
[SPEAKER_06]: I really want to play the old Strider NES game I know you guys don't like it as much as the Genesis one but I fondly remember the NES one from my childhood I really want to play that again, it's been a long time
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sure glad Loki's back after a C-section.
[SPEAKER_06]: My final thought tonight is... Ow.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, your final thought tonight?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought with a week being off, I'd be able to get more done with the Grand Theft Auto stuff, but some things just take time, I guess, when it comes to modding this stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: And also, I will still be angry at Nintendo because they just continue to disappoint.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't help it.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you make stupid decisions, I'm just going to call you out on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll have plenty more next week on the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, sadly not joining us next week.
[SPEAKER_06]: I won't be sad, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know you won't.
[SPEAKER_06]: But we will be back with another edition of Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll call in from the road.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know if we'll have a temp co-host or what we'll do.
[SPEAKER_07]: You have to call me.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_05]: You have to call me.
[SPEAKER_05]: We can.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: On the road.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yep, that's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're done.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're out of here until next week.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll do this all again next week.
[SPEAKER_06]: But in the meantime, that's another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Remember, of course, if you like what you heard here at Orange Lounge Radio, we are not a gigantic website with millions of hits.
[SPEAKER_06]: We don't have a magazine that backs us or a gaming company that backs us.
[SPEAKER_06]: We don't throw a bunch of commercials in your face.
[SPEAKER_06]: So all we ask, if you enjoy Orange Lounge Radio, tell some friends about the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: The example at the start of the show where a friend was playing it at his lamb party.
[SPEAKER_06]: Perfect example is an awesome A-plus move.
[SPEAKER_06]: So just tell people about the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Help spread the word about Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Get us some more voices to bring to the table here at the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't send DarkSakura a dollar.
[SPEAKER_06]: But come back next week for more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_02]: To join us for a live show, visit www.allgames.com Sunday nights at 6pm Pacific Time.
[SPEAKER_02]: The views and opinions expressed on Orange Lounge Radio do not necessarily reflect those of the entire staff of Orange Lounge Radio or allgames.com, but we're probably right anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: See you next week!
Thanks for watching!