Orange Lounge Radio
Who's your hosts?
Dark Sakura, Sky, and Loku
Tonight, March 25th, 2012
A classic arcade game will come to Xbox Live Arcade with Kinect controls
Amazon stopped stocking one release from this month
And could games soon carry a warning similar to cigarettes?
Orange Lounge Radio
Hello my friends out there on the internet and welcome back to another week of the show where every gamer has a voice
It's Orange Lounge Radio
And we're live with the 451st episode of our show for this
March the 25th of 2012
My name is Rob Roberts, I'll be joining you over the next few hours to talk about games and gaming culture and all that good stuff
With my co-hosts, first off, Dark Sakura or Jamie Summers
Hi
How are you?
Um, hungry
Hungry?
Are you about to participate in the Hunger Games? You're so hungry?
Shut up
Or the Hungry Hungry Hippo Games?
No I'm actually not hungry because I had broth but I will be fasting every Sunday now
Now is this a religious thing?
No
Well you never know, it's worth the shot right?
It's for my health
Okay, like a new, I don't want to say new craze but
No it's not
It's something I've been debating doing for like the last year or so so now I'm actually doing it
So I'm assuming you've done the appropriate research and all that good stuff
Yes
Just letting the listeners know
So
It's not something you're doing on a whim
In a month I will be discussing my results
Are you incorporating any exergaming into this?
Same stuff I'm always doing, I do yoga like every day
Mhm
So
Okay
Yeah
Alright, also say hello to definitely not fasting, Techmaster Loki
Funny you used to say that actually
My wife wants me to do that too starting after
Do you think your wife may or may not have been influenced by a co-host on this show?
No she did that because she had to not eat for a couple days for procedures she just had done so
She's like well if I can keep doing that I can lose some weight
Well this is dangerous territory though
No fasting actually isn't bad for you
It's a gaming show we're getting way off topic but this is much different than you know some people don't eat
I mean it seems like with this fasting thing you're still eating some and it's a scheduled thing
You're still eating some nutritional value things
It's just not a lot of the other stuff
It's basically just cutting out you know
And part of it for me that I really like about it is that I have a full 24 hours where I don't think about food
I have been more productive I've gotten so much stuff done
And honestly I felt super energized after I was done with my first one
That was Wednesday from 3 o'clock p.m. to Thursday 3 o'clock p.m.
Went to yoga that night felt great
And it really is kind of crazy it's just sort of like my energy level shot way up
I'm just trying to draw a clear line between what you're doing and what someone with a mental disorder who doesn't eat does
But I'm just trying to make that distinction clear
A person with a mental disorder would just not eat
You know completely not
Or maybe do like what was her face on the Partridge family Susan Day
Who ate nothing but carrots and turned orange
That happened to me when I was a baby
Well yeah it's beta-carotene
It's different when you're a baby
Yeah but I mean I'm saying that you know there's people that will just you know do all the stuff
And this is really something that I've put research into and read a bunch of different stuff
And I'm doing what I do with anything
I try it for a month
I see how I feel
Check my health
And this is someone who used to get blood tested every six months so
Just want to make that clear for the listeners
Especially if it's your first time listening
Just want to make that clear
There's a clear difference here
I'm not stupid
Alright
Loki sorry to cut you off but
Wanted to make sure the listeners understood that
But you are you are clearly indulging in a feast tonight
With your bacon and garlic pizza
I call that a meal but you know
Alright you can join us live here
We are of course live tonight Sunday night
So we're always here Sundays at All Games Radio
www.allgames.com
6 o'clock Pacific 9 o'clock Eastern
Right after the Bobby Black Wolf show
Although as he mentioned tonight he's going on a brief hiatus for the next two weeks
So you'll just have to tune in right at 6 o'clock for the next couple weeks
Because we'll be on there at All Games Radio
Again www.allgames.com
We also always have our chat room with us
www.chat.orangeloungeradio.com
If you want to join us and chat with us throughout the evening
And some folks are coming up with cute little names
Fitness Lounge Radio from ActDeaf
And Diet Diet Revolution there from Hitstun
There you go
Alright
We're going to get into some gaming news
And how our gaming weeks were and all that
But usually we have a little kick off topic here at the start
And I want to talk about this tonight
Because this is what lots of people
Lots of people are talking about
Facebook is any indication
It's like everybody's freaking talking about this
And that's that movie The Hunger Games
Which is announced today
Best non-sequel opening ever
Best, it beat Twilight
Which can't be bad news
I personally have not seen the movie myself
I haven't read the books or anything
I'm interested in seeing the movie
Mostly because all my friends are like
It's so good, it's so good
And I'm not going to hate something just because it's good
Loki you're doing it, did you go see it?
I'm not sure the wife took you to see it
What did you think?
No the wife didn't take me to see it
I had tickets to see it
Oh sorry, how dare I?
It was free
Free popcorn
It was alright
My wife had described it as Battle Royale meets Twilight
As in there's boyfriend, girlfriend, garbage
And people killing each other
The best description I read on the internet was
Battle Royale for soccer moms
It's not really, no
I mean they don't really touch on the whole relationship stuff that much
It's just kind of briefly there
And it actually is part of a plot point
It's not necessarily, without spoiling too much
They try to work up the whole relationship thing
To get more sponsors, to get more perks
In the actual games themselves
And so that's kind of why they're doing it that way
But it's not even like that big a deal
But I wouldn't go as far as saying, oh my god it's Battle Royale
Although I do have to say that the filmmaker
Must have gone to the Michael Bay school of camera work
Because that shit was shaky all over the goddamn place
I would rather you not mention that evil person's name
Oh does this have to do with a certain Ninja Turtle?
Shut up
Yes
I want to make this clear too
It was not bad
And Woody Harrelson's in it
That's always a pleasant surprise
Because Woody Harrelson's character is awesome
Before the Battle Royale, or excuse me before, oh boy
Before the Hunger Games fans shoot me down with a bow and arrow
I want to talk about the Battle Royale thing
Because I do think people are running a little far with this whole comparison thing
Because, hello, Battle Royale's like 12 years old
It's based, it's a completely different kind of book
That's very political in nature
Of course they're going to time the re-release with what's going on here
Because of the distant similarity
But my whole thing is that, you know, well for one
There was what? There was Logan's run
There was the Stephen King novel back in the 70's
You know, there's been other stuff about this type of topic too
And, how can you go Battle Royale and Hunger Games
Or like the same movie and Hollywood doesn't
How can you say that?
And turn your head away from the fact that we have this
Julia Roberts Snow White movie
And Chick from Twilight Snow White movie
Coming out within literally three months of each other
Going on over here
To which I hear the trailer for both were being played before the Hunger Games
And I'm like, how can you fucking sit there and compare the Hunger Games to Battle Royale
When this shit's going on?
No, they did not have the Mirror Mirror trailer
But yeah, I'm well aware of Mirror Mirror
At first I thought they were the same movie
I'm like, man, that first trailer was really dark
But this one makes it look like a comedy
I'm really confused with what's going on here
Right?
But, uh, yeah, it's just, um, it's a little bit dark
I mean, it's not as dark as Battle Royale
I mean, there's killing and stuff
And they have kind of the same stuff
There's alliances and, you know, that kind of thing
But I think Battle Royale is a lot darker
I mean, it's a little bit similar where they, you know, pick people
You know, fight to the death and stuff like that
But at the same time, it's just, it's a little weird
I don't know
Gamer Girl in our chatroom says Logan's run is getting a re-release too
And that's not really surprising
Anything remotely resembling the Hunger Games is gonna come back
Because, again, it's the biggest non-sequel ever
It has come to take Harry Potter's place for a few years in Hollywood as the young adult
Because ain't no one gonna admit they like Twilight
Next year we'll see The Long Walk and then another Lord of the Flies
That's the Stephen King novel I was trying to think of
They'll adapt that
That shit is getting green-lit
Then we'll get an American Battle Royale
I hope not
The next one's gonna be Andrew's Game
That's gonna be the next big one that's gonna be coming out in a year from now
By the way, you know, Logan's run came out the year I was born
Oh, really?
Yeah
Wow, that's an old movie
You set yourself up for that
I'm telling you right there
Ready Player One?
You finish that shit
That is gonna be box office gold right there
Here's what I really wanted to talk about
I didn't want to be at Hunger Games podcast tonight
What I really wanted to talk about was
Again, biggest non-sequel ever
And they kinda knew this was gonna happen, right?
Where's the video game?
Now, before you write your emails and chatters
Yes, I'm aware of the iOS video game
That's the whole indie developer collaboration
I've played it
It's pretty sweet
But it is a very simple game
That is a light, tight
I mean, it's fucking free
And it's got a pretty cool soundtrack
It's worth looking at
But it's not a video game based on the movie
It wouldn't work
How so?
How so? Because there's not really anything you could do
You play as a character and you go and kill other kids
I mean, do they really want a killing kids video game?
Ten years ago on this show, we used to love Battle Royale
Remember when we all first saw that movie?
We had the paper play stuff
And we said, there is no fucking way this movie is ever coming out in America
They are not gonna do it
And now they are
You can't put kids killing kids on the screen
Not in this day and age, ten years ago
In the wake of Columbine
And the reason why Battle Royale is coming out
Is because the mainstream studios wouldn't bring it out
And I think it's either Anchor Bay
Or some Hong Kong movie distributor
That's actually putting it out over here
It's not necessarily some mainstream
It's not like Warner Brothers or Lionsgate
Or something like that
It's putting it out here
But it wouldn't work
It's so much smaller scale
It wouldn't really work as an action game
Or a stealth action game
Or something like that
Because there's only twelve
Or twenty-four kids originally in that
And it's just not
Whereas Battle Royale is a little bit more free form
It's just hunting people down
And stuff like that
It just wouldn't really work
Now the later movies
Or later books would work
I was just about to say
Maybe, now without spoiling
But I understand the later books
Are more of a
Her against the government type of piece
Put it very plainly like that
So maybe that would translate better towards a video game
Yeah, that might work
Go to our chatroom
At chat.orangelinesradio.com
Stan says
I would love to see an American Battle Royale movie
With Selena Gomez, Justin Bieber, and all them assholes
Shoot each other
Except, wait a minute
There wasn't a lot of shooting in Battle Royale
There was some, but not a lot
There was plenty of gunfire
I thought most people died from explosives
And there was some
Like I remember
Meetsco got a hold of the thing
And then dude went all out with the automatic gun
And
Alright, so there were no guns in this movie
Which was my complaint
I'm like, okay
Because spoiling
Well, I don't know if I want to spoil
Don't, let me read another comment from chat
Derek Gage in chat says
Titanic was a sequel?
Hold on, I said biggest opening weekend
Remember, Titanic made all its money
Because it was number one at the box office for like
What, four or five months?
Because
A lot of people were going to see it multiple times
I'll admit, I saw Titanic in the theater three times
I didn't
I saw it once on VHS and I wanted to kill myself
It's not that I loved Titanic
But you have to
I realized my dad was very into Titanic stuff
Way before the movie
I remember watching a National Geographic special
And I was like seven years old, way before the movie
And I went to see it with him
Then I went to see it with some other friends in college
Because a bunch of them hadn't seen it and wanted to go
And then I ended up seeing it one other time
Really cheap for some reason
And you know, it was
It was a good movie
But I won't see this 3D re-release
I will not see the 3D re-release
But it's James Cameron doing 3D
That might not be bad
I don't care
So anyhow
So you're saying the Hunger Games
video game didn't happen because it's not possible
Even though it wouldn't be good
It would seem like there's all these
video game movie games that come out
Although, not a lot lately
Right? They never did a video game
for The Dark Knight
Right?
One had been cancelled or something like that I think
I don't think any had been announced for this
new Batman movie, which you think would be a perfect
tie-in
Surely they've got to be doing an Avengers game, right?
No, at least not that I'm aware
There's a Facebook game
The next movie game that they have coming out
is Madagascar 3
Did the movie video game genre die?
No, see in the month of May
You have Madagascar 3
from D3
You have two from Activision
Men in Black
and Battleship
The movie based off the board game
The video game based off the movie
based off the board game
And we will still not have our Liam Neeson
saying E5
Liam Neeson's awesome
My problem with the movie
Spoiler!
Even though it's not out yet
He dies! And I don't fucking
care about the rest of the movie after he dies
He needs to be there punching
aliens in the face
Just get out of the fucking battleship
He doesn't need the goddamn battleship
You can just punch him in the face with a goddamn broken bottle on his hand
I can't believe you would ruin Battleship the movie
Oh yeah, that
Who cares? So what? He dies, big deal
Honestly, Battleship the movie
is like Independence Day
You look back at Independence Day
I loved the movie, but it was fucking ridiculous
It made no sense, it was just ridiculous
This is true
But you know what? It's a fucking
I saw Independence Day
I think the second, the third, and the fourth
And maybe the fifth
I saw it like four or five days in a row
And it was great
every time
Did they make a video game out of Independence Day? I don't remember
Yes, they did on the Playstation 1
And it was fucking terrible
It really was
AcidicVampire in chat says
I hope the Battleship movie climaxes with a strategic battle
in the style of the board game
Me too, that's the only way you could convince me to see it
Liam Neeson and Rihanna
sit down and they go to town
on a game of Battleship
I don't even care, I think it's gonna be awesome
I mean, it's such a terrible
It's a movie you go into and you know
what it is, it's just explosions
and nonsense, that's Michael Bay for you
Explosions and nonsense, if that's what you want
then you go see that movie
And that's what I want, so I'm gonna go see that movie
And I'll see The Avengers because that looks awesome
But I
do need to catch up on the Avenger
movies, you know, leading up
to it because I've only seen Iron Man 1
I have only seen, you and I are in the same boat
Oh my gosh, you and I need to
get together and do this because
I have only seen Iron Man 1, that's it
I haven't seen any of the others
None of them, didn't see Thor, didn't see
Captain America
It's not that I, I'm not hating
I just, seriously, last year
I did not go to the movie, I didn't go to the movies at all
last year, you had a kid, I'm lazy
I saw Thor, Thor was good
I didn't see the second Iron Man movie
because it's just pretty much
Robert Downey Jr. being Robert Downey Jr
How's that a bad thing?
Drunken asshole
That Robert Downey Jr.
No, that's fine, that's fine
I own it, I just haven't bothered to see it yet
It's sort of like I wasn't excited
I liked the first one
And I saw Hulk
Even though it's, you know, not the same
Dude, I think it's like, same universe-ish thing
Which, honestly, I really wish they had had Edward Norton
Really wish they had Edward Norton
He was so good
You met the other guy, right?
Yeah, I have, he signed my Xbox
But man, I, Hawkeye
Black Wolf in Chat says
You guys did notice in the first Battleship trailer
that the bombs were in the shape of Battleship pins, right?
Yes, I did
I didn't notice that
So are there any other big movies this summer
that I'm not thinking of
that might have video games made out of them?
Seems like there was a lot of stuff coming out this summer
Um
I'm trying to think
No
I honestly don't remember what the summer lineup is this year
I mean, other than Batman
and the new Snow White movie
Which
I don't know, looks
alright, I'm gonna have to go see it though
My wife wants to see it
Alright, look, we'll start to talk more about the summer stuff
when it gets closer to summer
For now, let's talk about right now
this week, the types of video games we've been
playing this week in a segment we call
How Was Your Gaming Week? DarkSakura, how was your gaming week?
My gaming week was
retro
We bought Bust-A-Move 2
as in Puzzle Bobble
Arcade Edition for the PlayStation
And
My husband and I actually
had a fairly even match in playing
even though I'm usually the
much better player
Um
We also picked up
Taito Legends for PS2
and so
I have that on Xbox One
And so a lot of this afternoon was spent with
my husband screaming at Rainbow Islands
and screaming at Super Kicks
and then playing the hell
out of Rastan
And we also decided
that the biplane shooter
Tokyo sucks
And
And while this wasn't
we have video games related
to the series, but I have to say
that watching
the Evangelion 2.22
really is kind of depressing
but awesome
Just saying
Awesome, so it sounds like it was a bit of a retro day
with the Taito stuff
There's a series that had its ending changed
Yeah
If you want to talk about
partially from fan complaint
and partially from the creator wanting to
expand on it more
And it made no fucking sense
And guess what? They're redoing the whole thing now
in a series of movies
Alright, before we get to Loki's gaming week
from the chatroom at chat.orangelaungeradio.com
Some folks in the chat are naming
some other possible
titles. Tiger Claws says
maybe they should make a video game on Prometheus
That's supposed to be a pretty big one, right?
Well technically there's the
colonial marines which is coming out later
this year, so that could tie into
Prometheus
Infidel names one that I
particularly am looking forward to seeing
Abraham Lincoln Vampire Hunter
That would be pretty awesome
I'm looking forward to that one
Platinum Games putting it together, that'd be awesome
Meanwhile, your gaming week, Loki
So let's see, this week I didn't play a lot of games
I played
Call of Duty briefly
because I was only working for three days this week
The rest of the time
I've been just working
working in Excel
Why would I try to program something
in Excel? Because I'm weird like that
So, I like
programming it
No, it's not a secret, it never was
It was, um, I'm making a map editor
for Grand Theft Auto IV
It actually works, it's just fucking slow
because it's in Excel
In Excel
How does a map editor in Excel work?
Meaning you draw it out in the little cells?
No, no, no, it's like
basically it opens
a format, it's like a
WPL, it's a placement list or something like that
You can
import stuff I make out of
the Simple Native Trainer
which is a trainer in the game, you can spawn
objects, move them around, place them and stuff
and you can export those to a file
and dump them into this and then I can save them as
the actual map files that are used by the games
Huh
I can actually
paste the hex code in there
from, you know, you open up the file in the
hex editor and dump it in there and it'll actually
read everything and, you know, you can also save
it as that and it'll
do that fun stuff
But it works, and it's weird because
the editors that they have
out there now are broken, they don't really work
well, so the fact that I'm making something very
inefficiently, it works
and that's all I care about, is the fact that it works
Because I don't know how to program
in C Sharp or C++
or whatever, I could
I could, you know
learn how to
do that, but it just, for some reason
my mind can't wrap around that, yet complex
stuff in Excel I can do that
It's weird, like
Ridiculous formula, I mean
Let me put it this way, my Excel
file, I had to go, I had to convert it to
the new format because I was gonna try to make it
compatible with everything else, it ended up being
75 megabytes
It's huge. Will it work in open office?
Uh, no. Open office doesn't
really work that well for this
So, that was that
And then, kind of a weird
It's not weird
Something I'm doing, as I mentioned before
Mark Ruffalo's signed by Xbox before
and a couple other people have as well
So, now I have this Xbox that I'm kinda
using, it's almost like an autograph book
I get celebrities to sign it, you know
I don't know if people always consider these
people celebrities, but
Like, this week I had, we had a visit
from Duff Goldman
from, you know, Ace of Cakes
Duff Beer? No, not Duff Beer
From Ace of Cakes, or, you know
Charm City Cakes, you know, really cool guy
So, I had him sign my Xbox
He must have went like, I'm a cake maker
Why am I signing an Xbox?
He thought it was cool. Of course, he could see the other people
Yeah, he thought it was cool, I'm like
Oh, cause he wasn't really doing
signing of stuff, and I'm like, well hey
Can you sign my Xbox? He's like
Sure, who else has signed this
so far? I'm like, here's Orlando Bloom
Here's Mark Ruffalo, and Christopher
Thornton. Christopher Thornton is kinda
He's a
director, and he's not really a
Yeah, I mean, Orlando Bloom, that's
pretty awesome. That's almost like one of those like
you know, when they auction off the giant
like, you know, quilt
that every celebrity under the sun has signed
for a charity, it's like you're building one of those
for like D-list celebrities
Well, it's not even, I wouldn't consider
Orlando Bloom or Mark Ruffalo, who's starring
as the Hulk in the Avengers
B-list. Whatever, fine
But, I mean, it's just, I had
I have signatures from a bunch of different celebrities
at my work, like a bunch of posters
but they're sitting in a pile on my desk
and collecting dust, like I have
William H. Macy
and I had
Oh, who the hell is
Jeff Goldblum at one time
He's just, that guy is
fucking weird
He is, like, you know how quirky he is
and like everything, like movies and stuff
He is like that in real life, he's just weird
Just like this really
strange, off the wall
type guy, but you know, it's just like
stuff like that, I had
Rob Schneider sign a copy of the animal
I had on VHS
He was wearing a weird cowboy hat at the time
too, that was kind of funny
But yeah, like, you know, we met before
he died, you know, we met
Patrick Swayze
So that was kind of cool
I like to get pictures
Well, yeah, I get pictures
too, but you know, I just
I figured, because I like
I keep my Xbox in better shape
than those posters, so the way I figured
it's more of an honor to sign this
Xbox than it is
I can't, I mean
this guy is a big geek
He was talking about totally geeking out
at, like, LucasArts and
Skywalker Ranch and stuff like that when they went
and made the cake there, and, you know
Did he also try to fling meatloaf at George Lucas?
Hey!
But, uh, you know, so
I think that, I'm sure that
he plays video games, I'm sure that
he thought it was cool, so, whatever
I like Derek H.'s counter about Mark
Ruffalo's celebrity status, Derek H. says
Well, Ruffalo is Bruce Banner
A few hundred computers are playing the Hulk
That is true True facts
True facts, alright
Fair enough
Anything else you want to get out of there for your game?
Ummmm
I think that's all I've played
No, I tried playing a little bit of the Mario
Portal game, the Mario
game, and it's weird, I mean
I can't play that on my laptop, because it's
It's an art piece Yeah, it's just
It doesn't play very well with, like, a touchpad
I'm just, I'm not
very keyboard mouse, so it's very
awkward for me to play that Oh, yeah, yeah
So, it's just, um,
yeah, it's a little weird
Alright, well, that's it
Then my gaming week, um
As I mentioned earlier, I tried that new Hunger Games
on the iPhone Sorry, sorry, sorry
One, uh, I'd like
I did play one game
a lot this week, actually, I completely forgot
Um, Super Stardust Delta
Oh I love that game
It's actually really awesome That's right
Our buddy, uh, Brad from Pod Culture
Yes, he hooked me up with the code, and I've
been playing the crap out of that, and it's actually
a really fun game Yeah? Because I'm thinking about
getting it It's definitely worth it
It's very fun I still never cashed
in my 3G thing I never
did either That feature on my Vita
has literally gone to waste, I think I have till the
31st to do something with it, or you lose it
or something like that, so I gotta make sure I get that taken care of
You know, who cares
I think, well, they have the GPS, though, with
the, um, 3G ones, so
I mean, that's kinda helpful, but
Yeah, I mean, I just can't use
3G, I don't know
Alright, if you're finally done
I'm done, sorry Alright, my gaming week
Quickly, before I talk video games, I need to talk
board games, because I went to a board game
party yesterday, it was actually a lot of fun, and I got to
play some new board games, and one of them that I really
really really really liked was called
Seven Wonders, so I'm sure some of you
board card game enthusiasts will know this game
and, um, you know, not that I think
they should turn every game into an
Xbox game, but some of them have worked rather
well, right? Like, um, you know, Ticket to Ride
and Catan and all that, right? So,
um, I would like to see Seven Wonders
because that was, I had a lot of fun playing that game
that was cool They have a game called Seven Wonders
it's just one of those, a match three games
Oh, that's not even the same thing
this is a more, it was kinda like
it actually, to me, felt, and
Alan made this comment too, like, the stages
of the game are similar to, like, civilization
it's resource
collecting, and then you can kinda
head yourself into technology
or military, or
like, what I would call cultural
types of points, you know, you can kinda
it's, it's either really inspired
by civilization or kinda right down that same line
but you know I love Civ, so I like
this game too
and, uh, some
other friends of ours came
over, we played Dominion again
which I think I've talked about that on the show, but that's a card game I really
enjoy, that would be really hard to pull
off on a console though, I think that's something you really have to play
in person because there's so many ways you can kinda mix and match
the different cards and the expansions and all that
so yeah, I've been playing, like
tangible games this week
crazy, video games though
haven't been short on those
last week I talked about how I have
suddenly, just
I wanna say out of the blue, but not really
like Shane from Hoard House
kinda, like, we'll just say
he berated me into playing these games
but it worked, the games are really good, Mass Effect, right?
I
beat Mass Effect 1
now, I realize a lot of you might be going
yay, golf clap
for you, you beat a game that came out
five years ago, but really think about
that statement if you've been listening to Orange House Radio
for any length of time
I had the attention span
to beat a game, playing it
start to finish, that is
a huge endorsement I think for the game
so yes, I beat Mass Effect, and what did I do
when I beat Mass Effect? I put in my
Mass Effect 2 disc that I picked up last week for
twenty bucks, and I started on Mass Effect 2
so I'm about nine hours
into Mass Effect 2
and now I'm going to go home and start
Mass Effect tomorrow
yes, and now Jamie is taking my Mass Effect on Xbox
and she said she's going to check it out
however, she understands
she hasn't until the time I beat
Mass Effect 3 to finish
it, because then I want to play Mass Effect 1
again as a renegade
and as a woman, so I can have
lesbian romance
I'm just going to start off as a woman, because I play every game as a woman
because, it's fun
so
have you played Saints Row the Third yet?
me? tons
no, I haven't, because we don't have
a system that I can play it on right now
unless someone would like to lend me a copy of it
don't you have, I have the
361 from you still, right, so
you want to borrow the 361? sure
alright, I'm going to give it to her
alright, I forgot you even had it
well there you go, alright
so
yeah, I've been playing Mass Effect 2
again, I don't know
how constructive it is for me to review
a game that's about 2 or 3 years old
but, what? one question from AcidicVampire
who did you choose to bang?
I did not bang anyone
in Mass Effect 1, because
I am waiting for Mass Effect 3
because I know who I want to bang
and I know that they're not bangable until the third game
so, let me put it
this way, I made a very
important choice, I'm keeping this
spoiler free, I made a very important choice
in the first game
that will set it up so that in the third game
this person will be around
for me to bang, and I will bang them
lots
so that's, I'll just
leave it at that
let's see, what else
now I'm off track here, oh yeah, Mass Effect 2
the game's a few years old, but
it's, it's, it's really good
it's really, like the story, everything
is like, just a step up
in the storytelling and in the voice acting
and everything, like it's not that the first game was bad
but the second game is just even more, I have like
laughed out loud at the game
there's a particular character I just got
into my little squad that, like, literally
made me laugh out loud with what they were saying
it was, it was, it's awesome
the graphics
are a step up
they got rid of the Mako stuff
thank god, planet scanning's
a little derpy, that gets a little bit old
really fast, but whatever, the hacking's
better, the combat
I'm still, I still have
mixed feelings on, like I know a lot of people
generally agree that combat in 2
is better than combat in 1, but
I will agree it's more fast paced
because you can kind of map skills to buttons
so you don't have to bring up the menu
and you can kind of do things that way, but
I don't know, like, I kind of find, I don't like the way
that, just, enemies keep coming out
in waves and waves and waves
and you're kind of just, like, stuck in one spot
gunning them all down
at least that's the way I kind of find them doing it
just kind of gunning them all down until the way's finally over
and you can kind of move into the next room
like, I feel like the first game kind of made you
it was a little more Metal Gear in the way that
the enemies didn't just run out until they actually
saw you, so I
kind of, like, it made the
conflicts a little more consistent
but don't take that
as a harsh gripe on the game, I mean, it's a
really minor bitch, it doesn't take away
from the experience of the story
that I'm really, really, really enjoying
so
there you go
um, let's see
uh
what else have I been playing, what other game I want to mention
uh, on the Vita
ModNation Racers Road Trip
I played on the Vita for a little bit
it's okay
you know, it is what it is, it's the
PlayStation 3 version condensed down for the Vita
the graphics and everything
are, you know, pretty good
they look like they do on the PlayStation 3
the track editor
I was very impressed that it's pretty much all there
you can import all the stuff
from the PlayStation, which is pretty impressive
and, you know, you can, therefore
build up a pretty, pretty good library
of stuff, the only problem with
ModNation Racers is
they stripped out everything
online about the game
the only thing you can do online on the Vita
version is, like, have ghost racers
and you can download other people's tracks
but you can't do races online
which is kind of an
important element of custom
it's because a lot of these games
are just not able to do
that's why you get a lot of this asynchronous
multiplayer garbage
I mean, you can do ad hoc
in the same room, and do it that way
but it just, I don't know
it really feels lacking
and I'm kind of sitting here going
this racing game gets kind of basic
after you play it for a while
like, yeah, there's some interesting
power-ups and things they do, but
I mean, at the end of the day, I'm just like
this game gets kind of old
so, I mean, at least
it's only 30 bucks, I rented it through
I have an account with a game rental
company, and so I got it through a rental
but I think it's a worthy
rental, I don't know if I would pay 30 bucks
for it, if you really like racers
I'm sure you're getting a lot of objects for it
through the, you know, passing
I need some, check into Nier while you're here
because I need some of those objects
so, you know
we're going to talk about this later, because there's a story
coming up about LittleBigPlanet
Kart or whatever
I kind of, you know, everyone
the trailer looks cool, but it kind of
made my heart sink when I heard
by the creators of ModNation Racism
like, ugh
because their load time is fucking terrible
Yeah, the load time's really bad
but see, I
I was really surprised
at how much the online
piece being missing really hurt
the game, because I wouldn't call
the one on the Playstation 3 a basic bitch
tracer, because the community
element kind of saves it
because there really is just a
stronger sense of community in the Playstation
3 one, and you can really get these random
organic experiences
in the Playstation 3 one that just feel
very forced and very
vanilla on the Vita one, and that's
the problem with it. I mean, it's
impressive that they otherwise got
most of the Playstation 3 one
in there, I hope
LittleBigPlanet didn't get neutered this way
but then again, LittleBigPlanet, you could
play LittleBigPlanet online, but it wasn't as
key to that game
you know, I think LittleBigPlanet Vita will be alright
See, here's my question though, is if they
if they did that, though
you know, if it's really neutered, I guess
on the Vita version, do you
have the PSP version? Because I think
I got that as a PSP version
I'm wondering if it was neutered on there too
or if they had
online gameplay on the PSP one, but they're just
like, ehhh, the Vita
we're not gonna worry about writing netcode
God, that's work, so let's just
forget about it. Nah, I haven't played the
PSP one, or if I did, it was a long time ago
so I don't remember. Maybe they have some sort of
weird like, stipulation where you
can only have
multiplayer like, um, in your
game if you can play it over the 3G
or something, because I know only
right now there's two games that
have actual, well, three games
that actually have online multiplayer
and those are all the ones that have online passes
the Hotshots, Golf, Wipeout
and MLB 12
are the only games
I don't know if Unit 13 does
I don't think that did though
but those are the three
and possibly four games that I know of
right now that actually have, you know,
multiplayer. Um, now
I'll say this, I don't want to
totally bash out Monday's Racers because I don't think
it's a bad game necessarily, and
we have to remember it's a launch title
and for a launch title, it's surprisingly
decent
you know, I say that, you know, it's a
strong launch title for
the Vita, but it's not as
strong as say, Luminous
there's some of the other choices that are out there
um, or what also kind of
shoots this game in the foot a little bit is that
I have to say that free MotorStorm
game they put out last week
it's kind of a
better racing experience for me
I mean, maybe because it was free, but
and it was more like Ironman
off-road racing
which I really enjoy that style, but
well, see, the thing is, like, I'm kind of
embracing a little bit more of the
online, or not even online, some of the
digital stuff now
um, thanks to some of these offerings
the fact that, well, the fact that the Michael Jackson
game was free was kind of fun, but um,
you know, the, the
MotorStorm game is pretty awesome, and
I'm actually thinking of thinning out
my collection, because I have four games right now
in cart form, and I'm probably
gonna, well, Lil Deviance is gone
I mean, that game looked like terrible, terrible shit
um, and actually
Rayman, um, Origins
I'm probably gonna get rid of, because
I'm just not playing it, not that it's
a terrible game, it's not a terrible game at all
it's an awesome game, but it's just
I'm not finding myself playing, or
wanting to play that game, so, I don't know
uh, go to our chatroom at chat.orangelaundry.com
I'm just now catching up
on some of the, uh, comments from chat
AcidicVampire says, the characters
in Mass Effect 2 are some of the best
characters in any video game
you know what, I gotta say
although I haven't played enough of
Mass Effect 2 to really say
that's true or that's false, I
can see so far where that is
probably a true statement
because there is some strong characters in
part 2, like even, and it's
it's so funny I'm sitting here saying that, because
as I keep saying this about 2, I feel like I'm
bashing 1, but I'm
not, it's just that 1 set the bar
pretty high, and 2 actually
exceeds it, in almost
every area, so
pretty neat
and Shane says, picks
of Kaiden put him over to actually trying
the series out, that may or may not
be true, just saying
I deny these allegations
alright, that's enough about our
gaming weeks, let's get into some gaming news
after I quickly mention some housekeeping
um, don't forget to visit us on Twitter
twitter.com slash o-l-r, we're also on
Facebook, facebook.com slash orange
lounge radio, also searchable on
google plus, at orange lounge
radio, we have a steam community, lots
of places you can find the o-l
army, as we call the fans of the show
remember the number 1 rule of the o-l
army though, don't be a dick
if you're gonna play games online, don't be a dick
just be nice, that's it, you know
it goes a long way, if you wanna find other fans
of orange lounge radio and all your favorite gaming places
check out orange lounge radio.com in the upper
right hand corner, extended play
that box will have a bunch of logos to
other sites that we have a presence on
so check it out at orange lounge radio.com
let's get into gaming news, Loki
well, there's rumors that Sony is
shutting down one of their first party
developers, Zipper Interactive
who just put out the
Evita game, Unit 13
um, they may be
gone, um, apparently
there's been some chatter for several days
about an impending closure
and the possibility of cancellations
of a current project
of course Sony hasn't made a comment on it
and besides, you know, Unit 13
they're of course the ones behind
SOCOM, US Navy Seals, and
MAG, so they
kind of know they're shooters
but, I don't know
maybe is this because they can't really compete
with, say, Call of Duty
or Battlefield, maybe this is why they're
kind of letting them go, and I don't know, restructuring
who knows
hmm, well
it's never good to hear about Studios
Closing, but
I mean, wasn't SOCOM still a pretty
strong series, or did I miss something?
Um, I don't know how well SOCOM
4 did, um
I would have thought that they would have
you know, tried to, well maybe
they tried with MAG, maybe that was the whole thing
is, um, you know, they were trying to
you know, do something with that, but
maybe it just didn't really
work out, also
also, but it also is a rumor
also, the other thing
might have kind of hurt SOCOM 4
was the fact that SOCOM 4 launched right
before the whole Playstation Network
black out there. Oh, that's right
I thought I remembered there was something
that kind of like about SOCOM 4
that was like, iffy in the community
that's right, that's what it was
the fact that it came out the week they took
the network down for like a month
yeah, that probably didn't help
no, but interesting
that all this time later, something
happens. I'm also surprised
if that, in spite of that, they didn't try to
relaunch SOCOM for the holidays
or maybe they did, and I just, you know, that's not usually
a series I follow, so, but I
I'm surprised there wouldn't be like a SOCOM 4
game of the year edition
since that's what they're all called
or SOCOM 4 Platinum Guns edition
or something, that comes out at the end of the year
to try and relaunch it. I'm surprised
too, I mean, um
I don't know, I didn't think SOCOM 4
is a bad game, it, I think it got
pretty good reviews, it's just
um, I don't know
maybe it's just not enough room right now
maybe they're focusing on something else
maybe, maybe, maybe they're just getting rid
of these guys because they're going to have someone else working on SOCOM
who knows, maybe, um
you know, I don't know who, um
you know, the team behind resistance, what
they're working on right now, maybe they're going to be working
on a new SOCOM game or something like that
or kill, the team behind Killzone
you know, maybe they're free now, because Killzone
I don't know, well actually
Killzone might do alright
I think that if they went the route
of, with SOCOM that they
did with, just recently with Killzone 3
where they released a multiplayer
kind of, as free and then had people play
it and then you can, you know, kind of
free to play almost, with uh
you know, where you pay 15 bucks if you want to play the full
um, or level up fully
I think that might be a way to go with SOCOM
because, you know, actually free to
play would be perfect for a lot of games
but, it might help it out
especially since people like military first person shooters
and free is an awesome
amount of money for something
alright, well we'll see
what develops with that over the next
few months, I'm sure by E3 we'll see
what they're up to or not
um, meanwhile over in
Xbox territory there is yet another
arcade promotion going on
so it seems like Xbox
Microsoft and all of them have found success
in these, you know, summer of arcade
what's the winner one called? Block Party
right, so
since it's so successful, let's do it quarterly
let's do another one, alright, so now we have
Arcade Next starts
on April 18th
gotta say though, there are some pretty big
you know, titles here, Trials Evolution
is the first one, that is actually really big
I mean, you saw what their, Trials is a big
deal right, well yeah, but the level editor
in this thing is like little big planet-esque
I mean, it's like, you can make all
sorts of things, people made first person shooters
using that level editor
Bloodforge on April 25th
Fable Heroes on
May 2nd, now that is not the
it's not on Rails Fable, that's the
Mario Party Fable, right? That looks alright
it's kind of like a little bit Mario Party
crossed with Castle
Crashers, I guess, alright
interesting, and then
obviously this is the huge one
the big one, May 9th, Minecraft
is gonna be 1600
Microsoft points and
it should be noted too that because
of the recent change in the gamerscore
for Arcade, all of these games
will now offer the 400 gamerscore
it's not gonna be, cause April's the month
they're starting that, right? So all these
games will now have, you know, 400
gamerscore instead of 200 available
to you. I mean, I'd like to try
Minecraft out, you know, again
Yeah, I kinda wanna give
Minecraft a second chance, I don't really wanna
pay 1600 points for it, only to be
as, if I'm disappointed
in it, but all the Xbox
yeah, they come with demos, so I'll
let everybody cross your fingers
that the Minecraft one's really good
cause I wanna give it another chance
I do, so we'll see
I am kinda curious about Trials, I kinda skipped the first
one, but it sounds interesting
they showed another one, there was a picture I saw
where, I think it was the devs that did
Limbo, did a level that looks
like Limbo in Trials
That's awesome
I do wanna point out the price of the
other games, Fable Heroes will be 800
points, that's about 10 bucks, all the others
Evolution Bloodforge, 15 bucks
So that's the pricing for those games
Now what we haven't heard about, I have
not heard anything about what you get
if you buy all four games, because remember
that was an important part of the promotion
for Block Party and Summer of Arcade
is like, buy all four, get
400 points in the mail or something
like that, right, or get 1200 points
or get a game for free, you know
depending on what promotion it is, but yet
I'm not hearing anything with this
So this is just straight up a
send out
a press release to all the gaming sites and get
the games or exposure, right
Get an ad in the magazines
It's still a while away, I mean they could always
announce something, that's true, there may be something coming out
later, even if
it's something derpy like
something for your, I keep wanting to say
your me, but for your
avatar, like a little next shirt
or something, I mean even if they throw something
like that in there, there'll be people that
give it a shot just to have that
you know, so we'll see
Not very many people, but
there will be people
Never know, Derek H in chat
says, does that mean Minecraft is the highest
price Xbox Live arcade game
ever? No, the penny arcade
game was also $1600
I think there's a couple of those too
Well, some of them you may consider
Xbox Live Arcade and some you may not
Remember, some games are released not as
Xbox Live Arcade, but as actually
those games on demand because they don't fit
within the
you know, constraints of the file size
True, and one could argue that
you know, a game that didn't get
released here, like wasn't there that Japanese
import shooter that you could
only get through on demand
Right? Well, there was
original Crysis, two Crysis I think
it was HD or something like that, they had
come out, I don't remember if that was
20 bucks, I think it was at least 20 bucks
Yeah, but I mean
if you wanna count just strictly what's
in the category of XBLA
then it ties for most
expensive game ever, yes
Don't get me wrong, they're probably gonna try to
inch that up a little bit, but
Yeah, there might be DLC that'll bump it
up a little, especially in a game like Minecraft
it's possible
the question is, will they go there?
So, alright, let's move on
Dark Sakura
Well, we've discussed this till we
were blue in the face, but
Effect 3
We don't like the ending
Well
BioWare's listening
I don't know why, but they're listening
and
the co-founder Ray
and I always mispronounce his name, Musica
has said that they are
actually going to work to
answer those open-ended questions and give
closure to the fans
and describe
the fan feedback as
incredibly painful
So basically everyone
bitched and they're putting out some DLC
to
I guess expand more on
the ending, but he's saying
and this is a quote, our first instinct is to defend
the work and point out the high ratings offered
by critics, let you critics know
but out of respect to our
fans, we need to accept the criticism
and feedback with humility
So they're basically
they're like, uh, well
sorry you didn't like it, we're not gonna
change that much about it, but maybe you'll like this
That's
what I can tell
I guess the only thing
to do is wait and see
I think it's a terrible idea
I've calmed down
a little bit on the idea
I still don't think this excuses
certain behaviors of certain people
on the internet, namely those that are
harassing the employees of BioWare
that's totally fucking unacceptable
I don't give a fuck how much you've spent
or invested in the Mass Effect series
some of the vile shit I've read on the
internet about the creators of the
games, like seriously
fuck off
those people need to
and I mean this
they need to get a life
like, they literally need a life
and the guy
who took it to the government and all this
stuff, that was ridiculous
the whole, I don't think this is on the show
roll later, so the whole using
Child's Play
I think went a little bit far
I think maybe somebody was good intentioned
with that whole thing, but at the end
of the day, people were calling Child's Play
saying, how much do I have to donate
to get the ending changed?
And Child's Play's like, whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
whoa
What are we here?
Are we an organization that's supposed to
help you get
your beef with game publishers
resolved? Or are we an organization
trying to bring joy into sick children's
lives? And so they
came out with a clarification that if you do a
fundraiser for Child's Play, Child's Play
is the cause, there is to be no
other cause, Child's Play is the cause, and I say
bravo to that
Now
I'm not as harsh on that because I realize there might
have been good intentions there
but unfortunately some people
aren't smart
I don't know how else to put it
But like what you just said
and this is why I'm
just scared of what this kind of
precedent says. How much money do I
have to pay for them to change the ending?
And that right there
How much money do I have to pay for them to
change the ending? Really? Are people
actually asking that question? Funny enough
Go ahead, Jamie. I was gonna say
that right there is America
And I was gonna say, funny enough,
Loki, that's the part where
I become okay with this because although I've been
bashing all these things, I realize the vast
majority of people out there
that, you know, probably went to go
click like on the page or have said a nasty
tweet about, God that ending sucked or whatever
I realize the vast majority of those people
aren't, like, insane, like some of the
other people I just mentioned
But, you know, if they're gonna
put it out there, like, if BioWare does
a DLC ending, I will buy it and I will
support it, I'm kinda like
alright, then fine
At least you'll have the choice
if you want to invest that money or not
And it's like, if people want to buy it
then fine. It's a weird
weird precedent, and we were just
talking about this a little bit with Bobby before us
here tonight, and I was mentioning
about Final Fantasy 7
A lot of people hated that ending
too, and if that game came out today
a lot of people were probably doing the same thing
Like, wow, two of the characters were just fucking
missing in the ending. But, once again
though, it's so what that ending had
So what if it was a terrible ending for Final Fantasy 7?
People bought Final Fantasy 8
People bought Final Fantasy 9
People bought Final Fantasy 10, they bought 10 too
They probably bought 11
They bought 12, they bought 13
Did it really hurt
the sales of those because they didn't like the game?
Now, Loki, nobody bought Final Fantasy 11
I'm kidding, I'm kidding, don't send the hate mail
But there were a lot of Final Fantasy
fans that did
reject 11, but there were enough that embraced
it that gave us 14
When that shit goes free to play
When that shit goes free to play, watch how many
fans reject that
Anyway, back to the topic here
DLC is something
that is in the industry now
that we didn't have so many years ago
and in a way, EA being
one of the biggest DLC whores
in this industry, kinda
has themselves to blame for this mindset
that they can fix the ending
through a patch, or they can fix the ending through
DLC. EA kind of
invented that mess
Well, maybe they didn't invent it, but they perfected
it, let's say. They did start the
online pass, did they not?
So they've figured out how to milk all the extra
dollars for a video game, so in that capacity
EA kinda has
themselves to blame for the fan backlash
because if this were 10 years ago
fans wouldn't be saying
this because there wouldn't really be anything they could do
about it. They would have to just, you know,
write on their live journals
I don't like the ending. What they should do is just fucking
shut the hell up, and
get over it, because you know why?
They're like, oh, well I spent
how many hours playing this
series, and I'm so
disappointed at the ending. Fuck you!
The developers spent how many fucking years
putting these games together for you?
You know, what about
their time? Well,
devil's advocate, I'm not
agreeing or disagreeing with you, but just to give you another perspective
that's on the internet, there's a lot of talk on the
internet that the ending was changed at the last
minute, and that the writers of
the original ending were basically shafted
because I guess there was a leak
that had ruined it, or I mean
I wasn't following the Mass Effect series then, so I don't know
much about this, I'm just hearing it second hand,
but I guess there was a leak that spoiled the first ending
so the creator kind of
made this new ending
if the
internet is to be believed, literally pulled it
out of his ass, and that's the ending
we have, because they wanted
to get back at the spoiled leak, I
guess.
That doesn't make any sense.
Just saying.
And also, like, I take, you know,
I have a problem with the fact that
all these people hate it, and
like, you know, the game reviews and stuff, and granted, everyone
is, you know,
open to their own opinion, but
a lot of the game reviews have been really positive
for it. I didn't hear anyone
saying- Why's there not letting a 15 minute ending, or
even if it's an hour ending, ruin
what is otherwise- Exactly!
That's how everybody should take it, instead of just
being so god damn focused on
the last 15 minutes of the game.
Sg100Matt has some pretty strong words in our chatroom
at chat.orangelandraday.com
Let the artist paint the picture and write the
image they want. Gamers aren't
entitled to nothing. Just sit back and enjoy
the ride. If you don't like the ride, get the fuck
off it. Exactly! And you don't have to
purchase the next game, but see, I think that's why they did it.
Two reasons. One, so they could possibly
sell more DLC, because, you know,
the publisher's like, yeah, yeah, you
should make a new ending. We'll give you a little
bit of money, and we're gonna make a lot of money in
return. And it, you know, appeases
the fans so that when Mass Effect 4
comes out, because you know there will be a Mass Effect 4,
that they will buy it.
I just think this whole sense of entitlement
thing that's going on in this country
is probably the most ridiculous thing
to ever happen. It's a truly
modern phenomenon, and
people really need to get over themselves
and realize that, you know,
it not being what you want
or not getting what you want doesn't mean
that it's a complete affront to you
in particular. You know, that it's
they're doing this on purpose!
You know.
Stop being a baby.
If people are suggesting that they would
troll the fans because
one of the endings leaked, that doesn't
make any sense at all, because
if there's a leak coming from your company,
it's from within your company. Why would
you, well damn those fans, they
know my ending, I'm gonna make a terrible ending
instead! That'll show them, they'll
see that it's completely different and that
there's no possible way that it was a leak.
I mean, that makes no sense.
That sounds like fanboy speculation.
It's going to be interesting very
much to see the impact that this has
on an inevitable Mass Effect 4.
And yes, fans, I realize
that apparently they have
said there's not gonna be any more Mass Effect,
but seriously, you
can fucking believe that, seriously.
Yeah, there wasn't gonna be any
more Halo after Halo 3 either.
You know, they'll
find a way to do Mass Effect 4.
It may not be called Mass Effect 4.
The series will
continue. It's too fucking big
to not.
It might not be Bioware, so you
may really not want it to happen, but it'll happen.
Somebody will do it.
So, anyhow,
why don't we move on?
We can probably talk about this all night, and I'm sure we'll
get some emails and calls on it later.
Mailbag at orangeonshady.com if you want to send your
thoughts, or we'll open up the phones later in the show.
But for now, how about some more stories? Loki.
Yeah, so, Disney
Interactive announced Disney's epic Mickey 2.
The Power of 2.
Um...
I was really hoping for The Power of Love, but
you know, that's...
It sounds like a Mary-Kate and Ashley Olsen movie.
The Power of 2.
Um, you know, as all the
kind of, um,
rumors were, uh, it actually
is gonna feature both Mickey Mouse
and Oswald the Lucky Rabbit.
And, um, Oswald's
gonna be AI controlled. Um,
of course,
when other people are not around. Otherwise, it's, you
know, I guess it's jump-in
co-op, so that's kinda cool.
And then it will also be on PlayStation
3 and Xbox 360
on top of the Wii version, and the
PS3 version is supposed to support the move, which makes sense
I mean, because they're just gonna port the controls over from the Wii
onto the PS3 version.
Um, it looks neat.
I watched the trailer for it. I mean, I didn't play the
original game, which is kind of, you know, a fault
on my part, because it looked
like a pretty awesome game. Um, maybe
I'll check it out, you know, on the 360
when it comes out. Um, I'm just glad
Disney Interactive is making something, because
for a while there, they didn't have anything since
like, Disney Universe, and I was like,
damn, did they just go away or something?
I mean, I was getting worried,
but, um, well,
yeah, they had, uh, the split second
was, uh, is that?
Yeah, the split second was the Disney game.
And that studio got
obliterated, didn't it?
Yeah, that's unfortunate. There's another movie
tie-in game, Brave, has a movie coming up.
Okay, but you know,
I expect the kiddie games
to all get tie-ins. Those are usually the first
ones to have, like, the movie tie-in.
Well, there wasn't really anything for Twilight, unless you count
the scene at Twilight. Konami, way
to go, Konami. What in the fuck
would a Twilight video game be? Seriously,
I f- I can't believe
I'm about to admit this on the radio, but I
saw Breaking Dawn Part 1, it's the only
Twilight movie I've seen. In my
defense, in my
defense, put the hate mail down, in my
defense, it was with Rift
Tracks, which I think is the only- It was a party we hosted.
It was the only tolerable way to see. It is the
only way to see those movies. But my
God.
Where was the plot in that movie?
It was literally, like, 30
minutes of them fucking and
being on the beach, and like,
I love you, and I love-
we're gonna be together, and
I'm like, oh my God,
people paid a lot of money to see this in the
theater. You would pay $50
for a video game for Breaking
Dawn Part 1? The fuck
would you do? I would love
to see a game that was controlled
very much like Dragon's Lair.
It was just, like, left to right.
Be emo
to the left. Be emo to the right.
Sulk
to the right. Sulk to
the left.
Sparkle. Prevent
this wedding from becoming her hallucination
by pressing A repeatedly
to stop them from turning into vampires. I think it would
be kind of funny. I mean,
someone has to have the sense of humor to do that.
Ugh.
Anyhow.
Oh, and the 3DS
is getting the version as well.
Power of Illusion, which made me think of
Castle of Illusion, so maybe
that's a good sign?
Um, that is interesting.
Epic Mickey. We've known about
this for a while from some of the leaks. I know we've
talked about it on the show before, but putting
all that aside, are we
surprised it's actually happening?
Or no? Because Epic Mickey-
It sold well. Yeah? Yeah.
I guess maybe for those of us that
focus more on our 360s. It had a lot of neat
stuff in it. It did. I'm not saying it was
a bad game, but the Wii
only thing really kept it away from the hardcore.
Yeah, and see, that's kind of
that I think was the reason why
I didn't play the game, was remember the original
concept art for, you know,
Epic Mickey, where it's gonna be
really fucking twisted and dark. It was like
if, you know, not necessarily
Tim Burton, but like, you know,
Guillermo del Toro, like,
put out a version of Mickey Mouse that was
like fucking
the game, right there. It was just
really crazy and steampunk and all
this stuff. And then we got the version that
came out in the Wii, and they just kind of like
you know, kind of washed all that-
I mean, there was still a lot of dark stuff in there,
but it wasn't anywhere near like this
adult Mickey game that was supposed
to be coming out. It was kind of like, oh, it's
Mickey saving the land. Well, you can't
have a truly adult
Mickey game. Well, why
can't you have a- okay, let's put it
this way. Not an adult game, but a very
very dark, dark, dark,
dark, dark Mickey game. I think Epic
Mickey's about as dark as you're gonna get.
But, you know, it's the Disney image.
You don't want to associate Disney
with dark things. And I'm
talking the company and Mickey Mouse as a whole.
Disney does some
dark-ish- I mean, you could call
Alice in Wonderland a little bit dark.
Tron even is a little bit dark. Well, Kingdom
Hearts kind of goes a little bit dark with stuff.
But even Kingdom Hearts is a little bit kitty.
And I don't- I love Kingdom Hearts.
But I'm just saying, like,
touching on more of, like, you know, just having
the stuff be all really twisted.
Anything that's dark that comes out of Disney
really comes from Touchstone or
whatever their movie arm is. You know, they-
Fine. Buena Vista or whatever it's called.
We'll just have it produced by Touchstone Interactive
or whatever. Make up a company.
Who knows? Who knows?
Alright, um, I-
I'm glad they're doing PlayStation 3
and Xbox as well.
I think it'll be- you know, because the Wii-
The Wii's on its way out, especially with
Wii U coming out this year. I'm glad they're
stepping it up to the other systems. It really is
on its way out. I mean, there's literally
hardly any games coming out at all
for the Wii. Oh god, worse.
A page right out of the
23rd Magus Jokes book. You ready for this one?
Brad from Pod Culture in chat
says, adult Mickey?
Are you fucking goofy?
At least they got his main laugh.
chat.orangeloungeloungeradio.com
If you want to, uh-
Uh, Ray Genator
in our chatroom says, Sky, please tell us
you were either drunk and or high
when you saw Twilight. No, I was- I was
neither drunk nor high. I was
fat. I was eating pizza
at the time, so I was fat.
But I was not drunk or high.
Do you think pizza
contains things that'll get you wasted?
I don't know. Alright.
Twilight, even
Riff Trax couldn't make that movie
good.
I have friends
that love it. They swear
it's only for the guilty pleasure. You should really question your friendship
with them. No, no, because they're close
friends of mine, but it's like, oh my god.
Alright, you know what? I have my things
too. Not everybody understands Rocky Horror
Picture Shows, so whatever. Rob, I like
Xanadu. Yeah, you are
a little weird. Shut up!
Just being honest.
Alright. I'd like
to- speaking of Xanadu,
you know, some of the animation in Xanadu was done
by the guy who made this game. Yep, Don Bluth.
Dragon's Lair.
Dragon's Lair's coming to Xbox Live Arcade!
And I think a lot of us, when we
hear that, stop for a minute and say,
oh, it isn't on Xbox Live
Arcade. It's like the one fucking platform
Dragon's Lair isn't on. Because I could
get it on- oh god, I could
get it on DVD,
Blu-ray,
I could get it on my iPhone,
I could get it on the PlayStation. Sega CD.
This game has
been on everything CD-based.
However, when the early versions were out,
the best version was on the CD-i.
Why is that? Because it was the full version.
I didn't realize the other ones were cut down.
Yeah, the Sega CD one
especially was missing scenes and everything.
Oh wow, I guess they maybe couldn't fit it.
Well, I doubt this one will be missing scenes or
whatever, but the Xbox Live Arcade
is getting a version, and there was kind of a
leak that let people know that
Dragon's Lair was on its way out.
But Digital Leisure, who
is publishing the game,
kind of gave away a
little surprise about this.
This isn't just Dragon's Lair
as you would normally play Dragon's
Lair, but you can also
play with Kinect.
Think about that for a minute.
Dragon's Lair came out
in what, 84, 83?
It was definitely the early 80s when this game came out, right?
They've gone back to this
game that's damn near 30 years old
and put Kinect in it.
There's
several ways you can look at this. You can go
well, I mean, they've put it out
so many other times they had to do
something new to it. Or you
could look at it and go, they're
ruining my childhood in
front of my eyes.
How do you feel about this?
I especially want to know Dark Soccer
because you like Dragon's Lair. What do you think about
Kinect support? I'm indifferent
about it because I'm not going to buy it.
Seriously, how many other versions
of Dragon's Lair do I own?
You know,
it kind of would be like
for all the people who like...
Actually, I can't
think of a
benefit on this.
You know, people who may not
be able to use a controller
or
maybe people with no arms.
They can use their feet.
Well, to be fair, you would have
to, like some of the motions they're talking about are
raising your hand up to grab the rope.
So unless you can trick the Kinect to think your foot
is your hand, which maybe is possible,
or use something else.
I don't know. You're right. There could be somebody with
a disability where they can't use a controller.
But
I don't know how many
people would fit into the category of
can't use a controller can use these Kinect commands.
Maybe they have no hands.
Maybe they're
missing fingers. Now you're stretching.
Well, I'm just saying that
they put it out there for a reason.
Someone's gonna probably like it
and pay for it. Not me.
I just don't care.
Let them do whatever they want
to with it. It's not costing me any money.
Chat.orangelandtrader.com.
Stan in our chat room says, oh no, does that mean you can put
your face on that guy's face?
Dirk the Daring, you mean?
Let's hope not.
Let's really hope not.
Hackdeft says,
Dragon's Lair plus
Kinect. Why did they think this was a good
idea? I don't know.
I guess they're...
Props to them trying to do something new.
That's about the nicest thing I can say.
They're trying to make it a party game, a social
game. I mean, cause it's
Dragon's Lair. You gotta do something
to... Oh yeah, when I think party, I think
bust out Dragon's Lair.
Well, depends on what kind of friend you have.
I guess that's true. I mean, it's just, they're
just trying to mix it up. You don't have
to play it that way. They're not forcing
you to use Kinect in this game, so
who cares? It's an additional feature.
Why are you complaining about additional features?
If you think it's stupid, you don't have to use it.
Alright, let's move
on with some more gaming news. So, release dates
and Classic Game of the Week are still coming up, but first,
Dark Sakura.
I got your news. I got your news
right here. Um,
apparently exposure to Violet video games
has been linked to aggressive behavior.
Warning. Shut up!
Well, it's not true, but still.
Yeah, there is
another bill
that wants to
label any game
that's E or
higher than exposure
to Violet video games has been linked to aggressive
behavior. E or higher?
That would be all games.
That would be almost, like, I can
think of maybe, like,
two games that
had the Y, the youth rating on it.
Well, that's old. It's EC nowadays.
Whatever. Whatever it is,
I can think of maybe two games.
Well, this
was sponsored by, uh,
Frank Wolf, who is
the, uh, Republican representative for Virginia.
So, people in Virginia remember
who not to vote for.
And Joe Baca,
who is a California
Democrat, people in California,
don't vote for this guy.
Um, who basically
wants, they call it the Violence
and Video Games Labeling Act.
And, I mean, basically,
they've done this before. They did it in 2009,
which was for T and up.
They're just not giving up.
And it's already been proven to be unconstitutional.
So, I don't know what they're
thinking. You know, there's a
saying that doing
the same thing multiple times
in a row and expecting different results
is insanity.
Well,
they're insane.
People, don't vote for them.
I just, it's
kind of insulting in a way.
Because it's like, have these guys ever played a
video game in their life? Because
really, like, you're talking E-rated
video games. So, like,
I don't know. I'm trying to look at some of
the games I have over there that are rated E.
Bloom Blocks
is gonna lead to aggressive behavior. Fucking
blocks! You know, I will say this
Mass Effect 2 led to some aggressive behavior last night.
You should have seen me playing some Bust-A-Move earlier.
Super Mario Brothers Wii
will lead to aggressive behavior.
Imagine
babies. Forza. Sing Star Abba
will lean to aggressive behavior.
Forza. Well, here, basically,
this is what they said about the last
time they tried to do this.
Is that, basically,
that the Supreme Court
found all of the data lacking
and unpersuasive.
And really, even these own studies,
if you go and read them, they contradict themselves
because they also bring up
that violent movies,
or any movie,
causes the same reaction in a child
already predisposed
towards it. It has just as much
influence as a movie, as a
book, as songs, as anything
audio-visual.
So, this guy's just, these
men are, they're clearly insane.
That's the only thing that can say it.
Again, doing the same thing over and over
and expecting different results is insanity.
On a tangent here for a minute,
speaking of politicians who don't understand
video games, did you hear the latest in the
Lee Lin Yi saga? Oh, what?
He,
well, this is, this is actually, this is the interesting
thing, is that this is a bill that you look at and go,
yes, we do need this.
Remember, Lee Lin Yi was the guy in California,
I want to say Democrat out of
San Francisco, who was trying to pass
the bill on violent video
games not being able to be
sold at the store,
but it was
very vague as to what made a violent video game
because it didn't tie into ESRB or whatever,
and, you know, blah, blah, blah. They lost
at the Supreme Court level. State spent like a
million bucks defending this law that the dude wrote.
We're all sitting here saying, vote his ass out,
right? Because that's, he didn't win
mayor of San Francisco, so they didn't get
elected for that, but
he wrote a bill this week that
actually you look at and go, okay, now that
makes sense. That's technology he does
understand. He authored a bill in California
which will make it illegal
for employers to ask you for your
Facebook password, because you might
have been hearing the stories this week, the
nightmare stories about people that went into job interviews,
and the interviewees were like, okay,
log into Facebook for me
so I can check out what you're really like.
And everybody's like, wow, that's an
invasion of privacy. Employers shouldn't be
able to do that. And so, yeah,
you know, Facebook has come out and said, don't do it.
And now Lee Lin is going to make it illegal
in California. And I was kind of like, well, that's
a smart man. Oh, wait, no,
it's him. He's,
he's all right. Gotta read the fine text
and I'm sure he's got violent video games
stuff. It might be getting in there. You're gonna look for it.
You know, I actually posted
a comic on my Tumblr
yesterday that was
a woman that in interviews is like, okay,
well, you've passed all of this. Now,
let me see your Facebook. She's like, let me see
yours.
Oh, yeah. That's what I would say, too. I probably wouldn't
get the job, but would you want to work for a company
that does that? I don't know. It's tough because
in this day and age, people really, really
need jobs. And it's kind of
gross. It's just gross that
employers are exploiting that. It's
gross. I think employers
that do that should be called out. I think
we should have a list of employers that are
violating the privacy of their employees.
And create two Facebook pages.
I know.
I know, right? Or just say, I don't have one.
They won't believe you.
They won't believe you. They'll search for you, but
if you use a fake name on the internet,
it'll be hard to find.
And honestly, anyone can read my
Facebook page. I don't care. Don't post anything
private on there anyways. I don't care. I mean,
my mother and my rabbi are on my
Facebook. So, really.
But you can see where not everybody would want
their employers on their Facebook. You know what I mean?
It's just, for me, it's a private
Yes, I have co-workers on
Facebook, but it's, you know, my choice.
I don't want him on my Facebook either
because I just don't want him
I don't want to talk to him on Facebook.
I don't really care.
Alright, anyhow.
Let's move on with some release dates. We're going to travel
around the world and check out what is coming out
in a gaming store near you. We'll start with the
US. Ah, slowing down a bit.
Go, go crazy bones on the
Nintendo DS. I'm sure that was delayed to this
week. Melee to aggressive
behavior. Those crazy bones.
Damn them. Supremacy
MMA for the Playstation Vita.
That's coming out this week
as well. Myst
on the 3DS. It's in 3D
and it's Myst.
Yay. That game's awesome
fifteen years ago. You know, I have a
parody of that game called Pissed. I remember
that, actually. Yeah.
I never played it. I just thought it was funny. And I
can guarantee that there's a hundred percent more
Myst in that game than there is in the
Silent Hill HD collection.
I
see what you did there. Country Dance
All Stars for Kinect.
Dance
to country music.
Warriors Orochi 3 on
Xbox 360.
And then Tiger Woods PGA Tour 13
on Playstation 3 and Xbox
360 this week, including collector's
editions if you really need a collector's
edition for a golf game.
Sure, why not. The Capcom
Digital Collection on Xbox 360, which is a
collection of Xbox Live Arcade games that are already
out there.
And maybe
or maybe not this week because
no one seems to have the answer for it. Ridge
Racer Unbounded possibly coming
out this week. Possibly delayed to who knows
when. Because even Namco doesn't
know. So
possibly this week.
Alright. Going to
Japan. Are we good to go to Japan now?
Alright. So going to Japan. Yay! We're going to Japan.
On the Nintendo 3DS
Japan this week. Probably a
big release some of you might care about.
This might be worth importing to some of you.
Kingdom Hearts Dream Drop
Distance gets released on the
Nintendo 3DS this week in Japan on the 29th.
Remember you can't import
from the 3DS unless you
have a Japanese region 3DS.
Right. It is not region free like the original
DS was, right? Yes. So
well if you want to get a Japanese 3DS
there is specifically a Kingdom Hearts
3DS that you
can get. It's like a black one
that kind of looks nice. Like a little
like inscription of Disney. I don't know if that's like
a sticker they put on it. But it looks
like a picture. It looks like an inscription.
Oh okay. So it's
a little more permanent so that's good.
So that's kind of your big release
and that's on the 3DS this week. But there are some
other games coming out of Japan this week.
On the Playstation Vita
there's Pro Yakyuu Spirits
2012. O Tumao
To Sevanen no Himigimitachi
Shin Osamamonogatari.
That is coming out from
Konami this week. I don't know
if this is a series I recognize
on the Vita.
It's like a chibi
character role playing game.
When I saw the people at first I was
like oh it's like Suikoden but it's definitely
not. It's too cartoony to be that.
Something a little different
there. But that's from Konami which is a pretty big
publisher in Japan.
Going to the
consoles real quick. Let me take a look at the
Xbox 360. Japan
gets Duke Nukem Forever.
Stay away
from it. It's horrible.
Root Double Before Crime After
Days. Mahjong Dream Club
on the 360. And lastly
on the Playstation 3 this week. Grand Theft
Auto. Episodes from Liberty
City. Gets like a price reduction.
Duke Nukem Forever is out there as well.
The Silent Hill HD Collection makes its way
to Japan. Idol Master
Gravure For You
Volume 6
comes out this week on the Playstation 3.
So there you go. Your Japanese releases.
How about
UK? We do have a few.
For the UK releases
we have on the 28th
we have Wrecked Revenge
on the 29th
Silent Hill HD Collection. On the
30th Silent Hill Downpour
Naruto Shippuden
Ultimate Ninja Storm Generations
Ridge Racer Unbound
Warriors Orochi 3
Awesome.
Alright.
Let's do a couple more stories and then the classic
game of the week. Loki?
Alright.
Apparently
Ubisoft is hoping that
they can get rid of their DRM
that they have on PC.
According to a recent interview
with Eurogamer
Chris Early, who is the
Vice President of Digital Publishing at
Ubisoft, talked about
some of their anti-piracy
measures and how
it's a tricky balancing act.
Basically
they were talking a little bit about
how
it's kind of
leniencing some of their customers
and that at the same time
they don't want to put
they're having
a hard time convincing
themselves to not
put DRM on their PC tiles because they know
they're going to get pirated so they're trying to find
kind of a balance where
they can offer enough value in a game where
people will want to
buy it legitimately without having to
worry about DRM.
Kind of the same thing I think was at
CD Projekt Red was going through with
The Witcher 2 and stuff like that where that game was
really pirated and they're like
listen we're not doing DRM anymore.
I think that's mainly because it kept
failing in their pain to put DRM in there
and so you might as well recoup some money.
But
right now they're saying
the question is with enough ongoing
content development, content release,
engagement at the community level, we can
create that kind of MMO value system.
I think we can.
As the rest of the
game industry continues to evolve the more
you hear about cloud gaming
the more you hear about companion gaming
the less pirated game
the less
pirated games should work in all of that
environment. So basically they're
trying to
make it work here. Well cloud
gaming I mean they're basically making it where you don't
have any of the content you just kind of access it
and then the MMO stuff
just kind of more it sounds like
a lot of pay to
purchase, pay to play stuff.
Right. It's kind of like
they're trying to enrich it
by giving it more
to download. It's almost
like the Mass Effect 2 thing I'm going through
right now. I got a copy of Mass Effect 2 for
20 bucks, brand new. I'm like, fuck yeah
sweet, a copy of Mass Effect 2.
Almost got pissed as hell when I saw it
came with a free code for the Cerberus network.
Expires January 1,
2012. And I just bought it
off the shelf at Fry's, brand new.
But I tried using it anyway
it still worked. So crisis averted
right. So by the way
pro tip, those codes might not
actually expire when they say they do. Just throwing it
out there.
But the other thing I wanted to say is that
I find that now I'm being
told, oh I have to buy the $7
DLC because it
will change some things in 3 and then there's other
DLC. I might have to drop another 20
bucks in DLC to get the full experience.
So they're still going to get
40 bucks out of me for the whole game even though
I thought I was getting it on sale. What they
really should do, and like I was saying before
with the whole Killzone 3 online
thing, how that was free.
That's how you get people interested in
your game. You put that shit out there digitally
for free. Just, you can
even do it like a demo. And then
you add content and you're basically free
to play. You're free to start playing it but then
you pay for additional content. Or you
can get everything boxed together. And then
is that like the whole idea that Ridge Racer
on the Vita would be awesome if it was
free?
I wouldn't go as far as saying it would be awesome
but it would be a lot easier to
swallow that, okay yes there's only 3
tracks and 5 cars because this is the free version
of the game. Versus the $30
version of the game. Well there's the Motorstorm.
The Motorstorm game is free and they have
a lot of DLC for it. Exactly.
That's kind of a perfect example there. Although that
DLC you don't really need any of it. I mean
because it's just cars that change the appearance
of your cars. Which since you're not really
racing anybody
anyways, um
I don't really see the point of making your
car look different. Considering that I don't think
they handle any different. But whatever.
You know you can do that. And that
DLC though is anywhere from like a quarter
a pop to like a buck.
I mean which is something like
a quarter. I'm not even going to blink at that.
I mean that's nothing if I really felt like
I should buy it. But I mean
you know like do that with like the next
Call of Duty game or something like that. Imagine
a free to play Call of Duty game where you can
level up to say like
rank you know 20 or something like that
then oh you gotta pay
to you know rank up even further.
I think people would be all over that
shit. It would be
it would be immensely successful.
Um and I knew this comment
was coming in the chat room. AcidicVampire says
Sky just drop the money for it.
Mass Effect 2's DLC is worth it.
All the Mass Effect fans are joining in.
Infinel says you don't really need the weapon armor
DLC and Shane says yeah forget it
just get the story stuff. I'm like alright
yeah yeah you guys made your point but
you know and Mass Effect 2
is kind of one game out of
a lot that I would be willing to do that for.
I mean again I actually
it held my attention long enough to beat it.
That says a lot right there. So
alright.
When you get around to it I may have DLC
codes for you for Mass Effect 3.
Nice! For some
of the pre-order stuff. I think I still
have some left over. Send those my way!
Save one for when I borrow Rob's.
I love that Jamie
is already resigned to the fact that she's gonna
have to play the whole damn series. Oh and hey if anybody
needs any of the ganky codes
for Saints Row the Third I think I have like
200 of them still so
send me a direct message
on Twitter. By the way
Mass Effect fans in chat especially
Shane. Do I get like a big
old high five or a big old cookie for
paying it forward to Jamie where
now she's taking my copy and she's gonna
get sucked into this? Of course
she might come on the show next week
and go I hated it.
You guys are stupid. You know what? I think
right there that's a perfect example of how they
should be treating games instead of saying oh
well we want each person to play an online pass.
They should be fucking encouraging people to get
people to loan that game out so that people try.
Not necessarily the full version of the game but
like say hey this person played a demo
that's owned by this person like you can
send it to them and if they play it and they
like it or something like that you get a kickback
or something like that. That is the fucking way
That's a good point because if I loan her
Mass Effect 2 she might have to go buy the
DLC for herself.
Maybe. I mean we're making a lot of assumptions
here but. Well I think they just need to
rethink how they're you know
doing this. How they're approaching everything
and if they could just grasp
these wonderful ideas you know they could make a lot of money.
Alright.
Hitstone wants to know if any of those codes are for PC.
No. Oh.
Sorry. PS3 and 360 only.
Wah wah wah wah. Sorry.
Alright. One more
story for you guys. Look it's a slow news week
so I'm gonna let this story through.
In a more busy news week it would have been cut but
we needed something so I'm gonna
go ahead and address these rumors about Grand Theft
Auto 5. Supposedly
from an ex-Rockstar employee
on the GameSpot
forums so
big fat grain of salt
and I'm doing this instead of Loki
so that Loki can sit here and go
it's bullshit or oh it sounds like it's
legit.
Number one. There will be
one protagonist character. One
character alone. Albert Da Silva
is the name. Half Hispanic
man who was once a part of a crime city.
Crime family in Vice City.
True or false? I don't know.
You're not very fun to play with.
Sorry. Multiplayer will hold
32 people on the Xbox and
PlayStation 3. Unknown
about PC. Just like
Red Dead Redemption you'll be able to form
gangs. They're not ranked through XP
but through reputation.
Well we know that to be true
already but I think a lot of that is
just speculation. I think all this is
speculation. They don't know.
Alright.
Yeah I think a lot of this seems like educated
speculation to me when I read it too and I don't
know a dick about Grand Theft Auto. I don't know if it's educated
speculation but. Number
three. The map is about five times as large
as the Grand Theft Auto 4 map and the
city of Los Santos takes up just
under half of this area. So it's bigger than
two Grand Theft Auto 4 Liberty Cities.
Again, safe bet.
Um.
I don't know if they can do it like that.
I mean it could be bigger because
I think the Red Dead Redemption map was pretty big
but I mean it's a lot of it's just
fitting in textures and fitting in
the maps themselves. I mean
the object placement formats and stuff like
that it's pretty small
but it's when you get all the different textures in the
game. So I don't know if it's going to be five
times as large. I mean it's going to be pretty big.
But I
don't know. I just assume it's going to be larger.
Cars and guns are customizable
to an extent. For an example you
can customize a gun to have a suppressor on it
and you can install nitrous into cars.
I thought you could already do that in Grand Theft Auto.
Uh.
They used to have that in San Andreas.
Not necessarily the
suppressors but I mean that would be a nice feature.
I don't know if that's going to be
legit or not.
Alright let me get to some of the other
good stuff because this is getting
boring already. Radio stations
now do traffic reports that are actually
correct. So if you don't know what route to take
you can check the traffic reports on your phone or on the
Radio 7. The in-game TV
has more channels. Again that seems like a safe bet.
But once again though
those in-game TV channels are
fucking huge as far as the files go.
They're Bic encoded
or Bink encoded videos
that take up hundreds of
megs. I mean if they're going to fit
that shit on a disc they're going to have to do some sort of
compression or something because as of
right now on 4 in episodes
from Liberty City they're not
compressed at all besides
you know what the actual
encoder does but
that's why there's not that many stations
on like episodes from Liberty City
because they can't fit it on the disc.
The protagonist
can take drugs which will have
some effects but smoking weed
on the streetwalk will lead to getting a one
star wanted level.
That's like Saintsboro
one shit. I mean I don't even
know if I can go with that. I'm bored
of this story already so here's the biggest one.
The game is due in May 2013.
A more specific date has not been
decided because the game is still needing six
months to be fully developed. They
will have a playable demo at E3.
That's again speculation
because we already know with their
we already know the next quarter game is going to be
Max Payne 3. We already know what the
fourth quarter game is going to be which is going to be
well it's not necessarily the Rockstar but Take 2
which is going to be NBA 2K
NHL 2K if they actually put one out
this year and of course you know the big
big big one is
you know Bioshock Infinite
so of course that stuff is going to be
coming out and so you got to figure
you know it's going to be
first or second quarter and you know
estimating they've got
maybe they've got some other 2K stuff
oh shit I completely forgot
of like you know
XCOM is still in there somewhere
and
then I want to say like the
Summer Games probably
Spec Ops they've
still got in there somewhere in June I
believe
I don't know a lot of it just sounds like
speculation and you know
unfortunately because I do follow
a lot of Grand Theft Auto
communities and stuff there is like one person
each week saying oh I've heard something
from a random you know
Rockstar employee yeah and they're going to make
these educated guesses so that if they're close
then yeah people say hey I said it first
and then if they're wrong then no one will
remember. People have a need to be first
sometimes. Exactly.
I love some of the comments in our chat room
chat.orangessantria.com Porkchop
what a delicious handle in the
chat room says why would anyone
waste time watching TV in Grand Theft Auto
when you can go out and stomp hookers? We actually
did watch a lot of the TV when
Dan was playing it. It was funny.
You're boring. You should be killing more hookers.
SHJ100Matt
says what Grand Theft Auto 5 really
needs is the SimCity Action News
reporter just saying
God I love your topical sense of humor
I really do because it gives me an excuse
to play a clip from SimCity Action
News
is
picking up cars and buses
and throwing them hundreds of yards
as he moves closer to the SimCity Action
Studios which means
that this is Carol Davenport signing off
and getting the hell out of here.
Give her an Emmy. Give her a goddamn Emmy.
Lifetime Achievement
Award.
You see...
Let's give her a series on Bravo.
Jurassic Park had just come
out that same year. So that's funny.
Let's go back to a time
when
video games were less complicated
and didn't require full screen
videos and all that stuff
in a segment we call the classic
game of the week. Yay!
Dark Soccer is going to dive into
the gaming vault and find a game that she thinks
is great. You kids
need to stop playing
your Grand Theft Auto 5s and your SimCity
Action Newses
and you need to check out this
awesomely classic game. What is the classic
game of the week? Today's classic game is
Star Fox.
Yay. Fucking great choice.
Which came out of Starwing
in Europe and Australia because there was
a trademarked game that came out
like in
when the hell... 1983.
Can I just say I'm really hating the ads
on YouTube these days. Sorry. It's alright.
Not your fault. I didn't want
to hear emo bands singing first while I'm trying
to get some Star Fox action going on here
in the studio. We're the emo band
singing about Star Fox.
Our lives suck
cause we don't have Star Fox.
Anyway.
Star Fox
is a
rail shooter that used
3D polygon graphics. It's the first Nintendo
game to use full on polygons.
And it was powered by the
Super FX chip which was basically
a co-processor so that it could handle it.
So uh
the characters were all designed
by Takaya Imamura
based off of Kemono
characters basically
from old I believe 16th
century Japanese art.
This is pretty cool. You know basically
anthropomorphic characters.
What? Somebody in chat asked
if they could do a barrel roll so I slapped him with a fish.
Okay cool.
At any rate
God this music is so epic. I love the first
level music. The soundtrack was so
fucking good. Turn this up a little bit. Sure.
This is like seriously my favorite music in the game.
What the
planet music? The very first
level. Oh yeah the music
here. The canaria level. The whole
take off sequence and all that is awesome. Let's
listen here for a minute here.
Thanks. Emergency.
This brings me so much
worries.
Seriously the most epic
music ever right here.
Shut up Falco.
Shut up Slippy.
I swear I spent the whole game going
freaking hate Slippy die
and shut up Falco. That was me
the entire time I was playing this game. Seriously
this music just invokes the
world.
Fuck yeah.
For a Japanese game sure.
Anyway it
involves Fox McCloud
who is the leader of the Star Fox team
and they
have these ships called
Arwings which
are really floating polygon
things and they're pretty cool.
And you've got thrusters and
retrorockets that let you speed up
slow down and you've got
bombs and
pew pew laser things.
You hear the pew pew noises?
Pew pew pew pew.
So anyway
you've got
a little bit different thing
with your
in the damage on here. You've actually got
an energy shield that controls how much
damage you can absorb before the craft
destroys. So you can bump
into stuff and you take some damage
and don't just immediately explode.
Sometimes if your
wings clip against certain obstacles
they'll break off and it will affect
the handling of your Arwing.
Which was pretty innovative I thought
for a game of it's time.
The other thing that was interesting
about this is that it didn't have a difficulty
selection after you
finished the first stage you actually
would pick a path
that you could go on.
And so you could pick the easy
option, the normal option, or the hard option
depending on which path you took.
So you could mix and match your game
anyway and it had multiple
patterns. You know kind of like
an outrun.
You know how you can pick your different
paths and outrun. Oh yeah an outrun
you can pick your path but kind of once you
start going one way it's like you can't
really change it too much.
You can kind of slip back into something.
If you go left the first time you'll
never do the stage all the way at the bottom of the map.
Right you know that kind of thing.
The same thing was done in After Burner.
Yay Sega. Anyway.
So you also have
your wingmen. You have Peppy Hare, Slippy
Toad. Sucker.
And Falco Lombardi who I hated
Falco so much.
And it was kind of
cool because if you accidentally shot one of
your guys you wouldn't hurt them
but they would say hey
what are you doing shooting at me?
I'm Falco and I suck.
Hey I suck at these things off my toes.
Yeah you actually have to um
save your wingmen from being attacked by
other enemies too which was
almost always slippy.
So yeah
so you have to help them so that they'll always
be there with you and you even have the
little flying formation thing which is pretty cool.
So anyway
um
there were a few
really neat things with this too. Like I said
it was using the um
Super FX chip. It actually was
based off on
there was a prototype on the NES that was called
NES Glider that was
inspired by a game called Star Glider
and then they brought the prototype to the SNES
and once they uh
they actually uh hired
um a company to create
the Super FX chip so that they could have
the 3D graphics in there.
It was actually a lot
harder um a lot more
powerful than the SNES
uh processor. There was a joke going
around that the um
SNES was basically just a box to hold the chip.
Pretty cool.
So um the main game
uh was designed by Miyamoto
and um Eguchi
and uh like I said the characters were designed
by um Imamura
and that awesome music was by
um Hajime Hirasawa so
awesome music. We've got so many different
good versions of that song too.
Um
It was also stated
by Miyamoto that he wanted to use animal
characters since he didn't want to
do conventional sci-fi with
robots, monsters, and superheroes.
And uh so that's how
it came about.
So um moving
a little bit uh forward
there's secret levels in the game.
Did you ever do any of the secret levels Rob?
I did. Wasn't it the thing where you had to shoot the little
planet and the little planet that would pop out
for like a half second? You had to do something?
And then you had to shoot it in the eye?
There were, okay. If I remember this
correctly cause keep in mind it's been a while since
I've done it. To get to the um the black hole
level you have to shoot
these um like
rings that there's a little central
part. Is this the slot machine level?
That's the slot machine. I think that's the slot machine.
Yeah
is that going from the easy one to the
This video is somebody actually doing it. So
we'll uh. No that's the first one.
The slot machines
later on. Let me fast forward
the video a little bit then. Where's the slot machine?
Oh no that's the one.
That's the slot machine one.
Yeah I think somebody
accesses it here cause here's the
Yeah that's the slot machine.
Okay anyway let me
There was one where um
where you uh
have to shoot these certain rings a certain
way and then fly through the center of the explosion
and then this ugly ass planet
pops up that looks like um
you know it kind of looks like the moon from
Majora's Mask. It looks like a troll
face to me. To me it looks like
the moon from Majora's Mask.
And um you have to
shoot it or fly into it or something.
And so you get to go to the first
um black hole and the
black hole basically if you
whatever different ring pops up in the black
hole if you fly through it it warps you
to that level. Shut up Slippy.
Anyway.
The other one which is one that we were talking about
a moment ago is you get there from
asteroid field course three.
Is um
called out of this dimension.
And it plays um
different music as you go
through it um you actually have to shoot down
paper planes.
At first. And then the boss plays um
different parts. One is from a
Japanese folk song called Yuki.
Um the chorus from when the saints go marching
in and lightly row.
And uh you shoot parts of the machine
like the arm to cause
the spinners on the slot machine
to go. And basically um
when you land
on three sevens
um then you defeat the machine
and it explodes. And then you
actually fly through the ending credits
of the game and then the end shows up
but all the letters are flipped around. So you have to keep shooting
the letters and when it finally lines up the different way
it um basically just
I think starts you over.
It ends the game. Imagine that.
It's not just a clever title.
No this
crazy mode seven.
Ooh mode seven. And FX FX.
And FX exactly.
Wasn't there only like one other game that had the FX chip in it?
That would be Stunt Race FX.
I think there was one more.
There was a robot game.
Oh yeah there was. You're right. And keep in mind there's the
Star Fox 2 prototype.
That of course
we never saw.
Now the one I'm going to talk about next is actually
one that our friend Melody
used to have a copy of.
And that was the competition version.
Which is the Super Star Fox weekend competition one.
Where uh they had
a limited time play
and there were two thousand copies made
and she said she sold hers.
There was um you know we had
a number of Star Fox games come out since then.
Star Fox 2 was in the works for Super Nintendo.
Um
though um the head programmer said
that they actually finished the game.
Um there was
uh Star Fox 64.
There were
um there's actually ROM dumps of
Star Fox 2 that were from different stages
of development. And someone
actually translated it and made um
a patch for it.
There is Star Fox
on the GameCube that was Star Fox Adventures by
Rare. We had
Star Fox Assault for the GameCube
that was done by Namco.
And it was a third person shooter.
There was Star Fox Command that was on the DS.
And now there's um Star Fox makes
appearances in a micro game in Warrior
where Smooth moves.
And um you fight
basically the Nintendo robot
who has a huge munga zapper.
And
that's it.
Alright. A true classic.
Star Fox. Again
one of those games I had to go
she's never done Star Fox before? I know.
I had to go really? I've never done Star Fox before?
So yeah. So yeah
200 episodes into this or what?
Also funny.
The Starwing logo uses a completely different font
than Star Fox. Just saying.
Now some folks in chat were like
boy Nintendo really ruined this franchise.
You know some of the Star Fox Adventures of course
was not very well received and
you know I think people liked Star Fox 64
enough. Um and a lot of
Star Fox 2 kind of went into that but uh
yeah Star Fox Adventures wasn't really
pretty. So that's too bad.
Anyhow we are going
to take a quick break but don't go anywhere. We got
more Orange Lounge Radio to come. Things that might
actually be better than Star Fox.
Alright maybe not but they're still
pretty good so stick around. We'll be right back after this
with more of Orange Lounge Radio.
Welcome back everybody to Orange Lounge Radio.
We are live with episode number
451 for this.
March the 25th of
2012. Um I know we
can't play these live break songs that we do
um on the podcast but we were playing some
music from the DDR days and
by coincidence I happened to pick
songs that were both from Dance Dance Revolution
third mix Korean.
Um and man I miss
those games. I miss DDR back when it was
so good and like that
that community and everything we had and the songs
were like legit. Like not everybody
ever understood the songs. I'm sure some of you
listening to the show now probably go
really you guys kind of like that music but
like there is just something about DDR music. I can't
explain it. I can't put my finger on it but man
I miss those days. But
oh well. It was
actually asked um by
Technus who was played at a third mix
machine that was not a Korean version.
Me. Um they had one here
locally somewhere didn't they? Well they did.
The one that I played at I think it was
AX2000. Mhm. Was
um a Japanese third mix from
uh Arcade Infinity. Ah.
Nice.
I did hear I think
that they're trying to restart Arcade Infinity
in another location. Or like something
like it. So that's cool. I hope it
happens. We'll see.
Alright anyhow let's get back into some gaming news
with some rapid fire news.
Uh some quick stories for you guys. Loki.
So uh we've
heard about LittleBigPlanet Karting
um which was you know
leaked out of the
uh what was it
uh PlayStation
event. PlayStation event. PlayStation event.
What the hell was it called? Uh
uh
uh I can't remember. Anyways.
Uh you know
Loki uh PlayStation event
basically uh is gonna be coming out on
the Vita and PlayStation 3.
Uh not surprisingly enough though it's
actually being done by
um United Front Games
who are the developers behind
ModNation Racers.
So they kinda have a little bit of experience
in you know
play, share, create racing games.
Although
at the same time that makes me
a little worried because
Well maybe they'll take some of the feedback from the last
one and make it better.
You know. Maybe.
Hopefully. Um
I mean the trailer looks neat. They have
a trailer out for it now. Um
So it has potential. I'm just really
sad that Media Molecule is not
having a
like you know really
a lot of
feedback on it. At least I hope that
they do. I don't know. It didn't really say.
So.
Um
Destination PlayStation. That's
what it was. Destination PlayStation.
Um
So yeah. They're gonna be doing an Adventure Time
game for Nintendo DS.
And it's being done by
WayForward. Um. Who have
I guess they were behind
Uh
Some new. Oh what was it?
I'm trying to remember games they put out.
The Henry Hatsworth game.
Um. They had that come out.
Um. So that was not a bad
game. And I haven't really said
too much about what the game is.
Although the creator of the show
um
actually posted some really funny
like animated gifs. So
Neat.
I'm sure the game will be pretty
awesome. The show is pretty cool.
It's a great cartoon.
And last but not least
they announced that Max Payne 3
is gonna have kind of a
new feature for the multiplayer. They're
gonna have what they're calling crews
and now what the Max
Payne 3 crews are are kind of like these
multiplayer clans that you have
that you can um play
through the game and
uh kind of um create these
uh crews or clans
through the social club. The Rockstar Social
Club page. And what's
kind of neat though is when you create
your clan in Max Payne
3 you'll actually be able to transfer it to
Grand Theft Auto 5
when that comes in to play the actual multiplayer
and that. So it's kind of like a cross game
clan
crew or whatever you want to call it.
Um. Which I think is kind of cool.
Cause they're definitely doing a lot of social club
um interaction with the game
and I know like in the past when I used
to play a lot of Grand Theft Auto 4
and I really am sad I don't play a lot of
Grand Theft Auto 4 now but
you know last week or so
actually this is kind of one thing that we
didn't talk about but on the
hacking scene for Grand Theft Auto 4
they released online scripts for
Grand Theft Auto 4
um for multiplayer.
So you're gonna see a lot more hacking
shenanigans on Grand Theft Auto 4
um if you're playing that online
which is kind of sad cause I
legitimately had a really high rank on
that game um but unfortunately
you know now anyone can game it to
you get the top of the
leaderboard so it's kind of
over and done for now.
Um but 5 man I am looking
forward to playing 5 multiplayer
for sure from day 1 but uh
Max Payne 3
not much interest in that game.
Cause it's not Grand Theft Auto.
Alright
well moving on to some other games
uh kind of in the same
category as Grand Theft Auto another Rockstar game
uh L.A. Noire
is getting a touch controlled
version um
OnLive of course put out some
various tablet apps
um and Rockstar is doing
a touch version of L.A. Noire
making this kind of more of a
touch screen friendly game or an iOS
or whatever phone it is game.
Um OnLive says those controls are now
available so you can play L.A. Noire
with OnLive Mobile
and uh yeah you can uh
swipe across the screen to do
some motions I guess you don't need to use
virtual buttons or a wireless controller
or any of that. Uh you do need to
buy L.A. Noire if you want to play it
uh or you know and have an OnLive
account and all that but it is interesting that they actually
kind of adapted it. However, however
there are free trials for all the games and the Online
client is free. So you can check it out
for free. Okay that's good to know.
So if you want to see if this is up your alley.
I don't know if L.A. Noire would work in touch
motion for me but okay.
The problem is it's L.A. Noire.
The interrogation parts will be fine but it's
the rest of the movie. I got bored
with that game really fast.
Alright moving on Final Fantasy 13
2 um you know what's funny
is that I didn't finish 13
2 and part of the reason I wasn't able to do it is because
I got sucked into Mass Effect. Well
worlds can now collide on March
27th. They've announced that there will be
Mass Effect 3 DLC
for Final Fantasy 13 2.
What? Yes it's
true. It's not as big as you think
though. It's just that now Sarah and Noel
who are of course the big two uh characters
in the game are going to get
N7 armor
that they can dress up in to make them look like Mass Effect
characters and although there's a part of me that
goes that's stupid. There's another part of me that goes
but that's really awesome.
By the way Mass Effect is not the only
kind of you know game hopping
that's going on. Assassin's Creed
Revelations outfits are supposed to be on their way.
And that's I believe only in Japan right now.
Right I don't think a date has been announced
for the US. It'll eventually
happen though. Yeah. Uh
what else is interesting I think this is
really interesting
um Final Fantasy 13 2 got some other
DLCers getting some that
throws the game back to Final Fantasy
6. Don't get too
excited it's just a couple of the characters
but if you played 6 you'll remember
Ultros right
Ultros was the octopus and the annoying
little bastard. He has the
little jokes and everything. Uh
Typhon is the other one. Is it Typhoon or
Typhon is the other one. I'll say Typhoon.
But uh is the other
I only see 1-0 so whatever.
Uh but is the other character that will be available
as well. Uh this is
more of one of those arena fights and if you beat
them in the arena then you can use them as your monsters
cause you know your third person can always be a monster.
So I thought it was kind of funny that
they kind of went back to the
past with that so that's pretty cool.
So there you go. Uh
no announcement when that is out in the US
March 27th in Japan however.
So probably soon thereafter.
Um
this is just you know kind of unfortunate
but um some of the promotion
for Street Fighter X Tekken caused
Yoshinori Ono to need medical
treatment which is um unfortunate.
Uh the producer of course
he's the producer of the Street Fighter series
and you know this new direction they're
going in here. He was at a
Street Fighter X Tekken event in South Korea and he
just collapsed. He had to go to the hospital.
Uh they did post Capcom on
their Street Fighter blog. Immediately after
a Street Fighter X Tekken event in Asia
the physical condition of Street Fighter X Tekken producer
Ono-Chin, that's the nickname
he goes by, rapidly deteriorated
and he collapsed. He was taken to the hospital and he
is currently not coming into work.
Luckily it sounds like something that's
easily treatable.
Luckily it also sounds like he didn't suffer
from exhaustion the same way that that one
guy did that's all over THC. I was just
gonna make that joke.
But uh
yeah it's not something to really joke
about in this guy's case so too bad.
Hope he feels better.
Yeah that's sad. However you might feel
about the game aside um
Well both did suffer exhaustion
while handling their fight sticks.
So for a game
coming out in Japan called
well actually I think it's coming out here too. It's by
Platinum Games
Anarchy Reigns.
Famitsu put out images that Bayonetta
is gonna be in the game.
No other news about it
just hi Bayonetta.
What else do you need besides
I don't know a sequel to Bayonetta? I know right.
And also amongst the
30 some odd games that were removed
from the Japanese Wii Virtual
Console uh
basically 4 Sonic games are gone.
Sonic 1 to Sonic and Knuckles is gone
as well as the uh Master System
version of Sonic 1.
Which is too bad cause you know it's impossible
to get Sonic 1 on any other platform.
Well there's
no I mean the Master System.
I know what you mean but you know what I mean.
But there's
no word about it in the US or Europe yet
but I'm sure it's gonna follow.
And then fans of ThinkGeek
who have I'm sure seen more and more
and more Portal stuff pop up there
I sure have including an inflatable
Sentry and a little uh talking
Sentry uh plushie that I totally want.
Um the Portal gun
is for sale for 140 bucks.
5,000 replicas have been made.
And somebody better buy me one for my birthday.
That's all I'm saying.
No secret what you want huh?
Just saying.
Birthdays next month.
Let's go to the FUGL Question
of the Week. We missed it last week but it's back tonight.
The FUGL Question of the Week.
Uh Facebook and
Google Plus get a question every week
and we read some of our favorite answers
here on the program for you
guys and if uh those in studio want to
answer. I don't know if they repeat the question
in advance. It's kind of a toughie. This is one that
takes a little bit of thought tonight.
Uh so we'll start at Google Plus
with Orange Lounge Radio.
FUGL Question of the Week. If you could go back and change
a classic games ending since
you know it's all the rage right now talking about changing
the ending of games. What ending would you change
and what would the new ending be?
And I said let's stick to classics because
we don't want to spoil any new games. So I
did force people to think classics. It's interesting
though. We got a lot of varied responses that
weren't, that kind of took the question in a different
direction. And uh Derek H.
starts us off on Google in that direction.
I want to go back to the days when
games didn't have endings.
The only time it ended was because the
machine broke or you ran out of quarters.
I bet there's some guy in Ohio that's
still playing River Raid after 25
years and he's only on his
second man.
Imagine some kid complaining after the planet
exploded in Stargate or when Pauline
kept getting kidnapped by Donkey Kong
or that the ambulance always passed you in
Turbo. That would never happen because
in those days, gamers
weren't spoiled little punks who need
closure after having pretend sex with an
alien.
So some pretty strong words
there about uh
back in my day, back in the old day.
That's true though. A lot of Atari
2600 games never ended.
Very few had an ending. You know the ending
the only game I can think of
a couple of them that actually
had endings. Oops
no. No Holik during the uh
question. Thank you. Um
Pitfall and Pitfall 2.
And at the end of Pitfall
it just stops. It freezes.
I don't think there's anything to do it. And the ending of
Pitfall 2, he jumps up
and down a lot. And you won.
It's because games back then
were trying to recreate the arcade experience
games today are
about touching you emotionally.
Alright uh going to Facebook
some of the answers there.
Blue 2 says that's a tough one. I can't
think of any ending I would change. However like
thousands of gamers out there
finished Half Life already Gabe.
So uh he kind of ignored the question
of the week and just said finish Half Life. But actually
Alan was telling me about how
Half Life 2
Episode 1 did kind of
go back and
patch a few things up from what was originally
out there for Half Life so
they've kind of tinkered with those
endings before. Um
Let's see
Jim H answers on Facebook
saying since I just beat it again yesterday
I would change the ending of Super Mario Brothers 2
so it isn't a dream
at the end. I know it
I know it was a different
game they just plugged in Mario
characters into but since they did end up
using enemies from the game in later sequels
it would be nice if it fit into the
continuity better. Oh yeah the
original it was all a dream ending
Mario 2 right?
Yeah. But it
doesn't fit well into the continuity when it's all a
dream. I like that idea. That's good.
Uh let's see Stan H
on Facebook says I'd
change the ending of the
I Said No Holic
Thank you
I'd change the ending of the original
Super Mario Brothers. I'd make it so that when
Mario saves Peach from Bowser
she tells her that he
I think he tells her that he is enrolling her in some
Taekwondo lessons with Chun-Li
so that when Bowser tries to kidnap her
at least she'd be able to put up a fight and she
wouldn't get kidnapped so damn frequently.
Nintendo wouldn't have to whore the Mario
series out so much. Remember
she doesn't fight with Kung Fu she fights
with emotions. That's right
Super Princess Peach. That's what we learned.
Lastly Robert C
on Facebook says I'd change the ending to
Mortal Kombat. The mandatory
final fight would be between Katana and
Sonia. They'd suddenly both swap
fighting styles to Brazilian Jutsu
in a big pool of mud
or jelly. The final scene would
obviously be a slow motion montage
of them moving from fighting to kissing.
Cue the 70's porn music.
Oh
you.
I see what you did
there. It'd be kinda hot.
Any classic
games you guys here in studio would want to change?
I know you haven't had a lot of time
to think about the answer. I
would say let's go back to Ghosts and
Goblins and give them proper grammar.
How's that sound?
That was part of the fun.
I guess that's true.
Um
I can't
really think of anything because you know what
I'm not a little bitch with
a sense of entitlement.
We're just having fun.
I will tell you which
game needs another
different ending. The Legend of Zelda
it needs a third quest.
Actually
I would give a better ending to Zelda
to the past after how fucking hard that game
is. Kinda get a shitty ending.
That game was epic.
I mean yeah don't get me wrong it's a fucking tremendous
game but kind of a crab ending.
Dude.
They really, you know what would be awesome
totally on tangent here.
Is they should totally go with the
Little Big Planet style to
the Legend of Zelda games. You know how they have
a ton of ROM hacks and stuff like that with custom levels
for the Legend of Zelda. Why not have
a Legend of Zelda game that was like Link to the Past
but with a ton of fucking custom games
in there. Oh I know because no one would ever
play your new Zelda games because they'd be
too busy enthralled with
the custom made stuff.
You want the Legend of Little Big Planet?
I want the Legend
of Zelda with a really kick ass
editor
that's officially sanctioned. I'm trying to
think of just the endings of different games
and really I keep thinking back
to how epic many of them were.
You know like Hitler's head blowing up
at the end of Bionic Commando
or
you know
how you felt bad
for the baby Metroid when you know
it got killed
and
it's all kinds of sad-facedness.
I would go back and make sure
that every Silent Hill game had a dog
ending. Yes. I would
you know what actually I would change the ending
to Shattered Memories because I
wanted to like that game a whole lot.
In fact
I think that the next Silent
Hill game should be directed by Peter Molyneaux
and you should play as the dog.
Should be
called Silent Dog. Alright now you guys are getting
crazy. Let's move on with some more game news.
Yeah but wait wait wait Silent Dog
has a cat
let me finish let me finish has a cat ending.
I love the idea of a game called
Silent Dog.
Where the
This might be a dream game.
Hold on. Hold on. Alright dream game.
Silent Dog. The dog must confront
you know the
demons of its past you know like
all the legs they've peed on
chasing its tail and
yeah being chased by a
faceless postman with claw
hands. Tires that they can
just never catch.
Frisbees of doom with razor blades
on them. And mandatory
Kiryamoka is forced
to do all the music.
Cause it's
just not a Silent Hill game. Really it should just be
the dog song throughout the whole game.
Woof woof woof woof woof woof woof woof woof woof woof
That you know we need we need
to we need to play that Rob. I don't think I have
the dog getting music readily accessible.
Yes you do. You have
YouTube. Yes you do.
You know
I would love to see like the
saga of the UFO ending Silent Hill
as a UFO.
That would just be great.
Uh hold on I'm
finding it for you guys.
It was you the whole time?
Praying there's no uh
There it is.
It would be awesome.
But we can't forget about the most important
part of Silent Dog.
Which I think is at the very end of the song.
I like that he growls
at that one horrible guy.
Ugh this is so great.
Listen to Vampire wants to know this is the canon ending to Silent Hill 2 right?
Yes. Yes absolutely.
Was it Silent Hill 3 that had like the um
Here's the most important scene in the entire game.
Hold on.
Oh.
Does it do the chorus one more time?
Yes. Oh god.
I was wondering if the voice actor has been changed for the dog in the HD collection.
Here it is.
That's right the all important sex scene.
Where the adults are having sex and the dog is just forced to watch with that blank expression on their face.
Like what are my owners doing?
You know actually one of my live journal icons is the dog and it says game over.
You know as much as I love the dog ending I still like the um the Silent Hill theme.
Silent Hill. Silent Hill.
From one of the UFO endings.
Anyhow I don't know how we got on this topic but Silent Dog make it happen.
Woof woof woof.
So we were going to get into news at some point right?
News?
Yeah we were talking about Silent Dog though so that is very important.
Um.
Oh our dream game.
Silent Dog.
So someone needs to explain to me once again why we have these online passes because I swear it's just like I never hear anything going smoothly with them.
I mean I don't understand but whatever.
So Ninja Gaiden 3 came out this week and um yeah apparently no one could redeem the online passes for that game.
Not even the reviewers could redeem the online passes because they had forgot to flip the switch to allow those passes to be redeemed.
Ha ha.
Um so yes none of the codes worked at all at launch.
I think they work now. They may be working soon but as of you know earlier this week they were not working at all.
So fun.
Um.
And then on top of that MLB 12 the show another game with an online pass also had its issues.
Apparently the Playstation 3 and Vita versions had a problem if the Vita players tried to redeem the online pass they couldn't do it via the Vita.
They could only do it if they had a Playstation 3.
But here's the funny thing if they did it via the PS3 it unlocked online play for the PS3 version that they don't own.
So uh yeah apparently they were working out problems with that.
But I don't know.
It's interesting I guess.
And then last but not least there is one more game that had an online pass.
EA Sports MMA.
It had an online pass and it had online play.
It wasn't a very popular game.
And on April 13th they will be shutting down the server for it.
So it just.
It was on the failure board. Sorry.
It seemed appropriate.
Other games that are going to be shut are getting their servers shut down as well.
EA Create game which was supposed to take on LittleBigPlanet and that sucked.
And EA Sports Active 2 which I didn't even know that had online.
And the Xbox Live Arcade game Spare Parts is also going to be getting its servers shut down.
On top of that Boom Blocks for the Wii.
Burnout Revenge for Xbox 360.
Damn it I own Boom Blocks.
EA Sports Active NFL Training Camp for the Wii.
FIFA 10 for the PSP and the Wii.
Godfather 2 for the PC, Playstation 3 and Xbox 360.
Need for Speed Pro Street on PS3 and 360.
And the Saboteur for PS3 and 360 is going to lose the access to the Midnight Club.
Which is some exclusive club but that was in the game if you preordered.
And then on the 31st they're shutting down Battlefield 3 Aftershock for the iPad, iPhone, iPod Touch.
You know that game they just released.
And a few other iPad games.
But you know that $10 that funds that online pass.
It costs a lot to shut a server down.
Yeah must be nice I hope they're refunding money.
Oh of course they're not refunding money because you got your online play.
But just remember when you're paying for $10 for online for some of these games.
If it's not popular they're just going to shut the server down.
At least it wasn't as quickly as like say you know.
Oh what was that one MMO that was like Grand Theft Auto?
That they just re-released for free.
APB?
Yeah at least it wasn't that quick.
Dart Tetsuya in our chatroom says I called that section the online pass blooper reel.
I have to admit when I was reading all this news all I could hear in my head was.
Music
I mean those poor bastards that are buying some of those games used.
And now they're just going to be offline.
I mean shutting down the servers is nothing new.
But now we have a game that people paid $10 to play online and it's not forever.
And I understand that these games may not have been popular or whatever.
And I'm sorry that's nice that it might not have been popular.
But I don't know I mean I guess eventually it has to happen.
Figure out a way to consolidate then.
I mean I realize I'm talking out my ass here.
But shouldn't there be a way where maybe you could consolidate some of the servers.
And just have a computer that runs for whatever occasional game.
You know like combine servers.
Yeah I mean I can't imagine that like you know EA Sports MMA.
And the reason they shut them down is because not many people are playing them right now.
But there's still a few people playing them.
Just drop them out of servers that you have.
Drop of the one.
You can only have one person play online at a time.
Well I mean still that's better than none at all.
And especially for people that paid.
Just unfortunate.
Alright well anyhow here's something else that's unfortunate.
And kind of along the same topic of something we were just talking about.
You know the Silent Hill HD collection just recently came out.
And apparently it's getting very very mixed polarized reviews.
I haven't played it myself yet.
So I can't say one way or the other.
But you've got some people that are like yay it's Silent Hill it's in HD it looks great.
And some people are like the game is fucking missing fog.
The frame rate is hideous.
The voice acting is terrible.
And it's gotten to the point.
I don't know if you want to call this entitlement or what.
Amazon.com is no longer stocking the game.
That just came out two weeks ago.
Because there are too many user reports that there is a problem with the item.
So Amazon.com is doing an investigation to see if it's problematic.
It didn't even come out two weeks ago. It came out last week.
Oh my gosh.
And you know what though?
I have to agree with them as far as the fog thing goes.
Because even the art director or whatever said hey we use a lot of transparent textures for fog.
And you can even see there's a lot of objects that don't quite go all the way.
They're not complete objects because the fog would normally be obscuring them.
And so without the fog it looks like oh hey look I've got these telephone wires that just disappear.
What the hell? That doesn't make any sense.
But what's interesting I tried to go to like I wanted to see what the user feedback was.
So I went to Amazon.com to read some of the reviews and it's still kind of divided.
And like I don't know if that's like fanboys versus you know or what it is but it's very divided.
Because for like let me go to Metacritic real fast and do Silent Hill.
Now it should be noted the PS3 one is getting more flack than the Xbox 360 one seems to be.
So just to kind of put that out there.
Yeah the user score 5.1.
Six positive reviews. Five negative reviews.
So you have some people that are giving it tens going I don't understand why people are hating on this.
Konami says relive the two best horror games of all time, strong graphics.
And then you get some people that are bombing it putting the game has far too many bugs to recommend to first timers or veterans alike.
And it's interesting you look at the scores.
Okay eleven people have reviewed the game.
Here are the scores.
Zero. Zero. Ten. Ten. Zero. Ten. Nine. Zero.
And it's funny is that you have.
Nobody's in the middle. They're either all the way here or all the way there.
You have to. That's a perfect example right there of what's wrong with review scores.
And what's wrong with review scores by just average people sometimes.
Because those people are obviously fanboys.
Because a game. Trust me that game doesn't warrant a ten and it doesn't warrant a zero either.
It's just. It's ridiculous.
Now to be fair the critics.
The you know legitimate whatever you want to call it.
Critics. Although I think that's a shitty name.
Have given it. There's only three reviews up so far which is strange.
I thought more outlets have reviewed it.
But you have a ninety, an eighty, and a seventy.
So two good and one average.
I think it's been more average for sure.
I think that's what I've been reading out on the internet too.
It's kind of like if you've never played Silent Hill.
And the old games are too hard to get now then go ahead and play this.
But otherwise get your PS2 and go hook up the old games because they were better.
I don't know.
Rama in chat says how the hell they fucked this game up I'll never know.
Well not putting fog in there.
And I think was that only on the PS3 version or something like that?
Like they were saying oh well we had trouble rendering the fog.
Why would you have trouble rendering the fog on the Playstation 3?
Here's my other concern. Why did they feel the need then to put this game out now?
It's not like we have a shortage of Silent Hill in the world right now.
We just had Downpour. We're gonna have the Vita game coming out.
Why does this need to be out right now?
And okay let's just say that...
Go back and make it right.
Let's just say for whatever reason okay we can't do the fog.
Did anybody that was QA'ing that game realize hey it looks a little fucking weird that something that's supposed to not be there.
Or something that's supposed to be obscured by fog is just stopping in the middle of the air.
That doesn't make any sense.
Maybe we should I don't know recreate the object or something like that instead of porting all the assets over and going.
Eh whatever close enough.
I mean seriously come on.
Just like spend the two seconds it would take to recreate the object or I don't know go back and fix it.
Was the Metal Gear collection this bad?
It was fuzzy looking. I didn't like the look of it.
But I don't think it was this bad.
I honestly haven't seen because Dan keeps playing the MSX versions.
Does it really have the MSX games in there?
Yes.
In English?
Nice.
I think it got the Metal Gear Solid collection got good reviews.
Sg100Matt in our chatroom says it's a fucking Playstation 3 how can it not render fog?
That's a great question.
Why is fog on the PS3 difficult?
Fog in the same way they did it on the PS2 is probably difficult but ok.
Well take the time to redo it if you're gonna do this.
That's exactly my problem.
Just like those fucking people at Capcom.
They're complaining well we didn't know how to do local team play.
In Street Fighter X2 we didn't want to bother to learn that.
Boo fucking hoo that you couldn't spend the time to figure out how to program your game.
If you can't do any god damn programming then quit.
Because seriously you're of no use to us if you can't make a game.
Oh we had to make new assets for this game.
You mean I couldn't just straight port the shit over and up the res the textures?
Yeah you may have to do a little bit of work.
Porkchop in our chatroom says maybe we'll have a DLC bundle.
We'll call it the Fog and Dog Pack.
Maybe.
AcidicVampire says maybe someone should file an issue with the Better Business Bureau and get the fog eventually implemented.
Don't give people ideas.
But it's important to say this though.
Again the reviews were half and half.
So not everybody's hating on it.
And Konami they've had issues with the Silent Hill series.
They really have.
I mean.
Well Akira Yomoka going somewhere else didn't help.
Yes that's true.
I mean and it's not our show role but you know and as I mentioned weeks ago.
The Vita version has been delayed.
That's right again right to May or something?
Well the rumor is May right now but I don't think there's actually a date yet for it.
Wow.
But yeah the Vita version's been delayed.
They have one more chance.
Konami has one more chance at this HD collection thing.
They've got the Zone of Enders collection coming out in the fall.
So cross fingers.
Well if the Metal Gear 1 was pretty good and the Silent Hill 1 was not so good then maybe ZOE will be in the middle.
And we're talking like porting different engines over.
So maybe that has some issues.
But come on.
Try a little harder.
When did you think I mean come on you don't see any problem with hey you know that telephone pole just disappears.
You know like or hey that part of the fence is missing it just goes nowhere because you had fog obscuring it before.
It does also make me worry like if they can't render fucking fog like granted it's another company we're talking about here.
But is that Final Fantasy 10 HD remake gonna blow?
And it's not that they couldn't render fog they couldn't render enough fog.
Like certain textures they couldn't render.
Needs more fog.
Seriously it's like how did you fuck this up?
Transparent textures the PS3 just can't do that.
Or Konami doesn't know how to do that.
Alright let's move into the mailbag.
Speaking of strong opinions and so forth.
Every week you guys send us emails.
Mailbag at OrangeLawnsRadio.com and DarkSakura dives into the mailbag head first and picks.
Oh she got a little sticky tonight.
Picks a few of her favorite mails to read to us here in studio.
All two of them.
Mailbag at OrangeLawnsRadio.com email us.
Greetings OLR it's your friendly neighborhood turtle.
Last year when I bought my beast video card for my PC it came with Civ 5.
Rob I'm sorry but as much as I tried I was always so bored by it.
Get out.
But last week I found the answer.
Quick pace.
Ever since I found that little option I can't stop playing the game.
Alright you can stay.
I used to be a huge German board game player and this is a very involved board game to
me.
And it was because you always talk about how great the game is.
Thank you very much for that.
Also I have a request for OLR.
My wife of seven years just had her birthday and I was hoping that at the end of reading
this email you could wish a very happy birthday to french fry.
As always you are an integral part of my week your loyal turtle and filly series turtle.
Happy birthday french fry.
What if I'm more of a fan of onion rings?
Can we give a shout out to onion rings?
Don't be a hoe.
Alright happy birthday french fry.
Happy birthday french fry.
I like the sea salted french fries a lot at Wendy's just saying.
Last email.
Is there any relation to french toast?
This is me staring at Rob with a, you didn't just say that face.
This is me recycling the happy music.
Hearts.
I'm making hearts at Rob now.
Boy not eating makes you a bitch.
Does it?
I have lots of energy.
I've been drinking so much.
I'm just fucking with you.
All the times by the way that I have been quiet I've been in the bathroom.
I'm doing nothing but drinking broth.
Okay.
Robert HM here.
I'm peeing nothing but broth.
I said drinking nothing but broth.
Never mind.
Next email yes.
I never heard your thoughts on the Muppets DLC pack for LittleBigPlanet 2.
Myself I enjoyed it but haven't gotten to sit down to get everything yet.
Relatedly, is that a word relatedly?
Sure.
How do you feel about the level pack DLC for the game and possibly others staying hosted on the server?
Such as that the levels out at the time were inaccessible during the PSN outage.
I guess the only positive is that one doesn't have to wait for hundreds of megabytes at PSN speeds to download.
It does update the game itself though.
Or is the content now being loaded in and I have no idea what I'm writing about.
The LittleBigPlanet stuff is generally fun but frustrating content especially trying to get all the prize items.
I actually had no idea.
Okay confession time.
I loved LittleBigPlanet 1.
I still haven't bought LittleBigPlanet 2.
I'm waiting for it to go on sale and every time I check it's like still like 50, 60 bucks.
Granted it's the game of the year edition that comes with all the extra stuff but I'm kind of waiting for it to get a little cheaper before I buy it.
I just totally missed it.
It came out at a time when a ton of other games came out so I never got around to getting it.
And I want to get it so I can check out this Muppets DLC and all that so I'm not going to sit here and make up an opinion on something I haven't played.
But I'm still interested in checking it out. I'll put it that way.
As far as the server end stuff, I had no idea that was going on.
That's weird though. Why would you not...
I don't get it because you either have to download it to your drive or you have to download it to play it server side even.
It's not like it's doing an on live thing where it's streaming.
It's like...
I don't think it could handle it.
That's weird.
That sounds very like Final Fight Magic Sword locks you out when PSN is down type of thing to maybe prevent hacking and cracking like what we're seeing happen with Street Fighter X Tekken.
And that's...
You got something about that too coming up.
Sony needs to stop assuming that PSN is always going to be up because it's not.
Anyhow.
Very strange.
So anyway. That's the last email.
Alrighty.
Mailbag at OrangeLawnTrader.com to send us emails in the future.
Meanwhile, Loki.
Alright. Let's talk a little bit about hacking.
Not necessarily hacking of things that some people might find controversial but fan translated stuff for example.
For example, there's two games that recently have been kind of hacked to translate them into English because no English versions were made available.
One of those being Tales of Vesperia on the PS3.
Tales of Vesperia of course came out on Xbox 360 in the US but never on the PS3.
The PS3 version, which I believe was superior to the Xbox 360 version and had a lot more content to that, was available in Japan.
So what people are doing of course is hacking the game to actually use the Xbox 360 translation to translate the text in the PS3 version and of course doing their own translation for the new content.
And it's funny enough they said that actually the Xbox 360 translated version text was actually hidden in the PS3 code because you know you don't clean up your code.
So they're working on translating that.
They were originally doing the Tales of Graces but since that actually did get localized over here they stopped working on that when that announcement was made.
And I guess of course they're saying that this will have a patch to the game and of course it will require you to have a jailbroken PS3 with a firmware of 3.55 or lower.
And they're going to release documentation on how to patch your game if you wish to do so.
And then on top of that there of course is another fan translated thing that actually finished and that is Fatal Frame 4 Mask of the Lunar Eclipse has been translated into English for the Nintendo Wii.
And there's a big ol' effort with that. Of course you have to patch a version of the game that you have dumped to an ISO or you can always download a pre-patch version and run it from your hard drive because they made it so freaking easy to do that.
But very interesting.
I don't usually endorse the piracy of games but if they're not going to release it here, they're not going to give you the opportunity, what other choice do you have?
Exactly. And if you had it before then you might as well translate it into English so you can actually understand it. Also it should be noted that they have fully translated it into Spanish and German and French translations are about halfway done as well.
So it's pretty interesting.
Alright. Well Microsoft has put out an interesting patent. You know we sometimes get what's coming in the gaming industry from what's going on with patents.
And Microsoft has patented this weird helmet device. It's a laser scanning virtual image display and it will display an image very close to your eyes.
Apparently by doing this the two displays could be in a helmet and you'd be able to see stereoscopic 3D. It's kind of a similar trick to what the 3DS uses except it's putting those images right in front of your freaking face.
It doesn't necessarily mean that this is limited to video games. Remember Microsoft is a PC company as well so it could be something that's used with general PC games.
But it could be used in aviation as stated in the patent. Maybe this is going to be like a bitchin' flight simulator add-on or what do they call it now? They changed the name.
Microsoft Flight.
You know what? It's the Lawnmower Man.
Actually I remember like 20 years ago renting from the local store. Don't ask why we did this but we rented a headset VR display.
And all it was you put this headset on it fucking looked like something on Lawnmower Man. It was just a TV right in front of your eyes.
And it was the amazing VR display you could play Super Nintendo games on.
They had a VR type thing over at the boardwalk in Santa Cruz and you could play versions of Duke Nukem 3D or Quake.
And I actually played Quake on that and it was terrible. It was like I had my eyes straight up to my PC screen and that was it.
Oh go ahead.
I was going to say yeah it's so immersive with the 640x480 graphics.
And there's a 100 Matt in our chatroom at chat.orangetontrady.com brings up the Virtual Boy. It was kind of a similar gag too.
This image may be partially transparent so you can see the world around you.
So that way you can play your game and this sounds like something out of a giant picture.
It's the game from Star Trek.
So you can see the people laughing at you.
No seriously from Next Generation where they had the little thing that shot lasers in their eyes. Oh.
So you can see the people laughing at you for wearing a giant helmet.
Oh my god Chiggers at the exact same time you said that Chiggers in chat said it's like that Star Trek Next Generation episode and everybody will be zombies.
You guys are both really big nerds.
So.
Alright so there you go.
Before you even say oh this is the next Xbox.
No.
Sit down. It's not.
No we've been down that territory.
OMG Microsoft Portable.
No.
Sit down.
You know that Wii prototype or the one that was fake would have been pretty fucking awesome.
Mm hmm.
VR.
DarkSakura what do you have for us.
Well as mentioned earlier Capcom is cracking down.
Basically a statement and I actually did read this on the Capcom Unity forums.
But they're talking about people using the download character.
The downloadable characters on disk using hacked Xboxes.
And one of the big guys at Capcom Unity said quite ballsy for folks to be taking hacked Xbox 360s on live where they are detectable.
And they're also saying in any event we have open channels of communication with Microsoft on these issues Friday night.
And then they started asking people to take screenshots and record videos of the offenders.
But they closed the video and said oh we'll catch them ourselves.
They do realize that you can't take screenshots of a fucking Xbox 360 right?
Yes you can.
Well you can if you're a developer.
But what if you have one of those capture cards?
Okay well that's a capture card but I'm talking about like you can't just.
It's not like the Vita where I can push two buttons and take a screenshot.
And it wouldn't.
And there's iPhones and cameras.
And we wouldn't have this problem if they didn't put the DLC on the fucking disk.
I agree.
And this smells a lot like CD Projekt Red a few months ago.
We're gonna catch those hackers.
And we're gonna let the hackers go.
They're gonna be Batman. I'm Batman.
Well I mean I do agree with the point that you gotta be pretty bold to play this shit online.
Again it's kinda that gamer mentality you see sometimes.
And some gamers where it's like I gotta be the first and I gotta I'm gonna show these guys online that my penis is the biggest.
And I'm using characters you're not supposed to have.
You know it's a little bit silly.
Look at my E-Pain.
Exactly.
But it's kind of a dumb thing to take it online where you know they're watching.
I like what Chigurh says. I will hit you with a coelacanth.
I'm moving on.
Logie.
So this is I'm sure a disappointment to some of the people who are actually playing.
But Zynga has purchased the company OMG Pop. The makers of the game Draw Something.
And of course they purchased them for quite a bit of money.
Including approximately $200 million between I guess a cash deal and $30 million or so for employee retention payments.
And of course you know they're gonna be working with them to create some new games I guess.
In related news I deleted Draw Something this week.
I was playing it pretty hardcore for a little bit. I had like 15 games going at once. It was crazy.
And I said nope I'm done.
By the way there's another iPhone app you might want to check out if you are in the same boat I am.
It's called Sharadium.
C-H-A-R-A-D-I-U-M.
It was free at least for a little bit. I don't know if it still is but you can check it out.
Now before you go saying well Rob if you don't like Zynga because they rip games off.
Why are you recommending another game that's a rip off of Draw Something?
Because it is a little bit different. It's not like a direct rip off.
Unfortunately one of the best parts of the game which is the whole Wheel of Fortune round isn't really in there.
It's more of a chat type guessing thing.
But there's more paint styles and it's more of a robust paint program than Draw Something was.
You don't have to pay for extra colors and shit.
You have to pay for extra colors?
Oh yeah and Draw Something if you wanted more than just red. What was it? Red, blue, yellow and black were the only colors you could use.
If you wanted green and purple you either saved up enough tokens from winning games or you had to pay 99 cents to get them.
That's hilarious.
Oh yeah and I knew people that had tons of colors.
Well it's sad.
You know what? Your money spent by which you won.
And you know what though?
Until Zynga knew I spent 99 cents buying the legit add free Draw Something.
Because I'm like this is a great new game I want to support this.
And then this happened.
Honestly I can't fault some of the employees at Zynga because they're just working but it's obviously the higher ups.
It's the ones that are making the decisions.
The executives.
I actually have some friends that work at Zynga and there's some really talented people which I'm like what are you doing working at Zynga but hey whatever.
Well it's just like how we talk about GameStop.
I know lots of people that work at GameStop that are great people and they're just people trying to get by and make a living.
I don't have a problem in the world with people that work at GameStop.
You know and I even will go so far as to say they have some of the toughest jobs in the world and I respect that.
It's some of the decisions that are made at a corporate level at GameStop that I have a huge problem with.
Yeah.
That's the issue.
So you know I imagine it's a similar situation.
Why else do you think that Dan keeps getting class action lawsuit checks after he hasn't been working there for six years?
Wow.
Just saying.
Very interesting.
I want some class action lawsuit checks.
How do I get in on that?
Work for GameStop.
Well they might try to go the other way around and sue me.
Alright.
Anyhow one more story for you guys tonight and then we're going to open up the Skype line at 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype OrangeLoungeRadio but not just yet.
We have one more story for you guys tonight and it's another fucking Kickstarter.
This is a trend.
I'm not liking this trend.
I'm just going to say it's just too much.
Everybody in the world wants a piece of this Kickstarter thing and it's like I'm sorry.
It's kind of like those that got in on it early like the double fine and stuff.
Good for them but now it's just getting old.
However there may be some folks that are really into this so good for you guys.
Tex Murphy may make a comeback.
Big Finish Games is going to start up a Kickstarter page on May 15th.
That seems weird to me that you'd announce like six weeks in advance.
We're going to start a Kickstarter but alright they're going to round up funding for a sixth game in this Full Motion Video Adventure series.
Oh God I remember these games.
Wow.
On May 15th they're going to go live and you can donate to all this and the guy who plays Tex Murphy is on board.
And you can actually see him in a YouTube video where they're actually trying to kind of hawk the whole Kickstarter event.
So I don't know it's like I don't want to hate Kickstarter but I just hate the trend thing is what it is.
And I don't hate every campaign on Kickstarter but there's some that are pretty gross.
But I've already talked about that on a previous episode.
There's one in particular I saw that was downright offensive and I think people who contributed to it.
I think in some ways got suckered and swindled but that's your choice, your money.
Anyhow let's move on to happier topics or maybe worse topics.
It's all up to you guys in the hands of the listeners because the Skype line is open now at 1-877-GAME-OLR.
Our username on Skype is OrangeLoungeRadio.
Alright and going to our chatroom ddrdollarbill says I like the Tex Murphy games.
I'm not saying they were bad games.
It's just this trend is a little strange and I'm not a big fan of this.
Alright so going to our Twitter while we wait for some calls.
Again it's 1-877-GAME-OLR.
Our username on Skype is OrangeLoungeRadio.
Going to the Twitter we have gamergirl who tweeted us and says I need to get a new TV.
Anyone got any recommendations as far as price and model goes?
I miss my games, cries.
I'm pretty happy with our Panasonic.
Toshiba makes good ones too.
If you've got fries in town go to fries.
I have specials all the damn time.
Yeah don't buy anything on impulse.
It's so hard for me to recommend you a specific TV gamergirl.
Do not get a plasma.
Get an LCD.
It's so hard for me to recommend a TV gamergirl because I don't know what type of setup you have.
Do you have a gigantic living room that you want a gigantic TV to fill?
Or do you want something for your bedroom that maybe you're not going to be able to use the living room an awful lot.
Like if you want a bedroom TV and it's specifically for gaming because you said I miss my games.
Maybe you should look into that Playstation monitor that's out.
I hear it's not terrible and you could do the whole 3D games if you have the consoles to support it.
But if you don't really have a Playstation 3 then that TV is kind of a waste.
So something to think about. Again if you're going for a bedroom TV why not go for a computer monitor?
You can get a cable that will hook an Xbox 360 up to the computer monitor.
As well as a Playstation 3 can hook up to a computer monitor right?
With a particular cable. Am I correct in that?
In Japan.
HDMI?
HDMI yes it can hook up to a monitor.
Well HDMI you can hook it up through an HDMI to DVI adapter.
Otherwise they sell a device or they sell an actual cable in Japan that will do it.
That I'm sure will work with the USPS3s.
Brad from Pod Culture in our chat room suggests Vizio. Best bang for the buck.
That's actually what we have. I'm happy with the Vizio. That's the way to do it.
Rama says Samsung. Best TVs ever. Chigurh says Sony Bravia all the way.
So gamer girl it's really hard when we don't know your circumstance and your budget to pinpoint one correct TV.
But do your research. Do your research online. Read reader reviews.
Don't go to the store on a whim and let the sales guy know.
Yeah I need to get a new TV because I can't play games anymore.
Because they are going to try to take it to the cleaners.
Because they're going to know you need a new TV.
And they're going to be like oh this chick's not going to leave for that one.
It's like shopping for a car.
Yeah exactly. So...
Don't be afraid to say no and don't let them know you want it.
Exactly.
And don't buy a plasma.
Well now some folks in the chat room disagree with you.
Legend of Zaku says get a plasma. Very little lag.
Chigurh agrees though saying plasma hurts my eyes.
Niche or niche I don't know how to say that.
It says plasma is better than LCD. WTF.
Disagree because with plasma you can also deal with more burn in in some cases.
I would say also Gamer Girl go to the store and kind of look at the TVs.
Especially a place where you're less likely to get hounded like Best Buy or even like Target.
Good with a furniture store.
Or Walmart even.
Oh furniture? I never thought to get TVs at a furniture store.
RC Willy.
So yeah go to a place where you're less likely to get hounded and just kind of look.
And go oh I like the look of this.
Because then you can make your own decision on plasma versus LCD.
Maybe you'll look at a plasma and go I want this.
And then you know you can.
So I would do that.
I think a Target or a Walmart is a great place to look.
Because you're not going to get hounded by salesmen.
You don't have to buy. Just look.
In fact the TVs at Walmart are probably not.
I mean they're cheap for a reason. Remember that.
I actually super agree with Technus.
If you have a membership to Costco, Sam's Club or BJ's.
I recommend them because of the return policies.
Agree agree agree.
I think the best place in the world actually.
And here we go with advertisements.
But I'm saying it because I believe it.
I think the best place in the world to get a TV is Costco.
Because their return policy.
It used to be a lot more generous than it is now.
Oh my God I had a TV break like two years after I bought it.
And Costco took it back. I was astounded.
They did that with us. They didn't have our model anymore.
So we traded it in from a 58 inch to a 52 inch.
And paid just another hundred bucks.
Me too. I was astounded.
So I don't think their policy is as generous anymore.
You have to have a receipt now.
Yeah. But yeah.
Just the price and the fact you don't get hounded.
And the selection I think is a great place to try it.
Alright anyhow.
Wow the phone's not ringing.
I hope it's working. 1877 game OLR.
Our username on Skype is orangeontradio.
Or the listeners are just being shy tonight.
That's okay. That happens sometimes.
Meh. Meh. Meh. Meh. Meh. Meh. Meh.
It might have also just been a little bit of a slow news week.
You know what I mean? Sometimes that happens.
Yeah. Why don't you just call and ask me a question people.
Dar Sakura wants attention.
I'm just checking.
No. I'm just trying to get some life into the phone line.
I'm checking to make sure the 800 number is actually working.
Because it's been having some problems lately.
Yeah it's working.
There it is.
People who've got problems.
Alright. Anyhow.
Let's move on to a couple more tweets.
We have Tiger Claw links us to a story about NASA helped with Angry Birds Space.
Oh yeah. That came out.
I forgot.
But Angry Birds Space did come out.
And apparently NASA collaborated in this with what's called a Space Act Agreement.
Why does NASA team up with this?
It saw an opportunity to teach kids about space, science, and the laws of physics.
And considering that NASA's kind of taken some hits lately with funding and all that,
I can see why they'd want to get on board with this.
And you know, if I was a kid, I'd be really into this I think.
So I think this is actually a good thing.
I can't hate on this.
A comment from, what is this?
Space Station Trajectory Operations Officer.
It's a great way to demonstrate how we can use trajectories to get from one place to another.
It's a really good example of how interplanetary probes can take gravity assets from other,
or gravity assists, excuse me, from other planets.
Alright, hey, our phone line's lighting up now.
I think your hemming and hawing worked, Dark Soccer.
We got a call.
Hi, on Orange Launch Radio. Who's this?
Hi, this is Zach Deff.
Hey, Zach Deff. What's up, buddy?
Just checking if Skype works.
Yes, thank you. It does work. We're good.
Well, what's on your mind? What have you been playing lately?
Not much, really. I have been playing mostly Team Fortress 2 on Steam and Forza 4.
Forza 4?
Yeah.
Forza, that's a series I never really got into because it's a little too pro for me,
but what do you like about Forza 4?
Forza, pretty much, it's pretty much like Gran Turismo in the simulation sense.
It's very precise, and when you have to accelerate turns and all that, it's like driving a real car.
But the thing that Forza has as a series is that it has an arcade feel rather than a simulation feel.
Are you a car guy in real life? Do you like to mod cars and kind of pimp your ride and all that?
Somewhat. I do like cars, though I don't know that much to mod or modify cars like that,
but I am a car aficionado in real life, so I do know some stuff.
Okay, so yeah, I just kind of notice usually the people that get into these games are car aficionados,
and there's nothing wrong with that. Cars can be very sexy machines, even I recognize that.
I don't necessarily drive a state-of-the-art car, but I even parked next to a guy today.
I'm like, that's a sexy car. If I had more money, I'd want that car.
But yeah, something that Forza has, it doesn't feel like a simulation at all.
You have all the customization, you can paint your car, you can tune it out,
and you can pretty much do everything with your car, and it also drives like a real car.
But like I said, the moment you're playing the game, it doesn't feel like a simulation.
It doesn't feel like Gran Turismo, where the races are hard because you have to make very precise turns and all that.
And even though you have, but like I said, you have a lot of options that make it feel like an arcade racer rather than a simulation.
I was going to say, are you a fan of arcade racers, like the split seconds, the blurs, the burnouts of the world?
Yeah, I'm a fan of both types of games, really, though I do mostly play arcade racers like Ridge Racer, the Dirt series, and all that.
Then tell me, am I right or am I right? F-Zero needs to be a Wii U launch title.
Oh yeah, it does.
Thank you very much. That's another series I need Nintendo to bring back from the dead.
Although, speaking of series coming back from the dead, don't forget Kid Icarus came out this week,
and I've got it sitting in a box in my room, I haven't been able to play it yet, I've been kind of busy this weekend.
Yeah, I've been hearing that, that's pretty good.
I'm hearing, I was talking to Shane earlier about it, and he says the game's got a great sense of humor, he says he's reminded of Earthbound in the sense of humor,
and I'm like, ooh, that's a big name to invoke around Nintendo.
But that's pretty cool if it's got that sense of humor to it.
Alright, well anything else you want to share with our listeners tonight?
No, that will be all.
Alright, well take care buddy, have a good one.
You too, thanks.
Bye.
I should have asked if he was into Mario Kart too, because Mario Kart's kind of a racer that's a little bit toned down so everybody can get into it.
You know what I played randomly not that long ago was Mario Kart on the Wii again, I hadn't played that in forever, but it's still alright.
One other tweet here from Tigerclaw at Twitter.com slash O-L-R, where you guys can send us tweets every week.
Scammers attempt to trick fans with promise of new Mass Effect 3 endings.
Oh, this is terrible. God, there's always scammers that read the gaming sites and seem to figure out what's going on.
Like, you see this with Blizzard all the time.
Like, how Mists of Pandaria Beta just came out this week, which, funny enough, I can't believe I didn't bring it up on the show.
Maybe because there's, you know, Horde House, the whole other show I have for that stuff.
But yeah, the Mists of Pandaria Beta just started out of the fucking blue this week, which is a pretty big deal.
But of course, scammers want to get in on that and try to rip off, you know,
Congratulations, you're in the Mists of Pandaria Beta. Click here to give us all your information so you can download the client, like your credit card number.
And some people, unfortunately, fall for it.
Well, it's happening with the Mass Effect 3 ending stuff.
I'll come back to the story in a minute, but we have another call coming in.
Hi, you're on Orange Lawns Radio, who's this?
Hey, hey, it's Ranma.
Hey, Ranma, what's up?
Not too much, not too much. How about you, good friend?
Same old, same old. Just working, sleeping, playing Mass Effect.
Uh-huh, Mass Effect, I see that.
Yeah, what's on your mind?
Not too much, I was pondering to call and see if you have played Kid Icarus yet,
Because I'm more or less waiting on your review of the game before I go out and buy it,
But from the last call, you haven't popped it open yet, so I'm kind of anxious about it.
Oh, god, I will have a review next week, I promise.
I did buy it, I took a leap of faith and bought it.
I got it on Amazon, which is kind of funny, because I ended up getting, like, it was $39.99, right?
They refunded me ten bucks, because I guess Best Buy or somebody else put it out cheaper,
So they have that whole, if it comes out cheaper somewhere else, we'll refund your money.
So I thought that was kind of interesting.
That would kind of explain why I could not find it in Best Buy the last couple of days,
Because I just decided to walk in and check, just out of idle curiosity, nope, didn't have it.
Well, that means it's selling, which I guess is a good sign.
I would like for the series to come back.
I'm hoping the game doesn't suck, but the general consensus I'm reading on the internet is that the game is pretty damn good,
But the controls are so bad, it ruins it for some people.
Like, there's a reason the game came with the little stand.
That's kind of the general consensus I'm hearing, which is a little bit alarming.
If the controls are that bad, it's going to ruin the game.
But it's good enough to further explore the concept, is kind of what I'm getting.
Ah, okay, I get it. I get it now.
There's also the 3D re-release of the original Kid Icarus.
Apparently, it's not just the ROM.
I mean, this isn't a huge deal, but they went and added backgrounds, I guess, into it.
So they did kind of give it a little something, something they didn't have before.
That sounds interesting, because I'm kind of reminded of the times I used to sit there and play the Kid Icarus game for Game Boy.
Oh yeah, the kind of overlooked sequel that really did come out, yeah.
You know, I was reading some people hating on Kid Icarus this week, because they were saying it wasn't that good of a game.
And, oh god, that makes my heart hurt every time I read it, because I loved it.
But it was a hard-as-nails game.
It was a really hard game, and it did have some weird, quirky stuff in it.
But, and it tried to do a lot.
Like, I think they kind of stretched themselves thin with, suddenly, it's a vertical scroller.
Now, it's a side scroller. Now, it's a dungeon crawler. Now, it's a shooter.
You know what I mean?
That's a bit of a mindfuck if you think about it.
It is, but, I mean, for a child who was, you know, 8 years old with mild ADD, it was great.
Pretty much.
Maybe that's why it holds my attention so well.
Since we're on the topic of 3DS games, I'll make this quick before I bounce off.
I finally got around to playing Super Mario 3D Land.
Ooh, what'd you think?
Okay, I kept saying that I want a 3D version of Super Mario 3.
That's what I've been screaming for.
And this game pretty much comes close to my inner Super Mario 3 fandom.
It comes close.
It's really good.
I really think people don't give it enough credit for what it's doing to the franchise as a whole.
I think it's really good.
I mean, one of my main issues with the game is that all the levels are straightforward.
I thought maybe you'd be able to go to 1-1 and 1-2.
You could just go down another direction, go to 1-4, this and that.
Oh, like in Mario 64, kind of?
No, more like for the way it was in the original Mario 3.
Oh, I got you. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Have you finished the game yet or no?
I've fake finished it.
I don't want to say too much for spoiler reasons.
Okay.
Let me put it this way. It's got a Symphony of the Night-esque thing going on.
Yeah, I know.
I'm playing through the game.
In the back of my mind, I'm like, I can't believe I'm going through the levels the way I am.
It's like the difficulty kind of jumps around.
And then at that last section, I thought it was done and then this whole more of it pops up.
I'm like, Nintendo, what the fuck?
Exactly.
What the fuck?
Yeah, right.
But that's great.
That's great.
It's not often that games kind of invoke that feeling that you got when you realized,
oh my God, Symphony of the Night, I'm not even halfway done.
That's awesome.
That's all I got to say is just...
Well, good luck.
And you know, if you do well enough, you might get to be Black Luigi playing Luigi.
I've already gotten to that part.
Okay.
I like how they redid Luigi. I like that.
It's more playable.
All right. Anything else before we let you go tonight?
No, that's it.
All right. Take care, buddy.
You too.
Bye.
Agdeft in our chat room says, Rob, it's a Mario game.
Do we really need spoiler alerts for it?
Well, look, I'm just trying to be nice.
All right.
We have another call coming in.
Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
Who's this?
This is Shane.
Hey, you've been calling a lot lately.
What's up?
I know, because I stay up later for some reason, which is probably why I fail at work more
often than not.
It's all good.
This show's important, damn it.
Totally.
What's on your mind?
Well, I will say, first of all, this week I won't talk about Mass Effect, because I'm
pretty sick of both fanatics on each side, and it's just disgusting me at this point.
But I will call and talk about Kid Icarus.
Ah, that's what our last caller wanted to know about.
What do you think about Kid Icarus?
It's fantastic.
The way they pace the game with the terrible control scheme, because let's just be honest,
if a game makes you hurt your hands while playing on purpose, it's got a terrible control
scheme.
But the writing is so good, and I think the Earthbound comparison that I gave to you earlier
is spot on, because it's witty, it's stupidly cheesy, it makes terrible puns, and it breaks
the fourth wall constantly.
That's pretty cool.
Maybe that's because Nintendo is, for whatever reason, and this makes me hurt to say, please
don't be mad at me, fanboys, but maybe since Nintendo's kind of abandoned the Mother franchise,
maybe they're bringing Kid Icarus in as kind of their, you know, silly.
Or do you think it's just because it's for four year olds?
I think it's because it's made by Sakurai, is why.
Anything?
Yeah.
Alright.
Well, he's got a great sense of humor, then, because...
To be fair, in the interest of full disclosure, you're a big fan of Power Rangers and Pokemon.
Yes.
So, maybe the game's aimed at children.
I don't know, when one of the lines is, it's like a birthday party where everybody's trying
to kill me, I don't feel like that's really Pokemon.
Hey, Shane.
Yes.
Quick spoiler, because I forgot to talk about this last week during the segment that doesn't
exist.
Which game are you spoiling?
Oh, real quick, I was just gonna say, hey, I bet you don't know that there's a Kinect
version of Power Rangers Samurai coming out later this year.
You mean the game I feel the urge to pre-order now?
Yes.
Because I will totally morph and punch things in the air.
That's awesome.
You know, I played the crap out of the Super Nintendo one.
Oh yeah, that was great.
That one was awesome.
That was a really good beat-em-up.
And there was a Die Ranger game that came out in Japan that I had the ROM for that I
played the hell out of.
I bet that was pretty good too.
It was really good.
The only one I was kind of disappointed in when I played it besides, you know, the newer
stuff they put out was the fighting game on Genesis.
Oh, that was painful.
Have you already pre-ordered Black and White 2?
I almost did from Playasia for the Japanese copies.
Our chat room flailed at the mention of Pokemon.
Pokemon!
Well yeah, because everybody should be excited about that.
And not to cross-promote shows or whatever, but I'm sure on Horthouse we'll talk about
this week, they datamined some of the pet battle stuff and it shows what's weak to what,
what's strong against what in some of the new attacks.
So Pokemon in World of Warcraft is just going to make my day.
That is pretty awesome, I gotta say.
It's both the dumbest thing I've ever heard and the most awesome thing I've ever heard.
It's like a movie that's so bad it's good.
Yeah pretty much, and I will be doing that all the time.
It's going to take away from leveling, which is kind of sad.
So gosh, what else do I ask you about?
So thank you for the plug for Horthouse, that's good, we always try to cross-promote the shows.
And Kid Icarus, so you think Kid Icarus, because Rama said he's waiting for my review to check
it out, but you're saying don't bother, just go get it, and you can play the game in ten
minute bursts, so that way when your hand starts wanting to die, you can take a break
and it's okay.
Yeah, and I really like the way they scale the difficulty for you.
There's no hard easy mode, there's this bar and you wager hearts, and by wagering hearts
you get better rewards, and the more hearts you wager, the harder the game gets.
So if you lose, you lose a whole bunch of hearts, but if you beat it, you get better
rewards, and the difficulty just skyrockets.
I almost died wagering to a 4.2 level difficulty, it was pretty hard.
Is the eggplant wizard in the game?
Yes, and that was one of my favorite puns in the entire game so far, and I'm gonna ruin
it because I don't care, because it was so good.
So there's lots of back and forth dialogue in the game, and it constantly happens, there's
no cutscene for it, it's just you're fighting and oh, Palutena and Pit have to talk the
entire time.
So she's like, oh, remember the eggplant wizard and the nurses, and it previously would heal
you?
And he was like, or Pit was like, yeah, I went there so often they named it after me,
and she's like, what?
And he's like, hospital, get it?
Hospital.
Oh my god, that is terrible.
Isn't it?
But it's just so funny when you're playing it, it's like, are you kidding me?
This is great.
And it's all voice acted, right?
Yeah, there's not any text.
Oh, there's text, but I mean, it's all dialogue voice stuff.
Yeah, I gotcha, I gotcha.
Or when you are scaling a wall in one of the flying stages, and there's enemies pouring
down on you, and you beat them all and you get to the top, Pit's like, yeah, take that
wall.
I'm like, that sounds like something I would say.
That is something you would say, actually, very much.
That also sounds like something Dan would say.
It does, it does.
Any online-ish components, StreetPass, SpotPass, any of that?
Yeah, it does have, I believe, an online multiplayer, a local multiplayer.
I haven't done them yet, because I'm only to world four or five, because I fell asleep.
And then went back to playing Mass Effect.
Yes, and then I went back to playing Mass Effect.
It sounds like, from everything I've read, the multiplayer is really fun, and a lot of
the sort of high-risk, high-reward stuff happens in that too, because if you take, I guess,
one of your better weapons into multiplayer, if you, when you take a good weapon in there,
you take, you have a lower health bar, so it expects, if you have a good weapon, you're
going to be a better player, and I think that's really cool, because if I'm going to have
a god weapon, I should only have a little bit of health, because I earned that weapon.
All right.
Well, we've got to let you go to wrap up the show, but quickly, I know you said you weren't
going to bring up Mass Effect, but I just have to ask one Mass Effect-related question.
Yes, game's hot.
Jack is the greatest character ever.
There you go, answer.
Yes or yes?
What?
Sorry, say it again.
Jack is the greatest character ever.
Yes or yes?
No.
Don't lie to listeners.
But I do like Jack better in two.
I mean, three.
Don't lie to listeners.
All right.
All right, have a good one.
Shane.
You too.
All right, bye.
Bye.
That'll do it for the Skype line tonight.
Thanks to those guys that got through.
It was a little slow to begin, but then it started to fill up there at the end, so don't
be shy next week.
You guys can get through.
I've heard from some of my favorite people today.
Oh?
On the Skype.
Oh, on the Skype line, yeah.
Oh, I thought you were-
I'm especially...
I'm pleased slash angry with Shane, because of all of the music that I got in trouble
for buying on Amazon after being in a turntable with him.
Oh, you guys turntabling this week?
We did two nights ago.
Nice.
Yeah.
I don't remember because I can't remember anything, but I got in trouble for all those
music I downloaded.
I have good music, yay, but I'm poor boo.
There is an unofficial official turntable FM after party for Orange Launch Radio that
Hitstun puts together, so it's kind of one of those.
We endorse it.
It's not us doing it, but we endorse it.
I love turntable FM.
It's a great site.
It's one of the greatest things to happen to music in a long time since iTunes.
All right, anyhow, I want to quickly say I never finished up the tweet from earlier that
TigerClaw sent us, the whole scamming thing.
The new scam is Mass Effect 3, and there is a spam email going out, and I can't believe
people are falling for this, but unfortunately it's working.
You download a zip file containing a password-protected downloader for the supposed new ending, and
a text file in the zip tells you to go to a website where you do offers to get the ending.
I mean, this is shady as hell, right?
So don't fall for this stuff.
And then I'm sure the executable is a virus.
If something legit happens, it will be all over the internet.
We'll not only report on it here on the show, but if you can't wait until Sunday, just seriously.
The Mass Effect 3 stuff has been so big.
I don't know.
That sounds kind of legit to me.
I see stories on my news.google.com.
I used to kind of get the aggregate news a lot, and Mass Effect 3 is always in the technology
stories.
Anyhow, that's it.
That's it for calls.
That's it for tweets, and I think that's it for another episode of OLR.
Quickly, though, before we wrap it up and say good night, I need to ask if there's any
last-minute stories.
Dark Soccer, Loki, any last-minute stories you want to get out tonight?
No.
Nothing I want to get out.
Do you have a day on chat that says it's happening for the Guild Wars 2 beta, too?
That's unfortunate.
I really wish I was getting in that beta.
Well, maybe you'll get your zip file executable, and then you can download the password from
a website.
Stop.
All right.
Then let's go around and get everybody's final thought.
Dark Soccer, what's your final thought for the listeners tonight?
I want pizza.
Wait, we can't do final thoughts.
You know what?
We skipped something.
What?
We never did the FUs of the Week.
Fuck.
I'm just not angsty, Rob.
Well you can do a thank you, or bless you, or whatever you call it.
Actually, I do have a fuck you.
To the guy who is setting up the booth outside of Walmart that said get rid of Obama, vote
Republican, with a very poorly handwritten sign, first of all.
If you want to draw the right attention, you need a better designed sign, just saying.
Two, don't vote in Satan to get rid of a guy who's doing good, just saying, even if you
don't like him.
Don't vote in the devil, because, seriously, they're all evil, evil, evil, evil.
And a fuck you to my stomach for rumbling, I'm going to have to put some more tea in
you when I get home.
I like fasting.
I really do feel great, except I'm hungry.
That's it.
Logie?
Um, I guess, uh, I have to be tired, because I've had to work hard the last few days because
I've had to watch Josh instead of going to work and give me at least a lunch break.
My a few of the week goes to internet drama, because it's very, very serious.
The internet's serious business.
It is serious business, and our lives depend on internet drama.
Porkchop in our chat says orange launch radio is linked to aggressive and violent hosts.
Possibly.
All right, uh, last minute, or excuse me, now our final thoughts, because we did last
minute stories.
Final thoughts.
So Darkstalker, you get another go at it.
What's your final thought?
Tea.
Uh, my final thought of the night is broccoli beef.
Logie, your final thought tonight?
Uh, there are a lot of good projects on Kickstarter, so be sure to check out Kickstarter, but there
are a lot that seem, you just have to look at it and how professionally it's being approached
and stuff, and some of them are quite sickening to the amount of money that they raised for
what they've raised it for and for how long those certain things were going for prior
to putting a Kickstarter up, if you know what I mean.
I think that's as vague as I can get.
All right, and, uh, let's see, my final thought tonight, oh no, I did my final thought.
Hello.
Sorry, I got distracted by chat.
But I will say this, this is the segment I always say at the end of every show, it's
the final final thought from all of us.
If you like Orange Launch Radio, please tell a friend or two or five about the show, leave
us a nice review somewhere, spread the word of Orange Launch Radio.
You know, we do this show commercial free because we love the community, that's what
it's all about, so all we ask in exchange, help our community grow.
I've seen a lot of you guys give us links on your blogs, that's awesome, I've seen little
signatures on sites, somebody inevitably on every forum ever starts a what podcast do
you listen to thread, and people kind of say, I listen to OLR, and that's awesome, we appreciate
all of that.
So please, please help spread the word about Orange Launch Radio.
That's it for tonight, guys, we'll be back to do it all again next week, right?
It's a new month, it's going to be April next week, so crazy, crazy.
And remember, portal gun for me for my birthday, just saying.
Yeah, that's right.
Dark Stalker's birthday is in April, so what can I say, it's going to be a crazy month,
so we'll see you next week to do it all again here at Orange Launch Radio, have a great
week, be safe.
You've been listening to Orange Launch Radio.
Orange Launch Radio is an Orange Launch production.
To join us for a live show, visit www.allgames.com, Sunday nights at 6 p.m. Pacific time.
The views and opinions expressed on Orange Launch Radio do not necessarily reflect those
of the entire staff of Orange Launch Radio or allgames.com, but we're probably right
anyway.
See you next week!