[SPEAKER_06]: Tonight, March 11th, 2012, a new iPad claims to do something Xbox and PlayStation can't.
[SPEAKER_06]: One UK retailer is in financial trouble, and could the next Xbox be disk drive free?
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello my friends out there on the internet and welcome back to another week of the show where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: We are live with episode number 449 of our show for this March 11th of 2012.
[SPEAKER_02]: My name is Rob Roberts and I'll be joining you over the next few hours with my co-host.
[SPEAKER_02]: Say hello to DarkSakura or Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_02]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_11]: Full.
[SPEAKER_02]: Full, full of orange chicken I see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: One of my weaknesses.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because my DNA compelled me to eat it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Panda Express is like Starbucks around here.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a crack.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a place like, there's literally, you can go to a mall and there's Panda Express in the food court and then right next door in the other mall is another Panda Express.
[SPEAKER_10]: And they're all next door to Starbucks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's how it works around here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, also say hello to, you know he loves his food too, say hello to Tech Master Loki!
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_02]: How you doing, Loki?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm doing good.
[SPEAKER_02]: You went pretty basic with your food choice tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: You went to the McDonald's.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it was because I just, there's not, like I said, there's not a lot here to, or from my house to, you know, your apartment, so.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: And there's like, like a ton of McDonald's, a Taco Bell, and...
[SPEAKER_04]: That's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, this part of town is really sad when it comes to food.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, I mean, unless I pull off the freeway mid-trip, there wasn't really much for me to have.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was going to go to Quiznos, but I was like, I had Quiznos yesterday.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had pizza yesterday, so I was like, I'll just have McDonald's.
[SPEAKER_04]: It won't be that bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was actually pretty terrible, but it's all right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've been not eating McDonald's, so, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Burger King is the way to go.
[SPEAKER_02]: At least our food is palatable.
[SPEAKER_02]: and again 6 Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern and join us live in our chat room at chat.orangeloungeradio.com where some of the chatters are not too happy about us bringing up food Uni starts us off tonight saying OMG dang you for mentioning Panda I want it now lol and they don't even pay us for these ads these free ads that we're giving away here on the show we need to put the clamp down on that alright no more freebies meh
[SPEAKER_02]: I love my food from Redacted.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: So yeah, I finally started playing it, and while I'll save my opinions for a little bit here... I think it was the same year as Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_04]: Was it really?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, within a week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I figure they come out about every other year, except for, I think, Mass Effect 2 originally had been bumped back.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, it was a January release, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_04]: PS3 it was, because that came out a year later, I think.
[SPEAKER_02]: I could have sworn that when Mass Effect 2 came out, it was really early in the year because when it got a lot of Game of the Year awards, people were like, that came out this year?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yeah, it came out like right after Christmas.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, but anyway, this isn't about necessarily just the timing of things, but what I really wanted to ask was, has there ever been a game that just, it seemed like you missed the boat on it for so long, it just took you so long to get into it, and years later, here you are finally playing it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Have you ever had a game like that where it took you like five years to get into it?
[SPEAKER_02]: I really can't think of very many because I really can't play a lot of console stuff anymore.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yeah, because of your hand and stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: I played Mario Kart 7 for the first time yesterday.
[SPEAKER_10]: It didn't make me throw up.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, that's good.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought I let you play Mario Kart 7 when I got it.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_10]: I played Loki's Ridge Racer.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was it, and it made me sick.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, it's too bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, anything you can think of that was a little bit delayed for you?
[SPEAKER_04]: Call of Duty Modern Warfare.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's true, you've just been talking about the first game not that long ago, huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, we're gonna be going to three pretty soon, I think.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I asked them, like, hey, you guys wanna do number two?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, if we're gonna move to another game, we're gonna go to the latest one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not Black Ops or anything, because...
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not really into the Cold War stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're more into the Modern Warfare stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: probably five games were new that's a man I wish that was a goal I could realistically accomplish but I never beat games I really should force myself to but there's just there's so much other stuff I have to tackle that I wouldn't want to give myself a goal like that that's that's a lot that's up there with reading a hundred books in a year or something like that BlackWolf in chat says Beatmania 2DX I think I can think of one for you DarkSakra World of Warcraft
[SPEAKER_10]: I played it right at the beginning, though, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, that's right, you did.
[SPEAKER_10]: Remember, I had a vanilla account.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I forgot about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_02]: TheRobD says, playing new games is overrated.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, it's usually a lot cheaper if you wait, that's for sure.
[SPEAKER_02]: I finally beat every single puzzle in Best Move for iOS.
[SPEAKER_10]: and um it was pretty epic now I want them to release some more so that I can get more puzzles um I started another game called Star Mine that I bought on name alone and it's actually a pretty fun little puzzle game it's like a block sliding kind of game and then um I played some while on Sonic CD all right yeah there you go Loki
[SPEAKER_04]: I played just a few games this week other than Call of Duty.
[SPEAKER_04]: Played a little bit of the new Vita game, Motorstorm RC, which is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a little different than a regular Motorstorm game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's more like a Super Sprint or Ivan Ironman, Stewards, Super Offroad type thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: and I've been playing that a bit and one of the things I was trying to do was beat because they have ghost data that you race basically in the game and so I was trying to beat that stuff and I was pretty happy that I was able to beat the ghost data that was in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: well it's not terrible but hey it's free so I guess you can't complain um
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's a little frustrating.
[SPEAKER_04]: Unfortunately, I kind of ran the same thing with some of the other Ghost Data that I raced where I beat it and find out that, oh, look, I'm still ranked 3,000.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even though, oh, there's times they're faster than mine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, then why wasn't that the Ghost Data that I was racing?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just all really weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, you know, I complained to, of course, got to complain to them, Bill.
[SPEAKER_04]: Listen, bitch, I know this shit was free.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you say in an angry tweet?
[SPEAKER_04]: I did say in an angry tweet to...
[SPEAKER_02]: at PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why are your games broken?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, no, see, you would think it's at PlayStation, but no, it's at MotorStormRC.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have their own fucking Twitter account, and I'm like, what the fuck?
[SPEAKER_04]: You can't beat this goddamn ghost lap because it only does three of the four laps.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're aware of the issue.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're working on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I kind of did something similar this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: I sent a tweet.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is serious, not a joke.
[SPEAKER_02]: I sent a tweet to Awake NBC and I sent a tweet that said, please don't get cancelled.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I like the show and apparently not a lot of people are watching it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I sent them a tweet and I said, please don't get cancelled.
[SPEAKER_02]: They didn't reply to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe they've already been cancelled.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: I played a little bit of that.
[SPEAKER_04]: A couple of things that are a little frustrating with me.
[SPEAKER_04]: The camera is really annoying.
[SPEAKER_04]: I really wish this game was a first person driving game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I understand maybe the camera is top down because one, it's an RC game.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's fine, but I've played other RC games that were first person or at least behind the car type thing, not this
[SPEAKER_04]: I had to figure it out from the top of the track.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is this going to be about your love of Excite Truck again?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it's not going to be about Excite Truck.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, there was a racing game that was on, I think it was Revolt, was actually on the PlayStation 2 or PlayStation 1.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was actually pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was an RC game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just, it's a little frustrating though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like when you're racing, it's hard to see some of the track, get the really mess of the camera to, you know, get it just right.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then of course they have cars you can buy, which...
[SPEAKER_04]: as far as I'm aware they don't have stats on those cars so I don't know what any of these other cars that I'm unlocking do other than different types and assuming the different types handle differently but as far as different cars within the same type I think it's just the way they look um I did download the free cake car that you can it's a cake slice car um
[SPEAKER_04]: So that was free.
[SPEAKER_04]: What else?
[SPEAKER_04]: I played Luminous on the Vita as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: I went through and I decided, hey, I'm going to beat all the leaderboards on here, at least within my friends.
[SPEAKER_04]: And so I did that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I beat all the leaderboards and last I checked and I was on top of all of them.
[SPEAKER_04]: except for obviously uh some of the higher uh master class stuff because I haven't beat the master thing yet that's like really frustrating just trying to get all the trophies for that game um oh and ranked up to 50 because for some reason when I play Luminous it's actually when they start doing the world cube thing and you level up like 30 levels just by checking it once I still can't
[SPEAKER_02]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: 8 or 9 p.m.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pacific
[SPEAKER_04]: And of course, with the time change and everything, it might be 7 to 8 p.m.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pacific.
[SPEAKER_04]: So yeah, that's pretty much all I played.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: My Gaming Week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let me talk about a few things I've been playing this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: There have been a few things.
[SPEAKER_02]: Obviously, first off is Mass Effect.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I haven't played it enough.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, A, do you really want me to review a five-year-old game?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think...
[SPEAKER_02]: I think most of you probably know how you feel, but since I did see somebody earlier had said they haven't played it and DarkSakura hasn't played it, I'll just quickly say, well, I haven't played enough to give you a full review, but I'll tell you this much.
[SPEAKER_02]: I am way less annoyed by the combat than I thought I would be.
[SPEAKER_02]: because I know Mass Effect is very much about like use cover and hide behind things and get things and that's like why I could not play Gears of War and it's not that I think Gears of War is a bad game it's not it's a good game but I that whole like cover thing like no I want fucking Quake or Unreal where you run out there guns a-blazing that's more my kind of shooter so I thought the cover thing would really bother me but it's it's not and I think
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's be real, I think a lot of that is because I'm playing on easy.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I think my squad mates really pick up the slack for me, which is totally fine by me because I'm really more playing for the story.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I did find through playing Star Wars The Old Republic and a little bit of Dragon Age, I do like Bioware's whole little conversational style.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I really do see where the game can...
[SPEAKER_02]: Damn well be two completely separate games depending on how you are playing it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I kind of like that, that it can go in the different directions.
[SPEAKER_02]: But little annoyances I have so far.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some of the interface is just kind of crappy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now I hear that they fixed a lot of those issues in 2 and 3, so I'm not going to really harp on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But let me just say, I really value the one button maps.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's all I'm going to say.
[SPEAKER_02]: but those are kind of nitpicking otherwise what I think especially for five years ago was graphically a good game and you know um pretty I guess ahead of its time in some ways but um I'll let you know how things progress after I actually play more of it because if I told you where I was right now you'd be like oh Rob you barely touched the damn game um a couple other things I've played um
[SPEAKER_02]: Rune Spell Overture.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't remember if I talked about this game before on the show, but it's a game I bought in one of those indie bundle collections that I got a key for on Steam, and maybe I played it a little bit back when I first got it, and I might have mentioned it in passing on the show, but I played it more in depth this week, and...
[SPEAKER_02]: For those that don't know it, I would say it's a little bit Puzzle Quest 2-ish meets a solitaire slash poker hybrid.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I know that sounds really weird, but the way you battle enemies is that you kind of have a solitaire-ish hand, and then they have one, and you form poker hands by moving your cards around.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it doesn't follow the rules of Solitaire.
[SPEAKER_02]: It doesn't have to be red on black or any of that stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, you can take their cards too and move them up into your hand and you're trying to form like the best poker hands.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, you know, five of a kind would be the best one, which is more of a Yahtzee, but you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, and I, you kind of battle that way, but on top of that, you have spells, which felt a little more like puzzle quests because you can kind of activate those based on the power that you've generated.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, um,
[SPEAKER_02]: Pretty cool little time killer puzzle game and I imagine it's super cheap.
[SPEAKER_02]: I bought it in a bundle so I bought it when it was a very, very reasonable price.
[SPEAKER_02]: Soundtrack's good too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let me throw that out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pretty deep story.
[SPEAKER_02]: No voice acting but some dialogue questions and it definitely seems like there's a fleshed out story that I'm not far enough in to really appreciate yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: A couple other things I've been playing this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Journey
[SPEAKER_02]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know where to put... Journey is definitely more like a platformer, but don't think of it like a platformer.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm being very careful and choosing my words carefully here because I think Journey is best experienced not knowing anything about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I will tell you this, I sat down and played Journey.
[SPEAKER_02]: It doesn't tell you anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's no dialogue.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's no, you know, do this or you need to go here or arrow or any help.
[SPEAKER_02]: There is one little, you know, the little controller will show up and it will say, you know, A is jump.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like once in a while it'll kind of pop up.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you're kind of left to your own devices to figure out what the heck's going on.
[SPEAKER_02]: and it's a game that's told really through its soundtrack in a way like I just I found the soundtrack to be amazing and really moving and then there's a twist to it there's a reason why it's called Journey and some of you probably know but I don't want to ruin it for you if you don't already know the band pops out and starts playing you on your way therefore it's part of the soundtrack I wish, I wish that would make it even more awesome but there's a twist
[SPEAKER_02]: And when it happened, I was like, wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_02]: What the... Do you know what I'm talking about, Loki?
[SPEAKER_02]: Have you read about this game at all?
[SPEAKER_02]: I've read about the game, but... I'm trying very hard not to ruin it for the listeners.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll have to tell you during the break or something, but there's a little twist to it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And...
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't realize what was happening as it was happening.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I was kind of like, this is so... How do I explain it?
[SPEAKER_02]: As it was happening, I was kind of like, I didn't...
[SPEAKER_02]: Realize what it really was at first, and then it kind of hit me, like, oh my gosh, this is this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I know what you're talking about now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I know what you're talking about.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you really?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, but there, yeah, but you know, like, it's, and then suddenly when you figure it out, you're like, oh my god, I had no idea that this was part of the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then, again, I said there's no dialogue, and there's not a lot to it.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're finding all these interesting ways you've never thought about before to now play this game.
[SPEAKER_11]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_02]: and it can go a variety of directions it can go a very customary direction or it can go in a direction where I never saw this twist happen I'm just gonna ignore it I don't give an F I'm gonna go do this what I was doing before and the game still kind of works in both ways now
[SPEAKER_02]: The one thing I will say about it is that it's short.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like two or three hours tops.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's a $15 game.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that may not sit well with people.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which is fair because we've been taught to know that games like that usually shouldn't cost that much money.
[SPEAKER_02]: but I do think it's a it's a really good two three hour experience and there is some replay value in it I can see again there's several different ways to approach the game and um yeah I would recommend it but I think that play time is going to really scare some people off but and I think a lot of people are saying this this game is very much the games are art in motion
[SPEAKER_02]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wouldn't necessarily say, well, Roger Ebert needs to play this game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think he could appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But as somebody who's had some pretty miserable experiences on Xbox Live and had to put up with trolling in World of Warcraft and so forth, the experience that this game brought was really organic and neat.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess that's really all I can say about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Again, some of you know darn well what I'm talking about and you're just like, just say it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I'm telling you, there's a reason why I'm not telling you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I don't want you to be spoiled on that and seriously avoid reviews.
[SPEAKER_02]: The value of the game will be so much more if you know nothing about it going in.
[SPEAKER_02]: Trust me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't spoil it for yourself.
[SPEAKER_02]: You might figure it out right away.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know, that's all I'm going to say.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let me move on.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually had one more game I was playing.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is one I'm going to pick up this week, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wanted to pick that up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're welcome to test it out here if you want to see if it's worth 15 bucks or not.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know, because...
[SPEAKER_02]: you know it's again it's a pretty basic platformer the visuals are not I think it's a very beautiful game but some people are going to go it's all desert it's just the desert desert desert but there's some very beautiful things they do like there's one level where you're kind of it's almost like a race like you're falling down a hill and you're kind of like you know having to move like it's almost like hydro thunder or something and it's like you're falling through the desert as the sun is setting it's really gorgeous so I forgot that I had one more game you have one more game you want to add that's fine because I'm done what did you want to add
[SPEAKER_10]: I was playing Doctor Who The Mazes of Time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is that actually good?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's pretty good so far.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is that an iPhone game?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, you play as the Doctor and Amy and you have to, it's basically one person does one part of the puzzle and maybe has to stand on something so that it activates another part of the puzzle and then you have to figure out how to get both of them through the maze.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it's just a fun little, it's a dollar right now so get it.
[SPEAKER_02]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's talk about some housekeeping before we get into news.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually have something tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: And this is something I'm going to surprise DarkSakura and Loki with on air.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because aren't on-air surprises the best?
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, Lord.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, so let me tell you about this.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got a package in the mail this week from our buddy Brad at PodCulture.
[SPEAKER_02]: And this is the package that we got.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I had no idea what it was.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cardboard!
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, it's cardboard, but there's something inside this cardboard I think you should see.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you, Jamie, I think are really going to appreciate this.
[SPEAKER_02]: You ready?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, so here's what was sent to us.
[SPEAKER_02]: And listeners, this can impact you as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: These are vinyl decals of the Orange Lounge Radio album art.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's one for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's one for Matt.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, here's the cool thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wouldn't take that off because once you do, you're going to have to stick it on something.
[SPEAKER_10]: I check the ink on everything.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're a nerd like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have some extra decals here, and I'm sure we'll give those away at some point, except I want to keep one for myself.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's some other ones in here.
[SPEAKER_02]: These are hard to see, but hold them up to the light, and you can see.
[SPEAKER_02]: These are like the white silhouette ones that you see on the backs of cars.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but like the artist here took kind of like the art and did that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I really like the way that looks.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_02]: assuming that Loki and DarkSakura like this the guy is gonna I think we're gonna try he's offered to sell the stickers on his site so you guys can get them too of course you know they're not free guys it does cost money to make but I know the guy will be reasonable about the price I wouldn't mention it here on the show if I didn't think that and it's you know Brad from PogCulture is our buddy and of course I didn't put the name of the site here in front of me but I have the letter here it is
[SPEAKER_02]: DecalMike.com There it is, DecalMike.com and we're going to see what we can do to get that added to the store so you guys can check that out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now the listeners are demanding pictures.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think that... It's going to be hard to take a picture of.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm like, you have to remember it's a vinyl decal of the Orange Lounge Radio album art.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if you've seen the podcast... With Flash it could work.
[SPEAKER_02]: You already know what it looks like but they're like little stickers and they're about the size... How big would you say that is?
[SPEAKER_02]: The size of your phone.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's about the size of an iPhone but a little bit more square.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think it's a 3x3 or 3.5x3.5.
[SPEAKER_02]: So those of you guys that have been asking for OLR merchandise, because you know it's been how many years we still don't have a t-shirt, I think we'll be able to jump on this.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I want to say thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you to our buddy Brad at PodCulture, and of course Decal Mike for the hard work there.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Brad from PodCulture is the one that essentially, I guess for lack of a better term, fronted the money, I guess for that, or kicked around the idea to get that started.
[SPEAKER_02]: So props to him.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it's probably not going to show up very well.
[SPEAKER_02]: The iPhone will not do it justice, but, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if you're a fan of Airwolf or, you know, Back to the Future, there's also decals on Decal Mike's site as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_02]: I have to be honest.
[SPEAKER_02]: I haven't had a chance to browse the site yet, but he has some other stuff too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, there's stuff like from Airwolf.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's World of Warcrack.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's the Thundercat Sword, the Stargate SGC decal.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's all the shows that Brad talks about on his show.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not surprised at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, there's some...
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, there's, you know, it's hard to interrupt this.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's, you know, the pod culture stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, his other shows.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Type 40, Geekspin, and, you know, a lot of stuff from Occupy Wall Street.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's the Guy Fawkes mask.
[SPEAKER_04]: Adalic.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loves it!
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm putting up a few pictures.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks again, you guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: And listeners, if you want to get these stickers, I have to do some... They're not there yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have to do some DMs and all that stuff on Twitter and get that all arranged, but they should be up.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll remind you guys next week about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: My 3DS friends are asking for 3D pictures.
[SPEAKER_02]: You guys, it's a window decal.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're not in 3D.
[SPEAKER_02]: 3D is not going to do it justice.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now let's get into some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_02]: Less about us, more about the video games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there was a brief little web stream thing for the PlayStation Vita.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was hoping for a lot more US titles, but unfortunately they're all Japanese titles.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it doesn't necessarily mean that this stuff won't be coming out over here or in other territories other than Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: But as of right now, it's just all Japanese titles.
[SPEAKER_04]: So starting off, one of the titles that got announced was Phantasy Star Online 2 is coming to the Vita with PC cross-play.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you're going to be able to play against people that have the PC version as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there you go, your first MMO on the Vita.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not really sure how the online's handled, but hell, if anything, the old PlayStation, or not PlayStation, the old...
[SPEAKER_04]: Sega Dreamcast, Phantasy Star Online was able to work over dial-up, so Phantasy Star Online 2 working over 3G, maybe?
[SPEAKER_04]: Be kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: No word on when that's going to be coming out, probably later this year, but it's still pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: and then they also had a... I really hope this comes to America.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry, I don't mean to cut you off, but I really want this to come to America.
[SPEAKER_02]: I really liked... I'm probably the only person in the world that liked Phantasy Star Universe.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I know this is not PSU 2, this is PSO 2, and it's PSO 2 because PSU was not viewed as very good.
[SPEAKER_02]: But regardless, I'm a fan of this series and I hope that we are getting it in America because I was interested in it when they first announced the PC one.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like playing Phantasy Star Online offline.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well then you'd probably like those PSP games were just Phantasy Star Universe but offline.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, meh.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was the one where you could have the pizza box.
[SPEAKER_02]: Had some really weird tie-ins, remember that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, the Pizza Hut stuff, that was funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wasn't Colonel Sanders in there or something like that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it wouldn't surprise me because I think Pizza Hut, KFC, Taco Bell are like all the same people.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Brand Wars.
[SPEAKER_04]: Another RPG that's coming out as well on the Vita, Legend of Heroes, or Dragon Slayers, The Legend of Heroes.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's coming out on the Vita as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they also announced that Gundam Seed Battle Destiny will be coming out on the Vita.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's, I guess...
[SPEAKER_04]: The sixth game in the Gundam Battle series, of which I am not familiar with.
[SPEAKER_04]: I am assuming those were only Japanese releases.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not surprised.
[SPEAKER_04]: There was another one that was unannounced that was kind of like, oh, we're going to work with the fans to make this happen or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: It just reminded me too much of Mega Man Legends 3, so I just tuned that out.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yeah, unfortunately, no actual US titles or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: E3 E3 E3 E3
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I mean, and yeah, I mean, if you think about it, three months from launch, that's almost E3, so why not?
[SPEAKER_04]: And they've already, you know, kind of announced everything that's gonna be coming out, first party at least, up through the end of the second quarter, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: It would make sense that any of those other announcements are going to be at E3.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's probably going to be a little bit of a lull during the summer, but you're going to get a lot of fall games.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've got Resistance and Gravity Rush.
[SPEAKER_04]: In fact, Gravity Rush, that would be the June title.
[SPEAKER_04]: Resistance is going to be the May title.
[SPEAKER_04]: April, probably LittleBigPlanet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, now here's what I'm wondering, because this was a Twitter conversation I was in this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Somebody was asking when LittleBigPlanet was coming out, and I was like, well, supposedly it's April, but the box art isn't even finalized yet, and there's a lot that seems like it's still up in the air in the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, the game may be awesome, and I'm totally down with that if that's the case.
[SPEAKER_04]: Box art's finalized, just aside from the ESRB rating.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm really worried about them rushing it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just don't want a rushed game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think it's going to be rushed.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was thinking at this point it would get delayed to summer because we just haven't heard a lot about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, because this was your launch title.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's already been delayed.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think putting it out in March would have been kind of... I mean, it would have been alright, but I think it's good that they're spacing their titles out because they had two titles coming out in March and they're going to have one each month coming.
[SPEAKER_04]: Major titles coming out soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: At least there's a lot more releases than there were on the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I remember when the 3DS came out, the next month was pretty much... SpongeBob SquigglePants, there was... SpongeBob SquigglePants?
[SPEAKER_04]: SquigglePants, yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought it was SquarePants.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, SquigglePants.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is this his cousin?
[SPEAKER_04]: It was the one that was like WarioWare.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did he marry into the SquigglePants family?
[SPEAKER_04]: He must have.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, he changed his last name.
[SPEAKER_04]: I see.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I just remember that the releases were a lot slower, but...
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, it's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would like to see some other stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm hoping, because it's supposed to be a PlayStation Network title, I'm hoping that Retro City Rampage will be playable on the Vita, because that would be pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: It might be.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it doesn't have to push a lot of graphics.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, well, now that the Vita is out and they're talking about it, now our attention starts to shift towards the next batch of consoles that is the unknown.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be, of course, the Wii U, the PlayStation 4 someday, and the next Xbox, or whatever they're going to end up calling it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think they should do the Apple thing and just call it the Xbox all over again.
[SPEAKER_02]: The new Xbox.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's, like, so confusing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, seriously...
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we're going to get to it later in the show, so I'll talk about it then.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think it's as bad as people are making it out to be.
[SPEAKER_04]: I understand why they're doing it because of their other series of hardware devices.
[SPEAKER_02]: For anything, I bought a Corolla.
[SPEAKER_02]: or I bought a Xerox machine.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a lot of things that we don't necessarily address.
[SPEAKER_04]: Xerox machines have model numbers, Corollas, and different car manufacturers.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a 2012 Corolla or it's a 2011 Corolla.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know that, but people don't necessarily refer to it by that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: They can call the stupid new iPad.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what people are going to call it?
[SPEAKER_02]: You're having an argument we're supposed to be having in 30 minutes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you not get tonight's list?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, the next Xbox, the new Xbox Xbox Lube, Xbox I won't even call it that other number name because that's just a stupid name and I can't believe everybody always calls it that How about the X-Sphere?
[SPEAKER_04]: I hear the new system will be full of skateboarding games Yes, I was going to say the next Xbox Atari skateboarding game
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_02]: The big rumor going around this week about it, and what's interesting about this rumor is that we had a very similar rumor five weeks ago, and I seriously think everybody forgot, but we kind of already had this rumor.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it made the rounds again that the next Xbox won't have a disk drive.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, supposedly the code name is Durango, speaking of cars.
[SPEAKER_02]: But anyway, the next Xbox is supposed to not have a disk drive.
[SPEAKER_02]: um there's you know apparently it's leaked out even though there was big NDAs and all that and you know of course there's a way these things happen uh the next Xbox quote will offer the quote from MCV UK quote will offer compatibility with some sort of interchangeable solid state card storage although it is not known whether this will be proprietary or a more standard format such as SD so if I'm reading this correctly we've gone from cartridges to disc back to cartridge
[SPEAKER_02]: Right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Is what they're saying with the next Xbox.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's doing like a proprietary format like the Vita.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was basically for security because that thing was getting hacked to shit and publishers didn't want to make games for the system because they're afraid that it's going to get pirated.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, wouldn't that just be forward thinking on Microsoft's part that Blu-ray is going to get hacked to shit if it hasn't been already and they don't want to... A, it's...
[SPEAKER_02]: Sony's involved with Blu-ray, so why?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, of course, everybody's now crying.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the death of the used game market.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the death of retail.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the death.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because when you don't have a disc, therefore, there's nothing to interchange.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it is going to go belly up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although, why are people going here when we're talking about cartridges?
[SPEAKER_02]: This sounds like the Vita to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it'll probably be just like the Vita.
[SPEAKER_04]: It doesn't even matter.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's gonna have a drive of some sort.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're not gonna just get rid of physical discs.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's still gonna be disc-based.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that all these rumors are full of shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Where's their source?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, it's some guy that said he was under NDA.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I'm under NDA, and guess what?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a fucking robot.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a giant 50-foot tall robot.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the new system.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wasn't supposed to tell you because I was under NDA, but it's a giant 50-foot fucking tall robot.
[SPEAKER_10]: I used to be able to hear.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's a response to the Sony AIBO.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is a giant fucking robot.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was under NDA.
[SPEAKER_04]: You didn't hear it from me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Giant fucking robot.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, that is about how credible this is.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is so fucking stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've had all these... Because it's just feeding into the goddamn... It's just troll bait is all it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: or you can buy everything physical now whether the disc is going to be a blu-ray disc or it's going to be a cartridge or whatever it doesn't matter but there's going to be some physical part to it I don't think the cartridge idea is so far-fetched we know that those little memory cards those tiny tiny ass memory cards on the PlayStation Vita can hold up to 32 gigabytes and that Sony is charging way more than those cards are really worth
[SPEAKER_02]: So, you know, in a couple years' time, when the Xbox New is a reality, you could probably fit... How much can a Blu-ray hold right now?
[SPEAKER_02]: Is it 20 gigs?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like 50-some gigs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is it even... Oh, God, I thought it was less.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, because I was going to say, you could probably hold more on a card than you probably could... I mean, USB drives go higher.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're probably looking at something where you can hold more on a card than you can on a disc.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that even might be... And to be honest, I mean, that might be the reason why they're going that route is because...
[SPEAKER_04]: They're worried that they're going to run into the same problem they do with the DVD9 format where they're going to basically run out of disk space.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they're just thinking ahead saying, hey, maybe we shouldn't do this because we want to have some sort of support for whatever formats that are larger than this because we don't want to have to come out with a new console.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dungeon Buster in our chatroom says, Macrossbox.
[SPEAKER_10]: It transforms into a Valkyrie and flies away with your money
[SPEAKER_02]: that isn't on super high-speed internet or has that type of bandwidth a month.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think sometimes in our big urban areas, we live in a little bit of a bubble, those of us that live there, thinking everybody has that type of connection, but they don't.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can you imagine even, let's just say they do have a high-speed connection.
[SPEAKER_04]: Say we have a cable, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: Cable, it's pretty fast, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's not the time for digital only.
[SPEAKER_02]: that's not Microsoft's fucking problem nor is it something that Microsoft really I think has to concern themselves with because let's face it GameStops are going to end up like Blockbuster it's a matter of time
[SPEAKER_04]: But it just, the thing with, well, Blockbuster was a whole other problem.
[SPEAKER_04]: It wasn't necessarily that people weren't going to rent.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was just mismanaged.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I think people are still looking for physical stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, that's why Redbox is doing so well.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're still looking for discs.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just, you know, it's more convenient now to go to a kiosk versus a store.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I still think people are looking for discs.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, because they want to be able...
[SPEAKER_04]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I got to admit, if the new Xbox was announced as digital only, I would have a slight hesitation.
[SPEAKER_02]: At the end of the day, a system is only as good as the games that are on it, but I would want to know what's Microsoft... Clearly, Microsoft systems are not infallible to hacking, so how is my stuff going to be protected?
[SPEAKER_04]: and also on top of that I mean if they put out okay if Microsoft said we're gonna do only we're gonna do digital only and Sony said we're gonna do digital and disc people are gonna go with Sony they're gonna they're gonna buy a system that's gonna have physical media or medium but yeah I think though it's getting a lot more convenient to purchase digitally but it's not there's a lot of factors into just convenience and unfortunately the publishers are not quite understanding yet and
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's something to think about.
[SPEAKER_02]: I saw a great point to this on Twitter this week that I wouldn't have thought about right away, I must admit.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I thought it was just a great argument for why this is definitely a possibility that the next Xbox may not have any type of disc format at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: And even though everybody's rabble-rabbling about whether it would kill the used game market and da-da-da-da-da, if they got rid of the disc drive and da-da-da-da-da-da,
[SPEAKER_02]: Xbox wouldn't be the first person to do it in fact another company's done it another company's cut out the disk drive completely and they have the most popular fucking computer in the world right now that everybody wants who is it apple apple where's the disk drive on the ipad where is it how didn't they even release a laptop that specifically doesn't have a disk drive in it you have to have some type of like airport hub in your home and people are eating it up
[SPEAKER_02]: So if Xbox went this direction, they would not be the first.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, hold on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, you're comparing the average gamer with a hipster.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm sorry, it's just not going to work.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have to understand that people that buy Macs, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm not talking about iPods.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm talking about Macs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, Loki, I was listening to PlayStation before it was mainstream, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's all about...
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I like the brushed metal finish on this system.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's so sleek and wonderful.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I don't care if it has only one USB port.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't need those pesky USB ports.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, look, Loki, I only value the Atari 2600 with the wood paneling finishes on the side.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't bring me those little plastic refurbs because they're not the real deal.
[SPEAKER_10]: I had a four-controller system before any of you did.
[SPEAKER_04]: Listen, the only reason they took out the... I have two Atari 5200s.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_04]: The only reason they took out the disk drive is because they're like, we want to make the thinnest fucking laptop ever, and they did it, and then people are like, oh my god, it's so thin, I'm gonna buy it!
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, it's a fucking supermodel or something like that, and so they did.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then they're like, hey, I can't fucking install any software on it, and Apple's like, well, that's okay, because no software is really supported by our system anyway, so, oh well, you don't need to download anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: My Rob the Robot is 100% organic and gluten-free, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: I bought it at Whole Foods, thank you.
[SPEAKER_10]: To be honest, the Fairchild Channel app is totally underappreciated.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, if they're going to go the Apple route, why don't we charge $4,000 for the goddamn system?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because as long as it's sexy enough, people will buy it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even if it's, you know, performance-wise, not quite inferior to the competition for the same price.
[SPEAKER_04]: But hey.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_10]: Duke Nukem Forever is $5.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, the Japanese Sonic soundtrack is clearly superior to the American one.
[SPEAKER_04]: and if we're talking about like, you know, devices without Who shops at Whole Foods anymore?
[SPEAKER_10]: I go to Farmer's Market.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, if we're talking about devices without I just drive to Mexico.
[SPEAKER_04]: This drives and stuff like that and how well they worked out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Where's the netbook nowadays?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, that's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a format that failed.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I understand you have one, but I'm talking about the format.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm saying that the format itself failed.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're not making them anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're not making netbooks.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're not making netbooks anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: People like disk drives.
[SPEAKER_04]: They still make some.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, they're the old ones.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're clearing that inventory out.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's no new netbooks coming out.
[SPEAKER_10]: I like mine.
[SPEAKER_10]: And there's also the Transformer, which Dan has, which is a tablet and a netbook.
[SPEAKER_04]: And last I checked, most games out there are probably not a few megs versus the typical application size.
[SPEAKER_04]: But whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you want a system without a disk drive and you want it in a brushed metal finish and you want it to be sleek and have a glowing apple symbol on the back of it, then fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: You go ahead and purchase yourself a disk drive-less system and
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't come crying to me when you can't install anything on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, look.
[SPEAKER_02]: One more thing I want to say on this story and then we can move on.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that is the fact that Microsoft was asked to comment on this by the gaming blogs, as to be expected.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's interesting about it is that they didn't 100% deny it.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, you think you're going to get the line that says, Microsoft does not comment on rumors or speculation and the line, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: But here's the actual quote.
[SPEAKER_02]: Xbox 360 has found new ways to extend its life cycle like introducing the world to controller free experiences with Kinect and reinventing the console with a new dashboard and new entertainment content partnerships.
[SPEAKER_02]: We are always thinking about what is next for our platform and how to continue to defy the life cycle convention.
[SPEAKER_02]: Beyond that we do not comment on rumors or speculation.
[SPEAKER_02]: so it's just PR spin and the do not comment it is a little weird to me in a way it says to me why are you talking about the new Xbox we're still extending the life of the Xbox 360 stop focusing on this new Xbox and our plans for it there's plenty to go on the 360 but maybe I don't know this is crazy crazy tinfoil hat time ready maybe there's a new 360 coming out that's like the Microsoft version of the PSP Go
[SPEAKER_09]: You heard it here first on Orange Zone Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just throwing it out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: So maybe it's, well, maybe, maybe.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, God, here we go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_02]: All I want to say, but maybe the one mistake that Microsoft won't make that Sony did that ruined the PSP Go is that maybe the system is priced right.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, now, Loki, what's your witty retort?
[SPEAKER_04]: My witty retort is no one's going to buy it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's my witty retort.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're not going to do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Only Sony makes those stupid mistakes where they're like, Hey, yeah, we just announced the Vita.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, and we're going to put out a new PSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: Why?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, and it's not going to have any sort of Wi-Fi built in.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sure there's plenty more comments we're going to hear on this.
[SPEAKER_02]: By the way, I did want to say, though, one thing I forgot to tie this to is
[SPEAKER_02]: The story that this ties into from five weeks ago, we may not have been hearing about that they got rid of the disc, but we did hear the rumor about they won't play used games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm telling you, man.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was over in China the other day on the production line for the new Xbox, and that leg was a good 20 feet long.
[SPEAKER_04]: 50 foot robot, I'm telling you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Xbox GFR?
[SPEAKER_10]: Speaking about things that are full of shit.
[SPEAKER_10]: Mad Dog McCree.
[SPEAKER_02]: Aw, poor guy.
[SPEAKER_10]: I hate that game.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm gonna tell you a story about Mad Dog McCree.
[SPEAKER_10]: One day... One day... Shut up.
[SPEAKER_10]: When I was working at... Shut up.
[SPEAKER_10]: Serious.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was working at Cyber Station and we had a Mad Dog McCree.
[SPEAKER_10]: Freaking hate that because I had to clean that bitch.
[SPEAKER_12]: Did you have to wash Grandpa's balls?
[SPEAKER_10]: Not as often as you do.
[SPEAKER_12]: Did you have to polish his knobs?
[SPEAKER_10]: That has nothing to do with the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: So yeah, Mad Dog McCree Rob is having a spasm right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's just laughing at the fact he said balls.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank God it's radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: He's all red in the face.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's kind of cute.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway, a group called Engine Software is porting Mad Dog McCree to the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's going to be released on the eShop.
[SPEAKER_10]: And scores of gamers across the world go, why?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because honestly, that game was not very good.
[SPEAKER_10]: It had a sequel.
[SPEAKER_10]: How did that game get a sequel?
[SPEAKER_10]: It had it at Solomon's that was by my college in Alabama.
[SPEAKER_10]: Is Dragon's Lair on the 3DS out yet?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, and why isn't it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because, you know, when I think of Laserdisc games immediately getting ported to everything in the fucking universe, I think of Dragon's Lair.
[SPEAKER_02]: Immediately followed by Space Ace.
[SPEAKER_04]: When I think of Laserdisc games, I think your average consumer that has the 3DS probably doesn't know what a fucking Laserdisc is, nor would be interested in Mad Dog McCree.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have one more question about Mad Dog McCree on the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, since you were very familiar with Mad Dog McCree and you touched that machine in all its places, was Mad Dog McCree in 3D?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, it wasn't.
[SPEAKER_10]: Then why is it on the 3DS?
[SPEAKER_10]: Now I'm deaf in the other ear, thank you.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, and they said that they're not even going to port it over with any kind of 3D added into that.
[SPEAKER_10]: And the quote is, and I'm going to read it, there's really no 3D in the 3DS version because how are you going to do that?
[SPEAKER_04]: you know it's funny how are you gonna do that is also probably the answer to um we're gonna need to sell this game how are you gonna do that when no one gives a shit about this game seriously that game is awful i guarantee you'll sell you know twice as many copies as you did the wii version which is probably zero
[SPEAKER_02]: But Loki, two times zero is zero.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for the math lesson.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you just put them together, it's infinity.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, you know how much it's going to cost?
[SPEAKER_10]: $4.99 in US dollars.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know how much you're overpaying by? $10.
[SPEAKER_10]: They should pay you to play it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I gotta say, on the Wii, they were charging like $19.99 for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So the fact that it's only $5 is still gouging you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_10]: They should pay you.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's actually $15 overpriced.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because they should be paying you $10.01 to play it for them.
[SPEAKER_10]: So they can say, oh, people got our game.
[SPEAKER_10]: The end.
[SPEAKER_04]: Listen.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why didn't they just put tits in the game?
[SPEAKER_02]: Then people would want to buy it.
[SPEAKER_04]: True.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you're interested in playing a game that has that kind of Laserdisc vibe to it, and even a western theme, I recommend that you pick up Gunstringer with the DLC that was out there for it.
[SPEAKER_10]: What was that game, the time traveler game that was on Laserdisc?
[SPEAKER_10]: That had the cowboy.
[SPEAKER_10]: That horrible hologram one?
[SPEAKER_10]: I know, that was awful.
[SPEAKER_02]: I remember it in the arcades and it was a terrible game.
[SPEAKER_10]: I liked Cliffjumper.
[SPEAKER_02]: Neat technology though.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because it was really Lupin and the Castle of Cagliostro.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because you could literally touch that guy's balls.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know Lupin is coming back.
[SPEAKER_02]: Next story.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're not going to talk about balls anymore?
[SPEAKER_04]: If you want.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, thank goodness.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, let's talk about last week.
[SPEAKER_04]: And last week we talked a little bit about Street Fighter X Tekken and all the...
[SPEAKER_04]: The screwy things that they're doing with the download content with this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: For example, all the download content for the game is paid unlock content, which is fantastic.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, those wonderful PlayStation exclusive characters, aside from, okay, you know, the guy from Infamous, because it just wouldn't make sense that he was on the 360 version, and also, I believe, those two Japanese cats.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everything else was also on the disc.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, Capcom insinuates...
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the excuse you want to use.
[SPEAKER_04]: But at the same time, why are the beginning and ending movies there?
[SPEAKER_04]: All the data is on a disc.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I understand that you can use that for compatibility.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although, Saints Row the Third, for example, they have compatibility patches.
[SPEAKER_04]: And there's even some other games that have compatibility patches.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's a free download if you don't buy the DLC, but you can play against other people that have the DLC.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: Even though all the content's on there.
[SPEAKER_04]: How's the game selling?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just been out for a week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pretty good so far.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought maybe you'd know from your... I mean, it seems to be pretty good.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just haven't heard the day one sales yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't hear people talking about it like I did Street Fighter 4.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, granted, I'm not to profess that I am this fighting game guru guy, but I don't hear as many people talking about it nearly as I am hearing talking about Mass Effect or that we're talking about Street Fighter 4 when it came out.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's just, I find that interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just wondering if there is a backlash occurring, yes or no.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I know I'm not going to buy it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I, it's not even so much the content on the disc thing, although I think that's kind of skeezy.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just the whole, there's going to be an Ultimate Edition at some point.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, I know they're denying it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't believe them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't believe them maybe I'm being a fool but I'm gonna go off track what I could go off Capcom PR statement or I could go off track record PR track record I'm going track record
[SPEAKER_04]: Street Fighter 4, Super Street Fighter 4, Arcade Edition, Ultimate Marvel vs. Capcom 3
[SPEAKER_04]: And then on top of that, this is great, on top of that, the Xbox 360 version has an issue with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can't take your local teams online.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's stated in the manual that you can, and the PS3 version can, but the 360, meh, just doesn't work.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, fantastic.
[SPEAKER_04]: And their excuse is, well, the reason for that is the difference between, or the difference is because of the architecture differences between Xbox Live, gamer tags, and PlayStation Network IDs.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not sure of the technical details, but basically it amounts to Sony made it so that you can mix and match online and offline.
[SPEAKER_04]: Microsoft made it so you can't.
[SPEAKER_04]: However, Mortal Kombat allows you to do that just fine, so that's full of shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Halo 3 allowed you to do that too.
[SPEAKER_02]: How old is that game?
[SPEAKER_02]: But you used to be able to do split screen and you could go on Xbox Live together.
[SPEAKER_04]: yeah and also you can do that in Borderlands you can do that in Call of Duty I think you can do that in quite a few things but sure whatever yeah um okay so real quick I just want to talk about DLC because it seems like there's a whole lot of issues there's even one with you know I don't think it's one of the stories we have about Mass Effect 3 and the DLC and stuff like that
[SPEAKER_04]: I think we need to set some ground rules on what I think should be acceptable for DLC and what shouldn't as far as timing and that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: So let's start off with pay to unlock content.
[SPEAKER_04]: I never think that that should be acceptable at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's on disc.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're paying for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: The content was done before the disc was certified and it's ready to go.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's all ready.
[SPEAKER_04]: They planned it out so that you're going to have to pay for additional content for your game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It wasn't like...
[SPEAKER_04]: Day 1 DLC
[SPEAKER_04]: I think is fine because the reason for that, for example, in the case of Mass Effect 3, games certified a month or so ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: And during that time, they were working on DLC, which they got done.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not on disc at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: It may use some assets from the game, but come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, if you're using characters from the game, of course, you're going to reuse some of that, but a lot of it's brand new.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they put it out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I might take shit for this opinion, but F you, it's my opinion.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't understand the logic that the people that are hating on the Mass Effect DLC are using because the logic is you shouldn't charge me for something that was being... Or what is it?
[SPEAKER_02]: That you shouldn't charge for something that you were already making for the game before the game came out, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's kind of like the logic, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, if that was true...
[SPEAKER_02]: Shouldn't you have never bought Mass Effect 1 or 2 because, you know, they were just leading up to Mass Effect 3?
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, kind of.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or you should never have bought Saints Row 2 because you just get it for free with Saints Row 3 on PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_02]: You should never have bought White Knight Chronicles because you get the whole game free with White Knight Chronicles 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: White Knight Chronicles was there for a shit game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I mean, their logic is, okay, well, you should delay it until you have all the download content out for the game and you just put it on disk.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, they didn't do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: They actually just got it to the point where the first batch of DLC just happened to be done a month or so after they certified a disk, and boom, it's day one download content.
[SPEAKER_02]: A lot of it has to do with value.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is what you're paying for really worth what you're paying for it?
[SPEAKER_02]: And even though I'm not to that point in the series yet and I haven't formed my final opinion on Mass Effect, I'm pretty sure that for fans of Mass Effect, the on-disc experience presented with Mass Effect 3 is worth the price of admission.
[SPEAKER_02]: Going to Street Fighter X Tekken, you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: For a lot of hardcore fighting game fans and for those individuals, the price of the stuff that's on the disc and even the unlocked stuff is probably still worth it to them.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm not going to knock that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But for me, everything in that Street Fighter X Tekken has been devalued based on Capcom's history of how they treat fighting games.
[SPEAKER_02]: is what is on that disc worth $60?
[SPEAKER_02]: Not to me when I know in nine months it'll be down to $40 with everything online included.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the difference to me from where I'm sitting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, and if you think that that game, by the time that all the DLC is released, is still going to be $60, you are sorely mistaken.
[SPEAKER_04]: That game is going to devalue pretty quick, especially if it doesn't sell very well.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, look at the last Dead Rising 2 game that came out.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, off the record, didn't do that well, and it's already marked down.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think though like there's some companies that are just taking it too far like even with I don't even know if I wouldn't blame Volition because I don't think it's the developer's fault I think it's a publisher's fault but let's look at Saints Row the third aside from the DLC that they actually have made separately and beyond you know that you actually download which is fucking terrible so far and it's really sad everything else has been paid on locked content
[SPEAKER_04]: everything else.
[SPEAKER_04]: All the little costumes, all the little special weapons, those are all paid unlocked content.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's all stuff that was on there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Any of your pre-order bonuses, that's all paid unlocked content.
[SPEAKER_04]: Unless, of course, it's something that, okay, you get the first thing, a DLC that comes out a month after the game comes out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then that's not paid unlocked content.
[SPEAKER_04]: But for the most part, those special weapons or skins or whatever, that's all on the disc.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you're
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, paying money, you know, to have that right, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's kind of sad, though, that they're like, you know, the publishers are getting mad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not even the publishers, the developers, or maybe a little bit both.
[SPEAKER_04]: Developers and publishers are getting mad that people are complaining about, oh, well, you know what, too bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is how we wanted to do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, then, that's not really, I mean...
[SPEAKER_04]: Humor the consumer a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you're planning on releasing these characters, say these 12 characters or whatever, just don't put them on the disc.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just have it so you download them later on.
[SPEAKER_04]: You would be doing the same thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know as far as infrastructure costs go.
[SPEAKER_04]: If actually having more than just a key downloaded from Xbox Live or something costs more to the publisher or the developer than it does just the key.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: and then that way people wouldn't bitch about it and they'd be like oh my god this is a great value because look at all these extra characters Capcom supporting the game long after it's been out this is fantastic versus I'm getting fucking ripped off because all this stuff was on the disc already notice same thing you're providing the same amount of content but it's perception
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: so in other words the DLC allows you to not get something you know is going to be shitty exactly I didn't give a shit about Jill or Shuma Garath as we call him slash her Shuma-chan at home because all the characters I wanted to play were in the game when Ultimate came out I was like oh cool we get to hear you we have a new game I know this might be I already know what the answer to this question is but I'm going to ask it anyway what would you think if you went online and then suddenly you're fighting against someone else who's playing as the Mega Man you don't want to see
[SPEAKER_10]: DC.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'd seriously quit the match.
[SPEAKER_10]: Keep in mind, I'm the same person that if there is one single troll in my dungeon run, I will leave party.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because my time is important and I don't have to put up with shit I don't like.
[SPEAKER_10]: If I want a game, I'm going to buy the game regardless of what's already on the disc.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't really care.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, I'm going to try to wrap this up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bobby is sending a link to the official DLC response for Mass Effect 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: In a nutshell, I'm not going to read the whole thing, but it's kind of what we already know is BioWare's approach to this is that they finished Mass Effect 3 before they did the DLC, but in order to do DLC, you have to kind of put, and this is the part that's kind of more information,
[SPEAKER_02]: You have to put the seeds of the DLC in the game or you can't have the DLC interact with the game that's already pressed on the disc.
[SPEAKER_02]: If that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_10]: You have to have the code that's going to access the info.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I don't think there's any problem with having an outline of we know we want to do this, this, and this later on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Saints Row clearly did the same thing as Mediocre's content did.
[SPEAKER_02]: They knew what packs they were going to do.
[SPEAKER_02]: Didn't they advertise it from day one that Gangsters in Space was going to be an add-on eventually?
[SPEAKER_04]: Neato comment from E3VL or Evil I suppose in our chat room Whatever happened to unlocking characters the traditional way?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not... You can still do that in some games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some games.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not cost-effective.
[SPEAKER_02]: Probably not a Capcom game.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is a... But that's a sad... I mean, it's a good question, but it's a sad question.
[SPEAKER_02]: What did ever happen to that?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because the modern gamer, seriously, doesn't really want to work for anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hence why they'll put up the 99 cent unlock thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Exactly, because it's instant gratification.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll tell you exactly why that's not unlocked in the traditional ways anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because back in the day when a lot of that stuff was unlocked traditionally is through playing through the story mode.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nowadays, most gamers are split between single player and multiplayer, and a lot of people are purchasing this game just to play multiplayer, and they won't even touch the single player, and so why make someone go through the single player when they're not going to play it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Game In the same font as Game Boy
[SPEAKER_02]: Ooh, a type nerd would pick up on that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't pick up on that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Except their kerning is really tragic.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it's going to say closed pretty soon on the top of it if things keep going the way they're going because apparently game is in trouble.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, game, we've already heard of some trouble going on there.
[SPEAKER_02]: They didn't sell Mass Effect 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: It wasn't there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Street Fighter X Tekken, you can't get it at game.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is not good when the retailer will not sell the games people are looking for.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's...
[SPEAKER_04]: I know exactly what's going on here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because this exact same thing happened with Blockbuster.
[SPEAKER_04]: What happened was, when they get into these financial problems where they're facing bankruptcy, or I don't know if they've even filed bankruptcy yet or whatever, these publishers are concerned about getting paid for their product.
[SPEAKER_04]: and so they don't extend them credit anymore and so because of that they're unable to purchase games where in the case of Blockbuster Blockbuster had to purchase games through a distributor and the distributor basically covered they floated them the credit I guess some way and so basically they assume all the risk for them and unfortunately it sounds like there's no UK distributor although I
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't imagine that there's not UK distributors, or maybe at least someone that's not willing to float that kind of credit risk.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that's what's going on here.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's why you're seeing certain publishers that are not caring, certain games and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm assuming it's going to be a lot of publishers.
[SPEAKER_04]: If we're talking EA, Ubisoft, I can't remember the other one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Capcom.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not sure who the publishers are because I know there's different publishers in the UK.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I mean, you're going to see it's going to be specific companies that are going to stop giving them credit, and that's why they're not carrying the games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, just to further illustrate how serious this issue is, apparently game is behind on the rent.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have to pay some landlords in about two weeks, and if they don't...
[SPEAKER_02]: Thousands of jobs could be at risk, and that is obviously not going to be good news.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, there is a company that's kind of circling around like a hawk that might be picking these guys up, and that would be GameStop, or as we call it here on Sunday nights at all games, Evil G. GameStop particularly is interested in the Spanish arm of the business, apparently.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I think this has to do with the fact that GameStop did try to do UK before, but they closed some stores.
[SPEAKER_02]: But that doesn't necessarily mean they won't buy all of game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Spanish is of particular interest.
[SPEAKER_02]: Other countries, maybe.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're just waiting for it to devalue enough.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they'll swoop right in.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guarantee that they'll probably buy it because it just makes sense.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're not going to come out of this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, this is kind of probably past that point.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to have to be someone buying them.
[SPEAKER_02]: and Picaruno is in our chat room and I know he's from over there.
[SPEAKER_02]: The nice thing is with the whole spring forward here, we did a little early.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's an hour early for the folks overseas to tune into OLR Live now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Picaruno says, I have 15 pounds.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't see.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's pounds.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is it pounds?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, because I can't see how it translates over here because it comes up as special text.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have 15 pounds of vouchers with them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Need to spend it soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I would recommend if you have any sort of gift cards to the game, get those.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just buy something.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yep, buy something.
[SPEAKER_02]: Trade them in for cash if you can do that over there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know you can't in California, but if it's a certain amount.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, buy something soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it'll have to be an older game.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_10]: Rob Cares So it's The Vita version is going to have HD remasters Of Metal Gear Solid 2 and Metal Gear Solid 3 With all of the trophies And crap that the PS3 version does They didn't say anything about Peace Walker though
[SPEAKER_10]: There is something that says they have a rebalanced user interface that's going to go a little bit more with this transferring system that's being developed.
[SPEAKER_10]: What the transferring is, is basically some type of cloud storage.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's called Title User Storage, TUS, where your save game is going to transfer via whatever that cloud is, and you can access it on both PS3 and on Vita without using Wi-Fi.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's... How tiny the gamer memory is, because I completely forgot about transferring.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for reminding me.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, the Japanese release date is June 28th.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's summer over here, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's travel around the world and check out some games that are coming out a lot sooner.
[SPEAKER_10]: One other thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_10]: You've got different things available with the touch panel.
[SPEAKER_10]: You have zooming like with your binoculars on event scenes.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can close up in the cinematics.
[SPEAKER_02]: So kind of working in those little features of the Vita.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, make the Vita special.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I thought I'd add that.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Release dates.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki starting off here locally in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yakuza Dead Souls PlayStation 3
[SPEAKER_04]: GG, I don't know, something based off a toy.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess they have a toy that's hermit crabs.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, crappy DS game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Silverlicious, based off a book series.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's also on the DS as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: The 4-in-1 action pack from South Peak.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a bunch of really terrible PlayStation Network games.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that sounds like fantastic fun there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Naruto Shippuden, Ultimate Ninja Storm Generations on Playstation 3 and Xbox 360 Birds of Steel on Playstation 3 and Xbox 360 this week as well Tales of Graces F on Playstation 3 Ridge Racer on the Vita kinda wanna play that but it's still not fucking worth it FIFA Street on Playstation 3 and Xbox 360 Reality Fighters on the Vita
[SPEAKER_04]: and let's see what else here.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that would be it.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, traveling over to Japan and looking at the releases over there.
[SPEAKER_02]: In Japan on the 360, Mass Effect 3 gets released on March the 15th.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Japanese release.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if that means all the dialogue has been redubbed with Japanese voice actors.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would assume so.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know, there you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: SSX also coming out in Japan this week on the 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: Going over to the PlayStation 3, it's pretty much the same story.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mass Effect is there as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: and SSX but there are some other games coming out as well Resident Evil 5 AE or Biohazard 5 AE and Revival Selection HD Remaster Twin Pack so there's like a whole little like double games for a little less money Sengoku Basara 3 Utage Double Pack comes out as well as Shin Sengoku Musou Online Ryujin Ranbu comes out this week and that is obviously it's an online game is that Dynasty Warriors?
[SPEAKER_02]: Slaughter Mania 5 Black Lagoon
[SPEAKER_02]: But the cool thing is, it's a slot machine and then a chick with a big gun.
[SPEAKER_02]: She's like, you're going to give me that money or I'll put a bullet in you.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then it's a slot machine.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's little like anime cut scenes with guns and cigarettes.
[SPEAKER_10]: I like the twin B one.
[SPEAKER_10]: All sorts of vices.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also FIFA soccer on the Vita.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you can't shoot the players.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's no guns to be found in FIFA soccer.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can throw a ball at their heads.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can.
[SPEAKER_02]: Going to the 3DS real quick.
[SPEAKER_02]: Only one game coming out from D3 this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Onanoko to Mishitsuni Ittara comes out this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I don't know what it is, but it's another game featuring girls in school uniforms.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dating sim.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, man.
[SPEAKER_02]: I feel like the Dateline guys are going to show up at my house just for bringing that picture up on my computer.
[SPEAKER_10]: I told you from the beginning it was a dating sim.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have a seat over there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, no, no, Ko is like little girl.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't import the game or what's-his-name will show up at your house.
[SPEAKER_02]: Chris Hansen, is that his name?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't buy that game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Can we go to another country now?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, please.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, how about the UK?
[SPEAKER_10]: On March 12th, all zombies must die!
[SPEAKER_10]: On the 13th, shoot many robots.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's a clever name.
[SPEAKER_10]: And warp.
[SPEAKER_10]: On March 14th, Journey for the PS3, which Rob discussed at the top of the show.
[SPEAKER_10]: and ShootManyRobots on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_10]: On the 16th, Bit.Trip Complete on Wii and Bit.Trip Saga on 3DS, FIFA Street, Inazuma 11.2 Firestorm slash Blizzard on DS, Rayman Origins on 3DS, Sniper Ghost Warrior 2 and Yakuza Dead Souls and I'll go ahead and say the 17th because it's the Sunday and we'll be here is Tekken 3D Prime.
[SPEAKER_02]: 3D fighting movies.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's actually Saturday.
[SPEAKER_10]: So yeah, stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: A couple more stories for you guys and then the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, Loki, whatever possible surprise news story could you be talking about next?
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's talk about the iPad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I know, shocker, there was a new iPad announced this week and it's called the new iPad.
[SPEAKER_02]: In case you hadn't heard.
[SPEAKER_04]: In case you hadn't heard.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm full of lust.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was pretty much all the rumored stuff except for the really weird stuff that they started rumoring this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um,
[SPEAKER_04]: It's got the Retina display, it's got the upgraded camera that was in the iPhone 4S, quad-core A5X processor, and also a...
[SPEAKER_04]: What else?
[SPEAKER_02]: 4G connectivity.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now everybody's phone is starting to show 4G connectivity even though they're not 4G phones.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you're on AT&T.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's because of the multiple different types of 4G networks that existed and they're all being solidified into the one that I think Verizon uses.
[SPEAKER_04]: so those are out and of course it's going to range anywhere in price for the wifi version from $4.99 to $6.99 depending on how much storage you want or for the 4G $6.29 through $8.29 and they will go on sale this week March 16th fantastic of course with this they got to show that hey we can do games so they showed off a new Infinity Blade game
[SPEAKER_04]: Infinity Blade Dungeons.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a prequel to Infinity Blade and looked kind of like God of War.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then also a flight sim game called Sky Gamblers that kind of looked like Ace Combat, and that was from Namco.
[SPEAKER_04]: Unfortunately, no buttons.
[SPEAKER_04]: Still no buttons, other than the home button.
[SPEAKER_02]: Unless you buy an iCade, which isn't an official Apple product, so they don't talk about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_02]: Which is interesting because they made a claim, there was a claim during the press conference where they attacked essentially the 360 and the PlayStation 3 and said, this thing does more pixels at once than a, millions, millions more pixels at once than a Xbox 360 or a PlayStation 3 because the resolution is greater than 1080p.
[SPEAKER_02]: 1080 means 1080 by, and one of these suckers is what, 2000 something?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it was like 29-something.
[SPEAKER_04]: But once again, graphics aren't everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can have a really beautiful game that controls like shit, and it will be terrible.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's also how the developers utilize it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, because you have to up-res everything, or you have to make your games actually utilize that stuff in order for it to work out, plus the hardware and everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: limitations there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, don't get me wrong, those games are probably going to look really nice, but do I really want a game that controls via tilt or touchscreen?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, some of the touchscreen stuff, I mean, Infinity Blade was alright with touchscreen, but it's just... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Brag about your resolution of your screen and stuff like that, but at the same time, also, you gotta remember you do have some faults.
[SPEAKER_10]: There are people that are completely swayed by SHINee, so... Well, I'm not going to lie.
[SPEAKER_02]: I still kind of want one.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just... I don't feel like I need one right away at this point.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, I mean, not even from a game standpoint.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just like, I want to watch movies in bed on that thing because there's not going to be a better screen than that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I have a Vita, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't cry me a river.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to be okay not having one of those day one.
[SPEAKER_10]: And see, I was actually already planning on getting one because I have a legitimate need of it for school.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's some really good note-taking apps.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, they have the whole iUniversity book thing now, too, that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, well, there's also an app that will let you type in your notes and it timestamps your notes in conjunction with where you started it in the lecture while it records the lecture.
[SPEAKER_10]: And for me, with my hand, that's perfect.
[SPEAKER_10]: because then I can record my lecture and actually take notes and say this slide was used at this point or this and that and the other was used at that point which I'm using my notebook already yes I'm using my notebook which is just fine but for my hand problems you know typing on an iPad will be easier so I'm actually now that the new ones are you know there I'm going to get one that's the plan anyway I have a legitimate need for it I'm buying it for school
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, I probably don't even have to ask you how you feel about the new iPad.
[SPEAKER_02]: And by the way, just to go back to our chat room at chat.orange.com, Amiga777 says, Really?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's actually going to be the real name?
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought that the article I read was going to be a joke.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not that the name is the new iPad.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's not the name.
[SPEAKER_02]: The name is iPad.
[SPEAKER_02]: iPad 3 or iPad HD
[SPEAKER_04]: I would say iPad HD.
[SPEAKER_04]: I still don't know why they gotta be all stubborn about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, we're not gonna put a number on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: You make it sound like we release these things every few years or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, what the hell?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because it's branding and marketing.
[SPEAKER_10]: End of story.
[SPEAKER_10]: They do it that way because they have to do it that way.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because they want people, when you think of iPad, they want you to think of the newest, best version of it that they have.
[SPEAKER_02]: I get it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I feel bad for those that can't tell the difference.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because there will be people out there that buy iPad off Craigslist and get one of those first generation iPads.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let the buyer beware.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I'm just saying, I feel a little bad for those people.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't.
[SPEAKER_10]: If they didn't take the time to contact the seller and verify it, that's their fault.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, one more story before the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that is... Rock Band!
[SPEAKER_02]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_02]: Still relevant.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nope, I'm not talking about Rock Band 4.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, you know, I gotta admit, this is a really nice thing to hear.
[SPEAKER_02]: Harmonix has basically commented that Rock Band releases aren't stopping.
[SPEAKER_02]: One of the few things to come out of Game Developers Conference 2012, Harmonix says, quote, We've been really pleased with the continued performance of Rock Band downloadable content.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've delivered over four years of weekly DLC and over 3,500 songs to the music platform, and we have no plans to stop weekly releases anytime soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: If there's a song you still want, Rock Band folks encourage you to go look at the Facebook app that they have and vote for artists on the wish list.
[SPEAKER_04]: This kind of makes me wonder if Guitar Hero is ever going to come back because how can you compete with that kind of a library?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be difficult.
[SPEAKER_02]: Harmonix, by the way, also said they have no intentions of doing Rock Band 4 this year.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have some other projects going on right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: So maybe Rock Band is on the back burner until the next, you know, Xbox or PlayStations are being talked about.
[SPEAKER_02]: And maybe some of those features being used.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm strangely okay with this.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, as much as I love Rock Band and would love to see a Rock Band 4, I kind of get where, well, maybe there's not a whole lot else you can do with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So props to them for continuing to support the game with true DLC.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_02]: True, reasonably priced, varied, not on the disc DLC.
[SPEAKER_02]: DLC.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now that is continuing to support it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And when they say that they're going to support it weekly, they support it weekly.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they continue to support it, unlike some companies.
[SPEAKER_04]: Konami.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: has a song.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's crazy the obscurity of that stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: That might have been the first DLC bundle.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't remember.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I think that was the one you talked about a lot.
[SPEAKER_02]: Was it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, let's take a look.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, you can look it up.
[SPEAKER_02]: I played it when it first came out and I already forgot, sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: But now Rhythm Party, if you have all the DLC, is up to like, I don't know, 20, no, about 20 songs maybe?
[SPEAKER_02]: Quake!
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_10]: Seriously, if Alan can do Half-Life while I'm gone, then I can do Quake.
[SPEAKER_10]: Quake is... If you don't know what Quake is, then you need to get out from under the rock that you've been under for the last 20 years.
[SPEAKER_10]: Quake is a first-person shooter game that came out by...
[SPEAKER_10]: The same people that gave us Doom.
[SPEAKER_10]: Surprise, surprise.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it spawned a whole series of games.
[SPEAKER_10]: It actually came out on Steam on August 3rd, 2007.
[SPEAKER_10]: basically you have to go navigate through the level and you face enemies and you have to open doors and do different things but when you start a level you have three different pathways it's an easy medium and hard skill level and to get to like the nightmare level you have to go into a secret passageway and stuff
[SPEAKER_10]: So basically, you've got different episodes of about eight levels each, and there's even a low-gravity episode, too.
[SPEAKER_10]: But you collect all these different items, and you carry them on to the next level, and then the next level gets, you know, more challenging.
[SPEAKER_10]: When you die, you have to restart at the beginning of that level, but you can save your game as many times as you want.
[SPEAKER_10]: You also do have multiplayer, like a deathmatch.
[SPEAKER_10]: You've got, I think there was Capture the Flag?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: But, I mean...
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to switch from the ambient noises to the actual music here.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's pretty much what happened with this game after that.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was a VGA full color game.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's an ASCII version of it, did you know that?
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually did know that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's an ASCII version of Quake.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's where the Quake engine went with this.
[SPEAKER_10]: That game engine has been in so many other games.
[SPEAKER_10]: Basically it uses, it was polygon models instead of the sprites, you know, the way that Doom did it.
[SPEAKER_10]: You have full 3D level design, different light maps that are pre-rendered.
[SPEAKER_10]: You've got all kinds of abilities to modify it because there is a huge Quake modding community out there.
[SPEAKER_10]: I remember bringing up on the show playing Gacha Quake, which was a Gachamon patch for Quake.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's why we have talked about this on the show before.
[SPEAKER_02]: I knew it came out before, but it's not as pleasant as you believe.
[SPEAKER_10]: Did you know it was developed by John Carmack?
[SPEAKER_02]: I did know that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_10]: Also, Michael Abrash and John Cash, as opposed to Johnny Cash, who was dead.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who wasn't at the time.
[SPEAKER_10]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: And not his son either.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I was just thinking about, you know, the people that did the soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_02]: Johnny Cash was involved with the cover, but never mind.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_10]: But this was pretty much the king of first-person shooter games for the longest time.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was going to say, even I played the shit out of this game in college.
[SPEAKER_02]: We used to call.
[SPEAKER_02]: This was back when we used modems to dial into everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: But my friends at Sonoma State had one of those state-of-the-art T1 lines or whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we'd all call into their server at Sonoma State.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'd play the fuck out of this game until like 2 in the morning.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: So much fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Multiplayers.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, well, basically, before there was even a demo, id Software put out Q-Test, which is February 24th, 1996, that was a tech demo that had three multiplayer maps.
[SPEAKER_10]: And basically, it just lit a fire, because when Quake came out, there were servers everywhere popping up.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just basically like you were saying.
[SPEAKER_10]: And there were people reskinning the textures, reskinning the whole levels, making new maps, you name it.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's what really came out.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's basically scripted in Quake C, was I believe the coding for it.
[SPEAKER_10]: And the first Quake mod that came out was Team Fortress.
[SPEAKER_10]: which was capture the flag but it had that class system basically and we know where Team Fortress has gone since then so there was also three wave capture the flag there was you know I've actually seen where someone used they did it first in Quake and then went and did it in Half-Life where they redid the whole ending of of Cube 2
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: But there were like different, you know, they created different bots for it.
[SPEAKER_10]: There was Rocket Arena where...
[SPEAKER_10]: Quaked Unquick Quaked Unquicker
[SPEAKER_10]: So yeah, there's all kinds of different
[SPEAKER_10]: It's really blown up since then.
[SPEAKER_10]: Going to this image on here that's basically the family tree of Quake games.
[SPEAKER_10]: We have on here, coming from Quake, we have QuakeWorld that spawned Twilight, more QuakeWorld, ZQuake, FTE.
[SPEAKER_10]: Doom 3 eventually came from Quake 3, which was built on Quake 2, built from the first Quake.
[SPEAKER_10]: So we've got all of these different ones.
[SPEAKER_10]: Medal of Honor, Allied Assault.
[SPEAKER_10]: we have STV Elite Forces 2 on the list we have Paintball Jedi Academy there's all kinds of games on here that run off of variants of the original Quake engine so basically your first person shooters are what they are today because of Quake just saying and also you can play it on the Amiga
[SPEAKER_02]: God, that's how old this game was.
[SPEAKER_02]: It actually runs on an Amiga.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's a port for it on the Amiga.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: The ports I really need to get into.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, they made the source code public some time ago, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: The Commodore Amiga port was done in 1998 by Clickboom, but it's only available in 68K.
[SPEAKER_10]: There was a Linux version that was made by an id Software employee.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course there was a Linux version.
[SPEAKER_10]: For fun, in his spare time.
[SPEAKER_10]: and then in 1999 there's a retail version for Linux that was put out by Macmillan Digital.
[SPEAKER_10]: They also had two add-ons which was the offering for Linux.
[SPEAKER_10]: So there's a Mac version now that was done by MacSoft.
[SPEAKER_10]: It came out on Sega Saturn, Nintendo 64,
[SPEAKER_10]: There are all kinds of versions.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's Nintendo DS versions of Quake.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's Quake DS and SeaQuake.
[SPEAKER_10]: So you name it, you can play Quake on it probably.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can probably play Quake on a toaster.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: There it is, your classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_02]: A true, true classic indeed.
[SPEAKER_02]: Quake.
[SPEAKER_10]: I remember playing Quake 3 on the Dreamcast with our Ethernet adapter.
[SPEAKER_10]: Quake 3 was amazing.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: If you want to just play Quake-inspired games, go play Quake Live.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because that's basically Quake 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: And even though there's lots of differences between Quake 1 and Quake 3, eh.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's still a good time.
[SPEAKER_10]: Asky Quake.
[SPEAKER_10]: Asky Quake is just funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it's funny for like two seconds.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then you're like, this is annoying.
[SPEAKER_02]: Escape.
[SPEAKER_10]: This makes my eyes hurt.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ow.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, that's going to do it for Part A of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have plenty more to come.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't go anywhere.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't stop your iPods.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't turn off your live stream of all games because we've got plenty more to come.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rapid Fire News, Fugle Question, Mailbag, FUs, your calls, more news when we come back with more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Orange Lounge Radio, the show where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cammy greater than Chun-Li
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, I have to tell you where that came from.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_10]: Dan's little brother.
[SPEAKER_10]: Is it either Dan's?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, it was a friend of ours' son was saying, whenever Cammy does her wind pose and turns around, she goes, look at my butt.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's what he would say.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_04]: I was going to make the argument that it's because she's not American, though, so I can't make that argument, but I thought that they're drawing some sort of comparison to soundtracks of a certain other game, and one being superior to the other.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, the non-Japanese being superior.
[SPEAKER_02]: Stop it right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Stop it.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: But to be fair, the UK and Japanese have the same soundtrack, so ha!
[SPEAKER_02]: Akuma JP says, I don't use female characters.
[SPEAKER_02]: In any game?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that's just Street Fighter he's talking about, but I notice in fighting games that the female characters tend to be like the ones that are quick and agile, you know, I know that's kind of stereotype, but that's how I use almost all female characters.
[SPEAKER_02]: Me too.
[SPEAKER_10]: Except in King of Fighters where they all look androgynous.
[SPEAKER_02]: I used to be a pretty good Chun-Li player back in the day.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want a very non-agile, large female character.
[SPEAKER_02]: They probably do exist.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm trying to think.
[SPEAKER_02]: You'd probably have to go to the Neo Geo series.
[SPEAKER_10]: The only character that I can think of in the Street Fighter series that's female and sizable would be Elena and her legs.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's also...
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I can't think of one.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I know that there's male characters that are, you know... Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Vega, if you want to do Street Fighter.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I'm thinking of the sizable male characters.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, well, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rufus.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that's what I'm saying.
[SPEAKER_04]: We need a large, sassy black woman.
[SPEAKER_04]: You do?
[SPEAKER_02]: I was trying to think of one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you can create to your heart's content in Soul Calibur.
[SPEAKER_02]: which I was thinking Ivy doesn't exactly of course nothing in Soul Calibur is really agile I mean it's Soul Calibur is kind of a different style of fighting I guess that's not true some would say like Voldo is like an agile type of character but Voldo is also into bondage and shows off his package regularly not that there's anything wrong with that
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, anyhow, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've got to get back into some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_02]: We still have a lot of room to go here before we get to your calls later on in the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, Loki, how about some news?
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, let's talk about the new SimCity.
[SPEAKER_04]: They showed it off at GDC, and it looks pretty.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not scheduled to come out until 2013, and it will be on PC.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it looks like they've really amped up the detail.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everything from actually seeing the individual cars driving around to how much control you have over it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just ridiculous the amount of control.
[SPEAKER_04]: But pretty awesome looking.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it will run on this new glass box engine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which, like I said, it's really, really detailed.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, so very cool looking game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry, this has nothing to do with SimCity, but my mind is still stuck on the whole you want a large, sassy lady in a fighting game.
[SPEAKER_02]: And my mind, for some reason, instantly went to Latrice Royale from RuPaul's Drag Race.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that made me think, wouldn't RuPaul's Drag Race make the best fighting game ever?
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be great.
[SPEAKER_02]: The time has come for you to lip-sync for your life.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, really, your life.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was thinking that Oprah should be downloadable.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, they had a... I'm not talking about the first computer one, because obviously the old school one I think a lot of us have played, because there was a port of it on Super Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_02]: But there was one on CD that had, like, it whored the full motion video, and there was some bad video.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you ever play it?
[SPEAKER_04]: I did not play that one.
[SPEAKER_04]: The first SimCity game I played was on 5 14 floppies that was in black and white.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, the monitor I had was in black and white, but...
[SPEAKER_04]: Really old SimCity.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then I played SimCity 2000 a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't really care for it too much.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was like, whoa, this is way more complicated than SimCity.
[SPEAKER_02]: The minute I was like, wait, I have to build piping and shit too?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that's this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have to manage your sewer systems.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm like, I just want to build buildings and have Godzilla attack them.
[SPEAKER_10]: I saw the most scary thing ever, ever for SimCity.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_10]: Was this guy who basically created the most efficient city in SimCity with 6 million people and fully functioning everything, but the thing that he sacrificed was longevity of the people, so he had them dying off at like 50.
[SPEAKER_10]: But his city was the most efficient, and he spent four years making it.
[SPEAKER_10]: that's frightening and he's got himself exactly it's the forever alone guy he plays SimCity but seriously there's like a YouTube on there of him bragging about his shit with this epic music and all I can think of that's so sad speaking of YouTube I've got to play this for you guys since you haven't seen it this is one of the great
[SPEAKER_02]: Cut scenes from that SimCity PC.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember when everything had to have full motion video?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: So this was like that period where like every adventure game had it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, here's a great cut scene back from the SimCity days.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is like one of the action news sequences that would chime into your game when things happen.
[SPEAKER_01]: We've just received an emergency report that a serious meltdown has occurred at the SimCity nuclear power plant.
[SPEAKER_00]: And the Oscar goes to... Her horribly bad lipstick.
[SPEAKER_00]: Basic ass bitch from SimCity Action News.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie!
I couldn't help it.
[SPEAKER_02]: How insensitive.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: That might not be that different.
[SPEAKER_04]: We should try that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I am so fucking down with that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_10]: The first thing that popped in my head was Night Trap.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was like, Tino Plato.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jamie, shame on you.
[SPEAKER_02]: So?
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm all down for that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would like to know what happened to SimCityActionNewsLady.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some of these people might actually be famous, for all we know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think she is.
[SPEAKER_02]: But here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not doing this to harp on her acting skills or whatever, because let's face it, we all got to get work somewhere, moving from community theater to SimCity.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's been in one more game than I have.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: More people have seen her than listened to this podcast, I'm sure of that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But look, my point is, that stuff would just cut right into the middle of your game when you were playing SimCity.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, you'd be doing your thing, do-do-do-do-do-do, and then all of a sudden that fucking full-motion video would come in.
[SPEAKER_02]: Goddammit, I'm trying to play a game!
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yeah, SimCity 5, hope it doesn't suck.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think SimCity 1's gonna be in it, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, phew, thank God.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, poor, poor Dana Plato.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, is it my turn?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it's Loki's... Loki's done one story.
[SPEAKER_02]: Finish your shit!
[SPEAKER_02]: Rapid fire news.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, we were talking about... I derailed.
[SPEAKER_04]: We were talking about SimCity, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: My fault.
[SPEAKER_04]: I finished my coffee.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was delicious.
[SPEAKER_04]: I promise to be fast.
[SPEAKER_04]: The next one would be Sorcery finally has a date.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, hey, they talked about it during E3 as a big thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then it went poof, disappeared, and just delay, delay, delay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Diabolical Pitch, Grasshopper, Connect, Zombies, Baseball
[SPEAKER_04]: That game will be out April 4th.
[SPEAKER_04]: And man, what a weird fucking game that is.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that'll be out on Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_04]: And yes, it's a really weird fucking game.
[SPEAKER_04]: But would you have it any other way with Grasshopper Manufacturer?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm okay with weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Throwing baseballs at zombies.
[SPEAKER_02]: So with Kinect.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: PvP has been taken out.
[SPEAKER_02]: For now.
[SPEAKER_02]: which might lend a hint as to what the holdup is with this game.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've been talking about it here.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know I've been talking about it all the time on Horde House.
[SPEAKER_02]: This game has been delayed, delayed, delayed.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, no Blizzard game is ever truly delayed because they don't, you know, but let's be real.
[SPEAKER_02]: The beta's been out forever.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it seems like the game is done.
[SPEAKER_02]: So the question has been, what's the holdup?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it might have been PvP because this official press release came out on Blizzard's site that basically says, you know, we're counting down the days, getting ready to announce this release date.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have come to realize that PvP is not up to the standards.
[SPEAKER_02]: We will release it in a patch following the game's launch, to which a lot of people kind of roll their eyes and go, oh, patching in the content after the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: but let's be fair PC games kind of do this anyway a lot and something as robust as PvP and they're not going to charge you extra for it I think it's okay if they're going to do that PvP wasn't really in Diablo 2 so it was something new to Diablo 3 so whereas I'm sure some folks will be disappointed if it'll get the damn game out already then I'm okay with this taking a little bit of a break so they do say that when PvP does come out multiple arena maps, theme locations and so forth
[SPEAKER_02]: It wasn't in the beta, so I guess it's not that surprising that PvP is getting cut out.
[SPEAKER_02]: So hopefully a release date for Diablo before too long.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hopefully a release date soon for this game, too, because I know the screenshots that came out for it this week have me very excited, as I'm sure a lot of you.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that is Kingdom Hearts 3D, or Kingdom Hearts Dream Drop Distance.
[SPEAKER_02]: Get it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, some of the screenshots came out this week that show Sora in...
[SPEAKER_02]: Sam, son of Flynn
[SPEAKER_02]: and Riku.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, they don't.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would love to see a Kingdom Hearts 3 on consoles already, but I'll take this to hold me over.
[SPEAKER_02]: One other quick story here about Dead or Alive 5.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dead or Alive 5 has a new character on the roster.
[SPEAKER_02]: Might be familiar if you've ever played a little game called Virtua Fighter.
[SPEAKER_02]: Akira Yuki will be in the next Dead or Alive game.
[SPEAKER_02]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if you're a Virtua Fighter fan.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ooh, I'm not.
[SPEAKER_02]: Worlds are colliding.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wasn't really either, but there you go.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, my husband liked it and I was like, the only time I ever played any version of that game for like any period of time was because I was trying to knock off Kage's mask in Virtua Fighter 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: and then Assassin's Creed 3 will be on the Wii U and there is a trailer out.
[SPEAKER_10]: And isn't this the one that's like the Native American one that's taking place during the American Revolution?
[SPEAKER_10]: I do believe it is.
[SPEAKER_10]: So yeah, it actually has big battles that are going on including the Continental Army versus the British Army.
[SPEAKER_10]: All kinds of cool stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, actually I have to tell you something.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_10]: Assassin's Creed came up in my Renaissance history class.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because apparently it shows the towns so realistically that my teacher was able to use the models in the game to show us the Palazzo and all kinds of different places in Venice.
[SPEAKER_10]: I thought I would mention that.
[SPEAKER_10]: So...
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Is it really tie-in to the drink Propel, or is that just the name?
[SPEAKER_10]: Speculation.
[SPEAKER_02]: I see.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think it's just a clever name, but yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: But hey, yo, dog, I heard you like Propel, so you can play Propel while you drink Propel and propel your head through the screen.
[SPEAKER_02]: Old meme is old.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know, but it's still funny sometimes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, I'm done.
[SPEAKER_04]: Real quick.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, this might be a coincidence, but I was looking for the...
[SPEAKER_02]: Actress that played... I was just about to say the chatters found something on that, but go ahead.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see what you got first.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stephanie Fargo is the actress that did that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Funny enough, search for Stephanie Fargo on Facebook.
[SPEAKER_04]: You don't get Stephanie Fargo.
[SPEAKER_04]: You do, however, get Stephanie... I believe it's Goats, who happens to be a news reporter.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that a coincidence or what?
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: She's also blonde.
[SPEAKER_04]: It could be the one.
[SPEAKER_04]: She could have actually turned this into a career.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not saying that this is the person because there's very little to go on because, you know, IMDB and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, man, that would be a coincidence.
[SPEAKER_02]: OL Army, bring me Stephanie Fargo.
[SPEAKER_04]: I ask questions.
[SPEAKER_04]: And she looks like age-wise that it could be.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wait, show me because I can't find her like you've got it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Stephanie Fargo's photos, address, phone, email.
[SPEAKER_04]: See, look, I did a search for Stephanie Fargo.
[SPEAKER_02]: You shouldn't encourage people to stalk like this.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is borderline a problem.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I was like, news anchor reporter?
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, that would be a coincidence.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't get me wrong.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, it doesn't really look like her to me It's hard to say because that's like the 90s haircut Well, SSJ100Matt was the chatter that said Stephanie Fargo is the SimCity news hiker Her IMDB says that she's only been in SimCity Well, that's IMDB I was like, you all have problems Stop stalking these poor full motion actors
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god, you guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's go to the Fugle Question of the Week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Every week we ask you guys a question on the Facebook and the Google+.
[SPEAKER_02]: You put them together, it's Fugle.
[SPEAKER_02]: Facebook Google Question of the Week.
[SPEAKER_02]: With the recent announcement of the new iPad, the statement was made by Apple that the resolution of the device was greater than the PlayStation 3 or Xbox 360 experience.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you consider the iPad a gaming device for the core gamer?
[SPEAKER_02]: Why or why not?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think we've kind of said our piece on this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's go to some of the answers.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was a lot of answers.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't read them all, but I'm going to read some of these.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jennifer J. says, To be completely honest, I don't see it as much of a gaming machine.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, sure, there are games made for it and whatnot, but I really don't see it going anywhere.
[SPEAKER_02]: But then again, I might be wrong.
[SPEAKER_02]: John K says, Jim H says,
[SPEAKER_02]: However, it's a gaming machine of a different sort.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think you're going to see that Nintendo and Sony's newer portable consoles aren't going to sell like past incarnations because Apple and Android have all the casual pick-up-and-play gamers locked up.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think there's a story on that coming up in a minute here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hunter R says, First of all, the resolution claim is contingent on the apps that run on the iPad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember, the PS3 can do 1080p, but how many games actually run at that resolution?
[SPEAKER_02]: As far as the iPad being a gaming device, I don't buy it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't play many games on my iPad, and the games I do play are mainly board and card games.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is mostly due to the control scheme.
[SPEAKER_02]: Having my fingers get in the way of the display is a problem for most games, but is not a problem for board and card games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, I use my iPad more to watch videos, use Twitter, check my email, read online articles, and type up long rambling passages that may or may not be interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Such as this one?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Katsuhiko J says, for a pick-up-and-go experience, yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can say the full name on that one.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a...
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I always say first in the lesson at OTA, Janai.
[SPEAKER_02]: For a pick-up-and-go experience, yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: For a sit-down-and-play-for-hours experience, probably not.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is decided by the game, whether it's Tiny Tower or Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_02]: Realistically, I can see myself playing Tiny Tower for two to three minutes and be satisfied.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's no way I can play it for many hours straight, not even 30 minutes.
[SPEAKER_02]: It won't replace your PS3 or your 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: I kind of like that, kind of calling it out like that, because that's a lot of what I see and I've
[SPEAKER_02]: IOS Gaming versus, you know, playing on the consoles.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's really about that time investment.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a lot of games that just take, like, seconds.
[SPEAKER_02]: Last one from Facebook here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mike B says,
[SPEAKER_02]: I love the thinking, but you have to be living in a fantasy world for Microsoft to suddenly get along with the Apple devices like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But why aren't we seeing that type of stuff with the Windows phones?
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess we are a little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, there is Xbox Live stuff on there, and I think you can even go so far as to earn some achievement points.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know about the whole cross-platform playing, but if the Vita can interface with a PC, I mean, anything else is just a matter of time, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_02]: But as far as Gears of War, hmm.
[SPEAKER_02]: Owner Stephanie Fargo, a gorgeous Amazonian former actress with an uproarious laugh.
[SPEAKER_04]: I found that article too.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, it's Revolution Fitness.
[SPEAKER_02]: So she's a fitness instructor now.
[SPEAKER_10]: That might be her.
[SPEAKER_04]: She didn't look Amazonian in the video there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, she was also sitting down.
[SPEAKER_02]: She might have bulked up if she took a fitness instructor role.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_02]: Carlos M. says, Definitely.
[SPEAKER_02]: I do more gaming on my Zoom tablet than on my PS3 and Wii combined, and my Xbox beats it just because of Dragon Age.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can certainly vouch for the quality of games, not only graphics-wise, but also on their entertainment value.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, if only they'd release a Final Fantasy or Bioware RPG there...
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, to be fair, I just want to get this out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: There are some really good Final Fantasy ports on iPhone, which would be the Final Fantasy 1, 2, and 3, and I believe 3 has an iPad version too.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then there's, I think, Tactics too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mass Effect supposedly has a spin-off game that's on iOS, but my friends that are obsessed with Mass Effect tell me it stinks.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Loki's giving the thumbs down too.
[SPEAKER_02]: here's my favorite comment of them all from Derek H the iPad is a gaming device just like a picture of Bea Arthur as a contraceptive it'll work in an emergency but it should never be your first choice unless you're Deadpool
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: I gotta say, I know as much as you want to... First off, that was a hilarious comment in the beginning, but I will say for the second half of it, video editor...
[SPEAKER_02]: I've, I mean, I wouldn't use it for anything serious, but I took a trip up to like Lake Tahoe and I did like little video and I did it in iMovie and it was really easy and it made a cool, fun little thing to post on Facebook.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like I wouldn't make it much more serious than that, but I was actually really pleased with video editing on the iPhone because it was really super easy.
[SPEAKER_02]: But granted, if I was going to do anything professional, I would do it on a Mac or a PC.
[SPEAKER_02]: Credit card machine.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was at a restaurant the other day.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I saw the waiter taking my order on an iPod.
[SPEAKER_02]: Couldn't believe it.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's where technologies come.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was the same restaurant you were at the other day.
[SPEAKER_02]: You were telling me when you came in here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well something else too is that a friend of mine who used to do drive-by appraisals actually would do them with his iPad mounted on the front of his bike and would basically drive around the house on his bike and take pictures of the home.
[SPEAKER_10]: What a drive-by appraisal is for people who don't know is when a mortgage company hires somebody to go make sure the house is lived in.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: and, of course, it hasn't even quite hit a year yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: That will be March 27th, but close enough, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: By comparison, I guess they said 9 million units of software have been sold and $1.2 billion in revenue it's generated so far.
[SPEAKER_04]: The original DS sold 2.3 million units in its first year.
[SPEAKER_04]: And of course, during February, 200,000 of those are actually, or actually, I'm sorry, it's not 2,000.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, 200,000 systems were moved during February.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Mario Galaxy has sold 5 million units as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's doing pretty well.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Nintendo Wii also sold about 228,000 units.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the 3DS itself, 135.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's still not doing too bad, even though the 3DS is out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Microsoft didn't do too bad as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: They sold almost half a million units for the Xbox 360 and reached the top console spot for 14 consecutive months.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's not bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: The PlayStation Move, they've shipped 10.5 million units.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, as I've mentioned in the past before when they talk about shipping units for the Move, you can't really compare that to the Kinect.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because the Kinect, they've sold, I can't remember how many units for the Kinect.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's quite a bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's actually still more than 10 million units.
[SPEAKER_04]: But...
[SPEAKER_04]: What are they exactly counting for the PlayStation Move?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like the Wii, you can use multiple Move units per system.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are they counting the camera?
[SPEAKER_04]: Are they counting the navigation controller?
[SPEAKER_04]: Any accessories?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just Move units.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can bet the math is as fuzzy as possible.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'd be willing to bet, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, 10.5 million units, that could be significantly less households.
[SPEAKER_02]: And judging by the sales of move-only games, I would guess it's probably... I don't want to sound like a jerk, but I don't think I know anyone in real life that has a PlayStation Move.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know people on the internet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, you do?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do I play with it?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe that's why I don't know anybody, because nobody ever says, let's play Move.
[SPEAKER_04]: it's it's sad because it's not bad it's actually a pretty good peripheral I mean I would prefer to use the move over connect but you know I think for some things to connect is way better like dancing games I think it would be a lot better you know tracking you versus you know the move controller for like core games like um you know shooters and stuff it's probably way better like I would play um what was it uh
[SPEAKER_04]: God, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'd play some of the third-person shooters or whatever, the gun games and stuff, with a move controller versus trying to even remotely do that with a Kinect camera.
[SPEAKER_04]: It just wouldn't be accurate at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: Plus, it has buttons.
[SPEAKER_04]: Buttons are important, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Very important.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, what about the sales figures overall?
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, what do we think this is saying?
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, is the 3DS recovered or whatever?
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, this says to me, yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Wii, though, I can guarantee you that the Wii systems, even 200,000, that's still, I think, on the downturn.
[SPEAKER_04]: Looking at the slate of Wii games coming out, they're kind of done with that system.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, there's a lot of games that aren't getting Wii ports anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just gone.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, this might make Loki sad because I don't know who he's going to make fun of now, but Peter Molyneux has left Microsoft, meaning he's left Lionhead Studios as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ah, yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: His head was too big for the building.
[SPEAKER_02]: He had to leave.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think they had to carve him a new door on the way out.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's left for a startup called 22 Cans.
[SPEAKER_02]: 22 cans.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, 22 cans.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be a direction.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: He did leave some parting words.
[SPEAKER_02]: And his parting words were, quote, It is with mixed emotions that I make the decision to leave Microsoft and Lionhead Studios, the company that I co-founded in 1997, at the conclusion of development of Fable the Journey.
[SPEAKER_02]: I remain extremely passionate and proud of the people, products, and experiences that we created.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not on rails.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, I added the last part, but the rest of it's true.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because it is on rails.
[SPEAKER_02]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is apparently an amicable breakup.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're still Facebook friends, from what I understand.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe sometimes they'll just end up in bed together.
[SPEAKER_02]: They might throw some shade at each other once in a while, but that'll be the extent of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was going to make a game about a little boy named Milo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then Chris Hansen showed up, so now I'm on a limb.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I went to a company called 22 Cans.
[SPEAKER_02]: 22 Cans.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're a porn company.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stop it.
[SPEAKER_04]: 22 cans.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's the people that they have standing out on the street with an empty can saying, put money in me.
[SPEAKER_02]: What level is this show sunken to?
[SPEAKER_02]: Not low enough.
[SPEAKER_10]: Rob, Dana Plato.
[SPEAKER_02]: What you talking about, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_02]: Mailbag at orangelauntrader.com is where you send us emails every week and DarkSakura has to read them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why don't you read the emails from our kind and generous listeners this week?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, OLR, I like you.
[SPEAKER_10]: You're my favorite show ever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't make them up.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi, OLR.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just wanted to say thank you for talking me out of buying Street Fighter Cross Tekken.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was very excited to get it, but after hearing how over a quarter of the complete roster is paid to unlock, I had to say hell no.
[SPEAKER_10]: In fact, I went to GameStop yesterday to pre-order the game, but I got a 3DS instead.
[SPEAKER_10]: I got Mario Kart, so I'm down to play someone.
[SPEAKER_10]: The guy before me was buying a PS3 and Just Dance 3, and I pre-ordered the game as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was at the register next to him, and the lady checking me out asked if I wanted to pre-order any games, and I told her that I wanted to get Street Fighter X Tekken, but went on about how a quarter of the roster was paid to unlock, and the guy was checking out next to me, freaked out.
[SPEAKER_10]: You could totally see the surprise in his eyes when I blurted that out.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm sure she was pissed that I might have talked the guy out of a sale, oh well.
[SPEAKER_10]: But yeah, that's just nuts.
[SPEAKER_10]: 12 characters, probably $5 a piece to buy would mean that'd be $60, which is the cost of a game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Are you telling me that I'd have to shell out the same amount of money in order to get the full experience?
[SPEAKER_10]: There's a big link on there.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm not gonna relink.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is why they did it to save on hard drive space.
[SPEAKER_10]: But they didn't explain when they'd be unlocked, and I'm guessing $3 to $5 a piece, which is still too much.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sure, they did that with Jill and Shu McGrath in the two Marvel vs. Capcom 3 games, but that's just for two characters.
[SPEAKER_10]: If all 12 characters were available in a bundle for like $10, then I'll stop bitching.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I doubt that'll happen.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, I also thought it was funny that the PS3 exclusive characters can also be found on the Xbox version.
[SPEAKER_10]: Their files were found in the disc, so if anyone is good at hacking, you might be able to play as cool on the Xbox.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, that's it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thanks for reading this.
[SPEAKER_10]: I look forward to your 10th-iversary, Stan.
[SPEAKER_10]: And also, the reason why they're probably on the disc is because it's the same information just ported
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yeah, it's kind of lazy porting in a way.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I know that sounds really harsh, but it kind of is what it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: The other thing I want to say about that, it's kind of scary that we kind of talked not one, but two people out of buying the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not what we set out to do.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, I'm not trying to discourage people from buying the game because, you know, again, there's fighting game fans out there that are going to eat this up.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's your money.
[SPEAKER_02]: Buy what you want.
[SPEAKER_02]: but um you know we're all about people making informed decisions and it sounds like that's what happened in this case is that people kind of realized like wait a minute I'm gonna have to pay $60 and then if I want everything I have to pay 60 more dollars maybe only to see a super uber collection at the end of the year I I kind of talked myself out of it with that same logic I think that's why I asked Loki earlier what did the sales look like for this game because I want to see if it's just more than the three of us now that we're up to anyhow
[SPEAKER_10]: Next email.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dear Orange Lounge Radio, let me say first you guys and lady are amazing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Between Loki's rants of rage and DarkSakura and Sky's epic trolls, you make a three hour podcast very entertaining.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not a troll.
[SPEAKER_10]: Epic trolls.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not an epic troll.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not that you are a troll, it's that you have done trolling.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was trolling you for compliments.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bitch.
[SPEAKER_02]: Girl, please.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now, granted, I haven't listened to you guys from the beginning mostly because I was 10 when you guys started.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_02]: But for the past three years... Emailers, I totally appreciate your emails.
[SPEAKER_02]: Please don't say that ever again.
[SPEAKER_10]: But for the past three years, you guys have taught me about old school games, system hackings, and other stuff I can't think of off the top of my head.
[SPEAKER_10]: You guys can make a long car drive seem shorter, a boring day entertaining, and a regular guy seem crazy because he can't stop laughing in the middle of class.
[SPEAKER_10]: I hope you guys keep podcasting, really enjoy the show, signed Haseo Sumiragawa.
[SPEAKER_10]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_10]: If there are trophy whores listening to this show, you can add me on P.S.N.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's Haseo underscore Sumiragawa.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello, Hellions!
[SPEAKER_10]: What?
What?
[SPEAKER_10]: Being that China is an emerging market, not just in video games, but also in different aspects of our modern day economy, it makes sense that Blizzard would tailor make something for the Chinese public.
[SPEAKER_10]: This also makes me think of the possibilities that could happen if Blizzard decides to tailor make something to any other emerging markets.
[SPEAKER_10]: Finally, one of the possibilities began to take tangible shape in my mind.
[SPEAKER_10]: Behold, the Jersey Darians.
[SPEAKER_10]: Lord.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is funny now.
[SPEAKER_10]: Coming from the mythical realm of Shortopia.
[SPEAKER_10]: Smush, smush.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know what that means.
[SPEAKER_10]: The Jersey Darians are an orange race whose clothes, hair, and muscular definitions appeal mostly to people of their own race.
[SPEAKER_10]: The Jersey Darians are not a smart race, but just try telling them that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Criticizing a Jersey Darian may result in you getting your teeth punched in by an orange troll whose over-stylized hair makes up for the bulk of their height.
[SPEAKER_02]: One of them's pregnant, you know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I didn't need to know that.
[SPEAKER_10]: It just made my life hurt.
[SPEAKER_10]: Other possibilities for expansion packs for the emerging markets include, for the English, the Cockney Darians, for the Irish, the U2 Darians, for the Somalians, the not Jack Sparrow Pyro Darians, and for Utah, the Conservative Control Freaky Darians.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just thought of the best argument ever for gay marriage or, you know, equal marriage because there's really no such thing as gay marriage but I have the best argument ever I can't get married but Snooki can just think about that for a minute
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the country we live in, folks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rick Santorum wants Snooki to get married.
But not me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello, OLR crew.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was something else that email wanted to say.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, the Pandarian thing in China.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've talked about this on The Best Little Horde House in Azeroth, a show all about the world of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_02]: www.hordehouse.com Wink.
[SPEAKER_02]: um we talked a little bit about this and actually I don't think the claim is as far-fetched as some think it's ironic because there was a time when people were saying it can't be Pandaria they're not going to do Pandaria because there's laws in China against panda people like you can't that's defacing pandas and da da da da da da da
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think what you're saying is too far-fetched.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's kind of a win-win situation for Blizzard because, yes, they can do a very respectful thing for the Chinese culture.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, you know, here in the States and other countries like Canada and UK and so forth, we kind of like that culture.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a lot of people that are like, you know, pandas are cute.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, you know, they like the architecture and all that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it makes sense.
[SPEAKER_10]: I still forgot to reserve the name Orange Chicken.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello, all our crew.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ooh, to DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_10]: While I do respect you preferring the Japanese... Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_10]: The Japanese Sonic CD soundtrack, I must side with Bobby Blackwolf and claim the U.S.
[SPEAKER_10]: soundtrack is superior.
[SPEAKER_10]: Again, your opinion.
[SPEAKER_10]: Despite the fact that Sonic CDs... Where every gamer has a voice, a really... That's why I'm pointing out an opinion.
[SPEAKER_02]: A really wrong voice.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just got the hand.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, that was a high five.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought you were making me talk to that.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I was giving you a high five.
[SPEAKER_10]: Despite the fact that Sonic CD's musics have a style different from the other Sonic games for its time, at least to me anyway, the Japanese music sounds very cheesy.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's way too upbeat and has some hammy voice samples that are out of place.
[SPEAKER_10]: I believe the US tunes composed by Spencer Nielsen do a fantastic job of fitting in with the atmosphere of each level, even if it sounds a little new agey at times.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, that's kind of why I have a problem with it.
[SPEAKER_10]: It doesn't sound like Sonic music.
[SPEAKER_10]: Here's a question for the whole OLR crew.
[SPEAKER_10]: What are some of the best deals that you've had for video game or video game hardware?
[SPEAKER_10]: For me, I've recently had a Circuit City Tiger Direct Honor, an erroneous $40 price tag for a 32GB PlayStation Vita memory card.
[SPEAKER_02]: I literally just bought Mass Effect for $11.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought that was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is also by Full Brazilian.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love that name so much.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's the most that's ever been shaved off a price for you?
[SPEAKER_10]: I know one on Dan's behalf where he traded his Sega CD for a Neo Geo and games.
[SPEAKER_02]: What about Steam?
[SPEAKER_02]: Like anything on Steam?
[SPEAKER_10]: I bought like every Doom game ever for $3.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know there's a lot of good deals there.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I randomly get free games from people.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got my Dreamcast for $40. $40.
[SPEAKER_02]: Amazing deal.
[SPEAKER_02]: Those things are still fucking rad to have.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dreamcast Twin Sticks for Oratario Tangram.
[SPEAKER_10]: We paid $45 for them.
[SPEAKER_10]: They were going eBay for like $500.
[SPEAKER_04]: I won my Dreamcast at a QZAR all-nighter.
[SPEAKER_10]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, we've gotten...
[SPEAKER_10]: Our first model PlayStation when they were still going for $700.
[SPEAKER_10]: We got $100 back from Discover.
[SPEAKER_02]: $700 for that first PlayStation?
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess they were about that much in the beginning, weren't they?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, but we got $100 back from Discover.
[SPEAKER_10]: And Dan got his manager's discount on it.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I guess that's kind of good.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it still works.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it still plays all of our old stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: So next email.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, please.
[SPEAKER_02]: How many more emails?
[SPEAKER_10]: Three.
[SPEAKER_10]: Geez!
[SPEAKER_10]: I know!
[SPEAKER_02]: It's alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Every gamer gets a voice.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's why the show is three and a half hours long.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi, OLR.
[SPEAKER_10]: A couple weeks ago, DarkSakura did a classic game of the week, which inspired me to get the game for my iPod Touch.
[SPEAKER_10]: More specifically, Puzzle Bobble, a.k.a.
[SPEAKER_10]: Bust a Move.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was well worth the $5 I spent to get it.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's very addicting and is full of awesomeness.
[SPEAKER_10]: Keep up the good work.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sincerely, Vince Raven.
[SPEAKER_10]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_10]: Make sure everyone votes for President Cat in the elections.
[SPEAKER_10]: LOLXD.
[SPEAKER_02]: LOL.
[SPEAKER_10]: If President Cat was running for Republican, then I think everybody else would not make it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was trying to read if there was a question.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got distracted.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, there was no question.
[SPEAKER_02]: Somebody sent me naked photos of one of the people from Glee.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I was like, oh, I want to see that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then I wasn't listening to the... Female or male?
[SPEAKER_02]: Female.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, who?
[SPEAKER_02]: It was... It's a video game podcast, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: It was just thanking me for referring... What?
[SPEAKER_10]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Back to video games.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Is that vag in the background?
[SPEAKER_02]: It might be.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was a mirror.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you see, Jamie, women have a vagina.
[SPEAKER_10]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_10]: And so do you.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're a bitch.
[SPEAKER_02]: Read an email.
[SPEAKER_10]: Love you, mean it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Greetings, OLR.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's your friendly neighborhood turtle.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just heard that Diablo 3 is now removing PvP to speed up their release time.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm getting real tired of companies.
[SPEAKER_10]: It should be really tired.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry, what was the question?
[SPEAKER_10]: Girl.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's talking about the Diablo 3 removing the PvP and saying tired of games.
[SPEAKER_10]: Right.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, coming out with stuff that's going to be DLC later.
[SPEAKER_10]: And people having to pay for it.
[SPEAKER_10]: But they say they're not going to charge for it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, but I think it's still the, you mean it's not going to have everything on it?
[SPEAKER_10]: Meh.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm okay with it because I don't want to wait nine more months for the game to come out.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like waiting for a baby.
[SPEAKER_02]: How long have we been waiting for Diablo 3?
[SPEAKER_02]: And PvP was not one of the elements I personally cared about as much.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll play it later when they patch it in, but I don't need it right away.
[SPEAKER_10]: It is like waiting for a baby without the indigestion.
[SPEAKER_02]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_10]: I totally agree with the fact that gamers don't want to work for unlocks anymore i.e.
[SPEAKER_10]: Tekken 6 and Soul Calibur 5 everything is there to use right away and the modes are rather lacking the good old days of gaming are dwindling folks
[SPEAKER_10]: Agreed.
[SPEAKER_10]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or at least that's all I'm going to read.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mailbag at orangelaundry.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: It sounds like Jamie sadly had to cut a few out tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I didn't.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just said if any more arrived, I wasn't going to read them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Until next week.
[SPEAKER_02]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki will read them next week.
[SPEAKER_10]: That would be funny if Loki read them.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's done them before when you're not here.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know, but while I was here.
[SPEAKER_02]: The mailbag?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is the part of the show where we get angsty because... because...
[SPEAKER_10]: Upity male bitches.
[SPEAKER_10]: F you to uppity male bitches.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey!
[SPEAKER_10]: Not you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's, okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have a friend.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I know where this is going.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know where this is going.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know absolutely where this is going.
[SPEAKER_02]: I already know, you didn't even have to say it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who occasionally acts like a stereotypical hysterical woman.
[SPEAKER_10]: And doesn't admit.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it's Nathan Lane in the birdcage.
[SPEAKER_10]: and doesn't ever admit, well, except for this time, when said person has done something wrong or, you know, gives the roundabout, passive-aggressive type of apology, you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I'm sorry you feel that way.
[SPEAKER_10]: and I'm getting kind of sick of it and I'm getting sick of just that sense of entitlement so but you know what we talked it out things are better I hope that said person watches it but I really got so pissed off that I I haven't been this angry in a long time I got so pissed off I burped
[SPEAKER_02]: She's not lying.
[SPEAKER_02]: She sent me a message and wow, girl, I just burped.
[SPEAKER_02]: I am so angry.
[SPEAKER_02]: I burped.
[SPEAKER_10]: I threw up in my mouth.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was awful.
[SPEAKER_10]: And the place I didn't want to do it either.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was at synagogue.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was sick and had to leave.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was so mad.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was awful.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_10]: Girl, F you to Rob.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sounded like you were done.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I have one more.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now I forgot what it was.
[SPEAKER_10]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: F you to Daylight Savings Time, you whore.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who were?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because, okay, last time I went to the Jewish Film Festival, I come home at like 1 and sit down to, you know, check all my email and everything.
[SPEAKER_10]: I look at the clock, next thing I know it's 3 because boom, time skip.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then I'm not in bed until like after 4 because I had all this crap to do that I thought I still had another hour to do because I forgot about it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki!
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck you to the donut shop in Folsom for not having the baking maple donuts.
[SPEAKER_04]: You sold out of them at what, like 10 in the morning?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, seriously, that is just ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not a single donut.
[SPEAKER_04]: You would think that they would be popular and you'd make a ton of them.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, that's my thought.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's just unfair.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Any more?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because you know what happens if I cut someone off.
[SPEAKER_02]: My FU of the week goes to Daylight Savings Time as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which is a dirty whore.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've had two cups of coffee today to compensate.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not one!
[SPEAKER_02]: Two cups of coffee.
[SPEAKER_10]: I did two, thanks to you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, fuck, I had three.
[SPEAKER_10]: I need to catch up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Otherwise, I had a really crazy week last week, but a lot of good news and a lot of I don't really feel one way or the other about it news.
[SPEAKER_02]: When it rains, it pours.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's not necessarily an FU, but it's just, damn, I'm going to be busy.
[SPEAKER_02]: FU to the fact that there aren't more hours in the day.
[SPEAKER_02]: In fact, there's one less, thanks to Daylight Savings Time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did I say FU to Daylight Savings Time?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I really mean it.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: I think I can back you up in that completely because fuck it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Good, because I'm right.
[SPEAKER_10]: I like more night time.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want night time savings time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's go to some more news before we get to your calls.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, the 800 number works again this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's good, but we have a few more stories first.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's talk a little bit about hopefully not anything I was looking up there.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't need to talk about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: More boobs?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it's the same boobs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's talk about Valve.
[SPEAKER_04]: They, of course, came out and debunked the whole Steam Box debacle thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everyone was conspiring that they were making some sort of console, and of course, that's not the case.
[SPEAKER_04]: What they were doing, though, is they were making test boxes to test out their big picture initiative, which is basically developing an interface for Steam that looks nice on TV displays.
[SPEAKER_04]: so that's what those boxes were being used for not necessarily a game console but I mean if you think about it likely story no it actually does sound like a likely story so um you know if you think about it though I mean that kind of setup you could use a pc next to your hooked up to your tv and kind of treat it like a game box you know or something like that I don't know all right
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, are you bummed out with this news?
[SPEAKER_02]: Were you hoping for a Steam box?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I didn't really care.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't have a Steam account.
[SPEAKER_02]: Really?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's surprising.
[SPEAKER_02]: It would have been neat, but it's not the end of the world.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's still going to be a really good service for the PC, so...
[SPEAKER_02]: I still think I'm right on the Half-Life 3 thing, though, so that means there's not going to be Half-Life 3 until this Steam Box is ready, years and years away.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, maybe I'm trolling a little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not trolling as much as Adidas is, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, you know Adidas, the sporting company?
[SPEAKER_02]: I know we don't talk about them a lot with games, but THQ has been sued.
[SPEAKER_02]: I believe it's my coach.
[SPEAKER_02]: MyCoach247 got canned.
[SPEAKER_02]: THQ told Adidas in December that it would not be able to present the product and developers who were working on the project were laid off.
[SPEAKER_02]: So maybe this was one of those things.
[SPEAKER_02]: We heard about the layoffs of THQ.
[SPEAKER_02]: This was one of those things that was affected.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Adidas isn't happy.
[SPEAKER_02]: So they won $10.6 million in damages.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's all scary similar to that Beyonce lawsuit we heard about where they got sued over the canceled Beyonce game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, that wasn't THQ.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was somebody else.
[SPEAKER_02]: But anyway, THQ is refusing to turn over the publishing materials to an alternative developer.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's probably not good if that's true.
[SPEAKER_02]: Allegedly.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's all allegedly.
[SPEAKER_02]: Adidas is seeking an injunction preventing THQ from selling or transferring the rights to another company.
[SPEAKER_02]: So maybe this was something they were trying to sell off to get some of the money back.
[SPEAKER_02]: But nope, Adidas won't have it, and they're going to have to duke this out in a court of law.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hopefully, Judge Judy.
[SPEAKER_02]: But probably not.
[SPEAKER_02]: It'll get settled, as they always do.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, DarkSakura, we need something better.
[SPEAKER_02]: We need some more warm, fuzzy news.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I'm all for like... Okay, how about Samurai Yeti and Ninja Werewolves?
[SPEAKER_10]: There's a teacher, whose name is Ben Bertoli, he's a 6th grade teacher, who turned his classroom into an MMO.
[SPEAKER_10]: Basically, he set up an experience system and achievements for doing certain things in conjunction with his class, even giving out extra experience for when people turned in extra credit essays and stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: The students are actually helping him remember to keep track of everyone's experience on a tracking board.
[SPEAKER_10]: Don't talk about Class Realm.
[SPEAKER_10]: is completely voluntary.
[SPEAKER_10]: XP is the backbone of Class Realm.
[SPEAKER_10]: Every 10 XP you earn pushes you to the next level.
[SPEAKER_10]: Everyone starts off at level one.
[SPEAKER_10]: XP can be obtained by doing simple things as answering questions, joining in class discussion, working hard on an assignment, helping others, participation, random encounter Friday, and gaining achievements.
[SPEAKER_02]: Random encounter Friday is when he lets a wild boar loose in the classroom.
[SPEAKER_10]: 4.
[SPEAKER_10]: Achievements are gained by completing specific tasks.
[SPEAKER_10]: For example, a student can obtain Bookworm by reading two unassigned chapter books and explaining the plot and characters to me.
[SPEAKER_10]: Each achievement has four levels, Bronze, Silver, Gold, and Master.
[SPEAKER_10]: Each level is harder to reach than the one before it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Boys are pitted against girls.
[SPEAKER_10]: The gender that can acquire the most achievements by the end of the year will earn extra recess and an ice cream party during lunch.
[SPEAKER_10]: each Friday is random here's the secret because it's the sixth grade everybody will win the ice cream party so you don't even have to try because that's how these things work hush everyone who wants to battle will put their name in a hat I will draw out two names and they will battle students will be asked a question oh my god it's battle royale shut up
[SPEAKER_10]: I will repeat the question twice and start battle music The first to write the correct answer on the board and put their hands up will win XP You can only answer once Question subjects are chosen at random Students may join in alliances of up to six classroom citizens The alliance with the highest combined level at the end of the year wins a pizza party All info except for the current amount of XP each student has will be listed online and in the classroom for students and parents to see
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, apparently, it's been a big hit.
[SPEAKER_10]: And everyone's been super enthusiastic and really trying to participate in it.
[SPEAKER_10]: In fact, there's one he called the Newbery Achievement that's based off the Newbery Medal.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's earned by writing an unassigned five-paragraph essay.
[SPEAKER_10]: And he had 20 essays turned into him in the first week.
[SPEAKER_10]: that are written during students' free time outside of their other work.
[SPEAKER_10]: So apparently this is really popular.
[SPEAKER_10]: The kids like it and they're learning with it.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Little Sally, Little Jimmy, you've been called into battle.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't want to battle!
[SPEAKER_10]: Rob, for real.
[SPEAKER_10]: If it's getting kids to actually participate in school and enjoy learning, I think it's a great thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: In all seriousness, it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know I have to fuck with it because that's what I do here.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not that dissimilar from stuff even I experienced when I was that age.
[SPEAKER_02]: A long time ago, back when some of our listeners weren't even born.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I remember in the seventh grade, our science teacher used to have these meters that would fill up with time.
[SPEAKER_02]: And as we answered questions correctly or volunteered to do things or do extra work, we would move up the ladder a little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: When you get to the top, you got a free day.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was like a free day in the class, you know, like no work, no nothing.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was just like, you know, screw off day or study lab or whatever, which, you know, was kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's kind of a similar thing, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: You gain experience.
[SPEAKER_02]: I remember in the fifth grade, we had a whole little like village with its own economy because I remember one thing I did.
[SPEAKER_02]: I ran a shop that rented Nintendo games in my fifth grade class.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I would rent games to, you know, my classmates for like 10 of the fake bucks that were named after the teacher.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that was like my business.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shroop Bucks.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I just don't, you know, I don't want to.
[SPEAKER_02]: But no, that wasn't the name.
[SPEAKER_02]: But yeah, same idea.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the whole battle thing is just really funny to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't help but think of Hunger Games.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what everybody's all talking about right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't give a crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: So.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, at any rate, I say good for you, and he's apparently a regular reader and commenter on Kotaku, so the news is just really catching fire.
[SPEAKER_10]: I really hope that it's actually something that he can market for other schools.
[SPEAKER_02]: I see what you did there, catching fire.
[SPEAKER_02]: Never mind.
[SPEAKER_10]: What, don't stand in fire?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, this is the Hunger Games reference.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Hunger Games sequel is catching fire.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't give a shit about Hunger Games.
[SPEAKER_10]: The only thing I've ever heard of it is the name.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know anything about it.
[SPEAKER_10]: And guess who doesn't want to know anything about it?
[SPEAKER_10]: That would be me.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_10]: End of story.
[SPEAKER_10]: Don't care.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're hungry.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's about a bunch of hippos and they're really hungry.
[SPEAKER_12]: Do you know what that sound is?
[SPEAKER_10]: What?
[SPEAKER_10]: That's my head repeatedly hitting the microphone as I bang it into it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've successfully derailed the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, help us get back on track and then we'll open up the Skype line at 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_02]: TigerClaw says, I wonder what Rob was like when kids didn't return the Nintendo games on time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Were you mean to them?
[SPEAKER_02]: Nope, just one finger for each day late.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is how we roll.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right.
[SPEAKER_04]: So Tony Hawk, um,
[SPEAKER_04]: He's a little sad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sad, Tony Hawk.
[SPEAKER_04]: He says that Ride was a bit rushed and that people didn't give it a chance.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really, you should try Tony Hawk's Ride.
[SPEAKER_04]: Give it a chance.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because the game may have been a little rushed and the critics didn't like it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, that didn't stop them from creating a sequel that I would assume wouldn't have been as rushed because, you know, they would have had a whole year to polish it, but still sucked.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I don't see the logic there, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, it was rushed.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's quoted, I think Ride was a bit rushed for a number of reasons, mostly because probably for about the first half of the development process, it was just figuring out how to make a board and how to make it work.
[SPEAKER_04]: We were in uncharted territory.
[SPEAKER_04]: So the game was a bit rushed, but I still feel critics never really gave it a chance in terms of learning how to play.
[SPEAKER_04]: They got on it, and they went straight into expert mode because supposedly they were expert gamers, and they didn't really learn the mechanics of how the board works.
[SPEAKER_04]: And so I felt like already in their mind, they'd made up their decision before it came out.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was a gimmick, and it was a peripheral and whatnot, and they never really took the time to learn how to play it.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: You have no excuses, Tony Hawk.
[SPEAKER_04]: The game sucked.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was terrible.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was a dumb idea because Activision thought, hey, we're going to cash in on all these peripheral games because we made money on DJ Hero.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, I think DJ Hero came out around the same time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, we made money on Guitar Hero, so we're going to put out this peripheral game because people like peripherals.
[SPEAKER_04]: It makes them more interactive.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it just didn't work out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Get over it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, one more story for you guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then we're going to open up the phones at 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is about a little bit of resolution.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just reported on some legal troubles in one area, but this is about...
[SPEAKER_02]: Resolution to one lawsuit that was going to happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: This was between Bethesda and Mojang.
[SPEAKER_02]: You might remember this.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was over the name Scrolls.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember?
[SPEAKER_02]: Bethesda felt that the name Scrolls was infringing on its trademark for Elder Scrolls.
[SPEAKER_02]: And people might get confused.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just like when I reviewed Journey earlier in the show, I had to clarify that it's not the one about the 1980s band, you know, because the games are so similar once you've played them.
[SPEAKER_02]: But anyhow...
[SPEAKER_02]: There were some tweets.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love that official statements come from tweets now.
[SPEAKER_02]: That they have settled with yay heart.
[SPEAKER_02]: The settlement is that we give them the trademark.
[SPEAKER_02]: We get to keep the name and won't make an Elder Scrolls competitor using the name.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the settlement.
[SPEAKER_02]: Usually you don't get to hear about the details of the settlement.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just glad no finance stuff were changed or whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: They don't get to have a trademark on Scrolls, but Bethesda will leave them alone as long as they don't try to infringe on epic epicness of first-person role-playing games, which I don't think Scrolls was supposed to be.
[SPEAKER_02]: there you go fantastic fantastic
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, so we are going to open up the Skype line, 1-877-GAME-OLR, or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, oh, we're already getting calls.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, by the way, we will go to the Twitter here, also twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_02]: But first we have some calls coming in.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_02]: This is Shane.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, Shane, it's my co-host from Horde House.
[SPEAKER_07]: It sure isn't.
[SPEAKER_02]: What do you mean?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, you are.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're on that show.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh yeah, I guess I am sometimes.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right, except this week you could only talk about Mass Effect, which by the way, screw you.
[SPEAKER_02]: I bought Mass Effect this week, which was kind of like peer pressure in a way, and you do that a lot, and I kind of despise you for it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's kind of because I blew up your phone about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: You really did, my god.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hope you have unlimited texting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who is Kaiden, and why is Shane in love with him?
[SPEAKER_07]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_07]: What are you calling in for tonight?
[SPEAKER_07]: I was calling because I want to talk about something I don't normally talk about.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_07]: Mass Effect.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course!
[SPEAKER_02]: I've never heard you talk about Mass Effect before.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are you here to monopolize the show with Mass Effect chat just like you did on Horde House this week?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, what's up?
[SPEAKER_07]: I wanted to not talk about the story so much or how awesome the game is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't spoil it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't talk about that ending that everybody's petitioning.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know about the ending yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have not beat the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you hear that people are petitioning BioWare to change the ending?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's apparently that bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I'm kind of scared.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't want it to end so I don't get disappointed.
[SPEAKER_07]: But anyway, that's not what I'm talking about.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm talking about how much respect I have for BioWare now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, because this is the first game I have ever played in which I feel like they did not take any stereotypes seriously.
[SPEAKER_07]: and put them into their gay characters not a single one and I think they actually humanized them instead of using them for comic relief or something to just flirt with or hook up with what about Dragon Age?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, Dragon Age is totally terrible with that stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Zevran in the first game, especially.
[SPEAKER_07]: But in this game, I feel like they're just normal people who happen to be gay, and I don't see that in games.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it really, really makes me feel like BioWare is a company I should support more often.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not sure what else I can really say to that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have you only explored the male-male relationships in that game or have you looked into how it compares to male-female or female-female?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, and I'm only going to say it's for three because I've seen stuff on one where it was pretty, I think I described it at work, skanky.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, sometimes relationships are skanky.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, but I wanted something more, and this game has given it to me.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've only seen male-male, and actually the one I romance technically isn't gay, but it's just because I couldn't resist his charms.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I won't say who, because that could be a spoiler, I guess, but really, romancing people isn't a spoiler.
[SPEAKER_02]: I found it interesting because I asked you in an email this week when you wouldn't shut up about the game, I asked you what kind of different relationship options were available and it seemed like the people that choose to play FemShep who want to be in a relationship with a male, so an opposite sex relationship but with a female lead, was the most limited.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, in three at least it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: I found that to be kind of sad because, you know, I'm sure there's a lot of ladies out there that would like to romance some men in their games and they don't really get that option in this game.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, they get to romance ice cream tubs now instead because they're sad.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is very sad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, maybe DLC.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess you never know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is there a possibility they're going to add more romance options in later on?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I wouldn't imagine so because the first DLC character is...
[SPEAKER_07]: Not Romanceable, to my knowledge, and it'd be really awkward if they were.
[SPEAKER_07]: But you never know.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's Bioware.
[SPEAKER_07]: They can do whatever they want and do it right, apparently.
[SPEAKER_07]: But also, that game's amazing, and I have cried three times during it so far now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Three.
[SPEAKER_07]: It has beaten the previous game's record.
[SPEAKER_02]: What was the previous game before that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Suikoden II.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was twice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Twice.
[SPEAKER_02]: So just to kind of go back to the main point of the call, because, you know, to wrap up soon and all that, why is this so important to you?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because it's something I can relate to.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, I don't want to relate to, like, the skanky options that people would have before.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want, you know, a really nice story, and that's what I'm getting.
[SPEAKER_02]: What would you say to people who say, why does Bioware have to put gay stuff in every game?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because they want to give more options to everybody.
[SPEAKER_07]: That is what I would say.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god, did somebody get shot in the background?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, that is a washer being...
[SPEAKER_02]: Somebody just shot you for your opinion.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's really unfortunate.
[SPEAKER_02]: What a hideous place we live in.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are you okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: Are you still there?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I'm still here.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just trying to do another conversation at the same time.
[SPEAKER_02]: That works out great.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I guess, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, one thing I've sensed, even just from playing the first game before, not even talking about relationships or whatever, is that I do notice there's so many options in the conversation and so forth to play the game in many different ways.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's something I kind of noticed in Star Wars, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although in Star Wars, the paths were very well lit.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, that's another thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm glad you kind of said something about the choices and the paths.
[SPEAKER_07]: The one I took with the character I romanced in 3 for Mass Effect, it wasn't like we were having a normal dialogue conversation, then bam, here's a hook up with you option or a not hook up with you option.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was something that just kind of evolved naturally.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it actually kind of came out of nowhere in my opinion, but not in like a...
[SPEAKER_02]: You alright?
[SPEAKER_02]: He cut out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh no, I'm back.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry, I hit the wrong button.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was nice.
[SPEAKER_07]: It just kind of went natural, and I didn't have to pick skanky stuff to get there.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's one thing that some people, I guess, might misinterpret, is that there's not the option, like, you know, it isn't on the menu, like...
[SPEAKER_02]: What should we do now?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, well, let's go kill aliens, or let's do research on the next mission, or let's go upstairs and fuck like rabbits.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not like how it plays out.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, it's nothing like that at all.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like, I'm not, okay, gotta try to do this not spoilery and kind of be general.
[SPEAKER_07]: Something happens that's major, and then, well, if you've played Mass Effect, you can do missions, and then one of your home base of operations is the Citadel.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's not a spoiler.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's always around.
[SPEAKER_07]: So you do some missions and then something happens and then you can, you know, run around the Citadel and we just happen to have a friendly lunch conversation that turned into us going out all of a sudden in a really, really nicely written scene.
[SPEAKER_07]: and what's cool about that too is the actual gay guy in the game I was doing some conversations with him and he said something about looking at some eye candy and one of my options were no I'm interested in women and the other one was like well what about me and I picked up well what about me because I didn't want to screw up what I had already done and he's like well yeah of course I'm looking at you but I know you're with so and so so it's like oh crap the game actually knows the choices I've made and it's like commenting on them
[SPEAKER_07]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, I guess I'm going to have to hurry up and play one and two so I can see more of this in action in three because one's still kind of basic, but I just started.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, we gotta let you go to get more calls.
[SPEAKER_02]: Any other quick thoughts here before we let you go?
[SPEAKER_07]: Nope, nope.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, also the multiplayer is really fun, so sadly it's part of the experience to get the best ending from what I understand, but I played it for two hours straight today and had a blast, so I suggest people at least give it a shot.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, there you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for calling, Shane.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you, bye.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_02]: So two questions there.
[SPEAKER_02]: How do you guys stay motivated each week to do a show?
[SPEAKER_02]: That question was asked a couple days ago.
[SPEAKER_10]: Coffee.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've been thinking about that question.
[SPEAKER_02]: I honestly don't know if I have an answer.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know what keeps me motivated to do this show.
[SPEAKER_02]: The people, obviously.
[SPEAKER_02]: Seeing you guys come out and chat and support what we're doing here is a huge motivator.
[SPEAKER_02]: Getting to hang with Matt and Jamie and knowing that we're creating this thing on the internet that even if it's just two or three people that enjoy it, people are enjoying it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Coffee.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a huge motivator.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pinkberry.
[SPEAKER_10]: Pinkberry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Coffee, Pinkberry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are both very big motivators, certainly.
[SPEAKER_10]: And my own ego.
[SPEAKER_02]: And like the phone line is lighting up right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Look at that.
[SPEAKER_02]: My screen is like full of like rings right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's a huge motivator as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: And they're all names I recognize.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's go to another call and see who's on the line.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, what's up?
[SPEAKER_05]: This is X-Link.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, how you doing?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, doing well.
[SPEAKER_05]: Long time.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know, it has been a while.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, it's just kind of ironic, not to talk about Mass Effect 3, because I haven't played it myself.
[SPEAKER_05]: I did play the first two.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just love how they did do the stuff, though, from the choices you make in your first game can affect a lot of outcomes in the second game.
[SPEAKER_05]: and how I supposedly guess how the stuff in the first and second can also impact the third.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like how they added that kind of like a continuous storyline.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it's not like you're replaying something over and over and over again that's brand new for a three-part series.
[SPEAKER_05]: I kind of like the fact that how
[SPEAKER_05]: Everything can have a pro or con effect to something else within the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the entire reason I started with 1, because I will tell you, I was tempted to just jump ahead to 3, but I didn't.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, it's really cool to know the fact that they took the inventory system and made it better and more flowed and more easy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank God, because in 1, it's a bit of a nightmare.
[SPEAKER_05]: From 1 to 2, because 1 and 2 is so night and day, and the controlling was too.
[SPEAKER_05]: I played 1, and then there was a big gap between me playing 1 and Part 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm like,
[SPEAKER_05]: Am I doing this right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Is this the right way?
[SPEAKER_05]: Why does this feel like it's changed so much?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's kind of weird, but you get used to it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not too much, though, within the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: So what else have you been playing lately?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because you're not playing Mass Effect 3, but what are you playing these days?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well...
[SPEAKER_05]: Other than WoW, L.A.
[SPEAKER_05]: North.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know me, I'm a human whore.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm also such as for the Xbox, so right now I'm like
[SPEAKER_05]: My gamer ADD is so bad, I have only ever got every single possible achievement in one game.
[SPEAKER_05]: For my first one, my first one was Assassin's Creed.
[SPEAKER_02]: and that was a bitch mine you would never guess my perfect achievement game the only one is Rally-X on Xbox Live Arcade new Rally-X the remake because I used to legit love that game back in the day when I was a kid and so I'm pretty decent at it but yeah that's the only one yeah I thought my second one was going to be Uno but yeah some people can really mess you up in that game so still to this day so that's kind of intriguing so hmm
[SPEAKER_05]: Play Rusty Hearts 2, which is an awesome game.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you like WoW, I strongly suggest joining up with me whenever you see me on Steam, Rob, because we're friends.
[SPEAKER_05]: Play some Rusty Hearts with me, man.
[SPEAKER_05]: You'll like it, trust me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is this a free game, or is this like a pay one, or what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_05]: Free to play.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's absolutely awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can actually, believe it or not, I made my own little guild within the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's how cool this thing is.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's pretty much sky's the limit, and it's like
[SPEAKER_05]: How do you explain it?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like WoW type, but also it's like when you're running through the dungeons, it's more feeling like a first-person scroll, like you're going from room to room kind of like, and you're being off on stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the way, if you see him being played, it's really cool, so...
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, X-Link, any other quick shout-outs you want to get out before we get more calls?
[SPEAKER_05]: Not really at this moment, but also they need to quit putting the disc DLC within the disc and stuff and then charging double the money for that of the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's getting ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_05]: They really need to quit on that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I understand they're trying to make some extra money, but it's really seriously getting out of hand.
[SPEAKER_05]: I agree with a lot of people on that subject.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's gone too far.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Excellent.
[SPEAKER_02]: You take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Enjoy the various games.
[SPEAKER_02]: And one of these days I'll catch up in Mass Effect.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, absolutely.
[SPEAKER_05]: Quit playing Tying Tower.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do so.
[SPEAKER_05]: You'll love it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll try.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Alan makes me check on my tower.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm like, I don't want to play.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's like, show me the people in your tower.
[SPEAKER_02]: Show me the people in your tower.
[SPEAKER_05]: Probably said that way you can play Mass Effect.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then soon if, you know, what was said earlier.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did we get to that earlier?
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought we were going to talk about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I missed half of your show, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm running Dragon's Soul with my new guild, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_05]: The guild master put me in charge of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's like, oh, here you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're running this team.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm like, uh, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you're running it in the weekends.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm like, oh, gravy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I got to lead a raid this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we're going to talk all about it on Horde House this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sounds awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: We should swap notes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, man.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll talk to you later.
[SPEAKER_02]: I haven't done a raid since everyone stopped playing on our server I'm sorry, I just went where there was a lot of people I picked based on the times, it was all the times They were like, we raid this and this day from this and this time I'm like, great, that works for my schedule, let's do it Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio, who's this?
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi, this is Actdeft Hey, Actdeft, how you doing?
[SPEAKER_08]: Pretty fine, pretty good What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I know Jamie is already tired about the Sonic CD soundtrack thing, but... She's gonna go to the bathroom, I'll be back when you're done.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let him have his voice.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, okay, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_08]: Go ahead.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, I like both soundtracks, both the Japanese and the American one, but the best Sonic game soundtrack is Sonic 3 and Knuckles.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, totally.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god, finally.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like you are the peace convention calling into the show.
[SPEAKER_10]: Especially ice cap level, am I right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Even I can sign on to that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sonic CD, Japanese, American, they both suck compared to Sonic 3 Ice Cap, Ice Cap Music, so much the best Finally, a peace treaty has been negotiated Now we just need to get Bobby to sign, alright Yeah, we need to We'll see, we'll see Well, what else is on your mind?
[SPEAKER_02]: What have you been playing lately?
[SPEAKER_08]: Mostly Team Fortress 2 and Beat Hazard.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yeah, Beat Hazard.
[SPEAKER_02]: They just ported that to iPhone.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have yet to play it though.
[SPEAKER_08]: They need to port it to Android so I can play it there too.
[SPEAKER_08]: I play a lot of Beat Hazard.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think I'm at level 340 right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dang.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, that's a lot.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I'm not even on the top of the leaderboard, so yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: What are some good songs to play?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because, you know, Beat Hazard, you get to do your own soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_02]: So what are some good songs?
[SPEAKER_02]: What are some of your favorite songs to play in Beat Hazard?
[SPEAKER_08]: Mostly, I'm going to go by genre, electronic music, trance, lots of music with heavy bass.
[SPEAKER_08]: It gets you lots of points, and it's pretty fun to play, especially on suicide mode.
[SPEAKER_08]: Lots of enemies.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I would offer to play you sometime, but you probably would absolutely kill me, because I had some problems with some of those achievements for the holiday event, and it was pretty sad.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, anyhow, Actdeft, I'm going to wrap up to let you go and get more calls, but I leave you with the official Peace Treaty music of OLR.
[SPEAKER_02]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to jam to this while we wait for our next call.
[SPEAKER_02]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_02]: You too.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can only play a clip because, you know, copyright and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Going back to the Rob D question from earlier, how do you guys stay motivated each week to do a show?
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, obviously, a lot of it is the people.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I don't know if I have an easy answer for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: You just kind of have to make it a priority.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because if you allow yourself to be like, oh, but the Amazing Race is on tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I really would just rather watch that instead.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then it's going to kind of fall apart.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think all of us have just kind of made a commitment like, we're going to do OLR no matter what.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, of course, there's going to be some things that are more important.
[SPEAKER_02]: And sometimes it's just because we need a break, like Disneyland.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is Disneyland more important than OLR?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, yes and no.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what I mean, though?
[SPEAKER_02]: If we did it every week, then why would we do OLR?
[SPEAKER_02]: But anyhow.
[SPEAKER_02]: The other half of the question, real quick.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have you ever thought of doing pre-recorded segments on a regular basis?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, it's called Horde House.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Jamie had one for a while, too, and maybe she'll have something new in the future.
[SPEAKER_02]: As far as pre-recorded segments for the show...
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if that's a suggestion, but I'm always open to ideas.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was, I will admit this, there was a time where we were talking about doing not break music in the middle, but something else.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you never know what might happen here at OLR.
[SPEAKER_02]: We got another call coming in.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's go to it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Ranma.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's up, buddy?
[SPEAKER_03]: Not too much.
[SPEAKER_03]: I do have a couple things I want to discuss, but Ranma, yet again, I have a bone to pick with you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Me?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, you.
[SPEAKER_02]: What do I do now?
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, I missed part of the show, so before I go charging at you with guns blazing, what is this comparison to hipsters and video games, something like that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Could you kind of explain that to me?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I don't even know, what the hell was that about now?
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't remember what happened two hours ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm getting old for this.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was about comparing  because they were saying that, well, a console without a disk drive would sell well because the  was it the iPad or  not the iPad, one of the MacBook Airs or whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yeah, and you said everybody that owned an iPad was a hipster.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you need to go at Loki, not at me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, no, I
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh lord, passing the buck, huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what I do best.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I'm saying the people that buy MacBooks are hipsters.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or at least MacBook Airs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I've got the thinnest book ever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Great.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you a hipster, Ranma?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, but I live 20 minutes away from Williamsburg, the East Coast central point for hipsters.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, this is very true.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't hate hipsters.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just hate the hip.
[SPEAKER_02]: You should.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_10]: I love everybody.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, Rob.
[SPEAKER_10]: What?
[SPEAKER_10]: Really, the Fairchild Channel F is underappreciated.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I got mine at Whole Foods.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's totally the pinnacle.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's gluten-free.
[SPEAKER_10]: You go to Whole Foods?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I don't go to Whole Foods.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was going to farmer's markets way before there was a Whole Foods.
[SPEAKER_10]: Don't get me started.
[SPEAKER_02]: I only like partial foods.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you just call in to start shit, or do you have something gaming-related to talk about?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: Double thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: and then I'll name the characters Poop, Fart, Lol you know I used to rent Final Fantasy 3 like every time same game every time I went in one day to rent it someone came in like right before me bought the copy with my save on it oh ouch yeah
[SPEAKER_02]: Actdeft in chat says, isn't Seattle hipster central?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, go to Netflix and watch a show called Portlandia.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's all I'm going to say.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's totally true.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the last thing I called about was, I know that you're a big fan of Kid Icarus, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I like it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Have you seen the anime trailer?
[SPEAKER_02]: You posted that to my Facebook and I forgot to look because I got distracted because somebody else had posted the new Garbage single and I was like, well, what do I like more?
[SPEAKER_02]: Kid Icarus or Garbage, the band?
[SPEAKER_02]: And Garbage won.
[SPEAKER_02]: So let me look at it now.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is what you posted here the other day from your website?
[SPEAKER_10]: You didn't post me.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: no um I my roommate who has a 3DS told me I need to check out Nintendo Video more so last night I went to check it out and it was too um many episodes I watched I had no idea it was on there I once went in there and saw I think a Kirby anime was in there but I haven't seen the Kid Icarus one yet no I'm gonna totally go look at that yes and uh Jamie I think you'll like the people who did the Kid Icarus videos oh uh Studio IG nice yes hmm alright
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, Ranma, we're going to let you go so we can wrap up the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: But any other quick thoughts?
[SPEAKER_02]: Stay fabulous.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I will.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, bye.
[SPEAKER_11]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you guys so much for calling in tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Our phones were lit up tonight, so some of you didn't get through.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm so sorry, but send an email, mailbag at orangelaunchradio.com, and DarkSakura will read your thoughts next week.
[SPEAKER_02]: But we have got to wrap up, and I've still got some tweets to go here before we wrap up.
[SPEAKER_10]: Tweet, tweet, tweet, tweet, tweet, tweet.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's still several tweets.
[SPEAKER_02]: Damn it, I closed the tweet window to bring up that Kid Icarus story.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tweet, tweet, tweet, tweet, tweet.
[SPEAKER_02]: There we go with the Disney stuff again.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: We got a tweet from TechColor.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tweets us and says, do all of you really hate Minecraft?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's actually quite fun for like 10 minutes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hate is a strong word.
[SPEAKER_02]: I do not hate Minecraft because saying I hate Minecraft means I think that people that play Minecraft are not smart and that's not the case at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: I get why people like Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not really for me.
[SPEAKER_10]: I cannot like the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't really, keep in mind, I don't ever really like to use hate because I think it's a very strong word and a wasteful emotion.
[SPEAKER_10]: But you cannot like a game and not give a crap about who plays it, you know.
[SPEAKER_10]: If other people like it, that's their thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: But you can completely loathe the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, it doesn't mean that you think anyone else that plays it is stupid.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can say like, I hate Minecraft players, then that's, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hate is a word reserved for like doing my taxes.
[SPEAKER_10]: I thought I was really boring.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was bored.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I love watching Minecraft videos.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll give you that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like watching the people that are really into it online.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alan watches a lot of these and some of them are pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: But my mind when it comes to that, I have this big open palette and just do something with it before the goblins tear you up.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's weird.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know what to do.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was kind of thinking about trying it again with the high definition textures.
[SPEAKER_02]: I will say I did really try to do Terraria though.
[SPEAKER_02]: I couldn't get into it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I tried it too.
[SPEAKER_10]: You sent me that copy.
[SPEAKER_02]: I did.
[SPEAKER_02]: I even got like a four pack and sent it to my friends.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I tried.
[SPEAKER_02]: None of us could get into it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I tried.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was too, like there just needed to be more structure to kind of like, I needed a little bit of handling.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm the type of person that wouldn't play Minecraft the way it was supposed to be.
[SPEAKER_10]: I would turn off the enemies and just build shit all day.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's what I would do.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like this comment from DKPopMan in the chat.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would think DarkSakura would like it from an artistic standpoint.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not really an artist, but you are a designer.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, but the thing is, I have The Sims.
[SPEAKER_02]: I see, so you kind of just have a different outlet for it.
[SPEAKER_10]: and I don't really play the Sims anymore either.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, usually if I'm sitting down to do design, I've got InDesign open and I'm making something that I'm going to print.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or putting something in my portfolio.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm not trying to poo-poo on Minecraft at all, it's just I really couldn't get into it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I might try it again, but to be honest I'm still trying to find a job right now and I don't have the time to devote to anything else that's distracting me.
[SPEAKER_02]: But yet you're still here at this show Yeah, I've been here for 10 years I can't quit now Alright, Tiger Claw says there's a couple news tweets here I want to read Hold on, because I have to do this for something else coming up Okay Going to Tiger Claw, a couple tweets here Minnesota lawmakers seek to ban community broadband What?
[SPEAKER_02]: The title alone, that seems a little silly here
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll leave you the story from GamePolitics.com Minnesota would do legislation meant to forbid community broadband projects joining states like Georgia and North Carolina HF2695 bars any community from building a broadband network within the state
[SPEAKER_02]: Meanwhile, the companies that provide broadband in the state are refusing to expand their networks to underserved and unserved areas within the state.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember, I don't get to see these in advance because they're Twitter topics.
[SPEAKER_02]: They come in during the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: a trade group representing the industry in the state claims they are not behind the bill before lawmakers activists have their doubts why would this be why would you ban that I don't like I'm not seeing the other side of this what's the good and it sounds like other states have already done this why would you ban it
[SPEAKER_02]: A recent post on a community action group called Stop the Cap revealed that Georgia's bill has been effectively shelved by being turned into what is called a study bill.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, so it didn't pass in Georgia.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you're a citizen of one of the many towns not served by a broadband service provider, it would probably be in your best interest to ask your state representative not to vote for this bill.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's the pros about this?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not seeing anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: Can anyone think of what a pro would be about this bill?
[SPEAKER_02]: Why would this bill be necessary?
[SPEAKER_02]: Is it that they don't want... I mean, I thought competition was okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Chatters, help me out, because I'm not thinking of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe it's the cable providers or whatever, like, saying, hey, why are you giving away free broadband?
[SPEAKER_04]: That makes our expensive broadband look less wonderful.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't really see... I don't even really see a point to this, but...
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, I don't get it either.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm really waiting to see if somebody in chat can kind of jump in here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't steal.
[SPEAKER_02]: The government hates competition.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Another tweet from Tigerclaw here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fraud claim dismissed in ex-Infinity Ward heads versus Activision lawsuit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_02]: A state superior court judge dismissed one of the fraud claims by ex-Infinity Ward heads Jason West and Vince Zampella against their former employer, Activision Blizzard.
[SPEAKER_02]: They originally filed a lawsuit citing breach of contract.
[SPEAKER_02]: They added two counts of fraud to that, saying Activision never intended to honor their contract, but the judge dismissed one of the counts.
[SPEAKER_02]: agreeing with Activision that the claim should not go forward.
[SPEAKER_02]: However, there is still another claim of promissory fraud, and that will be on a trial starting May 7th.
[SPEAKER_02]: So one count's been thrown out, but there's still plenty of other counts to go.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the chatters say, we're all as stumped as you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good, good thought.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, let's go to a tweet from 101DKPopMan tweets us, tell me why I should get Mass Effect 1.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know how to answer this.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know enough about the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: I do know an expert that we could go to to answer this question.
[SPEAKER_02]: So let's get them back on the line here.
[SPEAKER_02]: If they answer.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi, Shane?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, I had to call you back because we have a tweet that I can't answer.
[SPEAKER_02]: I need your help.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, because I know you can answer this.
[SPEAKER_02]: 101DKPopMan sent us a tweet saying, tell me why I should get Mass Effect 1.
[SPEAKER_07]: because you if you want the full story which you really really do if you're interested in Mass Effect it is good to have one because I did say that you could just get the Genesis comic but no you need to play through one so you get the entire freaking story for this amazing trilogy jank inventory system and all yes because you only have to put up with it for one game
[SPEAKER_02]: How long is the game?
[SPEAKER_02]: How long is Mass Effect 1?
[SPEAKER_07]: I will say that I've only done one playthrough of it and I didn't do hardly any side missions I think I did it in about 10 hours Oh wow, that's a lot shorter than I thought it would be I just ran through it Conversely, Mass Effect 2 I did everything I could minus two DLCs and I did that in about 25 and I'm already past 20 hours on Mass Effect 3 Wow
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, well, there you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's all I wanted.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, bye.
[SPEAKER_02]: From the expert.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, one more tweet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Beware, Dyson, this vacuum actually hungers and lives.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, someone made a Sinistar Roomba vacuum cleaner.
[SPEAKER_02]: You remember Sinistar, the game that would say, Beware, I live.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it looks like somebody has made a Roomba out of that, and I'm linked to a YouTube here I've never seen before.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, Lord.
[SPEAKER_02]: It actually has a sticker on it that looks like the Sinistar.
[SPEAKER_09]: That is great.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god, that sounds like an airplane jet about ready to take off.
[SPEAKER_10]: It certainly does suck.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I get it, because it's a vacuum.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, that's a horrible noise to be playing on the podcast, so I apologize.
[SPEAKER_02]: But did you hear that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Beware, I live.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, that's it for tweets.
[SPEAKER_02]: Twitter.com slash OLR if you want to send some in for next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: It'd be funnier if you could do either the Space Corps or Wheatley.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, last minute stories.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, anything?
[SPEAKER_04]: No?
[SPEAKER_04]: I wanted to play the Portal Mario game thing, which the more I read about it, it looks even cooler.
[SPEAKER_04]: We talked about that last week.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: So play it for next week.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want a full review.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I found out the download that I had done wasn't correct, so I had to redownload it.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're at three hours plus.
[SPEAKER_02]: We need to wrap up the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've had a lot of long shows lately.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're just very opinionated.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we're going to go around to everybody's final thoughts so we can wrap up tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Final thoughts from me.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll start tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: My final thought is just thank you, chatters.
[SPEAKER_02]: And thank you, podcasters who download our show and listen to us.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, I really mean it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, I know I always say it at the end of each show.
[SPEAKER_02]: But just kind of like thinking about the motivation question and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, you guys really are a big part of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like...
[SPEAKER_02]: I know we were still doing a show back when literally there were three people in chat and we still had fun with it and I'd like to think that I would still have fun with it even if it was only one or two people but the fact that more and more people show up and the family is growing and all that is a huge motivator.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's huge.
[SPEAKER_02]: So thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_04]: Making a Grand Theft Auto map editor in Excel is difficult.
[SPEAKER_04]: And probably not the preferred language, or it's not even really a programming language, but the preferred method to do such thing, but programming languages seem to make my head explode, so this is what I'm comfortable with.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not sure I even want to know what you're up to over there, to be honest.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm making an Excel file that will direct... You don't say!
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I don't say.
[SPEAKER_04]: That will directly translate the hex code from a map file from Grand Theft Auto into edible form and then back into hex code again.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you can directly import it because the program that someone made did a lot of rounding with numbers and it really fucks everything up.
[SPEAKER_04]: And their program's terribly broken.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, your final thought tonight?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Stupid daylight savings.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you want another coffee?
[SPEAKER_02]: I would be very... Alright, that's gonna do it guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now here's the line I give you at the end of every show but it's for a reason.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you guys as always for tuning in and listening to our show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for supporting Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is a free show.
[SPEAKER_02]: We don't have commercials.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're not paid for those food plugs in the beginning.
[SPEAKER_02]: I swear, I swear.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: or, you know, of course, Five Star Reviews and iTunes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Votes and Podcast Alley even.
[SPEAKER_02]: This was brought up last week.
[SPEAKER_02]: We appreciate each and every single way you guys spread the word of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: That, my friends, is a huge, huge motivator.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I think I'm motivated to do it all again next week with my co-hosts DarkSakura and Loki for episode 450 of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: We don't have anything big planned yet, but if Loki and DarkSakura keep up the good work, maybe...
[SPEAKER_02]: We can do a full motion video actress where is she now clip.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know about the actress, but the actor from Mega Race has actually done quite a few things.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to hunt somebody down.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to hunt him down.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what I want for episode 450.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to try and make it happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll do our best.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: 451, if nothing else.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_10]: I heard Dana Plano went underground.
[SPEAKER_10]: Stop it.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're so hipster you only listen to underground bands?
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: I said, was she cast in Six Feet Under?
[SPEAKER_02]: You guys are bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bad kids.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Be nice to each other.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is she a working stiff now?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm ending the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_06]: To join us for a live show, visit www.allgames.com Sunday nights at 6pm Pacific Time.
[SPEAKER_06]: The views and opinions expressed on Orange Lounge Radio do not necessarily reflect those of the entire staff of Orange Lounge Radio or AllGames.com, but we're probably right anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: See you next week!