[SPEAKER_01]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and released to our podcast stream twice weekly To listen to the first half of this episode visit www.orangeloungeradio.com for links to websites with listings of past episodes Now the conclusion of this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_03]: And welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: We are live on this Sunday evening, November the 11th of 2007.
[SPEAKER_03]: Remember, we are released in two parts every week.
[SPEAKER_03]: So if you missed part A, you can go check it out on our podcast feed in the archives.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or, of course, there's always our live webcam feed on Operator 11.
[SPEAKER_03]: Visit it at www.operator11.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: And sometimes we do some other little bonus shows, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: In fact, we're going to be showing off a new game tonight after the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: So check our Operator 11 archives for that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, of course...
[SPEAKER_04]: It's actually pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have a bunch of different things you can do in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can browse the top voted, I guess it's like hot or not for me's.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can browse the top voted me's in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can check out some random ones, download the ones you like, which is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Post the ones you think are cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Other people will rate them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then they have themed contests like the one going on right now is design a me that looks like Mario without his hat.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: is when the message came on the Wii that the channel was up.
[SPEAKER_03]: So Loki and I briefly looked for, like, five minutes of the new channel during the break, and some pretty interesting Miis in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I liked there was, like, a Geordi LaForge Mii that was in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Somebody had created a little miniature picture of, like, a penguin on somebody's face.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, I thought that was really good.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have some pretty cool, you know, Mii's on there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know if I could post some of the ones I've made, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, you might get rejected.
[SPEAKER_03]: What happens if you send penis head in?
[SPEAKER_03]: That might get rejected.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: But anyway, the Check Me Out channel is available right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: And by the time most of you guys hear this, it will have been out for actually quite some time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Something moving on, speaking about the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Wii has been rumored earlier this week, based on a comment from Reggie Fils-Aimé, to have 200 virtual console games by the year's end.
[SPEAKER_03]: And people were kind of freaking out, like, wait a minute, in order for the Wii to have that many games by the year's end, they're going to have to really step up their production, putting out like four and a half games a week, four to five games a week.
[SPEAKER_03]: 4 and a half games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Lots and lots of stuff to check out.
[SPEAKER_03]: The old school stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: However, I would like to point out we are, what, 160 games in so far?
[SPEAKER_03]: And still no Guardian Legend.
[SPEAKER_03]: This makes me a sad panda.
[SPEAKER_03]: That is sad.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is a crime.
[SPEAKER_03]: Awful.
[SPEAKER_03]: That has been committed.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I don't know what rights you have to get, but you better get those really quick.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's all I have to say about the Virtual Console.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, for our friends in the UK, Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_10]: 3 is heading to Virtual Console.
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually, we are getting it on Monday.
[SPEAKER_03]: We got this Monday.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, we already got this Monday.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it's going to be 500 Wii Points.
[SPEAKER_10]: Also coming out is Blue's Journey for the Neo Geo, and that will be 900.
[SPEAKER_10]: And also Power Golf for TurboGrafx-16 for 600 points.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I'm glad to see that Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_03]: 3 is making the rounds worldwide, because it is a great game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is one of the all-time great NES classics, so everybody gets to enjoy it now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hooray!
[SPEAKER_04]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, apparently some Best Buys have been breaking street on Super Mario Galaxy and selling it early.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shame on them.
[SPEAKER_04]: And apparently a few people have been buying according to the Games Facts forum thread, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have pictures online including stuff
[SPEAKER_04]: But hey, you only have to wait a couple more days to play it, so... Hurry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, if they had Super Smash Bros., that'd be... That'd be a feat.
[SPEAKER_03]: I somehow don't think they can get that right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: ACHP is in our chatroom and is bragging, I got a copy!
[SPEAKER_03]: So apparently, somehow... Some folks were able to get one from Best Buy, so good job to those folks.
[SPEAKER_03]: So... Um...
[SPEAKER_03]: Moving on, speaking of Super Mario Galaxy, right now, right this very minute, there is an event going on at the Nintendo World Store in New York City.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is the Mario Galaxy Launch Party.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going on right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it started at 8 p.m.
[SPEAKER_03]: is when it started, but it's only been going until 10 p.m., so I guess it...
[SPEAKER_03]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, Zaku, how are you doing?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm just here in the rock right here, just seeing Mario Galaxy on screens, and people just going after t-shirts, and just freaking my ass off.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, yeah, that's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_07]: What the hell's going on?
[SPEAKER_03]: What the hell have they been doing there tonight, Zaku?
[SPEAKER_03]: They've had a Velcro wall?
[SPEAKER_07]: Large party.
[SPEAKER_07]: They have a live DJ right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're giving out free shit.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's people waiting in line for the launch.
[SPEAKER_07]: and I know one of them is the one that actually got the first Wii in this country last year before the rest of, you know, Times Square.
[SPEAKER_07]: That same guy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_07]: That same guy with the puzzle on his right hand.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's some hard... He's up on the line like one of the first two.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's some hardcore people out there right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I can't hear them but it's fantastic.
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: I was just gonna say it sounds like there's some hardcore people there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like a few thousand people.
Um, but there's like
[SPEAKER_07]: Tell us more about the special events that are going on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Have you actually been able to get your hands on the game yet?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, I played it.
[SPEAKER_07]: They had these...
[SPEAKER_07]: And like three guys with monitors basically sticking out from like a rod or something that they're carrying on their back with the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Kind of like how they did last year with the Segway.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, the Wii hooked up to the Segway, now they're basically walking.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're carrying all that gear, walking the game, you know, bringing the game to you by foot.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow, our chat room is just pretty excited to be hearing the actual live report from the show going on right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: In fact, Frisbee in our chat room says, this is the first time I've heard Zaku call in and not sound sleepy.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you definitely are excited to be there, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, come on.
[SPEAKER_07]: I had to bust my ass in the cold.
[SPEAKER_07]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm pretty much just going to get some coffee and take a leak just to get this call through.
[SPEAKER_07]: But yeah, so far it's been good.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, the game pretty much plays like Mario 64, only with motion control and slightly better graphics.
[SPEAKER_07]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, can you give a shout-out to the entire crowd that Orange Lounge Radio says hello?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm on the outside of the crowd, it's pretty thick right there.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to be hard to get inside there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Can you give a big shout out to everybody around you that Orange Hodge Radio says hello?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh man, they'll be just looking at random strangers just saying some crazy stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: If I knew about this earlier, then I would have just done my whole body with OLR promotion stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just would have put the West Side Dames.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's all good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Zaku, thanks so much for the report and have fun at the event.
[SPEAKER_03]: And don't go too crazy, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: Take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Later.
[SPEAKER_03]: Poor guy.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's one of our infamous callers, the Legend of Zaku, calling us live from the Mario launch event at the Nintendo...
[SPEAKER_03]: World Headquarters in New York City.
[SPEAKER_03]: Isn't that fun when we can do live reports like that?
[SPEAKER_03]: More stuff needs to happen on Sunday nights when we can do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can definitely hear in the background, just like there's tons of people there.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's amazing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, well let's move on then with the news.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you, Zaku, again for that special report.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, in other news, and I think that this is pretty cool because there are a lot of fans of this game.
[SPEAKER_10]: For a
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyone with a PSP, Disgaea is heading out to PSP.
[SPEAKER_10]: It will be called Afternoon of Darkness.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, so it's like a new game in the series.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sounds like.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're putting in a few specific things for the PSP, like a multiplayer mode where you can go against your friends worldwide or share items from your shop.
[SPEAKER_10]: It has an exclusive story line.
[SPEAKER_10]: and you're trying to become the beauty queen ultimate overlord.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not your goal in real life, DarkSakura, to become the beauty queen overlord?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, my goal is just to be the overlord.
[SPEAKER_03]: I see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know a lot of people really love Disgaea for its quirky sense of humor, and I played it once.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: I need to sit down and spend more time with it if I could ever tear myself away from those damn MMOs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, if you're in the U.S., you're in luck because it came out a couple weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sweet!
[SPEAKER_04]: Definitely worth picking up if you like Disgaea.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's very typical that the Brits are getting it a couple weeks behind.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, we still love you.
[SPEAKER_04]: PSP is a region free, so if you really, really, really, really, really need your Disgaea right away, then there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways, not a big surprise, but Sony has released a custom theme maker for the PlayStation 3, much like they did with the PSP after they had theme support for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, with the new firmware 2.0 allowing themes, you can now create your own.
[SPEAKER_04]: So yes, as soon as I get around to it, I will create new themes for the PSP website, and I'll also create a theme for the PlayStation 3 as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's about time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sheesh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm too busy playing stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just renewed the domain not that long ago, and I seriously considered just letting it expire, but then I remember that there were some people that were emailing us saying, I listen to you on the PSP, and so I figured, alright, for them we'll keep the site up.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was a really well done website.
[SPEAKER_03]: You don't see many PSP custom done websites.
[SPEAKER_04]: I did not renew the domain for OLRE since I never made a site for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Damn you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_03]: We forgive you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, also on the PlayStation 3, apparently, if you had your firmware before version 2.0, you usually only used to be able to see videos if it was supported in PlayStation 3's format.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, now after the 2.0 patch, apparently, the PlayStation 3 will now show you thumbnails, running times, and file names for other non-supported formats, such as Xvid and DivX.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, you can't play them, you can just see them.
[SPEAKER_03]: But certainly people are taking that one step further and saying, well, this is a sign that you're actually going to have support for DivX and Xvid in the near future on the PlayStation 3, which would certainly be a welcome addition.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: But for right now, you only get thumbnails and you get to know they're there.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just that it will say, you can't watch me, na-na-na-na-na-na.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, there you have it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, poor baby.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, so, it's about, you know, we've
[SPEAKER_10]: They have a preliminary settlement for the class action suit against Take-Two Interactive.
[SPEAKER_03]: For the hot coffee.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my god, this is years old.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, basically, the terms of the settlement, the ones who can benefit from that is if they bought a copy of Grand Theft Auto San Andreas before July 20th, 2005.
[SPEAKER_10]: B, were offended by the game's content that used the hot coffee modification.
[SPEAKER_03]: That means they would have had... I was offended that I had to unlock it.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, they said they were upset by the ability to modify and alter the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I was upset that you had to have an ability to do it and it wasn't just there, so can I have money?
[SPEAKER_10]: And that...
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_10]: So...
[SPEAKER_03]: There's still more money than GameStop will give you for it, so hey.
[SPEAKER_10]: Pretty much.
[SPEAKER_10]: Take-Two is committed to spend $1.025 million on the settlement benefits, and their out-of-pocket cost total is $2.75 million.
[SPEAKER_10]: and paying the court costs.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, Picaruno in our chatroom says, you can get free money if I say I'm offended by something?
[SPEAKER_03]: You have to have your proof of purchase.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have to have the proof of purchase.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who the hell has a proof of purchase that late?
[SPEAKER_03]: I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, that's how they get around it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I'm going to save it for Grand Theft Auto 4 because I'm going to be highly offended by that someday.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to see how many people actually have it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Highly offended that I didn't get my $35 sooner.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's a statement, by the way, from Ben Fetter, who's the CEO of Take-Two.
[SPEAKER_10]: If the case had continued, we believe the court would have agreed that Take-Two was not liable for consumers acting independently to modify their games with third-party hardware and software to access normally inaccessible content.
[SPEAKER_10]: Nonetheless, we believe it is in the best interest of the company to avoid protracted and costly litigation to prove our case and to finally put this matter behind us.
[SPEAKER_03]: Gerardimo says, I'm offended by your offense.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actdeft, our listener from Mexico who's listening, says, I'm suing the guys that made the Spanish training game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm offended and I need money.
[SPEAKER_04]: Spanish for everyone.
Awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would like to see if they're going to release figures on exactly how many people actually went and got money over this.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'd be kind of curious to see how many people actually had the proof of purchases and actually went through the song and dance to do this.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that would be kind of an interesting figure.
[SPEAKER_03]: I bet it's less than a couple thousand.
[SPEAKER_03]: If that, honestly.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, how many people are going to think to do this?
[SPEAKER_03]: Most parents were pissed off and they moved on, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, you know, there's going to be letters that go out to anyone involved that put their name in with the lawsuit.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess that's true.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways, so there's some interesting drama going on on the website, The Consumerist.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently, a PS3 owner had a problem with their PS3 not working, so they sent it in to be repaired.
[SPEAKER_04]: and, um, I guess, according to them, it was too dusty to be fixed.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they considered that it would, because of the dust, it was not covered under the warranty.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um... Uh-oh, my Wii's gonna be under, at a warranty as well then, with a thick layer of dust on that thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, they... Mario Galaxy's not out yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: They said that it was an act of God or customer abuse.
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be under.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it was funny, though, because there was a follow-up to this as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: God has smited my PlayStation 3 with a thick layer of dust.
[SPEAKER_03]: The horror, the horror.
[SPEAKER_04]: But there was also a follow-up to that I remember reading that that whole statement, of course, is not really true.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, Sony does.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dust does not void your warranty as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that was in the later follow-up, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: but this one lady that was adamant she said that she was like the head of the customer service department or something like that and anybody that they called you know oh and then the other thing too is the guy said well then hell you know take a picture of this dust and let me you know see what exactly you're talking about if it's so you know detrimental and they said oh no we can't take any pictures of that because all the pictures would be owned by Sony and then you can't you know see them without a subpoena or something like that you have to pay $150 to repair it out of warranty or something like that ugh
[SPEAKER_03]: Our chatroom is lighting up with conversation here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Odd1 says, it was an act of shitty games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Frisbee says, God made dirt and dirt don't hurt.
[SPEAKER_04]: Basically, I was just going to read some sections of this here.
[SPEAKER_04]: I kept my 60GB PS3 in an entertainment center since its purchase.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is known within the PS3 community that the thing is a huge dust magnet.
[SPEAKER_04]: I took good care of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have 10 Blu-ray discs that did not come free with my PS3.
[SPEAKER_04]: 5 games, 5 controllers.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why the fuck do you have 5 controllers?
[SPEAKER_04]: What the hell are you playing?
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe Specialty Controller?
[SPEAKER_04]: NBA Live, I'm guessing, because that game supports up to 7.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or not NBA Live, NBA 08 or whatever, or 07.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, we get it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Two 42-inch LCD TVs, one 50-inch Bravia LCD rear-production TV air, something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: A VAIO desktop, VAIO laptop, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways, one day I turn it on, I put a disc in it, and it doesn't show up, and it won't eject.
[SPEAKER_04]: Finally, I get it to eject, and I try Blu-ray, and nothing, the CD's nothing.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I called customer support, who originally told me they can't do anything because I don't have the original sales receipt.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was a gift.
[SPEAKER_04]: I stayed on the phone for hours explaining to them that I don't have the receipt because it was a gift.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: SSJ100 Matt in our chatroom says, was the owner Pigpen from Peanuts?
[SPEAKER_03]: And Azura May says, I hope I pronounced that right, says, PlayStation 3 weakness is dust, which makes me think of, like, the end of Signs.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, you know, it was water that was their weak point the whole time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now it's, like, dust.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, so, like, he goes back and forth, finally talking.
[SPEAKER_04]: The supervisor, who apparently was a bitch, named Daria Wu, extension 55682,
[SPEAKER_04]: basically told them that the PSP or picture of the PSP was property of Sony Computer Entertainment of America and that they would have to subpoena the pictures in order to see them.
[SPEAKER_04]: And blah blah blah.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then of course at the very end he says I don't get it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sony is including folding at home with their consoles.
[SPEAKER_04]: The auto start feature makes it so it's running almost all the time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course it's going to be filled with dust.
[SPEAKER_04]: Few reps said the reason they couldn't replace it is because it looked like at
[SPEAKER_04]: It had been two years worth of dust rather than eight months.
[SPEAKER_04]: The console hasn't even been out for years, so obviously that's less than a year's worth of dust.
[SPEAKER_04]: And of course, he's all pissed off about it and wasn't going to stay quiet, and that's why everybody ran it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then apparently, like I said, the follow-up, another consumer rep reported, I'm calling pretty much to clarify the PS3's warranty.
[SPEAKER_04]: If there's any clause in the warranty that makes it so the PS3 is too dusty, that the warranty is void.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the rep said, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: And no.
[SPEAKER_04]: The only way that it voided is if it were neglected, abused, dropped, or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Modification, like if you opened it up...
[SPEAKER_04]: If you don't have the sales receipt, Power Failures, Mother Nature actually avoids the warranty.
[SPEAKER_04]: Christ, there's a Bible written on this whole thing, isn't there?
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me put it this way.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why didn't they just fix it?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, seriously, they're... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: The fucking system obviously hadn't been opened up.
[SPEAKER_04]: So what?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's dusty.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're doing a horrible job of making a dust magnet.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, anyhow, I'm sure we're getting lots of colorful comments on that one.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you have something to contribute, if your PlayStation 3 has died due to dust, we'd love to hear from you.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think this is a job for Dust Cap 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mailbag at OrangeLaunchRadio.com if you'd like to send us an email.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Jamie will be opening up the mailbag very soon, but we have one more story for you guys before we get to that point.
[SPEAKER_03]: and that would be about Warner Brothers.
[SPEAKER_03]: Warner Brothers has decided to purchase Traveler's Tales and the parent group TT Games.
[SPEAKER_03]: You might know Traveler's Tales from the Lego franchise as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: So Warner Brothers just wants to own that shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: So there you have it.
[SPEAKER_03]: By the way, they'll be putting out Lego Batman very soon, which looks kind of awesome because I love old school Batman.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, well like I said, every week you guys send us email to mailbag at orangelongeradio.com And the one and only DarkSakura will open up the mailbag, dive on in, and read her favorite emails.
[SPEAKER_03]: And maybe some of the ones she didn't like either.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hopefully this is a good week.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, DarkSakura, was it a good email week?
[SPEAKER_03]: On a scale of 1 to 10?
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe a 6, a 7?
[SPEAKER_03]: R. It was an R. Okay, well anyway, I don't know how that works.
[SPEAKER_03]: But here goes DarkSakura with this week's mail.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mailbag at orangelongeradio.com
[SPEAKER_10]: The first email comes from Xenocore.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, folks.
[SPEAKER_10]: I recently acquired a copy of Ore no Rioni for PS1.
[SPEAKER_10]: I love this game.
[SPEAKER_10]: However, the emulators I have used with the game don't give me precise control on all analog sticks.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do you know of a better method to play this game, whether emulated or mod chip?
[SPEAKER_10]: I still have the initial launch PS2 and a 60 gigabyte PS3.
[SPEAKER_10]: What can I do?
[SPEAKER_10]: I love this game and can't wait to play it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Um...
[SPEAKER_10]: What game?
[SPEAKER_10]: Ore no Rionii
[SPEAKER_03]: I had never even heard of that game, I'm sorry to say.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I know we love obscure titles, but... No, not that one.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, and I gotta say, the PlayStation 1, I'm not... That was kind of the period of my life where I wasn't gaming a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_03]: I played a lot of the big games, like Final Fantasy VII and Symphony of the Night, but I missed a lot of shit during that period.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because that was when I was in college, and I was actually doing a little bit of work here and there.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was back in the day... Between Puzzle Fighter 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was back in the day when I was purchasing HK copies of...
[SPEAKER_04]: Games, importing Ridge Racer 4 and shit like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, even Google can't find this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Leave it to the chat room to say something about it, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Flawless Bolt X says, Funny how someone mentions a PlayStation 1 game when last episode Loki said no one plays them anymore.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, there's some irony.
[SPEAKER_03]: In the U.S.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry we don't have much more for you, my friend.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, we're going to be playing Vib Ribbon.
[SPEAKER_04]: True.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, but people that play PlayStation... Let me put it this way, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you want to play a PlayStation 1 game right now, you're probably either playing it on a PSP, whether it be modded or not, or you're probably playing it on a PlayStation 1 that you already have.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think people are out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe there's people out there that want to play Final Fantasy 7 or something like that to try it out, but I don't think there's actually people out there that are like, you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think I'm going to buy a brand new PlayStation 1 and some PlayStation 1 games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Most people don't really go back that far.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, we weren't much help on that one.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're not experts on everything.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just most things.
[SPEAKER_03]: But congratulations for stumping the host.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here's some free rice-a-roni.
[SPEAKER_10]: I couldn't find anything about that game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway, we get an email from Thomas.
[SPEAKER_10]: It says, OLR equals win.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, thank you, Thomas.
[SPEAKER_10]: And we get one from Robert M.,
[SPEAKER_10]: Freudian Slip
[SPEAKER_10]: Jamie, how dare you insult the listeners?
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I did go ahead and purchase that on iTunes Store.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have only two complaints, which are issues with all iPods games so far.
[SPEAKER_10]: First of all, it uses a lot of battery power while playing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Secondly, any session between syncing the iPod with your computer with iTunes in which FaZe is played even once appears to clear out your play counts for all podcasts and songs, which isn't even an issue if you don't care about play counts, but it can be problematic for podcasts.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's playing FaZe to a podcast.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow, that might be interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or not.
[SPEAKER_10]: Otherwise, the game is a lot of fun, simple but addictive.
[SPEAKER_10]: Most of it uses the back, select, and forward buttons.
[SPEAKER_10]: Tap to the beat of the music following on-screen scrolling options with a great artistic style surrounding it.
[SPEAKER_10]: A few parts use the scroll wheel to follow a line for bonus points, which build up stars needed to pass checkpoints.
[SPEAKER_10]: It usually works equally as well with songs you add to the playlist in iTunes as it does with its built-in songs, including new songs by Freeze Pop, Bang Camaro, among others.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sweet.
[SPEAKER_10]: Highly recommended for fans of music games.
[SPEAKER_03]: I bought my PS3 from Kmart and now they stopped selling Blu-ray discs?
[SPEAKER_03]: Those damn traitors.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is the person with the really cool signature that says this email is sponsored by the Olive Garden Home of Neverending Salads.
[SPEAKER_03]: and Breadsticks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't forget Breadsticks.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't want any more salad.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's gonna be more salad for you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, never mind.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was gonna say something but I lost.
[SPEAKER_03]: My train derailed.
[SPEAKER_03]: My train of thought.
[SPEAKER_03]: The salad destroyed your train.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I started thinking about the Olive Garden and the Olive Garden's awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, we have a long one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hooray for long emails.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is actually being sent to us by, well, if I just say Rick, because he didn't put a nickname in there, but it seems like he's from the UK.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi, guys.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let me know if you get the reference.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: It started with GameSpot, and then it expanded to IGN.
[SPEAKER_10]: Then I found this link to OLR on a random podcast site.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now my crack-like habit of listening to gaming podcasts creeps into my working day.
[SPEAKER_10]: I own a Wii.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know it may not seem as a hardcore system, but I love it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have owned every incarnation of Nintendo's system and enjoyed them all.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, even the N64.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dark was cool, apart from the last level.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I have never had a hardware failure with any of them, apart from when I made smoke come out of the back of my Super NES after playing Desert Strike for 24 hours solid.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hardcore.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know if I'd say hardcore, more so fanboy.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's all right.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not a crime.
[SPEAKER_10]: After frantically searching the internet, I found that the problem was with the video card on the Wii overheating.
[SPEAKER_10]: I rang the nice people at Nintendo and sent it away and after two weeks they returned it back to me all fixed.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now I am happy to say it all looks fab.
[SPEAKER_10]: Is this a common fault?
[SPEAKER_10]: I have never heard any of this on any podcast before.
[SPEAKER_10]: The 360 has its own podcast named after its notorious issues.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway, keep up the good work.
[SPEAKER_10]: I would love to hear my email on your show as I am a big fan and you always seem to have fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Why is it playing that noise?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I forgot to hit stop earlier and it was playing the Portal song from earlier.
[SPEAKER_03]: But anyway, I did find... Sorry, the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, IGN.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tonight's show was a lie.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, but what it was is that apparently it's... Yeah, we found some information on the game on IGN.
[SPEAKER_03]: Apparently it was a cooking simulator and it was the first DualShock enhanced cooking simulator on the market.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, it wasn't on the Dreamcast.
[SPEAKER_03]: It just came out the same day as the Dreamcast.
[SPEAKER_03]: But they did have a demo in the US.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: On the PlayStation Underground.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've been over Cooking Mama for about a month now, you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know, I have to get it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, I wanted to say to our... I want to make a cake.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wanted to say to our hardcore fan overseas that you are not the first person to have an exploding Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: That particular issue, I think, is the first time I've heard of that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Certainly, nobody else I've ever heard compares it to hemorrhoid, whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, you know, every system is going to have some that break.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, there's just some faulty stuff on the assembly line.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anything that comes off an assembly line is going to have a fault once in a while.
[SPEAKER_04]: That game, Counter Force, kind of looked like a bursting hemorrhoid, but, you know, that's just...
[SPEAKER_03]: That game, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the problem was, at least with the Xbox 360, that Red Rings of Death was very prevalent.
[SPEAKER_03]: A lot of people had that issue, and that's why it's become almost like a pop culture gag within the gaming scene.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't know there was a podcast called Red Rings of Death, but I'm somehow not surprised.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, that's why it's become such a phenomenon and why Microsoft had to specifically extend the warranty.
[SPEAKER_03]: To Nintendo's credit...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: So there's more.
[SPEAKER_10]: More.
[SPEAKER_10]: Can I finish the email?
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_10]: Spelled M-O-A-R.
[SPEAKER_10]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_10]: Where the fuck is my strategy game for the Wii?
[SPEAKER_10]: Surely it's perfect for Command & Conquer.
[SPEAKER_10]: I would even settle for Red Alert Graphics.
[SPEAKER_10]: Is that asking too much?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay then, Tiberium Wars?
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: are there any strategy games?
[SPEAKER_04]: Battalion Wars 2 maybe and then Fire Emblem Radiant Dawn but Fire Emblem Radiant Dawn unfortunately is apparently very much like the last game that came out in the GameCube almost exactly the same but we like Fire Emblem I just hate playing strategy games myself oh and a question for me
[SPEAKER_10]: Did you ever play Cannon Fodder?
[SPEAKER_10]: It was an awesome game, also should be remade for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_10]: War has never been so much fun, and so on.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know of it, I actually have not played it.
[SPEAKER_03]: That sounds familiar.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've never played it either.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yet another game stumping the panel here at Orange Library.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I think I did play it.
[SPEAKER_10]: We've talked about Cannon Fodder on the show before, I thought.
[SPEAKER_10]: Back in a while, but I do believe that we have.
[SPEAKER_03]: Escapist says in our chatroom, Cannon Fodder was good, General Chaos was better.
[SPEAKER_03]: See, when in doubt, when we're stumped, we always have the chatroom and plenty of people there to rely on, on their gaming knowledge as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's one more last bit to this email.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow, this goes on forever.
[SPEAKER_10]: Bye!
[SPEAKER_10]: It's capitalized, I had to say it that way.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Goodbye.
[SPEAKER_10]: Last, last email.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dun dun dun.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dearest OLR, with Journey of Dreams and a new Samba de Amigo coming to Wii and Rez coming to Xbox Live Arcade, which I think was Sega?
[SPEAKER_10]: It seems Sega is giving gamers a chance to play some of their better games that were probably missed by most people.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some of those that should have remained missed, yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: If this is the case, I was wondering which Shaggy games you would like to see remade slash sequelized slash playable again.
[SPEAKER_10]: Personally, I would love to see Space Channel 5 on Wii.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it's one of the few games I would like to play by shaking the Wii mode around, but only if Space Michael still has a part in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: You took my answer, jerk.
[SPEAKER_03]: You took my answer, Gerardimo, you jerk.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's exactly what I would have said is Space Channel 5.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now what am I going to say?
[SPEAKER_10]: Space Channel 5 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: They even do the freaking Thriller Dance, and I think that's fantastic.
[SPEAKER_03]: How about another Crazy Taxi game, but like a good one, not a cheap knockoff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, you know, Crazy Taxi kind of jumped the shark because there was like sequel after sequel.
[SPEAKER_03]: How about like a remade, really good Crazy Taxi that has more than just the offspring as the music?
[SPEAKER_10]: They had Bad Religion.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jet Set Radio?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ah.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's another thing that we need is definitely another Jet Set Radio because I freaking love that game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Odd One agrees with that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jet Set Radio, doing the graffiti with the Wiimote would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because you'd have to do it in that pattern, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: GS68 says Space Harrier and fuck Planet Harrier.
[SPEAKER_10]: Planet Harrier.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: I love Space Harrier, but the thing is that I could not imagine Space Harrier updated.
[SPEAKER_10]: The best version...
[SPEAKER_10]: I got one for you that's perfect for Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_10]: Fantasy Zone.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, hell yeah!
[SPEAKER_10]: They fully need to put out fantasies on it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Except I think that it would be kind of... You would have to do it, though, classic controller only, I think.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or how about... You know what game we haven't seen an incarnation of in a long time is Alex Kidd.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bring me some Alex Kidd.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what's actually going to be coming out here pretty soon, in January, I think, is that Sega Bass Fishing.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what that is...
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, let's remember the one on the Dreamcast with the fishing rod.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yeah, yeah, with the rod caliber.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, that game gave us rod caliber.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I know that I've mentioned this on the show a bunch of times, but you could play Soul Calibur with the fishing rod, and it was really cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, you can actually play that Soul Calibur Legends.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have that fishing rod that comes with hooked real motion fishing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Have you tried it?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I have not tried that game because, well, one, I don't want to buy hooked because it's a fishing game, and I don't.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't find fishing fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Simulating fishing I think would be even less fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways, any more emails?
[SPEAKER_10]: We actually got one from Rob with Two Bees.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a link to a story about a boy who hired a hitman to kill his parents for PlayStation punishment.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's funny.
[SPEAKER_10]: A boy, these parents told their son they couldn't play his PlayStation for poor grades and bad behavior.
[SPEAKER_10]: And the son tried to hire a hitman.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my God, what's this world coming to?
[SPEAKER_10]: These people in Maryland, Shannon and Joey Troiano from Maryland punished their son Corey by confiscating their PlayStation and hiding it and banned him from watching TV.
[SPEAKER_10]: So he tried to hire a hitman.
[SPEAKER_10]: and his mom actually set him up for a sting.
[SPEAKER_03]: God, that kid's retarded.
[SPEAKER_03]: What in the hell is wrong with this family?
[SPEAKER_10]: He promised that he would give him his stepfather's new pickup as payment for killing his parents.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_03]: And somebody was actually going to kill these people over a pickup?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe it was a really nice pickup.
[SPEAKER_03]: I somehow doubt that.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's crazy talk.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_10]: And she's quoted as saying, I miss him being at home and I miss us joking around and kidding around but in the same breath I don't know what this kid will do because that's not my son.
[SPEAKER_10]: That can't be my little boy sitting there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_10]: It said that his behavior got worse ever since his father left.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like Rosemary's Baby or The Omen or something crazy there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_03]: Any more emails to depress us?
[SPEAKER_10]: So that he dropped out of school and stole 45 bucks.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: This guy sounds like a real winner.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, that's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's it for emails.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you want to email us sometime, mailbag at orange lounge radio dot com.
[SPEAKER_03]: Meanwhile, more news.
[SPEAKER_03]: News.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_04]: So some pretty cool stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: According to Valve, they're adding the Orange Box games to the source software development kit.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that means that you guys can go out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: Valve's custom face poser tool that allows users to produce choreographed sequences in the Source Engine, a model viewer that allows artists to preview models and animations quickly, a source code that allows mod makers to create their own games based off of Half-Life 2 or Half-Life 2 Deathmatch, and all the tools required to make, build custom textures and models for Source Engine games.
[SPEAKER_04]: So,
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a whole lot of cool stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I've actually seen there were some custom maps out there, mods or something like that, with Portal that actually had some gravity modifiers in there as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like different sections of the map had different gravity and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that would be kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow, all right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: No, there's ways.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you put in a code where you can shoot portals anywhere on any surface, you can actually get it to where you can clip through the walls sometimes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, but there's also, I think it is kind of cool that the whole credit sequence when you're going through where the pipes are, you can actually, there is a glitch where you can go into that area because it is fully rendered and in the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, there's been a healthy donation of some SimCity made by EA.
[SPEAKER_03]: You've probably heard of the One Laptop per Child program.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is something where they were going to actually put laptops in classrooms in other countries for children in the classroom.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, EA has actually donated the original version of SimCity to be pre-installed on all machines.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pony the Money for SimCity 2000
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_03]: The classic is way better.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hate SimCity 2, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it's also the laptop's pretty old.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, well, not pretty.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're $100, hello.
[SPEAKER_03]: The processor in it's not exactly powerful and stuff, so.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, look, as long as they play Oregon Trail, what else do you need?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what kids need in school.
[SPEAKER_03]: Exactly, that's what it would have been.
[SPEAKER_10]: So then they would need a Mac.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or just an Apple IIe with the green monitor.
[SPEAKER_10]: Apple IIe.
[SPEAKER_03]: Those things are the shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I want all these kids to learn Logo.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pen down, forward 20, right 90, forward 20, right 90.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, guess what?
[SPEAKER_10]: Atari 2600 news.
[SPEAKER_10]: The Atari 2600 has been inducted into the National Toy Hall of Fame at the Strong National Museum of Play.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what the other two things that were inducted were along with it?
[SPEAKER_10]: Raggedy Ann, no, Raggedy Andy, sorry, and the Kite.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame, but with toys.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_10]: The museum's curator has said that the Atari system paved the way for today's gaming consoles and, quote, mesmerized a generation with games such as Space Invaders, Pac-Man, and Frogger.
[SPEAKER_03]: The kite.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm trying... Yeah, apparently it's also in there with the teddy bear, roller skates, and Mr. Potato Head.
[SPEAKER_03]: Light Bright is the greatest toy of all time.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: I would never use the things that came with them.
[SPEAKER_03]: I made my own pictures.
[SPEAKER_03]: Me neither.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just put, I make patterns.
[SPEAKER_03]: Patterns are my thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: But you know what I found?
[SPEAKER_10]: At a yard sale like a year ago, I found Transformers light bright patterns.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I kept them.
[SPEAKER_03]: I bought them.
[SPEAKER_03]: I totally want a light bright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Couldn't you imagine putting a light bright here on the shelf with a mirror on it?
[SPEAKER_10]: Guys, listeners, find us a light bright.
[SPEAKER_10]: We implore.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to, I swear to God I'm going to yard sales.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to eBay right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Please do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_04]: In case you've been living under a rock, the Writers Guild of America is striking right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just a surprise.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways, so what that means is a lot of movie productions have halted.
[SPEAKER_04]: And one of those movies that's kind of been put on the brakes, I guess, Wolfenstein.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Sci-Fi Wire apparently is reporting that the script is almost done.
[SPEAKER_04]: um but everything as far as the production date and that kind of thing won't be decided until after all of this is over and of course um you know Roger Avery fully supports the strike and yeah so darn we guess we have to wait for a Wolvenstein movie uh just a thought it's probably gonna suck so take your time
[SPEAKER_03]: And if the movie sucks, I will go on strike from doing this program.
[SPEAKER_04]: There was somebody, somebody commented, I want to say it was on Any Cool News or something like that, and I'm sure people have made the same kind of comments, that TV watchers and movie watchers should have their own guild and strike when there's like crappy movies.
[SPEAKER_04]: Refuse to watch them.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why the hell does a Light Bright have $52 shipping on it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Christ.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's a light truck.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then the ones, I found the Light Bright for $25.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I think the whole Rider Strike thing does kind of, I mean, it's unfortunate.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, the reason why it has $52 shipping is probably because the sale price, if it's cheap enough, they don't have to pay as much of an eBay tax, I guess, on that thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or the, you know, eBay doesn't get as big of a portion.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then that way they can just make it all up in shipping.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's cheap.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's working the system.
[SPEAKER_10]: They need to have one with a buy it now on here.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I would like to point out that Marissa in our chat room says, Light Bright has become modern with Light Bright flat screen.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, and I want an old one like the one I had from 1982.
[SPEAKER_03]: Can you find an Etch-A-Sketch while you're at it?
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, I found a 1986 Light Bright refill pack.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rad.
[SPEAKER_03]: We might have to get that so we get plenty of orange pigs.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyhow, something else from the 80s that is awesome is The Last Starfighter.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_03]: and remember how the last Starfighter had like a video game kind of in it but it was never actually a game it was supposed to be a game but it wasn't well what happened is that this guy actually put together a copy of the Starfighter game and actually put it in the cabinet Atari had made this full final version of the game but they never actually put it out but thanks to the love
[SPEAKER_03]: and Hard Cornus for lack of a better term of this guy he can now play Starfighter in his house I mean this comes complete with like the levers and everything this isn't just in any old cabinet this isn't like an actual cabinet like the one from the movie if you want to see this for yourself Roguesynapse.com let me spell that for you guys R-O-G-U-E-S-Y-N-A-P-S-E dot com you found a virtual light bright?
[SPEAKER_03]: one of our chatters linked it that's just not as cool I'm sorry to say I appreciate the effort but
[SPEAKER_03]: RogueSynapse.com
[SPEAKER_10]: Being put out by Aniplex's A1 Pictures.
[SPEAKER_10]: They are adapting it for, it's actually going to be called Persona Trinity Soul in January 2008, which is set a decade after the game and will center around three brothers in a city where the dead have turned their skins inside out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ew.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll probably watch it.
[SPEAKER_10]: That sounds really cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that kind of like the guy in PBS?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a lot of people that love their Persona, so this is, I'm sure, good news to a lot of the fans of Persona 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_04]: Inside out, man.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, speaking of eBay earlier, if you're desperate for some celebrity memorabilia, eBay, of course, is the place to find it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And since this is vaguely game-related, Gary Coleman is selling his GameCube
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, times are pretty hard for old Gary.
[SPEAKER_04]: And of course he is signing his GameCube as well as the games coming with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which if I remember correctly, there was one from Robots, the movie, the game, and some other crap in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: So let's see here.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you're interested in it, only $510 right now is the going price for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mortal Kombat Deception, Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_04]: Melee, Mario Kart Double Dash, Sonic 2 Adventure Battle, and Sonic Gems Collection.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Gary Coleman has signed each one of those things, so now you can own a piece of Gary.
[SPEAKER_04]: A little itty-bitty piece.
[SPEAKER_10]: He's welcome to keep it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Former gubernatorial candidate here in California.
[SPEAKER_03]: You might remember when Gary Coleman ran for governor.
[SPEAKER_10]: He didn't even freaking make the top ten.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Although that one porn star did.
[SPEAKER_03]: She was in the top ten.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mary Carey or whatever she was.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, I totally supported her.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wasn't she promising a blowjob for everyone that voted for her?
[SPEAKER_03]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's my vote.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I want an old school one, yo.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fifteen bucks for that.
[SPEAKER_10]: No way.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want an old, old one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I want an old school one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like the kind that gets so hot that you can't touch it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, but you know what you can do with that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Light bright companion cube.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good time.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what I'm going to do as soon as I learn how to sew?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to make myself a weighted companion cube purse.
[SPEAKER_03]: People are crazy about their weighted companion cube.
[SPEAKER_03]: I still have not played Portal, so these jokes go over my head.
[SPEAKER_03]: But this joke I get, and I think it's hilarious, because one of the first games I ever remember playing on the Commodore 64 was Zork.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Zork has apparently been smooshed with Pac-Man to create this homegrown game, Pact TXT, and it's available for play at pac-txt.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's Pac-Man meets Zork.
[SPEAKER_03]: And yes, it's as stupid as it sounds.
[SPEAKER_03]: You actually play Pac-Man, but it's in Zork format.
[SPEAKER_03]: In other words, you go, EAT!
[SPEAKER_03]: You have eaten another glowing dot and you type forward.
[SPEAKER_03]: You have moved forward.
[SPEAKER_03]: So stupid it's hilarious, but I'm sure it will get old in about five minutes.
[SPEAKER_03]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyhow, if you would like to give us a call, our Skype line is now open for business.
[SPEAKER_03]: 1-877-GAME-OLR Our username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: I doubt we'll have anything as exciting as the Nintendo World Store call from earlier and Zaku actually sounding not high this week
[SPEAKER_03]: But who knows?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sure our folks will try.
[SPEAKER_03]: So meanwhile, while we wait for some calls since there is a little bit of a delay, let's see if there's any last minute stories from here in chat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or here in studio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, I'm not a chat.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm a me.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways, here's an interesting one.
[SPEAKER_04]: E.G.,
[SPEAKER_04]: Anamura was interviewed in the last issue of Official Nintendo Magazine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, that's in the UK.
[SPEAKER_04]: Talking about what his interests are in the Legend of Zelda series and how he'd like to continue it.
[SPEAKER_04]: One thing he's interested in doing is a 3D remake of A Link to the Past.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which would be fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I hope they do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: And do it in the Wind Waker engine.
[SPEAKER_04]: None of this fucking Twilight Princess shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, we're getting a phone call.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's go take it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh my god, I'm on!
[SPEAKER_08]: This is Odd1 from the chat room.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sorry, what was your name again?
[SPEAKER_08]: Odd1.
[SPEAKER_08]: Odd1!
[SPEAKER_03]: O-D-D-O-N-E.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: You made it.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're a first-time live listener tonight, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I've been listening to you guys for years while I was working.
[SPEAKER_08]: You guys got me through some really tough, long hours, and I'm so grateful to you guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just want to say thanks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, it's words like that that seriously keep us motivated, because, you know, we do this
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_08]: Honestly, I didn't think I'd get through.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't have much on my mind.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just wanted to say thanks.
[SPEAKER_08]: And now that I get free time, I'm going to be listening live every week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Seriously, you guys are just the best.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you so much.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, then tell us about your gaming week real quick.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll ask you questions.
[SPEAKER_03]: How was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_03]: What games have you been playing?
[SPEAKER_08]: Man, all I got here is a GameCube right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is it Gary Coleman's GameCube?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's no good at all.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a money thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a stolen system thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't even want to go into it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's say you had $400 in your pocket right now, enough to buy any of the next-gen systems.
[SPEAKER_08]: Which one would you buy and why?
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, I'd probably buy a Wii and about 20 million of those Wii points because especially with the Neo Geo, the virtual console is just hot.
[SPEAKER_08]: I need that in my life.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is hot.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like seriously, my Wii wasn't even plugged in for about three weeks.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I finally went and plugged it back in today because I wanted to check out some of the new stuff like the Check Me Out channel and Mario 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I went back on and I saw that Simon's Quest was on virtual console and I completely forgot about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And when I saw it, I seriously, I think I got a semi.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, that game is so awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Even with the shitty translation, it's fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: What a terrible night to have a curse.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Game Is Alive.
[SPEAKER_03]: and don't want to hook up the whole Dreamcast and burn the CD or whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's something about it that just, I don't know, is worth the five bucks.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I mean, and also, you know, I associate my computer with work.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll play on it, but when I want to relax, I get on my couch and turn on my TV.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's a good point.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't like to play games on the computer that were originally designed for the console.
[SPEAKER_03]: Something like World of Warcraft or PC developed games, I have no problem playing those on the PC.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why do you think I have so many video game systems?
[SPEAKER_03]: So you can sit on the couch.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I can sit on my couch and use my original controller and play the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I'm going to let you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you so much for taking my call.
[SPEAKER_03]: No problem, Odd1.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's very nice to hear such enthusiasm.
[SPEAKER_03]: It makes us even more excited.
[SPEAKER_03]: So thank you, Odd1, for your call.
[SPEAKER_03]: We appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_03]: He just had so much enthusiasm, like was generally happy to be on the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love that.
[SPEAKER_03]: So great.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you so much.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's go to another call.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_09]: This is Azorme.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hello, Azorme.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_09]: Uh, yeah, I just wanted to talk about, uh, just, like, an overall, the gaming this year.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, you know, it's like, this week, Mario Galaxy and Assassin's Creed is coming out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do y'all find it hard to keep up with all these games?
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, I know we have, like, every, like, you're married, uh, Loki, along with, uh, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is a huge week for games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, this is feedback.
[SPEAKER_03]: With Christmas and everything, it's just like everything is coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I'm trying to say, do you get a chance to actually play them all?
[SPEAKER_09]: Do you find yourself able to play them?
[SPEAKER_09]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, as if you would play, like, you know, do you get all your fun out of them, like your money's worth?
[SPEAKER_10]: What was it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Do we have time to play all these games?
[SPEAKER_10]: Do we have time to play all these games that come out?
[SPEAKER_10]: I personally do not, just given that I have a very busy schedule.
[SPEAKER_10]: I haven't gone into a lot of detail on this, but I'm working on an illustration project.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm still going to classes as a massage therapist.
[SPEAKER_10]: I work as a massage therapist, too.
[SPEAKER_10]: And with my full-time job, I don't have as much time as I would like to play some of these games, although I am dedicating time to Portal next week.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_03]: My friends trying to get me into Tabula Rasa, which I really want to check out.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's just all these freaking MMOs I keep getting sucked into, and those are games that never finish.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you just keep going back for more, and I never have time to play the console games.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I do try to play a little bit of everything.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what makes it so easy to stay on top of the Xbox Live Arcade releases and everything.
[SPEAKER_03]: Those are delivered right to your doorstep, and they're usually really short games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I try to sample as much as I can, but I may not play everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: For example, right now,
[SPEAKER_04]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_03]: And so, you know, if we have more free games, we could easily dedicate, you know, an hour between three of us, you know, playing games or whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: The last free game I got was Dragon's Lair HD.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't remember the last free game we got.
[SPEAKER_04]: The last free game I got, and I don't want it, and I will be selling it back.
[SPEAKER_04]: Viva Pinata Party Animals.
[SPEAKER_04]: Aw, sorry to hear it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I take that back.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dan got us our Halo 3 for free and a bunch of other stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: The last free one I can remember getting was a Midway rep I met at a show was kind enough to give me one of those arcade classics, which was great for me because I loved that shit, those 80 games, so that was cool, but that was a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Play Overlord.
[SPEAKER_03]: Folks in chat are suggesting Gamefly.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, I will play Overlord, I swear.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will step away from Final Fantasy XI this week, the crack, the crack, and play some Overlord.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, Skype line is still open if you want to give us a call.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just a word of advice, call Echo123 before you call us on the Skype, and that way you can hear what you sound like, and you can hear if there's any echoing or any of that stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: If your microphone is really close to your speakers, that's what causes the echo, so sorry, it's okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Any other last-minute stories real quick while we wait for some more calls?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, of course I do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways, Attack of the Show is now in the Guinness Book of World Records for creating the largest arcade machine.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is 1,300 pounds, has 150 arcade games built into it, it's 14 feet tall, and has a 75-inch screen.
[SPEAKER_04]: Plus, it requires quarters that are 3 inches big.
[SPEAKER_03]: They like big things on that program, don't they?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because they made a big Nintendo once, didn't they?
[SPEAKER_03]: I remember that at 1E3.
[SPEAKER_03]: They had that out there.
[SPEAKER_03]: When I become rich, I will one-up everything they do.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, let's go to the phones.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have another call.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_03]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi, who is this?
[SPEAKER_03]: This is Marissa.
[SPEAKER_03]: Marissa!
[SPEAKER_03]: Marissa?
[SPEAKER_03]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm just calling to say hello.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's so nice to be able to hear the show this evening.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, so it's very random that you're listening to us live.
[SPEAKER_03]: We love it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I said it's very random that you're listening to us live.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's very cool, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: I actually finally came across this thing known as a computer, and I purchased one.
[SPEAKER_06]: I had been out of one for about a year because I just didn't have the money, but now I'm back.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I unfortunately have Windows Vista on a budget laptop, so I'm kind of screwed game-wise.
[SPEAKER_03]: Excellent.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, since you have a new computer, has your gaming on the PC consisted of Solitaire and Minesweeper?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, since she's on Vista.
[SPEAKER_06]: With what bloatware Vista is, yeah, because it eats all my memory.
[SPEAKER_06]: Although I was lucky enough, I went to Target before going to Seattle to try to get some games because I took a train trip to Seattle.
[SPEAKER_06]: And so I wanted to have something to pass the time because it's like 38 hours.
[SPEAKER_06]: and I got King's Quest.
[SPEAKER_03]: Awesome!
[SPEAKER_03]: King's Quest is the shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: They re-released all of them.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's supposed to be compatible with Windows 2000 but it doesn't work for Vista very well but oh well, that was cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: That sucks because the King's Quest series was amazing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I loved those games when I was younger, especially King's Quest 4.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was always my favorite because it was based on the fairy tales.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_03]: Very, very cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was really cool, but I don't like these episodic games because I don't like paying $20 for like half an hour worth of game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: You've got to get GameTap because not only are all the King's Quest games available on there, but they also have the Sam & Max.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the only bummer is you have to have an internet connection, so it's not so great for the train.
[SPEAKER_03]: But you can play for like $9.85 a month all the new Sam & Max games.
[SPEAKER_03]: God, I sound like a commercial.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I wouldn't...
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, sweet.
[SPEAKER_10]: Old stuff for me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Otherwise, the dude bought an Xbox.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, so now I spend my evenings falling asleep in front of the TV while he plays Medal of Honor.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_10]: He dates up at 360, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to have to talk to you later to get his gamer tag, and I'll give you Dan's and mine.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, quite simple.
[SPEAKER_06]: Long hair, Chris.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, that makes... My boyfriend, there you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: You do know, like, thousands of people that hear our show just heard that, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: If you get some more friend requests this week, you'll know why.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, okay, I'll go ahead and put Dan's on there, except I can't remember if it's with an underscore or not, but it would be Gunstar Hero.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, I'll let you know for sure later, and mine I never use, so I'll let you know later.
[SPEAKER_10]: But if he's got Halo 3, he should totally play with Dan so I can see Dan get punked.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's all play Uno.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's waiting for that, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not trying to talk him into getting the orange box, because I really want to play Portal.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want to stop singing the song.
[SPEAKER_10]: Isn't this song great?
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, I didn't get it at first, and it was when I finally saw it that I was like, this is the best song ever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Seriously, Jamie was, I remember when that song was in the cage match, and Jamie was like, this song is stupid.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why do people love this song?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, no, I said as a song without a frame of reference, it wasn't a very good song, but now that I have the frame, now that I logged into that stupid site and took the quiz that was on it, the personality thing, I was like, holy crap, this is messed up.
[SPEAKER_10]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, I think that's why it is so cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Although, it does bring a different dimension of weird when your co-worker is singing it in high-pitched falsetto while you're on the phone with a client.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, Marissa... I'll let you guys go.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was great catching up.
[SPEAKER_03]: But please, please log into Xbox Live sometime and we'll play Uno.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, sweet.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'll hook up my webcam and play Strip Uno.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, just kidding.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you have an Amazon wish list ready?
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't wait.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Come on, baby.
[SPEAKER_03]: Marissa, thanks so much for calling.
[SPEAKER_03]: We love you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bye, Marissa.
[SPEAKER_03]: Come back and be in the studio soon, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, bye.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, bye.
[SPEAKER_03]: She has to come back soon so we can hear more stories about the Wunderbra.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought it was the Wunderbra.
[SPEAKER_03]: Great.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, more last minute stories.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll take one more call if anybody calls in.
[SPEAKER_03]: 877-GAME-OLR or username on Skype, Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways, there's apparently a new Bioshock achievement that someone spotted on live.
[SPEAKER_04]: The rumor is the 51st achievement, which is actually on the list there, is 100 points and it is from, it's called Bulletproof.
[SPEAKER_04]: Complete the game on hard difficulty without using a Vita chamber.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, um,
[SPEAKER_04]: Be interesting to see if this actually surfaces maybe in a new update or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways, let's see here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Benjo Kazooie 3, not coming out on 360 anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's been axed.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, hooray.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, wait, there was something about, I saw on Twitter that there was going to be big news coming out about a 360 exclusive being axed.
[SPEAKER_03]: This must be it.
[SPEAKER_03]: That'd be the one, I think.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, snap.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, we're getting one more call.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, it went away.
[SPEAKER_04]: Never mind.
[SPEAKER_04]: One more thing to kind of go back to the MAME cabinet we were talking about earlier.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gamerator, it brings together MAME and beer.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a beer tap in a MAME cabinet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hold that thought.
[SPEAKER_03]: We've got a call coming in.
[SPEAKER_03]: I do want to hear more about the beer thing, but this is a conference call, so I'm always worried about these calls.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi, you're on Orange Lens Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_05]: Tech and Game Podcast.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Bucket, Tokis, and Raven's Dolphin.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's up, you guys?
[SPEAKER_05]: Not much.
[SPEAKER_05]: You were talking about Sam and Max?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Our last caller, Marissa, is a Sam and Max fan.
[SPEAKER_05]: I am huge.
[SPEAKER_05]: I beat the new one today, and oh my god, it's awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is it?
[SPEAKER_03]: About how long of gaming was it?
[SPEAKER_05]: About five hours, but they really changed up some things about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: They added Stinky's Tavern as a restaurant, 50s theme.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: I really love it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Santa goes nuts.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can't go wrong with that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Lots of funny stuff goes great.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is this taking a lot of time on your show recently, the Sam & Max series?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, Call of Duty.
[SPEAKER_03]: Call of Duty.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sam & Max is a good franchise.
[SPEAKER_03]: One of those ones I need to spend more time with, but those damn MMOs, you know how it goes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, but this one has a hint feature, so it's much easier for the noobs to get in.
[SPEAKER_03]: Marissa in our chat room actually follows up and says, Sam & Max rules, but Indiana Jones and the Fate of Atlantis is still number one in my heart.
[SPEAKER_03]: How about Loom?
[SPEAKER_03]: Where's the love for Loom?
[SPEAKER_10]: Loom is great.
[SPEAKER_03]: is awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, what else did you guys want to share with us?
[SPEAKER_03]: Anything else?
[SPEAKER_03]: Overlords on GameTap.
[SPEAKER_05]: Download it from there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I have a copy on Xbox 360 and that way I can get achievement points because I'm a whore for achievement points.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ah, you're right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can play Jericho or something on GameTap.
[SPEAKER_01]: Ah, Jericho.
[SPEAKER_01]: Doesn't Jericho suck?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I've heard that but I want to see that first hand if it does suck.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, because that's what everyone's said to me.
[SPEAKER_01]: Big disappointment.
[SPEAKER_01]: It sucks.
[SPEAKER_01]: Stay away.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what I keep hearing but I like to see these things first hand.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will tell you what kind of cool zombie game I've been playing on GameTap is Typing of the Dead.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've been playing that a little.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a steep learning curve to get all those letters in.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can type uber fast.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe because you can't type, Raven.
[SPEAKER_03]: You type with two fingers, Raven, you're not going to get very far doing that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, you're right.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, well, kids, we've got to let you go because we're going to wrap up the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: But thanks so much for calling.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for taking our call.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Have a good one, you guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: Have fun with your show.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Raven and DeBucket from Tekken Games.
[SPEAKER_03]: which I think is beating us on Op 11 still.
[SPEAKER_03]: You go, boys.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, any other last-minute stories?
[SPEAKER_03]: You were talking about the beer and MAME machine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Skype line is now closed, kids.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry to those who didn't get through.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Gamerator.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's $2,000, but it's a custom-built MAME cabinet, and it comes preloaded, of course, with 180 games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Plus, it's got internal AV hookups.
[SPEAKER_04]: It lets you throw your PC or console in there as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: and then of course it comes doubles as a keg it's got tap and everything so that's awesome beer and maim together another interesting thing I guess there is a sequel to Dig Dug 2 coming I guess it's called Dig Dug Islands it's actually being Namco Bandai has partnered with Verx to produce it as an online PC game
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you're interested in more Dig Dug, there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: There already was like a Dig Dug 1.5 on DS.
[SPEAKER_03]: I had it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, Dig Dug DS.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways, Nexen, of course that South Korean company doing a lot of MMOs and stuff, they're developing a couple games for, well, one for the Xbox 360 and one for the DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: MapleStory is coming to the DS, so that's one that's being worked on right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: The other one is an MMO called Mabinogi, and that's coming to the 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I guess Mabinogi is a cel-shaded MMO that looks interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then MapleStory, I think a lot of people are familiar with MapleStory, so for the DS that would be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then I guess Live is doing something for their 5th anniversary starting November 15th.
[SPEAKER_04]: Lots of parties online.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uno for everybody.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you know, that's interesting because that's starting on Wednesday.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wonder if they got any really kick-ass Xbox Live Arcade games for that day.
[SPEAKER_03]: They haven't said what's coming out this week, have they?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, not yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe they're sitting on something good.
[SPEAKER_03]: What are some really highly anticipated games we haven't got yet?
[SPEAKER_03]: Rez?
[SPEAKER_03]: Rez would be fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it's true.
[SPEAKER_03]: It could be that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, the hella famous shooter.
[SPEAKER_03]: Omega 5?
[SPEAKER_03]: Treasure.
[SPEAKER_04]: Omega 5?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, the one that's called... Ikaruga?
[SPEAKER_03]: Radiant Silver Gun.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ikaruga is the one that, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: But Omega 5, they've been pimping that out for a while now.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: That'd be kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, the party starts on Microsoft this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought Screwjumper was coming out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did that already come out?
[SPEAKER_03]: Screwjumper?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I think they have confirmed that is this week's title, Screwjumper.
[SPEAKER_03]: But there could be a second one that's really cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, there could be a second one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Screwjumper looks stupid.
[SPEAKER_03]: It might be okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, thank you as always for blessing us with your presence.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's your final thought?
[SPEAKER_10]: My final thought is I can't find where I can save this wallpaper to so that I can make it fit my desktop.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'll thank myself for blessing the show with my presence.
[SPEAKER_03]: And my final thought is I want enchiladas really bad because looking at this Aldo Berritos mug makes me crave horchatas.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, thank you as always for being here.
[SPEAKER_03]: And what's your final thought?
[SPEAKER_03]: DMN is still doing the insanest hour
[SPEAKER_03]: And Saturday, I believe Travis Donovan is back up and running after a little bit of a summer hiatus.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know he had a show this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: So hopefully by the new year, we'll be up and running with lots of shows.
[SPEAKER_03]: We are in talks to do some stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we'll get back to you with that.
[SPEAKER_10]: And just also the FYI, next week, week after, I will not be here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Cry.
[SPEAKER_10]: And the week after that.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: No, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_03]: We haven't decided yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: We could use a break, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: I take that time during Thanksgiving to travel somewhere, so I kind of want to go back to Magic Mountain.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've got to find somebody to go with me, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hopefully he hasn't burned down yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hope not.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, well, that's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you guys so much for tuning in to us and supporting independent podcasting and independent radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: We've said that a lot tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: Again, if you guys like what you hear, or even if you don't like what you hear, please still help us out by telling two people you know
[SPEAKER_03]: about the program.
[SPEAKER_03]: And if you can't think of anybody to tell, then spread the word on the internet.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can do that through iTunes by leaving us a positive review or one of those many, many sites like Podcast Alley, I don't know, Yahoo Podcast, Dig, whatever the hell.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just help us spread the word.
[SPEAKER_03]: We really appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_03]: You guys are awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Until next time, my name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_03]: That is Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: She is Dark Sakura.
[SPEAKER_03]: And together, we are... Are not Captain Planet.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, we are not Captain Planet.
[SPEAKER_03]: But we are Orange Lounge Radio, so take care and we'll see you next week.