[SPEAKER_02]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and released to our podcast stream twice weekly To listen to the first half of this episode visit www.orangeloungeradio.com for links to websites with listings of past episodes Now the conclusion of this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_12]: Ultimate Quest Ultimate Quest
[SPEAKER_12]: You've probably heard FootyMonster, maybe Xenocore, call in this show.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, they are hosts on another show over at All Games, and it's called Ultimate Quest.
[SPEAKER_12]: And that show should be out this week.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think they said Monday night or Tuesday afternoon-ish, so check them out at UltimateQuest.net.
[SPEAKER_12]: We had a conversation about MMOs, and I was kind of like the guy there that played WoW on Final Fantasy XI, but it was a good panel because they had another guy that was like City of Heroes, and a couple were playing EVE Online, and
[SPEAKER_12]: Lots of different MMOs being talked about.
[SPEAKER_12]: We were kind of talking about societies and getting into a pretty in-depth discussion.
[SPEAKER_12]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_12]: I approve.
[SPEAKER_12]: So thanks to the kids at Ultimate Quest for having me on their program.
[SPEAKER_12]: Now we can get back into some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, so Super Mario Galaxy of course is coming out not next week, but the week after next.
[SPEAKER_14]: And, you know, it's been revealed that there's going to be a certain hidden playable character in the game.
[SPEAKER_14]: Apparently, when you...
[SPEAKER_14]: All 120 stars in the game.
[SPEAKER_14]: Complete all the purple coin missions.
[SPEAKER_14]: Defeated Bowser a second time.
[SPEAKER_14]: You can play as Luigi.
[SPEAKER_14]: And actually, Luigi, he will jump higher and further.
[SPEAKER_14]: Also runs faster, but has trouble stopping.
[SPEAKER_14]: And says otherwise they have the same moves.
[SPEAKER_14]: Luigi needs new sneakers!
[SPEAKER_14]: At least it's not, you know, Luigi's Mansion.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, that would be, I'm glad it's not, you know, Luigi's Mansion embedded in the game.
[SPEAKER_12]: Although, I don't know, part of me thinks Luigi's Mansion got a bad rap.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I actually liked Luigi's Mansion until it got to the baby part, and then the baby part kind of creeped me out.
[SPEAKER_12]: Really?
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, I thought you liked scary video games, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a difference between stupid scary and, like, I like Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like Resident Evil.
[SPEAKER_12]: Mental screwing with your mind's scary.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, thanks to the ESRB ratings, some new games have been leaked for upcoming US Virtual Console releases.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alien Soldier is one of the games that is going to be coming to Virtual Console soon, as well as Shining Force 2 and Bubble Bobble will be coming to Virtual Console.
[SPEAKER_12]: And it is assumed that they have worked it out so that you can get past level 30 in the Virtual Console release of
[SPEAKER_12]: GoNintendo had a voicemail from...
[SPEAKER_14]: Mario himself.
[SPEAKER_14]: Charles Martinet.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_14]: Announcing Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_14]: 3 will be out tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love Super Mario Bros.
3.
[SPEAKER_12]: Mario 3 is fucking rad.
[SPEAKER_12]: I love playing through Mario 3 and not using Warp Zones.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because I love Giant World.
[SPEAKER_12]: Who doesn't love Giant World?
[SPEAKER_06]: Giant World's the best, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: My favorite is going in on Kuriboh's shoe.
[SPEAKER_12]: There's only like one level in the whole game where you do that, huh?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not even a mandatory level, is it?
[SPEAKER_06]: But with the Game Genie code back in the day, you could keep the shoe through other levels.
[SPEAKER_12]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which sort of made it stupid for the ones you have to fly to get shit though.
[SPEAKER_12]: Now all you need is to actually be able to play this game online.
[SPEAKER_12]: Like imagine if you could be Mario and play against a Luigi that's millions of miles away.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know that's not going to happen.
[SPEAKER_12]: It should.
[SPEAKER_06]: But will it?
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, for UK Virtual Console we've got some fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sonic 3D Flicky's Island for 800 Wii Points will be out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, the Sonic 3D games were sort of interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: They weren't really, really 3D, just sort of 3D, but anyway.
[SPEAKER_12]: I can't believe it's not 3D.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I can't believe it's not 3D, exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then, um, we also have, uh, as soon as it loads, Samurai Ghost, which was a TurboGrafx-16 game, um, which is a side-scrolling, you know, slash-
[SPEAKER_06]: Fighter, Shooter, you know, guy with a sword game.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I think it's funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: The whole purpose of the game, according to the opening screen, is it's an order from the King of Heaven.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then we have Art of Fighting, Neo Geo.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't need to say anything more about Art of Fighting because that's the game that gave us... King.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, well, besides King, it gave us the two characters that spawned the introduction of Dan Hibiki.
[SPEAKER_06]: in the Street Fighter series, which would be Ryo and Robert Garcia.
[SPEAKER_12]: Was Dan supposed to be like a parody of them or something?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, he was.
[SPEAKER_12]: How funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because Ryo was like a Ryu knockoff.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Robert Garcia had, I guess, he had some other moves, so they actually combined the two characters into, you know, Mr. Sucktastic Godoken.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I thought it was great.
[SPEAKER_06]: And again, keep in mind,
[SPEAKER_06]: Dan's like one of my favorite characters.
[SPEAKER_06]: Especially in Puzzle Fighter, because you have to be really freaking good to beat people in Puzzle Fighter using Dan.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because he drops all red blocks.
[SPEAKER_12]: So you have to drop a lot really fast.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, you have to be really good.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I can proudly say that I've beaten somebody using Devilot.
[SPEAKER_12]: Or pray that a red break gem never falls.
[SPEAKER_06]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, you know, I digress.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which is the whole point of the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Digression.
[SPEAKER_12]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_14]: Ah, anyways.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, you know, we don't really talk too much about Atari.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, they don't give us a lot that's worth talking about anymore.
[SPEAKER_14]: In case you haven't heard, you know, Atari, they have not too many licensed games out there.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, I think the last few licensed games haven't been that great.
[SPEAKER_14]: You know, what with the, they used to have the Driver series.
[SPEAKER_14]: Dragon Ball Z Budokai Tenkaichi
[SPEAKER_14]: It's kind of sad to see because really all that they're going to be left after this is gone is pretty much Alone in the Dark.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: This is what I have to say.
[SPEAKER_06]: First of all, two things.
[SPEAKER_06]: One about Dragon Ball Z and one about Atari.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dragon Ball Z has been off the air in Japan when I graduated college.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I didn't graduate college, but when I was out of high school.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I take that back because I had an episode taped off the TV.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, the series ended.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dragon Ball GT Dragon Ball GT
[SPEAKER_06]: But it still doesn't mean it's not even old over here.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's still old.
[SPEAKER_06]: The whole thing is saturated.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that and Atari, oh my god.
[SPEAKER_12]: Actdeft says in our chatroom, chat.orange.com, Actdeft says, Atari, doing nothing since the 1980s.
[SPEAKER_06]: And to tell Ranma, Dragon Ball GT, in my opinion, does kind of count because it was going back to the original flair of what Dragon Ball was.
[SPEAKER_06]: But Dragon Ball Z was better.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: Dragon Ball Z, Budokai Tenkai G3 Godzilla Unleashed
[SPEAKER_12]: and Jenga on the Wii and the DS.
[SPEAKER_12]: I remember reporting on this game when it was first announced.
[SPEAKER_12]: We were like, the fuck?
[SPEAKER_12]: Can't you just play, like, real Jenga?
[SPEAKER_12]: Which I believe they did at Penny Arcade Expo.
[SPEAKER_12]: They played real Jenga.
[SPEAKER_14]: And to be honest, then they also have another, like, classic compilation game coming to the PSP.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because that's all that ever comes out on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's all they have coming out of this year.
[SPEAKER_14]: And then Lone Dark...
[SPEAKER_14]: Dragon Ball Z was replaced by Brioni Kenshin.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rurouni Kenshin was replaced by Naruto.
[SPEAKER_06]: And now Bleach is doing its damnedest.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that's the transition I'd like to point out.
[SPEAKER_14]: And seriously, companies, stop making so many Naruto games.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, there's like five every year.
[SPEAKER_14]: Seriously, we don't need that many Naruto games.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think I have like a stack of them in our vault collecting dust.
[SPEAKER_12]: In the vault.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it really is the vault.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a whole room dedicated to my video game collection.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, anyhow, you know, they say imitation is the finest form of flattery, but I don't know about this one, because apparently there is now, Walmart is now selling these little knockoff Wiimotes.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's a device made by ToyQuest, and what it is, it basically looks like a Wiimote, but it has a little LCD screen on the Wiimote.
[SPEAKER_12]: And you actually can play tennis...
[SPEAKER_12]: with this Wiimote.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's a little tiny LCD screen, but I don't even think it has motion control or whatever because the screen is so fucking tiny.
[SPEAKER_06]: It would be hilarious if it did.
[SPEAKER_06]: How would you see it?
[SPEAKER_12]: I'll swing it and then, oh shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: Someone needs to hack it to be a VMU emulator and put a chow on there.
[SPEAKER_12]: Seriously, these things cost under $20.
[SPEAKER_12]: I want to say it said it was like $7 for this thing.
[SPEAKER_12]: That might be too much for this.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know about that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Quality People should give crappy useless toys to the bad children instead of coal Because you can actually use coal
[SPEAKER_12]: This is what you get for being a bad kid.
[SPEAKER_14]: Is that like driving kids by a burned out factory telling them that Disneyland burned down or something?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, that was deep thought.
[SPEAKER_12]: I know that was deep thought.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was jack handy.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anyhow, so yeah, those are kind of stupid.
[SPEAKER_12]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_12]: These types of things and these knockoffs and these unoriginal bastards and tiny little LCD screens that try to pass for a game, these things just piss us off and it makes us angsty.
[SPEAKER_12]: And when we get mad, people die.
[SPEAKER_12]: Or at least the FUs of the week are unleashed.
[SPEAKER_06]: F you goes towards the digestion problems I inherited from my mother.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mom, fuck your genes.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, I love you.
[SPEAKER_06]: And her birthday's tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_06]: So happy birthday to my mom, who will be 48.
[SPEAKER_06]: Happy birthday, Jamie's mom.
[SPEAKER_06]: But anyway, yeah, everything I eat really makes me sick.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I'm just going to stop eating altogether.
[SPEAKER_06]: Except for couscous.
[SPEAKER_14]: FU to Saints Row for not allowing you to change what your character looks like when you're playing system-linked multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_14]: So everybody looks like the same dude wearing the same black t-shirt and the same jeans.
[SPEAKER_14]: F.U.
[SPEAKER_14]: to the bruise on my leg that still kinda hurts this week but at least it's getting a little better
[SPEAKER_12]: Maybe I can roll my pants up far enough I can show you one cat.
[SPEAKER_12]: Actually, I probably can't.
[SPEAKER_12]: My bruise is like in here.
[SPEAKER_12]: I can't roll my pants up that far.
[SPEAKER_12]: I might be a little too much skin for Operator 11, so no show for you.
[SPEAKER_14]: I was going to say one more thing real quick.
[SPEAKER_14]: What?
[SPEAKER_14]: My cat tried to perform like a level 3 execution on my wife's legs.
[SPEAKER_14]: You know, Manhunt 2 reference.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: She attacked her leg with her back claw and it like sliced it.
[SPEAKER_14]: It looked like she was trying to like cut her leg off or something.
[SPEAKER_12]: Holy kitty.
[SPEAKER_14]: But, you know, without... It was the cutest level 3 execution ever.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's it, my F.U.
[SPEAKER_12]: just went to my bruise on my leg.
[SPEAKER_12]: So at least I don't have to have the band-aid on it anymore.
[SPEAKER_13]: Puppy!
[SPEAKER_13]: My F.U.
[SPEAKER_13]: goes to your neighborhood for there being no street lights and street signs covered by trees.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because I almost got lost getting here because I couldn't read anything.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I like followed him all the way from like the big main road over and I was like, hey, I bet that's Puppy.
[SPEAKER_06]: because I saw the college sticker on your car.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then I was like, he went right past Rob's street.
[SPEAKER_06]: I almost went right past Rob's street.
[SPEAKER_12]: It is kind of, yeah, they don't really have streetlights here.
[SPEAKER_12]: They didn't invent them yet, I guess, when these houses were built.
[SPEAKER_12]: What can I say?
[SPEAKER_13]: It's rural.
[SPEAKER_13]: And F you to the housing market because I got scared a little bit and when half the people that I work with at my company got laid off this week.
[SPEAKER_13]: D'oh.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, well, I work for a...
[SPEAKER_13]: I do drafting work for a carpenter, and they just laid off a bunch of their foremen.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hope I get laid off.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, seriously, because if I get laid off, I get like three months of severance pay and can collect unemployment while I start my massage business.
[SPEAKER_06]: That'd be fantastic.
[SPEAKER_12]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_13]: That would be nice.
[SPEAKER_13]: Nice little cushion.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, well that's going to do it for our FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_12]: Let's get back into some gaming news, shall we?
[SPEAKER_12]: Shall we?
[SPEAKER_12]: We shall.
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, why don't you take it away?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't wanna.
[SPEAKER_06]: You gotta.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why?
[SPEAKER_12]: Because I said so.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: For anyone who follows the Child's Play charity, the 5th annual Child's Play charity drive is beginning.
[SPEAKER_06]: Basically, it was the whole charity was the brainchild of the Penny Arcade Powers That Be
[SPEAKER_06]: and is now basically the gaming community's way of giving to those in need.
[SPEAKER_06]: For children who are in hospitals in 25 states and 5 countries.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you can donate your items through Amazon and it is considered a tax-deductible gift.
[SPEAKER_06]: So keep that in mind if you have those deductions coming up.
[SPEAKER_06]: The drive... Sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Their fundraiser dinner, I apologize, is set to take place on December 11th at the Washington State Convention and Trade Center in Seattle.
[SPEAKER_06]: So go play.
[SPEAKER_12]: Get the brainstorming, folks.
[SPEAKER_12]: We need to think of what we here at OLR can do to help out this lovely charity that gives gamers a good name.
[SPEAKER_12]: So we'll have to think of something we can donate or a fundraiser we can do.
[SPEAKER_12]: Maybe we'll have a ditter-thon, a DDR-thon.
[SPEAKER_12]: Wouldn't that be fun?
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, maybe not.
[SPEAKER_12]: You never know.
[SPEAKER_12]: We'll think of something.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, one awesome game that's coming out this year has gone gold, and that would be Crysis.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's due out November 16th, so I hope you have your new PC by now, because you're going to need it.
[SPEAKER_14]: And, of course, it'll be the first game to utilize the CryEngine 2.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, that's not the same engine used in Yaris.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's a different CryEngine.
[SPEAKER_14]: And, of course, hopefully it'll be coming to consoles soon.
[SPEAKER_14]: There is a single-player demo that's available now, which...
[SPEAKER_14]: Hackers have gone ahead and poked their noses through some of the DirectX workaround codes inside there.
[SPEAKER_14]: And they've found stuff like hidden weapons, vehicles, and bad guys from the full version.
[SPEAKER_14]: So now, with a little bit of cutting and pasting, they're able to play with every gun in the game, as well as tanks and attack chopper.
[SPEAKER_14]: Sounds like how I play games.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, it does.
[SPEAKER_14]: All the guns, a tank, and an attack chopper.
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_12]: So it's kind of like Think Sam and Max, but like really, really long.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's going to start in 2008 in the spring, and they're already running the ads on it.
[SPEAKER_12]: And the little quote from the ad says, And of course, you know, American McGee did that Alice in Wonderland game that was, you know, pretty fucked.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm sure you're going to see lots of your fairy tales done the right way.
[SPEAKER_12]: Dark and gory, the way they were originally.
[SPEAKER_12]: I will be looking forward to, I imagine this is going to have to be in it, the Hansel and Gretel, because I can't wait to push the witch in the oven.
[SPEAKER_12]: That'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: The original fairy tales were all kinds of messed up.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, who would read that to their children?
[SPEAKER_06]: I would.
[SPEAKER_12]: I would like to see... My mom handed me the book and said, go read it and don't come bother me until you finish this chapter.
[SPEAKER_14]: I would like to see the Grimm fairy tales done by Sam and Max because I think that would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_14]: That would be kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_14]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sony is going to be doing an animated Resident Evil movie.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's actually a CG animation.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're calling it Biohazard Degeneration in Japan.
[SPEAKER_06]: So...
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a presumption that it's going to be called Resident Evil Finding Necro over here, which is kind of a dumb name.
[SPEAKER_06]: They said it's going to have groundbreaking visual effects and a brand new storyline.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, oh well, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's supposed to be out in 2008.
[SPEAKER_12]: Nah, we won't see.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't really want to see it.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, I'm kind of over Resident Evil like 10 years ago.
[SPEAKER_06]: I liked the last movie.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, I did.
[SPEAKER_14]: If you're over Resident Evil, perhaps you may be interested in a few other films that are coming, including Onimusha, which is starting production in April.
[SPEAKER_14]: Apparently they also have a poster now revealed for the Tekken movie.
[SPEAKER_14]: Which the poster looks stupid, I might add.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's a giant T that looks like it's being held up.
[SPEAKER_13]: T for Tekken!
[SPEAKER_14]: Wow, it's creative.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_14]: It's already down the road of DOA.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's apparently the Onimusha... Dead on arrival.
[SPEAKER_14]: The Onimusha adaption, of course, is expected to begin April of 2008.
[SPEAKER_14]: And, of course, Silent Hill director Christopher Gans is going to be at the helm.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, that may not suck.
[SPEAKER_12]: may not and unfortunately the Tekken poster if I were to sum up the movie based on the poster I would say suck and how many times based on the poster I'd be all where's Big Bird to tell me this episode was brought to you by the letter T and the number 69 and how many times have fighting games made good movies
[SPEAKER_13]: Hey, I remember the Tekken anime that came out.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, animes are usually better than movies anyways.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Tekken anime, my problem with that is that it was all completely done on computer, and I prefer cell animation, so that's what was bad about that.
[SPEAKER_14]: That also had a lot of butt rock in it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, the US one.
[SPEAKER_12]: Video Games Becoming Movies
[SPEAKER_12]: Pirates of the Caribbean
[SPEAKER_12]: That probably means you can't actually type your own sentences.
[SPEAKER_12]: You have to make things from the pre-rendered things that are in there because we have to keep our children safe because these are Disney games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like using the Final Fantasy XI macros?
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know that for sure.
[SPEAKER_12]: Don't quote me on that.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know if that's the case in this game.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know if any of our chatters have played it, but I just know in Toontown that was the case.
[SPEAKER_12]: I had a friend that played Toontown for a long-ass time, actually.
[SPEAKER_12]: Pirates of the Caribbean, I wouldn't mind checking this out.
[SPEAKER_13]: I would check it out, but Puzzle Pirates would probably still be better.
[SPEAKER_12]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know, and plus, my fondness for Pirates of the Caribbean is the ride, not the movie.
[SPEAKER_12]: I know that might be like blasphemy to some people, but I could care less about Johnny Depp.
[SPEAKER_12]: Although he was a kind of cool addition to the ride.
[SPEAKER_12]: And, you know, some of the other stuff they added on the ride.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_12]: We will see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, well, um, we have one that says, Hey guys, I was wondering if you could recommend some older 360 games that might be worth picking up used.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was thinking about PSU, but not sure if it was any good, thanks.
[SPEAKER_06]: And this comes from Mark.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, PSU sucks, so don't play it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um,
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_14]: You can also play the offline version for free, so, I mean, don't necessarily think you have to play it online.
[SPEAKER_14]: Plus, the expansion's coming out here pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: It should, they've already done a buttload of, my friend Julie, Casame19, she plays a butt ton.
[SPEAKER_12]: She is always on that fucking game whenever I'm on live.
[SPEAKER_06]: She does nothing but play that game.
[SPEAKER_12]: Wow, amazing.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, she's like, that's her Evercrack.
[SPEAKER_12]: Tips from the chatroom, Rob with two B's is mentioning Circuit City has PSU on the cheap.
[SPEAKER_12]: So if you are interested in that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Some other folks are recommending some games.
[SPEAKER_12]: Actdeft recommending Condemned.
[SPEAKER_12]: DMN recommending Crackdown.
[SPEAKER_06]: Crackdown is the I like jumping game.
[SPEAKER_12]: I recommend staying the hell away from Perfect Dark Zero, first off.
[SPEAKER_06]: I liked Perfect Dark Zero.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I would suggest Marvel Ultimate Alliance.
[SPEAKER_06]: To me, that is the best 360 title.
[SPEAKER_06]: Burnout.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, I do like Cache.
[SPEAKER_12]: Even if it is an old game with souped up graphics.
[SPEAKER_12]: Or how about Test Drive Unlimited?
[SPEAKER_12]: That was a good game that I think was... How about No?
[SPEAKER_14]: How about Kiss My Butt?
[SPEAKER_14]: If you want some older games that have dropped in price, Dead Rising.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, Dead Rising is a good one.
[SPEAKER_14]: If you can find that.
[SPEAKER_14]: Actually, Far Cry Instinct's Predator wasn't that bad.
[SPEAKER_14]: I thought you said good games.
[SPEAKER_14]: And then I would also say probably...
[SPEAKER_14]: Not Prey, that's for sure.
[SPEAKER_14]: Definitely not Chromehounds.
[SPEAKER_14]: Prey was like Ghetto Portal.
[SPEAKER_14]: But I wouldn't buy Burnout, because there's a new Burnout game coming out in January.
[SPEAKER_14]: I would say probably... Okay, we've given enough suggestions.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's not that old, but Oblivion is also really good for a solo game.
[SPEAKER_06]: We have an email from another Mark.
[SPEAKER_12]: Your suggestion quota is up.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hi Mark.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, it's amazing.
[SPEAKER_06]: My brother and I were talking about Count Dekula, but we couldn't remember the name.
[SPEAKER_06]: We also loved You Can't Do That on Television.
[SPEAKER_06]: Barf.
[SPEAKER_06]: About Loki's a few of the week to women.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you haven't learned by now, you will.
[SPEAKER_06]: You as a male will always lose arguments against women.
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't believe it when people told me.
[SPEAKER_06]: True statement.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it's true.
[SPEAKER_06]: Men are from Mars and women have already invaded it and destroyed all that are holy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course we have.
[SPEAKER_06]: because we're excellent.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I'm trying to find more short ones because we've got a couple of long ones.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hold on because I'm trying to load a little something for that last emailer because I played the You Can't Do That
[SPEAKER_08]: Castle Ducula, home for many centuries to a dreadful dynasty of vicious- Tell me you would not play a fucking video game based on this.
[SPEAKER_08]: This would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Legend has it that these foul beings can be destroyed by a snake through the heart, or exposure to sunlight.
[SPEAKER_08]: This does not suffice, however, for they may be brought back to life.
[SPEAKER_08]: I apologize, the audio is so low.
[SPEAKER_08]: Once a century, when the moon is in the eighth house, we will be blood.
[SPEAKER_08]: The latest reincarnation did not run according to plan.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, it's ketchup.
[SPEAKER_12]: Here's the techno part, yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: In the Vampire Hall of Fame, yeah, there's no vampires any other.
Don't you, don't you hurt me.
Cause it's a vampire.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's the most random opening.
Count Ducula.
[SPEAKER_06]: Count Ducula.
[SPEAKER_06]: For anyone who doesn't know, God, it's so loud.
[SPEAKER_06]: Count Ducula was actually a character from Danger Mouse.
[SPEAKER_06]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: If anyone who ever watched Danger Mouse.
[SPEAKER_06]: So the southern one says, the classic game of the week segment seems to be like obscure cult hit of the week.
[SPEAKER_06]: It says, will you be featuring games that are a little more known to us?
[SPEAKER_06]: I did Cyberbots.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, like everybody knows Cyberbots.
[SPEAKER_12]: A lot of people know Cyberbots.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's Kong.
[SPEAKER_12]: and maybe she'll feature it later.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: I kind of like the obscurity for now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, keep in mind that all of the classic games that I like are really the more obscure ones anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, of course, if I'm going to be picking out the games, I'm going to be picking out all the weird shit that I like.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, but I covered Fantasy Zone.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's not obscure.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, okay, I'll do Guardian Legend.
[SPEAKER_12]: Even that's kind of obscure for some people.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is my favorite game.
[SPEAKER_12]: I say do what you want.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, I'm going to do what I want.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm going to do what I want.
[SPEAKER_12]: I go to school and I kill people.
[SPEAKER_12]: I run with gangs.
[SPEAKER_12]: I digitally insert Jabba the Hutt back in Star Wars.
[SPEAKER_12]: I do what I want.
[SPEAKER_12]: I run with gangs.
[SPEAKER_06]: But to be fair, I do like a good number of, I guess, more mainstream titles.
[SPEAKER_06]: I won't do one of Colibri.
[SPEAKER_06]: Neo Geo Pocket Color
[SPEAKER_06]: and on the... No, just on the Geo Pocket Color.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_12]: Don't bother defending.
[SPEAKER_12]: Just say, I'm going to do what I want.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm saying how people can find these games easily.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it did have a US release, so... Anyway, this one comes from J-Rod.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hi, J-Rod.
[SPEAKER_06]: Love the show you guys put on.
[SPEAKER_06]: I really dig how the show is live.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have two guitars on my PS2 with both Guitar Hero 1 and 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now the problem is I don't have my PS2 anymore, but I do have a PS3, a 60 gig that can play the old PS2 games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently Sony and everyone else didn't bother to make an adapter to get the Guitar Hero controllers to work on the PS3.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was wondering if any of you guys had any first-hand experiences.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you anyone who did with the aftermarket adapters out there and could give me a recommendation or review of any of them?
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks, and keep up the awesome show.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think Pelican makes one that works.
[SPEAKER_14]: There is an adapter out there I know that works.
[SPEAKER_14]: I would bet money it causes a delay, though.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't think it did.
[SPEAKER_14]: Really?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: I know there's one that we did as a story a while back.
[SPEAKER_14]: Luckily, I didn't actually bet the money.
[SPEAKER_14]: That actually does work, so...
[SPEAKER_12]: Xenocore in chatroom.
[SPEAKER_12]: See, when we don't know, we can always rely on chatroom.
[SPEAKER_12]: Xenocore in chat says, not true, I have the adapter.
[SPEAKER_12]: So there you have it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, also, I think that it was great.
[SPEAKER_14]: Sony doesn't love you there.
[SPEAKER_06]: I also think it's fantastic that it says this email is sponsored by the Olive Garden, home of the NeverEnding Salads.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know why I find that funny.
[SPEAKER_14]: Olive Garden.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not for the salad, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: OLR, I appreciate that you guys tell us the Japanese release dates, but I was wondering if you guys have any Japanese listeners.
[SPEAKER_06]: and I guess this comes from Thomas.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think we do.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm pretty sure we do.
[SPEAKER_06]: When we check the stats, we do see quite a number of connections from Japan.
[SPEAKER_06]: And we've gotten emails from listeners in Japan before too.
[SPEAKER_06]: We've got people all over the world because we are cool that way.
[SPEAKER_06]: So now for the really freaking long emails.
[SPEAKER_06]: How about that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Really freaking long email segment.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dear OLR,
[SPEAKER_06]: Pointing to a letter that was sent to you last week, it really shames me that a fellow gamer can be so blatantly ignorant.
[SPEAKER_06]: Has anyone ever considered the fact that one of the main reasons that Nintendo has managed to stay afloat for so long is because of its first party games?
[SPEAKER_06]: Starting with the Nintendo 64, the graphics of the system sucked.
[SPEAKER_06]: The audio play was horrible, but it still managed to give you a few of the great franchises that you and I loved, like Mario, Zelda, Metroid, and other well-known franchises, and bring them, though it still looked horrible...
[SPEAKER_06]: and Bring Them, but it still looked horrible.
[SPEAKER_06]: The GameCube may have been a different story.
[SPEAKER_06]: In my opinion, the GameCube was a great system.
[SPEAKER_06]: While not on par with that of the Xbox and PlayStation 2, it had excellent graphics and almost all games played in high frame rate.
[SPEAKER_14]: Pardon me for being ignorant, but what Metroid game was on Nintendo 64?
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: It wasn't.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because Prime was on... No, it was a big deal when Prime came out because it was OMGZ Metroid.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: Never mind.
[SPEAKER_14]: Just to make sure I didn't miss anything.
[SPEAKER_06]: Pokemon Snap, yo!
[SPEAKER_06]: Pokemon Snap, yeah!
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, so, to continue with this,
[SPEAKER_06]: It had excellent graphics and almost all games played in full frame rate.
[SPEAKER_06]: It also brought your favorite franchise into beautiful 3D detail, but it would have been so much better if they had online play.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wouldn't have even bought my GameCube if it didn't have a new Metroid game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nintendo's first party developers have managed to bring back our favorite franchises and make us love them that much more with each new title.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's mainly because of the fact that Nintendo first party developers and the fact that they make such great games are the only reason that Nintendo managed this far.
[SPEAKER_06]: Though I may not know everything, I just want to point out that these few details are far as it goes with Nintendo's first party games and developers.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's just hope that it doesn't repeat any past mistakes.
[SPEAKER_06]: To the Yaris, this is a letter that was sent to the Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_06]: It said...
[SPEAKER_06]: Dear Xbox Live Arcade, we have always had a great relationship.
[SPEAKER_06]: The day I met you, you sent me Geometry Wars.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now you send me Yaris.
[SPEAKER_06]: Does this mean you're breaking up with me?
[SPEAKER_06]: Sincerely, Anonymous.
[SPEAKER_06]: Brilliance.
[SPEAKER_12]: Winner.
[SPEAKER_12]: Email of the week right there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I've got another long one.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is the last one.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's by DJ Dysentery.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Best name ever.
[SPEAKER_12]: You have died of dysentery.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm not wearing that shirt tonight, sadly.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm wearing my panda with the panda and crossbones instead of skull and crossbones.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, OLR.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love your show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Y'all are amazing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do we have a southern guy?
[SPEAKER_06]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: I listen to y'all everywhere I go and named my firstborn daughter Skye.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_12]: Send the birth certificate as proof.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't believe it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So on and so forth.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: To beat the proverbial dead horse, your qualms concerning the term microtransactions would give even Captain Jean-Luc Picard a headache of massive proportions.
[SPEAKER_12]: would you say Halo 3 sold 3 giga copies?
[SPEAKER_06]: Micro in this sense is not used as a prefix for an actual numerical factor such as centi, milli, kilo, nano, etc.
[SPEAKER_06]: but more as a description of relative size in contrast with macro.
[SPEAKER_06]: Refer to the established English terms of macroeconomics and microeconomics, if you will.
[SPEAKER_06]: But no one says microtransactions anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because as the English language is to buzzwords, human being is to a horribly grotesque cross-species partial abortion, think Minotaur.
[SPEAKER_06]: It never should have
[SPEAKER_06]: should have been and should have been put out of its misery, which I'm quite sure the entirety of Orange Lounge Radio will be quite eager to do after reading this superfluous, verbose, and... Thank you, whoever emailed this in to make her read these words.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, I have very good pronunciation.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: A vexatiously nitpicky email comprised of run-on sentences.
[SPEAKER_06]: I do have to agree with you there.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is fairly run-on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Although actually you are grammatically correct in your last sentence, I have to say.
[SPEAKER_06]: I shall spare you any further opportunities to become tongue-tied and I wish you all the best.
[SPEAKER_06]: I look forward to each episode as eagerly as a cocaine addict awaits for his next hit of snow.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rubber buggy baby bumpers, DJ Dysentery.
[SPEAKER_12]: And by the way, you... By the way... Okay, he obviously was putting that in just to fuck with you.
[SPEAKER_06]: By the way, you misspelled cocaine.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_06]: There already is one.
[SPEAKER_12]: Is there really?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm pretty sure there already is one.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's also... You can find a podcast.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, there is a Grammar Nazi podcast because somebody sent it to me.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I'm not even kidding.
[SPEAKER_06]: Where can I download it?
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't remember who...
[SPEAKER_06]: Who did it, but I listened to it about a year and a half ago where they would receive emails about different grammatical mistakes and then try to give you the proper way to say that and certain usages and when it's appropriate to use this spelling or that spelling.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I also found one that was all about the differences between British English and American English.
[SPEAKER_12]: Where can I got that podcast?
[SPEAKER_06]: LOL
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: You can do what everybody else does and search for it on iTunes.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't wanna.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hate that my iPhone is making me use iTunes, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: Can you continue, please?
[SPEAKER_12]: What?
[SPEAKER_12]: We's done.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, no more emails?
[SPEAKER_06]: We is done.
[SPEAKER_12]: We is done.
[SPEAKER_12]: We done good on those emails.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, if you want emails, mailbag at orangelaunceradio.com.
[SPEAKER_12]: Sorry to the people we didn't get to tonight.
[SPEAKER_12]: There's just too damn many emails.
[SPEAKER_12]: What can we say?
[SPEAKER_14]: Back to the gaming news.
[SPEAKER_14]: Anyways, with all these patches and stuff being applied to new games for the PlayStation 3 and games that you might already have on the PlayStation 3, to support the DualShock 3 has gotten a lot of people wondering, hey, maybe I can just import a Japanese DualShock controller into my non-Japanese country and get to play these games with RumbleTastic features sooner than everybody else.
[SPEAKER_14]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because apparently importers like PlayAsia said they've already pre-sold their expected supply.
[SPEAKER_14]: And Sony, of course, doesn't support importing stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: So you will not be able to probably buy any anytime soon.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because actually importers are charging upwards to $80 per joystick for what you would probably normally get for $50.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I'm sure that's going to go up.
[SPEAKER_14]: of course you know new games you just had a patch for Resistance Fall Man that added Rumble I know Motorstorm has Rumble now there was a patch with Ratchet and Clank Future that has Rumble just fucking wait
[SPEAKER_13]: Why would they have to patch in rumble features?
[SPEAKER_14]: Because you know the original 6-axis controller had no rumble.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because rumble would interfere with the tilt sensors somehow in this magical world.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because you can't actually have tilt and rumble in the same controller.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh wait, no, Nintendo did that.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, hey.
[SPEAKER_14]: Just wait.
[SPEAKER_14]: Really.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, plain, you know,
[SPEAKER_14]: Resistance, Fallen Man with Rumble is not going to make it like, oh my god, this is the best game ever now!
[SPEAKER_13]: The only game I really want to play with Rumble is Rez.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I would hand off the Rumbler to someone else.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because, you know, Rez is on the PS3.
[SPEAKER_06]: We've all read that article.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, we have a, I guess, late-breaking news thing.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm going to jump in here with something that's panning out live while the show is going on.
[SPEAKER_12]: I need like a
[SPEAKER_12]: A fanfare or something.
[SPEAKER_12]: Or we need something.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: What do we have?
[SPEAKER_12]: How about a drum roll with a laptop?
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm looking for a fanfare noise.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_12]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_12]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_12]: We've got it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Now some late breaking news.
[SPEAKER_12]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_12]: Actdeft is practically flooding our chat room with what is going on in the latest Game Facts Battle.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know, every damn year they do a character battle, every year.
[SPEAKER_12]: This is the sixth year of the character battle.
[SPEAKER_12]: And what makes this year different is that instead of two characters doing battle, it's groups of four.
[SPEAKER_12]: And then two emerge victorious.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, we are now down to the final four.
[SPEAKER_12]: And typical winners, Link and Cloud, are in there.
[SPEAKER_12]: They've both won before.
[SPEAKER_12]: Solid Snake is also in the top four.
[SPEAKER_12]: But this is the amazing thing is that this looks to be the very first year that a Final Fantasy character or a Link character will not win
[SPEAKER_12]: L-Block
[SPEAKER_14]: Did I miss something?
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, seriously?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because Tetris is pwned.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because somehow an L block just fucking beat all these other characters.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know what, though?
[SPEAKER_12]: Well deserved, honestly.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well deserved, because Tetris is one of those games I think people forget, you know, that is the casual game.
[SPEAKER_12]: That was the casual game that really opened up the game to a lot of people.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm just glad that news had nothing to do with Tingle, so that's... Yes.
[SPEAKER_14]: I thought for a second there they were just going to be like, yeah, Tingle's going to win.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm like, fuck.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's going to suck.
[SPEAKER_12]: I can't wait for that.
[SPEAKER_12]: This just in, Eye of Judgment sold its millionth copy.
[SPEAKER_14]: Loki, get the tights.
[SPEAKER_14]: There's some interesting things about Eye of Judgment too.
[SPEAKER_12]: Do you know how many people have come into chat tonight and said, one down, 999,199 to go.
[SPEAKER_12]: Our whole contest has become counterproductive.
[SPEAKER_12]: We are driving sales of Eye of Judgment.
[SPEAKER_14]: I heard they have issues.
[SPEAKER_14]: How so?
[SPEAKER_14]: Let me put it this way.
[SPEAKER_14]: They have similar issues to Rock Band and Guitar Hero 3.
[SPEAKER_12]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_12]: Certain integral parts of... They're not even going to be able to make a million of them.
[SPEAKER_12]: You goddamn cheater!
[SPEAKER_12]: Loki fucking cheated in this contest.
[SPEAKER_12]: He knew they didn't have the parts to make a million of them.
[SPEAKER_06]: How about I cleanse the palette?
[SPEAKER_12]: Asshole.
[SPEAKER_06]: And didn't I say this was going to happen?
[SPEAKER_06]: Didn't I tell you?
[SPEAKER_12]: No, wait, I didn't, I'm sorry, I didn't do my actual story.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I thought you did.
[SPEAKER_12]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, fine.
[SPEAKER_12]: I have to do the Famitsu story real quick.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, fine, do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're going off on your tangents, confusing me.
[SPEAKER_12]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: God damn it!
[SPEAKER_06]: Chocolate!
[SPEAKER_12]: Get the bitch some chocolate, Christ almighty.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah!
[SPEAKER_06]: But I'm not going to eat it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here you go.
[SPEAKER_12]: And damn it, I accidentally closed the tab that had this story on it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Now I can't even do it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Famitsu ran a list of the top 100 games that readers dig.
[SPEAKER_12]: And actually, this is kind of similar to the character battle because I believe all the top games were basically Final Fantasy games and Zelda games.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm trying to bring up the list right now.
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_12]: were that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Other notable games on the chart, we should point out Street Fighter 2 came in at number 20.
[SPEAKER_12]: The Super Mario Brothers came in at 21.
[SPEAKER_12]: Final Fantasy 6 was in 25.
[SPEAKER_12]: The fuck?
[SPEAKER_12]: 6 is like one of the best ones.
[SPEAKER_06]: But Final Fantasy 7 has more fandom-y stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh well.
[SPEAKER_12]: Japan, you screwed that up.
[SPEAKER_12]: Chrono Trigger, number 28.
[SPEAKER_12]: Kingdom Hearts 2, number 29.
[SPEAKER_12]: The original Legend of Zelda, 46.
[SPEAKER_12]: 51, Pokemon Red and Green.
[SPEAKER_12]: And if you want to know where L Block ended up on the Famitsu list, 96 was where Tetris Game Boy ended up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Gradius was on there.
[SPEAKER_12]: Gradius was 98.
[SPEAKER_12]: Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_12]: 3 was 99.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to know where R-Type is.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, you'll just have to pick up this week's Famitsu magazine.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't want to go to San Francisco to go buy it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, you can do your story now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now again, didn't I say this was going to happen?
[SPEAKER_06]: And don't get me wrong, I love the technology.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have one myself built into my PS3.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love Blu-ray, but I also loved Betamax.
[SPEAKER_06]: and Betamax was far superior to VHS.
[SPEAKER_12]: I would also like to point out DarkSakura has an impressive Laserdisc collection.
[SPEAKER_06]: I do, because I used to go to anime conventions and they'd sell Laserdisc for five bucks a piece.
[SPEAKER_12]: So basically, if DarkSakura likes your media format, you're fucked.
[SPEAKER_12]: She probably has a collection of 8-tracks somewhere.
[SPEAKER_06]: Laserdisc did last for a while.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was the enthusiast format.
[SPEAKER_14]: You could saw off someone's head with one of those things, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, they were pretty heavy.
[SPEAKER_14]: Whatever happened to Videodisc?
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Enjoy.
[SPEAKER_12]: That would fucking rock.
[SPEAKER_12]: I hope PlayStation 4 has those large pizza-sized discs.
[SPEAKER_06]: That would be rad.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want my next system to be the size of three Atari 5200s.
[SPEAKER_06]: The end.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I want it to weigh as much as ten Xboxes.
[SPEAKER_12]: I want to have to get a dolly to put this thing in my house.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know the Xbox is larger than an Atari 5200, but not wider.
[SPEAKER_12]: Tangent.
[SPEAKER_12]: What were you going to say about Blu-ray?
[SPEAKER_06]: Kmart's not selling them anymore, so anyone, whatever, you know, no one really shops at Kmart.
[SPEAKER_14]: I didn't know Kmart was still around.
[SPEAKER_14]: I love the personal opinion that gets interjected in this show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, I take that back.
[SPEAKER_12]: Here's tonight's news.
[SPEAKER_12]: Kmart pulled Blu-ray.
[SPEAKER_12]: Whatever, no one shops at Kmart.
[SPEAKER_06]: I take that back.
[SPEAKER_06]: I did buy pillows at Kmart because they were on sale.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I bought my sheets for my massage at Kmart.
[SPEAKER_06]: But other than that, no one shops at Kmart.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay, I don't know if Kmart's exactly the demographic for Blu-ray.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's exactly what I'm saying.
[SPEAKER_12]: Who thinks, gee, I'm going to go get a Blu-ray player.
[SPEAKER_12]: Where can I get a really good, top-of-the-line Blu-ray player that's, I'm going to go to Kmart.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, keep in mind, even though Kmart did declare bankruptcy, they did go back and buy Sears.
[SPEAKER_06]: So.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: If I want an Icy, I'll go to Kmart.
[SPEAKER_06]: I go there to buy sheets for my massage table and that's about it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Or if heaven forbid I want something from the Martha Stewart collection, I'll go to Kmart.
[SPEAKER_12]: Or if I want to go laugh at the poor people.
[SPEAKER_12]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm among you.
[SPEAKER_12]: And Ranma is yelling in chat, hey dammit, I shop at Kmart.
[SPEAKER_12]: RavensDolphin says, shit, I shop at Kmart.
[SPEAKER_14]: Much like I go back to the conversation we had in part A where I said, LARPing, something you don't really want to admit to.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_12]: Here's the reason why I don't... Okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: Here's the reason why I don't shop at Kmart anymore, even though this isn't supposed to be Dude, they have little Caesars.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's why I shop at Kmart.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, I do also sometimes buy my DVR discs for my camera.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_12]: I used to, my fondest memories of going to Kmart going shopping were in the 80s.
[SPEAKER_12]: Like we used to go, you know, it would be like the big department store trip day, we're going to go to Kmart.
[SPEAKER_12]: Here's the problem, here's the reason why I don't shop at Kmart anymore.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because the store hasn't fucking changed a thing since the 80s.
[SPEAKER_12]: Besides what's on the shelves.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, not even the clothes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Except... Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Except I did find a cute sweater there.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it also was like one of those 80s revival styles.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think I saw some underwear for sale that was actually from the 80s.
[SPEAKER_06]: I bought socks.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can buy socks at Kmart because socks, you know, are socks.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think they actually still have those doors that you have to like step on the mat where it triggers the door before infrared technology or something like that.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay, can we move on before we get the hate mail from the Kmart?
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, they're not carrying Blu-ray players anymore, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, the hate mail from that one Kmart person, okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: Anyways, here's some exciting news, and I'm going to say this is very specific exciting news.
[SPEAKER_14]: It has nothing to do with Kmart.
[SPEAKER_14]: LucasArts and BioWare are teaming up for something.
[SPEAKER_14]: Something.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, that's right.
[SPEAKER_14]: They're working on an undisclosed interactive entertainment product.
[SPEAKER_14]: But it's LucasArts and BioWare, so what else do you really need?
[SPEAKER_14]: It's going to be awesome.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's going to be like Knights of the Old Republic or something like that.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's Knights of the Old Indiana Jones Republic, that's right.
[SPEAKER_12]: I feel the need to say something nice about Kmart now.
[SPEAKER_06]: They do carry the diet cranberry serumist.
[SPEAKER_12]: I will pre-order the LucasArts BioWare game at Kmart.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, I won't.
[SPEAKER_12]: But I will tell you one thing that Kmart's good for.
[SPEAKER_12]: They don't care about street dates.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because that's where I got Serenity, like two weeks before it came out.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I got it as an early Christmas gift for Extover, and he was all excited because he had Serenity on DVD before any of his friends.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, I'm sorry, LucasArts?
[SPEAKER_12]: They're making something.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hooray!
[SPEAKER_12]: Rumors, rumors, rumors.
[SPEAKER_12]: And this rumor has something to do with Oblivion.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's right, the Elder Scrolls Oblivion.
[SPEAKER_12]: The game that just won't stay out in the news.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, this game has been making headlines since it came out.
[SPEAKER_12]: And now, it should be noted that the parent company of Bethesda Softworks, that's ZeniMax Media, has registered the domain name
[SPEAKER_12]: Elder Scrolls Online.com Could this mean that Elder Scrolls Oblivion could make its way online?
[SPEAKER_12]: Be an MMO?
[SPEAKER_12]: Hell, somebody already hacked the game to do this on the PC version.
[SPEAKER_12]: Could this be a further way to milk the Oblivion franchise?
[SPEAKER_14]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_14]: It could give World of Warcraft a run for their money.
[SPEAKER_12]: Puppy, how many hours have you spent on Oblivion?
[SPEAKER_12]: A lot.
[SPEAKER_12]: A lot, right?
[SPEAKER_13]: A lot in a two-week span of time.
[SPEAKER_12]: So what would you think of this?
[SPEAKER_12]: If there was an Oblivion online, would you play it, or is this jumping the shark?
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: With as much characterization and customization areas, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: They would have to do a lot to expand the world.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because running around in the world in Oblivion, it's like running, running, running, running, tree, rock,
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh look, a rabbit.
[SPEAKER_13]: Run, run, run, run, run.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh look, hey look, a dungeon.
[SPEAKER_14]: We're going to be punching horses online.
[SPEAKER_14]: In the face.
[SPEAKER_12]: A sheep tossing contest would be fun.
[SPEAKER_12]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, but you know what it doesn't have?
[SPEAKER_06]: You can't kick bugs in the face.
[SPEAKER_12]: You can kick sheep in the face, probably.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can't kick bees in the face.
[SPEAKER_12]: Sorry, I'm looking at chat right now.
[SPEAKER_12]: I gotta go back to the Kmart thing because this shit's funny.
[SPEAKER_12]: SSJ100 Matt in chat says, Kmart still sells Rakas Dukakis shirts.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hilarity.
[SPEAKER_12]: Rob with 2B says, I go to Kmart to trip over stuff in the aisles.
[SPEAKER_12]: Blue light special.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, anyway, sorry.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, so Elder Scrolls may be online, at least if recent domain names are to be believed.
[SPEAKER_12]: Skypline is opening soon.
[SPEAKER_12]: You can call us at 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_12]: Our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: We have a couple more stories before we get there.
[SPEAKER_12]: Right, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, if someone would stop hogging the mic, puppy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Puppy.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, you're no longer our foreign correspondent.
[SPEAKER_06]: You live in my town now.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can be our resident puppy Video game story Hey Rob, guess what?
[SPEAKER_12]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: Game art Okay, so Namco Bandai I agree with Misty Why would you want to kick a bee in the face anyway?
[SPEAKER_06]: Just because it's the act of kicking a bee in the face Oh, well, shit I'm so sorry Just because it's the novelty How dare I
[SPEAKER_12]: What?
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know, Loki, you're just like, you look impatient over there like, I want this show to finish.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, he's watching that video again.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm not watching that video again.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Namco Bandai.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, Namco Bandai.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have announced a Wii exclusive.
[SPEAKER_06]: Soul Calibur Legends.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which is very, very happy.
[SPEAKER_06]: We will have everybody, so far.
[SPEAKER_06]: and hopefully new people.
[SPEAKER_14]: Wait, I think we're getting some late breaking news, Rob.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, sorry.
[SPEAKER_14]: Late breaking news.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_14]: Here's...
[SPEAKER_12]: We go to our correspondent, Loki, live in the OLR studio with Late Breaking News.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, apparently the reaction to Soul Calibur Legends going gold is, Who gives a fuck?
[SPEAKER_14]: It's going to be crappy anyways.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hey, did anyone remember, what was that stupid game with, it's like a spin-off of Tekken.
[SPEAKER_14]: God, I've blocked it from my brain.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, the one that had Nina, it starred Nina, didn't it?
[SPEAKER_14]: Quick, Jamie, Tekken Trivia.
[SPEAKER_14]: Death by Degrees.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's this game all over again.
[SPEAKER_12]: Ivy, Death by Degrees.
[SPEAKER_12]: But will she have the whip?
[SPEAKER_12]: That's all we need to know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I actually kind of wanted Death by Degrees just because of me being a big Tekken nerd.
[SPEAKER_06]: I even have the dumb Tekken game that was on Wonderswan.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's pretty sad.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was like Tekken Card.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's like buying Tekken on your cell phone.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: Quick, another story, then the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_14]: Anyways, um, yes.
[SPEAKER_14]: So this totally, I don't know, perpetuates all the stereotypes of...
[SPEAKER_14]: Halo 3 Players
[SPEAKER_14]: was told by his mother to turn off his Xbox 360 as it was getting late.
[SPEAKER_14]: After he refused, his mother took his AirCard, which is apparently an adapter you can use for your cell phone to get Wi-Fi, from the 360, preventing him from playing online and prompting a fit of rage that would see the child frantically search through the house before punching his mom in the face.
[SPEAKER_14]: The kid then retreated to his room, but soon had to deal with the local sheriff deputies, who his mom
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_14]: Kids these days.
[SPEAKER_14]: Kids do the darndest things.
[SPEAKER_13]: But now I can just imagine people on Halo yelling, Oh, you stupid mother puncher!
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, dude, this is stupid anyways.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, your fucking kid is, like, playing Halo.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's a maturity game.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh my god, it must be the violence of the game that caused him to punch his mom in the face.
[SPEAKER_06]: What I really want to know is, um, what have they been doing to their child up to that point?
[SPEAKER_06]: They would have a violent reaction.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or maybe their child already had psychological problems.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Took them to Kmart.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's our new OLR in-joke.
[SPEAKER_14]: We have Kmart.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hey, Timmy, it's Disneyland.
[SPEAKER_14]: This is Kmart.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, it's Disneyland.
[SPEAKER_14]: Kmart.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, Disneyland.
[SPEAKER_14]: Go play.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it seems to me...
[SPEAKER_06]: I was freaking some fucking noobs!
[SPEAKER_06]: You know...
[SPEAKER_06]: Dan's little cousin's kid comes over and plays games at our house sometimes.
[SPEAKER_12]: And has he ever punched you in the face?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's always been well-behaved.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's because his parents teach him right.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's a fault with the parents, but I do think it's good that she did have him actually stand accountable for what he did.
[SPEAKER_12]: ShadowCharlie asks, how old was this kid?
[SPEAKER_14]: The age and name were withheld.
[SPEAKER_13]: I heard he was just 15 or something like that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, I heard you suck.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, your mom.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, some Florida kid.
[SPEAKER_14]: Indian River County website.
[SPEAKER_14]: They have a website for Indian River County for Florida.
[SPEAKER_14]: Where to stay, where to dine, what to do.
[SPEAKER_14]: Discover our lifestyle choices, including dying.
[SPEAKER_13]: With pictures of old people on a golf course and on a beach and in a dining room.
[SPEAKER_13]: Dying.
[SPEAKER_12]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_12]: Lordy, lordy, lordy.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right, let's open up the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_12]: If you want to give us a call, the phone number is 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_12]: Or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: And you can comment on any of tonight's stories.
[SPEAKER_12]: or you can make a Kmart joke.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't really care tonight.
[SPEAKER_12]: After tonight's show, I'm like crying from laughing so hard.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's not that funny.
[SPEAKER_12]: I know I'm going to be listening to this show like in the car later, so I'm going to go, this show really wasn't that funny.
[SPEAKER_12]: Why were you laughing so much?
[SPEAKER_12]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_12]: It's the Midnight Special, Raven's Dolphin.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hi, Midnight Special, Raven's Dolphin.
[SPEAKER_12]: Did you just get back from Kmart?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, I just got back from Kmart, and guess what?
[SPEAKER_10]: There is no Blueway players!
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, what's on your mind, Raven's Dolphin?
[SPEAKER_10]: Mario Galaxy, that's what's on my mind.
[SPEAKER_12]: I know, but let's not go there.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know Jamie said that she's getting a retail copy at her store, so I actually got the chance to play it at a GameStop.
[SPEAKER_10]: And what did you think, young man?
[SPEAKER_10]: I think the game looked great.
[SPEAKER_10]: I love the controls.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think the game just looked great.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, well, the game was on an HDTV, so it left a lot to be desired, which was a little sad.
[SPEAKER_09]: A little sad about that, but the controls were great.
[SPEAKER_09]: Everything was great about it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is this a game that kids across the country are going to be craving come this Christmas season?
[SPEAKER_09]: Craving?
[SPEAKER_09]: They're going to be dying for it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Are you going to be shooting each other like they were PS3s?
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, I mean, you know, if you want to get the game, just never mind.
[SPEAKER_12]: I was going to make a joke, but I'm beating that joke on the ground.
[SPEAKER_14]: Super Mario Galaxy is so awesome, you'll punch your mother in the face just to play some more.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, is the game that great?
[SPEAKER_12]: Is it worth punching your mom in the face over?
[SPEAKER_12]: I think so, but...
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's go ahead and call his mom so that we know to hide.
[SPEAKER_06]: You don't know what your child is saying.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, what else did you call it to tell us about Ravenstaff?
[SPEAKER_12]: And you just wanted to say that Mario Galaxy is cool?
[SPEAKER_10]: Mario Galaxy and Phoenix, sorry, Charles and Turbobout is very good.
[SPEAKER_10]: Music's phenomenal.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, you know Shane, who used to guest on this show a lot before he moved back to Kansas.
[SPEAKER_12]: Like, okay, we have a Ventrilo server for World of Warcraft slash Final Fantasy XI, basically.
[SPEAKER_10]: Be careful on those.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, well, yeah, I've heard... No, I want Ventrilo Harassment Guy to sign on to our Ventrilo.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm like, roll out the fucking red carpet for him.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think that guy's fucking hilarious.
[SPEAKER_12]: But anyway, I would be so honored if he came on.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'd be like, yay, it's Ventrilo the Harassment Guy.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anyway, the thing about Shane, though, is that he has been signing on to Ventrilo this week.
[SPEAKER_12]: And we're like, Shane, where are you?
[SPEAKER_12]: You're not in WoW, and you're not playing Final Fantasy XI either.
[SPEAKER_12]: He's like, oh, I'm playing Phoenix Wright.
[SPEAKER_12]: And we're like, why are you signed on to Vent?
[SPEAKER_12]: He's like, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm playing Phoenix Wright.
[SPEAKER_12]: I just thought I'd say hello.
[SPEAKER_12]: He's like, okay, I've got to go.
[SPEAKER_12]: I've got a case.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what I need to do?
[SPEAKER_06]: I need to play Guild Wars and Ragnarok at the same time
[SPEAKER_10]: I've been doing this experimental podcast called the Cartoon Cast.
[SPEAKER_10]: We've been talking about Count Ducula and showing old cartoons like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I would love to see a Count Ducula game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who wouldn't?
[SPEAKER_14]: I would not like to see a Count Ducula game.
[SPEAKER_14]: Why?
[SPEAKER_14]: Because the show's been off the air for years.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, so Dragon Ball Z has been off the air for years.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why are we still getting games?
[SPEAKER_12]: Because Atari, that's all they got.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, you know what?
[SPEAKER_12]: They probably still show episodes of it on the Kmart TVs, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I've seen episodes of Count Dracula on TV a while back.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: But that's what the internet's for, right?
[SPEAKER_12]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: That important.
[SPEAKER_12]: We've got YouTube.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: YouTube's amazing.
[SPEAKER_12]: Is that it then, Raven's Dolphin?
[SPEAKER_10]: That is it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you for taking my call.
[SPEAKER_12]: You are most welcome, sir.
[SPEAKER_12]: Have a great week.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: Wow, he hung up on himself.
[SPEAKER_12]: I didn't even click the button.
[SPEAKER_12]: If you want to give us a call or use name on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio, or our phone number, 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, it's truly Legend of Zaku.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hello, Legend of Zaku.
[SPEAKER_12]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_00]: Um, nothing.
[SPEAKER_00]: Don't mind me for the fact that this girl just dumped me a short while ago.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm sorry to hear that.
[SPEAKER_00]: I am.
[SPEAKER_00]: But yeah, I guess, you know... Whiskey makes it all better.
[SPEAKER_00]: Jamie.
[SPEAKER_00]: Manhunt 2, you know, that whole, that whole controversy, that whole clusterfuck that, that Rockstar Manson Okay, seriously, Zaku, wait, I gotta stop you right here.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_12]: After breaking up with your girlfriend, I would not recommend playing Manhunt 2.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's gonna give you totally bad ideas.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm not gonna, I'm not, I'm a sidler, right?
[SPEAKER_00]: I've talked to him since I was like, what, 11?
[SPEAKER_00]: So, yeah, I guess, I don't know, I don't get, I don't get why, you know, why companies like Rockstar just, you know, they try to
[SPEAKER_00]: and try to half-ass their way by just covering up stuff, you know, covering up, you know, bits that were thrown back when the ESRB told them to, and all of a sudden, you know, hackers find a way to make us gamers look bad, to make the industry look bad.
[SPEAKER_12]: Honestly, when they said, oh, we're going to mask this stuff, that was just an open invite to the hackers to say, find out how we mask this and unmask it.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, I know I can understand that the rating board actually knew about the content.
[SPEAKER_00]: that was blurred out, but wouldn't it make more sense not to give ammunition to the critics, to anyone who's out to get people like Rockstar for the fact that they get called out on stuff that was supposedly rejected before but is still in the game, just not seen.
[SPEAKER_00]: Kind of like the whole hot coffee thing, where it still shouldn't have been on the disc in the first place.
[SPEAKER_00]: and they should have learned not hiding, not obscuring it from the ratings board, not doing that, but just not having the common sense to not keep it out of the disc in the first place.
[SPEAKER_00]: So be it if you have to recreate the build, but that shit happens in our job.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know what just occurred to me because we were talking about Oblivion a little bit ago?
[SPEAKER_12]: You know, this is very strange.
[SPEAKER_12]: It just occurred to me
[SPEAKER_12]: Did they not make Bethesda go back and re-rate Oblivion because somebody found a way to hack the game so that the girl's top could come off and you could have boobies?
[SPEAKER_00]: But you also have to understand... Isn't this the same fucking thing?
[SPEAKER_00]: You also have to understand that, you know, we don't know whether or not that company, you know, submitted that, you know, all the assets for the characters within, you know,
[SPEAKER_00]: for the ratings board.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: But hold on.
[SPEAKER_00]: I just had an epiphany with this whole thing.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, totally.
[SPEAKER_12]: Wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_12]: I just owned ESRB.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_14]: You didn't.
[SPEAKER_14]: And here's why.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's because...
[SPEAKER_14]: That was on the PC that they did the mod.
[SPEAKER_14]: Mods on PCs are fairly available, whereas a PSP version, the hack it, means you have to have an illegitimate copy of the game.
[SPEAKER_00]: But still, it's on principle.
[SPEAKER_14]: What a fucking great line we are walking.
[SPEAKER_00]: It shouldn't have been on the disc or on the actual... It's fucking boobies too.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think they should have just taken the AO rating.
[SPEAKER_12]: Honestly, I think the problem is that the AO rating is the kiss of death.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's the same problem with X-Men.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, because the problem is the AO rating means your game does not get published for the PlayStation 2, the Wii, or the PSP.
[SPEAKER_12]: And that's the problem.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's the problem.
[SPEAKER_00]: You only get limited to one platform.
[SPEAKER_00]: The other thing you have to understand is that legislators right now, they want to push bills that will add more quote-unquote truth in the ratings.
[SPEAKER_00]: Basically trying to find a way to call people out for mods, even if it wasn't the responsibility of the designer itself.
[SPEAKER_00]: Just for the fact that it shouldn't give people...
[SPEAKER_00]: should give hackers or any folks like that the tools to create that much controversy to give that much ammo.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm going to agree with Fursby in our chat room on that who says it's just fucking pixels.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I agree.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's pixels, but then it's something that the human brain can translate as boobs.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, let's also realize that the legislators making these decisions and trying to get all this stuff done, they're like generations behind us.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, they're only out to score political points.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, the bill's fate be damned.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_00]: All they care about is keeping their seat.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, once they die off and go away, we'll get some smarter people in there and things will be better.
[SPEAKER_12]: But then we're going to run into the same complaints.
[SPEAKER_12]: Zaku, I've got to let you go because we're going on five minutes of this call.
[SPEAKER_12]: We've got to get some more calls.
[SPEAKER_12]: But thank you for your perspective.
[SPEAKER_12]: We appreciate it as always.
[SPEAKER_12]: And sorry to hear about the girl.
[SPEAKER_12]: There's plenty of fish in the sea, Zaku.
[SPEAKER_12]: You'll find one.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: If you want to give us a call, 1-877-GAME-OLR or use our username on Skype, Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, this is Rob with 2Bs.
[SPEAKER_12]: Wow, Rob with 2Bs.
[SPEAKER_12]: How you doing, sir?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I'm doing fine.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just decided to call in because it was too long to write in chat.
[SPEAKER_12]: I was going to say, I think we hear from you a lot on email and totally appreciate it, but I think this might be the first time I can recall you calling into the show.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's
[SPEAKER_07]: VG Expo
[SPEAKER_12]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_12]: Sorry, I just said the forbidden phrase on the show.
[SPEAKER_12]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: Especially since the man is near rabid.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anyway, what did you want to say about America's VG Expo?
[SPEAKER_12]: Did you go, Rob?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I went on Saturday.
[SPEAKER_07]: It really is only worth a day trip if you live in the area.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was in Philadelphia Convention Center, which is downtown, about 10 minutes from the airport.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I hate to admit it, but it was a better location.
[SPEAKER_07]: They had the Rock Band Tour event.
[SPEAKER_07]: They had the Dell Intel Hi-Def Tour.
[SPEAKER_07]: Gosh, I'm trying to remember.
[SPEAKER_07]: They had a few contests on Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, that's all I can remember.
[SPEAKER_12]: It sounds like there was a lot to see.
[SPEAKER_12]: It sounds like it was E for All.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I didn't go to E for All, but you get done with things fast there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Plus, they didn't have much on the forums or anything.
[SPEAKER_07]: Basically, on the day I was there, they had the journalist forum, they had the Mortal Kombat movie, they had their Jack Thompson panel, and they had something I skipped, the Postal 2 preview.
[SPEAKER_12]: Sounds skippable.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want to make it short, so anybody who didn't go can understand what went on.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Game Journalists interviews is always a good one and nobody goes to it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's... Gosh, I can't remember the names of the people.
[SPEAKER_12]: What kind of game journalists were they?
[SPEAKER_12]: Were they independent folks like us that do podcasting?
[SPEAKER_12]: Or were we talking like folks from GameSpot, 1UP type people?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: We had one from 1UP, one from GameStop.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not GameStop, EGM.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: The original editor of EGM.
[SPEAKER_07]: When it was spelled out.
[SPEAKER_07]: And...
[SPEAKER_07]: They had the director of marketing for Ziff Davis.
[SPEAKER_07]: He was really informative.
[SPEAKER_07]: To make a long story short, the best thing he said was, if you want to be a game journalist, and he said this because it's in their own company, you should blog on 1UP and make reviews less than 90 words.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's
[SPEAKER_07]: Wait.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's the best way to get noticed.
[SPEAKER_12]: If you want to be a game journalist, you should get reviews that are less than 90 words?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yaris.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's really short.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sucks.
[SPEAKER_07]: It takes at least 10 more words to get your mom on Mother of the Year nomination.
[SPEAKER_14]: Really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really sucks.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, here we go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_06]: I got it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yaris.
[SPEAKER_06]: At least it's not E.T.
[SPEAKER_06]: on the Atari 2600.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, we can't actually bury it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, here we go, here we go.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yaris sucks, would rather have gone to Kmart.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, um... The sound you hear is a dead horse being beaten over and over again in the studio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, well, the Mortal Kombat movie is very good.
[SPEAKER_07]: It could make you motion sick, because they have a really long quake sequence in there, and it's, um...
[SPEAKER_07]: A lot of video game graphics running in the background while the interviews are going on.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's actually, in my opinion, it's too much video game graphics, but they do some really funny transitions.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it's worth a listen.
[SPEAKER_07]: It leaves the gray area gray.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then Jack Thompson and the guy he was sparring against was Lorne Lanning, who helped to co-create Oddworld Inhabitants.
[SPEAKER_07]: and they were sparring off and Jack was funny and he was civil and, you know, I really hate, you know, I don't have any dirt on him.
[SPEAKER_07]: He was very smart.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, he knew he was in enemy territory.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, you know.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, he probably went back onto the game politics, put comment forums a couple hours later and started slandering people.
[SPEAKER_13]: They all smelled like ass.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know, his comments on game politics are really like personality too.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: So,
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, Rob, we... Oh, yeah, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, Lorne pretty much lost the interview because he got emotional and he started attacking Jackie Poo's character, which was really a mistake.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oops.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, you know, it doesn't matter who won.
[SPEAKER_07]: It doesn't change my opinion.
[SPEAKER_12]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's just one debate.
[SPEAKER_12]: He may have won the battle, but he hasn't won the war.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you should have seen they made us go through the security check.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, Rob, we've got to let you go, but we really appreciate the call talking about the VG Expo, which we all forgot happened, so I'm glad somebody was there to remind us, alrighty?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I only live like 90 minutes from it, so... Nice.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, glad to hear you had a good time, and hope to hear from you in the future.
[SPEAKER_12]: Don't be a stranger.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, see ya.
[SPEAKER_12]: Take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_12]: I feel bad because I'm making our callers wrap it up, but, you know, I know there's still a bunch of people that want to call in, so we'll take maybe two more calls?
[SPEAKER_12]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or use your name on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: If you want to give us a call.
[SPEAKER_12]: I will open it up for some... Oh, never mind, we're getting a call.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_12]: Hi, you are on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: We cannot hear you.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hola, bienvenidos a Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: Quien es?
[SPEAKER_12]: Did you say Guinness?
[SPEAKER_03]: Did you plug in my mic?
[SPEAKER_12]: What?
[SPEAKER_12]: The crap is happening.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_12]: Were you not expecting to get through?
[SPEAKER_11]: No, I didn't plug my mic in.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, well, good job, DMN.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, hi, DMN.
[SPEAKER_12]: What's on your mind now that we can actually hear you?
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm actually calling in response to one of the long emails Dark Sakura had about Nintendo and ignorance and the Nintendo 64.
[SPEAKER_12]: Goodie, goodie, what do you have to say?
[SPEAKER_11]: Do any of you have any idea as to why Nintendo is still around?
[SPEAKER_12]: Uh, Mario.
[SPEAKER_12]: No.
[SPEAKER_12]: Handheld.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, um, because of their, uh, involvement still in the, um, Hanafuda card business.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's exactly it, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_11]: No.
[SPEAKER_11]: Pokemon.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: That game has sold well over 14 to 15 million copies, and that's just the originals alone.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's the reason why Nintendo's still in business.
[SPEAKER_11]: Had that game not have sold well in America, Nintendo would be kaput.
[SPEAKER_11]: So the Nintendo 64 tanked.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's all admit that it tanked.
[SPEAKER_11]: It wasn't that great a system.
[SPEAKER_11]: Nintendo lost a lot of money on it, and they didn't do that great on the GameCube either.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're just now rebounding back with the DS and the Wii.
[SPEAKER_11]: So saying that the Nintendo 64 kept it in their form, no.
[SPEAKER_11]: Did it have games I personally enjoyed?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I don't think it was that successful of a system.
[SPEAKER_12]: Rob with two B's, our last caller, is back in chat and says, Nintendo sells at profit.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's why they're still around.
[SPEAKER_11]: That too.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, the GameCube from its inception sold profit.
[SPEAKER_11]: The Wii, since its inception, has sold at profit.
[SPEAKER_11]: The DS, even with both models, has sold at profit.
[SPEAKER_11]: So Nintendo knows what they're doing with hardware.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's why they're still in it.
[SPEAKER_12]: And like I said earlier, Pokemon Snap is the shit.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, you know, Pokemon for the win.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: Any other thoughts for our listeners tonight, DMN?
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, man.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, Guitar Hero 3 massively multiplayer-a-thon that I talked about on my show.
[SPEAKER_11]: I want to pitch that really quick.
[SPEAKER_00]: What's this?
[SPEAKER_11]: If you are an OLR fanboy, listener, on-air talent, get together on Xbox Live or on a Nintendo Wi-Fi connection this Saturday.
[SPEAKER_11]: I believe it's November the 9th.
[SPEAKER_11]: and get together, play with some fellow OLR listeners and have some fun because Guitar Hero 3 is a very fun game especially on multiplayer this time around.
[SPEAKER_12]: Or you could join our band on the website.
[SPEAKER_11]: That too, I did.
[SPEAKER_11]: I joined it like just now.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, I see your request.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm going to go in and approve it right now.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm working on that right now as we talk.
[SPEAKER_11]: He's clicking on the red X. I am.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, and now I'm going to click on the button that hangs up on you, okay?
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: Bye, friend.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: They're saying that since the project started, they've been using 670,000 PlayStation 3s.
[SPEAKER_06]: According to this, it says the FAH is now the most powerful distributed computing network ever at over a petaflop.
[SPEAKER_12]: That sounds like something that would be on Dateline NBC, a petaflop.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's over 250 teraflops, which is a trillion calculations per second.
[SPEAKER_06]: So they have been using the PS3 as a computer.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the whole point of the folding project is basically to look how proteins fold because they have evidence to show that proteins that don't fold properly are related to Alzheimer's and other diseases.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: The amazing things being accomplished with the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_12]: What can we say?
[SPEAKER_12]: And Rob with 2Bs asks in chat, what's a microflop then?
[SPEAKER_06]: That would be this episode.
[SPEAKER_12]: Good point.
[SPEAKER_12]: We're getting another call on the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_12]: Let's go take it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hello, you are on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello, it's Rice Princess.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hi, Rice Princess.
[SPEAKER_12]: You're supposed to be here in studio tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: I totally was.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_12]: What gives?
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, I have a flat tire.
[SPEAKER_12]: Fired.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Too cute.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, well, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_12]: And put the mic a little closer to your mouth because you're barely coming in.
[SPEAKER_04]: This better?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it louder?
[SPEAKER_12]: Jesus Christ, yes.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_12]: Much better.
[SPEAKER_12]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_12]: What do you want to comment on tonight?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: You told me to call in.
[SPEAKER_12]: I told you to call in because you weren't here in person.
[SPEAKER_12]: I just wanted to debrate you over the phone.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: Shame on you.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, what have you been playing lately?
[SPEAKER_12]: Anything?
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't been doing much game playing for the past couple weeks.
[SPEAKER_12]: You haven't been playing a lot of WoW or anything?
[SPEAKER_04]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, gee, a video game podcast sure does you a lot of good this week, doesn't it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Doesn't it, though?
[SPEAKER_04]: My gosh, I've been playing so little, like, it's kind of pointless for me to be calling in.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right, well, then I'll hang up on you.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_12]: I'll hang up on you, then.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, jerk, you told me to call in.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, because I thought you'd want to say hi, because you weren't here in person.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, well, hi.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right, bye.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right, 1-877.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm going to get spanked for that one later.
[SPEAKER_12]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype, Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: Loki, got anything for us real quick?
[SPEAKER_12]: We'll take one more call.
[SPEAKER_14]: Circuit City is offering a pretty cool deal for people that purchase Call of Duty 4.
[SPEAKER_14]: You get Call of Duty 3 for free.
[SPEAKER_14]: And that's for... Because you probably already own it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hey, it's free.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because you wouldn't want to play it.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's free.
[SPEAKER_14]: And also been leaked to the internet from what I've seen.
[SPEAKER_14]: Sensible Soccer, or Sensible World of Soccer, is going to be coming to Xbox Live Arcade this month.
[SPEAKER_14]: Following, also coming out on the PSC.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, that's neat.
[SPEAKER_14]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_12]: Except the game is how old?
[SPEAKER_12]: We're getting another call on Skype.
[SPEAKER_12]: Let's go take that and then we'll get to any more last minute stories.
[SPEAKER_12]: This will be our last call tonight.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_12]: Shadow Next Gen Shadow Next Gen
[SPEAKER_01]: Contra 4, Call of Duty 4, Simpsons, there was Guitar Hero 3, Rock Band, there was quite a lot of games there to play.
[SPEAKER_12]: The biggest complaint I heard about E4ALL was very similar to what Rob had just said about Video Game Expo, and that is, you could have done it all in a day.
[SPEAKER_12]: Is that true?
[SPEAKER_01]: You probably could have, but I mean, I was there for the whole time.
[SPEAKER_01]: There was also the Video Game Live concert that I went to that was a lot of fun as well.
[SPEAKER_12]: Nice, sounds like fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: That was right across the street.
[SPEAKER_01]: Right across the street from E4L.
[SPEAKER_12]: Did you wait in line for Super Smash Bros.?
[SPEAKER_01]: I didn't have to because I got in early.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, nice.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I only had to wait about 5-10 minutes.
[SPEAKER_12]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_12]: How was it?
[SPEAKER_01]: Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_01]: was a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was... I believe I played as Link and they had a level from Twilight Princess in there.
[SPEAKER_01]: They had the bridge level where you're jousting with that big enemy on the Warthog.
[SPEAKER_12]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_12]: Do you think this game has the potential to be OMG best game ever?
[SPEAKER_01]: With all the new stuff that they're putting in?
[SPEAKER_01]: Could very well be with the level editor and the video record feature.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it seems like every week they keep adding new features.
[SPEAKER_12]: Sounds pretty hot.
[SPEAKER_12]: I know I'm excited about it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, and then I got to try the Wii Zapper I actually had fun with.
[SPEAKER_12]: Ah, yes, the Wii Zapper.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's going to be coming out pretty soon, huh?
[SPEAKER_01]: They have Link's crossbow training there, which was pretty good, especially if you're a Zelda fan.
[SPEAKER_14]: I have a copy on order because I've saved myself from purchasing other Wii games, so I'll be getting it.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm very excited to finally put the Wii Zapper bet to rest, because we still have that going on, too.
[SPEAKER_12]: I will kick your ass.
[SPEAKER_12]: The date bet.
[SPEAKER_12]: So anyway, we'll worry about that later.
[SPEAKER_01]: Mario Party DS was there.
[SPEAKER_01]: That was also a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_12]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh yeah, I saw Mario Party 8 this weekend, I forgot to mention.
[SPEAKER_12]: I saw it, I didn't play it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because it was another Wii game that came out at the party.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's just another Mario Party game.
[SPEAKER_13]: I got it for my brother when I got him his Wii for his birthday.
[SPEAKER_12]: But now you build hotels, I guess, or something.
[SPEAKER_12]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_13]: One of the maps has hotels on it, or something.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_12]: Sorry, Shadow Next Gen.
[SPEAKER_12]: What else is on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_01]: Um...
[SPEAKER_01]: I just wanted to say that E4ALL wasn't nearly as bad as a lot of the reports were making it out to be.
[SPEAKER_01]: They had about 18,000 people there, I think they said.
[SPEAKER_01]: which is almost about a third of what E3 used to draw.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I would say that's pretty good for a first year without Sony and Microsoft there.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, I'm glad to hear a dissenting opinion from someone who was actually there.
[SPEAKER_12]: We welcome that.
[SPEAKER_12]: What do you think, though, about next year?
[SPEAKER_12]: Because apparently they have it timed where it's going to be very close to Penny Arcade Expo next year.
[SPEAKER_12]: Do you think that's going to be a good thing or bad or what?
[SPEAKER_01]: Right now, I don't really see it being too good of a move because Penny Arcade is starting to get really huge.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know why they would want to draw away more potential exhibitors who would probably rather go up to Seattle.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, it's going to be interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: We'll have to wait and see.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hopefully they'll smarten up and either they'll put it in October again or they'll put it earlier in the year.
[SPEAKER_12]: They might be playing a game of chicken right now to see if anybody backs down first, but we will see.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anyway, shout out next time.
[SPEAKER_12]: We've got to let you go.
[SPEAKER_12]: We're going to try to wrap things up for tonight, but thanks so much for your call.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right, have a good night, guys.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right, you too.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's good to hear from somebody who's actually there, as opposed to all the hearsay on the internet.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm so sorry to those folks that didn't get through tonight.
[SPEAKER_12]: I know we have more people that wanted to call in, but sadly, we've got to get this show wrapped up, because we are going on a three-hour program tonight, and we've got to wrap this shit up.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, Loki, did you have anything else for Last Minute Stories?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, real quick.
[SPEAKER_14]: I was going to say, Heavenly Star is going to be in No More Heroes as well, as a song, apparently.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know, it should be pretty interesting.
[SPEAKER_14]: I guess...
[SPEAKER_14]: You find a hidden VHS tape in the game or something.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, it's kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_14]: Then, let's see here.
[SPEAKER_14]: I laughed when I read this story.
[SPEAKER_14]: Apparently, they were going to do some Assassin's Creed novels that were going to come out around the same time as the game.
[SPEAKER_14]: But apparently, a sect of real-life assassins paid Ubisoft to visit and told them no.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: I laughed at that.
[SPEAKER_14]: Then there was an interview with Naughty Dog about Uncharted where they said that they've only used 30% of the PS3's power for Uncharted.
[SPEAKER_14]: So if the game sucks that's why.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_14]: And then finally, Nintendo was also, the PR manager with Nintendo was interviewed regarding a couple things, including a hard drive and friend codes.
[SPEAKER_14]: Eric Walter, of course, revealed no plans for a Wii hard drive, despite the fact that the whole WiiWare service is going to be coming.
[SPEAKER_14]: And also, as far as the friends codes...
[SPEAKER_14]: Apparently, they've pulled people through different questionnaires and whatnot, and people don't seem to be... They are undisturbed by them, so they're going to stay.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hooray!
[SPEAKER_12]: I do want to add to the last minute news to follow up to our breaking news earlier.
[SPEAKER_12]: The character battle is over, and it's official.
[SPEAKER_12]: El Block is the new champion after the character battle.
[SPEAKER_12]: And now they're having an extra bonus round.
[SPEAKER_12]: and today the L Block is facing off against the Paddle, the Question Mark Block, and the Weighted Companion Cube.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, they're all doing battles.
[SPEAKER_13]: I can already tell the Weighted Companion Cube is going to win just because it's current.
[SPEAKER_12]: Actually, at the current time, now it is early on in the race, but at the current time, L Block is leading with almost 40% of the vote.
[SPEAKER_12]: Weighted Companion Cube is in second place, but only with 27% of the vote.
[SPEAKER_12]: That'll change.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think the portal jokes are going to get old pretty soon, you guys.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anyhow, show is over.
[SPEAKER_12]: Let's go around and get everybody's final thought.
[SPEAKER_12]: We'll start off with Puppy.
[SPEAKER_12]: Thank you so much for being here, and I'm glad you got to actually talk this time.
[SPEAKER_12]: So what is your final thought?
[SPEAKER_13]: I have cavities now from all that candy.
[SPEAKER_12]: I know.
[SPEAKER_12]: I need an insulin shot.
[SPEAKER_12]: Jesus.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right, DarkSakura, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_06]: I fucking love my iPhone.
[SPEAKER_12]: My final thought is I'm going to have a candy coma.
[SPEAKER_14]: Loki, your final thought?
[SPEAKER_14]: My final thought is I have way too many games to play this week.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I hope my Wii works.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_14]: The Wii console.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you guys so much.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm not worried about my Wii.
[SPEAKER_12]: I know that works just fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: Thank you guys so much for tuning into and downloading Orange Lounge Radio and supporting Independent Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: If you like what you hear, please tell two friends about our show or go leave us a nice review on iTunes, dang it, because we could always use some extra five-star reviews because that helps spread the word because we don't have a big magazine or website backing us.
[SPEAKER_14]: We don't have any of those fancy magazines.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_12]: We don't have any of that fancy schmancy stuff to back us up.
[SPEAKER_12]: We do this because we love you all.
[SPEAKER_13]: Expensive print material.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, we appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Seems like one of those fancy magazines you find at Kmart.
[SPEAKER_12]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, on that note, until next week, I'm Rob, that's Jamie, that's Loki, and we're Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: See you next week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_07]: For more information on our live and podcast programs, visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com See you next week!