[SPEAKER_00]: Tonight, November 4th, 2007, Manhunt 2 proves a pot of controversy all its own.
[SPEAKER_00]: Could Oblivion be headed online?
[SPEAKER_00]: We discuss the ultimate dodgeball showdown of pirates versus ninjas.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hello everybody out there on the internet and welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: We are that podcast dedicated to video games, gaming, gaming culture, and the gamer lifestyle.
[SPEAKER_06]: Pretty much like everything to do with video games, you know.
[SPEAKER_06]: That doesn't suck.
[SPEAKER_06]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_06]: Joining me as always, say hello to the one and only DarkSakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_06]: How are you doing, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_06]: And your mic is off.
[SPEAKER_06]: I see no... I turned it on.
[SPEAKER_06]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now we hear you.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just turned my mic on again.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe it was stuck.
[SPEAKER_02]: It might have been.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe your mic got all sticky.
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: A likely story.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to eat my salad.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, then you can eat your salad very soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: As soon as we do Gaming Weeks.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll get there very soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Forget that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to straight my salad.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: While she dives in, I'm going to introduce... Will you show Op11 your lovely salad from Quiznos before you dine in there?
[SPEAKER_06]: We webcast her on the webcam here at Operator11.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's her lovely salad.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura is tossing her salad in the corner.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to actually toss DarkSakura's salad right here on Off11Cam.
[SPEAKER_06]: Look at that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I will explain what I'm doing.
[SPEAKER_02]: When you get the salads that have lids on them, you can actually get away with using less dressing.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you pour however much you want on, close the lid and shake it up really well.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh yeah, that's what I always do.
[SPEAKER_02]: For anybody who is changing their lifestyle to eat healthier, there's a hint for you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tossing your salad can be good for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you don't have to dip your salad like the books tell you to because that's retarded.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_06]: Books are retarded.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like that thought.
[SPEAKER_06]: Very good.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's fat tire, not flat tire.
[SPEAKER_01]: Depends on when you buy the beer.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe they misheard it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe somebody made a typo.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I got the message on MySpace.
[SPEAKER_06]: When did MySpace replace email?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what I want to know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, nobody sends me email anymore.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just get messages on MySpace.
[SPEAKER_01]: I have something better than email.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_06]: Jamie whips out the iPhone.
[SPEAKER_01]: Put it on camera.
[SPEAKER_06]: Jamie bots herself an iPhone.
[SPEAKER_06]: It doesn't have your number on it or anything, does it?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Jamie bought yourself an iPhone.
[SPEAKER_06]: The screen went off as soon as I held it up.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_06]: You bought yourself an iPhone.
[SPEAKER_06]: You joined the army of those that have these.
[SPEAKER_06]: What made you decide to take the plunge?
[SPEAKER_01]: My husband did.
[SPEAKER_02]: He grabbed them and said, we want these.
[SPEAKER_06]: Really?
[SPEAKER_06]: And you were like, oh, no, please stop.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, what happened is I was going to get a BlackBerry.
[SPEAKER_02]: And being that, you know, I do all this business and I need to have a planner on me and I need to have, you know, something that I can keep track of all of my work and my dates and all that in.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was going to get a BlackBerry.
[SPEAKER_02]: On top of that, I'm a texting fiend.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I figured it would be cost effective for me to buy a BlackBerry instead of going out and buying a PDA.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we look at them and the activation on them and everything ended up that it would have been more reasonable or about equal when we did all the math that I could get an iPhone.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course, my husband doesn't want to be shown up by his wife.
[SPEAKER_02]: So he had to get one too.
[SPEAKER_02]: and I think this is highly ironic that he's like, we need to watch money, we need to watch money, let's break out the gold card and buy iPhones.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not a wise purchase, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: You see, you guys say that women defy all logic.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, hell no.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hell no.
[SPEAKER_06]: And let's, of course, introduce the always present other guest on our program, the chat room.
[SPEAKER_06]: Chat.OrangeLawnTrader.com is the place to be when we tape live here on this Sunday evening, which feels like a very late Sunday evening today, thanks to Daylight Savings Time.
[SPEAKER_06]: It feels like later than it should, and it got dark early and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: Daylight Savings Time in Ilimu is up until 5 a.m.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I was up until 5 too, but anyway, we'll get into that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Were you playing with your iPhone all night?
[SPEAKER_06]: Were you tossing your salad all night?
[SPEAKER_06]: What were you doing?
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura is tossing her own salad.
[SPEAKER_06]: Simply amazing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is she a contortionist?
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura is a woman of many talents.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not only is she like a classic gaming fiend, but she is a salad connoisseur.
[SPEAKER_01]: Except I don't think that's very good to put lunch meat in your salad.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is a little bit weird.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wonder Dog Harold also splurged a purchase this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: I got my refurbed Zune from Woot.com this past week.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's faboo.
[SPEAKER_06]: You don't hear a lot about Zunes.
[SPEAKER_01]: I love Woot.com.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's the best site ever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Woot.com is pretty fucking Woot.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it makes me say Woot.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've never bought anything on there yet, but I always get there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Whenever I see something I actually want, it's too late.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was gone.
[SPEAKER_01]: I almost bought steak knives on Woot.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why do you need knives?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because, okay, we have the same... For eating steak.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, not that I eat a lot of steak, but whenever I chop vegetables, I like to use steak knives.
[SPEAKER_06]: When she decides to chop and then toss her own salad.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: How old are we again?
[SPEAKER_02]: The steak knives that we have are the same ones that Dan had when I moved in with him ten years ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you need some knife upgrades.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want a set of Ginsu dinner knives.
[SPEAKER_04]: You need to go to the weapon vendor.
[SPEAKER_04]: Last time I bought knives, I chopped off the end of my finger.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dude, I was there when that happened, I think.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, you weren't.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, but wasn't that when we lived together?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm thinking of something else.
[SPEAKER_04]: I must be thinking of a deep fryer incident.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, you cut yourself on the knife using a steak knife to open boxes.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, that was me.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was using a steak knife to open boxes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, it was about maybe a year ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was around Halloween, I thought.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, Finger Mummy!
[SPEAKER_03]: That's my costume!
[SPEAKER_03]: Finger Mummy!
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, um... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Crazy bandage man, give me some candy!
[SPEAKER_04]: It was funny though, because they're like, I'm like, ow, or I'm like, I cut myself, are you okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm like, I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_04]: They come over and there's blood going all over.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just had a flashback to UHF.
[SPEAKER_06]: You get to drink from the fire hose.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, the guy doing the...
[SPEAKER_01]: The Carpentry and selling off his fingers.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just want to point out as well in our chatroom, ShadowNextGen is bragging, I got the $100 HD DVD player at Walmart.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you hear about that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Walmart's selling HD DVD players for $100 to try and push the HD DVD format.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sadly, I was in Walmart this week to buy a wireless GameCube controller.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, just a GameCube controller because I needed one right away because that's when I thought that I'd have my mod shipped all installed by Friday and fortunately it took a little longer than I thought.
[SPEAKER_04]: So,
[SPEAKER_04]: But yeah, Walmart sucks.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, actually, I might put in the money for one of those if they're still selling them before I go to Alabama.
[SPEAKER_02]: But then my house would be the ultimate high-definition entertainment home.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, if you have a 360, you can buy a $199 HD DVD player.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or I could spend $100 for a dedicated HD DVD player.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can actually use that on a PC, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I'm working on getting more characters to level 90-ish.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have one at 92 now.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then I also looked at Guild Wars, but I didn't play because my friend who I would play Guild Wars with now works Graveyard.
[SPEAKER_06]: You just kind of looked at it.
[SPEAKER_06]: You were like, hmm, it's still there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it's there.
[SPEAKER_06]: No scratches or anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Dan's been playing Phoenix Wright.
[SPEAKER_02]: A lot of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, I always hear the music.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like, you're playing it right, aren't you?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I am, though, going to be stealing the PSP, though, now that he's done with Rondo of Blood.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'll be playing the hell out of that because it's coming with me to Alabama.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not going to be able to play Ragnarok when I'm in Alabama.
[SPEAKER_04]: OMGZ.
[SPEAKER_04]: Too bad that powerful iPhone can't run Ragnarok.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I can, you know, go on my live journal.
[SPEAKER_02]: Posting a live journal on the iPhone, by the way, is ass.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not what the iPhones are for.
[SPEAKER_06]: iPhones are for phoning.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it has an iPod on it, so I can listen to stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can listen to the Ragnarok soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, when I actually installed the game, I didn't install the music in it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why did you do that?
[SPEAKER_02]: I just didn't feel like it, because, you know, the music takes up a lot of space, and I'm playing on my lappy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is your laptop that...
[SPEAKER_06]: Crunched for Space?
[SPEAKER_02]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not now that I have my portable hard drive, but I just don't want to bother with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I did actually play some of the games on the Homestar Runner site.
[SPEAKER_02]: Does that count?
[SPEAKER_02]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_02]: I was playing Trogdor.
[SPEAKER_06]: Flash games are awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what you could always do is you could do some LARPing when you're in Alabama, and you could pretend that you're in Ragnarok.
[SPEAKER_06]: You could be all, Hail...
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm here to kick you in the face.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then I'll ban you.
[SPEAKER_01]: Ban you forever.
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: I used to LARP in Alabama.
[SPEAKER_02]: I played live-action vampire when I was, you know, freshly in college.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're not supposed to admit to that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but I'm recovered.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, the first step of acceptance is... Admitting you have a problem.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: I admitted I have a problem.
[SPEAKER_02]: I moved.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ranma is reminding us of the best part of the LARP.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is the part where I run up to Jamie and go, Heal, please!
[SPEAKER_06]: No!
[SPEAKER_06]: Warp front once, please.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because, because, because, that's why.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't play a priest, ha.
[SPEAKER_02]: Except I'm playing a crusader and people come up to my crusader and go, Heal, please.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because Crusaders can heal.
[SPEAKER_06]: Kick them in the face.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_04]: It was okay, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: Once again, I did not play any of my Ratchet & Clank Future Tools of Destruction.
[SPEAKER_04]: Unshrunk the game, but didn't touch it.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I don't know when I'm going to play my PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then I played... What was it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh...
[SPEAKER_04]: God of War, Chains of Olympus
[SPEAKER_04]: Then, let's see, other than that, I played a little bit of Half-Life 2, some more Portal for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Finally figured out what the weighted companion cube is.
[SPEAKER_04]: So now I get all the jokes and they're not funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: And let's see, what else?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I also played some Halo 3, actually, over...
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, Halloween.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we played over live.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I don't really play much over live, but we went over to a friend's house and for Halloween we played Halo 3 while my wife and my friend's wife were playing Liar's Dice from Pirates of the Caravan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Halo 3 for Halloween, that infection playlist was fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Except we didn't really do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, no, wait.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: I take that back.
[SPEAKER_04]: We didn't play over Halloween because...
[SPEAKER_04]: The Halloween Party was last Saturday.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there, we already talked about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I did not play Halo 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: In fact, I did not hook up my 360 live at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I will assume you're playing Simpsons, the game, because that looks awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Although it's getting mediocre reviews.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what other game got mediocre reviews?
[SPEAKER_04]: Earth Defense Force 2017.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I still have to go back and finish that damn game, because I motherfucking can't beat the Inferno mode on that.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you burn yourself at all?
[SPEAKER_04]: I did not burn myself at all, but I was just so stressed out all week because I took it to work to do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: First off, I didn't want my wife really knowing that I was doing it right away because she would have said, you're going to break that thing, and I didn't want to have anything to do with that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Plus, if you've looked at my computer room, there's no way I can solder in there, although I did last night.
[SPEAKER_06]: And heaven forbid someone get between Mrs. Loki and her excite truck.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh God, I was so afraid.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm like, this thing better work when I'm done because she's going to want to play Excite Truck.
[SPEAKER_04]: Holy shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's honestly the first time I've ever heard you admit to fear.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it's just scary.
[SPEAKER_04]: But anyway, so I actually had it broken open in our conference room for Thursday and Friday.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: One of the things I did want to play when I get it all hooked up is the first Simple Series game on the Wii, which is that kart racing game.
[SPEAKER_04]: That should be fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know later on they're going to add some more to the Simple Series, so that's kind of what I'm looking forward to with this mod chip.
[SPEAKER_04]: Other than that, today when I left, I think I figured out what I did wrong, but it does play Excite Truck, so crisis averted for now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, the other thing, and we'll get into this a little bit later.
[SPEAKER_04]: I played Manhunt 2 on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: And once we get into the story a little bit later on, I'll explain.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can hack the hell out of that game.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm sure it was a completely unaltered retail version of the game that you would never think of reading about all these hack and crack stories and doing this to your precious copy of the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Rockstar never intended for that to happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: Totally didn't have a modded PSP or anything to do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: which I've played a lot more of.
[SPEAKER_06]: Last week I didn't really want to say a lot about it because I hadn't played much, but now I've played a lot of the game, and it is a worthy sequel, I think is the best way I can sum it up.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: and some of the design aspects.
[SPEAKER_06]: What are your bitches with the Guitar Hero 3?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, for one, the controllers he designed, way too sensitive for it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some of the design stuff on the notes and the note stream coming down, there's some stuff you're used to in Guitar Hero 2 and 1 where when the notes jump up on the board when you activate star power, it doesn't happen in 3 and it's hard to tell when you activate it just because it's the only thing that happens is it changes colors.
[SPEAKER_03]: True.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then some of the character designs, meh.
[SPEAKER_05]: They took out Pandora, which made me sad, because she was cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then some of the... I mean, it's cool that they got Midori.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't care what she says.
[SPEAKER_05]: As soon as I saw that character when I opened up the game, I knew that was who we were going to play.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you guys actually saying that you play Guitar Hero for the characters?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, that's like playing Karaoke Revolution for the characters.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's fun, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: Jamie says she played rock band.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let me get to that in a minute because I had a rock band experience too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I heart Midori.
[SPEAKER_06]: The songs are fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: I beat the game on medium because I'm not that great at Guitar Hero, but I'm working my way through on hard now, and then I'll work up to expert.
[SPEAKER_06]: But here's what Guitar Hero 3 has that the other games didn't have.
[SPEAKER_06]: Live, online, competitive play, which is actually a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: I played with one of my friends, and we were playing some co-op mode, and I couldn't really play co-op mode in Guitar Hero 2 because nobody ever really came over with their guitar.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's a really nice feature.
[SPEAKER_05]: I haven't done it on live yet, I've just been practicing on hard mode just to kind of get back into it since I haven't played Guitar Hero in almost a year.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dude, and Guitar Hero 3 has Raining Blood.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't even get me started on that shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I have fun with that.
[SPEAKER_06]: and that's all I can think of.
[SPEAKER_04]: All the games because all your live accounts are tied into you can bring them up on your PC and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: But the Guitar Hero thing has the leaderboards and you can make your own little clan online and have a message form and I'll tell you more about the OL Army Guitar Hero band in a minute and all that and I think that's kind of cool even if it's been kind of clunky these first couple weeks I'm hoping that in a couple weeks it will smooth out and things will run
[SPEAKER_06]: It's certainly something that Harmonix wouldn't have had the resources to do on their own.
[SPEAKER_06]: Cousin had a birthday, and he has a Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: And we went and played Big Brain Academy on the Wii, which is like, I guess, the brain training game on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's another mini-game collection, the kind of game that's easily accessible by anyone.
[SPEAKER_06]: But here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's not enough mini-games.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, I like some of the party modes.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought the competitive mode where you work your way through the mini-games as fast as you can against other people within the same room was kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: But
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: They call it Big Brain Academy for a reason, I suppose.
[SPEAKER_06]: Try before you buy Big Brain Academy because it's very limited.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you have young ones, though, I bet they'd get a kick out of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: How about this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Spend your $50 on something better.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a brain training game.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is a lot of money for this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: A brain training game on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're an idiot if you bought it.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know what I do to train my brain?
[SPEAKER_01]: I read.
[SPEAKER_01]: I study things.
[SPEAKER_01]: You can.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't need a game to help my brain.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_06]: Jamie, you wanted to talk about Rock Band real quick.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dan and I went to Best Buy because we were going to pick up Spider-Man 3, which actually we ended up getting a better deal at Target anyway because Best Buy had a two-disc thing and Target had a three-disc thing for like $2 less.
[SPEAKER_02]: But anyway, I digress.
[SPEAKER_02]: But they had the demo for Rock Band sitting out.
[SPEAKER_02]: and it was just okay the guitars were both destroyed and of course Dan went right for them but the drum set was pretty cool and it was a lot of fun I made him play Weezer because I love Weezer so it was really cool I probably went to the same Best Buy you did at one point this week because I had to buy the Twin Peaks Gold Box Edition which they didn't have at Best Buy I had to go somewhere else to get it but anyway nevertheless
[SPEAKER_06]: I really liked the little drum, you know, where you could, uh, uh,
[SPEAKER_02]: Freestyle a little bit, you know, where you could ad lib.
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't see that part.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, yeah, it'll bring it up to where all of the lines are lit up, and you can pretty much free play on those measures.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was really cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: What else did I play this week?
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that's about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought there was one other thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I helped William set up his new PSP, and that was about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So there we go, our gaming weeks.
[SPEAKER_06]: So let's move on then, and we'll talk a little bit about housekeeping.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I promised a little bit ago I would talk about our Guitar Hero 3 band.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you search for OLR in the tour groups on the Orange Islands Radio website, it'll take you right to our OLR band, which I'm happy to say is in the top 100.
[SPEAKER_06]: Number 76 Rockin' Top 10
[SPEAKER_06]: You're gonna be not resting for a while Well, I'm number two, so I'll be moving up
[SPEAKER_06]: That's really all I wanted to say.
[SPEAKER_06]: Obviously, I plugged in there.
[SPEAKER_06]: We have a MySpace and all that other stuff, so you should find us and add us.
[SPEAKER_06]: and of course we always tape live on Sunday nights and that's in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you miss the live broadcast on Sunday nights you can always listen to our rebroadcast on All Games Radio Monday nights after All Games Interactive or Tuesday mornings at 9 a.m.
[SPEAKER_06]: Pacific.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, enough plugging.
[SPEAKER_06]: News time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gaming news.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, so of course this week Manhunt 2 came out.
[SPEAKER_04]: What did I say last week?
[SPEAKER_04]: Everybody will be talking about Manhunt 2 this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's what's going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: And of course...
[SPEAKER_04]: Sooner than later, we have a mini hot coffee on our hands.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's basically the PSP version, the ISO of it, out on the internet like any other game out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: People looked into it and they hacked the distortion that would happen when you would do your kills.
[SPEAKER_04]: So now that's hacked out of the way, you now have an uncut version of the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, which is funny, because I actually kind of looked a little bit at this for research purposes, and, um, all they have, it literally is just INI files.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, stupid...
[SPEAKER_04]: Fully documented INI files.
[SPEAKER_04]: It even says, you know, this is where the distortion stuff is for your deaths.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you can take that out.
[SPEAKER_04]: I actually went as far as not only just removing the distortion in there, but I made all the guards blind and deaf, which was fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, I mean, there's a ton of things.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can edit everything in the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, the weapon damage, you name it, it's in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although, for some reason, when it did make the guys blind and deaf, everything got really, really bright.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Somehow, the lighting's attached to that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Controversy aside, I want to ask first off, is the game good?
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's... They're really, I mean, plot-wise for the game, I mean, there's, I guess, some sort of a storyline going along.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've only played through the second level.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, the third level.
[SPEAKER_04]: And...
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it's just death after death.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just all about murdering people.
[SPEAKER_04]: That really is... There's no big art thing in this.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just murdering people.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, granted, this is not art.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is an art.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's probably drugs in there somewhere, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, there is a storyline that goes along with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure when you play through the entire game, you figure out why he's killing people.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, I mean...
[SPEAKER_04]: You can just shoot somebody and they're dead, or, no, this game, you decide, I'm gonna kill someone with a pen, I'm gonna kill someone with a syringe, I'm gonna kill someone with, you know, a bit of barbed wire, and I'm gonna saw their balls off with the barbed wire.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, just a little over the top.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would think if I'm gonna kill someone with barbed wire, sawing their balls off wouldn't be the first thing that would come to my mind.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that's a little excessive.
[SPEAKER_06]: Piker Uno says, so it's a murder simulator.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it's not a murder simulator because you're not really simulating murder.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're just simulating a crazy guy that's running away and happens to be killing people to get away.
[SPEAKER_02]: If I was going to kill somebody with barbed wire, I would do one of two things.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would either run it across their leg on the inside where the artery is or across their neck where the carotid is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that's what they kind of did.
[SPEAKER_04]: They ran it across their leg.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's three different kills you can do with each weapon.
[SPEAKER_04]: One of which, I think for barbed wire, the big one was running it through their leg
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: I shut it off.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was stupid.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you have it?
[SPEAKER_06]: It was somewhere on the internet.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was on some of the big game blogs.
[SPEAKER_06]: I watched part of it and I was like, this is stupid.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, I reacted the same way to that video that I did to the movie, the Saw trilogy or quad trilogy or whatever it is now.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know I'll never watch them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, Saw 4 is not art either.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Number one movie at the box office last weekend.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's not art either.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's because people have no taste.
[SPEAKER_04]: They complain that the ESRB is being too hard on them and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I see them, with the whole hot coffee thing, I think rating that game adult only is stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do agree with that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But with Manhunt 2, you just watch the murder scene
[SPEAKER_04]: Piker Uno wants to know, can you kill someone with a boat fire?
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Which is bullshit anyways, because the hot coffee thing was a hack as well, but apparently they're dumb, and so... Well, didn't this time Rockstar disclosed everything that was in the game that was changeable?
[SPEAKER_04]: See, yeah, I mean, they didn't really hide anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, granted, all they did was remove the distortion.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess it's the same as saying, like, the Sims where they have patches where you can remove the blur so that you can see...
[SPEAKER_04]: Sim body parts.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it's stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: Personally, I do think that the game should have been released unmodified without the distortion on there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because to be honest, I don't enjoy it with the distortion on there because you can't see what the fuck is going on.
[SPEAKER_05]: On top of that, if you go further, it's kind of censorship.
[SPEAKER_06]: To me, the hilarious part about all this is why did anybody even run out and buy this game in the first place?
[SPEAKER_06]: The controversy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why was this game hacked within 24 hours?
[SPEAKER_06]: If word had never come out that there was another version of this game...
[SPEAKER_06]: That had the blurs taken away.
[SPEAKER_06]: I bet nobody would have ever thought, gee, let's go in there and hack the disc.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or they certainly wouldn't have done it in 24 hours.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's another thing, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was issuing a challenge to the hacking community to find the original content in the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they did it.
[SPEAKER_04]: You knew they would.
[SPEAKER_04]: In the past, I've actually been curious and looked at different ISOs.
[SPEAKER_04]: This has been the easiest to modify ISO I have ever seen.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is seriously fully documented.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_04]: It does not take a genius to fix this stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: You see the part where for blurring it out, you remove it, done.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, ooh, that's really tough.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, seriously, it's stupid.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you think they kept it easy because they had to fix it so fast to get the game out on Halloween?
[SPEAKER_04]: They did have to fix the game, and I understand that, but no, they could have easily encrypted that stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: It could have been a file that's not just a plain text file.
[SPEAKER_04]: It could have been encrypted.
[SPEAKER_04]: It could have been something that people couldn't find.
[SPEAKER_04]: Make it a little bit harder for them, but I don't know, it's just really stupid.
[SPEAKER_06]: TigerClaw says, keep in mind they only hacked the PSP version.
[SPEAKER_06]: An average person will not be able to figure out how to do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: So far, and I'm going to tell you this much, the PlayStation 2 version is going to be hacked before you know it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because, let me put it this way, the INI files that were documented in there, it was for both PlayStation 2 and PSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's only a matter of time.
[SPEAKER_06]: This whole controversy is just waving a red cape at the hacking community right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ole!
[SPEAKER_04]: If you've got a modded console, this is going to be hacked pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, no doubt about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I'm looking at just what they have in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Seriously, the INI files that were in there are documented for both PSP and PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure the Wii version is also the same as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: But those two were mentioned in that file.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I don't see why it wouldn't be the same.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just stupid.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I think they did it on purpose.
[SPEAKER_06]: TigerClaw says, I think the only way you can hack the PS2 version if they did it via the Pro Action Replay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, no, I think you can actually mod, I mean, because there's people out there that make custom Guitar Hero games, you know, for the PlayStation 2 if you have a modded console.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can create custom ISOs for that stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what this reminds me of?
[SPEAKER_06]: This whole thing reminds me of, remember when Nintendo made that controversial move to change the blood in Mortal Kombat 2 to sweat?
[SPEAKER_06]: and it was like suddenly it became this challenge all over like who can find the game genie code first that will change the sweat to red to bring back the blood into Mortal Kombat 2 it became a contest it was the red cape at the community going put me back the way I was supposed to be because we all know this game was fixed but here's the thing though I think even removing the distortion or whatever it really doesn't change anything in the game I mean
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it's violent and stuff, but to be honest, it's just like hostile.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hostile wasn't a good movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was just a violent movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just like this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not a good game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just a violent game.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's just changing cutscenes and not actual gameplay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just kind of pissed off at Rockstar for, I don't know what the fuck they're doing.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're trying to, like, ruin everything by making games overly violent so that people come down on them harder.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they're like, why do people keep coming after us?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's unfair.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, maybe you should stop, you know, I don't know, having people with limbs being blown off and stuff like that in very graphic manners.
[SPEAKER_04]: How about that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe that's a start.
[SPEAKER_06]: Manhunt Controversy
[SPEAKER_06]: Woot for them getting publicity.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, there you have it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wonder if that's just a demand thing, though, because when I think of big video game retailers, I don't always think of Target.
[SPEAKER_06]: Target has a very limited selection of games.
[SPEAKER_06]: They carry what's kind of current and popular, and honestly, controversy aside, I don't think this game is going to sell very well, and I think they kind of know that.
[SPEAKER_06]: They would rather be stocking games that are going to sell more copies.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it will sell well.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's cheap.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like $39.99 for the Wii, $29.99 for PS2 and PSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: well there are other people mad about Manhunt and for a different reason um in the manual for Manhunt they didn't mention one of the major parties that worked on the game being uh Vienna yeah let's sort of forget you know people who worked on the game here so um they uh that's kind of messed up well yeah well their studio was closed down but they still should have been um as Rockstar Vienna they uh
[SPEAKER_02]: Still should have been credited for all the work that they did.
[SPEAKER_02]: They said it was over 50 people working for two years on the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's almost like Rockstar Vienna got shut down and then all traces of it were erased in history because apparently they didn't get credited in this game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which might be good for them anyways.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would be pissed off too.
[SPEAKER_06]: But at the same time, do you really want your name on this game?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, really?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, I agree completely that people should get credit for the work they do, but I would be using an alias.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's my thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think they should have made Manhunt 2 just make it seriously, I mean, go all out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Put a PC version out there and just fucking go nuts.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, do what you would do in Manhunt 2 times ten.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, seriously, just crazy over the top.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: In other news, and this is actually a little bit of an opposite, Sony actually has a brand new advertising campaign coming out for the PlayStation 3 that, oh my god, does actually not suck.
[SPEAKER_04]: This campaign, of course, a little bit different than the last year's campaign, which is known as the White Room.
[SPEAKER_04]: And according to Peter Dill of the PSN Network and also the Senior Vice President of Marketing,
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently he says, uh, last year we launched a PS3 campaign that became known as The White Room, and we received a strong reaction to those ads for being provocative and demonstrating the PS3's power.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh, nope.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyways, um... Macman in our chat says, The White Room?
[SPEAKER_06]: Racist.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't get how he says they received a strong reaction for being provocative.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, they didn't make any sense.
[SPEAKER_04]: They didn't make any sense.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't understand why the PlayStation 3 is making a baby cry.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't understand why it was making baseballs explode or whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: It made no fucking sense.
[SPEAKER_04]: And now you actually have an advertising campaign or a series of commercials saying,
[SPEAKER_04]: They actually show gameplay, get people excited about the games and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what you should have done from the beginning.
[SPEAKER_04]: Instead of, ooh.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, seriously, all three consoles did the same thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: They did these really weird-ass commercials that made no sense.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, with Xbox, the whole jump-in shit, that makes no sense.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they have one going on right now, which they have, like, a little kid, like, singing a song and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then they show Mass Effect, Halo 3, and, like, oh, God, I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, Bioshock.
[SPEAKER_04]: All M-rated games, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: And there's, like, kids.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_04]: Xbox!
[SPEAKER_04]: But anyways, it's just like so stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: But seriously, I'm glad that they finally have a good marketing campaign.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't
[SPEAKER_04]: Seriously, next time you're launching a console, don't get all fucking crazy and hire this marketing team to come up with these stupid ideas like baby crying and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: It makes no fucking sense.
[SPEAKER_04]: People get creeped out by that shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're not going to buy your console.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, one of the new commercials I saw earlier today, it had tentacles and disembodied mouths coming out of the system.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what people want.
[SPEAKER_04]: Disembodied mouths.
[SPEAKER_04]: And tentacles.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think if I were marketing the PlayStation 3 right now, my marketing campaign would go along the lines of something like this.
[SPEAKER_06]: It would be like, let's imagine it was a radio commercial for the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Please buy one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Please.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll do anything.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have Motorstorm and I play Blu-rays.
[SPEAKER_03]: Please.
[SPEAKER_04]: They say that they have games out there, but I don't know about that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have home in 2008 some Final Fantasy XIII sometime in the future.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why won't you buy it?
[SPEAKER_04]: They are showing Gran Turismo Prologue though, even though that's not available over here yet at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: And to be fair, that's not really even a game.
[SPEAKER_06]: or another PlayStation 3 commercial could be buy a PlayStation 3 and fold proteins all day long.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, they did show that it plays Blu-ray and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_06]: The PlayStation 3 is helping to cure cancer.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you don't buy a PlayStation 3, that means you support cancer.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I am all for cancer.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yay, cancer.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a very tasteless little side tangent there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's talk about things that should probably be omitted from the campaign.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because it caused one particular company's stocks to drop a little bit this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that was the news that Metal Gear Solid 4 has gotten another little push.
[SPEAKER_06]: Got a little push back.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, surprise!
[SPEAKER_06]: Remember how Metal Gear Solid 4 was going to come out first quarter of 2008?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, scratch that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Make it second quarter 2008.
[SPEAKER_06]: The day this news was announced, by the way...
[SPEAKER_06]: Konami's stocks went down a little bit because this was the game that's supposed to be really giving a kick in the pants to the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: One of the few exclusives they have left.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sort of.
[SPEAKER_06]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Metal Gear Solid 4 delayed until quarter two 2008.
[SPEAKER_06]: The official reason, by the way, quote, further improvements to the quality of the game and provide even greater enjoyment for more customers worldwide.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't get me wrong.
[SPEAKER_06]: If this is what they need to do to ensure the game is going to be an A++ and not suck, I'm all for it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It just sucks for Sony right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, at least it's not being powered by the Unreal 3 engine, so we know it's not because of that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I don't care about the delay if it's going to make the game awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: As far as I'm aware, there's no flying dragons in this game, so I know it's not anything like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well...
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that with any game, they need to keep pushing things back if they don't have them done rather than release a buggy, unfinished, crappy product.
[SPEAKER_01]: What game do we remember that did that?
[SPEAKER_01]: It doesn't matter, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's seriously going to be like Twilight Princess.
[SPEAKER_04]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_04]: It'll get 10 when it's released because people have a fucking hard-on for that game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, there is actually something that might make people happy.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is still hanging out in rumor land.
[SPEAKER_02]: But there's speculation that there's going to be a new PlayStation 2 in 2008 for $99.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it actually is reported by NCV that it would be introduced in the UK at 75 pounds or lower.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I don't know because Sony hasn't, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think anyone would care
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tough.
[SPEAKER_04]: Final Fantasy VII for life.
[SPEAKER_02]: I busted out Jumping Flash, like, about a month ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, if you want to play Jumping Flash, you can buy yourself a PlayStation 3 and download that shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or buy a PSP and download that shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you shouldn't have to pay for it again.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why should I?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I actually own the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, then you should have bought a PlayStation 2 seven years ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have a PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, then this doesn't affect you.
[SPEAKER_04]: She wants more!
[SPEAKER_04]: Anybody that's still playing PlayStation 1 right now, I mean... But I'm just saying that there's still people who like to break out their classic games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good, then I hope they have a PlayStation 1.
[SPEAKER_04]: But they're not going to be buying new PlayStation 1 games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, whereas PlayStation 3 not playing PlayStation 2 games, that's stupid because they're still putting out new PlayStation 2 games.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I think it's safe to remove the PlayStation 1 backwards compatibility in this if...
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, that's what they're going to do.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just theorizing.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura says, Loki, no, don't give them ideas.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actdeft agrees that Jumping Flash is awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jumping Flash is freaking rad.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what they need to do.
[SPEAKER_02]: That will completely revive the PlayStation 3 as a new jumping flash.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh yeah, that'll be it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know everyone's out there going, gee, if only a new jumping flash would come out, then I would have something to play on this damn thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: How about Bubsy 3D Part 2?
[SPEAKER_02]: How about not?
[SPEAKER_02]: How about Clay Fighters?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm telling you, how long ago do we say this in a game?
[SPEAKER_02]: I miss playing Helga.
[SPEAKER_06]: Six months ago when these console wars were heating up and stuff, we said the first console that gets LaserCats the game...
[SPEAKER_06]: will win the next-gen wars, and we have yet to see LaserCats the game, so it's anybody's guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, there's technically, I mean... It's coming out on Dreamcast!
[SPEAKER_04]: Postal 3's got that one gun that's a bat, you know, a guy's hand up a badger's ass, so that's kind of close.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not really, it's not a cat with a frickin' laser on its head.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't know that they don't have LaserCats in that, I mean... Next story, please.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways...
[SPEAKER_04]: Another game that's been delayed a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: And now it's finally officially coming out on, well, PC at least.
[SPEAKER_04]: Unreal Tournament 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's been announced on PC for November 19th.
[SPEAKER_04]: The PlayStation 3 version is coming soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Probably 2008.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love that they're giving the same old excuse my mom gave when I asked, Mom, when's dinner?
[SPEAKER_06]: It'll be here when it's done.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's exactly what they're saying about Unreal.
[SPEAKER_06]: You will have it when it's done.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now sit down and shut up and watch TV.
[SPEAKER_06]: All I know is Unreal Tournament, the older games were fast.
[SPEAKER_06]: So if you like your shooters nauseatingly fast, Unreal's the place to go.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I want to see all the mods for this.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's really what I'm interested in.
[SPEAKER_06]: That will be kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: By the way, the PlayStation 3 version not only will have the characters, but it will have extra story sequences.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, of course, the 360 fans are like, you know, especially me, you know, I bought the game on 360 and I don't even own a PlayStation 3 as of yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm kind of going, can it be download content time, please?
[SPEAKER_06]: Please, can I have it?
[SPEAKER_06]: But we'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, Eternal Sonata on the PlayStation 3 with extra crap next year.
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh, yay.
[SPEAKER_02]: I still should play that, but I haven't had time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, this makes me relatively happy, although it's more of a, you know, because, hi, I'm tongue-tied.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is really, I think, great news is that the Final Fantasy 1 and 2 on PSP are coming out in the UK.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're doing a PAL conversion, so it'll be out in early 2008.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I think that's really, really good because it's, the second one especially is such a good game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although the third and fifth were my favorites.
[SPEAKER_02]: But anyway, we've had this for a while, and they're really good.
[SPEAKER_02]: The remakes have just been... Very sharp.
[SPEAKER_06]: The coloring and the graphics, very sharp.
[SPEAKER_06]: I actually bought, because I bought William the PSP for his birthday, and I bought him a copy of Final Fantasy I. Because he's a big fan of Final Fantasy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, what I was saying is that they're basically taking the old Nintendo versions and they're retooled with widescreen, new dungeons, redrawn artwork, just the works.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm really glad that it's coming out over there finally.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be really good.
[SPEAKER_06]: And there was much rejoicing overseas.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, back at home.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's time to travel around the world and look at some release dates.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_04]: Release date!
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways, this week marks the first of many very packed weeks with plenty of things coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: This week, though, there are some stupid things coming out, including Aqua Teen Hunger Force Zombie Ninja Pro-Am on PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you can't get enough of Aqua Teen Hunger Force, there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bratz for real on the DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Build-A-Bear Workshop.
[SPEAKER_06]: As opposed to Bratz for fake.
[SPEAKER_06]: Most of the things you see on the Bratz are probably fake, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: Build-A-Bear Workshop, where you can create your own... It's a teddy bear sim.
[SPEAKER_04]: To be honest, this game's $30.
[SPEAKER_04]: You could probably buy a real teddy bear for a lot cheaper, so that's kind of stupid.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think building a bear in the workshop and the actual store costs less than that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: That shit's expensive.
[SPEAKER_06]: The more bling you want to buy for your bear, that shit gets expensive.
[SPEAKER_04]: Call of Duty 4 Modern Warfare is coming out on both PC, PlayStation 3, the Xbox 360, and strangely enough, the DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dora the Explorer, Dora Saves a Mermaid.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not that anyone's going to be buying that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fire Emblem Radiant Dawn.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go Diego Go, Safari Adventure, Lego Star Wars The Complete
[SPEAKER_04]: Saga, what the fuck they're calling that now?
[SPEAKER_04]: PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, Wii, and DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Zoo Vet Endangered Animals on PC.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ooh, awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll have you know, I used to read my... Yes, yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bladestorm, 100 Years War on PlayStation 3 and 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: This was supposed to be a launch title for the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Glad to see Koei's really getting that stuff out.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're too busy working on more Dynasty Warriors games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, this is like Dynasty Warriors.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just set in France instead, and you can play as Joan of Arc.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dynasty Warriors English Edition Blazing Angels 2 The Secret Missions of World War 2 for PlayStation 3 Cabela's Big Game Hunter 2008 I can't wait to check this one out Chessmaster on PSP A game that everyone should really participate in Democracy for PC Go vote!
[SPEAKER_04]: Press A
[SPEAKER_04]: Fear Files for Xbox 360 and of course that also ties in with the PC release of Fear the Perseus Mandate which is their expansion for that and let's see here Gears of War on PC this week as well so that's going to be pretty awesome and are there no Sims games this week?
[SPEAKER_04]: E.A.'
[SPEAKER_02]: 's been having this Sims event going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wasn't this the week for Imagine Babies?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, Imagine Babies, I think I moved.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mario and Sonic at the Olympic Games, that's this week on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, seriously.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought that was a ways off.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: If you want to enrich your life, you guess you could buy this game or a series of these games.
[SPEAKER_04]: My French Coach, My Spanish Coach, My Word Coach, and also My Word Coach on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: Those are other games that were on the DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the hacking community will be creating my sex coach out of this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: How about my Lamaze coach?
[SPEAKER_04]: Really, they are milking that franchise into the ground.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's actually what you do in the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: You milk things.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a fantastically mixed metaphor.
[SPEAKER_04]: Seen It on Xbox 360 is coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the game I'm considering the game of the week, Silent Hill Origins on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's about fucking time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it's about fucking time.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that's not it.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a game based off of the series The Office coming out on PC.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Sims 2, Teen Style with Stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's... Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: Stuff?
[SPEAKER_04]: Teen Style Stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's coming out on PC.
[SPEAKER_04]: Viva Pinata is also coming out on PC this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: World Series of Poker 2008, Battle for the Bracelets on PSP and DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hannah... Wait, no, that already came out.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was going to say Hannah Montana on Music Jam.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's already out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Again.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um...
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see, I think that might be it here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let me get some comments from chat room while you're doing that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Chat.orangeonestranger.com, live on this Sunday night.
[SPEAKER_06]: Macman says, go Diego, go, straight to hell.
[SPEAKER_06]: Forget Diego, go Pyramid Head, go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actdeft says Eureka's Castle greater than all Nick Jr.
[SPEAKER_02]: shows in reference to... Eureka's Castle is great.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like pinwheels.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why isn't there a Eureka's Castle video game?
[SPEAKER_06]: Or better yet... I want my You Can't Do That on Television game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Where you have to, you know, make your way through the sausage factory and avoid the green slime and the pies.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it should be known that I'm so right there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's very Monty Python.
[SPEAKER_06]: The whole show was like a spoof of Monty Python.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was awesome.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dude, you could play as Barf.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you had Alanis.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I like how that show was like borderline child cruelty, which is awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, and that's it for this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: And a real quick tease for next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you smarter than a fifth grader on the DS?
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: I beg not to comment.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can't do that in a video game, is what they could call it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god, that'd be great.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who owns the license to that stuff?
[SPEAKER_02]: Someone in Canada.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, probably the Canadian Broadcasting Corp or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dear Canada, me wanty, you can't do that in a video game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Gimme.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, thanks.
[SPEAKER_06]: Your neighbor to the south.
[SPEAKER_06]: Japan, going over to Japan and looking at Japanese releases Just Cause comes out on the Xbox 360 with a very Che Guevara looking cover Holy crap, that's fucking old Well, they're just now getting it in Japan, so there you go Major League Baseball, sometimes we have to wait for their games, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, like Blue Dragon took how long to come out here in the Final Fantasy games?
[SPEAKER_06]: Sometimes they have to wait for ours
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm moving on to basketball.
[SPEAKER_06]: NBA Live 2008 on the PlayStation 3 out in Japan this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you're a sports fan in Japan, you're a happy camper this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tom Clancy's Ghost Recon Advanced Warfighter 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: I really like that cover.
[SPEAKER_06]: Making its way to Japan this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: And look, complete with Japanese text.
[SPEAKER_06]: That way you know it's authentic.
[SPEAKER_06]: A game coming out on the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: Kurino Okurimono is coming out.
[SPEAKER_06]: All I can tell you is it's an adventure game from Takuyo.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mario Party DS Castlevania, The Dracula X Chronicles, Minna no Golf, Hot Shots Golf, More Sports
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe you need to go to the potty?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: You want me to do your own release dates while you go release?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I'll do them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was trying to speak Lolcat, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: Failed.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you see the G4 Lolcat thing?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, it was fantastic.
[SPEAKER_06]: You said G4 and did you see it?
[SPEAKER_06]: The answer's automatically no.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but they make YouTube for a reason.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love the YouTube channel on my iPhone, by the way.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I forgot to mention.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can watch Cowbell Hero at work.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a couple games I forgot to mention that were coming out this week in the US.
[SPEAKER_04]: Christ!
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry!
[SPEAKER_06]: Fucking games are coming out this week!
[SPEAKER_04]: Dragon Quest Monsters Joker on the DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was coming out as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Empire Earth 3 on PC.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, look, you're done.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you didn't read them, they just got delayed to next week.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can all thank Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: My turn, please?
[SPEAKER_02]: Can I have the turn now?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, you may.
[SPEAKER_02]: On the 8th, Sam & Max episode 201, Ice Station Santa.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_02]: On 9th, Beowulf on Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: I remember when Beowulf was like a story and you could read it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And now it's going to be a movie so you don't have to read it anymore.
[SPEAKER_02]: The fuck?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's coming out on IMAX.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, it'll be big.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll go see it on IMAX.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll see anything on IMAX.
[SPEAKER_02]: On the 9th, Call of Duty 4 Modern Warfare on a bunch of stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: 9th, Dynasty Warriors Gundam.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, 9th also, EA Playground, Endless Ocean, Gears of War on PC, Jackass the Game, whatever, King of Clubs, whatever, Lair, okay, NASCAR 2008, Chase for the Cup, if you, you know, happen to be a European redneck, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like how Jamie is suddenly combining her release dates with her one phrase impressions of the game, whether she's played it or not.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I have a particular funny thing about NASCAR is that they're opening up a big NASCAR arena outside my hometown.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I get to go see it when I'm there.
[SPEAKER_06]: While you're on your way to Chick-fil-A?
[SPEAKER_02]: Dude, no way.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to Cracker Barrel.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know what you're talking about.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cracker Barrel and Waffle House.
[SPEAKER_06]: Release dates?
[SPEAKER_02]: Ninth.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nick Toon.
[SPEAKER_06]: Try not to get shot by Kid Rock while you're at Waffle House.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Nicktoons, Attack of the Toybots on Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's actually a cool name.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ninth, WWE Smackdown vs. Raw 2008.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because you can't have enough, you know, I guess bra and panty matches and, you know, steroidal men.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, you really can't, actually.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can't.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can't.
[SPEAKER_02]: Chatroom, would you agree?
[SPEAKER_06]: Is there such thing as too much bra and panty match?
[SPEAKER_06]: I really don't think so.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's too much bra and panty in those too much bra and panty matches.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, you know, they could lose the bra and panty and I'd be fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what game they need to make if they're going to do wrestling games?
[SPEAKER_02]: I like the WWE ones because I like the customizing mode.
[SPEAKER_02]: I fully would just pick random people and just make them.
[SPEAKER_02]: But they need a luchador game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nothing but luchadors.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, you make your mask and, you know,
[SPEAKER_02]: Sabado Gigante
[SPEAKER_06]: Sabato Higante is like this big clusterfuck of a game show meets a talk show.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like all of everything that exists.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then there's like telenovelas in it too.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like all of what is great on TV compressed into like one three-hour show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have you ever seen the Mad TV sketch where it's like this Asian guy?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like mini-show with two guys or something like that, but it's like different shows.
[SPEAKER_04]: They changed the theme of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like cooking show!
[SPEAKER_02]: Drama Show!
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what else game they need?
[SPEAKER_02]: This is inspired after watching Human Tetris last night.
[SPEAKER_02]: They need Japanese TV show the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry, Actdeft.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actdeft is reminding me that Sabado Higante is on Univision and not Telemundo.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have you ever watched any Japanese game shows?
[SPEAKER_02]: or just some of the live variety shows.
[SPEAKER_06]: I saw like Utada Hikaru on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_02]: Freaking bizarre.
[SPEAKER_02]: They need to do a game that's like that or like Takeshi's Castle the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would buy that.
[SPEAKER_06]: More news, please, because seriously, now this show is getting into, let's see, we've talked about Sabado Higante, bra and panty matches, and now we're just talking about release dates, so we need to get back into news.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, this week, as we mentioned, you know, of course, you're starting to see those Rock Band demo kits come to Best Buys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, some Best Buys, because some retarded Best Buy employees are starting to sell the demo kits like the actual game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thinking, hey, we only got one of these.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's put it out and sell it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then some idiot buys it, and then it ends up on eBay.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then it's all over the internet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Haha, I gots the Rock Band first sale.
[SPEAKER_06]: Firsties.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have the biggest penis on the whole internet because I have Rock Band before you.
[SPEAKER_04]: So yes, apparently people are selling the demo kits and people are actually buying them.
[SPEAKER_04]: The demo kit, actually, the drums kit is missing the kick drum.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, of course, it's a demo version of the game so it doesn't have all the songs.
[SPEAKER_04]: And what's really funny, if you want to
[SPEAKER_04]: It's been relisted on eBay because originally they pulled it down.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, and they pulled it down again.
[SPEAKER_04]: But last I checked it, the bidding was up to $770.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm like, why would you pay $600 more for a game that's going to be out in a few weeks anyways?
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's not even the full game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm like, you're an idiot.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sometimes I wonder if I'm even really in the same human race as all these other people.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, but yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: You, out of the gene pool.
[SPEAKER_04]: This particular case, it was the Marina California Best Buy that
[SPEAKER_04]: They sold it to somebody for, it rang up as $180.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that you're an idiot if you bought it for $180 and you deserve what you get.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, you know, maybe you do want to pick up one of these demo kits, because apparently they're going to be hard to find come holiday.
[SPEAKER_04]: According to EA President John, I don't know, John, anyways, I'm not going to try to pronounce his last name.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's predicting that Rock Band bundles me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Being tough to come by for a while.
[SPEAKER_04]: We won't be able to put enough inventory to meet the demand this fiscal or calendar year.
[SPEAKER_04]: Looks like Ricky Tileo told investors, adding that those who don't buy at launch won't be getting one for Christmas unless you know someone at one of our retailers.
[SPEAKER_04]: What John forgot to mention to people is that...
[SPEAKER_04]: Why do you suppose that they're hard to find?
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it because the game is so immensely popular that people are going to be buying it like crazy?
[SPEAKER_06]: It could be, or it could be they didn't make enough.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or it could be that they saw what happened with the Wii last year and they're like, we gotta do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, you see, here's a little funny thing about this.
[SPEAKER_04]: EA has never made a music game before, and they've never made music game controllers before.
[SPEAKER_04]: and so they're having a little trouble making the music game controllers and guess what?
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a lot of shortages because of that and because you pre-ordered one doesn't necessarily mean that you're going to be getting one either.
[SPEAKER_04]: Think the Wii again.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me put it this way.
[SPEAKER_04]: Guitar Hero 3, yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Same thing with that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks a lot, John.
[SPEAKER_04]: If there's ever a music game coming out that requires a guitar, a drum, a ukulele, whatever the fuck, it will be... Sitar.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sitar.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, Sitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_04]: It will be very fucking hard to find because for some reason people have trouble making fake guitars.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, if you have one pre-ordered, awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you don't,
[SPEAKER_04]: You're fucked.
[SPEAKER_05]: You better wait.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can just take a broom and stick some old arcade buttons on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: There you go, it's a guitar.
[SPEAKER_05]: I will be getting one of these, only because I have to lie, cheat, and steal.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, if you don't want to wait around, or if you aren't lucky enough to get your hands on a copy of Rock Band, you can always wait for Harmonix's next game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I need to take lessons in reading.
[SPEAKER_06]: Harmonix Harmonix
[SPEAKER_06]: So their next game will not have guitars.
[SPEAKER_06]: They will be revealing some secrets about the game at next year's Game Developers Conference.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're going to rip off DDR now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go Harmonix.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, this is what they said.
[SPEAKER_06]: Quote, beats would not be authored by tech-savvy musicians, but would instead be algorithmically generated.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dance Factory 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: There won't be a dedicated peripheral for the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Amplitude million.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, I would not mind a sequel to the Frequency Amplitude, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would be all for that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's finish off that trilogy with a real awesome game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now that they have the, you know, they can get some badass tracks in that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm all for it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or they could just make Freeze pop the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm all for that, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: By the way, let me take this opportunity to say, I will, uh,
[SPEAKER_06]: Jump in here before Jamie reads her next story.
[SPEAKER_06]: Freeze Pop is in Sacramento tonight in OLR headquarters.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're playing a show downtown tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: I did not know this.
[SPEAKER_06]: I swear to God, they go on stage in like two hours.
[SPEAKER_06]: Shit, I wouldn't have been here if I had known that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sucker.
[SPEAKER_06]: And here we are doing the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what I have is my alarm on my phone.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's that, Science Genius Girl or something?
[SPEAKER_02]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll just sit here and wait, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yep, you better.
[SPEAKER_02]: Except that I have news about Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_06]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's actually really cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, uh... I'd love to hear that cool news.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm ready to... No, it's not Get Ready to Rock.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's the other one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's Talk More Rock.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that's my actual ringtone right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, anyway... Oh, and... Money Python.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway... That was so worth the wait.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, anyway...
[SPEAKER_02]: I love my iPhone, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: So for anyone who is interested in the downloadable content for Guitar Hero 3, there has been a leak, which we hope is a real leak.
[SPEAKER_02]: There is stuff listed as, let me see if I can, this thing is kind of hard for me to read.
[SPEAKER_02]: because it's a picture taken off of a television.
[SPEAKER_02]: But there were boss battle tracks listed, the ones you could pick and choose, so it was pretty interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: That would be great because you can't practice those in the game in practice mode, and it's pissing me off.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because those boss battles are hard.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's the Slash Guitar Battle, Devil Went Down to Georgia, Putting Holes in Happiness, The Pretender, This is a Call.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's all on there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some of those are unlocked from the soundtrack, if I remember right, like the Putting Holes in Happiness and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, well, I almost bought the soundtrack just to, you know, see if, you know, how all that worked out.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, of course, I'm cheap and so I didn't.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's all right.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, well, basically that is actually paid unlock content because that stuff is unlocked with a code.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, well, just in regards to like the Putting Holes in Happiness.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it's not.
[SPEAKER_04]: I stand corrected, my bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Next story, please.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, Overlord, a game that I was playing quite a bit until Bioshock came out.
[SPEAKER_04]: is getting some awesome download content.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, three pieces of awesome download content.
[SPEAKER_04]: One, of course, is free, and it actually allows you to play a multiplayer split-screen co-op game, which is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, two overlords running around with 50 minions each, killing innocent people.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then, of course, two of the other packs will cost you some points.
[SPEAKER_04]: No...
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: I have a freaking copy of the game and I still haven't had a chance to play it because I've just been so distracted with everything else.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't point and make evil eyes at me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't give me evils.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I could be selling that game for... Don't give me evils.
[SPEAKER_04]: I plan on playing it at some point.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, last week on this program, I believe Loki reported that IPTV was going to be a part of the new fall update.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, it was a theory, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm just setting him up.
[SPEAKER_06]: That theory was nuked this week as Microsoft said, oh shit, we better make a statement on this.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Microsoft came out and said, quote, Internet protocol television, IPTV features, will only be available from the Xbox 360 through a service provider who has deployed Xbox 360 with Microsoft Media Room services.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is an isolated incident where these features were inadvertently exposed while the customer's console was being serviced and is unrelated to the fall update.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: In the fall.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it's in the middle.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is now fall.
[SPEAKER_06]: Check the clock.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I believe it's in the next few weeks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Next couple weeks should be when.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think last year was around the 12th or something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wonder what kind of cool shiz we're going to see in the updates since we're not seeing IPTV.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: Stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, yay.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, I got some stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: You got a salad?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: You ate it?
[SPEAKER_02]: It has an anime.
[SPEAKER_02]: An anime?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Um.
[SPEAKER_02]: So for people who are fans of Blue Dragon, we get an anime release.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course, if Toriyama is involved in it, you know there's going to be an anime involved, which is why I wonder why we never got Chrono Trigger, but that's another story.
[SPEAKER_02]: So yeah, Blue Dragon is going to have episodes coming to Xbox Live for free.
[SPEAKER_02]: November 15th through January 1st, the episodes will all be there to download and
[SPEAKER_02]: and it's more of a promotional thing for the budget edition that's going to be coming out for 29.40 yen which is 26 bucks here in the US and the fourth volume of Blue Dragon Anime is going to be out on DVD this month and by the way you have to live in Japan to get that for free
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: But does that trick still work where you can use a Japanese Yahoo account to sign in?
[SPEAKER_06]: Or do they block that shit?
[SPEAKER_06]: Remember how for a while we were signing in on a Japanese account to download game demos that weren't out here and stuff?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well that reminds me, I have to download the Guilty Gear 2 demo.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, it still works.
[SPEAKER_06]: Can you still use it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I thought a while they blocked that somehow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, sure they did.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah, they blocked it all right.
[SPEAKER_04]: So they didn't do shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Blue Dragon anime is only free in Japan.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wink, wink, wink, nudge, nuzz.
[SPEAKER_06]: But you don't have a Japanese Yahoo account or anything that you can sign up for.
[SPEAKER_04]: You don't even need a Japanese Yahoo account.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just have a Hotmail account that's like LokiOLRJP or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't even remember what it was.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everybody sign that address up for all the porn you can.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's really, really, really easy.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't check that address ever, so it doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I also have the internet, so I'll just...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, first of all, hardly anybody in America, unless they happen to be watching Nickelodeon in the mid-early 90s.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which was a fuckload of people, actually, in our generation.
[SPEAKER_06]: To be honest, I know the fucking Tomorrow People.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the Tomorrow People was like British sci-fi from the 70s.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's been around for a while, probably a complete and utter ripoff from X-Men, but still, it was really cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: I loved 70s TV when I was a kid.
[SPEAKER_06]: I grew up watching The Jeffersons and The Electric Company.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yeah?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: but I've been watching the Tomorrow People on my iPhone alright sorry I'm reading something about later it's just a funny can you do now so we can end part A real quick there's a quote Miyamoto says wait until you see the Wii 5 years from now yay when they're going to finally support online fully and stuff oh I only have to wait 5 years awesome pulling off the wrapping slowly
[SPEAKER_04]: Seriously?
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways, so other fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pirates vs. Ninjas, Dodgeball, such an awesome name for a game, I guess, has been confirmed to be coming to Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_04]: However, they haven't really nailed down an exact time frame, but early 2008 is when it's expected, and
[SPEAKER_04]: You'll truly be able to see who is better, pirates or ninjas, in the ancient art of dodgeball.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or zombies.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, we're ignoring a very important class of, you know, of, uh, you know... Pinjas?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, cowboys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck cowboys!
[SPEAKER_04]: They ain't got nothing.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're fucking pansies.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ninja versus pirates versus cowboys.
[SPEAKER_05]: Horse-riding losers.
[SPEAKER_05]: We never saw movies about gay ninjas or gay pirates.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not counting Johnny Depp.
[SPEAKER_02]: That wasn't gay.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was just, you know, Keith Richards.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alrighty.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I'm looking forward to seeing the ultimate pirate versus ninja showdown.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, honestly, I think this is a brilliant idea for a video game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Pirates versus ninjas.
[SPEAKER_06]: Somebody's finally doing it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: Now I lost my train of thought.
[SPEAKER_06]: God damn you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I was going to say Pirates vs. Ninjas.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, the dodgeball game that they had on the NES back in the day.
[SPEAKER_06]: That game was awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you can get it on the DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember the remake?
[SPEAKER_04]: That was a Cuneo game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just put Pirates and Ninjas in that game.
[SPEAKER_06]: How awesome is that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: TigerClaw says, Oh, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Having cowboys would give the Pirates and Ninjas an unfair advantage.
[SPEAKER_06]: Cowboys use guns.
[SPEAKER_06]: So do Pirates.
[SPEAKER_02]: Vampires use swords.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, they have ninja stars.
[SPEAKER_02]: Honestly, I think that the two enemy classes should be ninja and cowboy.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you have the pirate who's the hybrid.
[SPEAKER_02]: On top of that, they can swim.
[SPEAKER_02]: If they're a good pirate.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nerd!
[SPEAKER_06]: Lastly...
[SPEAKER_06]: The N-Gage
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you developing for the N-Gage?
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently EA, Capcom, and Vivendi are all stepping up to develop for the N-Gage.
[SPEAKER_06]: So there you have it.
[SPEAKER_06]: The N-Gage service is coming soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow, coming to you right now is the classic video game of the week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Every week, DarkSakura picks out a game from the archives of history that maybe I didn't know about before and says, damn it, you should be playing this game.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, DarkSakura, please reveal for us your classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sounded like you said DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm getting some sound here from Cyberbots.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tell the kids about Cyberbots while I get the sound here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cyberbots is a fighting game that uses Mecha.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you can choose different classes of Mecha and then each of them have three different ones that are in that class that have different types of weaponry.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's fairly customizable how you play it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it had these little cinema cutscenes and a cool storyline.
[SPEAKER_02]: But
[SPEAKER_02]: Puzzle Fighter
[SPEAKER_02]: and, um, her, uh, she has the best robot in the entire game, the Super 8, which is a big octopus robot, so it's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, this game also had one of the best, um, hidden characters was Mecha Gouki, which is basically, you know, Gouki is Akuma over here from the Street Fighter series.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have a Gouki robot that has all of his attacks and everything, it was pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, but also there was, uh, you know, for anyone now who goes back and plays Puzzle Fighter and you're here to see Devil Let's Go, you know, never heard of it, still to know Cyberbot is Capcom's number one game, that's what it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it actually got a special edition that came with, like, a book in this big box, and it was really cool, um, on Saturn.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you can actually still find the game for fairly reasonable, but it's, to me, it's actually, I think, one of Capcom's best games.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: It was arcade and Saturn.
[SPEAKER_06]: More Sega love from DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: Saturn was one of the best systems.
[SPEAKER_06]: There was a lot of overlooked games on the Saturn.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what I did find related to Sega?
[SPEAKER_02]: There's many ITX computers that people are building.
[SPEAKER_02]: Someone built one out of a Sega CD and a Genesis.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was looking on the site.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was really cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mine is collecting dust, by the way.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, well, that's going to bring part A of our show tonight to a close.
[SPEAKER_06]: But we will be back very shortly with more of Orange Lounge Radio because we tape two halves in one night here on Sunday night and then release it twice throughout the week.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you get more Orange Lounge Radio to listen to throughout the week.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we're going to take a quick break and we'll be right back with a little more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and is podcast to the world twice a week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Stay tuned to our podcast feed for the conclusion of this week's Orange Lounge Radio.