[SPEAKER_12]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and released to our podcast stream twice weekly To listen to the first half of this episode visit www.orangeloungeradio.com for links to websites with listings of past episodes Now the conclusion of this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_13]: And welcome back everybody to Orange Lounge Radio on this Sunday evening, November the 18th of 2007.
[SPEAKER_13]: By the time most of you guys hear this on the podcast, it'll probably be Thanksgiving time.
[SPEAKER_13]: So to all of our fellow American listeners, happy Thanksgiving and hope you're having a good day today.
[SPEAKER_13]: To all of our non-American listeners, happy Thursday, whenever that happens to fall for you.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right, let's go back into the gaming news.
[SPEAKER_13]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_13]: Happy Thursday from wherever that happens to fall.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because I'm thinking in my mind Thanksgiving.
[SPEAKER_13]: Never mind.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm out of it tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think Thursday lands on the same time of the week each week.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyways, not when you have the international date line involved, okay?
[SPEAKER_11]: It's still the same time each week.
[SPEAKER_11]: Their time.
[SPEAKER_07]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_11]: I hate you.
[SPEAKER_11]: So another reason I guess people are kind of bitter, you know, Club Nintendo, this wonderful little program that they have in Japan where they get a bunch of cool free shit that we don't ever see anywhere else around the world.
[SPEAKER_11]: Super Famicom Super Nintendo Super Famicom
[SPEAKER_11]: and two 2008 tabletop calendars.
[SPEAKER_11]: Of course, if you want these, you have until December 2nd to select one of the above items.
[SPEAKER_11]: But anyways, according to IGN's translation of the site, those Famicom controllers are going to be delivered by April 2008.
[SPEAKER_11]: But still though, I think those are pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: Too bad we don't have anything like that over here.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know, that's...
[SPEAKER_13]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: Why don't they do that over here, you think?
[SPEAKER_13]: Is it just a money thing?
[SPEAKER_13]: Too many people would get in on it or what?
[SPEAKER_13]: Why can't they just do it like a contest or something silly?
[SPEAKER_11]: Because they don't like us.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: They don't like us?
[SPEAKER_13]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, God, we buy their freaking Wii's even though they haven't put out that many games this year to support it.
[SPEAKER_13]: We've stood by them.
[SPEAKER_13]: We should get something out of it, don't you think?
[SPEAKER_13]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_13]: I guess not.
[SPEAKER_13]: Jerks.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, I'll just continue to play the virtual console games with the...
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, what's interesting is that there do appear to be some other games coming on board with an upcoming peripheral, and that is the Wii Balance Board.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's coming out, I believe, early next year with Wii Fitness.
[SPEAKER_13]: A new game has been announced that will use the Wii Balance Board.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's Namco Bandai's Family Ski.
[SPEAKER_13]: Famitsu has recently revealed this game, and it will be compatible with the Wii Balance Board.
[SPEAKER_13]: Notice that's compatible, not required, but certainly it does look like you'll get to use, you know, Mii-like characters in the game.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm sure your own Mii's...
[SPEAKER_13]: with skiing.
[SPEAKER_13]: The game is supposedly going to come out winter of this year or 2008 even in Japan.
[SPEAKER_13]: So kind of interesting the game may actually be out in Japan before the Wii Fit board actually is out.
[SPEAKER_11]: So kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: Kind of like how we have DualShock 3 support for PlayStation 3 games over here even though the controllers don't come out until the spring.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: What is that?
[SPEAKER_13]: Odd1 in chat says, oh man, and by the way, chat.orangelaunchradio.com, we always love our chatters, the ever-present fourth host on our show.
[SPEAKER_13]: Odd1 says, oh man, the Wii balance board is going to be the best way to randomly tackle friends and loved ones ever.
[SPEAKER_13]: What?
[SPEAKER_13]: That might be kind of scary, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was going to say that they're also going to have a game in Wii Fit that's going to be a skiing or snowboarding game that's going to use the balance board as well, so...
[SPEAKER_13]: So wait, are we just going to see a lot of knockoffs of those type of games, kind of like we've been seeing in Wii Sports?
[SPEAKER_13]: Like, suddenly there's all these golf games and, you know, tennis games.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, it's just like when Wii Play came out, hey, we could do shooting gallery type games in this?
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, let's make a bunch of them.
[SPEAKER_11]: That'll suck.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey, there's nothing wrong with, you know, another skiing game using it, because it's going to be a full, you know...
[SPEAKER_11]: Fleshed Out version of Skeen.
[SPEAKER_13]: Now, Namco Bandai is a pretty respected third-party publisher that's not known for doing a lot of these type of knock-off games.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know how certain third-party publishers are kind of known for being nothing but a bunch of knock-off games?
[SPEAKER_13]: That's not really Namco Bandai, unless they're knocking themselves off or ripping themselves off with Katamari.
[SPEAKER_13]: But, you know what I mean.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think the game will be fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, this is actually something else that I think a lot of people are looking forward to on Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okami will be on Wii and it will excuse me that wasn't fun but basically for the folks at Capcom they had actually been asked if Okami was going to have a Wii release before the PS2 version even came out so they were already thinking about it and so they're going to bring it out
[SPEAKER_13]: And we like widescreen.
[SPEAKER_13]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_13]: Especially me since I have a TV.
[SPEAKER_13]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_13]: And you know those TVs are going to be more and more out there as this Christmas goes on.
[SPEAKER_13]: So I think, you know, because that should be a big seller this year now that HD TVs are getting more and more affordable.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think you're going to see more and more houses have those.
[SPEAKER_13]: So it'll be kind of interesting to see the gaming scene kind of have to evolve to catch up with that and all the games supporting widescreen.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're looking at you, Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_11]: And your 480p HD.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_11]: Um...
[SPEAKER_11]: No price drop.
[SPEAKER_11]: Boo.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't think you need a price drop yet unless your system is like sucking.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's when you start dropping the price of your system.
[SPEAKER_13]: Drunami in chat says, Beatings will continue until morale improves.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_13]: Skate or Die
[SPEAKER_11]: and I know over here we're getting Air Zonk on Monday or Super Air Zonk.
[SPEAKER_11]: How did you find that out?
[SPEAKER_11]: Because... You have ways?
[SPEAKER_11]: No, actually because they announced it on, I believe, the Turbo... There's something like TurboGrafx-16 site that lists a bunch of this crap.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was officially announced, so... I think we should get that and Skate or Die here.
[SPEAKER_13]: That would be an awesome week.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hudson, I'm sure, did it.
[SPEAKER_13]: What do you think they'll give us for Christmas on a virtual console?
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, they could give me Guardian Legend, but I somehow don't think that'll happen.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Have they made a Shrek game on the Super Nintendo?
[SPEAKER_11]: No, I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know what I want?
[SPEAKER_13]: What?
[SPEAKER_13]: Kirby's Avalanche.
[SPEAKER_13]: Get Dr. Bean Machine or whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it actually plays differently on the Super Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_13]: That would be pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm a whore for P.O.P.O.
[SPEAKER_13]: Wait, I want to say Kirby's Avalanche is out there.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm getting it mixed up with a golf game.
[SPEAKER_13]: They should have, well, maybe kind of like 1080.
[SPEAKER_11]: Remember that?
[SPEAKER_11]: What about 720?
[SPEAKER_11]: Fuck 720.
[SPEAKER_11]: 1080 was a snowboarding game.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know, but 720 was a skateboarding game.
[SPEAKER_11]: What's your point?
[SPEAKER_11]: It wasn't a very good skateboarding game.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was an awesome skateboarding game.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: You got killed by bees.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: That makes it all better.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes, it does.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's got bees in it now.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, Actdeft says Kirby's Ambulance is already on the virtual console.
[SPEAKER_13]: You missed it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I didn't see it.
[SPEAKER_13]: You were sleeping that day.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what I get for not playing my Wii for, you know, two weeks.
[SPEAKER_13]: So Actdeft says both those games are out.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't really look at a lot of them so much because I actually have Kirby's Avalanche and a Super Nintendo, but I still kind of want to play it on my Wii.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, there you have it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Christmas comes early for you this year.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_04]: But no, I want Guardian Legend.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if they're doing Sega games, then I freaking want Fantasy Zone.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, that would be kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fantasy Zone.
[SPEAKER_04]: because the Genesis, all you needed was the power base converter to play Master System games on it so you could do it.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know what game they'll probably give us for Christmas?
[SPEAKER_13]: Huge selling Nintendo game that Nintendo made.
[SPEAKER_13]: Big court battle over the rights to the game because somebody else put an off color version of it out first and then Nintendo put a subpar version out themselves.
[SPEAKER_13]: I bet you you'll see Tetris on Christmas.
[SPEAKER_13]: I bet you anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: They should do the Tengen collection.
[SPEAKER_13]: I somehow doubt that Color Dreams games showing up on my Wii I would set fire to my Wii Those games were ass
[SPEAKER_13]: But Tengen Tetris was so much better.
[SPEAKER_13]: That game was cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'll give you that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Tengen, I didn't mind them so much.
[SPEAKER_13]: Those were just basically Atari games like Klax.
[SPEAKER_13]: Those games were cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: But the Color Dreams games were also like non-licensed games.
[SPEAKER_13]: They were ass.
[SPEAKER_13]: Those games were horrible.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know actually what game I wouldn't mind?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh shoot.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was on Super Nintendo but I used to play it in the arcade all the time.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was a caveman game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Trog.
[SPEAKER_13]: Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you remember that one?
[SPEAKER_13]: No.
[SPEAKER_13]: I do not.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, well moving on with other virtual console news.
[SPEAKER_04]: One game in the UK.
[SPEAKER_04]: One game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Double Dribble.
[SPEAKER_13]: At least it's one fucking good game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Double Dribble is pretty good.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, I don't play a lot of sports games, but I did play a shitload of Double Dribble.
[SPEAKER_13]: And NBA Jam was like the all-time greatest basketball game is NBA Jam.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you ever play any of the arcade NBA Jams that had the Mortal Kombat hacks?
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_13]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_13]: Scorpion is an unlocked character, absolutely.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you can play, like, as, you know, the president.
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyway, how did a double dribble story turn into one?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because you said NBA Jam.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Your fault, Rob.
[SPEAKER_03]: Haha, tangent.
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh-huh, uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, if you're not into double dribble, maybe you're into betting.
[SPEAKER_11]: And, of course, coming to Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_11]: Can I bet on double dribble games?
[SPEAKER_11]: No.
[SPEAKER_11]: Coming to Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_11]: Brawl is a spectator mode, and they will have online betting.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ooh!
[SPEAKER_11]: Nintendo is encouraging gambling!
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh my god!
[SPEAKER_11]: Send out all those stupid, uh, you know, parent groups or whatever.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's ban the game.
[SPEAKER_11]: Now.
[SPEAKER_11]: It'll get your children knocked up as well.
[SPEAKER_13]: Isn't spectator mode kind of stupid, though, because you don't know who you're watching?
[SPEAKER_13]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_13]: But at least I think if the person is on your friends list, you should be able to see their name, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyways, it will allow you to observe, of course, players' battles, including the betting system, where you can use your hard-earned coins to wage your own combatants during brawl battles.
[SPEAKER_11]: And winning can pay off big, of course.
[SPEAKER_11]: You can also earn stickers.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hooray!
[SPEAKER_13]: Stickers!
[SPEAKER_13]: Like real stickers?
[SPEAKER_11]: Or fake game stickers?
[SPEAKER_11]: Or real stickers?
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, tough.
[SPEAKER_11]: You don't get real stickers.
[SPEAKER_11]: And, of course, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: It sounds neat, I guess.
[SPEAKER_11]: But once again, I have a feeling that people are going to be like, Hey, you can bet money on it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't think it's going to be that big a deal.
[SPEAKER_11]: I wonder if you're going to get people throwing matches and stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: Like this big underground scheme?
[SPEAKER_13]: No, you can't, because you don't know who's playing in it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: Odd1 says, all games should have a mechanic by which they mail you stickers.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't care if they're not related to the game, I also want stickers.
[SPEAKER_11]: So are you suggesting we go back to, was it the Activision patch system that they had?
[SPEAKER_13]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, if you think about it, Xbox Live achievements are indirectly inspired by the old Activision patch thing.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know what I think they should do?
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, Activision.
[SPEAKER_13]: Please tell me someone from Activision is listening.
[SPEAKER_13]: Here's a fabulous idea.
[SPEAKER_13]: Put all those old Activision games together yet again in one of those bundles, but have the achievements be the old patches you used to get.
[SPEAKER_13]: Like, you know, when you would get so many points in a game, then you can unlock the little picture of that patch.
[SPEAKER_13]: That might be kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: Even though we've seen those Activision packs like a million times for different consoles or whatever, I think one more would be kind of cool for nothing else but that, and maybe put some Xbox Live in it.
[SPEAKER_13]: and put Oink in it for God's sake.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oink was awesome.
[SPEAKER_13]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_13]: Rant.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oink.
[SPEAKER_13]: Guess what store is promising Wheeze?
[SPEAKER_13]: T.J.
[SPEAKER_13]: Maxx
[SPEAKER_13]: I used to live right next to one, and it's basically just like Ross Dress for Less, but like one step above it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't think it's a step above.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, I think it's really on the same tier as like Ross Dress for Less.
[SPEAKER_13]: So how TJ Maxx got Wii bundles is beyond me.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's what makes this story funny for those that don't understand.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know, is TJ Maxx nationwide?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, we had him in Mobile.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, okay, then they're pretty nationwide.
[SPEAKER_13]: They have him here.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was really ghetto.
[SPEAKER_13]: Overseas.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's like...
[SPEAKER_13]: DJ Maxx is an interesting place.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_11]: I hope you like golf attachments and tennis racket attachments.
[SPEAKER_13]: And the potato chip holder that will also hold your Wiimote.
[SPEAKER_13]: They never released that because it sucks.
[SPEAKER_13]: God damn it.
[SPEAKER_13]: That thing actually looked kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: Just buy a damn bowl.
[SPEAKER_13]: No.
[SPEAKER_13]: Put your chips in.
[SPEAKER_13]: You don't need a fucking little thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: How about we cleanse the palate with the undead?
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Zombies are great.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love The Undead.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, loathe The Undead.
[SPEAKER_13]: I know.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's turn zombies loose in TJ Maxx.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would totally, totally film that and sell it as a movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, for those of us who love The Undead, who dig their zombies, House of the Dead 2 and 3 are going to be on Wii, using the Wii Zapper.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you can shoot your zombies in the head.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you don't have to press A. Fuck House of the Dead.
[SPEAKER_13]: I want Typing of the Dead on Wii.
[SPEAKER_13]: Now that they support the USB keyboards.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, that's true, that's true.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, they put out that patch a while back, and now they support the USB keyboards.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I love House of the Dead.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I love Typing of the Dead.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I had House of the Dead 2 on Dreamcast.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was freaking sweet.
[SPEAKER_13]: I have Typing of the Dead on GameTap.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had Typing of the Dead on Dreamcast.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think I might as well.
[SPEAKER_11]: Um...
[SPEAKER_11]: This new pack is actually kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm seeing Sega releasing some of these gun games, and hopefully they'll release more, because I know with Ghost Squad they started that off, and of course they're going to use the Wii Zapper.
[SPEAKER_11]: The other thing which no one else has really mentioned so far, other than the fact that it's coming out in March, is that it's also going to be priced the same as Ghost Squad, which is $29.99 retail.
[SPEAKER_11]: So you may be thinking, oh hey, $50 for games that don't look that great on the Wii...
[SPEAKER_11]: It's only $30, and it's actually a pretty good collection, and hopefully it's as good as Ghost Squad, because Ghost Squad is pretty fun, and I think a lot of people are going to overlook it.
[SPEAKER_13]: And it's zombies being shot in the face by your Wiimote.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, that is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love shooting zombies.
[SPEAKER_13]: And look at it this way.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's not the movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just zombies are great, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: Zombies are great.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyways...
[SPEAKER_11]: So another thing that you're going to probably be pissed off about, especially if you just bought a DS, is that there's a rumor saying that there's another DS redesign coming your way.
[SPEAKER_11]: In fact, it's supposed to happen after the holiday sales kind of die out, probably next spring, which is kind of interesting because spring is when they released the last revision, the DS Lite.
[SPEAKER_11]: The rumor is that it's thinner.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's not going to have a Game Boy Advance port.
[SPEAKER_11]: It will have onboard storage and larger screens.
[SPEAKER_13]: So... And you know that onboard storage is going to then be used by all the cool games that come out next, so everybody has to upgrade to one of these things.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_13]: Nintendo, I just bought this fucking thing like three months ago, and already...
[SPEAKER_13]: You're thinking about making me upgrade.
[SPEAKER_13]: You bastards.
[SPEAKER_11]: I just bought a DS Lite myself, too, so I don't have to play my wife's pink one.
[SPEAKER_11]: I bought a nice black one.
[SPEAKER_11]: Haven't played anything on it, though, yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: I still have my white one, and I like it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But remember, I had to get a pink Advance back in the day.
[SPEAKER_13]: Now, people in the chat room are screaming, rumor, rumor, rumor.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes, it's a rumor, but honestly, would it surprise you?
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, really, think about it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Look at Nintendo's track record.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, do you see why this is popping up everywhere?
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, it definitely...
[SPEAKER_11]: That sounds true to me!
[SPEAKER_13]: The Game Boy Advance SP The DS I have all of those too And now one more DS Whatever they're going to call this thing DS Slim and Light They'll call it the DS Uber DS Rape Because that's what I keep feeling Super DS
[SPEAKER_13]: Tiger Claw, oh yes, Tiger Claw says the next version of DS will probably be the DS Micro.
[SPEAKER_13]: And of course, the advanced Micro.
[SPEAKER_11]: I have a Game Boy Micro.
[SPEAKER_13]: You're probably the only person I know that has a Game Boy Micro.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I didn't pay for it either.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're still selling those at work.
[SPEAKER_11]: Or should I say we still have the same 10 that we've had since...
[SPEAKER_11]: Game Boy Micro
[SPEAKER_13]: Like Jamie's Puzzle Fighter, I could see that.
[SPEAKER_13]: But it's got interchangeable fails.
[SPEAKER_04]: I tried playing Kingdom Hearts on it and that did not work.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my god, I couldn't read.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, even worse is playing a shooter on that damn thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: It doesn't happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: You do not play a shooter on...
[SPEAKER_13]: Do you remember back in the day on the old school Game Boys, they used to have the magnify and light things that you could put on top of them, these really hideous things.
[SPEAKER_07]: But they worked.
[SPEAKER_13]: They would slightly magnify the screen and light, and you'd totally get a headache.
[SPEAKER_13]: They need that for the micro, like a magnify thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: Would that kind of defeat the purpose of buying a micro in the first place?
[SPEAKER_13]: You know people would buy it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because they're dumb, right?
[SPEAKER_13]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_13]: Microsoft improperly allowed his underage kid to use his debit card to subscribe to Xbox Live and automatically renew the subscription without authorization.
[SPEAKER_13]: He says that in October 2005, this is being done by Francisco Garcia in Georgia.
[SPEAKER_13]: He says in October 2005, his son Silvario used his debit card to buy a $50 one-year subscription to Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_13]: A year later, Microsoft automatically billed him for an additional year of Xbox Live without his knowledge or consent.
[SPEAKER_13]: And he says that the charge sent his checking account into overdraft and that the bank slapped him with a $35 penalty.
[SPEAKER_13]: This is why you should be careful when using your debit card as a credit card, but never mind.
[SPEAKER_13]: And then the plaintiff goes on to say that Microsoft refunded the subscription fee but would not cover the bank penalty.
[SPEAKER_13]: It actually would be a son that committed fraud because a son would have had to put it in his father's name to go through.
[SPEAKER_13]: Nowhere is it said how in the hell the kid got the debit card in the first place.
[SPEAKER_13]: But I guess that's not important.
[SPEAKER_13]: Garcia goes on to say that Microsoft broke Georgia law when it allowed his kid to use a debit card to sign up for Xbox Live and then continue to break the law when it renewed the service without written authorization.
[SPEAKER_13]: He's speaking unspecified damages and asking the court to broaden the case to include all Xbox Live customers in Georgia with similar problems.
[SPEAKER_13]: So in other words, kids that steal their dad's wallet and use the cards to buy things.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not Xbox's fault.
[SPEAKER_04]: In fact, I've seen how hefty the authorization process is to that because I couldn't use my debit card.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had to use one of my other credit cards to run it through.
[SPEAKER_04]: So first of all, they're very specific on putting in the information.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have to have the complete billing information for the person who owns the card.
[SPEAKER_04]: Therefore...
[SPEAKER_04]: It is not Microsoft's fault.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's, first of all, that guy's fault for letting his kid be able to get into his wallet so easily.
[SPEAKER_04]: And second of all, it's the kid's issue for basically committing fraud.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, but yet there's more.
[SPEAKER_13]: Actually, technically, that's borderline on identity theft.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, you want to hear about the kid committing fraud?
[SPEAKER_13]: Here's more.
[SPEAKER_13]: Here's more, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_13]: Microsoft has asked the federal court to dismiss the case, saying that they have paperwork that proves that the child misrepresented his age when he subscribed to Xbox Live by falsely stating that he was 18 years old.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, even though he would have had to have done it under his parents' name for it to have gone through.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's, it's... What's the chatroom saying?
[SPEAKER_13]: Sorry, chatroom.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkDeadSuya says...
[SPEAKER_13]: Nevermind credit card.
[SPEAKER_13]: This is why condoms were invented.
[SPEAKER_13]: That is brilliant.
[SPEAKER_13]: Our chatter of the week, everybody.
[SPEAKER_13]: Dark Tetsuya, everybody.
[SPEAKER_13]: Round of applause.
[SPEAKER_13]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hooray.
[SPEAKER_13]: Loki, no comments?
[SPEAKER_11]: That's just an idiot.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, seriously.
[SPEAKER_11]: He didn't notice the charge was on his credit card in the first place, and then it rebuilt itself.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, seriously.
[SPEAKER_04]: How do you do something like that?
[SPEAKER_11]: And this is funny, though, because this must have been on an original Xbox account, because now, if your account runs out, all that happens is it turns into silver again.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: It doesn't have an auto-renew option.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have to renew it.
[SPEAKER_11]: There is no auto-renew.
[SPEAKER_13]: That auto-renew thing was...
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_13]: or let your kid steal it in the first place and put it on there and then not do anything about it the first time.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, a year went by between.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't think this case has a lot of chances.
[SPEAKER_11]: And it's not Microsoft's fault that your bank account was so low that you overdrafted.
[SPEAKER_11]: So you know what?
[SPEAKER_13]: If you didn't want to overdraft, use a real credit card that would have denied it if it was going to hit your limit.
[SPEAKER_13]: Although I kind of agree.
[SPEAKER_13]: The bank should have denied the charge, but at the same time, this is how banks make money off of people who overdraft.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's face it, that's one huge way they make money.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, on top of that, there's often times where a bank will write off an overdraft charge if it was erroneous, if it can be proven.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, it's just really a case of this man in Georgia being a complete and utter moron.
[SPEAKER_04]: End of story.
[SPEAKER_13]: You deserve that $35 charge, dumbass.
[SPEAKER_13]: F.U.
[SPEAKER_13]: Time F.U.
[SPEAKER_13]: Time
[SPEAKER_04]: The first F you goes towards this man in the black Toyota truck who pulled out of the gas station and into my lane and cut me off.
[SPEAKER_04]: You are a stupid piece of shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, you know, you totally deserve to have that, you know, cop car pull you over.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, that was a winner.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, Loki.
[SPEAKER_13]: Um, my... Oh, it's two part, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_13]: F you to Rob.
[SPEAKER_13]: I thought you said that was mine.
[SPEAKER_13]: And then I was like, okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, well, that's okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: You go.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'll be nice.
[SPEAKER_13]: You sure?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, and I guess the two-part is F.U.
[SPEAKER_13]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, F.U.
[SPEAKER_13]: Jamie!
[SPEAKER_13]: How's that?
[SPEAKER_13]: You're cutting in front of Loki to say F.U.
[SPEAKER_13]: Jamie.
[SPEAKER_13]: Your mom.
[SPEAKER_04]: Last night.
[SPEAKER_13]: In bed.
[SPEAKER_11]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't really have much to be angry about, but I am annoyed at the Priuses that were driving in front of me today.
[SPEAKER_11]: Apparently, owning a Prius means you drive slow.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, screw you, Prius owners, and I don't give a shit if you're helping the environment.
[SPEAKER_11]: You're not helping the environment because you're making me late.
[SPEAKER_11]: Or later.
[SPEAKER_11]: So.
[SPEAKER_13]: F you to the macaroni and cheese pizza at John's Incredibly Shitty Pizza because that shit was nasty.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was good!
[SPEAKER_07]: The macaroni and cheese pizza was nasty.
[SPEAKER_07]: The macaroni and cheese pizza was good.
[SPEAKER_04]: The peanut butter pizza was kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: I liked the peanut butter pizza too.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the best was the barbecue chicken.
[SPEAKER_13]: The barbecue chicken Alfredo was okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: It makes the Incredibly Shitty Pizza not that shitty.
[SPEAKER_13]: I liked the macaroni and cheese pizza though.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, you're weird.
[SPEAKER_13]: F you to Jamie twice.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, well, F you back to your... F you infinity, plus one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, you can't add plus one to infinity.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because infinity is already infinity.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I just did.
[SPEAKER_13]: What are you going to do, tell God to smite me?
[SPEAKER_03]: Sometimes the chat room just needs to be here.
[SPEAKER_13]: That silence, by the way, was Jamie actually praying.
[SPEAKER_13]: I know that was great radio, boys and girls, but there you have it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I want to point out though real quick about some of the previous stories.
[SPEAKER_13]: GS68 had a great comment about the whole father and the kid thing.
[SPEAKER_13]: The father should cut his credit card and stab his kid with one of his sharp edges.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: I almost think GS68 might have just taken the crown of Chatter of the Week.
[SPEAKER_13]: We might have to have a good old fight over this.
[SPEAKER_11]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyways...
[SPEAKER_11]: Flashback Consoles
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: But anyways, you know, what, they had such wonderful series that they sold off to Ubisoft Driver.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ooh, that was awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: Such a wonderful game.
[SPEAKER_11]: It had no flaws at all.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, wait, no, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_11]: Stuntman, that was okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: But anyways, so yeah, the Test Drive series has been now licensed to InfoGames, which had, if I remember correctly, didn't they have the really cool, like, theme song that they made for their company?
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm sorry, it wasn't cool at all, but it was a theme song for their company.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know how I knew Atari was going downhill about 15 years ago?
[SPEAKER_13]: Did you ever play a game in the arcades called Pit Fighter?
[SPEAKER_13]: I remember Pit Fighter!
[SPEAKER_13]: I think this game was Atari, yes?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I don't think it was Atari.
[SPEAKER_04]: Was it Atari?
[SPEAKER_13]: It sucked.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it was Mortal Kombat digitized, you know, type.
[SPEAKER_13]: Game Game Game Game
[SPEAKER_11]: Yay, Jenga.
[SPEAKER_11]: Who thought that was a good idea?
[SPEAKER_13]: Odd1 says, Pit Fighter for Super Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_13]: Proof that I was stupid as a child.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's okay, Odd1.
[SPEAKER_11]: Seriously, Jenga, what the hell were you thinking?
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, it's hard enough to play the game as it is, but oh, let's play it the way, that'll be even easier.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because everyone wants to play, the only reason that people aren't playing Jenga is because it isn't set under the sea or in some fantastic fictional world.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's why people aren't playing Jenga.
[SPEAKER_11]: Not because, you know, it's Jenga or anything.
[SPEAKER_13]: Seriously, look at this box art.
[SPEAKER_13]: Here's the Sega Genesis version, which was put out by Tengen and, yes, developed by Atari.
[SPEAKER_13]: Look at this.
[SPEAKER_13]: I forgot about the Dominatrix lady fighter they had in it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, this is a horrible fucking game.
[SPEAKER_13]: Why is the guy just in his underwear?
[SPEAKER_13]: Because that's what they wore when they fought.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was panties.
[SPEAKER_13]: Dominatrix fighter.
[SPEAKER_04]: They would be manties.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes, manties.
[SPEAKER_13]: Digitized Mantis.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's what you have to look forward to in Pit Fighter.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, good riddance, Atari.
[SPEAKER_13]: Your time is up.
[SPEAKER_13]: Your 15 minutes are over.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, Loki jumped the gun a little bit because we were actually supposed to have the mailbag segment before that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Eh, whatever.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_13]: We can be fluid here on the show.
[SPEAKER_13]: We can change things around on the fly.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, DarkSakura, are you ready to do some mailbags?
[SPEAKER_13]: Sure!
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, when you send us emails at mailbag.orangelongeradio.com, Jamie will read the emails and she'll pick out her favorite emails and read them.
[SPEAKER_13]: And that's what she's going to do right now here on the program.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's open up the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_04]: First email comes from Robert M.
[SPEAKER_04]: who is a regular writer, I would say, to our station.
[SPEAKER_04]: And actually, I have a slight problem with my email because what happened is I had a problem with Firefox doing its... I'm going to close a new thing again!
[SPEAKER_04]: And it didn't reload all the windows, so let's go back to this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just to clarify last week's letter, while playing the game to a podcast would indeed be a bizarre-
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's say I listen to OLR Part A, 30 songs play days through my break at work.
[SPEAKER_04]: I listen to 20 more songs, followed by a viewing of the latest Ask a Ninja episode.
[SPEAKER_04]: Once I sync my iPod to my computer, but the iPod and iTunes will completely forget that 50 songs and podcasts have been played.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not sure why this is.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have the 5th generation 30GB model, if that makes any difference.
[SPEAKER_04]: Secondly, any idea by Nintendo doesn't add an option to view the most recently added Miis.
[SPEAKER_04]: Since two of the four options, one of which is the default, show that most popular Miis assumes that the most popular Miis can only get more popular and the newer ones get entirely overlooked.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you ever see any Miis who look vaguely like members of the U.S.
[SPEAKER_04]: whose line is it anyway, let me know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Looking forward to your next show, Robert M. That would be nice, but it'll never happen because they're lazy.
[SPEAKER_04]: That has been sort of proven.
[SPEAKER_04]: Next one.
[SPEAKER_04]: and actually we got an email from someone who's asking technical questions on the station which I will actually be replying to off of the air but I'm acknowledging that we received one from DJ Mikey Mike which I think is actually kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then we got a review of a game from Xenocore who actually sent the email about Ore no Riori which we had Rob look up and
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey Ola, the Xbox 360 controller is a good addition to my control set for my PC.
[SPEAKER_04]: I use it for my classic games quite often.
[SPEAKER_04]: However, I wonder if anyone else is having the same issue that I am.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whenever I test the inputs for the controller, both triggers seem to be on the same axis.
[SPEAKER_04]: If I use the left trigger, the axis goes to 0%, and if I pull the right one, it goes to 100%.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pull both of the axes, it stays at 50%.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, the right stick will only show movement in the low left to high right diagonal.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't use it as a second analog control.
[SPEAKER_04]: What the fuck?
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought Microsoft made PC controls better than this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hopefully, it's just the crack my roomie snuck into my food.
[SPEAKER_04]: One more thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hmm?
[SPEAKER_04]: Since my question had folks guessing, allow me to tell you why I seek the knowledge that I do with a quick review of Ore no Ryori for the PS1 Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: My cooking, as it is known in the US, is a DualShock-centered cooking simulation.
[SPEAKER_04]: The player is a head chef of a cooking establishment that has you preparing various dishes depending on the restaurant's theme, ramen, fast food, etc.,
[SPEAKER_04]: To use the first stage as an example, you take the customer's order as they walk in, start the soup for the ramen, chop the vegetables for the ramen, the thinner the better.
[SPEAKER_04]: One stick is used for your hand position, the other controls the chef's knife.
[SPEAKER_04]: You take the soup off of the heat before it burns, you put the ramen in the brim, blah blah, okay, you cook ramen.
[SPEAKER_04]: The game comes in here, you have six seats that can be full at one time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Managing what you work on and when is the name of the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fall behind in your prep time, your orders will pile up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, isn't there a flash game like that on Yahoo?
[SPEAKER_04]: Except you're just serving people.
[SPEAKER_04]: Diner Dash?
[SPEAKER_04]: Diner Dash, that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: While you were running the restaurant, other random events occurred.
[SPEAKER_04]: These show up as attacks on the other players in versus mode.
[SPEAKER_04]: A customer may leave without paying.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have to chase him down, kill the roaches that flood into the restaurant with your shoe, call the police on wandering drunks that enter the restaurant, and washing dishes.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a link here on that.
[SPEAKER_04]: The game is a blast to play.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you like Cookie Mama and want to feel like a short order cook from Rolf House, give this game a shot.
[SPEAKER_04]: It makes Cookie Mama look like a walk in the park.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, this game is especially worthy of a spot in your import collection.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hopefully you won't kick Cookie Mama to the curb after playing this one.
[SPEAKER_04]: As always, keep up the good work on the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yours truly, Xenocore.
[SPEAKER_13]: Ranma is suggesting Iron Chef for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_13]: And SonOfDad in chatroom is suggesting Hell's Kitchen for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_13]: I would check it out, yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_13]: People do play stuff on PS1.
[SPEAKER_04]: Howdy, OR!
[SPEAKER_04]: I've heard Sky mention a fondness for old-school Zork and an enthusiasm I share.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought you guys might be interested in this, and this is www.ifcomp.org, I-F-C-O-M-P.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's one of the few yearly contests this one just wrapped up for Homebrew Text Adventures.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's quite a community out there of interactive fiction enthusiasts.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've designed a half-assed IF game or two, but never finished anything, so I think that these intrepid designers deserve a round of applause.
[SPEAKER_04]: I encourage anyone interested in the medium to check it out.
[SPEAKER_04]: It can be used in some fascinating ways and often surpasses gaming in story and character development.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anywho, keep keeping on.
[SPEAKER_04]: You guys rock.
[SPEAKER_04]: Atreyu.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, I want to say about a year ago, there was somebody that did an Orange Lounge Radio Text Adventure game.
[SPEAKER_13]: I seem to remember playing it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Sky, DarkSakura, and Loki Yeah, it's this question again.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's the story behind them and when did you start using those names?
[SPEAKER_04]: As for mine, Osfer, it's simply a cross between Zephyr, one of my favorite Bimani songs, and Austin, which is my real name.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I guess you wanted us to know if we were reading it online.
[SPEAKER_04]: Random comment, Final Fantasy Tactics, The War of the Lions is my new anti-drug.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks, Osfer.
[SPEAKER_04]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know that you'll do what you want, but I still insist Restore for the Sega Genesis.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've tried to describe this game to people and I get weird looks, but trust me, it's a gem.
[SPEAKER_04]: Play it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, I've played it.
[SPEAKER_04]: PPS, Yara, sponsored by Kmart.
[SPEAKER_04]: P-P-P-S, I want to hear Loki rant in an English accent.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, maybe we can get Loki to tell us about his name in an English accent.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, I'm not doing that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Why don't you give us a jolly old story?
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm not even trying tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, tell us about your name.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's named after a Norse god.
[SPEAKER_11]: I started using it when I was playing Cusar.
[SPEAKER_11]: A lot.
[SPEAKER_11]: OMG, you didn't get it from Dogma?
[SPEAKER_11]: No.
[SPEAKER_11]: Actually, if anything, I got it from The Mask.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, mine was... I used to be a Japanese major when I lived in Alabama.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go fig.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was actually going into the JET program, which is why I was doing it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But our teacher decided that she would give all of us names in Japanese in class so that when we were...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_13]: Because you were emo.
[SPEAKER_04]: This was pre-emo.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes, but you're always on the cutting edge, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_04]: I am.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the other funny thing about this is that I met somebody on AOL who went by EvilSakura who was mad at me for getting DarkSakura, but it turned out her boyfriend knew Dan because Dan at the time had RichterDX, as in DraculaX, and
[SPEAKER_04]: and DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_13]: But that name is taken on a lot of sites.
[SPEAKER_13]: Apparently there are five other green skies out there, so it's hard to use that name.
[SPEAKER_13]: So at one point I decided to spell sky differently.
[SPEAKER_13]: So you put an I-E instead of Y. So it was green sky.
[SPEAKER_13]: And then one day I said, I'm not green anymore.
[SPEAKER_13]: So it was just sky.
[SPEAKER_13]: And that's the real deal, like how my name came about.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's just one constant evolution after another.
[SPEAKER_13]: So it's not ski or grenski or whatever people say.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's just sky.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And to tell GZDR4EV, I actually had the name before there was a Dark Sakura, before there was a Sakura in Street Fighter.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was in college in 94, no, I started taking Japanese in early 95.
[SPEAKER_04]: So this predates.
[SPEAKER_04]: However, I did think it was funny that there was a Dark Sakura later, and I said that I should sue Capcom for name infringement.
[SPEAKER_03]: You should.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was a joke.
[SPEAKER_04]: You should.
[SPEAKER_04]: That'd be fun to watch.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's right, gaming news out of Brazil, and this is actually pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's this company called TechToy, and what they're doing is that they're basically licensing from Sega the right to make an official portable Genesis, or if you will, Mega Drive.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's an official portable Mega Drive, and it has a little controller and three buttons on it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I would say it looks like a Game Boy Micro, but bigger, and it has the buttons on it, and it has 20 games.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alex Kidd, Sonic & Knuckles, Golden Axe, Echo the Dolphin, and of course the color of the unit is blue, just like Sega.
[SPEAKER_13]: The 20 games are already pre-installed on the unit.
[SPEAKER_13]: Unfortunately, you can't add to them or take away from them once you have the 20 games.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's all you get.
[SPEAKER_13]: It runs on three AAA batteries.
[SPEAKER_13]: Kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_13]: It will cost about the Brazilian equivalent of $100 US.
[SPEAKER_13]: December 5th is the day it comes out, just in time for Brazilian Christmas, which there will be no snow.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll tell you something about that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, there might be.
[SPEAKER_13]: Brazil's a big country, and there's lots of mountain ranges, but I think it's the other time of year over there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, something about that is that actually Dan was pointing out to me, and this was a couple years ago that he pointed out to me, is that the Sega Master System actually still has a very big following in Brazil.
[SPEAKER_04]: and because a lot of the Master System sites that he found or even a lot of ROMs that he found when we both used to be heavy into emulation were games that were Genesis games that we knew on the Genesis but had been put out for Master System because they had come out over there on Master System.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think all of our Brazilian listeners, of which there ought to be a few, because Brazil's a big fucking place, right?
[SPEAKER_13]: It's just as big as the U.S.
[SPEAKER_13]: almost, right?
[SPEAKER_13]: So I think all our, if not bigger, Brazilian listeners should get together and pool money enough.
[SPEAKER_13]: If everybody chips in, let's say there's 10 people listening to Brazil, I'll chip in $10 and send us one of these, because it sounds kind of funnish.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll fully pay for one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me know what the ratio is, and I'll totally pay for one.
[SPEAKER_13]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want one.
[SPEAKER_13]: I want one too, but I don't want to have to pay for it because I'm cheap.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyhow, so that's all I got to say on the portable Mega Drive.
[SPEAKER_13]: It is out in Brazil.
[SPEAKER_13]: Or coming out soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, this makes me a very, very sad panda.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: Although I'm not a panda.
[SPEAKER_13]: It makes you a sad Jamie?
[SPEAKER_04]: It makes me a sad me.
[SPEAKER_04]: But not an MII.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, what is it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Stuff!
[SPEAKER_04]: Marvel Universe Online, there's actually a rumor of cancellation going out.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's been stated that the MMO has run into, quote, serious, potentially stalling developmental troubles.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, I find it funny that my reference here, which is on Joystick, said that probably because everyone wants to be Wolverine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not me!
[SPEAKER_11]: So apparently it wasn't Banjo-Kazooie.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, is that the big name game that looks like it's getting cancelled?
[SPEAKER_13]: Marvel, huh?
[SPEAKER_13]: Was that supposed to be an Xbox 360 exclusive?
[SPEAKER_13]: I thought it was on PS3 and Xbox.
[SPEAKER_13]: No.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_13]: That is a big deal then, because that was like Xbox's MMO.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was only going to be playable on that system.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, because it wouldn't have totally been just exactly like City of Heroes or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_11]: But it would have been Marvel.
[SPEAKER_11]: It might have been kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: No.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_11]: I want to see a fighting game.
[SPEAKER_11]: I need to do that Mortal Kombat vs. DC.
[SPEAKER_11]: That'd be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyways, so the King Kong game is coming out here pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wait, the King of Kong game?
[SPEAKER_11]: DVD.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think Donkey Kong came out like 20 years ago.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey, they're going to make a game based on this movie.
[SPEAKER_11]: You watch.
[SPEAKER_11]: There's a lot of bad ideas out there and people are waiting to jump on that stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: Orange Lounge Radio, bringing you the late breaking news.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, hey kids, did you hear about that totally rad Donkey Kong that's coming out?
[SPEAKER_11]: No, listen dude, okay, the King of Kong game, okay?
[SPEAKER_11]: You'll play as the people playing Donkey Kong.
[SPEAKER_11]: This is like even better than Donkey Kong.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because you're playing people playing Donkey Kong.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyways, so yeah, the DVD's coming out...
[SPEAKER_11]: Soon, in January.
[SPEAKER_11]: Being put out by New Line.
[SPEAKER_11]: Actually, we're doing something at our work for this thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're having me set up some sort of Donkey Kong competition.
[SPEAKER_13]: Are you going to have the guys there?
[SPEAKER_11]: No.
[SPEAKER_11]: They should come.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, we're low budget, okay?
[SPEAKER_11]: They asked me to download the virtual console game, yet I see no monies for this.
[SPEAKER_11]: They said they'll pay me back later, and then they're going to put it on our big theater screen.
[SPEAKER_11]: But, um...
[SPEAKER_11]: Anywho, so yeah, it's going to be coming out apparently January 29th.
[SPEAKER_13]: But it'll be out on the internet long before.
[SPEAKER_11]: Probably as soon as screeners come out for that and people pirate that shit like crazy.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm sure there's already a version that's one of those cameras.
[SPEAKER_11]: The question is, why would you want to pirate this?
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, seriously.
[SPEAKER_11]: I've heard it's a good movie.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's a good movie, but seriously, is it worth wasting a DVD for me?
[SPEAKER_11]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_11]: I want to see it.
[SPEAKER_11]: You should not talk negatively about this.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm not talking negatively about it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm just saying, no, it's like...
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: It would be like pirating Geely.
[SPEAKER_13]: The one crazy dude we met at all games, I think, is in this movie, Mr. Awesome.
[SPEAKER_13]: Was he there when you and I both went?
[SPEAKER_13]: I know there was one time I went down there and he was there.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think it might have been a different time when I was there by myself.
[SPEAKER_04]: It might have been just you because I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_13]: I was there one time by myself because I was there on a trip.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think he was in the movie.
[SPEAKER_11]: Obviously, I'd remember someone named Mr. Awesome.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean... Wasn't he at... Was he at E3?
[SPEAKER_13]: He was probably at E3 that year.
[SPEAKER_11]: Fuck if I know.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Someone named Mr. Awesome needs to be punched in the face.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, seriously.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm Mr. Awesome!
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, you're gonna die.
[SPEAKER_13]: This guy... was interesting.
[SPEAKER_13]: There's really no other word to describe.
[SPEAKER_13]: He was one of the most interesting fellows I've ever met.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, I'm sure he was interesting.
[SPEAKER_13]: You're all retarded!
[SPEAKER_13]: No, just... I'm not gonna talk negatively, Loki.
[SPEAKER_13]: We're not gonna have that on this program.
[SPEAKER_13]: He was just interesting.
[SPEAKER_13]: Um...
[SPEAKER_13]: Also interesting is the fact that another movie is being made into a hip new game.
[SPEAKER_13]: Ghostbusters!
[SPEAKER_13]: But I'm not talking about that old ass Commodore 64 game.
[SPEAKER_13]: Although that game was rad.
[SPEAKER_13]: That was one of the first Commodore 64 games I ever remember owning.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I believe this was on the 2600 and all the other systems.
[SPEAKER_13]: But there was a new Ghostbusters game coming out.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's not a remake of the old one.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's a brand new Ghostbusters game.
[SPEAKER_13]: This being previewed by an issue of Game Informer Magazine.
[SPEAKER_13]: Apparently some game footage has already hit the internet, although it's kind of a bit of a rumor.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, it's been confirmed.
[SPEAKER_11]: If you go to GhostbustersGame.com, there's a bunch of stuff there too.
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyway, the game is supposed to be a sequel to the first two films, since they never did make a Ghostbusters 3, and now the actors are getting kind of old.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, the game is supposed to be a sequel to the first two films.
[SPEAKER_13]: Zootfly is developing it, and we don't know exactly what platforms it'll be on, but you can probably guess it'll be most of the next-gen systems.
[SPEAKER_13]: I do kind of hope, though, it's on Wii, because I think that would be fun to try and not cross the streams on the Wii, with the whole zapping things.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know if it might be coming out on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_13]: Here's the other great thing about it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Bill Murray, Dan Aykroyd, Harold Ramis, they are all actually a part of the game.
[SPEAKER_13]: They're apparently writing the script and doing all the voiceovers.
[SPEAKER_13]: So that is kind of cool to know that it's authentic.
[SPEAKER_13]: Please don't suck this game.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know if Zootfly is actually developing it, though.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know that they were doing something similar.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think this is actually NVIDIA.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's the same team that worked on... Oh my bad, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was originally rumored at Zootfly.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's the same team that put together the Scarface game, so, you know.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_13]: GameGame.com
[SPEAKER_11]: That's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm going to try and find... Here's the game.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, this looks like the game itself.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, good.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's not like an actual first person.
[SPEAKER_00]: I can't listen to this.
[SPEAKER_00]: But it looks cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: It looks like Resident Evil, but like Ghostbusters.
[SPEAKER_00]: What I like about it is that it's an over-the-shoulder view and not a first person.
[SPEAKER_13]: I just think that's highly inappropriate to do to give me such subpar...
[SPEAKER_04]: I have noticed something that if you try to click on the video in window to the next sometimes it'll leave the old thing copied.
[SPEAKER_13]: Brilliant.
[SPEAKER_04]: That happened to me with the paddle cap.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, here we go.
[SPEAKER_13]: Somebody grade out the G4 part in the beginning.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_13]: I approve of this link.
[SPEAKER_13]: That does look kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_13]: I hope that is the Wii.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's a 360.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, the graphics look very 360.
[SPEAKER_11]: They do.
[SPEAKER_11]: Keep going because there's a part where they show the Stay Puft Marshmallow.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_13]: Wow, they shot him in the face.
[SPEAKER_13]: That game looks like it's going to be kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_13]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_10]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would play it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But guess what else I would play?
[SPEAKER_10]: What else would you play?
[SPEAKER_04]: Luminous.
[SPEAKER_13]: Luminous is a good game.
[SPEAKER_13]: I would play that too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Luminous is coming to Windows.
[SPEAKER_13]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_13]: Is it going to have Shinen?
[SPEAKER_04]: It better.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it better have Heavenly Star and it better have everything else that's awesome about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yeah, it's going to be on Windows.
[SPEAKER_04]: So isn't that cool?
[SPEAKER_13]: That's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: Although, then again, if you think about it, Luminous has been whored on every other thing out there, including my cell phone, so this does kind of make sense.
[SPEAKER_04]: I need Luminous for my iPhone.
[SPEAKER_04]: Give me Luminous on my iPhone, I'll be happy.
[SPEAKER_13]: Keep on dreaming.
[SPEAKER_13]: Now, you know what would be cool is a version of Luminous on your iPhone that uses the songs from your iPhone.
[SPEAKER_13]: That would be cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_11]: Something not so cool is apparently R-Type Command, which is better known as
[SPEAKER_11]: R-Type Tactics
[SPEAKER_11]: It's being put out by Atlas, and I believe, if I remember correctly, it says, the game requires, or it says, excuse the lightning-fast reflexes needed to avoid enemy fire, instead offering a turn-based, hex-based strategic gameplay.
[SPEAKER_11]: You will not just control one ship, but a fleet of ships.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: It sounds stupid to me.
[SPEAKER_11]: If it's tactics, it sucks.
[SPEAKER_11]: Awesome!
[SPEAKER_11]: If by awesome you mean not at all, then yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, yeah, not a game I'm very interested in checking out.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, our type is cool and all, but it's not that cool, let's face it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Skype line, open for business, www.orangeloungeradio.com, click on interact with us for all the details.
[SPEAKER_13]: Our Skype name is Orange Lounge Radio, and our telephone number, 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know how long we've been doing Skype?
[SPEAKER_13]: A long time.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think we are actually like one of the first shows ever that use Skype.
[SPEAKER_13]: Maybe the first, I don't know if we can stake that claim, but it might be worth a shot.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's go to the phones!
[SPEAKER_13]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio, who's this?
[SPEAKER_13]: This is Jason.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hello!
[SPEAKER_02]: The awesome, the awesome, the Jason, or something like that.
[SPEAKER_13]: The ex-awesome Jason, ex-awesome V, what's up?
[SPEAKER_02]: I was kind of curious, has anybody ever played Marble Mania on the Wii?
[SPEAKER_13]: Marble Mania on the Wii?
[SPEAKER_13]: Marble?
[SPEAKER_13]: Kororimpa Marble Mania, or Marvel?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, Kororimpa Marble Mania.
[SPEAKER_13]: I have played Kororimpa, and my old roommate, known as Extifer on this program, was obsessed with that game for a little while, for like a week.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I played it too.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was a very, very cute and very interesting game.
[SPEAKER_02]: My old roommate from Arizona came up here, what, two weekends ago, I believe.
[SPEAKER_02]: And this is one of the games that he owned, and I had never even heard of it before.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's, to me, you know, I don't know how...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_13]: and it made this little p-p-p-p noise and it was like really, really funny in a five-year-old kind of way.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I never actually played with it, so I used the more mission-targeted ones.
[SPEAKER_13]: Check it out, it's hilarious.
[SPEAKER_13]: And yes, it was a Konami game, and they also did, you know, obviously DDR and Dewey's Adventure and all this other stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: You don't say.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, they came out around the same time as Wing Island as well, and they were both kind of very under-the-radar and kind of average games,
[SPEAKER_11]: I thought it was kind of neat though because you could play two players on one controller if you had one person use the nunchuck and the other person use the remote.
[SPEAKER_11]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well then, three cheers for Kurarimpa from our studly Jason.
[SPEAKER_13]: What else have you been playing lately?
[SPEAKER_02]: I have been playing Super Paper Mario, which is immensely better than Paper Mario.
[SPEAKER_02]: I never played Thousand Year Door, but Super Paper Mario is actually pretty addicting.
[SPEAKER_13]: You sound pretty in love with your Wii right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: If it's not 360, which in this week it hasn't been so much, I go between the two.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was marching through Resident Evil 4, which I still haven't beaten.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, Resident Evil...
[SPEAKER_02]: Much like I revealed the I don't play Zeldas very often and everybody called me a blasphemer, I know, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've played Resident Evil 2 a couple times, but all of these kind of stopped not too terribly far into it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Code Veronica was the one game that I got, I think, about halfway through with, but I just kind of stopped playing it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Resident Evil 4, with the Wii controls...
[SPEAKER_02]: Big exception.
[SPEAKER_02]: That made that game so unbelievably fun.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, I haven't played Resident Evil 4 on the Wii yet, but honestly, I thought it was great on the GameCube.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, like, the Wii would just add even more to it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Widescreen and motion controls sounds hot.
[SPEAKER_02]: Widescreen, free aim pointing, that's the best part of it, is that you have the full screen to aim with the remote.
[SPEAKER_02]: Makes it the best, makes...
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, it's great.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's so fun to control.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's so fun to play.
[SPEAKER_13]: Sounds hot.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right, Jason, we've got to let you go to get some more calls, but any other thoughts from our listeners?
[SPEAKER_02]: I own Metroid Prime Corruption, and I haven't even opened it and played it yet.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, my God, that game is great.
[SPEAKER_13]: You need to do that now.
[SPEAKER_13]: I know, but I have so many things I want to play.
[SPEAKER_13]: Tonight, Jason, tonight, you are to open that game tonight and play.
[SPEAKER_13]: You must.
[SPEAKER_13]: Don't tell me no.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know you can't tell me no.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm cute.
[SPEAKER_13]: This is true.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right, Jason, and say hi to Rye for us.
[SPEAKER_13]: Will do.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right, bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_13]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_13]: Our lovely webmaster, Jason, VXJason, X, awesome, X, V, sex, V, Jason, calling in.
[SPEAKER_13]: 1-877-GAME-OLR, or we could just take this call.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yo, what's up?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's Ranma.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ranny, what's up?
[SPEAKER_09]: Remember a few weeks ago you talked about the movie Press Start?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes, wasn't that that one that looked like this horrible, not even a B-movie, but a C-movie production?
[SPEAKER_13]: But not that that's necessarily a bad thing, done by total hardcore nerds.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was fucking awesome!
[SPEAKER_13]: Did you see it?
[SPEAKER_13]: Was it great?
[SPEAKER_09]: My roommate ordered it and we watched it last night.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh my god, it was great!
[SPEAKER_13]: Now, without ruining it too much, tell us something that was really funny about it.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just the homages and the parodies and the respects they gave to old school gaming.
[SPEAKER_09]: The plot was very Final Fantasy-ish, the opening was Paperboy, and well, it went on from there.
[SPEAKER_13]: Nudity Nearly Naked Chick
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, well, that's right.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's close to nudity.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's partial nudity.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: Then we'll have to put that on our Christmas list to check out that movie.
[SPEAKER_13]: Anything that you've been playing this week?
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've been playing Phantom Hourglass, and thanks to Jamie, I've been playing R.O.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, dear.
[SPEAKER_13]: Watch out.
[SPEAKER_13]: The cancer is spreading.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's not bad.
[SPEAKER_09]: Plus, I fired up Age of Mythology.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've been playing that again.
[SPEAKER_13]: Rob, how come you're not on American Idol?
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_13]: Horrible.
[SPEAKER_13]: But I do, I mean, even though that's the end of it, I can do without.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think it's extremely flattering that people actually took the time to create something related to Orange Lounge Radio and some of our in-jokes.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's incredibly flattering.
[SPEAKER_13]: So thank you to everybody who was involved.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because I knew, like, probably like six different people contributed, stepfiles, backgrounds.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, it was a group project.
[SPEAKER_13]: So well done to all.
[SPEAKER_09]: Definitely.
[SPEAKER_09]: And after playing it, I suggested to DT we need to do something new.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, then you'll have to get hard at work on OL Revolution Second Mix Plus.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_09]: Not dancing.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, a new game.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: I suggested Orange Lounge the Revolution, the fighting game.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, wait.
[SPEAKER_13]: What about  A new game, right?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_13]: There was OLR versus AGI, wasn't there, at some point?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, before we get to that, we've got to have the first game, which would have to be Orange Lounge to Fighter.
[SPEAKER_13]: I see.
[SPEAKER_09]: Then AGI to Fighter, then the Versus match.
[SPEAKER_13]: I see, I see.
[SPEAKER_13]: So we will build to the Versus game.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's good.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, you guys get to work on that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Any last thoughts for the Callers, Ranma, before we let you go?
[SPEAKER_09]: I think we'd start this after the holidays, you know, when everybody's like, oh, let's make a Fighter.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's when I'm going to finally get around to redoing the website into something viewable.
[SPEAKER_13]: We'll be around the holidays.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Take care, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_13]: Love you guys.
[SPEAKER_13]: Later.
[SPEAKER_13]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_13]: If you'd like to give us a call, 1-877-GAME-OLR or username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: All one word smooshed together.
[SPEAKER_13]: No spaces, no dashes, nothing.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: TheRobD says, good luck with the AG side, I'm one of the few fighting fans.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I guess AGI's been on a bit of like, kind of like a little bit of a hiatus in the past few weeks, and I think that's because Scott's been going on the road, doing like a reality show type thing with these guys who are like a Counter-Strike team, I think it was.
[SPEAKER_13]: I watched the pilot that he had posted, and it wasn't bad.
[SPEAKER_11]: Is it because his writers went on strike?
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_11]: I saw that bus, I'm like, oh my god, there's a Counter-Strike bus at that fucking next level place.
[SPEAKER_13]: Now we have a reason to have the OLR fighting game, because someone needs to punch Scott in the face for not calling us when... Well, obviously it was in Loki's backyard.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was there, I went to see a movie, I'm like, god, there's a Counter-Strike bus here?
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm like, why would they... Well, because it went to this land center next level or something.
[SPEAKER_11]: Haven't we all been there?
[SPEAKER_11]: I have a customer that hates...
[SPEAKER_11]: They're competing LAN centers or whatever, and they absolutely hate them, and they talk crap about them all day long.
[SPEAKER_11]: But, you know, so I saw them, like, why is there anyone here?
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, seriously, it's Eldorado Hills.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, like, does anyone actually play LAN games here?
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, well, there you have it.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right, well, we're going to go back to the phones, and we'll take another call, and then we're going to get into some last-minute stories.
[SPEAKER_03]: Be someone awesome.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hello, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_13]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_13]: Hi Legend of Zaku, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_03]: I said awesome!
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, not much, just chilling on this weekend, coming, basically just coming back from the tournament and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_06]: What tournament was it this time?
[SPEAKER_06]: It was one out in Jersey.
[SPEAKER_06]: You heard of this arcade called Fun and Games, which is closing down for five months to relocate nearby.
[SPEAKER_06]: So they were just having a whole thing, shitloads of tournaments yesterday.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, the only arcade I've been to in Jersey is that eight on the break, which is pretty well known, I guess.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: But besides that, I'm just, you know, just gloating over the fact that, you know, a game like Mario Galaxy can, you know, can be as evocative.
[SPEAKER_13]: Now, last week you were so freaking excited.
[SPEAKER_13]: Like, you had so much energy last week when you called in.
[SPEAKER_06]: The thing is that it's like Mario, it basically plays like Mario 64.
[SPEAKER_06]: The whole thing plays like it, but with, you know, most controlled games.
[SPEAKER_06]: It plays, it's motion, you know, it's basically Mario 64 motion controls and spikier graphics.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, you know, I mean, when you play Mario 64, I mean, you get that feeling of just, you know, that new, innovative, that new innovative, you know, gameplay where you just, you know, die instantly and you have life.
[SPEAKER_06]: Whereas this one, I don't know, I guess it kind of...
[SPEAKER_13]: Here's what it boils down to.
[SPEAKER_13]: Here's what it boils down to, Zaku, is that did you have fun?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because if you have fun playing it, then it's good.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just gotta give it a little bit more time since I only played it in the Nintendo World launch last week.
[SPEAKER_13]: Then again, I haven't picked up the full game myself yet.
[SPEAKER_13]: I tried to go to Toys R Us this week to pick up the game because they're doing that whole $25 gift card thing.
[SPEAKER_13]: And once you know it, they didn't get the game the day it came out.
[SPEAKER_13]: There was some shipping delay.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: Probably some frickin' truck full of Super Mario Galaxies tipped over on the freeway or some shit.
[SPEAKER_13]: So I didn't buy it.
[SPEAKER_13]: But we did that preview last week and I was lucky enough to get to play it for the 40 minutes.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: I enjoyed it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would get a week for, you know, I would just
[SPEAKER_06]: I would seriously get a Wii if there was, you know, more in terms of a little bit more hardcore games.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know they're trying to stick to the, you know, trying to stay on the course of the whole casual thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, I already know Metroid and, you know, whatnot.
[SPEAKER_06]: But stuff like, I don't know, just gotta make good use of the motion controls.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, and especially the online stuff, that's pretty much lacking.
[SPEAKER_06]: If they want to compete, you know, against Microsoft and Sony.
[SPEAKER_13]: But Brawl's gonna be sexy.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know, I hear.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's going to be the new game for anime conventions.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, Lordy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, you're going to see a whole bunch of those Otaku folks just duking it out with the motion controls and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's going to be the new tournament game in February.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right, Zaku, any other thoughts for our listeners before we take some more calls?
[SPEAKER_06]: Just got to love the hypocrisy of people banning Mass Effect one day and unbanning it the other.
[SPEAKER_06]: Talking to you, C4.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Rock on, Zaku!
[SPEAKER_13]: Mass Effect was... Oh, it's too much talking, though, right?
[SPEAKER_13]: It's seriously 25 minutes to get into some action.
[SPEAKER_13]: So it's like listening to the Skype segment of this program, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: It's not necessarily like that.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's just, you know, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_11]: We got to set up the story, blah, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's funny, though, because, like, you pick your backstory and stuff, and it's just, it's really... But there's lesbian sex.
[SPEAKER_11]: And the way... You get the name of your character, but they all call you by your last name because you can't change that.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, we're getting another call, sir.
[SPEAKER_11]: We got to get to it.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right, hi, you're on Orange Lost Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_05]: This is Brad from PodCulture.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes?
[SPEAKER_05]: Picked that up yesterday, and let me tell you, it's the most fun I've had in the game in a long time.
[SPEAKER_13]: And that's what a lot of the reviews are saying.
[SPEAKER_13]: Did you hear this week?
[SPEAKER_13]: Mario Galaxy is now the official number one rated game ever on that...
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know if it's Metacritic or one of those other game rankings.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's what it is.
[SPEAKER_13]: GameRankings.com has surpassed Ocarina of Time as the number one game.
[SPEAKER_13]: Now granted, one negative review will fuck that all up at this point.
[SPEAKER_13]: But right now it is the number one game of all time.
[SPEAKER_13]: Which actually kind of surprised me because I thought generally Bioshock was getting better reviews this year.
[SPEAKER_13]: But go fig.
[SPEAKER_05]: People love their Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_05]: I haven't played Bioshock yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't judge on that.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's the first Wii game I've seen where the controls haven't felt tacked on.
[SPEAKER_13]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because this was the game, and I think a lot of people have kind of described it this way, this was the game that the Wii was kind of made for.
[SPEAKER_13]: Like, this was Miyamoto's big idea, like, here's how I want to do the next Mario game, and they're like, okay, Miyamoto, you're so fucking awesome, we'll build a console around it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is, it's really cool, because it just feels natural in playing it, and it still, it was...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: When you're in one of the hidden levels and you have to pick up the notes, it plays the little Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_05]: scene.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, that's right.
[SPEAKER_13]: I remember that.
[SPEAKER_13]: That was cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: We saw that in one of the levels we played.
[SPEAKER_13]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_13]: Anything else you've been playing lately besides Mario Galaxy?
[SPEAKER_05]: Nah, too busy getting stuff ready for my girlfriend's trip to the hospital.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_13]: Sorry to hear that.
[SPEAKER_13]: I hope everything's okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: Just...
[SPEAKER_13]: We'll have her in our thoughts.
[SPEAKER_05]: And some plumbing removed.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, we'll have her in our thoughts and hope everything is well.
[SPEAKER_13]: And you'll have to bring her a DS or some games to cheer her up.
[SPEAKER_13]: Or maybe some Doctor Who DVDs.
[SPEAKER_05]: We picked up Harvest Moon for her.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Picked up Harvest Moon for her Game Boy Advance.
[SPEAKER_13]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_13]: That will keep a person occupied for a long-ass time to finally get anything accomplished in that game.
[SPEAKER_13]: It'll be great.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just got a call in and say that Super Mario is probably the...
[SPEAKER_05]: Most fun in a long time on the game You think it's going to be game of the year?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's got a broader appeal than some of the other games that have been rating real high Like Battleshock won't appeal to everybody Or Halo 3 won't appeal to everybody But Mario Galaxy has more of a wider appeal, I think
[SPEAKER_13]: That's a dang good point.
[SPEAKER_13]: You're right.
[SPEAKER_13]: A lot of the games that are kind of leading the race for Game of the Year right now may not have that same family-friendly, quote-unquote, appeal that Mario Galaxy has and that is so important during the Christmastime rush.
[SPEAKER_13]: Very good point.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, Brad, thank you so much for calling in as always.
[SPEAKER_13]: We'd love to hear from you and hope everything is okay for you this holiday season.
[SPEAKER_13]: All righty?
[SPEAKER_13]: All righty, guys.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_13]: Later on.
[SPEAKER_13]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_13]: Very good point there.
[SPEAKER_13]: Super Mario Galaxy may not be the game of the year for the hardcore gamer, but certainly a broad game.
[SPEAKER_13]: Of course, we will be doing a grand Christmas show this year, just like we did last year, or I should say end of the year show.
[SPEAKER_13]: More details on that throughout the month of December.
[SPEAKER_13]: We have more calls.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, what's up, guys?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's Robby.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's been a while.
[SPEAKER_13]: Wow, it has been a while.
[SPEAKER_13]: How are you, Rob?
[SPEAKER_08]: Not too bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've mostly been working on Sunday's closing, so...
[SPEAKER_08]: I work at a bookstore, so, you know, retail gets no time off.
[SPEAKER_13]: Gotcha, yeah, especially in the next few months.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I haven't been able to listen live in a while, so it's nice to hear you guys.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes, it's nice to have you on the program, and congratulations, you guys have got an icon as well on the Marketplace this week, I understand.
[SPEAKER_08]: That is true.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now we actually need to put out a show.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes, and your icon is very nice looking, too.
[SPEAKER_13]: I was very impressed.
[SPEAKER_08]: Funny story about that, actually.
[SPEAKER_08]: We thought about just toning down our original iTunes artwork, but we figured that wouldn't be good enough for Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_08]: Right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, I, uh, I went to one of the all-games chatters, DC Nate, uh, awesome guy, uh, and we talked a little bit about, came up with an idea for the clock and everything, and, uh, prepared all of that in, I think, four hours, because that was how much time we had left before, uh, the deadline came through.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, we had to get that stuff in fast, I remember that, because, like, it was... Yeah, because Black, Bobby was, uh, Bobby was very firm about the deadlines, and, uh,
[SPEAKER_08]: He gave us warning and gave us some time, but it was a very hurried process.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm actually going to show the chat some of the rejects for the icon, because we actually had a couple icons that were almost there, but they were rejected.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm going to actually paste some of those in chat.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm going to do the one I did.
[SPEAKER_13]: The one I did has the three faces, and I don't know how...
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_13]: What were you saying?
[SPEAKER_13]: What did you call in to talk about before we derailed the call?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, my first question, well, actually my only question to you guys is, now that most of the games have come out for this holiday season, with the exception of Mass Effect, which I actually, that's still due to be released before the holidays, before Christmas, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Hasn't been delayed, there isn't anything new that I haven't heard about.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, it comes out in a couple days.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yep, almost here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: Where would you rank this holiday season compared to other big ones in video game history as far as quality of games go?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'd say it's pretty far up there, but I think 1998 with Ocarina of Time and Metal Gear Solid was probably better, and 2001 with Halo, Melee, and what was the other big one?
[SPEAKER_08]: GTA 3 was probably better.
[SPEAKER_08]: A big complaint about this year's games is that to me there's a lack of games that can be truly considered timeless, like a Metal Gear Solid where people will be coming back to it years later and playing it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe Galaxy falls into that mold, but
[SPEAKER_08]: Bioshock is a first-person shooter.
[SPEAKER_08]: First-person shooters get tossed to the wayside like yesterday's dinner.
[SPEAKER_13]: Especially with no multiplayer to keep people coming back.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, I gotta say, here's the thing about this year's batch of games that I think does make it better than years past, and that is the fact that there's no new consoles this year.
[SPEAKER_13]: There's nothing in the realm of new consoles.
[SPEAKER_13]: There's console redesigns, kind of, but there's no new consoles.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's really the first year we don't even have a new handheld system.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's wide open.
[SPEAKER_13]: as to what's out there.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I think, therefore, the consoles that are out in the marketplace have had a little more time to mature.
[SPEAKER_13]: Unfortunately, I don't feel PlayStation 3 has used the time to its best of ability, which kind of makes me think, honestly, PlayStation 3 should have just come out this year.
Probably.
[SPEAKER_13]: But who am I?
[SPEAKER_13]: I can see why maybe they didn't do it, because they want to be out there or whatever.
[SPEAKER_13]: But
[SPEAKER_13]: All that aside, you kind of see that now, okay, it's not so much the launch games, where you're getting into the second generation of games, and you could say even with 360, perhaps even starting to get into the third generation of games for the system.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think next year's going to be even better, honestly.
[SPEAKER_13]: And then probably the year after that is when you're going to start seeing stuff about the Xbox 720 or their next project, so you'll kind of start to die down.
[SPEAKER_13]: But I do think kind of like next year will be even better than this year for that reason, that the consoles will have had a little time to age.
[SPEAKER_13]: and I think that's the thing about, I think you cited 98.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think that was the time when like, you know, 64 had already been out.
[SPEAKER_13]: PlayStation had already been out a couple years.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think those, you know, systems kind of had their time to really get, you know, some of their best stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: Like a fine wine, Jason says in chat.
[SPEAKER_08]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, that's what I was thinking.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, it'll be interesting to see how the PS3 brings it next year because Metal Gear Solid 4, hopefully, will be out by next holidays.
[SPEAKER_08]: And, uh,
[SPEAKER_08]: 360 really brought it to the table this year.
[SPEAKER_08]: PlayStation 3 brought a few things with Heavenly Sword and...
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, a couple of the other ports that came over from the 360.
[SPEAKER_13]: And hopefully next year they can just really keep it moving.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hopefully the developers don't jump ship because home looks really exciting.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think Final Fantasy XIII is going to have people drooling.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think there's a lot to look forward to from PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_13]: But again, it's been a very slow start.
[SPEAKER_13]: But who knows?
[SPEAKER_08]: That's a real question.
[SPEAKER_08]: Can developers get used to the PS3 and use it to its full potential, which...
[SPEAKER_08]: Most people seem to agree that it does have a lot of potential.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just really hard to develop for with the 8 trillion cores it has on there.
[SPEAKER_13]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm getting a message from DMM that says, 21 Xbox Live users have the OLR pick, according to whatever he found.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's amazing.
[SPEAKER_13]: I would be thrilled if two people were using it, honestly, myself and Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, Bobby is winning by...
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow, Bobby.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow, that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bobby has 381.
[SPEAKER_08]: Evil Avatar has 487.
[SPEAKER_13]: Now, see, Evil Avatar has a huge community behind them, so I believe that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, you guys have 22.
[SPEAKER_13]: Rock!
[SPEAKER_13]: Bobby has, what, like 15 times the number of people using his picture than we do?
[SPEAKER_08]: AGI has 47.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, no, they have 43.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have 8.
[SPEAKER_08]: Woo-hoo!
[SPEAKER_08]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_08]: Go meet in the Matrix.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, we need to...
[SPEAKER_13]: We need to get the shows back.
[SPEAKER_08]: Damn it.
[SPEAKER_08]: We need people.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, people using Bobby pictures.
[SPEAKER_13]: He doesn't need it.
[SPEAKER_13]: You need to switch over to the OLR pic or a T-Dig pic.
[SPEAKER_13]: Bobby don't need the numbers no more.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think it's great.
[SPEAKER_08]: He's getting a lot of support.
[SPEAKER_08]: Kudos to him.
[SPEAKER_08]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it's great people are using him at all.
[SPEAKER_13]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right, well, Rob D., we've given you way more time than the other callers.
[SPEAKER_13]: I've got to let you go, but any quick final thoughts for our listeners?
[SPEAKER_08]: Game on.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll try to get T-Dig back, but unfortunately I can't make promises since I
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to work practically full-time in school, half-time, but you guys know the excuses.
[SPEAKER_08]: You guys have been through that before, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_13]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_08]: See you later.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right, take care, Rob.
[SPEAKER_13]: Good luck to you.
[SPEAKER_13]: T-Dig was a good show, and he had a whole other guy that edited it, too.
[SPEAKER_13]: Lots of work that went into that show.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right, maybe one more call.
[SPEAKER_13]: We've got time for one more call, then we'll jump into the afterbirth in our Rock Band post-show.
[SPEAKER_13]: Actually, I don't see the line ringing, but let's do some quick last-minute stories.
[SPEAKER_13]: Jamie, you have anything for last-minute stories?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm out of Mountain Dew.
[SPEAKER_13]: Almost.
[SPEAKER_13]: I see a little more Mountain Dew in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a little left.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, all right, Loki.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was going to say Avatar, The Last Airbender, The Burning Earth.
[SPEAKER_11]: You can get all 1,000 achievement points in two minutes in that game by just backing up into a corner and hitting a button over and over and over again.
[SPEAKER_13]: Amazing.
[SPEAKER_13]: We got another call.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hi, you're on Orange House Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_13]: This is DMN.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hello, DMN.
[SPEAKER_13]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_10]: I have a challenge for the three of you.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, shit.
[SPEAKER_10]: No!
[SPEAKER_10]: This isn't anything stupid.
[SPEAKER_10]: I promise.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know about that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I challenge the three of you to convince myself and everyone listening that Dance Dance Revolution is not dead.
[SPEAKER_10]: Go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is what?
[SPEAKER_13]: Dance Dance Revolution is not dead.
[SPEAKER_04]: I saw people playing it the other day at the pizza place.
[SPEAKER_13]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'll agree with you because I picked up Supernova 2
[SPEAKER_10]: and it's arguably the worst musically Dance Dance Revolution game I've ever played in my life.
[SPEAKER_13]: Interesting because not a lot of people necessarily felt the same way.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't think necessarily it was received that poorly by the community but I don't think people make such a big deal out of these releases anymore.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think Universe 2 is coming out soon and it's kind of being met with this big hmm.
[SPEAKER_13]: And this is it.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's
[SPEAKER_13]: DDR is back and it's alive again!
[SPEAKER_13]: And the reason why I always praised the Ultramix series on this show previously is that like three quarters of the innovative shit you saw on the console games were all coming from the Xbox series.
[SPEAKER_13]: Things like quest mode, things like song lists reaching out into independent music scene, you know, all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: That was all innovated by the Xbox team.
[SPEAKER_13]: And that's why that...
[SPEAKER_13]: Those types of innovations, at least even when they fail, because not everything is done very well, like the quest mode in Universe was god-awful, but I give them props for at least trying to innovate a dead game.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, and then the other thing too is that they keep making so many damn games for it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, seriously, if anybody's to blame for killing the series, it's Konami.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's because...
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, let's see.
[SPEAKER_11]: This year alone, we had DDR Universe come out, DDR Supernova 2, DDR Hottest Party, and we're going to have DDR Universe 2 coming out.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then next year already, I can think of at least two more games that are coming out in the DDR series.
[SPEAKER_11]: One of which is the never-talked-about DDR Disney Mix, or DDR Disney Channel.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, it's crap like that.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's watering this shit down, and it's not really innovative.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's just, let's throw some more songs in there, and that's it.
[SPEAKER_11]: But, you know, they still sell very well.
[SPEAKER_11]: We always sell out of them.
[SPEAKER_11]: And, you know, if you look in the past, you know, recent, well, I don't know about the recent charts, but I know that DDR Extreme 2 was on the top of charts for a long time, or at least Supernova was.
[SPEAKER_11]: And Supernova 2's not doing bad at all.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, probably their expectations are lower, but
[SPEAKER_11]: I think a lot of it is Hottest Party Yay, use the remote nunchuck That was crap Universe 2
[SPEAKER_11]: is going to be, you know, not much more innovative.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, great.
[SPEAKER_11]: They brought freestyle mode back.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's a game where you don't have arrows.
[SPEAKER_13]: Fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_13]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, Konami, one of my favorite game companies ever.
[SPEAKER_13]: I've known people that have worked there.
[SPEAKER_13]: I have great relationships with a lot of the folks that work there.
[SPEAKER_13]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_13]: My honest, like, friendly advice to the folks at Konami, take a page from Harmonix.
[SPEAKER_13]: because look at what Harmonix did is that basically they were given the challenge of oh look Guitar Hero got taken away from you but we want to make we want to have you make kind of the same thing and they like took what essentially was kind of the same fucking game and just really ran away with it and with this rock band and kind of made something completely new out of it and this whole like you can print your band's t-shirt like this is all like crazy stuff like running away with innovative ideas I think honestly DDR
[SPEAKER_13]: might want to hire a consultant from Harmonix.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know, what do you think?
[SPEAKER_10]: I will say, you're talking about Universe, I think Musical Universe is actually one of the best DDR mixes I've ever played.
[SPEAKER_10]: It had a great variety of music, some things that were poppy that I could actually stand, because anybody who knows me, and I don't know if many people know me that personally, I do not like pop music at all.
[SPEAKER_10]: Um...
[SPEAKER_10]: Going from Slam to 8-Bit to Don't Play Nice, which is a song I actually enjoyed, was a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_13]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_13]: Universe has an excellent song list.
[SPEAKER_13]: And that's really what D.D.
[SPEAKER_13]: Abrams went on to.
[SPEAKER_10]: The standard list from Supernova 2, without unlocking anything, was just a disappointment.
[SPEAKER_10]: There was one song I was like, huh, this is awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, wait, two, because I didn't know one song and there was my gold press.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was a good song.
[SPEAKER_10]: But Rockefeller's Gang was the only song I'm like, huh, this is a good song.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, everything else didn't really stand out.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it was a bit of a disappointment.
[SPEAKER_10]: And again, I paid nothing for it, so I shouldn't complain too much.
[SPEAKER_13]: I stand by that I firmly believe that the best home mix to come out in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_13]: or Japan anywhere, anytime, and probably will always be the best DDR game that comes out on the home consoles is Ultramix 2 on the Xbox.
[SPEAKER_13]: And the reason why is because that is where...
[SPEAKER_13]: They took the most risk.
[SPEAKER_13]: They completely changed the people that did the steps to people that really knew the game of DDR inside and out.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's where they took some big risks with the song list that paid off in a huge way.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's where they added these new modes that changed the game and had that Xbox Live dancing that was kind of explored in the first Ultramix game but totally improved on with the different types of versus modes in the second game.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't think there will ever be a DDR game as good as Ultramix 2, period.
[SPEAKER_13]: that makes me feel as excited about DDR as I did when I first played Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyway, we've got to let you go.
[SPEAKER_13]: Our time's about up, but thanks for the call, DMN.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Happy Thanksgiving, guys.
[SPEAKER_10]: Were we able to meet your challenge somehow?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, it was a good discussion, and I actually wanted to call in and not be a bumbling idiot for once.
[SPEAKER_13]: We appreciate that.
[SPEAKER_04]: We like it when you're not a bumbling idiot.
[SPEAKER_13]: If they want to hear you being a bumbling idiot, they should just download OL Revolution.
[SPEAKER_10]: They listen to Jamie saying your name over and over in a song.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's nothing wrong with that.
[SPEAKER_13]: But you and Drunk Drunk Revolution, seriously, WTF.
[SPEAKER_13]: OMG, WTF, BBQ, LOL.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, bye DMN.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, that's it for the Skype line today.
[SPEAKER_13]: We gotta close it up.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_11]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, this is for anyone who is waiting for Unreal Tournament 3 on Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: They actually said that it works already and has worked since last spring.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that they've actually put on hold any further development on it because of getting it to work on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_13]: But what about that whole, like, it's supposed to be out on PlayStation 3 first for like a week though, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: It is going to be out on Windows and PlayStation 3 first.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then they're taking Christmas off and are going to start working on the Xbox 360 version so that they can get it to work with mods and everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's where the delay is, but it works, and it has been working, and it could be done by now, but no.
[SPEAKER_13]: But there's that deal.
[SPEAKER_04]: But there's the deal, and there's also the fact that they're trying to get it to work on live.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, Loki.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyways, Microsoft is doing an offer, which is less cool now because originally we thought it was for everybody, but apparently if you own an original Xbox and you have a paid Xbox Live account...
[SPEAKER_11]: And if you purchase an Xbox 360 between November 21st and December 21st of this year, you'll be entitled to a free copy of Halo 3.
[SPEAKER_11]: So you fill out some sort of form and you get a copy mailed to you.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hooray!
[SPEAKER_11]: Postal 3.
[SPEAKER_11]: Apparently Uebol is in the game and you can kill him.
[SPEAKER_11]: In the game.
[SPEAKER_11]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: and then the Wii Zapper apparently there is of course some pictures that floated on the internet with some unboxing of that and there is a second configuration which also begs the question why the fuck do you actually need this then where you take the nunchuck basically out of the Wii Zapper and you just hold the Zapper with the remote in there like you would hold the remote normally so it's a piece of plastic that's completely useless
[SPEAKER_11]: Hooray!
[SPEAKER_11]: But we will soon see.
[SPEAKER_11]: Can I use the Wii Zapper on a Wii Bowl?
[SPEAKER_11]: Maybe if they put out Postal 3 on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_13]: Have you played Manhunt 2 on the Wii yet?
[SPEAKER_11]: No, I really don't care.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's just the PSP, huh?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, I was all excited to get it originally when it was adult only.
[SPEAKER_11]: And now I'm just like, eh, whatever.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's just not as controversial anymore.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'll play No More Heroes.
[SPEAKER_11]: That'll be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: But, you know, Manhunt 2, I don't care.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_13]: I want pie.
[SPEAKER_13]: Ooh, my final thought is I'm going to steal DarkSakura's iPhone.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, no, it's mine.
[SPEAKER_13]: But I also want pie.
[SPEAKER_13]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_13]: My final thought is I need to take some more extra strength Tylenol.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yay, sorry to hear about your headache.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, that's it for this week.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, have a good two weeks off.
[SPEAKER_13]: Have fun in Alabama.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe I will call you on Sunday.
[SPEAKER_13]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think originally we were going to take a week off, but I haven't heard that chatter, so I don't think we are going to do that.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think we are going to be live the next two weeks.
[SPEAKER_13]: So we'll be here doing our thang.
[SPEAKER_04]: It could be possible I'll be here the week after, but I might just be dead.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, no, if you need the night off, go for it.
[SPEAKER_13]: We'll find some of our local favorites to help fill in, and possibly the wheat zapper challenge happens.
[SPEAKER_04]: But if any of our, I'm actually going to be hopefully meeting up with a friend of mine back there who I met again through DDR, who I met while I lived out here, and then, so I think it's kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_13]: So.
[SPEAKER_13]: Puppies already volunteering to fill in for a night when you're not here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, puppy.
[SPEAKER_04]: And send me some chocolate.
[SPEAKER_13]: Will you allow puppy to sit in the fluffy blue chair?
[SPEAKER_13]: Puppy can sit in the fluffy blue chair.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: It used to be the big green chair, the big green monster chair, but now it's the fluffy blue chair.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's lightweight and fluffy.
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's it, folks.
[SPEAKER_13]: We've got to play the outro and get on out of here.
[SPEAKER_13]: Thank you very much for downloading and supporting Independent Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: If you like what you hear, leave us a nice review on iTunes.
[SPEAKER_13]: Tell some friends about the show.
[SPEAKER_13]: Spread the word because we are Independent Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: Now you can change your icon to the OLR icon or just some independent radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: Remember, we thrive on word of mouth, so we really appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Until next week, I'm Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's Loki.
[SPEAKER_13]: And in three weeks, you'll be DarkSakura again.
[SPEAKER_13]: We are Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_01]: For more information on our live and podcast programs, visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com See you next week!