Make it, if I have this, I'm sure Make it, it's a pure world, but I'm fine I don't care, so I'll send you a ticket later Take you, to the five-star sky, someday Take you, to the five-star sky, someday
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_18]: The following live program is a special presentation of Orange Lounge Radio.
Tonight on Orange Lounge Radio, live, it is episode number 150!
[SPEAKER_05]: Which is a landmark number.
[SPEAKER_05]: And to celebrate this landmark occasion, we're going to do the same old crap we always do.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to sit on here and pretend to do a show about DDR and never talk about it throughout the whole three hours.
[SPEAKER_06]: And we'll find out what the difference between white bread and rustic white bread actually is.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Orange Lounge Radio bringing you the news you really want to know.
[SPEAKER_05]: about games that we're supposed to be talking about, but we're not.
[SPEAKER_05]: For the past 150 episodes.
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: In all seriousness, we have brand new MP3s from Happy Sky for those three of you people who haven't already torrented them.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have some news on something I wanted to say.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, the lawsuit.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's more stuff about the lawsuit because we didn't get bitched at enough for talking about the lawsuit too much last week.
[SPEAKER_05]: All this and more tonight after this brief introduction.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yada, yada, yada, yada, yada, yada, yada.
[SPEAKER_12]: Orange Lounge Radio is presented in the TMI sound format.
[SPEAKER_12]: Orange Lounge Radio
Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_13]: Call me Daddy.
[SPEAKER_19]: Orange Lounge may contain adult content.
[SPEAKER_19]: Orange Lounge may contain many four-letter words.
[SPEAKER_19]: Orange Lounge may contain a scene of nudity.
[SPEAKER_19]: Orange Lounge may contain plenty of... Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_05]: Orange Lounge Radio will not contain any of that in this episode.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, isn't that special?
[SPEAKER_20]: Orange Lounge Radio Live is a fully interactive program via our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com And now, here are your hosts for Orange Lounge Radio Live, DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: We are live!
[SPEAKER_05]: And this is episode number 150 for this July the 17th, 2005.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're tuned in to Orange Lounge Radio, radio that gamers really want.
[SPEAKER_05]: And this is Orange Lounge Radio Live, your home for all the news and discussion on rhythm and music games, as well as the gamer community and the pop culture world.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're plugged in and fully interactive through our website, www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_05]: You might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_05]: Joining me, as always, are my awesome co-hosts.
[SPEAKER_05]: In this corner, the happiest bunny on the farm is Jamie Summers, also known as DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, she's not here right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: She, in true Orange Lounge Radio fashion, whenever we have like a really big show number, like a landmark show, she's off doing something else.
[SPEAKER_05]: She will be here tonight, boys and girls, she'll just be a little late, because there's a birthday in the family.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's grandma or aunt or somebody's having a birthday, so she's off there, but she'll be here around the 7 o'clock hour, so she's probably on her way right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: But we do have the one and only Tech Massa Loki!
[SPEAKER_05]: I am here.
[SPEAKER_05]: And how are you doing?
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, okay, I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know, did you go on a diet or something?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because you used to bring in the Pizza Hut every night.
[SPEAKER_06]: Pizza yesterday.
[SPEAKER_05]: And now you brought in the Togos.
[SPEAKER_06]: I had pizza yesterday.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I see.
[SPEAKER_06]: I see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, we do have the one and only, uh, Loki's fiancé with us tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_05]: So she's gonna fill in for Jamie, giving us the female perspective.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hello, I'm Jamie, I hope she's not listening.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, she's not.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, I have to know, um, what are your favorite video games?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know, Matt.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tetris?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, Tetris!
[SPEAKER_07]: I like Tetris.
[SPEAKER_06]: She also likes Zookeeper.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, and I like Zookeeper and I like Pac-Man.
[SPEAKER_05]: What do you think of DDR?
[SPEAKER_07]: It kind of looks like line dancing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because when you have the two people and there's... It kind of does, don't you think?
[SPEAKER_07]: Kind of.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kind of.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because you just have to do little heel clicking.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh yes, it's going to be a fun show tonight, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll be back after this brief introduction.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to play some MP3s from the new Happy Sky soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_05]: Happy Sky!
[SPEAKER_05]: Does that make you a Happy Sky?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, actually, I'll tell you what I think about 2DX12 style in a little bit.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: I do like this first song we're going to play.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to start it off with a remix of Thunder.
[SPEAKER_05]: A new DJ Taka song from Happy Sky.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, not the same Thunder I thought it was.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, but it's that...
[SPEAKER_05]: You know the one everybody used to play on ASL?
[SPEAKER_05]: Such a horrid song.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, they remixed it for Happy Sky.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to play that.
[SPEAKER_05]: You'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're the recognizer or you don't.
[SPEAKER_05]: Inazuma.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll be back after this.
Thank you.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_12]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: And as a homosexual, I'm going to say Happy Sky is the gayest name I've ever heard.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Super Happy American Dad's Party!
[SPEAKER_05]: In that break, we heard DJ Taco with Inazuma, which is a remix of Thunder.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I got bitched at in the chatroom because, you know, Jazz came in and was like, Nuh-uh!
[SPEAKER_05]: You did not just bash on Thunder!
[SPEAKER_05]: Nuh-uh!
[SPEAKER_05]: No, you didn't!
[SPEAKER_05]: And, um, okay, I like Thunder.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like it a lot.
[SPEAKER_05]: But let's face it, that song was horrid when 2DX8Style was that.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was that and Beauty of Silence.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I love Beauty of Silence, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: But those songs were all horrid.
[SPEAKER_05]: So...
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry, I was having trouble paying attention to those songs because Nelly here keeps trying to violate me with this stupid Ethernet cable.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, hey, hey, hey.
[SPEAKER_05]: Stop sticking that Cat5 up his pants.
[SPEAKER_07]: We've got to put that... I stuck it up Rob's butt a minute ago and he didn't even notice it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did you, Rob?
[SPEAKER_05]: Can I try and do the show here, please?
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: After that break, also in that set, Ryu with In Motion, Mr. T with Vault of Heaven, and the one more extra stage, oh my gods, Amuro vs. Killer with Mei, which means dark in Japanese.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what else it means?
[SPEAKER_06]: It means, I made the same song three times!
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what it means.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let me just run my hand up and down the piano again.
[SPEAKER_06]: Seriously, it's the same damn beat!
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I made a song with piano in it!
[SPEAKER_05]: Here, I'm going to run my hand up and down the piano.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh wait, no, that's not the part.
[SPEAKER_05]: Where's the part that has the... Here we go.
[SPEAKER_05]: See?
[SPEAKER_05]: And you know that's just going to be key presses all over the place, and people are only going to be able to beat it by putting it on random unless you're just insane at 2DX, which, you know, if that's the case, then more power to you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Me personally, I haven't really sat down and listened to all the Happy Sky MP3s.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't get the MP3s earlier in the week.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just got them last night, so I haven't had a chance to listen to all of them.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the ones I did listen to, I was kind of like...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Even with 2DX Red, I was kind of...
[SPEAKER_05]: 2DX is going the way of Guitar Freaks
[SPEAKER_06]: It was some cool song, or crappy song, I mean.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, um, so now, um, I don't know, The Killer sounds like something like a metal band.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that would have been awesome, like, you know, heavy metal guitars with the piano, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that would have been cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: But that was, what did he do?
[SPEAKER_06]: The Killer's like, I'm gonna speed the tempo up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Look, I'm done.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was it.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was my contribution.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, anyway, so that's my rant on Happy Sky.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like, you honestly wonder, yeah, we need one more extra stage song.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ugh!
[SPEAKER_06]: Fine, let's take a piece of that, piece of that, speed it up, up, done.
[SPEAKER_05]: There are a couple songs in 2DX Happy Sky I do kind of like.
[SPEAKER_05]: I liked the Thunder remix because I loved the original Thunder.
[SPEAKER_05]: Even though it was horrid, so horrid.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I liked it until she started singing.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the part that comes from Thunder.
[SPEAKER_05]: The rest of it's all different.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, yeah, that's why.
[SPEAKER_06]: That would be like having the intro part there and then also let the move breaks in there.
[SPEAKER_06]: It just doesn't fit.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's the same with that.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, remember Ultramix 2 and it had a remix of Make a Jam, which wasn't bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was actually kind of cool, the Make a Jam remix.
[SPEAKER_05]: You remember that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Somebody could remix Let Them Move and make it a good song.
[SPEAKER_05]: They really could.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just nobody wants to.
[SPEAKER_05]: or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, Let Them Move could be remixed into a good song.
[SPEAKER_05]: Please.
[SPEAKER_05]: If they could make Make a Jam a good song, Let Them Move remix for Ultramix 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: Please.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Michael Jackson can make a comeback too.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll start off tonight's show as we usually like to start off the show playing a little bit of How was your week?
[SPEAKER_06]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, how was your week?
[SPEAKER_05]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_06]: It sucks.
[SPEAKER_06]: It started off good and then it just ended up crappy.
[SPEAKER_06]: I had to go do that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Luckily, ironically enough or whatever...
[SPEAKER_06]: The air conditioning stopped working in our apartment.
[SPEAKER_06]: Luckily, we're in another house, so it doesn't really matter right now, but... No, this is the second time it's happened since we've lived there, so... That's not good.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then, um... What else?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh!
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, the dog is on this weird routine, because my mom works weird hours.
[SPEAKER_06]: She works, you know, really early in the morning.
[SPEAKER_06]: Gives up, like, four in the morning, so the dog wakes me up three times during the night.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like, once at eleven, once at three...
[SPEAKER_06]: once at 7, and then once at 10, it's just like, knock it off, and like, she'll wake you up, and you're like, okay, you want to go outside?
[SPEAKER_06]: Nope, just staring at you, just, I don't want anything, I just wanted to wake you up, it's fucking annoying, so, that sucked, and then, I don't know, really, other than that, not too much has been going on at work, it's been okay, I've been just kind of
[SPEAKER_06]: Trying to pay attention to work as much as possible and not, you know, fiddle with my PSP.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because people want me to put games on there because they outed me as saying it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh yeah, that guy knows how to put Nintendo games on your PSP.
[SPEAKER_06]: So everybody calls it, or walks up to me, are you busy?
[SPEAKER_06]: Put games on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I have to constantly do that.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, you know, it's cool, you know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's wonderful that you work for the game distributor and you're a big old pirate when it comes to things like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, seriously.
[SPEAKER_05]: There are pirates inside every company and they wonder why this stuff turns up on the internet days after release.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't pirate games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Much.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't pirate any games.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not the person that puts them on the internet.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm just the person that downloads them off the internet.
[SPEAKER_05]: And shares them with all your coworkers.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't... Okay, I share the Nintendo games with them, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: They're so small.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, Loki, are you busy?
[SPEAKER_05]: Could you come rob a bank with me?
[SPEAKER_06]: These other games that I'm testing out are just games that aren't coming out over here yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's all Japanese games on my PSP.
[SPEAKER_06]: By the way, I should say that my PSP has four commercial games on the memory card itself.
[SPEAKER_05]: Your internet penis is huge.
[SPEAKER_05]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, yeah, so that's pretty much my week.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's been just that, so...
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I forgot.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yesterday we had our bad movie night.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: It came from somewhere else, which was really retarded.
[SPEAKER_06]: All the gore and nudity scenes were all in color, but the rest of the movie was black and white.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then we started watching this movie called Hanzo the Razor or something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I highly recommend no one watches this, because I thought, okay, samurai exploitation movie or something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was made in the 70s or whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: and Hanzo's like torturing himself, you know, first.
[SPEAKER_06]: Then all of a sudden, out of nowhere, he's pouring hot water on his penis and then puts it on a Lego board and starts beating it with a stick and then starts screwing a bag of rock salt.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was like, what the hell are you watching?
[SPEAKER_06]: Why did you make me watch this?
[SPEAKER_06]: And the whole movie, I read the back, I'm like, oh my god, why are we watching this thing?
[SPEAKER_06]: So we turn that off and then we watch Attack the Gas Station, which that movie is awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, it ended on a good note.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, um,
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, Hanzo the Razor, don't watch it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Awful movie.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was my week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who made you watch that movie?
[SPEAKER_06]: My friend Jason.
[SPEAKER_06]: He brought it over, he said this movie's awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: He didn't even watch it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm like, dude.
[SPEAKER_06]: And we're like, oh, come on.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, he didn't even, like, showed it, but it was kind of blurred out, you know, out of focus.
[SPEAKER_06]: But he's just all...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: Ugly damn people in this movie, but no one wanted to watch it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Santa Claus saves the day.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have I ever made you watch Desperate Living, one of my favorite movies, John Waters?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: With the amazingly humongous black woman that's like full-frontally nude through a lot of the movie?
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, I probably would enjoy the movie just because I enjoy weird movies.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like one of my favorite movies ever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, there's another one I'm getting.
[SPEAKER_06]: I haven't paid for it yet, but it's inbred.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or is it Bloodsucking Vampire Rednecks?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's going to be coming.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you look up the...
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, let me just say there's this really ginormous person in this movie that's nude in it as well, and she must weigh like 600 pounds.
[SPEAKER_06]: I kid you not.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, you and I need to go to that Trash Film Orgy sometime.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_05]: They do this thing here in Sacramento where, you know, we all live and the show's based...
[SPEAKER_05]: They do this trash film orgy at the big artsy theater downtown and they show all these really horrid, horrid movies.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, this old friend of mine that I used to do Rocky Horror with way back in the day, she is like the trash film queen or whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I'm surfing MySpace yesterday and I see this picture and it says the trash film queen and all it is is a picture of breasts with stickers taping over it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm like, dude, that's Sarah!
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_05]: But the scary thing is, I recognized a picture of a girl from the breasts alone and nothing else.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's pretty odd.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, but those are huge-ass tits, so you can see them from... She's awesome, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyways, I just wanted... I know this is great radio, but I wanted to show you a picture of this woman that's in this movie.
[SPEAKER_06]: And this is the reason why... This movie is just so awful, but let me see here.
[SPEAKER_06]: There it is right there.
[SPEAKER_06]: She basically sits on some guy's head and it, like, kills him.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what I look like naked.
[SPEAKER_06]: See, look at that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, so can you post a link in our chatroom to that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, you're not in the chatroom, are you?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not in the chatroom.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just look it up on somethingawful.com, go under their movie reviews and look for blood-sucking vampire rednecks.
[SPEAKER_06]: and go to page 4.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love reading SomethingAwful.com's movie reviews because they're hilarious.
[SPEAKER_06]: But anyways, yeah, it's nasty.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, it's kind of like last week when I was trying to show all the videos on air.
[SPEAKER_05]: You trying to go in and show people the...
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it's like if you were to take some really nasty biker woman at an eye patch and her leg is like the size of an elephant, that would probably be an accurate description.
[SPEAKER_06]: Seriously, that's... Anyways, I'm done.
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't lie, you know you think she's hot.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh yeah, I want to do her folds.
[SPEAKER_05]: Speaking of videos that we play.
[SPEAKER_01]: Common behavior years ago can now be sexual harassment.
[SPEAKER_07]: Smells like vagina in here.
[SPEAKER_07]: My vagina?
[SPEAKER_07]: Smells like fresh vagina in here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Are you talking about my vagina?
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nellie, how was your week?
[SPEAKER_05]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_07]: It was the same as Matt's, except I watched that video and that was pretty funny, and I showed it to my co-worker, and she told me a funny story about how she had sex with this guy, but not really, where he kind of slipped and he entered in between her butt cheeks.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know we have children that listen to this program.
[SPEAKER_05]: Keep talking.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what my week was like.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was like talking about funny shit like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it was wonderful, and today was great because I got laid.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ironically enough, so did I. No.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bugged just joined us.
[SPEAKER_05]: My old friend Bugged, who's known me longer than most people.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yes, and I feel like I don't know you anymore.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why is that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because these freaks.
[SPEAKER_05]: The chatroom is telling me I'm not actually gay because of the fact that I was able to ID a woman based on her tits.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're saying I'm not gay.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, no, no, that has nothing to do with... Bugged has known I was gay longer than I have, actually.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's true!
[SPEAKER_23]: Alright, anyway.
[SPEAKER_23]: How was your week?
[SPEAKER_23]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_23]: Not as exciting as anyone else's.
[SPEAKER_23]: Did you get laid today?
[SPEAKER_23]: No.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's too bad.
[SPEAKER_23]: We've got to make them blush, not us.
[SPEAKER_07]: What was Rob like when he was just this little whore?
What?
[SPEAKER_05]: I was never a little whore.
[SPEAKER_05]: You must specify it, Dan.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm a younger whore.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't lose my virginity until I was like 20 years old, but you have to remember I had all these issues going on at the same time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Andrea issues?
[SPEAKER_05]: Talk about my ex-girlfriend on the air.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're famous on the internet.
[SPEAKER_05]: She might listen for God's sake.
[SPEAKER_23]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just looking at Loki's screen.
[SPEAKER_05]: Stop.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're horrible.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's why you keep me around.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, now I lost my train of thought.
[SPEAKER_05]: Forget it.
[SPEAKER_23]: Now my week wasn't exciting to anyone else.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know what I was going to say.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you're still 20, 21, and you haven't lost your virginity, it might just be because you're gay.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm totally kidding you guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I had all those issues.
[SPEAKER_05]: Stop it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Was that your problem, Matt?
[SPEAKER_06]: My plate caused the deaths of thousands of people.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's a great story.
[SPEAKER_05]: You should tell it on air.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's why it took so long.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I was like, do I like pussy?
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, no, I don't.
[SPEAKER_05]: I kind of like guys.
[SPEAKER_07]: Everybody likes pussy.
[SPEAKER_05]: My hands smell like tuna.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anything else you want to say about your week and your day?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's fucking hot.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is the AC on in here?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_23]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_23]: You live here.
[SPEAKER_23]: Your TV's running.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, that's true.
[SPEAKER_05]: And nobody's out there watching it?
[SPEAKER_23]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, that was my week and my day.
[SPEAKER_05]: As of like an hour and a half ago, I just purchased a new HDTV, a 30-inch HDTV, because I wanted it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Must be nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have some extra money right now because this is a three-paycheck month.
[SPEAKER_05]: And so I was deciding, do I want to get a PowerBook or do I want to get...
[SPEAKER_05]: and a new TV.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I was going to get the PowerBook, but then my friend said, oh, it'll take six weeks to get here.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm like, fuck that, because I'm going to the East Coast, because I'm going to get the discount, because my friend works for Apple.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it would take six weeks to get there.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I said, well, fuck that, because I'm going to Pennsylvania in two weeks, and that's what I want my laptop for.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'm just going to use my parents' shitty old video.
[SPEAKER_05]: How is this whole nexus with Pennsylvania?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just this void where I get sucked into.
[SPEAKER_23]: My roommates just moved there.
[SPEAKER_23]: My new roommates are from there.
[SPEAKER_23]: You're bouncing through there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I know, it's weird I feel sorry for everyone in Pennsylvania So anyway, I really want to get a PowerBook But it'll wait until the end of the year Because I also really want a TV So I'm getting the TV first Instinct gratification But get this, the TV, it's not bad I got it at Costco, only $600 No shit Yeah, not bad for HDTV The picture's pretty good You should see a DVD on that thing Pop in the Xbox, put it on widescreen Looks hot Mom's looking for a new TV But I have to set up her TiVo tomorrow
[SPEAKER_23]: I have to set up her new TiVo tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can join our chat room, www.orangeloungeradio.com Or not.
[SPEAKER_05]: On chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, join it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a good time.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I've got some comments here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Somebody is saying, somebody is shaking their fist at me because they're 28 and still a virgin.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dude, it's all right.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: Let me give you the truth about sex, okay?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, this should be good.
[SPEAKER_05]: Once you have it, you always want it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is it a boy or a girl?
[SPEAKER_05]: Seriously, don't lose a boy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, I'll tell you why you're still a virgin.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because you're in that chat room.
[SPEAKER_05]: Stop it!
[SPEAKER_05]: He's a nice guy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Stop it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry if you're nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, hey, our chat room gets people laid.
[SPEAKER_05]: Look, I'll tell you what, once you have it, you always want it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So stay a virgin until you're 40, honestly.
[SPEAKER_05]: What else is there?
[SPEAKER_05]: Somebody wants to know if there's an Apple store here in Sacramento.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, there is, and I was just there today because my roommate, his extifer, is having a birthday on Tuesday, and his parents got him a gift card for the Apple store, and he went and bought an iPod.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the little bastard, for the same price I bought my iPod for, like, what, in December, he got a color iPod.
[SPEAKER_05]: I got mine for $190, 20 gig.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fucking Apple.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fucking price cuts.
[SPEAKER_05]: He should have paid more than what I pay.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not fair.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which pay?
300?
300.
[SPEAKER_05]: 300.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that's what he paid today.
[SPEAKER_05]: And he got a color one.
[SPEAKER_05]: I got a 20 gig black and white.
[SPEAKER_05]: He got a 20 gig color.
[SPEAKER_05]: So he's like, and of course he has to come in here and show me, Look, Rob!
[SPEAKER_03]: I have album art on my iPod!
[SPEAKER_23]: I look at my iPod twice a day.
[SPEAKER_23]: The rest of the time it resides in my armrest.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: The rest of my week and my day.
[SPEAKER_05]: I saw Charlie and the Chocolate Factory.
[SPEAKER_05]: Where the hell was the elevator?
[SPEAKER_05]: The Elevator was in the first movie.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was in the very end.
[SPEAKER_23]: Not as prominently as it was in the book.
[SPEAKER_05]: Exactly, exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: And just the songs were different.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Veruca Salt's whole scene was completely different.
[SPEAKER_05]: But some people like that because she had the whole, I want it now.
[SPEAKER_05]: She had her whole little song and some people loved that.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that's not in the new movie.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that drives some people crazy.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I'm telling you, the new movie is awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: I loved it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I highly recommend it.
[SPEAKER_05]: The reason why I liked it, one of the reasons why I liked it is because Johnny Depp,
[SPEAKER_05]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_14]: See, like, the songs are just, like, nutty in this one.
[SPEAKER_14]: Like, they range from that little, like, weird ballad thing.
[SPEAKER_14]: Before Christmas was, you know...
[SPEAKER_05]: Danny Elfman did all the songs, so it's like Oingo Boingo revisited.
[SPEAKER_05]: He sung it all and did the whole nine yards of that.
[SPEAKER_05]: But then some of the songs are way different.
[SPEAKER_05]: Then Veruca's Salt song is like a ballad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, I liked the movie.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was cool.
[SPEAKER_23]: I stopped the lighter for that one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Go see it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I highly recommend it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was good.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't go in expecting Gene Wilder or Willy Wonka and the Chocolate Factory because that's not what you're going to get.
[SPEAKER_05]: But if you read the books as a kid, you're going to be very pleased.
[SPEAKER_23]: What about Johnny Depp as a pirate?
[SPEAKER_05]: But Johnny Depp doesn't play a pirate in this.
[SPEAKER_05]: I heard his inspiration for this movie was Marilyn Manson, which kind of makes sense.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, he said no.
[SPEAKER_06]: He said it was the original movie.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, it can't be because he's nothing like Charlie.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was Michael Jackson.
[SPEAKER_06]: We know it's Michael Jackson.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's just not admitting to it.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, it can't be.
[SPEAKER_05]: It can't be Michael Jackson because, hey, DarkSakura's here.
[SPEAKER_05]: His inspiration can't be Michael Jackson because Michael Jackson loves kids almost a little too much.
[SPEAKER_05]: And in this movie, Johnny Depp hated children, and that's what made it so amazingly wonderful.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's why I liked it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, DarkSakura, you're here.
[SPEAKER_05]: In classic Orange Lounge fashion, you're tardy to a landmark episode number.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_10]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was doing Grandma Doody.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whose birthday was it?
[SPEAKER_05]: I couldn't remember.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dan's grandmother's 70th birthday.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dan's grandma's 70th birthday.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I was in Granite Bay.
[SPEAKER_10]: In like John L. Sullivan's neighborhood.
[SPEAKER_05]: Granite Bay is like the Mormon central of Northern California.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's also where rich people go.
[SPEAKER_10]: And they form colonies.
[SPEAKER_23]: There's no difference.
[SPEAKER_23]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_23]: We went to a school that had half of Granite Bay in it.
[SPEAKER_23]: So the parking lot was like Bugs, old Mustangs, and then Mercedes and BMWs.
[SPEAKER_10]: I felt very ill the whole time I was there.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was not too funny.
[SPEAKER_23]: You didn't go to Wendy's, did you?
[SPEAKER_23]: My brother works there.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, we had like, like, gourmet chicken.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_10]: And, hey, it landed the right way.
[SPEAKER_10]: And ribs and all kinds of rich people food.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you have hors d'oeuvres?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you have... I had cheese.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's rich, white, snobby people food?
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you have...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, you're here just in time.
[SPEAKER_05]: How was your week?
[SPEAKER_05]: How was your day, my friend?
[SPEAKER_10]: I played some PSO.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Seriously, that was it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I got really bored, my computer decided to die, I put those stupid Windows updates on it, and I'm so ready to get a Mac.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm getting tired of all this Microsoft bullshit.
[SPEAKER_21]: Come to the light side.
[SPEAKER_21]: No!
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what, you need to get off of your little I hate Mac piece of shit, because you know what, they're really good computers if... You don't know jack about computers, that's what they're good for, is if you don't want to do anything.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, they're more for the people who are specialists in their fields.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow, they rock at gaming too.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can also put a bunch of Macs together and get a lot more processing power out of them.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm warming up to Macs.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want one.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I'm not going to play games on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want it for audio.
[SPEAKER_10]: If I want to play games, I get myself a G5 and put Virtual PC on it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I can play any game I want to and a story.
[SPEAKER_10]: And on top of that, I have a system that's good for graphics.
[SPEAKER_10]: This needs to move.
[SPEAKER_05]: What is this?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_10]: I do admit that there's a lot of really stupid Mac users out there who are ultimately clueless because it actually can do a bunch of stuff for you.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then there's, like, the smart people.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I think, like, the middle-of-the-line people, the mediocre people are all PC.
[SPEAKER_05]: Are you still thinking of Macintoshes as what we used in high school, though?
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe that's the problem.
[SPEAKER_10]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, not you.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's because he's inflexible and won't learn to adjust.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I understand flexible.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think we're going to go to a break.
[SPEAKER_06]: Next thing you'll say is, you know, in the groove, it's just as good as DDR.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I want to talk about... No, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_10]: I go for innovation, not stupidity.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to talk about the lawsuit, just for a little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: The chatroom got mad at us because we talked about it too much last week, but I want to say there's a little bit, there's a little bit of news going on, so I want to talk about that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, the chatroom got upset.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, the chatroom also needs to learn how to be flexible, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, we'll be back after this.
[SPEAKER_05]: In this break, I want to play a new song from the new Katamari Damacy game, because I got some rips from it, so we're going to play this one.
[SPEAKER_05]: I haven't even listened to any of them yet, but this one's called Katamari Holiday.
[SPEAKER_05]: How bad could it be?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a holiday song.
[SPEAKER_05]: They need Katamari Damacy the movie.
[SPEAKER_10]: Katamari Damacy did have the track You Are Smart, the one that gave me splitting headaches.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, we'll see how this one is.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll be back after this with more Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_14]: I love you I love you I love you I love you I love you
[SPEAKER_14]: Subtitles by the Amara.org community
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_14]: Yattara Setsugai Asa Kumori Manobi Singo Yu Kimi no Sugata Katadoru Natsukashii Ashioto ga Taiyoku Suru Yo Masanshain Warawou
[SPEAKER_14]: Sometimes it sways, a lump of water, the scent of the flowing wind, the hand-pulling train.
[SPEAKER_14]: For dream of you, the ripples of the dream, the feeling of the wind, are various colors.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you for watching.
[SPEAKER_14]: Please subscribe to my channel.
I met you a long time ago
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_14]: It's been a long, long, long time since I've been with you.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: Orange Lounge Radio, Mamani Music, and more.
[SPEAKER_05]: Howdy boys and girls, we're back with more Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hope you enjoyed that rather long song from Katamari Damacy.
[SPEAKER_05]: But dammit, we just wanted to see if the music in the second game would be just as good as the first game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: I probably didn't play the best song.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just picked a good sounding one because I honestly haven't had time to listen to the whole soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I just picked one with a good name.
[SPEAKER_05]: So maybe I didn't pick the right one.
[SPEAKER_05]: We are back.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll talk a little more about the DDR and some of the other games we've been playing.
[SPEAKER_05]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_05]: The chat room over at OrangeLaunchRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: Click on chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're saying I sound like Cookie from You Don't Know Jack.
[SPEAKER_05]: And this is not the first time this subject has been brought up.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know what they're talking about.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've played You Don't Know Jack, like the first one, but I... Then there's like You Don't Know Jack, like every type of edition under the sun.
[SPEAKER_05]: There was like, you know, You Don't Know Jack.
[SPEAKER_05]: Monkey edition.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's crazy stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: D.D.R.
[SPEAKER_05]: World
[SPEAKER_05]: DDR Freak likes to play the smoking gun in these types of situations and they dig up the legal documents and post them on the website for everybody to see.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you can head on over to ddrfreak.com and you too can check out the amended complaint against Red Octane and Mad Catz.
[SPEAKER_05]: So everybody can try to be a lawyer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_05]: Which just makes the forums light up with blah blah blah blah blah blah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think I'm a lawyer.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know that this, this, this, and I know this, this, this, and the real fact of the matter is nobody knows shit unless you've been to law school.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, it's just interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Everybody's kind of got their own opinion on this whole thing going on.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought, however, there was a really excellent article that was done by our buddy El Mullet.
[SPEAKER_05]: InsidePulse.com
[SPEAKER_05]: This is how they're in violation of the law, end of story.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, it doesn't matter how much you go, oh, blah, blah, blah, you're wrong.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because if it were a good game, it wouldn't matter.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, this is what ticks people off, and this was in the original lawsuit documents, and of course it showed up in these original documents too, is that Konami in their lawsuit says, In the Groove is an inferior game.
[SPEAKER_05]: And people go, ahhh!
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, all the In the Groove fanboys, it goes, ahhh!
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's got the minds, and it's got the increased steps, and it's got better music.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, despite, you know, I don't really want to have that argument again.
[SPEAKER_05]: Either you like In The Groove more than you like DDR Extreme or any of the previous mixes, or you don't.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're one way or the other.
[SPEAKER_05]: You think they're okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: What I did find was interesting about it was the whole, they were showing their patents and stuff, and they were showing pictures of their concept for DDR and stuff, and the arrows were supposed to be scrolling downwards as the original concept.
[SPEAKER_06]: Those were actually, those documents were in the first
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, A, in their minds it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, it's a fact of the matter.
[SPEAKER_05]: B, just the fact that I think a lot of it has to do with the setup of the game being inferior.
[SPEAKER_05]: And this is why I talked about when the first lawsuit came up is that the hardware itself is the inferior part.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because in the beginning, and I'm not talking about in the group too, and neither is the lawsuit.
[SPEAKER_05]: In the beginning, in the group did not have its own cabinet.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was built to be a stowaway game in other cabinets.
[SPEAKER_05]: Therefore, the hardware is inferior.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course, now this lawsuit addresses the home versions, etc., etc.,
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, so I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess they call it inferior because of the fact that it's basically... Inferior?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a mock-up of DDR.
[SPEAKER_05]: It kind of started, if you think about it, Stepmania, it's built off of Stepmania.
[SPEAKER_10]: You mean a mockery of DDR?
[SPEAKER_05]: If you think about it, Stepmania was built to simulate DDR, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: So a simulator is always going to be inferior to the original, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess that's one way you can look at it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't want to get too far into this.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like how the step charts are already online for In the Groove because they were easily ripped from the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, guess what?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's In the Groove.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow, that was difficult.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: How do you like them apples, In the Groove, Roxor?
[SPEAKER_05]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think it hurts them at all because the same people that are into the step mania scene, I think, are a large part of the In the Groove fan base.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're self-accepted.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was before retards.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't understand why you won't even give the game a chance.
[SPEAKER_06]: You just- That fucking sucks!
[SPEAKER_06]: You've been anti-integrity- I can crap out better themes than that.
[SPEAKER_06]: And honestly, I suck at making themes.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, those are the plainest looking things I've ever seen.
[SPEAKER_06]: It looks like something you would see in beta.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like a beta game.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, he really wouldn't touch it if it was on a Mac.
[SPEAKER_06]: I really wouldn't touch it if it was on a Mac.
[SPEAKER_06]: That'd be just crap.
[SPEAKER_06]: It kind of reminds me of the Mac.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's nice and smoothed out and plain colors.
[SPEAKER_06]: And pointless.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because there's games out there that are better.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just because it tries to look pretty.
[SPEAKER_06]: But iTunes is cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Go iTunes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just, you know, run iTunes on your PC.
[SPEAKER_06]: Intel PC.
[SPEAKER_06]: or actually better than Intel PC, your AMD PC, and you're good to go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, if you have a Mac, you might as well just get one of those Cyrix chips and throw it in your PC.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's step back a generation, shall we?
[SPEAKER_05]: We've got some folks in the chat room that are going, let me at them, let me at them.
[SPEAKER_05]: We will open up the Skype line in a little bit if you want to give your comments and feedback.
[SPEAKER_05]: And those cards and letters, love letters addressed to Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: www.orangeloungeradio.com
[SPEAKER_06]: I have the same problem with Apple that I also have with VW.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's make cute cars that suck.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because people like cute, so they'll buy cute.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have you driven one?
[SPEAKER_06]: VW has the worst ratings as far as reliability.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've driven in one.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's not driving one.
[SPEAKER_10]: Have you driven one?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, then you don't have room to talk.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't want to drive your crappy car, no.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm sorry, you do drive a Ford.
[SPEAKER_10]: Six thousand repair daily.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, my Ford is fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've never had any problems with my Ford.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait, wait three years.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait three years.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm a former, I hate to say it, Loki, I'm a former Ford owner.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wait.
[SPEAKER_10]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_10]: The only Fords that last any time are the old ones, like my fiance's Mustang.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh yeah, that's a sexy car.
[SPEAKER_05]: I will never buy another Ford.
[SPEAKER_05]: 1969 Mustang.
[SPEAKER_05]: I will never touch a Mac.
[SPEAKER_05]: All my cars from now on will be foreign.
[SPEAKER_10]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: My Lancer completely kicks all your cars' asses combined.
[SPEAKER_05]: There will be some.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: You're a remixer.
[SPEAKER_05]: You remix songs.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have never been enticed by some of the Apple products like GarageBand or any of this stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I can get the same thing on a PC.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know?
[SPEAKER_06]: So what?
[SPEAKER_06]: Ooh, it's got GarageBand.
[SPEAKER_06]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a PC equivalent for that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Honestly, if you have a decent sound card, it's going to sound just the same.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Mac does not have anything that a decent sound card can't be better than.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, I don't really care.
[SPEAKER_06]: Honestly, the thing that I hated about the original Macs and stuff was the fact that everything was hardwired.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I still hate those stupid iMacs.
[SPEAKER_06]: Those things are dumb.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, you can take the new G5s and put new hard drives in them and upgrade the RAM and everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it's about time that they got with the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just they don't tell you you can do this, but you can.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, kids.
[SPEAKER_06]: Skype line is open.
[SPEAKER_06]: Give us a call.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's about time to get those Intel processors in there as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: www.orangelunchradio.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: Click on Skype.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you want to talk about the lawsuit, you want to yell at Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: Although, please, kids, we can go back and forth on this all day long.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is the classic interweb debate, is Mac versus PC.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought this debate ended like five years ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: Leave it to Loki to bring it back up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why do we get to the FUs of the week?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I've got a whole other thing that I'm going to re-bring up again.
[SPEAKER_05]: Goody, goody.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: So the Skype line's open.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you want to call in, www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: Click on Interact With Us.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, and look at that.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're starting to get some phone calls.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think this one's really been wanting to get through.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I figured I'd come back.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've got to jump in on this Mac versus PC debate here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Can you guys hear us in studio?
[SPEAKER_02]: I've got firsthand experience on this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, what's up?
[SPEAKER_02]: I work on these things.
[SPEAKER_02]: Introduce yourself, please.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, introduce yourself, sir.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm Reznor.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi, Reznor.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've called in a couple of times.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're the one that does the con on the East Coast, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, I remember this guy.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: So what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I work on PCs and Mac day in and day out.
[SPEAKER_02]: I used to really hate Macs.
[SPEAKER_02]: And after working on them for about three months, Macs can kick PCs' asses all up and down the block.
[SPEAKER_02]: If I have to just fix another PC user that brought it in because their stupid kid downloaded Kazaa and got Spyware all over it after I just cleaned it up, I'm going to scream.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll give you that because people assume that nobody uses Macs.
[SPEAKER_05]: They haven't been as much of a target for the spyware and everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've had so many PC people just come in and ditch... One guy traded in three PCs and bought two iMacs and a PowerBook on the spot because he was so sick and tired of his machine crashing and all sorts of crap.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well...
[SPEAKER_06]: Yep, those stupid users need a stupid computer, so it fits right in!
[SPEAKER_02]: Cause, you know, goddamn retard's true!
[SPEAKER_02]: Honestly!
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually own both, um, so, uh, there's things, obviously the PC does gaming a lot better,
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: You like their power tools.
[SPEAKER_06]: They granny you to death, and Microsoft does the same thing, and I hate both.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what it is?
[SPEAKER_05]: You like to build your own PCs, don't you?
[SPEAKER_05]: Damn straight.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's why you don't like Macs, because Macs don't allow you that flexibility.
[SPEAKER_05]: You like being able to buy a part here.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd like to differ with them on this one.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've got about six PCs laying around that I just built from just parts laying around.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll build them day in, day out.
[SPEAKER_02]: and many more.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't stand Dells either.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't agree with you on that one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Buying an Apple is not like buying a Dell.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, because the difference between a Dell and an Apple is Dell is sort of a put-together piece of crap, except for my laptop, which is pretty nice.
[SPEAKER_10]: and Apple's actually work.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dell is kind of like if you took a giant pile of shit and then you put a nice little case around it and you painted it black.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whereas with an Apple, you actually put something useful in it and made it really small.
[SPEAKER_10]: But to one thing say in defense of Dell's, which I really do need to say, their PCs are crap, but the laptops are pretty nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not talking about the quality of service or anything like that because we all know Dell outsources their customer service and Apple's got a pretty decent customer service setup.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not talking about that whole actual act of going in and purchasing, but I'm talking about that all-in-one feeling where you're buying a computer in a box.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's face it, the Mac Mini is totally a computer in a box.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, you can mod those things, but the average user isn't going to be doing that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right?
[SPEAKER_23]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_23]: Whereas to build a PC, you really have to think about, okay... The average user really has no need to modify a mini.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's why they buy a mini.
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah, I understand that.
[SPEAKER_23]: You plug it in and it works.
[SPEAKER_23]: Except for freaks like us who buy the mini and then mod the hell out of it.
[SPEAKER_23]: But I can... You're not a normal user.
[SPEAKER_23]: I have an iBook and I run Terminal Live.
[SPEAKER_05]: You run Linux.
[SPEAKER_05]: The minute you install Linux on anything, you are already reached geek levels.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Mac is Linux.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the cool thing about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know the Mac is Linux-based, but I'm talking about the hardcore stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: because even though the Mac runs on Linux now, it is still a Mac.
[SPEAKER_05]: It still feels like the old black and white Macs that we used to play Number Munchers on, okay?
[SPEAKER_10]: I always played Where in the World is Carmen Sandiego, thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_06]: I played that on my Commodore 64.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dark Castle.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, I'd like to correct you.
[SPEAKER_06]: It would be black and green.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I'm eating this old school shit up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, keep on going.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oregon Trail, yo.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just, Kix.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dude, where is Oregon Trail on the PSP?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what we need.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, Kix on an Apple IIe.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh my god, Kix, oh my god.
[SPEAKER_05]: Was that the name of the Dark Castle?
[SPEAKER_05]: It was only on a Mac, they didn't have it on PC, and you were going through, that game was sex.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was a great game.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, it was Kix and Lode Runner on an Apple IIe.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lode Runner, oh my god.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've lost countless bets trying to beat high scores in that game.
[SPEAKER_05]: But see, all these games you all are talking about, they had on the Commodore 64.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, I remember sitting there with my TI-94 computer with the cartridge crappy thing, trying to program little bouncing balls, blipping the little blippy music in BASIC.
[SPEAKER_06]: I remember loading BASIC stuff onto my TI-86, or not TI-86.
[SPEAKER_05]: TI-85 calculator?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, not 85.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's the actual old... The TI-99?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it's the old Texas Instrument computer.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, not the calculator, actually the old computer.
[SPEAKER_06]: Using a cassette tape, okay?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, I had one of those.
[SPEAKER_05]: You owned a TI-99 and you dare to bash on Macs now?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, this was when I was five, and it wasn't a TI-99, it was my first computer.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was a Texas instrument when I was five.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not, um, TI-99 was a calculator.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm angry at my grandmother for throwing this thing away, but I had one of the old Coleco computers with a tape deck.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, and Adam.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, jeez.
[SPEAKER_10]: and my grandma threw it away and I was like, NO!
[SPEAKER_10]: That's my album!
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting side story about Texas Instruments.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was the reason that they banned all the graphing calculators at my high school when I was going there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually went out and sprung to get the data transfer cable and I downloaded tons of games for it like multiplayer Tetris and everything and I would bring them into school and then transfer them to other people's calculators and eventually
[SPEAKER_02]: The entire 12th grade was doing nothing but playing games in class.
[SPEAKER_05]: They hadn't figured that out yet when I was in high school because I had a nice graphing calculator and I was an AP Calculus and I was programming the complex formulas into my calculator so I could cheat on all the tests.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what, Rob?
[SPEAKER_10]: I find it very funny that, you know, I think I graduated a year ahead of you, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was playing pole position on those calculators in history class.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, pole position.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkTetsuya is so winner for this comment in our chatroom.
[SPEAKER_06]: He wants an Oregon Trail MMO.
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dude, Oregon Trail MMO would rock.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki could die of dysentery.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_02]: Oregon Trail Damacy.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, honestly, that could work.
[SPEAKER_05]: An Oregon Trail MMO could so work.
[SPEAKER_05]: We need to get on that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's start an online petition because those rock.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, online petitions always do the trick.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's what we should do.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to make an online petition.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll get it slash dotted.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who the crap is going to play an Oregon Trail MMO?
[SPEAKER_02]: Me, motherfucker, me!
[SPEAKER_02]: You get to Oregon and then you have to build a castle and then you can make a blacksmith and put shoes on horses.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's great fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, then you go back.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: When we talk about the Oregon Trail, we always talked about the people who are going out west to seek a better life.
[SPEAKER_05]: We never talked about those people that got there and then realized, this place sucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, wagons east.
[SPEAKER_02]: Any game where you can have four people die because your wagon flooded in a river that's two inches deep is retarded.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have major issues against Oregon Trail.
[SPEAKER_23]: You need to make something more like Kingdom of Loathing.
[SPEAKER_23]: OMG, looking for party, need to cross river.
[SPEAKER_23]: Need cock.
[SPEAKER_11]: Fear and Loathing in Oregon, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Morphine, please.
[SPEAKER_05]: Looking for Black Mage who can cast Float on my fight.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe you'd see MRPH and PLZ.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or my favorite is when I'd go hunting and I'd just kill everything and just have way too much meat.
[SPEAKER_02]: You killed 40,000 pounds of meat, but you can only carry 100.
[SPEAKER_02]: That used to happen to me all the time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, PETA would be all over your ass in that MMO.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was killing buffalo, like every buffalo in sight.
[SPEAKER_02]: He smells like death.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, we're going to give him a... I love the smell of decay in the morning.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then somebody's going to have a speed hack, and people are like, hey, you stole my bear kill.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my god, someone unlocked the sex hack in Oregon Trail.
[SPEAKER_09]: And all it does is a bunch of women showing their ankles.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, we just unlocked this feature in Oregon Trail.
[SPEAKER_05]: When we stop at the next fort, you can either shop for wagon parts or you can stop in for hot coffee.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then the new add-on where you steal the Indians' land.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd like to know what the expansions are going to be, yo.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Alaskan Trail!
[SPEAKER_05]: The Canadian Trail.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yeah, you have to dodge Mounties.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Pacific Trail where they have to cross the ocean.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Mexican Trail.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm sorry, now I'm thinking of like a Ren and Simpy with the Royal Canadian Kilted Yaksman.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, was there ever a sequel to the Oregon Trail?
[SPEAKER_05]: Like a different trail?
[SPEAKER_05]: It was called Everybody's Dead!
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it was a remake of the original thing and it sucked.
[SPEAKER_02]: It sucked, really.
[SPEAKER_05]: They needed a sequel to the Oregon Trail.
[SPEAKER_05]: Every other... Number Munchers got a sequel.
[SPEAKER_05]: They got Word Munchers.
[SPEAKER_05]: What else was there?
[SPEAKER_05]: What other classic... There's only one Oregon.
[SPEAKER_02]: How can you make a sequel of a historical... How can you make another Oregon?
[SPEAKER_02]: You could- Oregon Trail 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oregon Trail 2 is back and it's pissed.
[SPEAKER_02]: We made it!
[SPEAKER_02]: We're taking the Oregon Trail through the ghetto now.
[SPEAKER_02]: We don't have to worry about drive-bys and crack whores.
[SPEAKER_14]: Are you John Connor?
[SPEAKER_05]: If it's gonna go through the ghetto it would have to be Oakland Trail.
[SPEAKER_05]: There has to be another trail somewhere in the world that they could do a game off of.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Iraqi Trail!
[SPEAKER_05]: There you go!
[SPEAKER_02]: You've got to make it down the sand road.
[SPEAKER_05]: Trail of a thousand tears.
[SPEAKER_02]: We can do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Puerto Rican trail.
Puerto Rican.
Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, this gets my vote as the most politically incorrect episode ever.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a landmark number.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: What number is it?
[SPEAKER_02]: I've been like at a circuit.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's 150 tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's divisible by 50.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, it's divisible by 50.
[SPEAKER_05]: And two.
[SPEAKER_02]: Holy crap, I need another beer on that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, yeah, me too, I think so.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, Reznor, any other closing thoughts?
[SPEAKER_05]: I gotta get some other calls, but we do enjoy having you on the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: You bring out the old school in us, I appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, you gotta keep in touch with your roots.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hell yes we do, so that's all I use my PSP for, Kid Icarus.
[SPEAKER_05]: Woot.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, I'll let you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have a good one, my friend, and take care.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for the call.
[SPEAKER_05]: Later.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was a fun call.
[SPEAKER_05]: Turtle, the MMO.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's take another call.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oregon Trail 2, Arcade Edition Anyway, hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio, who's this?
[SPEAKER_00]: You're on Oregon Trail Radio Sephiroth1215 and SSJ100Matt and many other people Many other people?
[SPEAKER_05]: Are you having like an Orange Lounge listening party or something?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah It's the Orange Lounge orgy, that's awesome We have hit a new level of tastelessness, congratulations to us People have moved from having Buffy parties to having Orange Lounge parties That makes me feel kind of cool
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, what's on your mind, guys?
[SPEAKER_00]: Not much.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's someone that wants to talk about the Mac and PC thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Goody, goody.
[SPEAKER_05]: Put him on.
[SPEAKER_00]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who is this?
[SPEAKER_05]: Introduce yourself.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm Chris DeCruz.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_04]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_04]: Quite frankly, I don't care if you know my real name.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway...
[SPEAKER_04]: About the Mac and Intel thing, they're saying how you can run virtual PC on a Mac and play any of the PC games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Emulators cause massive slowdown, and it's not feasible at all.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know people who've done it.
[SPEAKER_05]: In the chat room it was kind of brought up, we kind of addressed this during the break, that it's more...
[SPEAKER_05]: If you want to play the DOS-based games, you'd be okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, the DOS-based games.
[SPEAKER_04]: But say, for example, Battlefield 2 is not going to be running.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: If you want to play Battlefield 2, you really should... Who wants to play that crap?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, look, if you want to play Battlefield 2, you should own a PC anyway.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm talking about Ragnarok and PSO, which I play on my laptop.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, PSO and Ragnarok... Oh, Ragnarok is what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sprite-based?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: And PSO is six years old?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, the PC version's new, but you're right.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't give a shit about Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think that game is ass.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, Final Fantasy XI is horrible.
[SPEAKER_10]: Which is why I quit it twice.
[SPEAKER_05]: Look, my response to the fact that the PC emulators on a Mac will play DOS-based games is I said, well, then it will play ZZT, and that's all you need.
[SPEAKER_05]: Honestly.
[SPEAKER_04]: My DS will play DOS-based games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't understand your point.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want ZZT on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_03]: Go buy a PassMe and blank ROM cartridges and just install everything on there.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anything else you want to share on the whole Mac versus PC thing?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think they're demanding me to get off this before you kick everyone else off.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for your input.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're getting passed around like a bong at this party.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_00]: First of all, I'd like to ask, you're going to be on the East Coast in a few weeks, and are you going to be anywhere else but the place in New Jersey?
[SPEAKER_05]: Am I making any more live appearances, so to speak?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, nobody's really asked.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm actually going out there for work, so my Monday through Fridays are kind of booked with the real world work stuff, but on the weekend I'm open to suggestions.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you have something, just email me and I'll see what I can do.
[SPEAKER_00]: Um, alright then, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the New Jersey thing right now is definite.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to do the New Jersey tournament, because I haven't been to a DDR tournament in like years, so I think it would be funny to go to one on the East Coast for the first time, so.
[SPEAKER_23]: Make sure you kick those plugs, it kind of smells.
[SPEAKER_23]: Stop it.
[SPEAKER_23]: It does!
[SPEAKER_23]: I was in Philadelphia, it smelled like New Jersey!
[SPEAKER_00]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, I've been there, it wasn't all that great, but it was alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_05]: Didn't you go to some con recently you wanted to share with us, and...
[SPEAKER_00]: Go to New York?
[SPEAKER_00]: Basically, anything...
[SPEAKER_00]: Fantasy, Sci-Fi, Nerd, stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it's kind of like a Comic Con.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, there's a big furry thing, if you want to know that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, it's a furry convention.
[SPEAKER_05]: How lovely.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_00]: That was just a large part of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, well, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it's kind of like at an anime con out here, hentai is always a big part of it, no matter what.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can't escape it.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, hentai was big there, too.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, yeah, there was...
[SPEAKER_00]: There's a big gaming room for anything gaming, huge screens, whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you get to play any new import game type things for the first time?
[SPEAKER_00]: No, I didn't get to.
[SPEAKER_05]: There was good stuff, but... I've been to Connecticut, it's not that awful.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's better than Delaware.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's better than Delaware, come on!
[SPEAKER_00]: There's not much to do in Connecticut.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's not much to do in Delaware.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm going to put SJ100 Matt on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_05]: Puff, puff, pass.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey, what's up?
[SPEAKER_01]: Good.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, I'm going to elaborate a little bit more since Sephiroth is playing Smash Brothers, so... What?
[SPEAKER_05]: He's playing video games while he's trying to talk to us?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, we got several people here.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's trying to play video games and losing badly.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, anyways... I can owe it all of you at Smash Brothers.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ha, ha, ha.
[SPEAKER_05]: They might take you up on that, be careful.
[SPEAKER_08]: They'll have to come to California.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_01]: When the revolution comes out, we'll all be playing online.
[SPEAKER_05]: Aha, there you have it.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I will still own you all, because I am the master of Kirby.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's on your mind, SSJ?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, the... Kineticon was really good in the fact that it had a lot of workshops, a lot of...
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: Gaming, Magic Cards, and other card game matches going on.
[SPEAKER_01]: Dude, Magic Cards are still around?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: My co-worker participates in tournaments.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh my god, that was like ten years ago I was in a Magic Card.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not knocking the Magic Cards thing, but I'm just saying, wow, I can't believe it has this longevity going on with it.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is crazy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, sorry.
[SPEAKER_01]: But, yeah, the gaming room, they had
[SPEAKER_01]: Smash Brothers Tournament going on, and they had a Halo 2 tournament going on.
[SPEAKER_05]: How was the Smash Brothers Tournament?
[SPEAKER_05]: I liked that game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, actually, we...
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, actually, we kind of entered it, but we didn't go to it, because it was like a couple-hour preliminary rounds and all that, so we didn't have time for that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gotcha.
[SPEAKER_01]: But we donated a GameCube for a short time, which actually gave us tickets to the next Kineticon for free.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, there you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: How often do they have Kineticon?
[SPEAKER_05]: Just once a year, or...?
[SPEAKER_01]: Once a year.
[SPEAKER_01]: This was the first time that they had it in the big Hartford Convention Center.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, right on.
[SPEAKER_01]: For Connecticut, that's big.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's really big.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, yeah, well.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm pasting a link to the pictures on the chat room.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right on.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hope our listeners want to check that out, especially if they're on the East Coast and missed it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Then they can see everything they missed, and they'll go next year.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: and they had a Beatmania tournament, a poppin' music tournament.
[SPEAKER_05]: What style were they doing the Beatmania thing on?
[SPEAKER_01]: I heard someone mention 8, but I'm not positive.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: Poppin' music, I think they had some sort of tournament to win like a Naruto customized poppin' music pad or something, which looked interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then, of course, the dealer room, which was interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: and plenty of cosplays.
[SPEAKER_05]: Any scary cosplays?
[SPEAKER_01]: What do you mean scary?
[SPEAKER_05]: He's talking about boobies.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm talking about, like, super fat Sailor Moon.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I'm talking about the guys who dress up like... Sailor Menchi.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm talking about fat men who dress up like my... Sailor Menchi.
[SPEAKER_01]: There were a couple of really scary ones, you know, the chubby girls who thought they could be Kagome from Inuyasha.
[SPEAKER_01]: from the WNFL Ares.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, we saw a WNFL Ares.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like Final Fantasy 7?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, well, you know, she looked like she could play in the NFL.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, okay, I get it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Quite scary.
[SPEAKER_01]: There was one girl who wore a Darkstalkers costume.
[SPEAKER_01]: Very revealing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I see.
[SPEAKER_05]: How about any good cosplay?
[SPEAKER_05]: Were there good ones?
[SPEAKER_01]: There were several.
[SPEAKER_01]: I actually posted up a lot of the good ones in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_05]: Check out the pictures there.
[SPEAKER_14]: Did somebody say Goatse cosplay?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's disgusting.
[SPEAKER_10]: How would one cosplay that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Very slowly.
[SPEAKER_05]: It would be real pain in the ass.
[SPEAKER_01]: Out of the 12 people in this small room, there's about 11 of them who are wise asses.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's 12 people over there?
[SPEAKER_01]: In a tiny room, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dude, that's more people than listen to our show regularly.
[SPEAKER_05]: And everyone's fully clothed.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, I might add...
[SPEAKER_01]: are actually voting for you on that whole thing that you have.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, the Podcast Awards thing?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you kindly.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't even remember to mention this.
[SPEAKER_05]: We got nominated Best Gaming Podcast over on PodcastAwards.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: Go vote for us, because we like attention.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, actually, I have a quick little story that happened at Kineticon.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: My buddy Sephiroth was playing, what song was it?
[SPEAKER_01]: At least.
[SPEAKER_01]: Could this kid even play 2DX?
[SPEAKER_01]: Because I've had the kids at Roosevelt Golf Land that are like 12 years old try to make fun of me.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then it's like, you know, well, dude, if you're so good at DDR, you want to play a match against me?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll pick the song, you know, Healing Vision Angelic Mix or something.
[SPEAKER_01]: I hinted that to him.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's like, well, I've seen him play a couple times, but, you know, he plays on 1.5 and 2X, and if you don't do that, you're considered a noob.
[SPEAKER_17]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_01]: But, no, you know what?
[SPEAKER_01]: I didn't want to, like, get into an argument with him.
[SPEAKER_01]: I didn't want to, like,
[SPEAKER_01]: Be mean to him because he's like a 16-year-old kid.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think with his overweightness, I'm sure life has already dealt a poor hand to him.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, you sometimes wonder what happens to children to make them turn out so strange.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, but he was very rude, so I had to step in and save my friend over here.
[SPEAKER_01]: Other than that, Kineticon was very good.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's
[SPEAKER_01]: I have to tell you one thing.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, he has one thing to say.
[SPEAKER_00]: I got to meet Tiffany Grant, who is also the voice of Asuka.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right on.
[SPEAKER_01]: And also, we met Piano Squall, if you know who that is.
[SPEAKER_05]: No idea.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have to be honest, I don't follow the anime thing that closely.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like, I like some of it, but... There's one thing that you're going to be jealous of, and we got to meet Freeze Pop.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: I am jealous.
[SPEAKER_05]: I am jealous.
[SPEAKER_05]: I got to meet Togo at E3.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do I get a cookie for that?
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to let you go so you guys can get back to your party.
[SPEAKER_05]: We get back to our show.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_05]: For 12 people, I can make the time.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's twice our normal listenership.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's huge.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have a good time, kids.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, my gosh.
[SPEAKER_05]: Orange Lounge listening parties.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who would have thought?
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, we're going to go to a break, kids.
[SPEAKER_05]: When we come back from this break, we're going to do the Cage Match, some other news going on.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're doing Happy Sky Music tonight, going to continue on with that theme.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to have in this break, we're going to have a song, a brand new Akira Yamaoka song is going to start it off.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to have a song that's actually a Papa Music crossover in this break as well, and a song named after a dog.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll all be in this break.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we'll be back with more Orange Lounge Radio and the Cage Match and the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe some Ask Orange Lounge if we have time, and if we get around to it, some actual DDR news.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll be back.
Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_14]: Thanks for watching!
Thank you for watching
[SPEAKER_21]: For up to a minute of Ammanian gaming news, discussion forums, and for access to the chat room, visit our website at orangeloungeradio.com Happy Sky
[SPEAKER_05]: Zephyr, a very epic song in there, and then Y&Co, folks behind Monkey Dance, Daisuki, their new song, Poodle!
[SPEAKER_05]: Cute.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I see you over there, DarkSakura, reading the new Harry Potter.
[SPEAKER_10]: I did the same thing last time.
[SPEAKER_05]: I do remember when that... God, this show's been on a long time, because I remember when the last book came out.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to say when Goblet of Fire came out, you were on here, too, but I think that might have been before.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, yeah, I was.
[SPEAKER_08]: Were you?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, my gosh.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, I've got to ask you about this, because this was something that was kind of pissing me off, but it seems like there's kids on the Internet that are loving spoiling this new book.
[SPEAKER_05]: What do you think about this whole thing?
[SPEAKER_05]: The spoiler.
[SPEAKER_10]: So what?
[SPEAKER_10]: You have the option of reading it or not?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, but there's people that have gone on LiveJournal and they'll post it in their journal, not behind a cut, in really big font, the big spoiler, so that all their friends can read it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Nobody's done that on mine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, because they know you'll defriend their ass, but I've seen it on mine.
[SPEAKER_10]: I wouldn't do that.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's petty.
[SPEAKER_10]: But to post a spoiler like that is petty, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, it's stupid.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's rude, but it's not something that's worth all of a sudden not being somebody's friend over.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it would really depend on how close you were with somebody in the first place, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: If it's just somebody you just kind of knew on the internet, they added you because they thought their LJ was cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: But if it was somebody I knew in real life...
[SPEAKER_05]: I wouldn't do it, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Nobody has posted any big-fonted spoilers on my live journal.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I just think...
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, let people have their thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think it has to do with the general character of the people I've been friending.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, that's good, but I mean, I think, I'm just kind of like, you know what, let people have their thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: You might be making fun of the Harry Potter thing, but let's face it, you listen to a DDR radio show, I'm not talking about you guys specifically, I don't think anybody that listens to this show is in on this, but you know, the people that are posting spoilers, it's like, you know what, and then they go, oh, I'm spoiling it because Harry Potter fanboys are stupid.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm just like, you know what, you probably got your stupid thing too.
[SPEAKER_05]: How would you like me to go take a dump on that?
[SPEAKER_10]: I already know what's going to happen, so I don't care.
[SPEAKER_10]: For me, it's how they get there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, I decided I would have a Guinness in celebration of our 150th episode.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm having a celebratory drink since I don't have to drive tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm having an upset stomach.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm supposed to plug something.
[SPEAKER_05]: They actually made a chat room called Channel Oregon Trail.
[SPEAKER_05]: to discuss the latest news and events behind everybody's favorite upcoming MMO, The Oregon Trail Strikes Back.
[SPEAKER_05]: So join that channel.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a good time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Moving on with other news going on throughout the gaming world and the Bomani world.
[SPEAKER_05]: DDR with Mario had their site open up and it actually happened a little while ago but it kind of happened under the radar because I think a lot of people might have given up on DDR with Mario once they heard that
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, heavy or whatever it was.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think it was the hardest, hardest difficulty, because not all songs had that, but it was like one below it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it was about the equivalent of Five Footer, and I triple-a'd it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm not the type of person that sits there and triple-a's all these songs on DDR.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I've done some, but I'm by no means like this excellent DDR player.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, DDR with Mario is kind of simple.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the Japanese site opened up for DDR with Mario because I believe the game actually might have come out in Japan.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have to be honest, I haven't really been following this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, it did just a few days ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: July 14th was the release date in Japan.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, there you have it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you can look at the website and look at all the features and
[SPEAKER_05]: All that stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Although it's all in Japanese, so unless you can read Japanese, you're not going to be able to read it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Unless you run it through a translator or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, so I guess that's some big Bumani news.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's interesting because there's still a lot of speculation going on with the new DDRs coming out, Extreme 2 and Ultramix 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just kind of been keeping a pulse on what's going on on the DDR-freak threads, which is where the majority of the discussion's been occurring.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think a lot of people were expecting Extreme 2 to make a debut at Comic-Con
[SPEAKER_05]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: Still the date.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think the only one that got pushed back was Karaoke Revolution Party.
[SPEAKER_06]: It got pushed back one week later, so it's not coming out the same day as Ultramix 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's coming out the week after that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I heard some things were going on with Karaoke Revolution Party, but I can't talk about them.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can tell me, because I pretty much know everything that's going on.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why can't you tell me?
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's have this discussion off air, please.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's going to rock.
[SPEAKER_05]: You all should pick that up.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then there's Ultramix 3, which I think is interesting because one of the very most recent posts in the Ultramix 3 thread was by somebody who's actually in our chat room right now, Renee, although I always want to say Rini, because there's so many E's.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to get punched for saying that.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it actually referenced our own site and the lovely DarkSakura, her photo gallery.
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember how you took just a shitload of pictures of E3 of everything?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, somebody finally decided to look at the pictures and
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: But the things that were shown here, Emi being in a schoolgirl outfit, I didn't realize people didn't know that before, but yes, Emi was in a schoolgirl outfit in the E3 demo, and it was cute.
[SPEAKER_05]: I liked it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just like the graduation video.
[SPEAKER_06]: I liked slut Emi better, though, for Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_08]: Slut Emi was a piece of shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: I liked slut Emi, too, actually.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was a lot of fan service, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you guys got slut Emi, I'd get hands-less rage.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, no, it's not three-titted Emmy.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's only, you know, slut Emmy.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you'd have to get... And I'd get man-poor rage.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, you'd have to get, like, rage in tight shorts or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: The result screen is a, and I quote, bubbly bubble bubbly bub in the background, and not fancy, just plain and simple.
[SPEAKER_05]: However, it shows...
[SPEAKER_05]: How many calories you've burned.
[SPEAKER_05]: Doesn't look like workout mode because the numerical score is shown.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't even notice that when I was playing.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I've been saying for like two years now that they just need to integrate workout mode into the normal DDR.
[SPEAKER_05]: So if that actually happened, that makes me very happy.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't even notice that when I was playing, but I was just so jazzed to be playing Ultramix 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wasn't looking for all the little things when I was playing it.
[SPEAKER_05]: But that's very cool because I don't think workout mode should be separate because you can't unlock things when you play in workout mode.
[SPEAKER_05]: At least I don't think you can.
[SPEAKER_05]: But from what I remember about Ultramix 3 and the interface, basically, take Ultramix 2 and replace whatever blue futuristic background thing they had with the bubbles, and that was Ultramix 3's interface.
[SPEAKER_05]: The main part of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So if you want to see that, that's over on DDR Freak.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I will get my pictures up at some point.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think my pictures show anything new about the game, but I guess you never know.
[SPEAKER_06]: But you do have a picture of me with Mario.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I do have a picture of you with Mario, and it rocks.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have a picture of me with Mario, and one with Link.
[SPEAKER_05]: I took some pictures of the Beatmania demo, too, but the Beatmania demo really didn't have anything in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, the Beatmania demo was just Night Style plus Oh My God's five key songs in it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_05]: And it was stuck on Training... What the hell is the one-star mode called?
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't even remember.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, Beginner Mode.
[SPEAKER_05]: Seven Key Mode was stuck on Beginner Mode, which I thought was kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's not going to be that way in the regular release, so don't worry, guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: Any day now we should start finding out new songs for these games.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm surprised no new artists have leaked out what songs are going to be in it or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: We should start finding out some songs pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would hope that they're going to put out a finalized release pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, before that, don't you think, when the press gets a hold of these games, they're going to start posting pictures on their website?
[SPEAKER_05]: Has GamePro reviewed it again yet?
[SPEAKER_05]: Not yet, but you know it'll happen.
[SPEAKER_06]: I swear, does Konami not learn with GamePro?
[SPEAKER_06]: I would seriously try to sue them for, you know... Well, no, because it created buzz for their games.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it had a positive effect.
[SPEAKER_05]: It created buzz on the games and got people talking.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh my god, here's the song list.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh my god, oh my god.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, you know, I don't think it was a bad thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wouldn't sue them over it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It got people talking about the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Free advertising.
[SPEAKER_06]: Where I'd make them review the Ninja Turtles game over and over and over again.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or Frogger.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright kids, I think it's time to get into tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you want to be a part of the cage match, you've got to join our chat room over at www.orangeloungeradio.com Alright, and the way the cage match works...
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to play three songs for you guys, last week's winner.
[SPEAKER_05]: A clip of it, anyway, because it won last week, so you've already heard the song.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to play that, and then we're going to play two new songs for you guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: You guys vote on your favorite, and the winner goes into rotation all week long on Orange Lounge Radio's Bomani Music & More program, which plays 24 hours a day, 7 days a week, on the station when we are not live.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, here it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Last week in the cage match.
[SPEAKER_05]: Blur with Girls and Boys
Thanks for watching!
My battery's been cut Can't look for someone to pray for My thing is nothing is wasted Only repurchase You cannot be blessed
[SPEAKER_14]: Girls who are boys, who like boys To be girls who did boys like they girls Who did girls like they boys Always should be someone you really like
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: Woopies!
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're gonna get into song number two of tonight's Cage Match, so that was song number one, Blur with Girls and Boys.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's song number two.
[SPEAKER_05]: Song number two tonight is my pick, and I decided to pick, um, I kinda like the new, um, Utada album, so, um, I picked a song that's actually a remix, because I like this remix, because it's different than the song on the album, and, um, I think it's a little bit better.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I was also just desperate to find something at the last minute, so I just went ahead and picked this one.
[SPEAKER_05]: So here it is, song number two of tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Utada with Exodus 04, the Double J Radio Mix.
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: Song number two in tonight's cage match, that was Utada with Exodus 04.
[SPEAKER_05]: It smells like beer in here.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wonder why.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see if that song should go on in Exodus or if it should stay here forever.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_10]: Kind of generic and sounds like all the rest of her stuff, so it gets a six.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like the instrumental, but the vocals just sounded like... I guess it just sounds like her, so... It was okay, it was just...
[SPEAKER_05]: I agree on that it's a little repetitive, but it's kind of a dance mix.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I think it improves on the original, because I don't like the original.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like a low-energy dance mix.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it's kind of a closing time.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm standing there drunk, and I'm kind of bobbing my head to the music.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, so I give it like an eight.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, song number three, Loki's pick.
[SPEAKER_06]: What did you pick for us tonight, Loki?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, if you want retro, here's retro right here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sort of.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's retro redone.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's Stayin' Alive.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like the Bee Gees?
[SPEAKER_06]: Like the Bee Gees, but done by Ozzy Osbourne.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's good.
[SPEAKER_10]: What?
[SPEAKER_10]: Wait.
[SPEAKER_06]: Staying Alive.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, I have this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, here we go.
[SPEAKER_10]: I already know what I'm reading it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Song number three, Staying Alive by Ozzy Osbourne.
[SPEAKER_05]: Enjoy.
Oh yeah!
Well, you can't deal with the way I use my work I'm a woman's man, sometimes it's all easy-going
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_14]: Day in the Life, Day in the Life, Day in the Life, Day in the Life, Day in the Life
[SPEAKER_14]: It's alright, it's okay, we may go the other way We can try to understand, but we don't have nothing to say It's alright, it's okay, let's see another day We can try to understand, but we don't have nothing to say Ha ha ha ha ha
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: now my ass smells like beer because I sat in the wet beer part of the chair
[SPEAKER_05]: Song number three, Ozzy Osbourne, Stayin' Alive.
[SPEAKER_05]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_05]: Stayin' Alive or should we pull the plug on that song?
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_10]: Stayin' Alive was a crap movie.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've had that particular song for quite a while now and I've listened to it quite a lot.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I think it's a wonderful cover.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I don't think it's cage-matchy, so it gets a seven and a half.
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was all I got in five minutes, so it gets an eight.
[SPEAKER_05]: My synopsis, somewhere the disco train derailed.
[SPEAKER_05]: I give it a five.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was the crazy train, not the disco train.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, boys and girls, we're going to recap the three songs, and then you get to place your vote.
[SPEAKER_05]: Song number one you can vote for tonight is Girls and Boys.
[SPEAKER_05]: and song number two you can vote for tonight is Exodus 04 by Utada and song number three you can vote for tonight is Ozzy Osbourne with Stayin' Alive that just cracks me up to say
[SPEAKER_05]: Please vote now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Send a private message to Sky in the chat room with your vote for song number one, The Blur, song number two, The Utada, or song number three, The Aussie.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think Stand Alive would be cool if it was in Guitar Freaks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, that would be cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, there's the Guitar Heroes coming out, and it's supposed to have a lot of covers.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to have Bowie in it, which is cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to have Hendrix.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to be the total stoner game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Guitar Freaks needs something different.
[SPEAKER_06]: They really, I'm very disappointed that they got rid of Keyboard Mania.
[SPEAKER_05]: Me too.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, that was kind of, they should have instead of getting rid of games that plug with Guitar Freaks, they should have added stuff to it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, maybe a karaoke game to go with it, you know, and you can sing the vocals to the songs, or maybe, I don't know, another instrument or something that they could be playing?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Keyboard Mania, the reason why I'm pissed off that Konami got rid of Keyboard Mania is because Keyboard Mania was a one-but-money game that it was actually pretty good at, that a lot of people don't take the time to be good at.
[SPEAKER_05]: And so I got really good at Keyboard Mania, and it was, like, I wasn't blue good, but I was good.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can actually pass songs on doubles, which I think is good.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I can pass, like, six, like, I can pass, like, you know, most of the six stars.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think the only one I could never pass was the crazy one from, I don't even remember the name of it, it's been so long since I've played.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it pissed me off, because I was like, you know, I could have, I could have been really good.
[SPEAKER_05]: I could have been a contender at Keyboard Mania, and they went and pulled the plug on my game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bastard.
[SPEAKER_05]: D.R.O.S.C.
[SPEAKER_00]: Psychopath Edition
[SPEAKER_06]: because most of the entries dropped out.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, yeah, eight songs.
[SPEAKER_06]: The theme of this mix was basically, or this contest was basically... Dude, I got eighth place in the SimFile competition.
[SPEAKER_05]: I rock.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it's basically funny songs.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was the point.
[SPEAKER_06]: So they picked funny songs, did step files for them, and right now, basically, you can go download them.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's on the front page of MyStyle, and there's reviews and discussion.
[SPEAKER_06]: So go check them out.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm sure there's another tourney mix coming and we don't care.
[SPEAKER_05]: What number tourney mix is this?
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that'd be six.
[SPEAKER_05]: What happened to tourney mix five?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, five happened.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought five happened.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't keep track of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't follow that stuff anymore.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe five didn't happen.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe it was four I'm thinking of.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, so five, tourney mix five is supposed to happen.
[SPEAKER_06]: The rules are going to get more retarded and
[SPEAKER_06]: Honestly, it's... Are they going to remove the names of the people who made the... No, no, no, the one intelligent... We've been saying this for years.
[SPEAKER_05]: The way to make Tourney Mix fair is to remove the names of the people who made the step files until the end.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the way to do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the only way you can judge fairly instead of making it just a popularity contest.
[SPEAKER_06]: But no, they're not going to do that because they're retarded.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_06]: and nothing else going on as far as Japanese mix type things.
[SPEAKER_06]: No one's really making any progress, so who knows.
[SPEAKER_06]: Everyone's busy playing games or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Should we go to a call?
[SPEAKER_05]: We're getting a call on the Skype line even though I had it turned off, but why not, huh?
[SPEAKER_05]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, why not?
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll pick up this call.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_17]: Hi, Turnimix 5 came out a while ago.
[SPEAKER_17]: I think it was last year.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can see how much... You know what, honestly, I have to admit, I kind of got off the Turnimix train a while ago just because it was kind of getting... To me, in my opinion, it was getting way overrated.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, people were taking Turnimix way too seriously.
[SPEAKER_05]: And taking the people that were successful in Turnimix way too seriously.
[SPEAKER_05]: And there would be good stuff that would be put in Turnimix that nobody would download because they didn't know the person who did it.
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't pay any attention to forum drama, I just download the actual songs and everything and delete the ones I don't like.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tons of new step files for your step mania.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'll tell you what, one other good thing about it is that I actually pick up usually a couple new good songs that I like that I wouldn't have thought to download before.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because there's a couple people out there that have similar taste in music than I do.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who would have thought?
[SPEAKER_05]: And so sometimes I find good new music through Tournament Mix.
[SPEAKER_05]: So for that, I support it, but that's about it.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, I mean, I don't even know who are on any of them because I just don't pay attention.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_17]: You know, it's just, I don't care who wins, I just care about, you know, what's there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you ever enter these things?
[SPEAKER_17]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you ever enter the competitions?
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh no, I don't make any sim files because I'm not very good.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what my problem with making sim files is?
[SPEAKER_05]: I make heavy steps, and then I don't have the time or effort to make standard or light steps.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nobody's paying me to do it, so I don't have any incentive.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then my art skills are ass-tastic.
[SPEAKER_05]: I cannot draw backgrounds for crap.
[SPEAKER_05]: And honestly, it's kind of sad, but if you have a good background, it'll make your step file ten times better in some people's opinions.
[SPEAKER_05]: So for that reason, I don't do step files.
[SPEAKER_17]: Was I supposed to identify myself?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, what's your name?
[SPEAKER_05]: GameBoyGuy13 Hello GameBoyGuy13 Are you also DSGuy13 or are you just strictly GameBoy?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't have a DS because I don't have money That's a reason that stops a lot of us from getting a DS, so I sympathize with you there I don't even have an SP, I want one but don't have one Oh no, so you're playing on an old style Advance?
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, just an Advance Do you have a backlight on it?
[SPEAKER_17]: No, it's an advance.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, yeah, but, you know, you can get those things modded, put afterburners in them.
[SPEAKER_05]: You poor guy.
[SPEAKER_05]: My God.
[SPEAKER_05]: The first wave of Game Boy Advances were bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, for that reason.
[SPEAKER_05]: It needed a backlight so bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you were a brave man for putting up with it this whole time.
[SPEAKER_17]: What's really funny is I went in a used game store and found a really old Game Boy for like five bucks.
[SPEAKER_17]: I considered buying it, but decided not to.
[SPEAKER_05]: One of the old paperweight Game Boys?
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would buy a Virtual Boy for $5 just so I can give my friends headaches.
[SPEAKER_05]: Come here, play this cool new game I got.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, I have one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you really?
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought you knew.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you have every system under the sun, so it really shouldn't be a surprise.
[SPEAKER_05]: We need to do a show at your house eventually and whip out all the old game systems and play them on air.
[SPEAKER_08]: I am not going to play the Virtual Boy.
[SPEAKER_05]: I will drink and play Virtual Boy on air.
[SPEAKER_10]: I can't play that for more than five minutes without getting a raging headache that makes me have to pass out.
[SPEAKER_05]: What games do you have?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, hell if I know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't touch the damn thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you have the Mario Crash or whatever it was?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, and Tennis and something else.
[SPEAKER_10]: I remember the old stupid commercials.
[SPEAKER_06]: By the way, yes, Loki, I forgot to mention.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tourney Mix 6 is actually going on right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they call it Tourney Mix Final because, thank God, they're not doing it anymore.
[SPEAKER_06]: Basically, it says...
[SPEAKER_06]: The deadline for registration is July 25th.
[SPEAKER_06]: Deadline for file submission is the 29th.
[SPEAKER_06]: Your basic rules format here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Score breakdown and info.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see what we got here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Load.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyways, DDR East Coast Invasion, which is a site that I haven't been to in a long time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow, and it's working so well, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyways, the info, you can find it there...
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, okay, we get it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Turnimix.
[SPEAKER_05]: It hasn't changed.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, anything else you want to share with us, Game Boy Guy?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, oh.
[SPEAKER_11]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, then, Game Boy Guy, I'm going to say goodbye.
[SPEAKER_05]: But thank you for calling in, and have a great night.
[SPEAKER_17]: Uh-huh, you too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Later.
[SPEAKER_06]: Get this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's the song restrictions and time length restrictions.
[SPEAKER_06]: You may not use the song from any of the following home or arcade games, Dance Dance Revolution, Dancing Stage Series, Pump It Up, In the Groove, Turnimix 105+, B.O.T., and additional series.
[SPEAKER_06]: You may use songs from other rhythm and game music, or rhythm and game music games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hooray, more 2DX whores.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_06]: You get penalties for using games for 2DX.
[SPEAKER_06]: You get minus 10 points penalty, popping music, minus 10, beat mania, minus 3, para, para, para, minus 2, martial beats, minus 2, um...
[SPEAKER_06]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Parappa the Rapper, Minus Two, Unjammy Lemmy, Minus Two, Frequency Minus Two, Amplitude Minus Two, Takano Tatragin, Minus Two, Guitaroman Minus Two.
[SPEAKER_05]: No minus points for Bust a Move.
[SPEAKER_06]: Remixes, though, you get plus five.
[SPEAKER_06]: Completely custom remix, plus five.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tsugaru Four, whatever, Su Four, whatever that is, plus one, basically, it's like, I don't know, B4U Max plus zero.
[SPEAKER_05]: Plus zero?
[SPEAKER_05]: What's the point?
[SPEAKER_06]: Basically, they're talking about how good the remixes are.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, yeah, whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: If it's over 2 minutes 40 seconds, you get a 5-point deduction, and it keeps going up from there.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just like...
[SPEAKER_06]: Basically, they score you on background animations, one point.
[SPEAKER_06]: Movies, one point.
[SPEAKER_06]: Challenge steps, one point.
[SPEAKER_06]: These are additional to what you're doing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Beginning steps, you get another point.
[SPEAKER_06]: Double steps, you get one to four points.
[SPEAKER_06]: Lyrics, one to four points.
[SPEAKER_06]: Breakdowns, it says all entries are counted and checked for correct file formatting errors.
[SPEAKER_06]: Entries are then randomly sorted in the brackets.
[SPEAKER_06]: Each week, a bracket will be released to the public.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it says...
[SPEAKER_06]: Public will have no say in the first round.
[SPEAKER_06]: Public's sway has been removed.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_06]: The number of judges will be working on 10 points for light, 25 for standard, 50 for heavy, 5 points for appropriate danceable step file, 5 points for readme, 5 points for background and banner.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you get 80 points, it grants you to the next round.
[SPEAKER_06]: Total of 100 extra entries plus 5 penalties minus 35.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's basically... Anyways, I'm just trying to see how... I was trying to see if they had the actual... whether or not the people's names would be displayed, but it does not say, so I'm going to have to assume that's a yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you're really interested, ddrei.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's the last one, thank God.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: You guys want to hear who won tonight's cage match?
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tonight was a landslide victory, by the way.
[SPEAKER_05]: We haven't had one of these in a while.
[SPEAKER_05]: We've had a lot of ties lately, but tonight was a freaking landslide.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yep, it sure was.
[SPEAKER_05]: So here it is, tonight's winner, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ozzy Osbourne.
[SPEAKER_05]: Stayin' alive.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sheep, all of you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: All aboard the disco train!
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sharon!
[SPEAKER_03]: Sharon!
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, let's take a break.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to take a break.
[SPEAKER_05]: When we come back, we'll get into the FUs of the week, most definitely.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, if somebody else wants to give us a call via Skype, talk about Happy Sky a little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: And whatever else we can dig out of our butts when we come back from this break.
[SPEAKER_05]: Lots of poo.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's start off with this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some poor person in the chatroom has been begging me to play this song all night long.
[SPEAKER_05]: So here it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to start it out with a song called 12th Style, which is what the game should be called.
[SPEAKER_05]: Damn it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So here it is, 12th Style.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll be back with more.
[SPEAKER_05]: Happy Orange Lounge Radio after this.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, what did you think of that song?
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought it was lame.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's some Akira Yamaoka then.
DarkSakura
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: Have you ever walked into Radio Shack and hit the demo button on all the keyboards?
[SPEAKER_05]: So that you have like 60 keyboard demos all playing over the top of each other all at once.
[SPEAKER_10]: That sounded like yuck.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what that song sounded like to me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Honestly, that sounded like me playing the keyboard.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I can't play the keyboard, so that's what it would sound like.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was just a bunch of random notes and beats.
[SPEAKER_06]: It just had nothing to... It was not even a song.
[SPEAKER_06]: Needs more cowbell.
[SPEAKER_06]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: Needs less suckiness.
[SPEAKER_06]: Where they have some... I had my cat walk across the keyboard.
[SPEAKER_05]: One more song to go, please.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good, cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_14]: and beyond which there is so much more.
I know it's hard to really love someone It takes a long time to trust someone But I don't care how long it will take My love is of so much So be brave and let me show you
[SPEAKER_22]: Hi, we're back with more Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was an okay song, that good, cool, except you could totally tell that that was a key sound rip from the game because, like, the singing sound.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's pretty bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: First Resolution was the name of that song.
[SPEAKER_05]: 100% Mini Moog was the one that sounded like 60 RadioShack keyboard demos all going over each other.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Akira Yamaoka, Empty of the Sky, which I kind of like that song, I dig that.
[SPEAKER_05]: And we're Akira Yamaoka whores here, so we have to play all of his new songs every day.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then 12th Style, of course, starting that set off, which Loki didn't like.
[SPEAKER_05]: He just wanted to share that with you guys, he didn't like that one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Skypline's open because I know we had at least one more personal one to get in, so call in.
[SPEAKER_05]: During the break there, it was being suggested, and now they're telling me to talk about this, it was being suggested that if Konami were to continue DDR, they should put out, which we really hope they do in the arcades, but they should put out DDR ABBA mix, which would be nothing but ABBA songs.
[SPEAKER_10]: They already canceled the SMOP mix.
[SPEAKER_05]: SMOP?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's basically the Japanese version of Medudo.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, it was in the works a few years ago and they axed it.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what was funny?
[SPEAKER_05]: You heard all that news about Live 8, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: I tried to ignore all of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, Dreams Come True played the Japanese Live 8 and that just made me laugh for some reason, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was like, oh, Dreams Come True, they're still around, who knew?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, you're on Orange Songs Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Guy, Siggy here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello, Siggy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, it's my pronunciation hero.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's new with you?
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, I'm just gonna, first of all, Sky, it's not Daisuki, it's Daisuke.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like Daisuki.
[SPEAKER_15]: Actually, it's not a ke, it is a ki.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's ke, Daisuke.
[SPEAKER_10]: There is not a ke sound in a ki spelling.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello, it's Japanese.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know, and the I ones are all i, a, i, u, e, o, ma, mi, mu, me, mo, ta, chi, tu, te, to, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right!
[SPEAKER_05]: I see.
[SPEAKER_05]: So what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_05]: What did you call in to talk to us about tonight?
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, I just want to say, you know, I just want to pronounce the songs on Happy Sky Daughter in Japanese.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_05]: And what songs are these that you want to share with us?
[SPEAKER_15]: The artist's name is Chonan Chiharu, and the song title is Rakuen, which means paradise.
[SPEAKER_15]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_15]: And then, well, this one's not really Japanese, but, you know, it's a very hard, you know, pronunciation, very foreign one, which is the Akira Yamaoka song is Ton Pi Pour Trois.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right, which is kind of more French than anything else.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, and thanks to Sakurina, she corrected me on what it means.
[SPEAKER_15]: It means too bad for you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Too bad for you.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is a little bit of that song there.
[SPEAKER_05]: We played that a little earlier in the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_15]: And then there's by Tomosuke.
[SPEAKER_15]: The song title is Tizona del Cid.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, we have a little bit of that one here too.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a little jazzy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Come on down and play 2DX Happy Sky.
[SPEAKER_05]: All this can be yours if you put in a quarter.
[SPEAKER_15]: And then there's Captivate Joker.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, we have a little piece of that song.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_15]: Which is the remix of the 2DX Red ending.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought this sounded a little bit familiar when I first heard it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was like, where have I heard this before?
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: And then there's the one by Hoshino Kanako is Gekko, which means moonlight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who did that one?
[SPEAKER_15]: I think, I believe it was by Hoshino Kanako.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if I have that one handy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, but okay, so there's that one.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, and then the E-Amusement songs.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I don't even know if I have those.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_15]: Agnus Dei by Asaki.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, okay, I do have that one.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I do have some of these E-Amuse songs.
[SPEAKER_05]: Goodie.
[SPEAKER_15]: Speaking of Asaki, the Guitar Freaks Drum Mania artist, Asaki, is currently working on an album.
[SPEAKER_15]: His very first project album.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, which is scheduled to be released September 16th.
[SPEAKER_15]: Also, Good Cool.
[SPEAKER_15]: Good Cool is also making Greatest Hits.
[SPEAKER_05]: A Greatest Hits Album Yeah, I think I saw it on KonamiStyle Oh, what's that?
[SPEAKER_05]: I've been following that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, Double... Okay, what's that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah
[SPEAKER_15]: I'll just mention all of them in order.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's Ace, Double Ace, Blocks, Colors Radio Edit, Fake Time, Gigadelic, Innocent Walls, Moonchild, One More Lovely, 108, Piano Kyosok Kyoku Daichiba Sasoribi, or Piano Concerto Anti-Ares, or Scorpion Fire, Please Don't Go, Sakura... Really?
[SPEAKER_05]: Please Don't Go is a new one, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_15]: Sakura, Setsugekka, Spyka, Stoick, and lastly V
[SPEAKER_05]: Samurai, Ace, Double Ace, Blox, Cheer Train, Dixie, or DXY Dixie?
[SPEAKER_05]: I've never heard it pronounced Dixie.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's actually pronounced Dixie.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh my god, but if I were to call it Dixie, I'd think... Which is so not the song.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't call it Dixie, I can't, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's going to have to stay in Japan.
[SPEAKER_15]: It doesn't matter, it doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, alright, fine.
[SPEAKER_15]: And then Era Stepmix, Big Time, G2, Garden, Genocide, Ghost Revival, Holic, Inazuma...
[SPEAKER_15]: Innocent Walls, Jam, Kakumei, Karma, Lesson 5, Logic Board, Love is Eternity, Lower World, Minimalian, Nemesis, Number 13, One More Lovely, Piano Kiyosaki, Daichiban Sasoribi, Wazor, I'm just kidding, Wristlim Remix, Sakura, Setsugekka, Sig Sig, Sphere, Spike, Spica, Starmind, Stoic, and Zephyr.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a shitload of flashing 12s on doubles, but you know doubles is some scary shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you play doubles at all?
[SPEAKER_15]: I've never played doubles.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm trying to play on normal when I have another controller.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm waiting for it for the US release.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what, that's why I've been kind of holding off on playing the 2DX at home lately, because I'm holding off, because my controller sucks balls.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm looking forward to being able to get cheap controllers here, because I'm thinking, what, the controllers here are going to cost, what, maybe $39.95?
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know, don't quote me on this.
[SPEAKER_10]: You think more?
[SPEAKER_10]: I can get confirmation very soon on that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really?
[SPEAKER_05]: You've got some hookup I don't know about.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, that's because they send price lists to GameStop before they put the stuff out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Find that shit out.
[SPEAKER_05]: For pre-orders.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Really?
[SPEAKER_10]: More than $40 for the controller?
[SPEAKER_10]: I would think so.
[SPEAKER_10]: Logically, I would think so.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hope not.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know some other company is going to put out a cheap one, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, of course, you have to go the regular Konami one because the other ones are going to suck.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, wait a second, I'll get the prices of them off Konami Style.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, there were rumors going around that they were going to improve the controller when they released it here.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if that's still true, but that would be nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to cost a significant amount, I'll put it that way.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, damn.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, sorry about that, Siggy, we just had to have that little discussion.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's alright, that's alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have you heard anything about the 2DX controllers being released over here?
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, no, none so far.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I can tell you at E3 they just had the Japanese ones.
[SPEAKER_05]: I looked, I looked, I wanted to see if it was different, but it was just the regular Japanese ones.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, I saw.
[SPEAKER_15]: And from what I've heard, from what I've read on the Japanese forums and message boards, Eden is the continuation of the video doll.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what somebody was saying in the chat room earlier.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if that was you or somebody else.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've heard about that, and a lot of the anime fanboys especially really like the doll videos.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's good.
[SPEAKER_05]: One of my favorite parts of 2DX is the videos, so I really like hearing when they do...
[SPEAKER_05]: I just read something interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think this is a goalie art book.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I heard about this.
[SPEAKER_10]: Konami style.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, that's good.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm not bringing up any images right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Isn't that going to be a great coffee table book to have?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, it'll have to go with my DDR second mixed step book.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, anything else on your mind today, Siggy?
[SPEAKER_15]: One more thing.
[SPEAKER_15]: The videos for e-amusement songs like Agnes Day and Pink Rose and stuff, they were actually recycled from Guitar Fix Drum Mania.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, so the Guitar Fix, okay, that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_15]: And then Pink Rose, I saw the video, and it's like a modified version from the keyboard mania.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I mean, it's okay for them to recycle stuff if, you know, it's good stuff to begin with.
[SPEAKER_15]: And then for Votum Stellarum, it's an original.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, cool.
[SPEAKER_15]: And then they, whatchamacallit, they gathered all the videos from DJ Taka.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_15]: Like, they mixed them all in one, and then in the last part...
[SPEAKER_15]: They just featured the video for V where Tran is walking down the spiral staircase.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's the last part for Votum Stellarum, the video.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, well, I can see that.
[SPEAKER_05]: That kind of fits.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_05]: Pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm hoping that a Happy Sky Machine shows up nearby at some point.
[SPEAKER_05]: And by nearby, I mean if I have to go to SoCal to play it, then I do.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I can check this out, because I want to see this.
[SPEAKER_05]: I still have not played 2DX Red, really.
[SPEAKER_15]: But we won't be able to see the e-amusement songs, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yeah, because that whole hookup is missing here.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: It kind of sucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, thanks for the call, Siggy.
[SPEAKER_05]: I always appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_05]: As always, you stay on top of the 2DX stuff more than we do, so we appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, take care, bud.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, later.
[SPEAKER_05]: Later.
[SPEAKER_05]: Our buddy Siggy there from Vegas calling in to talk about 2DX.
[SPEAKER_05]: And of course the chat room is yelling, what about ToeJam?
[SPEAKER_05]: What about ToeJam?
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course, ToeJam being a transplant song from Ultramix 2, which was kind of one of the weird ones there.
[SPEAKER_05]: ToeJam is also an EMU song.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I know that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know that's what I meant.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, anyway, I think it's about time to get into the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is the part of the show where we get downright angsty.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because we're mad, we're upset, grr.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, DarkSakura, why is it that we do... By the way, if you guys have your own FUs, you can send them in right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: But DarkSakura, why is it that we do these FUs of the week every single week?
[SPEAKER_14]: Uh...
[SPEAKER_10]: My first FU goes toward having to sit at family functions with a bunch of people I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: With many people in there.
[SPEAKER_10]: In the more wealthy part of the area.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't want to be wealthy.
[SPEAKER_10]: I would rather be comfortable and happy and be a real person, you know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, they're nice and everything.
[SPEAKER_10]: Don't get me wrong.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're nice.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're great people.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just don't think that I could stand having to keep up illusions all the time.
[SPEAKER_10]: if I had a bunch of money, I don't think I would act like it
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean just in here I know, I know, but we got the air conditioner going, doing the best we can Another FU goes towards my hoid digestion problems That's it, I'm done Oh yeah, this book is, you know, FU to my fiance Freaking finishing a book before me Butthead, I told you to wait Dang, that was quick
[SPEAKER_10]: I would have read it this fast, I've just had other real life things to do.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm reading it right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good participation tonight, by the way.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, I'm participating and reading.
[SPEAKER_05]: I am talented.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're multitasking.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, multitasking.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like a Mac.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like a Mac, except I'm a lot cooler.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, let's get to Loki's FUs of the week then.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm a good driver.
[SPEAKER_06]: Before you start saying that, listen, okay, I said most of the population.
[SPEAKER_06]: Unless you want to, you know, make noise and put yourself as part of that, you know, percentage, then no.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is especially appalling because, you know, I'm always wondering why the problem isn't solved around here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, today, on my way over to the studio, there was a cop that pulled out in front of me.
[SPEAKER_06]: First blew through the red light like nothing.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm talking about not stopping under red to make a right-hand turn, just, you know, completely blown through, cutting me off.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which is fine, it's a cop, you know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Then she proceeds to get into the right turn lane, to which then she goes straight cutting me off again.
[SPEAKER_06]: Then she goes and makes another right-hand turn without stopping at all at the stop sign, and flips a bitch right there in the middle of the street, and guess what?
[SPEAKER_06]: She's on her fucking cell phone.
[SPEAKER_06]: A goddamn cop!
[SPEAKER_06]: Fuck you, Sacramento PD, and your stupid female cop that was driving down, you know, the road here.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, god damn it, you guys are supposed to set an example of what's right, and here she's violating all the traffic laws, going, I'm talking on my cell phone, you know, the hell with you people, no wonder your problem's not getting solved, I'm gonna talk to my congressman, god damn it, and get that stupid cell phone law passed.
[SPEAKER_06]: Then we'll work on the female driving issue.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fuck you to the fact that my air conditioning's not working in our apartment.
[SPEAKER_06]: For some reason, I think there's a leak in the Freon hose, because they filled it up about a month ago, and now there's none.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, that would lead me to believe that either there's some Freon fairy that's stealing the Freon in the middle of the night, or there might be a hole in the hose, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: So, well, that sucks.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, luckily for me, though, I have to babysit the dog.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which brings me to my next FU, because that stupid dog wants to wake me up three times during the night because it's used to a routine.
[SPEAKER_06]: That routine being to wake me up three times during the night and piss me off.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fucking hate that dog.
[SPEAKER_06]: I gotta do this for a week.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then finally, fuck you to the people that made the stupid Hanzo the Razor movie because no samurai movie should be about some guy that mutilates his penis to then to have sex with women to interrogate them.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's not a samurai movie, that's a porno movie.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't get too confused.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's all.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to give an F you to the fact that I'm total retard in general.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, but when it comes to hooking up the Xbox to the new HDTV, because I use the Xbox as a DVD player, because believe it or not, the Xbox actually makes a pretty decent DVD player, but I cannot for the life of me figure out how to get Component and get the really pretty HD picture via the Xbox.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I went to GameStop and they didn't know, and I went to RadioShack and they didn't know, and I went to Target and, well, shit, they're never any help.
[SPEAKER_06]: to buy the component cables.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, neither of these stores, none of these stores have them for the Xbox, and I'm starting to wonder if they even exist, so I have to do research online later.
[SPEAKER_05]: Somebody in the chatroom needs to help me out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Got a Best Buy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I'm thinking Best Buy might have them, so I'll check that out a little later.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, so an F you to that.
[SPEAKER_05]: An F you to Impulse Buying.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't believe they don't have them at GameStop.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've seen them there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, they didn't have it at this one, so F you to this GameStop.
[SPEAKER_05]: And an F you to Impulse Buying, because I just bought a multi-hundred dollar TV today.
[SPEAKER_05]: But that's alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: I deserved it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was a good boy this year, and I deserved a good present.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's kind of a late birthday present to myself, really.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, um... Gosh, I think that's really it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, oh, oh.
[SPEAKER_05]: F you to the impending nurses strike at UC Davis, because it's going to postpone my dad's surgery again.
[SPEAKER_05]: Again, for the second time.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I realize, you know, nurses, they need their rights and everything, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: So just F you to the timing of the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, just screwing it all up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Especially those male nurses.
[SPEAKER_05]: Stop it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, let's get to the chatroom FUs, shall we?
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see... Rini would like to give an FU to my PlayStation 2 for screwing up my speedruns in Katamari Damacy, because the analog feature kept dying on my brand new controller.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sakura S1N F you to my nephew for being a retard and just being a stupid dumbass
[SPEAKER_05]: Misty would like to say, fuck the person that broke the subwoofer caging on the Indigroup 2 dedicated cabinet at tea time.
[SPEAKER_05]: If I ever find out who it was and I actually meet them, there's gonna be hell to pay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Especially if it's somewhere that's not one of my arcades.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hope they decide to keep the machine, and one goes to Loki, because as I typed this out, I was thinking he's probably gonna laugh or something when he hears this.
[SPEAKER_05]: He actually just ran to the bathroom, so he got away with it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Misty says, also, I want to pass this one along from a friend that doesn't have IRC.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fuck all the Harry Potter spoilers.
[SPEAKER_10]: Double amen to that, although I've been lucky.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sakurina is a guy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Says, F you to myself for eating too much tonight and suffering a stomach ache.
[SPEAKER_05]: An F you to the heat here, especially since we celebrated Christmas today early.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's kind of early.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jammer J would like to send an F you to roof repairs after hurricanes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ouch.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry to hear about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Reznor says an insane fuck you to Sony for making it so damn hard to become a Jedi in Star Wars Galaxies.
[SPEAKER_05]: And fuck you to the Mac haters out there.
[SPEAKER_05]: You hear that?
[SPEAKER_05]: And fuck you to Logitech for making a shitty joystick that doesn't work worth anything.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm so sorry if I fuck up this pronunciation.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kamui, Kamui, Kamui, 988 says, I say F you to being broke and my laggy as hell Windows computer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, my laggy XP craptacular computer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Illusion, we have a lot of FU's tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Illusion says, FU to getting a fever this weekend and not being able to go to a party.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was lame being sick.
[SPEAKER_05]: GameBoyGuy13 wants to just give an FU to Max.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ron Chan would like to say, FU to my family for being dipshits all you die already.
[SPEAKER_05]: FU to my friend Carmen for only showing up in the city every six months and hanging out with her causing me to miss most of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Visit more, woman!
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that Carmen San Diego?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I don't think it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: VidPower would like to say, can F you to lint?
[SPEAKER_05]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_05]: Lint is annoying.
[SPEAKER_05]: Where does lint come from?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what I want to know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I never really bothered to read on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: But where?
[SPEAKER_06]: The lint wasn't on the shirt when I bought it.
[SPEAKER_06]: You notice how your shirts become a little bit thin and you can start seeing through them?
[SPEAKER_05]: F you to whoever can't design a shirt right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Last up, DarkSetsuya says, F you to whatever's causing the voices to be really quiet on Fox.
[SPEAKER_06]: So guess what?
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe it's time to stop watching Family Guy.
[SPEAKER_06]: I ran in there to watch a part of Family Guy.
[SPEAKER_06]: God damn you!
[SPEAKER_06]: And they were talking about how Peter is fascinated with the world of never-ending story.
[SPEAKER_06]: And he was riding Falcor and he was too heavy so Falcor crashed into the ground.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's hilarious.
[SPEAKER_05]: Will you stop giving free plugs to the competition?
[SPEAKER_05]: I love that show!
[SPEAKER_05]: Family Guy is our competition now.
[SPEAKER_05]: You must hate it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I watch every episode.
[SPEAKER_06]: on repeats on the internet.
[SPEAKER_05]: On BitTorrent, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: On BitTorrent.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's TiVo.
[SPEAKER_06]: I call it TiVo.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to go to a quick break.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just a couple songs.
[SPEAKER_05]: Then we're going to come back and we're going to do some Ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's your guys' chance to control the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I notice we have a lot of new listeners tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm wondering if that's coming from the podcast or what.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's your chance to ask us any question you want within reason.
[SPEAKER_05]: Keep it clean.
[SPEAKER_05]: Speaking of which...
[SPEAKER_06]: Go to podcastawards.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: You'll notice at the bottom of the page to the right, you'll see the best video game podcast.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, oh, look in there.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's Orange Laundry as it goes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Vote with every single email address that you have.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: Be careful because I don't want us to get disqualified.
[SPEAKER_05]: So if you just remember to vote every day, just use one email address is enough.
[SPEAKER_05]: Honestly, it really is.
[SPEAKER_05]: You don't have to worry about the multiple.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is that okay?
[SPEAKER_05]: Just get all of your friends to vote too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, that's it.
[SPEAKER_05]: You don't have to use multiple.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just get your friends to vote from their IP addresses.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the key.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, it's fine.
[SPEAKER_18]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, you should check out our podcast anyway in general because it's really cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you can subscribe on iTunes and it's so easy.
[SPEAKER_05]: All you have to do is do a search for Orange Lounge and we show up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Imagine that.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, listen to us.
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't hear that.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you do a search for DarkSakura, all one word, on Google Images, the third picture you come up with is my cat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do they get any pictures of you?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I think our listeners are curious what you look like.
[SPEAKER_05]: They've been wanting to see your picture for forever.
[SPEAKER_10]: All they have to do is pull up iTunes and look at our little picture there.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can see a little teeny tiny 50, or not even 50 by 50, teeny tiny picture.
[SPEAKER_10]: When I get back from my special break, I will post a picture in the chat room.
Yay!
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, we'll be back.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to play a song.
[SPEAKER_05]: I feel like, I want to hear something from Red.
[SPEAKER_05]: Since we've been playing Happy Sky all night, I want to hear some Red.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we're going to get to Kikak.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kikak.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll be back after this.
Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_22]: Please listen to Orange Lounge Radio because real radio makes Captain Jack cry.
[SPEAKER_05]: We are back here on Orange Lounge Radio, and it's time to get into some Ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_05]: But first, actually, what I wanted to state, this is a response to something that was said in the chat room like an hour ago, but I forgot to respond to it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Somebody was mentioning a Magical Drop 3 tournament, and I was like, oh my god, Magical Drop is like one of my favorite puzzle games ever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, it's right up there with like Meteos.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, I have that on Neo Geo CD.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have Magical Drop on my cell phone.
[SPEAKER_05]: How hardcore is that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Give me some credit.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love Magical Drop.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, I just wanted to say that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Too much metal for one hand.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's get into some... Oh, by the way, in that break we had Kakak from 2DX Red, Everyday Lovely Day, my favorite consumer song.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love that song.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Dixie.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I'm sorry, I can't do it without laughing.
[SPEAKER_05]: DXY, all in that break.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I knew if we didn't get in some taku that our one and only DarkSakura would be very upset.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I would have screamed bloody murder and murdered everybody.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have a freaking ton of questions tonight in Ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_05]: Are you ready for this?
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's ask Orange Lounge some stupid question.
[SPEAKER_05]: What will we find out this week on Orange Lounge Radio?
[SPEAKER_05]: I have to admit I'm a little bit scared because there's new people listening tonight and who knows what they might submit.
[SPEAKER_05]: It might be questions we've heard a thousand times.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a different song every time.
[SPEAKER_06]: We need to make one long compilation of all this.
[SPEAKER_10]: I am officially halfway through the book.
[SPEAKER_10]: I like that it has purple text on black on the spine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rini is asking about, could you elaborate more on Togo's presence at E3?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the first I'm hearing about him being there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, Togo was there.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know why he was there.
[SPEAKER_05]: I imagine, I think it has something to do with Beatmania being in the US.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think he might be a part of that.
[SPEAKER_05]: please don't quote me on that, I think I had heard something about that he's kind of a part of that, which makes sense, because he's been kind of heavy in the Japanese consumer style side, but I did get my picture with him so when I finally stopped being lazy and put up my picture gallery, which maybe I'll do tonight if I can tear myself away from my new HDTV he was there, Sana was not, Akira Yamoko was not there this year, which made me a little sad, so Togo was kind of the token Bomani artist that was there, but he wasn't doing any type of talks or anything like that so, that's all we know
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to be launching a retro lunch program here on the station very soon.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to play the greatest in 8 and 16-bit music.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have all the 8-bit music done.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just need to get the 16-bit music done, and then we're ready to go.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, all right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see, GameBoyGuy13 wanted a clarification on that site where we could vote.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was PodcastAwards.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: Although also, if you want to be so kind, PodcastAlley.com has a voting system, A-L-L-E-Y.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the more people that vote for us there, just do a search for Orange Lounge, the higher ranked we are and the more attention we get.
[SPEAKER_05]: And again, we here at Orange Lounge Radio, we like attention.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Socorino wants to know, what do you think the next 2DX style will be called?
[SPEAKER_05]: Since there is, you know, Happy Sky, 2DX Red, what do you think the next one will be called?
[SPEAKER_06]: 2DX 13.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just 13.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkLionXVI, also known as Siggy, just wanted to point out that I mispronounced K-K-K because I just like saying it that way.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's actually K-Chak.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: JammerJ wants to know... Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was a request.
[SPEAKER_05]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not a question.
Whoops.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_05]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_05]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's all the questions we've gotten so far.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I guess that's it for Ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess so.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're reading some other things in the chat room there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: 2DX Violet is a suggestion there.
[SPEAKER_05]: 2DX X2.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then they're back to talking about Harry Potter, so go figure.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just, I couldn't.
[SPEAKER_05]: Get into the Harry Potter books.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have RDD.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have Reading Deficit Disorder.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't read the big books.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_05]: I try.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the weird thing is I used to when I was a kid all the time.
[SPEAKER_05]: I used to read Judy Blume.
[SPEAKER_05]: I used to read R.L.
[SPEAKER_05]: Stine.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Ramona Quimby books.
[SPEAKER_05]: Come on, those things were the shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't roll your eyes at me!
[SPEAKER_09]: I can roll my eyes at whoever I want to!
[SPEAKER_05]: Ramona was the shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Reznor wants to know, what is your favorite Magical Drop 3 character?
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, actually, most of the Magical Drop I played was number 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't really play number 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't know there was a...
[SPEAKER_05]: for number three yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I haven't really played much of three, just two.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I don't really know the characters that well.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just play it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Rini wants to know pancakes or waffles?
[SPEAKER_05]: Waffles.
[SPEAKER_05]: Neither.
[SPEAKER_05]: Belgium waffles.
[SPEAKER_05]: Waffle House waffles.
[SPEAKER_05]: The peanut butter and banana waffle from the country, what was that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Country waffles?
[SPEAKER_05]: Not Waffle House.
[SPEAKER_05]: We don't have those here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Country waffles.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is the banana and peanut butter or the
[SPEAKER_05]: Love it!
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, that's going to do it for another episode of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you for listening and tuning in to us and listening to our show and our rants and our raves.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now it's time to go around and get everybody's final thought.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, your final thought tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: My final thought is this week's going to suck.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why?
[SPEAKER_06]: Reject false icons and people stop getting in my way of me reading the book.
[SPEAKER_05]: My final thought is I'm going to go play with my new television.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to go play Xbox really big.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can't wait.
[SPEAKER_05]: And 2DX.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm still playing 2DX tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: I played Guitar Man on mine.
[SPEAKER_08]: How was that?
[SPEAKER_08]: 50 inches of Guitar Man goodness.
[SPEAKER_05]: I actually have a widescreen TV.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have to set your PlayStation option to the widescreen.
[SPEAKER_05]: I won't forget.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because it'll look kind of funky if you just do it on TV.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, but I'm going to play 2DX widescreen and I'm going to probably...
[SPEAKER_05]: Spill beer in my pants.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can also do Ultramix in widescreen.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think Ultramix supports HD.
[SPEAKER_05]: That made me sad.
[SPEAKER_05]: I looked on the back.
[SPEAKER_05]: It doesn't support HD.
[SPEAKER_10]: But the thing is that for the PS2, you have an option in your menu to change the graphic option.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can't wait.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Final word of the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: One word to sum the whole damn thing up for everybody.
[SPEAKER_05]: Happy episode 150, you guys, by the way.
[SPEAKER_05]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think this should be the last one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's finish.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're done.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, we'll be back next week with episode 151, and then we're going on vacation for a little while.
[SPEAKER_05]: At least I am, so I think that means we all are, unless one of you guys is going to be doing a show for your house.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll talk about that later.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe we should do like a...
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a countdown episode.
[SPEAKER_05]: Countdown episode?
[SPEAKER_05]: Can we just get on the air?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll work on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: 5, 4, 3, uh, uh, uh.
29! 28!
[SPEAKER_05]: How about when the doors close, you just say go?
[SPEAKER_05]: Go!
[SPEAKER_05]: The chat room wants me to remind you all of Channel Oregon Trail, a brand new station.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe we should start Oregon Trail Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_05]: And now the dysentery song.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Join the Oregon Trail Channel.
[SPEAKER_05]: It owns your soul.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Final word of the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: One word to sum it all up.
[SPEAKER_05]: TV spot soon.
[SPEAKER_22]: And now, here is your fortune cookie message of the day.
[SPEAKER_16]: Hello, my name is Susuki Gangura.
[SPEAKER_16]: I love hair extensions, platform boots, and fun time happiness.
[SPEAKER_16]: My favorite band is Gorillaz.
[SPEAKER_16]: Their debut album is now out.
[SPEAKER_16]: You can listen to it on Clinton Eastwood, Nike 2000, Lock the House, and Tomorrow Comes Today.
[SPEAKER_16]: Thank you very much for listening, and we'll see you next week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, off to go tape our podcast where we won't talk about Bomani much to the disappointment of Rini who asked me earlier this evening why we don't talk about Bomani on our podcast.
[SPEAKER_05]: We do once in a while but we just try to be a little different on the podcast.
[SPEAKER_05]: We talk about games that don't suck and some that do.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we're off to go do that and we'll see you guys later but for right now you guys are getting booted from the stream because we're going back to our Bomani Music and More program.
[SPEAKER_05]: So reconnect to the stream in about 15 seconds or so and