We're male, we're male for the night I'm forever hiding out Take it or let on your star
[SPEAKER_17]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_23]: The following live program is a special presentation of Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_06]: It is time for another episode of Orange Lounge Radio on tonight's program.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to talk about another podcast that we fully endorse that you all should go check out.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're also going to have Orange Lounge Day at the Movies.
[SPEAKER_06]: And today's movie clip features us!
[SPEAKER_06]: This should be interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is brand new, by the way.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have not even looked at this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I saw it when it was on TV, but I have not looked at the digitized format of it, so we're going to check that out very soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: And remember, kids, podcasting is fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll be back after this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Orange Lounge Radio is presented in the TMI sound format.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_16]: Call me Daddy.
[SPEAKER_26]: Orange Lounge may contain adult content.
[SPEAKER_26]: Orange Lounge may contain many four-letter words.
[SPEAKER_26]: Orange Lounge may contain a scene of nudity.
[SPEAKER_26]: Orange Lounge may contain plenty of... Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_06]: Orange Lounge Radio will not contain any of that in this episode.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, isn't that special?
[SPEAKER_25]: Orange Lounge Radio Live is a fully interactive program via our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com And now, here are your hosts for Orange Lounge Radio Live, DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: We are live!
[SPEAKER_06]: This is episode number 151 for this podcast.
[SPEAKER_06]: July 24, 2005.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're tuned in to Orange Lounge Radio, radio that gamers really want.
[SPEAKER_06]: And this is Orange Lounge Radio Live, your home for all the news and discussion on rhythm and music games, as well as the gamer community and the pop culture world.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're plugged in and fully interactive through our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com My name is Rob Roberts, you might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_06]: Joining me as always are my awesome co-hosts.
[SPEAKER_06]: In this corner, the happiest bunny on the farm, Miss Jamie Summers, also known as DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, she's not here.
[SPEAKER_06]: She's running a little late tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: She had some family business she had to take care of.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hopefully everything's okay, but she's going to be here a little bit later on, just so you know.
[SPEAKER_06]: However, we do have the one and only Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: I am here.
[SPEAKER_06]: And not in the cushion of the seat.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was very good timing, by the way, finding your microphone.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, Jamie should be sitting on both of the microphones then.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not sure.
[SPEAKER_06]: It probably got put there during the party last night.
[SPEAKER_06]: We had a little bit of a house party last night.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe I shouldn't be talking with this microphone against my mouth.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that the loud, sensitive one?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, who knows?
[SPEAKER_06]: No?
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, so Loki's here, and then special guest-wise, we have nobody.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, what the hell happened?
[SPEAKER_06]: We used to have special guests here every single week.
[SPEAKER_06]: There'd be somebody here, and lately, nobody loves us anymore.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is it because we're in this new place?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't get it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Something's weird.
[SPEAKER_06]: Can they give him bad directions?
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess so.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like I lied to him about where I live or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh well.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fine, see if we care.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll just sit here and do the show ourselves.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we have some fun stuff to talk about tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: We were famous this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you know, we're always famous.
[SPEAKER_06]: But no, we were on local news this week, so we have to show that clip later in the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which makes for great radio, by the way, showing video clips.
[SPEAKER_06]: But even the audio of it is going to be pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki's bit in it is priceless.
[SPEAKER_06]: Love it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we'll be airing that for you guys, and telling you guys how you can get a copy of the video, because some of you guys are asking about that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just like Publish Media, too, you'll get the best of me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, last time when we were in the paper, it was your foot.
[SPEAKER_06]: More of my foot in this one, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: They actually, well, we'll get to that later.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, we'll get to that a little later.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also, we gotta talk about our buddy MidiHead.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's been doing some fun stuff this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: And we'll play a little clip of his new Ultramix 3 song, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't want to play the whole thing...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_17]: Mr. Night, you make me cry, I need your love
Listen to the song, the melody will set you free.
[SPEAKER_17]: You need my love, it's in your mind.
[SPEAKER_17]: I need you, I love you, I can't sleep with you.
[SPEAKER_17]: You gotta save your life.
The night makes me cry.
I need your love, it's in my mind.
I need you, I love you, I can't sleep with you.
Listen to the song.
Thank you for watching.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_17]: From Step Squad to Orange Lounge, this PDR sucks!
[SPEAKER_17]: Holla, holla, holla, holla, holla, holla, holla, holla, holla, holla, holla, holla Welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think I threw up in my mouth a little bit during that last break.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: We had some vomit-inducing songs.
[SPEAKER_06]: Admit it, there's at least one song you hated in that last break.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think
[SPEAKER_06]: I think during that break we'd have people in the chatroom be like, Oh, I love that song!
[SPEAKER_06]: And then there'd be other people going, God, I hate that song.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then during the next song, it would switch around.
[SPEAKER_06]: Cartoon Heroes by Barbie Young.
[SPEAKER_06]: Speed Over Beethoven by Rose.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nori Nori Nori, Judy Crystal, and Living in America from DDR Max 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I don't remember the artist on that because I'm too lazy to look it up.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I never play that song, so I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh well.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we're here with another show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, hello!
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's the lovely DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_06]: She's here.
[SPEAKER_06]: And we were about ready to chat about what's going on in the Bomani world.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, before that, though, we always have to start off each week's show with a little bit of, How was your week?
[SPEAKER_06]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_06]: And DarkSakura just joined us.
[SPEAKER_14]: She usually starts us off, so... I'd rather not talk about my week, thanks.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, then we'll move on to Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: My week was hot.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's hot.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, it's because...
[SPEAKER_05]: The air conditioning is broken for a week, so that sucked.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I have a house with a dog, my mom's dog, and that sucked also.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, um, what else?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, just a lot of sucking.
[SPEAKER_05]: Basically, you know, staying at my mom's house sucked because she is on dial-up and no one likes dial-up.
[SPEAKER_05]: And also the fact that the dog, you know, wants constant attention all the time, including at 3 in the morning, and it's just, you know, very tiring.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then I finally get home...
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, on Friday, you know, okay, I'm done.
[SPEAKER_05]: Finally, you know, the apartment complex has had a week to fix their, you know, AC.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nope, nope, nope, they're not done yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're not going to be done until Monday.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, all weekend, it's been like 95 degrees in the apartment.
[SPEAKER_05]: What are they having to do for your AC?
[SPEAKER_05]: They replaced the whole thing, the whole entire unit, and then they said they clogged something, so they've got to do something on... Jesus.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm like, oh, God, you're fucking retarded.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: Your situation is starting to sound like the plot of Dark Water.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's about more than a mold spot.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is, but that's where they try to get the scares wrong.
[SPEAKER_05]: with mold, you know, cause that killer mold, the black mold, it's always gotta be the black mold, you know, what do they got against the black mold?
[SPEAKER_05]: So yeah, basically, um, it sucked a lot, and then, um, I don't know, then the rest of the week was just basically, um, you know, work stuff, playing PSP, played more Killer7, and that type of thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: My week and my day was okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nothing to scream about, really.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's been very hot here in the city, so it makes you not want to go out and do a lot.
[SPEAKER_06]: I went and saw Charlie and the Chocolate Factory for the second time.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because that movie rocks.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I went to this restaurant called the Cheesecake Factory.
[SPEAKER_06]: And this is for my roommate's birthday.
[SPEAKER_06]: And this place is very, very expensive.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's kind of known around town for having a very, very long wait.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't remember if this place is a national chain or if it's something on the west coast.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know they have more.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is it national?
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, then they've got one of these probably near you somewhere.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've never been before.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's brand new in this part of town.
[SPEAKER_06]: They have crappy pizza there.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've never had the pizza, but the food in general... You had good orange chicken.
[SPEAKER_06]: I actually had the orange chicken, and to be honest, I wasn't a fan of the orange chicken because I felt like I was paying $14 for the orange chicken here, and I could pay like $6 over at the little Mon Pod Chinese restaurant, and the orange chicken was just as good, if not better.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it was one of those things where like, okay, well, you're paying for atmosphere, but the host that we had was kind of a doof.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Luckily, the cheesecake itself was really, really good.
[SPEAKER_06]: So at least, if you're going to call your restaurant the Cheesecake Factory, you should have good cheesecake.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that they did.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I forgive them for at least having subpar rest of their food.
[SPEAKER_06]: But still, the bill being quite a large amount of money for three people, I expected more.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wanted showgirls dancing or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: I expected more.
[SPEAKER_05]: Our waitress at the San Francisco restaurant juggled
[SPEAKER_05]: Ketchup Packets.
[SPEAKER_05]: So she earned her tip.
[SPEAKER_14]: Where was this at?
[SPEAKER_14]: The San Diego one is really the best one I've been to.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's in San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the top of Macy's.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's on the 13th floor or something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: And basically you can go walk over and look at the balcony and stuff on top of the roof there.
[SPEAKER_05]: They had some stupid Christian thing going on after the gay pride parade.
[SPEAKER_05]: They equal everything out.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_13]: Us, of course.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, you want to talk about us?
[SPEAKER_06]: So we were on the news this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: They came out to do a story.
[SPEAKER_06]: When were they out here?
[SPEAKER_06]: Monday?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: They were out here Monday.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, they were out here originally on Friday, or they were supposed to be out here originally on Friday, but real news happened somewhere, so we got bumped to Monday.
[SPEAKER_06]: But they were out here, and the reporter guy was very, very nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: And...
[SPEAKER_06]: The Cameraman.
[SPEAKER_06]: They actually stayed quite a while.
[SPEAKER_06]: They were probably here for about an hour just filming different things.
[SPEAKER_06]: They filmed interviews with all three of us, and then they filmed us playing DDR on my new TV, which was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Always a bad sign.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I got a note here that says I got to take a picture of you guys playing DDR.
[SPEAKER_05]: What does that have to do with our show?
[SPEAKER_05]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_05]: But yeah, I'm supposed to do that.
[SPEAKER_06]: always a bad sign you're just bitter because your feet always somehow end up in it somehow
[SPEAKER_07]: We did our research a lot.
[SPEAKER_07]: You guys play during the show, don't you?
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't you?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, you idiot.
[SPEAKER_06]: We do not.
[SPEAKER_06]: We have.
[SPEAKER_06]: We did like twice.
[SPEAKER_06]: We did the Xbox Live tournament online, which nobody showed up for.
[SPEAKER_06]: Remember we were going to have our big gala 16 person DDR online tournament and then like four people showed up.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't remember anything about that.
[SPEAKER_06]: It must have been a week you weren't here or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was.
[SPEAKER_06]: You remember this, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: It was an impromptu.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was when we were unveiling Ultramix 2 or something like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what it was.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was one of those unveiling shows.
[SPEAKER_06]: And we tried to get all these people to come and only four people showed up, which shows you how many people listen to this program.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, I mean, people are on Xbox Live and we'll see, whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: And have Ultramix too, I don't know, I guess not that many, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we tried to do that and it failed miserably, but we have done the play DDR thing on the show before, it's just not the focus about our show.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess, you know, and we do talk about DDR, we talk about 2DX on the show, so I see where they get that impression, but the playing DDR on the show was a little crazy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently, we talk about it on the podcast too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, so...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, you haven't seen this yet, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura is going to get to see this for the very first time, so here we go.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't want anybody to see me though.
[SPEAKER_06]: Too late.
[SPEAKER_06]: Too late?
[SPEAKER_06]: You were on the news!
[SPEAKER_14]: Too damn late!
[SPEAKER_14]: I needed to ask to be pixelated and have them spell my name right!
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe I should have been the spokesperson because that's the only way I'm going to get on air.
[SPEAKER_06]: When you see what they did to Loki, Extifer, my roommate and I, laughed until we peed.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was so funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fuck.
[SPEAKER_01]: The governor is one of the many people joining the podcasting craze.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's becoming a web craze, but what is it?
[SPEAKER_01]: How does it work?
[SPEAKER_01]: KCRA 3's Brian Hickey tonight shows us how people are using podcasting to inform, entertain, and share their thoughts with the world.
[SPEAKER_06]: By the way, this report comes from a local news station, Channel 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the reporter was very nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: He was a very nice man.
[SPEAKER_06]: I liked him.
[SPEAKER_06]: He was good.
[SPEAKER_06]: And he had done his research because I was very impressed with what he did know about the station before he came here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course, I know he'd been talking to you quite a bit, so you probably filled him in on all that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course!
[SPEAKER_06]: When he headed off to the editors, all hell breaks loose.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hold on, hold on.
[SPEAKER_15]: and there's Jamie playing DDR.
[SPEAKER_15]: It started off tiny and it's grown.
[SPEAKER_06]: It started off tiny and it's grown.
[SPEAKER_06]: If I didn't know you were talking about a podcast there, I could sell that clip for some blackmail.
[SPEAKER_06]: And there's us.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would like to point out that they may not realize it, but look what they're showing in the background.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did they blur that out?
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't tell.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's too far away.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, there's the Jay and Silent Bob poster, which hangs here in the studio.
[SPEAKER_06]: We have a Jay and Silent Bob poster, and I quote, All you motherfuckers are gonna pay.
[SPEAKER_06]: You are the ones who are the ball lickers.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're gonna fuck your mothers while you watch and cry like little whiny bitches.
[SPEAKER_06]: Once we get to Hollywood and find those Miramax fucks who's making the movie, we're gonna make them eat our shit, then shit out our shit, then eat their shit, which is made up of our shit that we made them eat.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then all you motherfuckers are next.
[SPEAKER_06]: Love, Jay and Silent Bob.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can actually see that poster in the background a little bit.
[SPEAKER_14]: And we digress a bit.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's go ahead and keep going.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't look hideous.
[SPEAKER_06]: Look, if we could get the word fuck on the news in any way, shape, or form, I think that's worth a comment.
[SPEAKER_13]: We've done our job.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, here we go.
[SPEAKER_06]: We should report ourselves to the MPA.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let me roll it back a little.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, we're going to have to re-rate our show adults only.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_11]: A subculture of pop culture.
[SPEAKER_11]: And these are the voices to unite and inform the gaming fans.
[SPEAKER_11]: And where am I?
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, stop, stop.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would like to note, where am I?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, there are my feet!
[SPEAKER_07]: But where am I?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, that's right, they cut me behind the goddamn door.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: and you can see me doing the chatting and then you see Loki's feet dangling and his belly kind of hanging out from behind the corner
[SPEAKER_14]: I look so short.
[SPEAKER_14]: My feet don't touch the ground.
[SPEAKER_04]: And when they say, you're right, your feet are dangling.
[SPEAKER_04]: Look, look at my feet.
[SPEAKER_04]: You look like you're sitting in Santa's lap.
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: But when they go, these are the faces of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: They show Jamie, they show me, and then they cut to another picture.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, because I have a face for radio, apparently.
[SPEAKER_06]: And those of you guys that are complaining that you can't see this, you will eventually.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're working on, it's just a bandwidth thing right now, but we're going to get it uploaded sometime tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you guys will have it by tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_06]: But anyway, here we go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let me finish the story here.
[SPEAKER_11]: Welcome to another episode of our podcast.
[SPEAKER_11]: From their apartment in Rancho Cordova, using revolutionary technology, they're podcasting to the world.
[SPEAKER_06]: And apparently we all live in the same apartment.
[SPEAKER_06]: I look horrible.
[SPEAKER_14]: I look horrible.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have you freeze-framed right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: I look like I'm about to puke.
[SPEAKER_06]: The way you see my picture, it's even better.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hold on, hold on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let me roll this back slightly so we can hear what Jamie has to say about podcasting.
[SPEAKER_15]: We basically give the news for video games, popular culture...
[SPEAKER_15]: Basically what gamers really want to know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, so they spelled Jamie's name right on the text over at least.
[SPEAKER_06]: They didn't spell it right online, but they spelled it right on the text over.
[SPEAKER_11]: ...podcast producers record their programs, then send them to a number of websites now hosting the shows.
[SPEAKER_11]: Now anyone can create, edit, and... Ooh, David shot at me.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, but no pictures of me.
[SPEAKER_15]: Lots of pictures of Rob, lots of pictures of Jamie, but no Matt.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hold on, I didn't hear what Jamie said there.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've got to roll it back.
[SPEAKER_11]: ...to anyone else willing to download it.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's something they can take with them.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's a much more flexible way of spreading the information.
[SPEAKER_11]: With nothing more than an MP3 player and a set of headphones, you can listen to it anywhere.
[SPEAKER_12]: Now people can talk about things they like to talk about.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, who's this random guy?
[SPEAKER_06]: Now they're interviewing random guy on the skateboard.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like some dude they found.
[SPEAKER_14]: Where's the name?
[SPEAKER_14]: Casey Ryle.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you listen to our show, email us If Casey listens to the show, the more power to him I'm glad one of our listeners got to be a media whore But I'd also like to point out, Casey only owns an iPod Shuffle So he's not even that hardcore Anyway Again, if I didn't know he was talking about podcasting, I'd find that pretty amusing
[SPEAKER_06]: What grade am I in?
[SPEAKER_06]: Keep playing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let me get the reporter here.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would like to point out that that is the only time in the entire
[SPEAKER_06]: or in the entire news clip that our actual show name is put somewhere because they never say Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: But when they're showing how to get to the podcast and stuff, that's when they bring up the Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like they show the person searching for Orange Lounge Radio and it comes up in our little entry into iTunes stores.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, you know, that's nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good for them.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm glad they plugged the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like maybe the SACB did.
[SPEAKER_06]: At least they put our damn URL in there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Extifer, do you still think the reporter was cute?
[SPEAKER_21]: I did think the reporter was cute, actually.
[SPEAKER_21]: I still, I hold to that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: That lot could be some podcasts.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you see?
[SPEAKER_06]: First of all, they have Loki sitting in DarkSakura's chair, but oh, it's so much fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, God, you guys.
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't even have my goddamn name on there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Where's my name on there?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, God, you guys, that's so much fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, it's so much fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's so much fun?
[SPEAKER_07]: What am I talking about?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, Kelly people, it's so much fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, you know, Klostomy, that's so much fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, what the hell am I talking about?
[SPEAKER_07]: They don't say anything.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just retarded.
[SPEAKER_07]: I said a whole lot more than just, oh, it's so much fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, it's so much fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, look at that!
[SPEAKER_07]: I look like a goddamn chipmunk!
[SPEAKER_07]: My head looks like it has exploded!
[SPEAKER_07]: So, I'm super fat!
[SPEAKER_07]: Look at me!
[SPEAKER_06]: It's so much fun being a... Did you think that maybe you are super fat?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I am not!
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not like that!
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm just having a momentary mental image of Krim.
[SPEAKER_07]: Me and that shit, we go... It was a night out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait, let me see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me see.
[SPEAKER_17]: Let me see if I can.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wait, let me see if I can.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let me see if I can.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let me see if I can cue this up.
[SPEAKER_14]: That should be in the next intro.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, Loki, what do you think about gay sex?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, it's so much fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't worry, this will be continued later in FG's.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have not forgot about them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's let this finish up here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Speech for everyone.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, it's so much fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's great that, you know, just anybody out there who really has a desire to want to be heard, you have an outlet for your voice to get out there.
[SPEAKER_06]: God damn, I can't believe I let people watch this.
[SPEAKER_11]: In Rancho Cordova, Brian Hickey, KCRA 3 reports.
[SPEAKER_01]: See, everybody's a broadcaster now.
[SPEAKER_01]: Recently, Governor Schwarzenegger began... Oh, good for the governor!
[SPEAKER_01]: He gets a fucking plug, but do we know?
[SPEAKER_01]: What the fuck is up with him?
[SPEAKER_01]: So you can listen to it in the car, in the walk, or even in the gym.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I'm sure his podcast is very easy to listen to.
[SPEAKER_07]: When you understand half the words... We're going to slash the budget now!
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for downloading my podcast!
[SPEAKER_13]: It's so much fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, it's... I love my podcast!
[SPEAKER_04]: It's so much fun!
[SPEAKER_04]: It's tiny, but it's good!
[SPEAKER_04]: All of you that own iPod shuffles, the iPod shuffles are the girly mans of iPods!
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, so not only did they not plug our show, not even mention who our show was, not even put me on there, gave me some really crappy line, one I had a whole lot more to say, you know?
[SPEAKER_07]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, so basically we're going to ask you a lot of questions.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to get you saying something really stupid, cut to you for about a second, because we know we have to, and then we're done.
[SPEAKER_05]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_05]: What's up with that?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like the pictures of podcasting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, oh, we forgot one.
[SPEAKER_14]: I had a cleavage shot.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's like, gee.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: Orange Lounge Radio has more name recognition than Arnold Schwarzenegger.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, someday we will.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, we can if people don't fucking plug our show.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_07]: How long is it going to take?
[SPEAKER_07]: Take the extra two seconds.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can find this podcast here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Boop.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, put the URL up there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Done.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, or just say, you know, just like this show out of Sacramento, Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just mention the name once.
[SPEAKER_07]: Once is all we're asking.
[SPEAKER_07]: Show the website.
[SPEAKER_07]: Show something.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you think that maybe we don't get our name on TV because here we are just...
[SPEAKER_06]: Fuck them!
[SPEAKER_07]: Sack beat all the way!
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't give a shit if my goddamn foot was in there and that was it.
[SPEAKER_07]: At least they fucking mentioned our show.
[SPEAKER_07]: The hell with them, because they made me look like a fucking idiot.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what I have to say about that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't give a crap, okay?
[SPEAKER_07]: I honestly don't give a... If they showed me at least saying something intelligent, like, podcasting, you know, we've, you know...
[SPEAKER_07]: So, Loki, what do you think of your anger management courses?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, it's so much fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know what this is going to turn into.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's going to be just like the other goddamn thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, oh, I shot my foot.
[SPEAKER_14]: Loki, you're purple in the face.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not purple in the face.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm angry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can you see your face?
[SPEAKER_05]: You are purple.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not purple.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're splotchy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, no, I'm violet.
[SPEAKER_07]: Damn gum.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, anyways.
[SPEAKER_07]: I turned into a blueberry.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, it's so much fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: I couldn't resist.
[SPEAKER_06]: I had to do it one more time.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: That won't be the last time, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_06]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's going to be cut down into a little clip, and then you're going to be like, hey, Matt.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, Logan, what do you think about this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, it's so much fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, oh, oh, it's so much fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe we could compile some of this together and remix it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have an idea.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's send them a friendly letter commenting on how wonderful they covered our show.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sitting here going, you know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: No TV station give a rat's ass about us before.
[SPEAKER_14]: I look at it this way.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was about podcasting.
[SPEAKER_14]: We were just podcasters who were convenient and had the most interesting material.
[SPEAKER_06]: We were just pawns in the big operation, really.
[SPEAKER_05]: Damn the man!
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm glad they mentioned everybody on the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh wait, no they didn't.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right, they didn't.
[SPEAKER_06]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: We are going to put that up on the internet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Check our website.
[SPEAKER_06]: You guys will be able to download it soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also, big goddamn... You know what they're going to do?
[SPEAKER_07]: They're going to play this at my work in front of goddamn 100 people.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, it's so much fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: And we're going to hear all goddamn day long next week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, great new week!
[SPEAKER_07]: Perfect way to start it off!
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you, KCRA3!
[SPEAKER_07]: I cannot wait!
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you done?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you done yet?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_14]: I have actually news that happened to me this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, what's that?
[SPEAKER_14]: Now that I'm no longer bitter.
[SPEAKER_14]: Actually, I'm going to be addressing most of it during the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_06]: My work.
[SPEAKER_14]: My package arrived.
[SPEAKER_14]: My prize.
[SPEAKER_06]: Your package?
[SPEAKER_06]: Did it start off small and get a little bit bigger?
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, no, seriously, what is it?
[SPEAKER_14]: My gorilla stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, that's right.
[SPEAKER_06]: You were a winner on some stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: I am a winner.
[SPEAKER_14]: I won shit that wasn't really shit.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was really cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: What kind of stuff did you win?
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, it was from Filter Magazine.
[SPEAKER_14]: And first of all, it was going to be just a CD and the autographed magazine.
[SPEAKER_14]: I had misunderstood the first email, the price.
[SPEAKER_14]: But since I already had the CD, and since I actually, you know, when I was talking, I had to actually call the lady to give her my change of address because she didn't get my return email.
[SPEAKER_14]: And we were just talking about stuff, and, you know, I said that, you know,
[SPEAKER_14]: I actually, uh, moderate on Gorillas Unofficial, which is a really cool site for anyone interested.
[SPEAKER_14]: Um, but, uh, what?
[SPEAKER_06]: Nothing, just something, I was giggling at something a listener wants to say.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey!
[SPEAKER_06]: Jamie time!
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_14]: You can either pay attention to me or piss off, okay?
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_14]: Anyway, as I was saying...
[SPEAKER_14]: Um, because, because, you know, I wasn't just some random person filling out the, the little prize thingy.
[SPEAKER_14]: I actually got, um, a mobile that I haven't seen anywhere else except a couple of lists that I saw on eBay, but that's like it.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I got, um, the autographed magazine, and I got, uh, the sticker sheet, and the little promo book that's like, ooh, cool promo book.
[SPEAKER_06]: So how much would you say all this is worth?
[SPEAKER_14]: On eBay?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: I've seen the promo book go for a lot of money.
[SPEAKER_06]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: So... So what are you going to do with it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you going to put it on display in your house somewhere?
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you going to keep it locked away in a little box to take out on days when you need some gorillas?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: What do people do with these things?
[SPEAKER_06]: I've never won anything like that before, really.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, Dan and I have actually been off looking at office furniture.
[SPEAKER_14]: And so once we get the office set up, it's going to go in my area of our office.
[SPEAKER_06]: The most exciting music-related thing I ever won was when I got to meet Matchbox 20.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wasn't even that big a fan of them, but I just won tickets off the radio and backstage passes, so we got to go meet Matchbox 20.
[SPEAKER_06]: And so I just have my little autograph hanging on the wall, but that's about it.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm not really an autograph collector, you know, but this is just really cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not much of an autograph collector either.
[SPEAKER_06]: However, I got Rob Thomas to sign my thing and it says, To Rob, I think you're cute.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's worth saving.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a whole story behind that, but I don't like the story.
[SPEAKER_14]: When we get the scanner hooked up, I'm going to scan the magazine because I love how DJ Danger Mouth signs it.
[SPEAKER_14]: He signs a DM with a circle around it, sort of like the old Danger Mouse logo.
[SPEAKER_14]: I thought that was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: I had major happy nerd moment right then, and they're just staring at it for about five minutes going, Ooh, Navy Seals!
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, wrong movie.
[SPEAKER_06]: Going back to it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, since now we've had Jamie time, let's take a minute and have some Loki time.
[SPEAKER_06]: God damn!
[SPEAKER_07]: Out of my foot!
[SPEAKER_07]: Why did I shoot myself in my foot?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh my god, it hurts so bad!
[SPEAKER_07]: No, my foot!
[SPEAKER_07]: I need that for walking!
[SPEAKER_06]: It's only funny if you were there for that episode.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, somebody in the chatroom asked if I still had that sound clip, so I just had to play it for them.
[SPEAKER_06]: We need to have some Loki singing during the break.
[SPEAKER_06]: We also... I think I actually deleted those mp3s finally.
[SPEAKER_18]: No!
[SPEAKER_06]: I got them somewhere, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: They are safe in my... No!
[SPEAKER_06]: Sakurina has a comment here in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_06]: It has a suggestion for DarkSakura's next advice column on your show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, the advice column's theme would be how to piss off Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: And here we go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Number one, get his foot on TV.
[SPEAKER_06]: Number two, oh my god, it's so much fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: Number three, talk about how In The Groove is awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Number four, say you'll buy him a Mac.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the final piece of advice, just stay away.
[SPEAKER_14]: That would piss him off.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you know how usually your final piece of advice is, you know, just don't, like when you're doing that, how to, you know, fly out of a cannon, your final piece of advice is don't get in the fucking cannon.
[SPEAKER_14]: I was thinking that my advice was going to be on how to safely inflate your ego without it exploding into brain bits all over your company.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, that'll work.
[SPEAKER_14]: I've been having lots of practice with that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have an advice column.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's how to shoot an interview.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because apparently, you know,
[SPEAKER_05]: I was watching the other segments that they cut to.
[SPEAKER_07]: Before ours, so meaning these were more important That would be that it's hot The same story they've covered all week Oh, guess what, it's still hot In case you didn't figure that out by walking outside Loki, if you wanted to headline the news Let's get Joe Hotperson on the street and see what he thinks It's hot out here Come on You know what, when I want to know exactly how hot it is I go to the Weather Channel's website and put in my damn zip code
[SPEAKER_14]: And then I know it's hot.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, if you want to be headline news, kill someone.
[SPEAKER_06]: Then you'll headline the news.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, thank you.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it'll be press for us.
[SPEAKER_07]: We caught a killer today.
[SPEAKER_14]: This guy's the host of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_14]: Ghost poster and kills 50 nuns because his foot was the only thing on the TV.
[SPEAKER_07]: I should be a reporter.
[SPEAKER_06]: It looks like it's another crazy killer who is inspired by the Grand Theft Auto San Andreas games.
[SPEAKER_06]: When asked about how much he enjoys Grand Theft Auto San Andreas, the killer replied, It's so much fun.
[SPEAKER_14]: GameStop is no longer allowed to take them in as trade-ins.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, because they're not going to be selling it anymore.
[SPEAKER_05]: Subtitles by the Amara.org community
[SPEAKER_06]: I was going to save this for the podcast, but now you've got me on this subject, so I want to talk about this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, we've seen this happen before, with DDR even, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Remember how when you put in the DDR USA, remember the very first release of DDR USA on the PlayStation?
[SPEAKER_06]: As poopy of a game as it was, it was what got DDR in the door on PlayStation here in the U.S.,
[SPEAKER_06]: remember that people put in that disc and they hacked it and what did they find on the disc they found the background for Butterfly and they found the background for Bad Girls but with the gun taken out so this obviously was at one point or another those songs were meant to be even if not Butterfly if they were just lazy from the Best Hits conversion and left that in there somebody altered the Bad Girls background that song was intended to be in DDR USA at one point or another but instead of
[SPEAKER_06]: What they did, instead of removing the song, removing the background, removing everything from the code completely, all they did was they took the pointer out.
[SPEAKER_06]: The thing that points to bad girls as being a song in the game, they took that out.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that's exactly what they did with Grand Theft Auto San Andreas.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that this sex thing was intended to be in the game the whole time.
[SPEAKER_06]: But during some final QA review process or something, they decided, you know what, if we have this sex thing in the game, I think that's crossing the line.
[SPEAKER_06]: So instead of going through the efforts to take it out of the programming, which would be a pain in the ass, they simply took the pointer out.
[SPEAKER_06]: and so they thought well if we just take the pointer out you take everything that points to the sex thing out nobody's going to find the sex thing because all the pointers are out whoops did they underestimate the PC hack community out there once the PC hack community found it it was just a matter of time before somebody got the codes to basically what they're doing is putting a pointer in that points back to the sex game and now it's this whole big thing of oh Rockstar Games knew it all along that they were going to have this sex game well yeah they knew they had a sex game in there but they thought they took it out
[SPEAKER_06]: It's lazy programming, is what happened here, I think.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's still retarded, though, that people are coming after this game.
[SPEAKER_05]: But anyways, we'll see you on the third podcast.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, now you got me started on that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's talk about how In the Groove sucks.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, I'm gonna... We do that every show!
[SPEAKER_06]: I know, and I'm not even... I don't even think In the Groove sucks as much as you do.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't quite have the budget to buy In the Groove today.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought about doing it just so I could play it once and say it sucks, and then write it sucks ass on the front cover.
[SPEAKER_05]: and then, you know, give it away.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: I actually plan on playing In the Groove 2 two weeks from now.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll be playing In the Groove 2 because I'm doing my East Coast trip and I'm going to go buy aid on the break while I'm out there and I'm going to check out In the Groove 2 so I can come back and give a review on the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can tell Loki that it's probably not as bad as he thinks it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it's going to be awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to have it on a new HDTV.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it's going to be really crisp and higher quality looking graphics.
[SPEAKER_05]: They still suck!
[SPEAKER_07]: They're just going to be on a bigger TV!
[SPEAKER_07]: Wow, crap blown up!
[SPEAKER_05]: Just like saying all the speakers in the world will not make those songs any better.
[SPEAKER_06]: What can he do?
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe, you know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: Knock it off!
[SPEAKER_07]: Stop playing the damn video clip!
[SPEAKER_06]: I think, though, one day, one day, you guys, there's hope.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki will change his mind.
[SPEAKER_06]: And we'll sit here and we'll ask him, Loki, what did you think of In The Groove 2?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, it's so much fun.
[SPEAKER_17]: For me to hope on!
[SPEAKER_05]: Can we, like, change the topic to something I don't have to yell at?
[SPEAKER_06]: Poppa Music
[SPEAKER_06]: and we'll be back after this with more Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Your calls on the Skype line also in this very next break.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we'll be back after some murmur twins kicking it off.
Thank you.
Thanks for watching!
Thank you for watching
[SPEAKER_02]: Please listen to Orange Lounge Radio because real radio makes Captain Jack cry
[SPEAKER_06]: Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_06]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_06]: The old days.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was the porno that was inspired by Dance Dance Revolution somehow.
[SPEAKER_06]: When I say inspired by... Very loosely.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, like most of the girls in it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, I don't even think there was a part other than the title.
[SPEAKER_06]: But they dance.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was like Dance Dance Fuck Max something six or... Yeah, it was like Dance Dance Fuck Six or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dance Dance Fuck Max.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't remember what it was.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was years old though.
[SPEAKER_06]: I always thought the porno that had the Final Fantasy X Final Fuck X That was the better one It was good cosplay Yeah, they had some good cosplayers in them And then they got naked and had sex But the Lulu actually had a little stuffed muggle Anyway Sorry kids
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh yeah, by the way, children, don't listen to this program.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bad for you.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, I'm scared that I might have co-workers listening to this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because they all found out about the news thing that happened last Friday and some were asking, what's the web address?
[SPEAKER_05]: What's the web address?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm like, I don't care anymore.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't.
[SPEAKER_05]: Honestly, I don't.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just, it's not worth it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not worth it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just,
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, you keep it under wraps pretty good, which your weekend hobby is.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hell no!
[SPEAKER_14]: I tell everyone, hey, I'm on the radio!
[SPEAKER_06]: Really?
[SPEAKER_14]: Hey, listen to this, hey, look at this, because I don't really care.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're not worried about them hearing you talk about Dance Dance Fuck?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_14]: They've seen my cubicle.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, they know you're into porn.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, I am not into porn, okay?
[SPEAKER_14]: That was Loki's piece of crap.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, I was looking for quality Dance Dance Revolution products.
[SPEAKER_05]: I came upon that and I was like, quality.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was like, I have to get that.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay, I have the Happy Bunny magnet that you gave me in my cubicle.
[SPEAKER_14]: With Happy Bunny pointing down to his crotch saying, I bet you love my thingy.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm going to be taking my other one there too that says, I love everybody except you assholes.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think I have...
[SPEAKER_06]: I think you mentioned it a couple times.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like my job, but since I'm a presenter, I'm in front of people most of the time, I have to stay politically correct.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a very interesting challenge.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some of my friends theorize that's why I do this program, is because I have to be so politically correct when I'm in front of a class teaching that this is my way of venting the other half of that, the unpolitically correct side of me, where I get to come on and say shit, piss, fuck, and people listen to that and laugh at it.
[SPEAKER_06]: You mean they don't throw lawsuits our way?
[SPEAKER_06]: Why is that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because we're on the interweb.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: No one likes the internet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Speaking of places you can't say shit, fuck, and cunt, there was...
[SPEAKER_06]: All three of us need to try out a new co-host.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because you know Loki on Attack of the Show would be hilarious.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's come on the show drunk every day.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh my god, it's so much fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I'm seriously thinking about doing it.
[SPEAKER_06]: My only issue is, though, since I'm going to be gone for two weeks, I have a feeling that that's when they're going to be here in San Francisco is when I'm gone, so I'm not going to be able to do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they're going to miss out on a great candidate if I can't be there to do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're just going to get some big breasted chick that doesn't know jack about technology done.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, I should apply.
[SPEAKER_06]: You may have adequate boobage, but you actually know technology.
[SPEAKER_06]: You have a bigger gaming collection than the two of us combined.
[SPEAKER_14]: I have a bigger gaming collection than each of you combined.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just grab one of the chicks off that stupid show, The Whipset, or whatever.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'll go to the audition with my Turbo Express and my WonderSwan.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was looking at the KevinPereira.com, which is the guy that's still the host on Attack of the Show, who, by the way, I like more and more as I see the show more and more.
[SPEAKER_06]: When the screensavers first came out, I was kind of like, okay, this guy's a boob.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't like him.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I'm really warming up to him, and I think what they're trying to do with the show, he really does kind of fit it, and he's kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: and I think now that he's... Yeah, he'll have to go.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think when it first started as the screensavers, I think it was always kind of trying to fit a square peg in a round hole kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I think he realizes this, so even if, you know, for some weird reason you heard me saying this, you wouldn't be offended because I think he realizes this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because even he says that first episode of the screensavers was bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: But we're not looking for someone that just is about the technology.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're looking for someone that wants to be on TV talking about technology.
[SPEAKER_06]: And for some reason, they're having a hard time finding that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm volunteering.
[SPEAKER_06]: But wait a minute, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: You don't want us to point the webcam at you, yet you would be on television?
[SPEAKER_14]: I'd hire a trainer.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'd do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I could talk about technology.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's all I talk about.
[SPEAKER_14]: You want to get me to lose weight?
[SPEAKER_14]: Put me in a social situation.
[SPEAKER_14]: Every freaking day.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hear knocking.
[SPEAKER_14]: I guarantee you I won't eat for a month.
I hear knocking.
[SPEAKER_14]: I hear cabinets is what I hear.
[SPEAKER_05]: I heard knocking.
[SPEAKER_05]: I could do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Easy.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's so much fun.
[SPEAKER_14]: Is it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Is it now?
[SPEAKER_14]: You know it's tiny, but it's grown.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: Rob, you abandoned us.
[SPEAKER_14]: How dare you?
[SPEAKER_14]: 50 lashes with a chocolate whip.
[SPEAKER_07]: To hell, Rob.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can't go on an antagonist show because we need to do our show.
[SPEAKER_06]: If somebody offered me money to do a live television show, I'd be all, screw you guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to L.A.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love you guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'd at least give you my two weeks.
[SPEAKER_06]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bastard.
[SPEAKER_14]: At that point...
[SPEAKER_14]: At that point, you have a Menchie hat!
[SPEAKER_14]: Give!
[SPEAKER_14]: From Anime Expo, you want it?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_14]: I have a Menchie hat.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, let's eat her!
[SPEAKER_06]: She's the emergency food supply!
[SPEAKER_14]: I have a Menchie hat.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, joining us, by the way, who hasn't been at this show in an awfully long time is the one and only Explicit, with three X's.
[SPEAKER_13]: Our angry guy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just what we need this show.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm not going to be angry this time.
[SPEAKER_21]: I got some more important than that.
[SPEAKER_21]: More important than just being angry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, we were talking about TV earlier, and we were talking about Attack of the Show and how we're all going to be on it soon, because we want to do that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Supposedly, some folks were emailing them, too, about us going on, so I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nobody contacted us, so I guess it wasn't enough people, so...
[SPEAKER_06]: Go email them and tell them we're ready to whore ourselves out to be on cable.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because we figure, okay, we've done the newspaper, we've done local TV, now we have to do basic cable.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the next step up.
[SPEAKER_21]: So far, like, I'm in Canada, Tony and me got the spotlight right there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, I was going to say, what happened... Now, you also had a television experience recently.
[SPEAKER_06]: We had Channel 3, but you had another station in town.
[SPEAKER_06]: What was yours the thing about?
[SPEAKER_21]: It was basically like...
[SPEAKER_21]: The scenery of the DDR, and introducing the game to people for both perfect attack and freestyle, in addition to how this one person lost this much weight on DDR,
[SPEAKER_06]: So they were kind of doing more of like a DDR story.
[SPEAKER_06]: They were doing that typical Dance Dance Revolution in the news story where DDR, it's better than Grand Theft Auto because instead of making kids want to kill people, it makes them get up and exercise and want to lose weight.
[SPEAKER_06]: But then, now the little piece I saw of it had Andrew dressed up like a pirate.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yep, that's true.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that other guy that's always with him dressed up as Darth Vader.
[SPEAKER_21]: A different Andrew.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they were just, you know, being themselves, but on TV.
[SPEAKER_21]: Or in the media, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would have totally gone if I didn't have to work.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_21]: You would bring Orange Eyes Radio to the TV.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, so we had to go get our own gig, since we couldn't go to yours.
[SPEAKER_06]: I heard about Channel 3, so... We actually, we played the clip earlier, you missed it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, oh.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, Loki, I'm so glad you suggested it here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let me get to the little piece here.
[SPEAKER_06]: I found it.
[SPEAKER_06]: What'd you find?
[SPEAKER_06]: What'd you find, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_14]: I found the Menchie hat, because I want one now.
[SPEAKER_21]: You want that?
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes, this is from Anime Expo.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm just giving away some stuff from Anime Expo.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay!
[SPEAKER_14]: If you don't want the Menchie hat, sure!
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, thanks.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is just for you, Jonas.
[SPEAKER_14]: Menchie hat!
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, Loki, what did you think about being on television?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, it's so much fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was Loki's big television debut.
[SPEAKER_17]: That was it!
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_21]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, from what I heard from the taping, though.
[SPEAKER_14]: Loki, you know what this is?
[SPEAKER_14]: The world's smallest violin playing My Heart Bleeds For You.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, from what I've heard from the taping, like, the two Andrews were there, and some background people doing PA, and then me and Cam Canada doing a little freestyle to introduce it to the scenery.
[SPEAKER_21]: And I'm not really sure if Scott Farah, the gaming guy of Channel 31 KMAX, introduced the tournament.
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't even know we had a gaming guy on local television.
[SPEAKER_21]: We had a gaming guy?
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, his name is Scott Farah on the morning show.
[SPEAKER_21]: Usually he's there on Mondays.
[SPEAKER_06]: On the guy.
[SPEAKER_06]: The gaming guy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that his job?
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that strictly his job is to be the gaming guy?
[SPEAKER_06]: Dude, I want to be the gaming guy!
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm cute.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can be on TV.
[SPEAKER_21]: You're going to be there on the tournament if you're still interested in going on the 30th.
[SPEAKER_06]: I might, except I have a flight leaving the very next day, so I'm going to try and make it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tell us, plug your tournament, plug your tourney thing that you're doing.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, we had one tournament, they won the tournament already on yesterday for the initial D section.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh yeah?
[SPEAKER_21]: How'd that go?
[SPEAKER_21]: It turned out pretty okay, so-so in certain ways, because we had some problems with someone's card didn't read it.
[SPEAKER_18]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_21]: But then again, they said the car was bent, so I don't know what happened.
[SPEAKER_21]: It was eight competitors.
[SPEAKER_21]: The first place winner was some guy named Jay.
[SPEAKER_21]: Second place was T, and third was Kenshin.
[SPEAKER_14]: Jonas, you know what you and I need to do?
[SPEAKER_14]: We need to work on Shaft 2.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh yes.
[SPEAKER_21]: But we're going to post it though, so far.
[SPEAKER_21]: What's your plans?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, but I need to, we need to talk.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because I've been needing to get Shaft to run for a while and they've been kind of being assholes at RVGL.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, that's what I don't do with RVGL.
[SPEAKER_21]: Their management with tournaments, no.
[SPEAKER_14]: This facility would be great, otherwise I don't want to deal with what's-his-face.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, it's funny, because their management also put repairing their machines as no, and listening to the customers as no.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's really ironic the way that works.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_21]: Are you serious?
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay, first of all, RV Chill's a business, so... We'll ask you in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hold the microphone a little bit back.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which is funny, because Jonas actually doesn't hold his microphone that close to his mouth.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's just got that kind of voice, kids.
[SPEAKER_21]: But that's all right.
[SPEAKER_21]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_21]: Let's see, I don't know why RBGL doesn't want a tournament, because I've done this before myself.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, that's where FU was supposed to be held, but then I decided to do PI because that's the only place that would host a tournament.
[SPEAKER_21]: Scandia, they want to do their own gig.
[SPEAKER_21]: Of course, you've been to one of their tournaments.
[SPEAKER_06]: I did go to one of those Scandia tournaments.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was cute.
[SPEAKER_06]: It wasn't like a large-scale DDR tournament.
[SPEAKER_06]: It wasn't the kind of thing you should drive in from San Francisco for, but it was cute.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_21]: First off, Jamie, first I'll take care of the tournament that's happening this Saturday.
[SPEAKER_21]: Then we'll talk about Shaft 2.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, I meant Shaft 2 because I've got to deal with school starting.
[SPEAKER_14]: Once I get in my school schedule, I'll have more time to plot to that.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right.
[SPEAKER_21]: Just give me a call anytime and reply and we'll see what's up.
[SPEAKER_21]: So many people want to help out with the whole tournament issues.
[SPEAKER_14]: And Shaft had such a good turnout, and it ended up being one of the big ones when it was out, that I think that, you know, putting the name on it would give us a big draw-in.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_14]: We got a few people, we got a couple of the Yamaha people.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I remember that, that was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was a good time.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the 2DX tournament, too, was cool, except we won't be having that again.
[SPEAKER_21]: Wasn't that Marsh Brandes, though?
[SPEAKER_06]: Uh, we did it at Shaft, too.
[SPEAKER_21]: That was at Shaft.
[SPEAKER_06]: We did both, it was both.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway...
[SPEAKER_06]: What we're going to do now, I was going to talk about the MidiHead thing, so let me get into that.
[SPEAKER_06]: MidiHead, our buddy that had a song over in Ultramix 2, he did, you know, the In My Eyes remix was in Ultramix 2, remember that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Pretty good song there, very well liked, fan favorite.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's back, he's going to be in...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: What MidiHead did is he kind of put this whole show together.
[SPEAKER_06]: He engineered this 30-minute show where he plays his track from Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: He played the Wraith song from his upcoming album.
[SPEAKER_06]: He played... What else did he play?
[SPEAKER_06]: He played Raise Your Hands.
[SPEAKER_06]: He played Take Me Away From Here.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then he plays the new...
[SPEAKER_06]: Jellykiss
So it sounds pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: It sounds like it's going to be a fun little remix there.
[SPEAKER_06]: I remember playing it at E3, and I loved the remix of Jelly Kiss, so it was probably my favorite thing.
[SPEAKER_14]: I actually tried to play it.
[SPEAKER_06]: What did you think of the song?
[SPEAKER_14]: My hip ended up being a screaming nightmare of agony.
[SPEAKER_06]: But that's not because of the song.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, I liked the song.
[SPEAKER_14]: I wish I could have played it.
[SPEAKER_14]: I only got halfway through it before my hip gave out on me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Check that out on DDRFreak.com You can just download the MP3 right there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which, by the way, I think would probably be the only time I've ever seen a Bomani-related MP3 so blatantly on DDRFreak.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that's kind of a historical thing as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: So check that out.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bimani Style isn't hosting the file per se, but they ran an article on it, and so did DDRUK.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's thanks to one of our listeners, actually, who is mod on all those sites.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, check that out.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a good time.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a good podcast.
[SPEAKER_06]: The thing about MiniHead, too, is he does these funny radio voiceovers during the whole thing, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's just like, this is MiniHead!
[SPEAKER_06]: He's just going crazy during the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, you got a shout-out on the thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't get a shout-out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Jamie didn't get a shout-out.
[SPEAKER_06]: You got a shout-out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Your mic's not on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Damn straight, because the mic needs to be on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I'm awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I hang out on his forums.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, you just get it because you have to shout out because you hang out on the forums.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what it is, basically, what it boils down to.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, Loki, what did you think of the Middy Head podcast?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's so much fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not as much fun as this McDonald's barbecue sauce.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, since you guys are eating... By the way, MidiHead also teases the fact that there's a third song he's going to have in the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: He pretty much all but says, I have a third song in Ultramix 3, but he's teasing us.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's not telling us what that song is.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we're assuming that the reason why you might want to subscribe to the podcast and not just download the direct file, unless you're lazy and don't want to set up podcasting...
[SPEAKER_06]: You probably want to subscribe to the podcast because whenever this third song is announced he will probably do a podcast part two and that's going to be the first place you're going to hear this new song.
[SPEAKER_06]: So he pretty much all but said he's going to have a third song in the game so we're kind of interested to see what that is.
[SPEAKER_06]: But you notice that they've kind of in general been very, very quiet about these recent DDR games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like they haven't been doing the clues.
[SPEAKER_06]: They usually do the clues around this time where people try to guess what the songs are that are going to be in the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: They haven't been saying a whole lot about the features.
[SPEAKER_06]: We've really gotten not a lot since E3 besides this MIDI head thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not a problem.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll send another demo for GamePro to review and boom!
[SPEAKER_06]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why do you think that is, that they're being so tight-lipped about it this time?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because GamePro sucks?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, not GamePro.
[SPEAKER_06]: It has nothing to do with GamePro.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm talking about, in general, Konami's lack of playing around on the forums.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, some of the Konami reps are playing on DDR Freak, and they chime in once in a while.
[SPEAKER_06]: Even Miklatov, who's been on the show a couple times, he's jumped in there, but you notice that when Miklatov has been on the show, he hasn't said anything.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not nearly what he was telling us this time last year.
[SPEAKER_06]: On the show, he's not saying a whole lot about the new games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, they're doing some weird things with the releases coming out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good things, but weird things.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm thinking they're probably just going to keep it in the wrap so when it comes out and people go, Oh, wow!
[SPEAKER_05]: Instead of, Ah, it sounds like crap.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then they don't buy it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, it's more of a shock factor.
[SPEAKER_05]: They don't really have to give hints.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why?
[SPEAKER_05]: No other companies give hints about what their games are going to be like.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fuck it, wait.
[SPEAKER_05]: Be patient.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rockstar's on their forums going, hey guys, did you know you can unlock a sex game?
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: I think there was an E3 strategy that worked very well for them, and that is that they didn't say shit about Beatmania USA until E3 itself.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was a very, very quiet thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: They had said, oh yeah, we're going to have, you know,
[SPEAKER_06]: Extreme 2 and DDR Ultimix 3 and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: But they didn't say anything about... They didn't say anything about Beatmania.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because if they had said something about Beatmania, people were going to come up with all these preconceived notions about what they wanted in Beatmania.
[SPEAKER_06]: And when that wasn't met, they were going to be disappointed.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have a feeling it's a similar thing they're doing here.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're not saying anything about the games, because if they do, people are just going to go, Why isn't this feature in the game?
[SPEAKER_06]: Why didn't they put this song in?
[SPEAKER_06]: I think they're just trying to avoid that this time because it seems like that's what happens when they tell us the song list is people go, although there are the people that are appreciative of the hints and that deserve to know these things in advance, there's just a few bad apples that ruin it for everyone.
[SPEAKER_06]: The people that get on there and go, why don't we get this song and why haven't we gotten Cartoon Heroes and DDR yet?
[SPEAKER_05]: Wasn't Genie in a Bottle in DDR Extreme 2?
[SPEAKER_05]: They had something like Christina Aguilera's song or something like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then they got, like, Britney, I think, in there, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm actually interested to hear those again.
[SPEAKER_06]: They weren't in the E3 thing, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was just a preview.
[SPEAKER_06]: They had a clip.
[SPEAKER_06]: They had a thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: There was a clip of the Genie in the Bottle thing that was on some video of somebody from E3 or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, they did have Genie in the Bottle in the E3 demo, but it was so freaking loud you couldn't hear it.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right, and I thought that they mentioned something about Oops I Did It Again, too, being in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I remember after that, people were like, Oh, long versions are coming back!
[SPEAKER_05]: And we're like, no.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oops wasn't in there, but I think it's kind of assumed that it's going to be a different cut of Oops I Did It Again.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm just kind of reading what's going on in the chat room, and I think some people are kind of agreeing with the same thing, that, you know, people are basically... Konami isn't wanting to deal with the obnoxious people that whine about everything they release, and all that other stuff going on there.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then, let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought the E3 build of Beatmania was just a throw together.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think in some ways it was, because some things weren't enabled in there, but I think...
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's going to be what they're going in the direction towards.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it is going to be basically a night style redone for us with different songs.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the whole five key songs and five key mode, which I think is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know if it was necessarily thrown together because that five key song and five key mode probably took a little extra programming.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's supposed to be thrown together.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what a beta is.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think they wanted to show what they were going to do, but not, I mean, obviously they probably haven't made a lot of progress on the game because they're working on the DDRs.
[SPEAKER_06]: You kind of wonder with these fans, oh, what, I expect the full game to be done.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, you idiot.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're not going to have the full game done.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's obviously a work in progress.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, they're just showing off what they have.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's why they have the E3 version.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, people are like, oh, the full game's going to suck because it doesn't have 7 key and wine.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, you know,
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, what we're going to do now, I guess we're going to go to a break.
[SPEAKER_06]: When we come back from break, we'll take your calls on Skype.
[SPEAKER_06]: I promise that we do the Skype thing this break, but we didn't get around to it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we'll take your calls on Skype when we come back from this next break.
[SPEAKER_06]: And we will also do the cage match tonight, because I keep promising we're going to get into that as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: So let's start off this break with...
[SPEAKER_06]: I think we'll do some home version song here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also, you know what I feel like?
[SPEAKER_06]: I feel like playing that one Love is Orange mix.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a little bit longer of a song, but I think we're going to fit it in here, because I feel like playing that.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we're going to play that, and we'll be back with more Orange Lounge Radio and the Cage Match and your calls on the Skype line after this.
[SPEAKER_17]: Thanks for watching!
Thank you for watching!
DarkSakura
Thanks for watching!
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_24]: Easier to dance to than that freaking catch-up song, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi kids, we're back with more Orange Lounge Radio here.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to get into the cage match somewhat shortly, but we also wanted to start taking your calls on the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_06]: So if you want to call us, head on over to the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's www.orangeloungeradio.com and just click on interact with us and it has all the information that you need to call us and talk live with us.
[SPEAKER_06]: And so while we have that open up, I don't see a whole lot of people signed in.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe we'll get a couple calls.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: But meanwhile, I want to remind you guys about something.
[SPEAKER_06]: Podcast Awards.
[SPEAKER_06]: We were nominated in the recent Podcast Awards.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you should vote for us.
[SPEAKER_06]: Head on over to www.podcastawards.com and make sure that you vote for us once every day.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good evening, everyone.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good evening.
[SPEAKER_06]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm fine.
[SPEAKER_20]: Well, just, you know, just some off-topic stuff.
[SPEAKER_20]: I got some 2DX, you know, Happy Sky, some entering stuff about Happy Sky.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ooh, what's going on with Happy Sky?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to get to those MP3s you sent me later, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: I haven't forgotten.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just want to save it for later.
[SPEAKER_20]: Well, you can play a small clip if you want.
[SPEAKER_20]: I'm just going to announce some hidden songs.
[SPEAKER_06]: Unless they're upgraded to a new 2DX mix.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, we have a little clip of that one here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, cool.
[SPEAKER_20]: Let me check.
[SPEAKER_20]: It's by Hoshino Kanako, and it's Get Cold.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that this one that doesn't have a label on it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that this one?
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, that's not Get Cold.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know which one that was then.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe I don't have that one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you know which one that was I just played?
[SPEAKER_20]: Oh, never mind.
[SPEAKER_20]: I'll just say the next song.
[SPEAKER_20]: It's Plasma by...
[SPEAKER_06]: Soda Fujimori did Plasma, yes?
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, here's a clip of Plasma.
[SPEAKER_06]: This one sounds kind of cool, okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Kind of sounds like every other Soda Fujimori song, but that's alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know if I have that one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you send me everything?
[SPEAKER_20]: I have... I forgot to send you... Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_20]: And then the last one is... This is going to be a very complicated to say.
[SPEAKER_20]: It's by Ginger.
[SPEAKER_20]: It's called... That sounds like it should have a long, complicated name.
That's kind of interesting.
Okay.
[SPEAKER_20]: This one's translated into English.
[SPEAKER_20]: I just translated it on some site.
[SPEAKER_20]: And it says, What?
[SPEAKER_20]: That's what it's translated.
[SPEAKER_20]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_20]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_20]: Weird.
[SPEAKER_20]: And here's some stuff about Hidden Plus and Sudden Plus.
[SPEAKER_20]: Here's something interesting.
[SPEAKER_20]: On Hidden Plus and Sudden Plus, you can actually change the width of the cover not only before the song begins, but also during gameplay by holding the start button and adjusting it with the turntable.
[SPEAKER_06]: Weird.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you can actually adjust the windows that you're hiding or, you know, either way.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_20]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_20]: Yeah, not only before the song starts, but during gameplay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow, that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, like, if you decide that, oh, a little too much on the sudden thing, or maybe I put it on accidentally, then I could just use the start button to, like, take it off by rolling it so much that it would just not be there.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_20]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_20]: And then there's already a new way of accessing the extra stage, which is Scream Squad by Cap.
[SPEAKER_20]: And the way you do it is, on the first and second stage, you have to double A in another of any level with hard mode.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, so you can get the extra stage that way just by double A-ing in another on hard.
[SPEAKER_20]: I'm not done yet.
[SPEAKER_20]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_20]: On the final stage, you have to double A a level 10 or higher...
[SPEAKER_20]: either in hyper or another with hard mode, no random, no mirror.
[SPEAKER_20]: And that's to get the one more extra stage?
[SPEAKER_20]: No, that's how you get the extra stage.
[SPEAKER_06]: Really?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, dang, so they just raised the bar on that, basically.
[SPEAKER_06]: More complicated, yeah.
[SPEAKER_20]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_20]: Usually on the previous 2DX styles, like until 2DX Red, you just double level 8 another with hard mode.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_20]: That's the simplest way, but now they made it more complicated.
[SPEAKER_06]: Disco Yotsu Uchi Inochi
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, thank you for issuing that correction.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was very honest of you.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wish the regular media could be that way.
[SPEAKER_20]: Anything else you want to share with us about the 2DX world?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, just
[SPEAKER_20]: Just to name some artists.
[SPEAKER_20]: I'll just name the artists that have songs.
[SPEAKER_20]: Don't Let It Go by Uchis, Uchida Brothers.
[SPEAKER_20]: And then there's, what do you call it?
[SPEAKER_20]: Spark by Silver Fox Productions featuring Hoshino Kanako.
[SPEAKER_20]: Under the Sky by Minami Sayaka from B4U with Platonix.
[SPEAKER_20]: What else?
[SPEAKER_20]: Yeah, there's Happy Angel by Jun Fichin Takirik or Tahiri.
[SPEAKER_20]: And these are more songs that are in Happy Sky, yes?
[SPEAKER_20]: Yeah, the ones that have Japanese characters that you might not understand.
[SPEAKER_06]: Gotcha, okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_20]: And then there's Garden by Aokiriye.
[SPEAKER_20]: I'll just type them after this call.
[SPEAKER_06]: Works for me.
[SPEAKER_20]: Whenever there are song titles, just point me out and I'll type them in.
[SPEAKER_20]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alrighty.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, thanks for the call, Siggy.
[SPEAKER_06]: We appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Later.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's our resident 2DX whore, Siggy?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yay whore!
[SPEAKER_06]: Calling us.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was going to load the It's So Much Fun clip again, but I think we've really run out of the ground.
[SPEAKER_06]: Right.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's so much fun?
[SPEAKER_05]: Playing the clip over and over?
[SPEAKER_05]: Is that so much fun?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, actually it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tons of fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: Somebody said they were going to make a ytmnd.com site out of that.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know that's the site where...
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, the one I think of is the con one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have you seen that site?
[SPEAKER_06]: It just repeats that file over and over.
[SPEAKER_06]: Con!
[SPEAKER_17]: Con!
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's the background is the, you know, William Shatner going, ah!
[SPEAKER_06]: Somebody was going to make a site.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you know how, like, now they have this site where you can build your own YTMND site?
[SPEAKER_06]: Somebody's going to build one of those for you going, oh, it's so much fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, it's so much fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: It'll be hilarious.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, we got another call on Skype.
[SPEAKER_06]: That sounds like a winner.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sorry, but I have to do a little rant here about the whole hot coffee thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: You have to introduce yourself first.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm Reznor.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, Reznor.
[SPEAKER_06]: Reznor calls us quite a bit.
[SPEAKER_06]: The resident drunk.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, we like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was the resident drunk last night, but I'm okay now.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sorry, but the whole media finding... The media is basically behind the times on anything that relates to anything related with a computer or a video game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ooh, hot shit.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's sex in a video game.
[SPEAKER_08]: We can't have this.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it's fine and alright to have people doing drive-bys and shooting people and ripping off heads.
[SPEAKER_08]: Violence is quite alright, but doing somebody in the ass isn't.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, this just goes back to what is acceptable in R-rated movies as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, remember the whole stink with that movie Eyes Wide Shut where, oh no, they're going to show some titties and some penises and it's going to be NC-17.
[SPEAKER_06]: But meanwhile, the latest like Terminator 3 where they just blow shit up left and right is, you know, just a relatively mild R. Exactly.
[SPEAKER_08]: Case in point of horrendous violence being completely accepted would be Dead Alive where in a movie this guy is fighting zombies with a...
[SPEAKER_08]: Freaking Lawnmower strapped to his chest and he runs up to him and chops him in half.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not to mention the fact that he is also de-birthed by his demon mother, sucked right into her vagina and then pulled right the hell back out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh my god, I have this movie.
[SPEAKER_08]: I need to watch it now.
[SPEAKER_14]: Sweet.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay, okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: This inspires me.
[SPEAKER_14]: Zombie movie night at my house.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, let's not segue into zombies.
[SPEAKER_14]: Dead Alive and Wild Hero.
[SPEAKER_06]: Reznor wants to finish his thought.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sorry, but the media are complete idiots when it comes to anything technological.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anything.
[SPEAKER_08]: The story on podcasting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, it's so fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I just had a local story in the local news.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's like, kids are attending these new parties called LAN parties, where they come together for 24 hours of caffeine-fueled fun, playing very violent games and swapping files back and forth.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello, we've been doing this crap since what, 1995?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just now reaching the media?
[SPEAKER_08]: Pull your collective heads out of your asses for a change!
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh my god!
[SPEAKER_06]: I remember the LAN forum, because that's the only way you could play like Doom 2 multiplayer was to do the LAN thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, doing dial-up and then have phone calls like $500.
[SPEAKER_14]: I remember playing 11-player Duke Nukem 3D on a LAN.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, that's right, Duke Nukem is another one.
[SPEAKER_14]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sorry, but the media are just such whores.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'd like to round, as I said in the chat room, I'd like to round them all up in a pit and reenact the scene from HUD where they're shooting the cattle.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's such bullshit.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what amazes me about this whole thing is that Grand Theft Auto is a bit of a scapegoat because it's not like we have never had sex before.
[SPEAKER_06]: or very, very sexual things in games before.
[SPEAKER_06]: This could go all the way back to Custer's Revenge.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, granted, Custer's Revenge was not a runaway sales hit, shall we say, and neither was Night Trap, even though that game didn't have sex in it.
[SPEAKER_06]: But God of War has a sex minigame in it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think the only reason that they're scapegoating Grand Theft Auto is because it's been in the spotlight before.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm surprised they didn't start whipping out Doom 3 and just saying, oh, there's demonology and rituals and there's blood all over the place.
[SPEAKER_06]: But that's okay because that's blood.
[SPEAKER_08]: Exactly, but they're only scapegoating GTA because it was in the spotlight before, and they just want to rile up the collection of Bible-thumping parents out there and say, ooh, look, there's titties and a money shot.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ignore the fact that the game says the F word and nigger half the time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, no, it's great, though, too, is, like I predicted, this is only the beginning, it's the whole nipple gate all over again, and as we'll be covering in our podcast later, they're coming after Sims 2's nude patch now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, yeah, you're saying that it's appealing to pedophiles.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a huge difference.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, Newsflash, there are Ken dolls underneath those blurs.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not on the patch that I have!
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a huge difference, too, between the Sims 2 thing and the Grand Theft Auto thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: As I pointed out earlier, I believe the Grand Theft Auto thing to be a case of lazy programming.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: That they break it down into second grade language for these people so that they understand.
[SPEAKER_06]: And draw pictures if you have to.
[SPEAKER_06]: To understand the difference between what happened with Grand Theft Auto San Andreas and people outright making the nude patches for other games.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, God, within like five seconds of the Tomb Raider game being out, somebody had a patch so you could see Lara Croft's pussy.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, that's just...
[SPEAKER_08]: I still think that our society is so fucked up that where you can rip somebody's head off with the spine attached, dangling with blood dripping off of it, it's considered alright, but a money shot of man goo in the face of a woman on her knees is so taboo.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, to put it into perspective though, the spinal cord attached to the head thing, and I assume you're referencing Mortal Kombat, I seem to recall that did have this whole theory of the attention with it.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's why it wasn't in the Super Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_06]: Basically what it's basically boiling down to is
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll bet you anything here's what happens about this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because parents are lazy and can't figure out how to do these things themselves, remember what they had to do for televisions?
[SPEAKER_06]: That it's mandatory that the V-chip be installed in all television sets?
[SPEAKER_06]: So that you can block programs above a certain rating if you want to.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that way parents could still leave their kids unattended and the TV does the babysitting for them.
[SPEAKER_08]: The only problem with that is the parents are half stupid about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: They can't even work the VCR half the time.
[SPEAKER_08]: The kids have already figured a way to hack around the VCR.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not going to disagree with you there.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I bet you anything, as a result of this, it's going to be required in these next-gen systems that they do some similar type of...
[SPEAKER_06]: This is really crazy.
[SPEAKER_07]: They already have that!
[SPEAKER_07]: It's already in the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's already on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's already on the Xbox.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're pre-programmed in there.
[SPEAKER_07]: But guess what?
[SPEAKER_07]: Nobody knows about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because they're not responsible parents.
[SPEAKER_07]: Even if this game is adults only, kids are still going to be playing it because their dumbass parents go and buy it for them.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what I hope happens?
[SPEAKER_07]: Here's what I hope happens.
[SPEAKER_07]: The game gets rated adults only.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck it, let's do whatever the fuck we want.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want to have it where the main character goes and rapes babies and sends people on fire.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck it, you know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: I can do it now because it is an adults-only game.
[SPEAKER_07]: So fuck you, can't say shit, adults-only.
[SPEAKER_14]: You just make a game that says, fuck your children, this is adults-only.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want to be able to ride around in a car that has a collective of child heads lined up on the front of the car for the grill, and I also have a rocket launcher that fires chickens butt-first out of it towards little old ladies that are carrying groceries.
[SPEAKER_08]: And if you happen to knock one old lady into another, and her head gets stuck up her butt, you get a bonus score.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's the problem though with the AO, you know, we're going to have this adults only orgy of games now.
[SPEAKER_06]: The thing is, is that the targets, not really the targets, but they're part of it, the Walmarts of the world, the Best Buys of the world, the GameStops and... Oh, don't even get me started on stupid fucking Walmarts.
[SPEAKER_06]: All these stores, all the big stores are going to pull, they're not going to have these games because they're the equivalent of porn.
[SPEAKER_06]: So the only way you're ever going to find these AO games is in the back room of some video clearance center, rundown shack.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, time for the mom and pops to come back.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what, if these big store chains don't want to carry the hot games out there, people will go other places and find them.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what the internet's for.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a wired world out there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fuck Walmart.
[SPEAKER_14]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_14]: No one buys games anymore anyways.
[SPEAKER_14]: They're always pirating them off the internet.
[SPEAKER_14]: You can probably end up buying them out of vending machines in Japan.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, I want to buy an adults-only game right next to being able to buy beer and sweaty girls' panties.
[SPEAKER_08]: Shit, I'm out of beer.
[SPEAKER_06]: Reznor, can't say we necessarily disagree with you.
[SPEAKER_06]: You bring an interesting perspective to it, and I'll tell you what, you should be a game designer, because I think the Rabing Grandma game or whatever you had going on here was pretty hot, and I'd buy it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Raping Grandma's 3, now with the new raccoon tail power-up.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's the Grandma game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because you can fuck Grandma across the Oregon Trail.
[SPEAKER_06]: You just wanted to work in the words Oregon Trail into this show, didn't you?
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, not really.
[SPEAKER_14]: Someone has pointed out to me that the game that you're talking about sounds a lot like Death Race 2000.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, yes, it does.
[SPEAKER_06]: Can you imagine the grandma game, though, where they've got, you know, oh, here's grandma number one.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's Maude.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, Grandma Maude, answer this question.
[SPEAKER_06]: You've got to flash your titties.
[SPEAKER_08]: Whoa, whoa, okay, that's one instance I agree against porn.
[SPEAKER_14]: You say Maude, and I think of Bea Arthur now, so that's scary, because she had that show.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then you have the movie Airheads, it's like, I want naked pictures of Bea Arthur.
[SPEAKER_06]: No you don't, no you don't.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, all kidding aside, you bring up some good points, Reznor, and I hope America's listening.
[SPEAKER_08]: Long live USA.
[SPEAKER_06]: Any other final thoughts for us?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I'll save it for the FU.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sounds good to me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you for being a friend.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_14]: You're the kind of listener we encourage.
[SPEAKER_14]: One more call.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_22]: Loki for president, please.
[SPEAKER_22]: I nominate Loki for president.
[SPEAKER_22]: That was just awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, come on.
[SPEAKER_06]: His ego doesn't need any more of that, please.
[SPEAKER_22]: Hey, you can be vice president.
[SPEAKER_22]: DarkSakura can be the first lady.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, I'm the meat dictator.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm the Illuminati!
[SPEAKER_06]: Jamie would be evil dictator of the country that would start World War III with Loki's country.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's kind of how it would work, so...
[SPEAKER_22]: Right now I want her and Hillary Clinton in a ring, three minutes, no polls barred, no TQ match.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's what I want.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'd be taking out the brass knucks and breaking her face.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm glad this is uncensored radio because we could get in an AO right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bitch, no you didn't.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fuck that bullshit.
[SPEAKER_22]: Just bring it on.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was going to say, I was going to run that clip again.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, what do you think about running for president?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, it's so fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I'm too lazy to queue up the clip again.
[SPEAKER_06]: So what else is on your mind, my friend?
[SPEAKER_22]: This is Ranchan, by the way, and a lot of crazy things have been happening to me the last couple of days, last two, three days.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like what kinds of crazy things?
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't forget it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was going to make a sitcom reference or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: Forget it.
[SPEAKER_06]: What kinds of crazy things?
[SPEAKER_22]: Let's say I order a package for a friend of mine for a birthday gift.
[SPEAKER_22]: It shows up the day after the party.
[SPEAKER_22]: My family just went into utter turmoil right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I'm sorry to hear that.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, you don't know.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'll probably PM you that later.
[SPEAKER_22]: On the good side, I just found out there's going to be an anime con in Sacramento this weekend.
[SPEAKER_06]: I heard about some anime con that's going to be at the mall or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, goody.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not that one again.
[SPEAKER_22]: I sent Jamie the information already.
[SPEAKER_22]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: Remember the last time?
[SPEAKER_14]: I have saw the email and then I got bombarded, so... Sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember the last time we went to that thing?
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm afraid of anime cons in a mall.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was basically a bunch of vendors getting together to sell shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it was okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: The typical Sunrise Fest.
[SPEAKER_06]: The video room was the old McDonald's that is converted into like every store possible.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was pretty funny, I have to admit.
[SPEAKER_22]: Anime Cons of the Mall, I got you beat.
[SPEAKER_22]: My anime cosplay club had like a little picnic in Central Park last weekend.
[SPEAKER_22]: We came across another cosplaying group known as the Naruto Crack Crew.
[SPEAKER_22]: They came in full Naruto cosplay gear and we're just staring at them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow, that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_22]: I mean, I wore my forehead protector and that was it.
[SPEAKER_22]: I mean, no more Naruto cards, please.
God, no.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um... We might go check out the con.
[SPEAKER_06]: My only problem is that I'm actually flying out to the East Coast on Sunday, which I think is the day that the majority of the con is taking place, so I don't know if I personally can go, but maybe my esteemed co-presenters can go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Go where?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll think about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: The, um...
[SPEAKER_06]: Go hand out flyers for our show or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll go buy a pretzel.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I like their pretzel.
[SPEAKER_06]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_22]: Get me a box of tofu.
[SPEAKER_22]: Are you still meeting me when I come out to the East Coast?
[SPEAKER_22]: Yes, a few of my friends are going to get together after the tournament.
[SPEAKER_22]: We want to drag you off to a diner.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sounds good to me.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, as long as I'm back at a decent hour, because I do have to work the next day.
[SPEAKER_06]: But yes, I can do that.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's the whole problem.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_22]: We'll keep the alcohol to a minimum, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: Sounds good to me, because I have a low tolerance.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Excellent.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anything else you want to share with us today?
[SPEAKER_22]: Can I get a request of Let's Groove, my tips and tricks, please?
[SPEAKER_06]: I will try and work it in a little later.
[SPEAKER_22]: Sweet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Send me a private message so I don't forget.
[SPEAKER_22]: I will.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Later, my friend.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, good calls tonight, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_06]: We appreciate... We like our intelligent listeners.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is what really motivates us to do what we do here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, and now something that takes no intelligence whatsoever.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's the Orange Lounge Radio Cage Match.
[SPEAKER_06]: In tonight's cage match, three songs will do battle.
[SPEAKER_06]: Whoops, where'd Hollick go?
[SPEAKER_06]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Three songs will do battle in tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_06]: Last week's winner, you get a clip of it, two brand new songs.
[SPEAKER_06]: Your votes in the chat room at OrangeLoungeRadio.com, clicking on chat, will determine the winner.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the winning song goes into rotation all week long on Orange Lounge Radio Live, Milani Music and more programs.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, first up we get last week's winner, last week in the Orange Lounge Cage Match, a very interesting spin on a 70s classic one, and it was kind of one of those moments where DarkSakura and I went, huh?
[SPEAKER_06]: But you guys voted for it, you voted for Loki's pick of Ozzy Osbourne with Stayin' Alive, so it comes back as song number one this week, here's a clip, Ozzy Osbourne, Stayin' Alive.
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_17]: Stayin' Alive!
Stayin' Alive!
[SPEAKER_17]: It's alright, it's okay, you may go the other way We can try to understand, but you don't have to think of me It's alright, it's okay, come and see another day We can try to understand, but you don't have to think of me Ha ha ha ha ha
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, that was song number one in tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ozzy Osbourne was staying alive.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, song number two in tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to do my pick for song number two.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I've decided to pick this group.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's somebody I got turned on to by a friend who just saw them live recently.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I went and downloaded some of their stuff on iTunes, and I really dug it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I wanted to share one of their songs with you guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um...
[SPEAKER_06]: Bjerg Bjorg
[SPEAKER_06]: But it's actually pronounced Bjork, but everybody says Bjork.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then there's what, Sigurjs and all those bands too?
[SPEAKER_06]: Sigurjs.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sigurjs or whatever, Figaro.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh my god, they should have like all the Icelandic bands do like one song together.
[SPEAKER_06]: All three of them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not to make fun of Icelandic bands, because there's actually some pretty kickass music from Iceland.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just funny names.
[SPEAKER_06]: So anyway, this band is Roisk... I think it's Roiskopp.
[SPEAKER_06]: Roiskopp?
[SPEAKER_06]: Roy Scopp, we'll say that, Roy Scopp, and the song is called Only This Moment, and it's song number two in tonight's cage match, enjoy.
Thanks for watching!
Thank you for watching!
All your things are just together, close to perfection Nothing else will always be right Trust in the light, stand on the side of the line, survive All your things are just together, close to perfection Nothing else will always be right Trust in the light, stand on the side
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, that was song number two in tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was Roixop with Only This Moment.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see if the other folks in the room liked it or didn't.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_14]: I liked it, but it was probably something I'd listen to if I was trying to go to sleep or like working on a picture or something.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's very good, I would give it an 8.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki!
[SPEAKER_06]: I actually kind of like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would give it an 8 as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: Jonas!
[SPEAKER_06]: Exquisite!
[SPEAKER_21]: I'll give it like an 8.5 on this one.
[SPEAKER_21]: I actually like the tunes, kind of like, it reminds me back in the 8-bit days because of the tunes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that's kind of what I like about it too.
[SPEAKER_21]: And it makes me feel relaxed and stuff.
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't care if it has cultural relevance!
[SPEAKER_14]: Shame, shame.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's all good, don't worry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: What song are you putting in the cage match tonight, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_14]: It's a song we freaking should have had in rotation a long time ago, which I was afraid it already was.
[SPEAKER_06]: We have a different version, like a different mix of it in rotation.
[SPEAKER_14]: Like the crap version.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: I am a big fan of the Best of Move series.
[SPEAKER_14]: I always have been.
[SPEAKER_14]: I can kick anybody's asses on this game.
[SPEAKER_14]: Challenge me.
[SPEAKER_14]: I swear I will own you.
[SPEAKER_06]: I challenge you.
[SPEAKER_14]: You know I'll own you.
[SPEAKER_06]: On-air duel.
[SPEAKER_14]: On the first one, I used to have all the commands memorized.
[SPEAKER_14]: I would play without them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: On Busta... Well, for me it was Busta Groove, because I was raised on the US one.
[SPEAKER_06]: That is what I played non-stop before DDR, so... I think we would probably have to do like... We would just get perfect scores all the time.
[SPEAKER_14]: It would be a tough match, I'll put it that way.
[SPEAKER_14]: Anyway, this is from the first one, it's Kitty N's theme song from the Japanese one, so it's the good version, and not the one trying to sound like the real McCoy.
[SPEAKER_14]: I forgot who exactly was the singer on it, but it actually made top ten in the charts in Japan, from what I understand.
[SPEAKER_14]: And it's a big Avex Tracks song, so it's I'll Show You No Knife.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, here it is, song number three in tonight's cage match.
Thanks for watching!
Thank you for watching.
Please subscribe to my channel.
See you next time.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, what you think?
[SPEAKER_14]: Actually, it was pointed out to me that the file actually went wrong with the name.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's Alzora.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_14]: But, at any rate, yeah, I love that song.
[SPEAKER_14]: I've loved that song forever.
[SPEAKER_14]: It gets an 11.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if it was an 11, but it was okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I'd give it a 7.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, it sounds just like the original one to me.
[SPEAKER_14]: It is the original one.
[SPEAKER_05]: It sounds like the English one, okay?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, it doesn't.
[SPEAKER_05]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just okay.
[SPEAKER_21]: Jonas.
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't see the big difference between the English version too much, except that the Japanese is a little better, but I'll say it's 8.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like that song a lot.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wish we had had that version of it in our Bust a Move, but we didn't.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it's getting, it's kinda, I don't know, it's kinda old.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the only thing it has really going against it is that the song's kinda been out a while.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it's still a good song.
[SPEAKER_06]: I give it an 8 as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, let's recap the three songs you kids can vote for tonight in the cage match.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then you can place your votes.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, let's start it off with song number one you can vote for tonight is Ozzy Osbourne with Stayin' Alive.
[SPEAKER_06]: And song number two you can vote for tonight is Royce Skopp with Only This Moment.
[SPEAKER_06]: And song number three you can vote for tonight is Avex with Pronounce This For Me, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, place vote now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Send a private message to Sky in the chat room with your vote, and we'll tally them up and let you know who the wiener is.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, this is usually the part of the show where I ask you what's going on in the sim scene as if you're paying any attention to it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I am paying attention to it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I check my cell every day.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: We already talked about tourney mix and how we don't care.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, last tourney mix in case you missed it last week.
[SPEAKER_06]: is coming out pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: Get your files in if you really want to participate.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then that's on ddrei.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then, of course, the DDR OSC competition, the Psychopath Edition, which is all funny files, that was judged and I think is over with.
[SPEAKER_05]: And nothing else going on.
[SPEAKER_18]: What about the fun mix?
It's a fun event.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you retired from the sim scene?
[SPEAKER_06]: You're not making your crazy-ass sim files?
[SPEAKER_05]: There is a guy that actually posted a song file that said that he made it, I think it was a Max Remix, that said, by explicit.
[SPEAKER_05]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_05]: Serious.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't make this up.
[SPEAKER_21]: Interesting, I remember this before, someone sent, like, two of my sim files into B-Style, and I hammered it up too hard, so...
[SPEAKER_21]: except we got some, well I can't say the word new, who's that someone else by the name Explicit Alpha, because I'm Explicit Gamma on the B- style, he said some guy named Explicit Alpha sent a file called Legend of Trance 2004, hell no, that's the same person, I just have various Alpha, Beta, Gamma, Delta, I don't know what's next, that is all.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: While I'm tallying up the cage match votes over here, DarkSakura, why don't you fill us in on some of the other lovely programming we have here on Orange Launch Radio, at least the one other show we have right now.
[SPEAKER_14]: The one other show.
[SPEAKER_14]: On Tuesdays, pre-show starting at a quarter to seven, show starting at 7.30.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's Pacific time for everybody else.
[SPEAKER_14]: We have Pump Up the Volume, which is a music request show in theory, although I pretty much just submit everybody to whatever I want to play for them.
[SPEAKER_14]: It goes on to about 10.30.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'd like to catch everybody up on this week in Max Remixes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Starting with Maximum, with three X's, by Mochi13.
[SPEAKER_06]: We have Max 300, the MSG Remix by Fear of the Dragon.
[SPEAKER_06]: Requiem for Max, Max 100, Max Takedown, Max Relord.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why Relord?
[SPEAKER_06]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_06]: That doesn't make any sense.
[SPEAKER_06]: Relord, Max Cremation, Max Dominator, Zephyr, Max Speedmix, Max Francis, Max 300 Period, Max Hold.
[SPEAKER_06]: Stop.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just stop, people.
[SPEAKER_06]: But there's one, though, I swear.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I know it's one I downloaded just to check it out to see what it was.
[SPEAKER_06]: Max Takedown.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they say that the friend says, this is a version of Max that my friend Explicit made.
[SPEAKER_05]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_05]: So, yeah.
Wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Told you.
[SPEAKER_21]: Wow, just wow.
[SPEAKER_21]: There's only one Explicit.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Legend of Vertax
[SPEAKER_21]: Because they try to fuse In The Groove and DDR together, so they come up with this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, I found this great new remix of Max recently.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a really good Max mix.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is a good Max mix, huh?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh wait, I'm just kidding, that's Energizer from In The Groove 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: That joke never gets old.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh no.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's go to the cage match winner, shall we?
[SPEAKER_06]: You want to know who won tonight's cage match?
[SPEAKER_06]: You can't handle who won tonight's cage match!
[SPEAKER_17]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, the winner in tonight's cage match, very, very close.
[SPEAKER_06]: Very, very close battle tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, in the end, one song squeaked by to win it, and it's the song from Bust a Move.
[SPEAKER_06]: Woohoo!
[SPEAKER_06]: Who knew that there were so many fanboys and fangirls in there for Bust a Move?
[SPEAKER_06]: Very, very close with the Roy Scup song, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: Very, very close.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which is unusual for my song to get that many votes, so... Damn you, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_21]: Damn you to heck.
[SPEAKER_21]: Whatever sounds better.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know, it's alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: I won't take it personally.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's go to a break, shall we?
[SPEAKER_06]: I promised a break.
[SPEAKER_06]: I unlocked the first picture in this wonderful game I'm playing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Playing Gal's Panic!
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I'm not playing Gal's Panic.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm playing Peekaboo Poker for the NES.
[SPEAKER_07]: One of the few adult games.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is that like Bubble Bath Babes?
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe by the same company.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, it says, Hi, I'm Full House Francine.
[SPEAKER_07]: Are you feeling lucky tonight?
[SPEAKER_07]: Want to fill up my house?
[SPEAKER_05]: And this is like the worst graphics in the world.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is what they need to be coming after.
[SPEAKER_05]: These really sick games for the Nintendo Entertainment System.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bad Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to go to a break, you guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: And this song here, we're going to start it off with a special dedication.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is Let's Groove from DDR Max.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Ron Chan wanted to hear this one, so we're dedicating it to him.
[SPEAKER_06]: And here it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: Enjoy.
[SPEAKER_17]: All right!
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_13]: Mr. Random Person on the Street, who, by the way, is not an actor, what do you think of the Orange Lounge mainlining music in Morse Show?
[SPEAKER_09]: The music is like being transported to just this dancing spaceship place.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's...
[SPEAKER_09]: on Earthly.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like being in a club, except you don't have to actually ask someone to dance.
[SPEAKER_06]: Jonas, that goes double for you.
[SPEAKER_06]: You haven't been here in a while.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know you've got some stored up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you going to cut it up like they cut me up in the interview?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, I will cut you up just like they cut up Loki's interview.
Remember, I cut myself up with
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, yeah, that's right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_06]: First, before we get to the FUs of the week though, Loki wanted me to talk about this because he's like, Rob, you have to talk about this story I posted, so fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: DJ Maxx, it's this Korean online rhythm music game and it's going to be coming out for the PSP.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tell us a little more about DJ Maxx, Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: DJ Maxx was by the creators of Easy to DJ, those who may not remember Easy to DJ, was the actual competitor for Beatmania out there.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was 5 key with turntables, kind of set up like Beatmania 2DX where the turntables are on the outside.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also had foot pedals on it, just like Beatmania 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: So this game's coming out now.
[SPEAKER_05]: DJ Max though, it's only 5 key, I believe it's only 5 key and no turntable.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, actually I take that back.
[SPEAKER_05]: 7 key, no turntable.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the songs are awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're by the same artists that were in Easy to DJ and the quality is just really good.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's an online game right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it is coming, well they have a cell phone version I guess, but this one's coming to the PSP.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is it going to suck as much as like Beatmania on Gameboy?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think the way they can do it, because it's just five key presses, so I'm sure they can map it out in some way that'll make sense.
[SPEAKER_06]: They should do the type of thing where you can turn it like on its side, so you can see the notes coming down better.
[SPEAKER_06]: They did that on Wonderswan.
[SPEAKER_06]: PSP Keyboard Version 2.0 Firmware Next Week
[SPEAKER_06]: So, um... Is that the white PSP coming out at that same time, too?
[SPEAKER_05]: White PSP's coming out in September.
[SPEAKER_06]: It will be built in with firmware 2.0, so... Didn't you say you were going to buy two, just so you could have your old emulator PSP?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I wanted to buy two just because of that, because I'm...
[SPEAKER_05]: Curious to see, what I want to do is if the PSP looks like it can download files, and if it can download audio files, it can download our podcast.
[SPEAKER_05]: If it can download our podcast, I'm going to make a PSP page where you can download the podcast on the format for the PSP and whatnot, special content, that type of thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, but this looks really cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: First, like, rhythm music game that I think is coming, well, unless you count Luminous, but that's not really a rhythm music game, it's more of a puzzle game.
[SPEAKER_05]: But this is going to be coming out, um,
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: This is all happening because of you.
[SPEAKER_06]: This was all your idea.
[SPEAKER_06]: Your big evil empire that you've built since episode one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why is it that we have to do these FUs of the week every single week?
[SPEAKER_14]: My big, humongous FU goes for the... First FU to that microphone because it's fucking up again.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're just gonna have to replace the damn thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Go ahead and try.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, what about the one I bought?
[SPEAKER_06]: We could always sub that in.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, we'll have a look.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's right there behind you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is it plugged in?
[SPEAKER_14]: No, I can just take the top off of it.
[SPEAKER_14]: First off, he goes through technical difficulties.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hold on a sec.
[SPEAKER_14]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_14]: Much better.
[SPEAKER_14]: Bye bye, piece of shit microphone!
[SPEAKER_14]: Anyway, F you to the microphone.
[SPEAKER_14]: F you to work.
[SPEAKER_14]: Specifically, and now keep in mind, I adore, you know, I adore my co-workers.
[SPEAKER_14]: My boss is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: But, just, a good manager should not let their stress bleed onto their employees, right?
[SPEAKER_14]: That's been happening.
[SPEAKER_14]: and I have been getting all stressed out at work and it's not good if I get all stressed out Thursday I went home sick with a combination of fatigue, low blood sugar and a pretty high level of stress ended up having a venti green tea frappuccino which I finished in twice the time Dan finished his and I still laid down at 9 o'clock and didn't wake up until 2 when he came home with his new car which is a model up for mine and brand new but my car still looks better I digress
[SPEAKER_14]: That's really it, really it.
[SPEAKER_14]: And also, oh yeah, F.U.
[SPEAKER_14]: to how expensive the furniture we want is.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay, I'm done.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, let's move on to Loki's F.U.s of the week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it's so fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: The first F.U.
[SPEAKER_06]: of the week goes to KCRA3.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, now, I have to preface this with the fact Brian, the interviewer, he was great.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, the reporter was awesome, the cameraman was awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just whoever edited the damn thing, not awesome, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: They really need to learn we're better than heat, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: So, no plug, they fucking suck for that, and the fact that they cut this, like, really stupid clip of me talking and saying, it's so fun, you know, don't even put me in it at all, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because at least I don't look like a fucking idiot.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm definitely going to have some written contract for the next person that interviews us.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's going to be some serious issues.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_06]: So fuck you to that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fuck you to stupid people that are driving too damn slow.
[SPEAKER_06]: Especially people from Arizona.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like this woman today, uh... It was like... I don't even remember what it was.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was like... Like... Old... Old... Toot or something like that is what the license plate said.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was just like...
[SPEAKER_05]: No, old fart or something, old toot, you know, I'm like... Okay, so I think it was actually this old guy.
[SPEAKER_05]: When we drove by him, the guy looked like he was a corpse driving the car.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, head is back like... Driving the car.
[SPEAKER_06]: Really hilarious.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is what you do.
[SPEAKER_06]: You tell them it's a health hazard.
[SPEAKER_06]: They'll be on it fast.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, they're just retarded.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're replacing the whole unit and they fucked something up so they have to, you know, come out Monday first thing and fix it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently this wasn't the first apartment that they did that to because they were telling me that, oh yeah, we replaced the whole unit and it's defective already.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we had to sit there for messing around with it and figure out what was wrong.
[SPEAKER_05]: So fuck you to that and fuck you to my mom's stupid dog for keeping me up every night because she wanted attention at three in the morning.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: My turn.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'd like to give an F you to 12-hour workdays like the one I had on Friday.
[SPEAKER_06]: That kind of sucked because I came home and I napped for a long time and then I ended up staying up until like 4 in the morning because my sleep schedule was just all screwed up.
[SPEAKER_06]: But don't get me wrong, I love my job.
[SPEAKER_06]: I could do without the 12-hour workdays.
[SPEAKER_06]: If I could do my job 8 hours evenly every day, I'd be fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: So...
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh well, I guess it comes with the territory.
[SPEAKER_06]: An F you to the fact that I have to travel soon because I'm going to miss being here for two weeks.
[SPEAKER_06]: It makes it hard to do a podcast every single week when I'm not going to be here and trying to do a three hour show as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'd like to be here for that.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, a general angst to leaving and then going to an area that's going to be, you know, it's not like I'm going to Disneyland, people.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, oh well, it comes with the territory.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then, um,
[SPEAKER_06]: An F you to the fact that when I tried to play 2DX 6 style and 3rd style earlier this week, they wouldn't work with my component cables for some reason.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't figure out if that's a resolution thing or what the hell is going on.
[SPEAKER_06]: So F you to me being a technological idiot when it comes to the new TV.
[SPEAKER_06]: But otherwise, I love my new TV.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's so pretty.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, and F you to how bad I suck at Halo 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's all.
[SPEAKER_06]: Moving on to the one and only Explicit Alright, I'll keep it quick in quick summaries, alright?
[SPEAKER_21]: FU to the whole adults only for GTA Like everybody already mentioned it a while ago And the fact that the ESRP is gonna kill sales for all those M or AO games Look what you did And FU goes to the neighbors for blaming us for killing their plants over water issues First of all, we didn't spill any water
[SPEAKER_21]: or leak any water out of nowhere.
[SPEAKER_21]: Second of all, is it even our house that was leaking water?
[SPEAKER_21]: And after it goes to the spot being broken still, I still need to get a hot tub massage.
[SPEAKER_21]: And after it goes to my tail bump being all fucked up, I gotta go check on the doctor for that one.
[SPEAKER_21]: And after it goes to Manfei on Anime Expo.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh my god, Manfei is back?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, he is back.
[SPEAKER_14]: I saw Manfei at, uh, at Faname a few years ago.
[SPEAKER_14]: A guy who cosplays as Fei, and he's really hairy.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I don't mean hairy as in scary, although Yae is scary, but I mean hairy as in covered in fur like a bear.
[SPEAKER_21]: Surprisingly he got arre- well, he didn't get arrested, but he's banned from Anime Expo, but he's-
[SPEAKER_21]: almost mooned and stuck his ass up with my friend who tried to tag on his shoe.
[SPEAKER_14]: I have only, sorry, I've only ever once seen good crossplay as in a guy crossplaying a girl.
[SPEAKER_14]: And that was a really pretty, pretty guy crossplaying Utena.
[SPEAKER_14]: From the movie.
[SPEAKER_21]: A pretty guy.
[SPEAKER_14]: A really pretty guy.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, what was I going to say?
[SPEAKER_21]: Effie goes to...
[SPEAKER_21]: This one lady that hit me during the time I was in L.A.
[SPEAKER_21]: She rear-ended me and even though there was no damage, she hit and run and blamed it was my fault.
[SPEAKER_21]: How is it my fault when you drove 15 miles an hour on the goddamn drive-thru?
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't understand that.
[SPEAKER_21]: You drive 15 miles an hour on a drive-thru and you accuse someone because they stopped.
[SPEAKER_21]: Who's to blame here?
[SPEAKER_21]: Uh, let's see.
[SPEAKER_21]: An FB to... Sir, stupid little kid just stepped on my foot!
[SPEAKER_21]: It might be really this big.
[SPEAKER_13]: And... I'm not gonna make a comment.
[SPEAKER_21]: And because I want to make sure I don't get cut off, I'll say doopie continue.
[SPEAKER_21]: Wait, actually, one more.
[SPEAKER_21]: There's one more.
[SPEAKER_21]: And a big if it goes to the whole tournament drama that was leading to the pit tournament.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh yeah, they wanted to ban some guy, that didn't make me happy.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, even though I cleared it out in a bad way, it damaged my reputation in a way.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well not you, don't take it personally, it's not you, it's the other guy.
[SPEAKER_06]: He needs to go out, he needs to be publicly spanked.
[SPEAKER_06]: He might like that though.
[SPEAKER_21]: I wonder what's going to happen in the tournament, that's all I want to know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know I gotta back Toadie up, no matter what happens.
[SPEAKER_21]: I know the band decision was uncalled for.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's why I cleared everything up to make sure, in a peaceful manner, drama.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, it's cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: It'll be cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, let's move on to the chatroom FU, shall we?
[SPEAKER_06]: And somebody said that this song is so horrid that I had to use this as the background music.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see, Misty wants to say an FU to the USB reader on the Indigroove 2, not responding to my card or any other card that was tried.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hope it's a problem that can be fixed with just a reboot.
[SPEAKER_06]: Socorina says, FU to the retard who let my 9-year-old brother play Grand Theft Auto San Andreas.
[SPEAKER_06]: Acer800 says, FU to the AC not working for a month, and my mom getting mad at me for listening to the FUs last week.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not a children's program.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not saying you're a child.
[SPEAKER_21]: Adults only.
[SPEAKER_06]: Buy headphones, okay, if you're gonna listen to our naughty language.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also, we have Reznor says a nice fuck you to cum shots being more risque than shooting someone in the ass with a hand cannon.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sakura Sin says F you to Nintendo for not making any good puzzle games lately to keep me busy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hello, did you play Meteos?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I realize Nintendo didn't make that, but Meteos is very cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've got to recommend that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Illusion says, F you to cutting my gums a few minutes ago, and now they're bleeding.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Ron Chan says, F you to the post office.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was supposed to come Friday, but it came Saturday, and I had left.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fuck you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, and F you to me running out of space on my hard drive.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's it for our angsty chatroom F yous.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it was kind of light on the angst tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was angst light.
[SPEAKER_06]: Diet angst tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, what we're going to do now, I think we're going to go ahead and go to another break.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll make this a quick break.
[SPEAKER_06]: Someone wanted to hear... There were some songs that folks wanted to hear and I already forgot what some of them were.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think someone wanted to hear System Romance.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I'm going to get to System Romance and I'll get into another song that somebody else wanted to hear.
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_13]: Last Message.
[SPEAKER_06]: You want to hear Last Message?
[SPEAKER_06]: Fine, we'll get to Last Message.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to make this a short break because we're looking for questions for Ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's right, it's time to Ask Orange Lounge or tonight you can ask Jonas as well if you want to.
[SPEAKER_06]: What the hell is that metal that you're wearing around your neck?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what I want to know.
[SPEAKER_04]: John Cena's a spinner.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a spinner?
[SPEAKER_21]: This is what I got from the WWE event.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's the spinner from John Cena.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hey, you can't see me.
[SPEAKER_14]: Obfuscate.
[SPEAKER_14]: For anyone who's ever played live action Vampire, his little waving his hand in front of his face thing is also the obfuscate action for live action Vampire.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, you can't see me.
Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, that was the other request.
[SPEAKER_06]: Somebody wanted to hear something from Silent Hills.
[SPEAKER_06]: So how about instead we hear some You're Not Here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that acceptable, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: You gonna be okay?
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay!
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, so we'll get to that.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll be back after this with more Orange Lounge Radio.
It's got to be forever, the raindrops blowing, the wind is dancing
[SPEAKER_17]: It would be a much better sight with you with me If you hadn't met me, I'd be fine on my own, baby Never felt so lonely when you came along
[SPEAKER_17]: So now what should I do?
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm strung out, addicted to you My body aches now that you're gone My sublime fell through You let me give me everything you had and more You craved my happiness when you made me feel joy in me Just smile for now
Oh hi, dead air because I forgot to put in a promo there.
We're back!
[SPEAKER_14]: Listen to Orange Lounge Radio or we eat your liver!
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's ask Orange Lounge some stupid questions.
[SPEAKER_06]: What will we find out this week on Orange Lounge Radio?
[SPEAKER_06]: What will the chatroom ask?
[SPEAKER_06]: Will it be a G-rated question?
[SPEAKER_06]: I really hope so, because this show's already too much A-O.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see, Tomokun wants to know, why was 180 mode pissed away on Parapara dancing and not in Parapara Paradise?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm assuming that's when you can turn around and do Parapara the other way?
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, so people can actually watch you doing the dancing?
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't play enough Parapara to follow that stuff, I have to admit.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, I thought it was cute for like a week, but... Do you know anything about that?
[SPEAKER_14]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know!
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, sometimes they just take modes out.
[SPEAKER_06]: But if you look up, aren't there only sensors on the front part of it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't they not have sensors on the back part of a Parapar machine?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, they don't, but you could probably put one there.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can mount it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess you could flip it around if you wanted to, but... No.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, well.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry, don't know enough about Parapar to answer your question.
[SPEAKER_06]: Boy, do we suck or what.
[SPEAKER_06]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um...
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, this question is pretty much setting us up to drop the clip again.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know that, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Illusion basically wanted to know, what does Loki think of sex with children?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's great that... Free for the producers.
[SPEAKER_10]: Free speech for everyone.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's so much fun.
[SPEAKER_17]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_10]: Shut up!
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Way to go, Rob.
[SPEAKER_17]: Bird!
[SPEAKER_06]: Give me that, then!
[SPEAKER_06]: Misty says, what song was playing during Explicits FUs?
[SPEAKER_06]: I think I recognized it, but I'm not sure because I hardly heard it.
[SPEAKER_06]: The song that was playing during Explicits FUs was EVO 66 from 2DX Red.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what song we had.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is the worst part.
[SPEAKER_03]: There we go, here we go.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was the song I was playing, Wall 5, 2DX Red.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought it was an appropriate F.U.
[SPEAKER_06]: song.
[SPEAKER_21]: I didn't even know there was a background when I was listening to F.U.s.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, RainbowsInTheNight wants to know, how can I fix my metal dance pad from Red Octane?
[SPEAKER_06]: Half of the up arrow works and the back arrow doesn't work at all.
[SPEAKER_06]: Red Octane was all like, take it to a TV repairman.
[SPEAKER_06]: Problem being, I'm broke.
[SPEAKER_06]: Any suggestions?
[SPEAKER_06]: I've already disassembled and cleaned it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Same problems.
[SPEAKER_06]: The closest DDR machine is 40 minutes away on an interstate because Virginia's pretty lame.
[SPEAKER_06]: Help would be nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, Loki, you built your own metal pads before.
[SPEAKER_06]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_06]: TV repair, man.
[SPEAKER_06]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not a TV.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_05]: Send it back to them.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's their own fucking pad.
[SPEAKER_05]: They should fix it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, now, how do the sensors work in a metal pad?
[SPEAKER_06]: At least you can explain this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, a metal pad depends.
[SPEAKER_05]: Most likely, it's just going to be contacts in there, and if half the up arrow works or whatever, probably half the contacts or something broke or something or fell off.
[SPEAKER_05]: I haven't really looked at their metal pads.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've taken apart crappy metal pads, and that's the way they work, but...
[SPEAKER_06]: How long has he had it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, we don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can ask how long he's had it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would ask, I mean, honestly, if you buy it from Red Octane, isn't there some sort of return policy or something?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, you've got to assume it's past the return policy time, though, if he's asking this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, he says, out of warranty and yes, contacts.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, my first suggestion would be clean the contacts, and he says he's disassembled and cleaned it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, does that just mean one of his contacts is broken and he's shit out of luck, or what?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not necessarily contacts.
[SPEAKER_05]: It'd be a loose wire or something, also.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hmm, that's a good thought too.
[SPEAKER_21]: What, Jonas?
[SPEAKER_21]: Give him a mic.
[SPEAKER_21]: Usually if you clean up the whole thing, usually it's not that case, because I've seen vendors actually try fixing this.
[SPEAKER_21]: You have to check if one of the wires is burnt or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: So in what case is he absolutely screwed?
[SPEAKER_06]: How would this guy know if he's just screwed and he shouldn't even bother wasting his time?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because the shit could have just broke, and that's sad.
[SPEAKER_21]: I can't answer that question unless he tells you how long he has it, how many... Yeah, he says Christmas, he says.
[SPEAKER_21]: And how many times has he been playing the game, like how many songs?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you can assume if there's no DDR machine nearby, it's probably quite a bit.
[SPEAKER_21]: All I can say is that they don't last that long.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess the best answer we can come up with is that it sounds like you already kind of have an idea how to fix this thing because you've opened it up and you've cleaned it.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's probably not a whole lot else we could tell you except take a look at the wiring and make sure you don't have any loose connections going from the contacts to the actual, like,
[SPEAKER_06]: What do they call it where it all comes together towards the top?
[SPEAKER_06]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Check your wiring, but if a wire has shorted or burned out, there's really not a whole lot short of replacing the wire that you're going to be able to do, which is something you probably don't want to try doing yourself.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, you don't want to waste too much time on it.
[SPEAKER_21]: Usually it's just to get a new pad because it's basically worn out.
[SPEAKER_21]: Wait, what games have you been playing, though?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, assuming it's DDR, some...
[SPEAKER_21]: I mean, like, there's DDR and In The Groove as well, that uses the same pads.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, but it wouldn't matter.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I can understand if In The Groove ruined those pads.
[SPEAKER_06]: Stop it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's such a horrible game.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like, I can't take it!
[SPEAKER_06]: Stop it.
[SPEAKER_06]: He says he plays every day about three to four hours a day on heavy mode, so I think you've probably just beat that pad to death.
[SPEAKER_06]: The sad thing is, those red octane pads don't last forever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I mean, honestly, if it's just, like, a metal pad or something...
[SPEAKER_06]: The contact's in it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sure there's ways that you can mod them and upgrade them.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a whole thread on DDR Freak about modding, fixing, doing stuff to your metal pads.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just go there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Take a look there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ask your question there.
[SPEAKER_06]: See if they can't help you over on the Freak.
[SPEAKER_06]: Otherwise, make Red Octane give you a better answer because that's a shitty answer they gave you.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you should email them again and tell them the people on the radio said that they gave you a shitty answer.
[SPEAKER_06]: Get that person fired.
[SPEAKER_06]: They can't say that, really.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the best thing that we can give you guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Acer 800 wants to know, who would win in an actual cage match?
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, DarkSakura, or me, Sky?
[SPEAKER_06]: Good question.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, who would win in an actual cage match between the three of us?
[SPEAKER_14]: I would.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why?
[SPEAKER_14]: Because I exercise regularly, lift weights, and I've taken karate.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've got that killing urge.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, but that's when you need to be sloppy and make mistakes.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've got a lot of smarts up here.
[SPEAKER_06]: I could... I'd make you... See, I would make Loki and DarkSakura beat up on each other while I just kind of watch.
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then that way I save my strength.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'd use you as a bludgeoning tool.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see about that one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Honestly, Acer 800, we would not know the answer to that one unless we actually tried it, which maybe we'll do one of these days.
[SPEAKER_06]: As a rating stunt.
[SPEAKER_06]: Reznor wants to know, what's the status on the old school show?
[SPEAKER_06]: The old school show was supposed to launch a couple weeks ago, and I'm really sorry it hasn't happened yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: A decision was made on the staff that we want to make it not just 8-bit music, but 16-bit music as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I've just been so freaking busy that I haven't had the time to update the 16-bit music as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I'm going to try and get on that this week, because...
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll keep you posted on that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I definitely want it to happen before summer's over.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hopefully before August gets here, so I will work just for you on the 16-bit stuff this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: Promise.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Socorino wants to know, can you make an mp3 of that Ask Orange Lounge song?
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, it's a song called Journey to the Wonderland by NPB, and it's in Keyboard Mania 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you want a clip of me actually singing it... Hey, I still have Bumblebee disguised voice mix.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh my god, that's old.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think I played it like a couple weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's very, very old.
[SPEAKER_06]: You actually played it on your show?
[SPEAKER_06]: Several times.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bitch.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Sakurina also wants to know if we could play the actual Silent Hill because I fucked up last break.
[SPEAKER_06]: He wanted to hear the actual song Silent Hill and not a song from Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_06]: So my bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're running out of time on the show, so here's a clip.
I wish we could live
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, that's all you get, sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're running short on time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tomokun wanted to make a point, just to follow up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, Parapara Dancer did have sensors on the back as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, that's why Parapara Paradise didn't have the 180 mode, because they didn't have sensors on the back.
[SPEAKER_06]: Probably a cost-cutting thing, honestly.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's my best answer.
[SPEAKER_06]: Neo Dude wants to know, what do you guys think about the Konami Red Octane Rocksaur Madcatz lawsuit?
[SPEAKER_06]: Didn't we talk about that a few weeks ago?
[SPEAKER_06]: We kind of did talk about it a few weeks ago on the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to assume that we've got a new listener on our hands, which is cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, welcome to the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hope you enjoy.
[SPEAKER_06]: But there have been, you know, a few recent developments, and you know, the chat can sometimes sway your mind.
[SPEAKER_06]: What do you think, Loki?
[SPEAKER_06]: What's your latest perspective on this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Although I already know what you're going to say.
[SPEAKER_05]: My latest perspective on this is,
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, Konami's within their rights, you know, to do this because, you know, these companies are making, you know, crappy games and, um, well, not necessarily crappy games.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're making games that obviously are too much like DDR.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, they're just trying to, like, kind of get people like, oh, hey, you like DDR?
[SPEAKER_06]: Then you'll like this almost like DDR game.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, um, you know, when it comes down to it, it's just an inferior product, just like those Apple products.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, um...
[SPEAKER_06]: You know that they were having a huge debate in the chat room before this started and it simmered down and I was hoping they would shut up already about the Apple vs. PC thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: But no, you had to go in over your big fat mouth and bring up the Apple thing again.
[SPEAKER_14]: This is because you don't know how to use it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, that's right.
[SPEAKER_14]: On!
[SPEAKER_14]: Where's your on button?
[SPEAKER_07]: How do I upgrade this thing?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, that's right.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's all built together.
[SPEAKER_06]: Stop it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've upgraded Max before.
[SPEAKER_06]: Somebody wanted me to point out that there is a... Now I don't have the exact thing, but I'm sure somebody will...
[SPEAKER_14]: I have opened up Macs before and changed out their memory, changed out the hard drives, put in new graphics cards.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, you can upgrade a Mac the same way you can a PC.
[SPEAKER_05]: No matter what you do, they're still inferior.
[SPEAKER_14]: and you're talking out of your ass.
[SPEAKER_06]: Can't we just all get along?
[SPEAKER_14]: Isn't there room for... As soon as he stops talking out of his ass and actually talks about something he knows about, maybe.
[SPEAKER_21]: Wait, now that we're on the contrary with Konami, Rockstar, and Red Octane Madcast, what would happen with this Neon FM game since... It's nothing like DDR.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's why.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'll tell you what's... That's the only thing I'm thinking about since, you know, like the Konami thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's my perspective with it.
[SPEAKER_06]: As long as Neon FM doesn't try to invade the home markets, they'll be fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I think they're going to be fine anyways because they've been working with actually Konami on this.
[SPEAKER_06]: They've actually flown the people in or whatever and had them look at the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hopefully though, hopefully though, they're not just feeding us BS with that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because the In The Groove team said, shut up, we know it's legal, and now here you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: But honestly, looking at the gameplay of this game, it is quite different from, I mean, the setup of the pads are different, the gameplay looks different, it's got just really different stuff in it, so I don't think they're going to be really in
[SPEAKER_06]: Fringing Out, whereas In The Groove looks like DDR just with different shaped arrows.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it's pretty much the same damn game.
[SPEAKER_06]: And honestly, the Mad Catz game was just a shitty game in general and brought everybody down, so it just needed a spanking, basically.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's the only question I have with what happened to Neon FM, because everyone's saying, ooh, it's Beatmania on feet.
[SPEAKER_21]: But then again, I think as long as they aren't
[SPEAKER_06]: I think as long as it's different enough from DDR with the foot layout and everything in there, in-game layout appears to be very different, I think they'll be okay, just like Pump It Up's okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: But of course you have that whole lawsuit thing, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, long story short, what I believe, what's going on with this lawsuit, In The Groove should have never tried to come out for the home systems because it awoke the Konami sleeping giant, and that's what's happening now.
[SPEAKER_21]: What anime slash video game character would you all cosplay and why?
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, you actually do cosplay, so I should start with you.
[SPEAKER_14]: I've never actually cosplayed a character from Anonymy.
[SPEAKER_14]: I've cosplayed a character from a manga.
[SPEAKER_14]: I went as Mad Hatter from Sanctuary.
[SPEAKER_14]: I've also cosplayed Baiken from Guilty Gear X. Dan didn't like that because I didn't have anything to hold my boobs up.
[SPEAKER_14]: I've cosplayed Jill from Resident Evil.
[SPEAKER_14]: I've, I actually still have that costume, I've cosplayed Emi, uh, as in 3rd Mix DDR, uh, who else have I done, oh yeah, Shorty from Bustin' Move 2, um, I really don't know, and I've been trying to think of who I would, um, Leona from,
[SPEAKER_14]: I've done Leona The costume is actually three sizes too big for me now Take that back, four sizes too big for me now So it's officially retired I was working on doing Richter Belmont from Dracula X
[SPEAKER_14]: I want to do one from an anime, I just don't know who, although it's been suggested to do Hyatt from Exosaga.
[SPEAKER_14]: But I don't want to do that outfit, and I don't want to carry around fake blood and cough.
[SPEAKER_06]: I went as Ash Ketchum one year for Halloween, does that count?
[SPEAKER_06]: I hate that name.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love Pokemon.
[SPEAKER_14]: You're watching the American Craft.
[SPEAKER_06]: Speaking of that, I am watching the American Craft.
[SPEAKER_21]: I've seen a shitload of Pokemon trainers up in Anime Expo.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, somebody start a thread on the Orange Lunch forums that should I cosplay.
[SPEAKER_14]: Loki, what would you cosplay as?
[SPEAKER_06]: Gendo the Uber Pimp.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_21]: Let's see, I'll probably cosplay as Bronco for next year.
[SPEAKER_14]: I am not cosplaying as Noodle, thank you.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know, that would be fun.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh yeah, we get some body paint and do something for the masquerade for Anime Expo.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, we have another really good question from the chat room.
[SPEAKER_06]: Illusion wants to know, what does Loki think about do-it-yourself abortion kits?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's so much fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_06]: It'll never get old, Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, but you've got to clip it out.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Tomokun would like to point out, Loki, a Power Mac, it's like a PC.
[SPEAKER_06]: They are 100% upgradable.
[SPEAKER_06]: From shit to crap.
[SPEAKER_06]: Stop it!
[SPEAKER_06]: You are... You know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: For your birthday, I'm buying you a gift certificate to the Apple Store.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I will set it on fire.
[SPEAKER_06]: You could just suffer.
[SPEAKER_06]: You will have to find something you like.
[SPEAKER_05]: I will buy... If you give me enough money to buy an iPod, I will buy enough... Buy an iPod, and I will take a sledgehammer to it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I... And then I will sell it.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're just a bastard.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love my iPod.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like the best thing ever.
[SPEAKER_06]: They said, I am a little upset because my roommate just bought an iPod and he paid the same price for his that I paid for mine, but because he bought his six months later, he got a color one.
[SPEAKER_10]: Bastard.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, that's going to do it for Ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you guys for submitting your questions.
[SPEAKER_06]: And now, it's 9.30.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's time to end the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Final thought time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Explicit, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, it's nice to meet you guys again.
[SPEAKER_21]: Just like the good old times.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm glad you found the new house okay.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, that too, and I finally got a chance to come over here to introduce the tournament, finally, since I've been so busy.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, there's a tournament that's in July 30th, this Saturday.
[SPEAKER_21]: DDRPA and Freestyle, and it is a possibility that newspaper journalists will come in for, like, Sacramento Bee.
[SPEAKER_21]: And don't forget, there's Lumpia and Ice Cream.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you might get your foot in the paper.
[SPEAKER_21]: Mmm, Lumpia.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mmm, Lumpia, I agree.
[SPEAKER_21]: Say again, what about my foot?
[SPEAKER_06]: You might get your foot in the paper, just like Loki did.
[SPEAKER_06]: If Sac B comes out, because you know Loki's foot was in the Sac B, playing DDR.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have fun at the tournament.
[SPEAKER_06]: That'll be at Paradise Island in Sacramento, California.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, indeed.
[SPEAKER_21]: In addition to a Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_21]: meetup for those who are interested in that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll just do, you know my strategy at Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_06]: is to just play as Ness.
[SPEAKER_18]: PK Fire!
[SPEAKER_06]: PK Fire!
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki!
[SPEAKER_06]: Your final thought.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just unlocked the third picture in Peek-A-Boo Poker, in which Xylox said... No, wait, no.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, what are you guys doing out there while you're watching my moves?
[SPEAKER_05]: What the hell does that mean?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's retarded.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't think that's what the fanboys are watching.
[SPEAKER_05]: See?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: My final thought is...
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm craving dinner because I haven't eaten like a real meal yet today and you guys ate all those chicken nuggets and didn't save me one.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I ate the two barbecue sauce packets.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ew.
[SPEAKER_13]: I bought cheese and cherries.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, I hope you go home and find all your computers that were replaced with Macs.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_14]: Reject false icons.
[SPEAKER_14]: And somebody buy me that 2D shirt at Hot Topic.
[SPEAKER_06]: The final word of the show, one word to sum it all up, since we actually have a special guest tonight, I'll give it to him.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, next week on Orange Haunts Radio, are we taking a vacation for two weeks?
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_06]: We might do something.
[SPEAKER_06]: Stay tuned to the website.
[SPEAKER_06]: Our podcast will still be coming to you no matter what.
[SPEAKER_06]: You may have DarkSakura chat.
[SPEAKER_06]: We don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Something will happen on the station the next couple of weeks, whether it be reruns.
[SPEAKER_06]: It won't be our normal three-hour show, but something.
[SPEAKER_06]: or maybe it will be the three hour show just sounds sky we'll see maybe we have to hash that out this week in big board meetings so we'll see you're fired we'll see alright that's going to do it final word of the show Jonas Mitchie that does it for another episode of Orange Lounge Radio Live Orange Lounge Radio Live is an Orange Lounge Radio production
[SPEAKER_02]: For more information about our station, visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com And now, here is your fortune cookie message of the day.
[SPEAKER_11]: Crumbs Chief, what do we do now?
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm taking the direct approach.
[SPEAKER_17]: Thank you very much for listening, and we'll see you next week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright guys, we're going to disconnect the station now.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can reconnect to Orange Lounge Radio in about, what is it, about 15 seconds to resume hearing all your favorite DDR, 2DX, and other video game favorites.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, what do you think about your new channel, Loki Sucks?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, it's so much fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_06]: Goodnight guys, have a good one.