[SPEAKER_03]: Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition, week of July 25th, 2005.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're tuned in to the Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition, your podcast home for all the latest video game news and gamer chat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, here are your hosts, DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hello, everybody, and welcome to another week of the Orange Lounge Radio to-go edition.
[SPEAKER_03]: This, by the way, if I've done my math right, is our 30th show.
[SPEAKER_03]: Can you believe that?
[SPEAKER_03]: We've been here every single week for about the past six months, a little more, seven months.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ever since January, we've started this thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: So thank you guys for sticking with us throughout this whole thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, of course, hello to our new listeners as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: We appreciate you guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: Deciding to check us out and listening to our little program here about video games that don't suck.
[SPEAKER_03]: Although sometimes we have to talk about the sucky ones too.
[SPEAKER_03]: But just to warn you to stay away from them.
[SPEAKER_03]: My name is Rob Roberts, you might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_03]: Joining me as always are my awesome co-hosts.
[SPEAKER_03]: Right over there, the one and only DarkSakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yo, yo, yo.
[SPEAKER_00]: What up?
[SPEAKER_00]: Menchie Hat.
[SPEAKER_03]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_03]: What is the Menchie Hat for those that may not know?
[SPEAKER_00]: It's a hat that looks like the top of Minchi's head for anyone who's ever watched Excel Saga.
[SPEAKER_03]: Excel Saga.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, and over there is the one and only Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes I am.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm right here.
[SPEAKER_03]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm doing good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, let's go around.
[SPEAKER_03]: We always like to start off the podcast letting you know about our gaming week and how we're doing in our gaming worlds.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'm going to start off with DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_03]: What have you been up to?
[SPEAKER_00]: I haven't played much of anything except DDR at the beginning of the week.
[SPEAKER_00]: Like one game.
[SPEAKER_03]: What got you into DDR suddenly?
[SPEAKER_00]: The fact that we were being filmed for the news.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh yeah, I totally forgot to say that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hello to anybody who might have seen us on the local news here in Sacramento.
[SPEAKER_00]: That was my really cool jeans.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh yeah, that you saw in the article?
[SPEAKER_00]: I was playing Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_03]: We were featured in a story on podcasting in the local news, so hello to anybody that found us through that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hopefully you weren't scared off by the way we look.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or Loki saying, gosh, podcasting is fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gosh, I'm an idiot.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or his sound clip, whatever he got.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, let's cut it down to really something stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's the stupidest line he can say?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, there it is, there it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Get it, get it, get it, get it, get it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Got it, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I laughed.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, you laughed and he called me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, you're an idiot.
[SPEAKER_04]: They made me look like a dumbass on TV.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I watched him like.
[SPEAKER_03]: IntelligentLicense IntelligentCube
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: But other than that, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: Does it have orchestra music?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I remember Intelligent Cube had a very strange soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was all this big orchestra music.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's got pretty good music in it, so it's decent.
[SPEAKER_04]: More of the same.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I've been playing that a lot.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then, what was it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Just recently I've been playing Peekaboo Poker.
[SPEAKER_04]: Please.
[SPEAKER_04]: On the Nintendo emulator, which is one of the three adult games for the...
[SPEAKER_04]: Nintendo Entertainment System, and it's very craptastic.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's by the same people that did Bubble Bath Babes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bubble Bath Babes and Hot Slots, so I have all three of those.
[SPEAKER_04]: There are some winning games right there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I remember seeing Bubble Bath Bays back in the day in a rental store, and I was like, I'm going to play that someday.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I did, and I was disappointed.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then I played Killer7.
[SPEAKER_04]: I progressed through another two levels.
[SPEAKER_04]: And there's these one Heaven Smile things you have to attack.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have t-shirts, and it's cool because you can just shoot them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then they have Giant Smile.
[SPEAKER_04]: This game right now, I thought progressing through it, I'd figure out what's going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: The more and more I progress through the game, the less and less I understand what's going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's still fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm playing through it still.
[SPEAKER_03]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anything else?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: My gaming week.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mentioned this very briefly at the end of the last podcast.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just got a new television because my old one, the RCA yellow thing was coming loose and so my video kept fading in and out.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I just finally decided to upgrade my TV and I went over to a big warehouse type store
[SPEAKER_03]: and I bought a 30 inch HDTV widescreen.
[SPEAKER_03]: So now I'm all about the widescreen games.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm like, oh, I gotta go back and play all these games because they're gonna look pretty and widescreen and I gotta find the ones that have the good graphics.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I thought, okay, I'm gonna play Halo 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's a very pretty looking game.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I got on Halo 2 and I've been downloading the new maps and checking them out.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I also got on and decided to play on Xbox Live again.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because they've been doing all these updates to the game lately, so I thought I'd see if it played any differently.
[SPEAKER_03]: And for someone like me, who's a casual Halo 2 gamer, I can't tell there's been any differences at all.
[SPEAKER_03]: Except for the new maps.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the new maps, you know, good idea.
[SPEAKER_03]: Keeps the game fresh, so that's good.
[SPEAKER_03]: One thing I did realize, however, is that I am the worst Halo 2 player on the entire internet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Seriously, I'm horrible.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've played several games and my ranking hasn't budged.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's how bad I am.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, if you ever see me...
[SPEAKER_03]: Halo 2 Halo 2
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's get into some gaming news tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: And tonight I want to start off, actually I should mention, since I was talking about Halo 2, there actually was a new Halo 2 update this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're calling it the Banhammer update.
[SPEAKER_03]: Basically what they're doing is that
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for watching, and I'll see you next time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: Cheating is not honored around here and we will ban your ass type things.
[SPEAKER_03]: Obviously they don't use that kind of language, but you get the idea.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're trying to put these little public service announcements that we catch you, we ban you type things.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're just trying to curb the people that feel like they have to cheat to get ahead in Halo 2 because being the number one person on the Halo 2 leaderboard apparently wins you all this type of fame and fortune and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Every kid wants to be it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't understand.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why would somebody want to cheat on Halo 2?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just to get ahead.
[SPEAKER_00]: Nothing better to do.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's fun to get away with it.
[SPEAKER_00]: They use the internet for self-validation.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just like people in Final Fantasy XI who are teleporting themselves around.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have people on our link show that do that, actually.
[SPEAKER_03]: Speaking of Final Fantasy XI, maybe for not much longer, because they actually had a patch this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Their patch actually had a little something to do with Chains of Promethea.
[SPEAKER_03]: They actually added a little more to the story in Chains of Promethea, and they added some more
[SPEAKER_03]: So basically they're trying to wrap up the storyline there.
[SPEAKER_03]: 43 megabyte download for PC users.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a pretty big quest.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm so glad I quit that damn game.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: Quit raining on the rest of our parades.
[SPEAKER_00]: What, did you start playing again?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm thinking about it.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, no, you said you played PSO with me.
[SPEAKER_03]: I haven't played in a month.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, no, no, PSO.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm thinking about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I downloaded the patch.
[SPEAKER_03]: But you haven't played the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't played in a month.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because the woman is yelling at me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, one thing that'll make the Final Fantasy fans happy, and this is actually something that made me happy because I've been waiting for them to do this for a long time, and it is something that is making me consider going back, but I'm not making any decisions until my work trips over next month.
[SPEAKER_03]: But what they did is that they are going to have some of these items that were selling for tons and tons of Gil, the Leaping Boots, the Emperor's Hairpin, now they're rare EX items.
[SPEAKER_03]: So Gil sellers can't camp them anymore for Gil, so...
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, they'll find other ways to make their money with the gil selling, but they're trying to at least curb that a little bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, very interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: By the way, Squeenix, what we call Square Enix, they recently registered a brand new trademark.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's called Treasures of Aturgen.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hmm, maybe a new Final Fantasy XI expansion?
[SPEAKER_03]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_04]: There was actually two names that were registered.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I didn't see the second one.
[SPEAKER_03]: I only heard that one.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't remember the other one.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll have to look it up.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, either way, rumors going around that with the Xbox 360 release, we're going to see a new expansion pack anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, all right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Cut it out.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's open up the old mailbag.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll get into something DarkSakura might be interested in.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll go to the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_00]: I've got lots of good ones.
[SPEAKER_03]: We got some good mail this week in the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_00]: I got more than what I actually ordered.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you want to start off by reading one, then?
[SPEAKER_03]: Or do you want me to go to one?
[SPEAKER_00]: Go ahead.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, I'm going to start it off with an email.
[SPEAKER_03]: This one came in from Rob.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rob wanted to follow up with something that we were saying about the Silent Hill last week.
[SPEAKER_03]: We were talking about Silent Hill 4 last week.
[SPEAKER_03]: And somebody had been dogging on Silent Hill 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, you like Silent Hill 3, right, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it might have been our emailer was dogging on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: But Rob wanted to say that the PC version of Silent Hill 3 is a gazillion CDs, but it's only $9.99.
[SPEAKER_03]: Best of all, it contains the Silent Hill 3 soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_03]: I bought the soundtrack and got a game for free.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a good way to check both out.
[SPEAKER_00]: My response to him was if you buy Silent Hill 3 for the PlayStation 2, you get the soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_03]: Really?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: But for PC it's only $10.
[SPEAKER_03]: How much is it on PS2 right now?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's got to be at least a great $10, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: So either way, I like that when they throw in those bonuses like the soundtrack and things to get you to check the game out.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I just mentioned the other name that was out there that Square Enix registered was Scars of War.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: That could be its own game, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_00]: I also got another one from him talking about...
[SPEAKER_00]: How is in Toys R Us the other day, and the six-year-old could understand that an M-rated game was for a teen and not for the kid, but parents don't seem to understand that?
[SPEAKER_00]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think that's pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_00]: In a very sad way.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, in a very sad way that the six-year-old understands the ratings better than his parents, certainly.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wanted to read another email here that came from... Let's see, who was this person?
[SPEAKER_03]: TheBrainTrust was the person that sent this email.
[SPEAKER_03]: And he was actually talking about the hot coffee mod.
[SPEAKER_03]: He talked a lot about that in the beginning of his email.
[SPEAKER_03]: And he had an interesting perspective on that, basically, that he thought that video games overdo it sometimes.
[SPEAKER_03]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tell that to the fundamentalists.
[SPEAKER_03]: To that I say, you're right.
[SPEAKER_03]: When we're kind of poking fun at the whole thing and we're saying that Christians think that these games are evil, I'd like to think that usually we preface it by saying that it's
[SPEAKER_03]: The extremists we're talking about in this case.
[SPEAKER_00]: The ones who actually publicly make the complaint.
[SPEAKER_03]: The 700 Club.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not every Christian is a crazy, foaming at the mouth, like crazy, I'm going to ban games.
[SPEAKER_00]: Like the morons behind the Chick Tracks.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, whoever has succeeded Jerry Falwell in his camp.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, the fundamentalists.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I have some good friends who are Christians, and I'm not, you know, I personally am not into that religion, but I have no problem being a Christian.
[SPEAKER_01]: I went to church today.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Besides, it's not really hip to make fun of Christian people.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's hip to make fun of Scientology.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yeah, that's true.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have a new religion to be making fun of.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's always been funny to make fun of Scientology.
[SPEAKER_03]: In all seriousness, and you can say this about any group of people, whether it be a religious group, an ethnic group, a, I don't know, whatever you come up with, a group of anybody, gamers even, there's always a few bad apples that ruin it for everyone.
[SPEAKER_03]: So when we poke fun, we're only poking fun at the extremists
[SPEAKER_03]: Obviously, there's plenty of great Christian folks.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have friends that are Christians, just like I have friends that are Buddhists and friends that are other religions.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the great thing about the country where we live in, playing the anthem, is that you can have freedom of religion and choice and all that good stuff.
[SPEAKER_00]: But not for much longer!
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, freedom of choice, but the government knows better.
[SPEAKER_00]: Remember, keep voting in those conservatives.
[SPEAKER_00]: That'll be gone real quick.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't start the political thing or we're going to get tons and tons of emails.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm not, I'm not, I'm not.
[SPEAKER_04]: I watched Outfoxed last night.
[SPEAKER_03]: You got another email you want to read, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_00]: I lost my place.
[SPEAKER_03]: I got another one then, if you don't have one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Keep going.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wanted to read this one.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: This was from a guy named Chris, and he actually works on a site called A Society Wildcard.
[SPEAKER_03]: He wants to say, I wanted to thank you guys for providing an excellent, entertaining, and informative podcast amongst the mediocrity and crap that is swimming out there in the podcast ocean.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's quite a compliment.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's very cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's no way to be talking about Governor Schwarzenegger's podcast.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, so please, um, make sure you subscribe to the show via iTunes or via iPod or some other form.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't rely on necessarily, um, Podcast Alley.
[SPEAKER_03]: Although it's a great site, I'm not going to knock Podcast Alley, it's a great site and we have a lot of great people who have voted for us over there as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um,
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just really, really big, and they don't have time to work on each little individual podcast and its problems.
[SPEAKER_00]: He's given us a plug on his show.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think it's only fair to do the same for him.
[SPEAKER_03]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's got a show.
[SPEAKER_03]: You want to do that?
[SPEAKER_00]: If you go to thechrissshow.blogspot.com, his podcast is available there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_03]: And he says he's a filmmaker, so I just want you to know that if you need a good actor, I do all my own nude scenes, just so you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can do voice acting.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have my kick-ass one-liners like podcasting.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's so much fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, you got any more emails for us, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll do one more.
[SPEAKER_00]: I know I sent you a bunch.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think we got most.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, here was another one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here's one.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll read this one.
[SPEAKER_03]: This will be the last one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um...
[SPEAKER_03]: This one comes to us from Brian in Michigan.
[SPEAKER_03]: And he says he's been listening to the podcast for a few weeks now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: And he enjoys the discussion and our thoughts on the news that's interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: He likes the fact that we kind of talk about things.
[SPEAKER_03]: We don't just kind of report, report, report.
[SPEAKER_03]: So thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: We appreciate that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, another vote for the Drunken Loki episode.
[SPEAKER_03]: He liked that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have one more.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, no, I want to say the rest.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's another part to this here.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's got a suggestion for us.
[SPEAKER_03]: How about some discussion on popular mods for PC games?
[SPEAKER_03]: He says, I don't think mods get enough airtime, and there are some great ones out there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's also not forget how many mods have become full games and how many modders have received jobs in the industry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Very interesting point.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have to admit, unfortunately, I don't play a lot of PC games.
[SPEAKER_03]: I do most of my gaming on console.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not that I don't respect a lot of PC games out there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm actually really looking forward to Civilization 4, which, by the way, is supposed to be very mod-friendly.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're supposed to be building this whole programming language, and they're going to make it very mod-friendly.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that's very cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, you would probably know more about the modding thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why don't you talk about the PC mods so much?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I don't play a lot of PC games anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: Honestly, what I've been playing...
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe Grand Theft Auto a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have the hot coffee mod.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't actually played the hot coffee portion because getting the damn girlfriends to actually understand you and like, you know, you have to take them out on dates and it's really hard because they want to go do drive-bys and they end up dying a lot of times.
[SPEAKER_04]: They get shot in the head and you're like, oh, your girlfriend's dead.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, damn.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I don't do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Instead, what I do is I download even more mods like the spider car mod where you can drive cars up walls.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just crazy stuff like actually doing my own modding where you just
[SPEAKER_04]: Adjust the aspects of different cars and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: But there's some pretty cool ones.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's one for, I think it was Unreal or Quake, the Enter the Tube or whatever like that, the Penny Arcade mod that they had for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a lot of mods out there, but unfortunately, I don't play a lot of them.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just not in the budget for us to be getting a lot of PC games.
[SPEAKER_00]: The last mod I ever did was Gatchaman Quake.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's old.
[SPEAKER_03]: Quake was almost 10 years ago, so it's old.
[SPEAKER_04]: Quake Rally, where they turned that game into a racing game.
[SPEAKER_03]: But some of those like that get adopted and get huge followings to them.
[SPEAKER_03]: If any game publishers out there want to send us some free games, and we will definitely look into how the internet is modding your game on the PC, we'll certainly talk about it on the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: Drop us an email, togo, T-O-G-O.
[SPEAKER_03]: at OrangeLingerie.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you should do that anyway if you have any general comments on the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: You got one more email for us?
[SPEAKER_00]: We had one from someone named Spencer just talking about the music games.
[SPEAKER_00]: Wanted our opinions on Rockstar, Red Octane, Mad Catz.
[SPEAKER_00]: And he's apparently an Indie Group fan.
[SPEAKER_00]: But I have to say that if you really want our true opinion on the music games, you should probably check out our live show.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's true, we do talk about it for three hours.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, that's kind of a loose term.
[SPEAKER_03]: A three-hour train wreck.
[SPEAKER_03]: We talk strictly about the music games.
[SPEAKER_03]: We do do a live show on OrangeLawnRadio.com for three hours every Sunday night, and you can hear Loki really rip on In the Groove, because he doesn't care for the game.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I will second that, because In the Groove is kind of, but...
[SPEAKER_03]: I, on the other hand, I'm not bothered by In the Groove.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it does some good things for the dance game community.
[SPEAKER_03]: For those who don't know what In the Groove is, it's kind of controversial in the music game scene because it was a game that was made by fans of Dance Dance Revolution who were sad to see that Dance Dance Revolution stopped.
[SPEAKER_03]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_03]: Basically, it's just very controversial.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like In the Groove somewhat.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like some of the things that it brings to the table.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like some of the music in the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think Mines, when used appropriately, is an interesting new twist on the dance game.
[SPEAKER_03]: But there's a lot of things I don't like about it, and a lot of it has to do with the online community.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hate to say it, but I just really hope you're not one of these guys that's online saying, you know, oh, DDR is dead and DDR sucks because In the Groove owns everything.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, In The Groove does one-up DDR on some things, but... It would not have existed without DDR.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, we have to can't forget that In The Groove would not exist without DDR, and the fact that DDR is not dead, it's got plenty of home releases still coming out, including Extreme 2, Ultramix 3 coming out later this year.
[SPEAKER_03]: And again, not to dog on the scene as a whole, because I know some really nice people in the In The Groove scene, but just some of the message boards really ruffle my feathers.
[SPEAKER_04]: I too got an email, but it was something funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was referring back to the episode in which I mentioned how games help kids fight with diseases.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I mentioned Tumor Raider.
[SPEAKER_04]: Someone sent me a Clarisworks file.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if I remember correctly, I think Clarisworks is a Mac.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's something that runs on an Apple PC.
[SPEAKER_04]: Unfortunately, I do not, you know, I do not have such inferior PCs.
[SPEAKER_00]: We're not even going into this.
[SPEAKER_00]: Next story.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not start the Apple versus PC thing again.
[SPEAKER_00]: Because we do not need to hear the closed-minded speak out of his ass.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hey, I have some fun news.
[SPEAKER_03]: You have a fun news?
[SPEAKER_03]: What do you want to tell us about?
[SPEAKER_00]: Not really fun.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's really depressing.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Can we play the happy music again?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: No.
[SPEAKER_00]: This would be horrible.
[SPEAKER_00]: All right.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, read the story.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Read the story.
[SPEAKER_00]: A 12-year-old named Gary Lloyd, apparently in London, hung himself after his mother took away his PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_00]: It turned out to be he was doing it to get attention, and his little prank went wrong.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, any children listening to the show, if your mom takes away your PlayStation, don't hang yourself, because you'll die.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, try going outside.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or do something else.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, there's like a world out there with air and birds and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: All he needed was just an extra life.
[SPEAKER_00]: So wrong.
[SPEAKER_00]: Wah, wah, wah, boo!
[SPEAKER_00]: But it is pretty crappy, just... Kids... Half of me wants to say it's Darwinism at work.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, there's something else going on here.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll have you know, Grand Theft Auto does not have hangings.
[SPEAKER_04]: Texas does, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: Moving on, speaking of Grand Theft Auto and like stories, we have a story about the Miami attorney Jack Thompson.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe you know this guy.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's crazy!
[SPEAKER_03]: He's foaming at the mouth crazy when it comes to wanting to rip video games, a new one, for being too violent.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, guess what game he's going after now?
[SPEAKER_03]: Sims 2!
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, he says that naked people in The Sims 2 is just...
[SPEAKER_03]: Horrible.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here's a quote.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sims 2, the latest version of the Sims video game franchise, contains, according to the video game news sites, full frontal nudity, including nipples, penises, labia, and pubic hair.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, come on.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's pathetic.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, it doesn't.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just wanted to say all those words on a podcast.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, it doesn't.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's the mods that put that on there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think there's a big, big difference between what's going on here and what's going on with Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_03]: I call what happened with Grand Theft Auto, San Andreas, and the whole hot coffee thing lazy programming.
[SPEAKER_03]: The reason being, and we've seen this happen before with DDR.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because we, you know, DarkSakura, Loki, myself, have been talking about DDR for years, so we've been following the franchise.
[SPEAKER_03]: And when it had a release on the PlayStation, its very first release, some hackers found on the disc a background for the song Bad Girls where somebody had airbrushed out the gun.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it makes it look like that they had prepped that song to be ready for U.S.
[SPEAKER_03]: audiences, but they took the song out at the last minute.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or if you even want to go more recent, DDR Extreme, where they had a completely, a song that wasn't even in the game, but you could play it.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's right, you had Memories, remember that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Memories is completely in the game, and with hack codes, you could hack your memory card file to play Memories on DDR Extreme.
[SPEAKER_03]: Even though the song wasn't supposed to be there for whatever reason at the last minute they took it out.
[SPEAKER_03]: But what did they take out?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a pain in the butt, I guess for compiling or whatever reasons, I'm not a programmer, but it's a pain in the butt to take out the entire chunk of game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's easier to take out the little pointer that points to that file because all these games work on a giant flowchart.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's easier to take out the pointer that says play this song.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's what I think happened with Grand Theft Auto, that Rockstar had every intention of doing this sex thing, but at the last minute somebody thought, you know what, maybe this is a little much.
[SPEAKER_03]: So instead of taking the whole thing out of the game, what did they take out?
[SPEAKER_03]: They took out the pointer.
[SPEAKER_03]: and when the PC version came out, it was exposed that the hot coffee thing was in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Somebody put the pointer back in and sure enough, PlayStation and Xbox versions, the pointers, they figure out how to put them back in.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rockstar has to admit, yes, the sex thing was in the game the whole time but they didn't intend on it being discovered.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I believe it, that they probably had taken the pointers out, not realizing.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's lazy programming, I call it.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, but now with the Sims, that's not, you don't have a pointer, or at least with the Sims 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rumor is in the original Sims, and I didn't play enough of the Sims, but that there actually was a code where you could undo the blur or whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's a patch.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's another mod.
[SPEAKER_00]: But the thing is that even under the blur, there was no detail.
[SPEAKER_00]: All it is is another skin that has the detail.
[SPEAKER_03]: Right.
[SPEAKER_03]: And even there was actually a quote.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jeff Brown, Vice President of Corporate Communications at EA, says, This is nonsense.
[SPEAKER_03]: We reviewed 100% of the content.
[SPEAKER_03]: There is no content inappropriate for a teen audience.
[SPEAKER_03]: Players never see a nude sim.
[SPEAKER_03]: If someone with an extreme amount of expertise and time were to remove the pixels, they would see that the sims have no genitals.
[SPEAKER_03]: They appear like Ken and Barbie.
[SPEAKER_03]: Right.
[SPEAKER_04]: What they're talking about, though, is the nude sim patches where people have actually modified, because in The Sims 2, you can actually modify your character, and so they added that stuff in.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the thing is, and this guy's like going, oh, well, they're just letting that happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, they want people to make mods so you can make new clothing, you can make new items, etc., because that stuff, they have whole communities built around that where you can buy new skins, you can make characters that look like Austin Powers, etc.
[SPEAKER_00]: On The Sims 2 site themselves, they offer a mod of the month, basically.
[SPEAKER_00]: Right.
[SPEAKER_03]: They would not highlight a nude patch as the mod of the month.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have that kind of case.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they have houses.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can buy houses and bring them in or whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: But that same thing's been going on for years.
[SPEAKER_03]: Remember Tomb Raider?
[SPEAKER_03]: They had the nude Laura patch within six months of the game coming out.
[SPEAKER_03]: And where was this guy then?
[SPEAKER_04]: He doesn't do his research.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's clearly what it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: So take this one to court.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're going to nail you in the ass.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that's what they're going to find the difference is.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I hope somebody sits down in front of Congress and explains this to them.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can't control what the people on the internet are going to do to the code of the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: But in the case of Grand Theft Auto, I think it was a lazy pointer programming thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: But even still, if that was the case, this shouldn't have even gone as far as it was, even if it was lazy programming.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because it's stupid.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's really dumb.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think all games are going to suffer because of this, not necessarily content-wise, but programmers aren't going to be so lazy anymore, and they're going to push back the release dates of their games so they can clean out the code so you people don't find them.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know what's going to suffer?
[SPEAKER_00]: Free expression.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's what's going to suffer.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, it's kind of funny though, because there are a lot of lazy programmers out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: One of the Dance Dance Revolution games, they sometimes used to have these things like dummy files that they would put on the disc to fill up space or whatever, so it would make them harder to rip or whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: One of the Dance Dance Revolution games, I think it was Max 2, had the entire source code for Beatmania 5 on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I'd heard about that.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, what's going on in the UK for our friends overseas?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, actually this is more of an international thing.
[SPEAKER_00]: About Hironobu Sakaguchi, you know, Final Fantasy creator Basically is saying that he's got a couple games in works on the Xbox 360 However, they will not be playable at the Tokyo Game Show in September Oh, interesting But they are basically making progress on it They're getting the graphics in order It's just been slow progress What about Final Fantasy XII, dammit?
[SPEAKER_00]: Also in news, Archer McLean, he was the creative director at Awesome Studios.
[SPEAKER_00]: They actually were the company that put out Mercury.
[SPEAKER_00]: He resigned.
[SPEAKER_00]: But said that overall he was really more of a figurehead, so it's not really a major loss.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Loki, your review on Mercury pretty much convinced me not to buy the game, so I guess this is no big loss.
[SPEAKER_04]: It wasn't that great of a game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was sort of different, but I got bored with it really quick.
[SPEAKER_03]: What could they have done to make the game better?
[SPEAKER_04]: I was expecting something sort of like Marble Madness.
[SPEAKER_04]: The mazes were too short, and it was just very... A lot of levels, they were really short, and it just didn't do it for me.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was just kind of a pain in the butt.
[SPEAKER_00]: Now, the last thing is a game I haven't heard much on coming up for the U.S.
[SPEAKER_00]: market.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm sure it will, but it's called Another Code, Two Memories.
[SPEAKER_00]: Basically, it's sort of like a combination of an interactive sim.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's kind of like the dating sims were, except you also have a little map where you guide somebody through a house, and you have puzzles to get them through this house.
[SPEAKER_00]: So you're using both screens, one for your communication with a ghost,
[SPEAKER_00]: and the other to navigate.
[SPEAKER_00]: So it's supposed to be a little semi-survival horror puzzle game.
[SPEAKER_00]: It looks pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's move on to some other news, talking about Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_03]: There was actually a story posted on, I'm not sure if this is Gamasutra.
[SPEAKER_03]: I always want to say Gamasutra so it can rhyme with the book, you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I think it's Gamasutra.
[SPEAKER_03]: They ran a story earlier this week that says that Microsoft is announcing 2 million Xbox Live subscribers.
[SPEAKER_03]: The last time that they had made an announcement was back in January.
[SPEAKER_03]: 1.4 million users at that point.
[SPEAKER_03]: This growth rate, by the way, would be the equivalent of one new Xbox Live member every 30 seconds.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm kind of surprised that
[SPEAKER_03]: Xbox Live is still growing so rapidly.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I guess Halo 2 has a large part to do with that.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it just doesn't seem like there's been a whole lot of... The hype of the 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, some of the new games include the free two-month trial as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, Abident Rising had two-month trial in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, I could see that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And plus, with the console coming down in price, it makes Xbox... Like, I didn't buy Xbox when it was first out.
[SPEAKER_03]: It wasn't until they slashed them to $200 when I finally decided to pick one up.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I guess that helps kind of motivate sales as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: By the way, also in this article, the company mentions what titles are going to be out for Xbox Live and Xbox 360 Live that will be out before the end of the year.
[SPEAKER_03]: Online playable titles for Xbox 360 include Perfect Dark Zero, Project Gotham Racing 3, Madden NFL 06, Dead or Alive 4, and Call of Duty 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some games for the current Xbox that will be enabled on Xbox Live
[SPEAKER_03]: Star Wars Battlefront 2, Tony Hawk American Wasteland, Battlefield 2, Modern Combat.
[SPEAKER_03]: So for those Xbox fans, a lot of sequels in there, so some games to look forward to.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think Dead or Alive will be cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dead or Alive 4.
[SPEAKER_04]: American Wasteland is going to be pretty cool too.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like Tony Hawk Underground, but free roaming.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's
[SPEAKER_03]: All one huge level.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some of those clips of Dead or Alive 4, though, look so great.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I've not usually been a really huge Dead or Alive fan, but Dead or Alive 4 looked pretty hot.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to see the Dead or Alive movie.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also another game being teased this week, Resident Evil 5.
[SPEAKER_03]: The website Gamefront had some scans of the publication, Famitsu, which gave some news this week on Resident Evil 5.
[SPEAKER_03]: The interesting thing about Resident Evil 5, remember how Resident Evil 4 was GameCube only, at least in the beginning?
[SPEAKER_03]: Resident Evil 5 will only be on PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360 when it first comes out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nintendo's getting the shaft.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I say this is because Nintendo is being so secretive with their revolutions.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, because they haven't released their system yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: The system's like, uh... It'll come out sometime.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a feeling Resident Evil 5 will make its way to the Revolution, but because Nintendo is releasing it later... Well, honestly, I haven't even heard if the Nintendo Revolution dev kits have even gone out yet, so... Well, you can't really make a game without that, so... Well...
[SPEAKER_03]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: They also have the trailer up for this, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Looked pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Speculation from the early screenshots say that Chris Redfield, who was in Resident Evil 1 and Code Veronica, looks to be the main character in this next game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It looks like the over-the-shoulder style from Resident Evil 4 will be coming back in this game as well, at least in some way.
[SPEAKER_03]: But what was surprising from the early screenshots, the game appears to be a little brighter.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_00]: Acetaminophen can cause liver damage in conjunction with alcohol, Ibuprofen can cause severe stomach irritation, and Aspirin thins the blood, which may exacerbate hangover.
[SPEAKER_00]: Sorry again for talking too fast.
[SPEAKER_00]: 2.
[SPEAKER_00]: Drink a lot of fluids.
[SPEAKER_00]: Dehydration from alcohol can be treated with water, sweet juices, or sports drinks.
[SPEAKER_00]: Potassium also helps you overcome shaky feeling of a bad hangover.
3.
[SPEAKER_00]: Take vitamins.
[SPEAKER_00]: A good multivitamin or vitamin B complex can be used to combat vitamin depletion.
[SPEAKER_00]: And when you drink, vitamin B is the first thing to go.
4.
[SPEAKER_00]: Eat starchy food.
[SPEAKER_00]: Lots of it.
5.
[SPEAKER_00]: Rest or sleep for as long as possible.
6.
[SPEAKER_00]: Repeat steps 2 through 5 if you wake up with a hangover.
[SPEAKER_00]: But my number one bit of advice on how to sober up fast, don't go to any Rob's parties.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't use the double shot glass to make double shot drinks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks, guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: Appreciate your support.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: Just for that, you get a story about UE Bowl.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just for that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dungeon Siege is the next movie that's going to be coming out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ray Liotta was just signed for Dungeon Siege the movie.
[SPEAKER_03]: He'll be playing a villainous character in the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's his title.
[SPEAKER_03]: Die, villainous character, die.
[SPEAKER_03]: Isn't the name of the main character Farmer or something like that?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's kind of dorky.
[SPEAKER_00]: It could be like what in the Trogdor game, Peasant's Quest.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's enough about Yui Bol.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, what's going on in the hack and crack scene?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, there's some interesting stuff that should put a damper on the homebrew scene.
[SPEAKER_04]: PSP Firmware 2.0 was announced at the PlayStation Conference just this week, and PlayStation 2.0 will be adding the elusive internet browser.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right, folks, you can actually build a browsing internet without having to have Wipeout.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, let me think.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sony realized that people were hacking their way into getting a web browser, so they thought, gee, a good idea to curb this would be to just release our own web browser.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: Download our podcast without having to do anything special.
[SPEAKER_04]: Find a Wi-Fi spot, download podcast.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go!
[SPEAKER_04]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ooh, an iPod-er for the PSP would be cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: What I'm wondering, is this only in Japan or is this actually going to happen here, the TV thing?
[SPEAKER_04]: The TV thing right now I think is only in Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: The version 2.0 is supposed to launch in Japan on July 27th.
[SPEAKER_04]: So next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: And also, they're going to be launching a brand new color PSP, white, which is coming out September 21st.
[SPEAKER_04]: Virginal white.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ceramic white.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's going to be coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be with firmware 2.0 on there.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you can't run the homebrew games, but you've got an internet browser.
[SPEAKER_03]: But how long before they hack the 2.0, you think?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, it's gone.
[SPEAKER_04]: What they're going to do is they're going to take the firmware update, rip the browser right out of there, and it'll be in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: New applications are coming along, though, because they accidentally revealed Firmware 2.0 on the internet, and some people downloaded it, and it crashed their PSPs.
[SPEAKER_04]: But they're going to be having a calculator, a word processor, and I think a day planner.
[SPEAKER_03]: A word processor on your PSP?
[SPEAKER_04]: Word processor.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, the thing is... That means there has to be a keyboard attachment coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that's what I was just about to say.
[SPEAKER_04]: Keyboard support is now being added with the PSP, I think via their IR or a USB adapter type thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there's going to be a PSP keyboard coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, so that's all the wonderful official stuff that's going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, we don't really want to know about the official stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: We want to talk about... Well, I found the official stuff to be interesting, for one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Talk about the unofficial stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: The unofficial stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Brand new loaders have been...
[SPEAKER_04]: We are back group has released another loader.
[SPEAKER_04]: These ones bypassing the update checks and now running over clock stuff and running the full library files so you can have all this wonderful Wi-Fi and music and everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: Only a matter of time before 3.0 comes out and everything runs.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not going to matter anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I just thought I'd mention that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, upgrades to your favorite emulators.
[SPEAKER_04]: Super Nintendo 9X is now running almost full speed.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ooh, I gotta check that out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that's really awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, for research purposes only.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, homebrew stuff I don't think is a problem, but anyways.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'll check it out for playing Seiken Densetsu 3 on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: And my personal favorite, the
[SPEAKER_04]: Scum version 3.0 or version 3's come out which can run Monkey Island and stuff so if you have the old Monkey Island game like I do I have a CD somewhere out there for it I can copy it over and play it on my PSP and Loom I love Loom I was playing this one though called I don't remember what it's called the initials are B-A-S-S anyways it was an okay game but it ran really well I was surprised for emulating a PC game runs great
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, I found my copy of Loom.
[SPEAKER_03]: Really?
[SPEAKER_00]: I was going to install it and play it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Was Maniac Mansion on that same software?
[SPEAKER_04]: The Day of the Tentacle was.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ah, that's where I'm getting confused.
[SPEAKER_03]: Day of the Tentacle was.
[SPEAKER_04]: But Maniac Mansion played on the NES emulator.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good point.
[SPEAKER_04]: And finally, the last thing I'd say is PSP Paint version 3 is out.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I made a cool little picture and it's not really good.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you can save your pictures now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, I saw your lovely interpretation of Grand Theft Auto that you had painted in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: GTA made me kill.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: One more story for you guys tonight, and it has to do with the resurrection of Acclaim.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, somebody is going to be zombifying Acclaim by injecting it full of Worcester sauce.
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, what's going to be happening is that Central Investment Holdings is trying to sell the rights.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: Reject false icons.
[SPEAKER_03]: My final thought is, you are the ones who are the ball lickers.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that was the little poster that made a cameo appearance in the news article.
[SPEAKER_03]: What was blurred out like the genitalia on a sim?
[SPEAKER_03]: Good night, everybody.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll see you next time on the Orange Lounge Radio to-go edition.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the end of another Orange Lounge Radio To Go edition.
[SPEAKER_02]: This podcast is a proud part of www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: See you next update.