[SPEAKER_05]: Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition, week of August 1st, 2005.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're tuned in to the Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition, your podcast home for all the latest video game news and gamer chat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, here are your hosts, DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello once again, everybody, and welcome to another edition of Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition.
[SPEAKER_05]: Our podcast dedicated to all those cool games, the niche games, the cult games, and games that don't suck, all the news you really want to know about.
[SPEAKER_05]: My name is Rob Roberts, you might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_05]: Joining me, as always, my awesome co-host over there, say hello to DarkSakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_01]: I sound so dead.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm undead.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm so dead, it kind of makes me think of zombie I actually have Resident Evil t-shirts
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm mad though because the shirt that I want they only sell online.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really?
[SPEAKER_05]: What shirt's that?
[SPEAKER_01]: 2D.
[SPEAKER_01]: They have a Gorillaz shirt.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's only online.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's not the same Resident Evil I'm thinking of.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, anyway.
[SPEAKER_01]: I already have a bunch of the ones they give to the video game stores.
[SPEAKER_01]: I have all kinds of swag.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, we know you get the hookup.
[SPEAKER_05]: Lucky you.
[SPEAKER_01]: I got the major hookup.
[SPEAKER_05]: For the rest of us, there's the store.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_01]: I got the major hookup this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Orange Launch Radio needs to give some of our listeners the hookup.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, we got some prizes we gotta start giving away.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we'll have to do that in the next few weeks, but not tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're actually taping a little bit early this week because I'm going to be leaving.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm flying away.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to the East Coast very soon.
[SPEAKER_01]: I have something for our listeners to hear.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Your DS?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's very quiet.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's hard to hear.
[SPEAKER_05]: What is this?
[SPEAKER_05]: I hear some ambient noises.
[SPEAKER_01]: I have Nintendogs.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nintendogs?
[SPEAKER_05]: How did you get Nintendo?
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, this is not the Japanese version.
[SPEAKER_01]: Nope, it's not.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is the U.S.
[SPEAKER_05]: version.
[SPEAKER_05]: We can barely hear it on there.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know, it's not very loud.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tell us about your gaming week.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's going on here?
[SPEAKER_01]: What's up with the Nintendogs?
[SPEAKER_01]: I have come into a copy of the five-minute demo of Nintendogs.
[SPEAKER_05]: A lot of people were going to start writing you some nasty emails if you had the full version, but still, you got the demo.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've been playing with my puppies.
[SPEAKER_05]: What, Loki?
[SPEAKER_04]: I've got news on that, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: There are going to be people coming into the copies of Nintendogs early.
[SPEAKER_05]: How so?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, if we want to get in the news right away.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, let DarkSakura talk about the game first, then we'll get to that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, so tell us a little more about the game, because at E3, the line was so big to play.
[SPEAKER_05]: I heard it bark.
[SPEAKER_05]: The line was so big to play this game at E3 that I barely got a chance to really look at it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know it was one of my favorite games of the show, but you've actually had a chance to play it a little more in detail this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: What the heck is Nintendogs?
[SPEAKER_05]: What makes it so dang special?
[SPEAKER_01]: You play with your bubbies.
[SPEAKER_05]: What makes it so great, though?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's it?
[SPEAKER_05]: You just play with dogs?
[SPEAKER_01]: Listen to this.
[SPEAKER_05]: What are you...
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, so they're barking, we get it.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's cute.
[SPEAKER_05]: If we had the graphics, especially, because the graphics are a real cute part of this game.
[SPEAKER_01]: You can play music to your puppies and they start barking along with it.
[SPEAKER_01]: And you can throw the frisbee and they catch it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have you noticed an object to this game at all?
[SPEAKER_05]: You play with your puppies!
[SPEAKER_05]: But even in Animal Crossing, which was a very free game where you could do practically whatever you wanted, there was still that goal of paying off your house.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, as you play through the game, you can train your dogs and stuff, and you compete in different events and stuff, like they have dog training events.
[SPEAKER_04]: and you unlock more dog breeds.
[SPEAKER_04]: And also, if other people, say for instance you have Nintendogs Chihuahua and someone has Nintendogs Labrador Retriever or something like that, if you're nearby and they interact with each other, it unlocks the Labrador Retriever and the one with Chihuahua and Chihuahua and the one with Labrador Retriever.
[SPEAKER_05]: So even though they're selling this game, when they announced it was going on sale it sounded like Pokemon Red and Blue or only certain...
[SPEAKER_05]: All the Japanese dogs are unlockable through the unlocks.
[SPEAKER_04]: What we need to see, though, is if the Japanese version and the US ones will interact.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, that would be interesting, because I know people over here with the Japanese version.
[SPEAKER_01]: And if you walk by with the game and someone else has their dogs, they'll start barking.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: If it detects another copy of the game on and playing nearby.
[SPEAKER_05]: What did you think after your five-minute demo?
[SPEAKER_01]: Puppies!
[SPEAKER_05]: So in other words, you're sold on this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: You'll be buying the full version when it comes out?
[SPEAKER_01]: All they need, Mike, is Nintendo kitties.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I am buying all three versions when this comes out.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you don't need all three versions!
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't care!
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm buying them for the strict purpose of annoying my co-worker because he hates this game because it's so damn cute.
[SPEAKER_04]: And so I'm going to be playing it with the volume full blast.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: There's three of us, three versions of the game.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm getting in the lab already.
[SPEAKER_05]: We should get the three different versions.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll get the Chihuahua.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, there we go.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'll get the Shih Tzu.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hopefully it's in a different one.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was going to get the lab anyway because it has other breeds that I want.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like a Jack Russell Terrier and I think the miniature Dachshund.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just going to buy all three.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can't wait to trade.
[SPEAKER_05]: You just need all three.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, at least I know where I get the dogs from.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, anything else in your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_01]: I play lots of Ragnarok.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ragnarok Online
[SPEAKER_05]: Like around the corner.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was something that was going to be here by year's end.
[SPEAKER_05]: I could have thought I read somewhere.
[SPEAKER_01]: I hope.
[SPEAKER_01]: I keep checking Gravity's site.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then there's another game that one of our listeners suggested to us.
[SPEAKER_01]: I got an email from Iris, who is in South Korea.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hi, Iris.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was my grandma's name.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really?
[SPEAKER_01]: That's a nice name.
[SPEAKER_01]: Who suggested a game that I actually haven't had too much of an opportunity.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's called Darwinia.
[SPEAKER_01]: I like the name already, but I actually was intending on downloading it a couple of days ago and I had some computer issues.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not actually going to buy any more movies, but I've been playing that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I played Bomberman Panic Bomber, which I was hoping it was more of a Bomberman game, but it's another puzzle game.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is the PSP one?
[SPEAKER_04]: PSP one.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have a lot of puzzle games for the PSP out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really, yeah, those have been the games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything else?
[SPEAKER_04]: Just those games?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I wish I had played some PlayStation 2 stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm waiting for Graffiti Kingdom.
[SPEAKER_04]: They sent out a press release on Thursday saying, Oh, the game got shipped!
[SPEAKER_04]: Go to GameStop.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, we have our information that says it's coming out on August 8th or August 9th.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm like, yeah, that's what I heard before this press release came out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because nobody wants Graffiti Kingdom but you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, they told me.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're all, you're going to have to pre-order this game if you want it at all because we're getting like three copies total.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm like, fuck you, I will go to Fry's.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, eat that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is that the sequel to Magic Penjel?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sort of.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a sequel in the game sense, where you have the same gameplay and stuff, but the storyline is not a direct sequel.
[SPEAKER_05]: Magic Penjel, for those that don't know, was this kind of cultish game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think it was really big.
[SPEAKER_05]: It had a rock-paper-scissors battle style system, so it was pretty simple in concept.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you could draw your own monsters, which was really the cool thing about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: You literally drew your own... It's like Pokemon, but you draw your own Pokemon.
[SPEAKER_05]: So of course...
[SPEAKER_05]: My friends and I were playing this game and we were drawing all sorts of phallic things and just all the two-year-old type humor you could think of we were drawing.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the game doesn't stop you.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, there was the big cock monster.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I remember there was like the big cock monster.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then I'm like, you know, I walked out of the room for a bit and I come back in.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm like, is that a cannon?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, it's a penis.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, you can't draw.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_01]: Terminator, Robocop,
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_01]: Basically, I'll just read the little blurb on here.
[SPEAKER_01]: The world of Darwinia is a virtual theme park running inside a computer network built by a computer genius named Dr. Sepulveda, I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: Darwinia is populated by a sentient involving life form called the Darwinians.
[SPEAKER_01]: They are the product of decades worth of research into genetic algorithms.
[SPEAKER_05]: So what kind of game does it look like?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I thought this was just another, you know...
[SPEAKER_05]: Ye Olde RPG style game, but this looks like a futuristic type thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: It looks like The Sims meets Tron.
[SPEAKER_05]: It looks kind of like Lawnmower Man.
[SPEAKER_05]: To me, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let me look at a few more of these screenshots on here, though.
[SPEAKER_01]: It really does look very...
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's download the demo and check it out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because the listener was wanting us to check it out.
[SPEAKER_01]: I had intended on doing so.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'll probably get that started when I get home tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: It'll be a follow-up in the future.
[SPEAKER_05]: My gaming week, I didn't play anything new, guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry to say, I've been preparing for my trip.
[SPEAKER_05]: But for some wacky reason, I decided to get back into Guild Wars.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I was like, okay, I'm not going to pay money to reactivate my Final Fantasy XI account when I'm going to be leaving soon.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I don't want to start a new game again.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've been contemplating checking out World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_05]: One of my friends is really, really trying to get me on there.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know, PSO.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura's trying to get me on PSO.
[SPEAKER_05]: But Guild Wars, luckily, loving it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Once you buy it, you can play it forever for free.
[SPEAKER_05]: No monthly fee, so I can go back whenever I want.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I knew I would do this, too, that I'd play it for two weeks, leave, go back again.
[SPEAKER_05]: But here's the weird thing about my habits with Guild Wars.
[SPEAKER_05]: I started a new character.
[SPEAKER_05]: Everybody in my old guild doesn't play the game anymore, so it's just me.
[SPEAKER_05]: So here I am playing the game by myself, and I'm thinking...
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm playing an MMO by myself.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's the point?
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's still kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think I'd be having more fun if there were people out there that would play with me.
[SPEAKER_01]: If someone would buy me the game, I would play.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, got 50 bucks to spare?
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe we've got a really nice listener out there.
[SPEAKER_01]: I sure as heck ain't paying money for it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've seen Guild Wars.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like Guild Wars.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's neat.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's...
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't like the style.
[SPEAKER_01]: It doesn't bother me.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's not pretty.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's more of a strategy, like strategy action fused, which is kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_04]: You'll have to pull my cold dead body away from Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_04]: I may not have played it for over a month, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: I am not quitting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not from my cold dead hands.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm just pissed off that I can't download the Korean version of Ragnarok online.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because the...
[SPEAKER_01]: The Korean Ragnarok site is letting me get it, and I don't want to have to pay $30 for three more months of Ragnarok Online to play my old dead character.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thing is, my character on the old Ragnarok will never be deleted.
[SPEAKER_05]: For those that don't know Ragnarok, because we've talked about it an awful lot tonight, real quick, describe it.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's really cutesy MMORPG.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's adorable.
[SPEAKER_01]: I found the picture of your character who wore the little ribbon.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, I had a character that wore a ribbon.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's like Secret of Mana in a way.
[SPEAKER_01]: Kind of.
[SPEAKER_05]: But imagine it as an MMO.
[SPEAKER_05]: In a 3D world.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's really adorable.
[SPEAKER_01]: If you just go to rocknrockonline.com Not 3D in the Halo or Doom 3D sense.
[SPEAKER_05]: 3D in the up at an angle shot.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like
[SPEAKER_01]: It's a 3D environment, but the characters are sprites.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Quick news story on Final Fantasy XI, since Loki brought it up to start us off tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Since you're saying they won't tear the game from your cold, dead hands, how about a story that might tick you off?
[SPEAKER_05]: Final Fantasy XI, the Vanadil Collection, will ship for the PC on August 16th.
[SPEAKER_05]: What is this, a new expansion pack?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, it's just Final Fantasy XI, Rise of the Zillert, and Chains of Promethea, and Tetra Master, all bundled together for $29.99.
[SPEAKER_05]: So those of you guys that spent $50 on the game and $30 on the expansion, just got screwed.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it happens with every MMO, it really does.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, look at Rise of the Zillards at one time.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was being sold as an expansion, and then they just update it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, just thought I'd share that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see, I actually have an abundance of Square news tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let me get some of these other Square stories out of the way.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kingdom Hearts 2 has a date.
[SPEAKER_05]: This being announced at the Squeenix Party 2005 event in Tokyo, hence why we have all the Squeenix news tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kingdom Hearts 2 will be out in Japan this year in December.
[SPEAKER_05]: No set-in-stone date for the U.S.
[SPEAKER_05]: yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: However, they've really been pushing to localize their games quickly.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have to admit, I'm surprised they're going to miss Christmas at this rate.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would have thought Kingdom Hearts 2 would be a very powerful Christmas title to have out there.
[SPEAKER_05]: It seems kind of silly to miss Christmas here, but it ain't my company.
[SPEAKER_01]: Also keep in mind, though, when we get it, it's going to be better than the Japanese one.
[SPEAKER_05]: People are going to buy it no matter what.
[SPEAKER_05]: What makes you say it's going to be better than the Japanese one?
[SPEAKER_01]: Just like the last one.
[SPEAKER_01]: They actually had to redo an international version.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, Square Enix kind of does that stuff where they add... Because the Sephiroth battle wasn't in the original Kingdom Hearts, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: That was something new for North America.
[SPEAKER_01]: It actually wasn't in ours either, but they brought out the sort of updated international version that had the Sephiroth battle and the deep dive trailer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Final Fantasy XII also got a date at the Squeenix party.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ships in Japan on March 16th, 2006.
[SPEAKER_05]: So still a little wait.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that's just Japan's date, meaning we've got to wait three to four months.
[SPEAKER_05]: So maybe we're looking at Christmas next year for Final Fantasy XII.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rumors why?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because Final Fantasy XII supposedly is in the can.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's done in Japan.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's ready to go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just they're putting the finishing touches on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: But supposedly, because of the Kingdom Hearts 2 news, that's why they're waiting on Final Fantasy XII.
[SPEAKER_05]: Final Fantasy VII Advent Children will be released in theaters in Japan
[SPEAKER_01]: and probably in theaters in Berkeley and little tiny theaters.
[SPEAKER_04]: I told those Sony reps when they came to our work, I'm like, you got to fucking put this in theaters.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, man, it's all this marketing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm like, word of mouth, word of mouth.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, nothing, not even news on any type of U.S.
[SPEAKER_05]: release.
[SPEAKER_05]: Little distributionary, no North American distribution as of yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's the reason why I'm thinking it's not going to happen in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_05]: because it's going to premiere in Japan on September 8th.
[SPEAKER_05]: The DVD, by the way, comes out September 14th.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it's really just a super sneak preview for those diehard people that have to see it in the theater.
[SPEAKER_05]: And if I was in Japan, I'd be one of them.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think it's going to have a limited run here.
[SPEAKER_05]: You think?
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't... Escaflowne.
[SPEAKER_01]: That had a limited run.
[SPEAKER_05]: But would they get that?
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, we're talking... We're only about six weeks out from this now.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think that's enough time to put together a theater release.
[SPEAKER_01]: I do believe that there would be time.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_01]: Slap some subtitles on that.
[SPEAKER_01]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Screwdubs.
[SPEAKER_05]: Still more stories, still more stories.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kingdom Hearts 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hikaru Utada, of course, did the theme song for the first Kingdom Hearts game.
[SPEAKER_05]: She's coming back.
[SPEAKER_05]: She's going to sing a song called Passion, which will be in Kingdom Hearts 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: No word yet as to whether she's going to record it in English and Japanese, but since she did the first one in English and Japanese... And she is fully bilingual.
[SPEAKER_05]: Exactly, and she has her own album out here, which I don't think did so hot.
[SPEAKER_01]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's easy breezy and you're Japanese-y.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, so she'll have the song Passion.
[SPEAKER_05]: The single should be coming out, being put out by Toshiba EMI.
[SPEAKER_05]: It will come out around December, same time as Kingdom Hearts 2 is planning to come out.
[SPEAKER_05]: One more story I got, and it's a Final Fantasy XI story again.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know how Xbox 360 Final Fantasy XI has everybody going, OMG, OMG, what's going to be different in the Final Fantasy XI version on Xbox 360?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you're going to find out if you live in Germany.
[SPEAKER_05]: Get this, they're actually going to be showing it in Germany at the Games Convention in Leipzig.
[SPEAKER_05]: That happens August 17th through the 21st.
[SPEAKER_05]: It doesn't say in the press release that it's going to be playable, but it does say in the press release that European gamers will get their first look at the next generation gateway to the world of Anadyl.
[SPEAKER_05]: Should be interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, I heard a rumor, one quick rumor about, for those of you Final Fantasy XI players, I don't know if this is true or not, but...
[SPEAKER_05]: What they're going to do with the 360 is they're going to put the same upgrades in 360 that they do on the PC and PlayStation 2 users.
[SPEAKER_05]: Unfortunately, you're going to get left behind in this.
[SPEAKER_05]: But they're going to make the capes viewable.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's supposedly something... Because you know how your character won't wear a cape in Final Fantasy XI, but you never see it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Supposedly, that's going to be one of the graphical upgrades.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Take it with a grain of salt, people.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll find out when the game is shown in Europe.
[SPEAKER_05]: But that would be kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_01]: Maybe it's an option you would be able to turn on in the PC version if you have a high enough graphics card.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I don't see why not.
[SPEAKER_01]: Certainly.
[SPEAKER_01]: My graphics card would handle it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, most of them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I'm surprised they haven't released a patch like that for capes in the PC version.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, maybe they're waiting for this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you never know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, they can do... Who knows?
[SPEAKER_04]: With the new 360 game coming out, they're probably going to release another expansion at the same time.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_05]: We don't know yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, possibly.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, let's go past the Squeenix news, and let's get into inflating our egos a little bit by opening up the old mailbag.
[SPEAKER_05]: So if you want to send us an email...
[SPEAKER_05]: All you have to do is send an email to togo, T-O-G-O, at orangeloungeradio.com and DarkSakura will have something to say to you.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, what do you have to say tonight?
[SPEAKER_01]: I actually got a bunch of email.
[SPEAKER_01]: And one, um... The first one I want to bring up is by, um...
[SPEAKER_01]: Someone named Rue, who wrote in to us about the whole hot coffee deal.
[SPEAKER_01]: And actually, and this is something that I actually didn't see on any of my references, but when I went back and dug deeper after receiving the email, yes it is true.
[SPEAKER_01]: The whole deal was actually sort of launched off by Hillary Clinton.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kind of.
[SPEAKER_05]: She got behind it, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think having her behind it really threw the thing into orbit.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, it was kind of like where it went to the next level.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I believe it was originally brought to the attention by Assemblyman Leland Yee, I think, because they had this guy on G4 TV.
[SPEAKER_05]: And usually I don't talk about G4 TV because...
[SPEAKER_05]: They have a reputation for having bad programming, but actually it's gotten a lot better.
[SPEAKER_05]: I actually watched G4TV.com, and ever since they got that new guy on the show, he's really brought it up.
[SPEAKER_05]: The two girls are up to that same level, I think, because they actually had the Leland Yee on their show.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was actually a pretty good interview, I have to say.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was kind of interesting, I thought.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, I just wanted to interject that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, this email, though, basically it's not just the conservatives that are behind it.
[SPEAKER_01]: we've got basically everybody and you know it also brought up to the whole reason why I didn't go Democrat way back you know because of Lieberman I was not going to have Lieberman and Tipper Gore anywhere near our video game industry
[SPEAKER_01]: There was also, though, another article, though, this made me think of, that I'm going to get back to the mailbag, I just have to see where I stored this article, about how actually the rate of crime in our country's youth decreased.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you have a link to this?
[SPEAKER_05]: I bet a lot of people would be interested in reading this.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, I do, and it's going to...
[SPEAKER_01]: Take me just a brief moment.
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, if you'll take care of one of our other emails.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I'll go to one of the other emails.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just want to say, was that the same guy who you invited to do the article for the site?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_01]: I invited him to write an editorial regarding that for us.
[SPEAKER_05]: That would be cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like I said, guys...
[SPEAKER_05]: Politics and gaming podcasts sometimes don't mix, but that's alright, you know, hey, we gotta, you know, whatever you believe in, at least go out and vote, cause we get the freedom to do that in this country.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jesus, you know, here's what it comes down to, okay, the whole hot coffee mod hit a little too close to home, if you know what I mean, with Hillary Clinton, because the whole hot coffee mod starts off with CJ coming in for some lovin',
[SPEAKER_04]: What's the woman do?
[SPEAKER_04]: She gets down to business.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, damn.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, oh, oh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, that happened to Hillary.
[SPEAKER_04]: That happened to Hillary.
[SPEAKER_05]: Look, look, look.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think the issue here is really about the regulation of the games, not trying to ban them.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I think, remember, guys, Hillary Clinton isn't trying to ban the games.
[SPEAKER_05]: She's trying to regulate them.
[SPEAKER_01]: She's basically, again, encouraging parents not to do their job.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which, you know, even though I am a Democrat, I'll admit it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't necessarily have to support her on every little thing she does.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is one of those things where I think every senator, Republican, Democrat, and the one independent guy could all be educated on the gaming world a little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, I did have that article here.
[SPEAKER_01]: It can be located, I'll go ahead and give the address.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's gr.bolt.com slash articles slash violence slash violence.htm Hey, it has violence in there twice.
[SPEAKER_01]: It can't be that bad.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyway, this was written by Duke Ferris, who writes on this site.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's a game revolution is what it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: So he's basically presenting facts to show that violence has gone down, not up, amongst children.
[SPEAKER_01]: This information that he's reported on here, it's actually a very well-written article, which really surprised me for this site.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's using statistics put out by the U.S.
[SPEAKER_01]: Department of Justice Bureau of Statistics.
[SPEAKER_01]: and information also pulled from the files of the FBI, public files.
[SPEAKER_01]: Basically, it's showing that since right before the release of the PlayStation, we've got basically a mark showing from 93 on, crime has decreased.
[SPEAKER_05]: See, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's got to be a loophole somewhere because, and now granted, I'm about to say, watching the news every night, you would think the complete opposite to be true.
[SPEAKER_05]: But yes, I know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Of course, the news is trying to glamorize us.
[SPEAKER_05]: The news sensationalizes it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because, you know, again, they make their money by fooling the public.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here come those emails again.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait, you mean it's not hot outside?
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: Check out the article.
[SPEAKER_05]: Give the link one more time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Draw your own conclusions from this, guys.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_01]: Again, keep in mind, I'm not really talking, you know, your local news is cool, I think.
[SPEAKER_01]: At least, you know, whenever I watch the news here, I don't see anything sensational or anything out of the ordinary.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm talking about, like, they pick one instance, and then it's all on CNN.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're talking about, like, MSNBC doing the Michael Jackson trial 24-7.
[SPEAKER_01]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now that I can agree with.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's like they take one issue, blow it way out of proportion until suddenly the entire public thinks every kid who ever plays a video game is going to come cut off my head in my sleep.
[SPEAKER_01]: Lord have mercy, we all is going to die from GTA.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which I'm sure you're going to talk about the grandma.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah, I'll bring up grandma in a minute.
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: Go ahead.
[SPEAKER_01]: There was one other thing in here.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, it's basically one of the charts on here, which is what I would like to show to most of our listeners, is that there is a very good chart on here that separates everything by age, by age group.
[SPEAKER_01]: And actually in the group, the biggest decline in violent crime was between the 14 and 17 year old group.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, well, give the link one more time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let folks draw their own conclusions.
[SPEAKER_01]: Give them the article.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's dr.bolt.com slash articles slash violence slash violence.htm And I'll go ahead at some point... Post that in our forums.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, actually, we'll repeat a link to the article on our announcements on the website.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, did you still want me to read the next letter?
[SPEAKER_05]: Good point.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, I got an email here from Justin M, and this is nice because this is just nothing but an ego inflation letter.
[SPEAKER_05]: I, like many others, discovered your fine podcast through iTunes version 4.9, and I just wanted to let you know that you were doing a wonderful job with it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have heard of Orange Launch Radio before, but didn't have the time to sit down and listen to a live show every week, the shows we do on Sunday night.
[SPEAKER_05]: Having it readily available on my iPod to listen to whenever, I'm ready to just...
[SPEAKER_05]: The grammar gets weird here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Unbelievably huge step in the right direction for talk shows, and it really helps bring out some of the talent that would otherwise lie untapped.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, that's quite a compliment.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you very much for that email.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the most we can ask, get a friend to subscribe to the show, tell one person about the show, and then the news of Orange Lounge spreads everywhere, and we're all happy, and you're happy because you get a new show every week, and et cetera, et cetera.
[SPEAKER_01]: I did want to make a mention that one of our listeners, Michael, thought it was really cool that we were talking about Scorched Earth.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dude, Scorched Earth was the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was my junior high school lunches for like a year.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is still the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: In fact, I'm still waiting for them to finish the PSP homebrew version.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're doing a PSP homebrew version?
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh-huh, they are.
[SPEAKER_05]: I fully endorse the PSP for these reasons.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then there was also...
[SPEAKER_01]: One of our Macintosh supporters wrote in, but... I know where this is going, Loki.
[SPEAKER_01]: I forwarded this to Loki earlier.
[SPEAKER_01]: No offense, because I appreciate receiving the email, but when one is speaking of the general intelligence level of a Macintosh user, make sure you use your spell checker and grammar checker before sending your email.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because I counted no less than 15 grammatical and spelling errors.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's ironic.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, just shut up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't go there.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have a Max story at the end, and I think it's cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Listen, I'm not knocking the Max, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because, granted, the processing power may not be what I'm looking for.
[SPEAKER_04]: Their cases look cool, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: Their cases are nice.
[SPEAKER_01]: Freaking widescreen monitor.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_01]: The monitor is nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did we go to Bizarro Orange Lounge Radio?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I just heard Loki say something nice about a Macintosh.
[SPEAKER_04]: The cases look nice, but that's all they are is just a big graphing calculator inside of a nice case.
[SPEAKER_04]: Somebody put a death threat out on you, didn't they?
[SPEAKER_01]: No.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's like I had... You know, when we were conversing about this while I was supposed to be at work...
[SPEAKER_01]: The Mac is a very, I think, best used for either people who are not up to a PC or for the professional needing the specific benefits that a Mac provides.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me put it this way.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you're going to pick between a Mac, an iMac or whatever, and an eMachine, go with the iMac because eMachines suck even more, and that's pretty bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was kind of a nice thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Make sure you're on there.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_01]: E-Machines, however, are very good for modifying.
[SPEAKER_01]: They are very easily upgraded.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, back to the games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Although I was at the Apple Store today.
[SPEAKER_01]: I went to Fry's and I'm thinking about getting an iMac G5.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just because a regular G5 is freaking expensive.
[SPEAKER_01]: And that 30 inch widescreen monitor.
[SPEAKER_05]: I got an email here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can I read this one?
[SPEAKER_05]: This was somebody who has way too much time on their hands.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's from Cliff R. Cliff sent us an email letting us know our statistics.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't care before, but I do now.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was very cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: Our live show wrote in, DJ Ranma S. Ranchan, in his email, he said this.
[SPEAKER_01]: His 13-year-old cousin got GTA San Andreas for PS2.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now he plays this game all the time and, believe it or not, knows better.
[SPEAKER_01]: The interactions of the game has no effect on him.
[SPEAKER_01]: I say that because his mother and me talk to him all the time about these games, gang's life, and everything else.
[SPEAKER_01]: I admit he does hang out with friends that act more ghetto than CJ at times, but I
[SPEAKER_01]: I can't believe that he doesn't do anything they do.
[SPEAKER_01]: And that I was right.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I'm going to quote here.
[SPEAKER_01]: Parents, if you're listening to this podcast, your kids need home training.
[SPEAKER_01]: Teach them the difference between real life and fantasy, for God's sake.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well said.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think gamer parents are pretty well aware of that stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hope.
[SPEAKER_05]: I really hope.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_01]: We're going into a new generation of gaming parents.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember, parents, treat games like they're drugs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Talk to your kids.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you talk to your kids about drugs, they're less likely to do drugs.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're more likely to know the difference between right and wrong if you talk to them.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're in a very nice mood tonight, Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're all about love and affection today.
[SPEAKER_04]: Once we bring up Grandma, it's going downhill.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can I have a hug?
[SPEAKER_01]: No.
[SPEAKER_01]: That made me think of one thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: Where did you learn to do that?
[SPEAKER_01]: I learned it from you!
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, I'll talk about Grandma now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Get this.
[SPEAKER_05]: An 85-year-old woman suing Take-Two Entertainment over the hot coffee mod.
[SPEAKER_05]: She purchased the game for her 14-year-old grandson and is now suing Take-Two.
[SPEAKER_05]: This has been passed around on every gaming message board.
[SPEAKER_05]: Surely those of you guys that are checking gaming websites of any capacity have heard about this.
[SPEAKER_05]: and you probably just went, WTF lady, why were you buying this game for your 14 year old kid in the first place?
[SPEAKER_01]: Again, that's another case of a person in a parental position not doing their research and not doing their goddamn job.
[SPEAKER_05]: And she's got some balls to be suing Take-Two Entertainment over it too.
[SPEAKER_01]: She's gonna lose.
[SPEAKER_01]: She bought the game and gave it.
[SPEAKER_01]: If she did not want offensive material to be put in the hands of a child, she would have done her research, don't you think?
[SPEAKER_05]: But what she's saying is that now the game is A-O.
[SPEAKER_05]: She wasn't fully educated before.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_01]: It still had an M rating on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just playing devil's advocate here.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not going to say I disagree with you people.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just playing devil's advocate.
[SPEAKER_01]: It still had an M rating on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like, damn it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought that game was rated R, not NC-17.
[SPEAKER_04]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, listen, Grandma.
[SPEAKER_04]: First off, okay, I know you might have watered in there, you know, because...
[SPEAKER_04]: You didn't know where you were and you might have bought this game for your grandson.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I'm thinking the grandson probably begged her to buy it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, so she bought the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did it say in the article that he figured out how to unlock the hot coffee mod content?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it did not.
[SPEAKER_04]: It specifically said because she found out that that content was in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Therefore, we could say that he may not have been exposed to this content at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, she's retarded.
[SPEAKER_04]: She is friggin' retarded.
[SPEAKER_01]: She has no legal precedent either way.
[SPEAKER_01]: Her lawyer's not going to try to dissuade her because her lawyer's still going to make his money.
[SPEAKER_05]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, you have a story on this one.
[SPEAKER_05]: A blind teenager from Lincoln, Nebraska, who...
[SPEAKER_01]: can kick anybody's butt at Mortal Kombat, basically.
[SPEAKER_01]: Although I think this article is pretty stupid just because they talk about decapitations in Soul Calibur that don't happen.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was the first thing I noticed in the article, too, that made me kind of go, stupid media person, do your research before you talk about games.
[SPEAKER_05]: They talk about decapitation in Soul Calibur, which doesn't happen.
[SPEAKER_05]: This guy probably thought that Soul Calibur, that the reporter must have been blind, too, because apparently Soul Calibur 2 and Mortal Kombat Deadly Alliance are the same game.
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_01]: But at any rate, it sounds like he just learned by trial and error how to play.
[SPEAKER_01]: People would correct him when he did something wrong.
[SPEAKER_01]: His favorite thing, he wants to be a video game designer when he graduates.
[SPEAKER_01]: Which, you know, I could see happening.
[SPEAKER_01]: No pun intended.
[SPEAKER_01]: He plays facing away from the screen.
[SPEAKER_01]: People challenge him strictly on his blindness and he still kicks their butt.
[SPEAKER_01]: Which I can actually understand that if you understand the timing of your attacks, know who you're using, and hear the reaction on screen, there shouldn't be any reason.
[SPEAKER_05]: I challenge you on mute.
[SPEAKER_05]: But still, but still, a heck of an accomplishment.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, even though we could kind of think about, okay, this is probably how he does it still.
[SPEAKER_05]: What a lot of time and patience and discipline to become that good at a game.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, hats off to this guy.
[SPEAKER_01]: Apparently he enjoys freaking people out by playing backwards.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can we play him on Xbox Live?
[SPEAKER_05]: Does it have a screen tag, gamer tag on there?
[SPEAKER_01]: This is on Yahoo News.
[SPEAKER_01]: Ah.
[SPEAKER_01]: But, you know, if he happens to be listening to, you know, his, what's his name, Bryce?
[SPEAKER_01]: If he is listening to this podcast, or if anyone who's listening to this podcast knows him, we would love to interview him.
[SPEAKER_05]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_01]: And we would love to challenge him on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_05]: To DDR.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have the Mortal Kombat game.
[SPEAKER_05]: We could play that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or Halo.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anybody can beat my ass in Halo.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, I had an 8-year-old kid blow me away the other day.
[SPEAKER_00]: He's holding an Xbox controller.
[SPEAKER_00]: I see an Xbox on the floor.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Moving on, another news story coming up here.
[SPEAKER_05]: G4ia, that big video games award show that happens on G4 every year.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is going to air on August 9th, but that doesn't mean we won't ruin it for you right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: The game of the year was Halo 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Favorite character was the Kratos in God of War.
[SPEAKER_05]: EB Gamer's Choice Award went to World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did Katamari Damacy win anything?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Best innovation?
[SPEAKER_05]: That one game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see how many awards Halo 2 got.
[SPEAKER_05]: Best Boss, Best Multiplayer Game, Best Original Soundtrack, Best Shooter, Best Sound Design, Best Voice Performance, and Game of the Year.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it's a Halo 2 whoring fest.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, and other than Licensed Soundtrack, where's the love for Grand Theft Auto?
[SPEAKER_04]: That game was at the top.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's still at the top of the charts.
[SPEAKER_04]: And all the guys, Best Licensed Soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_04]: Best Licensed Soundtrack was the only award that came out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Lame!
[SPEAKER_04]: Lame, lame, lame.
[SPEAKER_04]: Halo was just another first-person shooter.
[SPEAKER_04]: Grand Theft Auto San Andreas was a revolution.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's tons of emails coming your way that are going to disagree with you on that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Personally, I actually enjoy Halo 2 more than Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_05]: I do.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think the multiplayer party aspect of it makes it, for me, a more fun game.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, you have any other news stories for us tonight?
[SPEAKER_05]: Um...
[SPEAKER_01]: We actually... A game that's coming out shortly, and I'm actually trying to get the US release date, because I know it's coming out very soon.
[SPEAKER_01]: Fire Emblem Path of Radiance is coming out.
[SPEAKER_01]: My fianc has just been pissing his pants waiting for this to come out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you for that visual.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, he's been even downloading... Because we were very disappointed when...
[SPEAKER_01]: You know the Fire Emblem on Game Boy Advance that had Marth and Roy in it?
[SPEAKER_01]: It didn't come out over here.
[SPEAKER_01]: But the one after that did, which actually is a prequel to that, and then the one following came out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Dan's just really been into Fire Emblem, and it actually may be the first strategy game that I might actually give a serious chance.
[SPEAKER_01]: The last one I played was the Macross game on the PC Engine, which... Anyway, but Fire Emblem, Path of Radiance is coming out to GameCube, and I was checking out the UK news, and of course I saw that, I instantly went to it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Path of Radiance has a November release date.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't have the specific date, but it's said to come out this November.
[SPEAKER_01]: Loki, what's going on in the hack and crack world right now?
[SPEAKER_04]: Lots of stuff, especially with people getting their panties in a bunch over version 2.0 of the firmware for PSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: You've got a brand new homebrew version of a web browser that's actually been released right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now there's four options for web browsing.
[SPEAKER_04]: This one is called actually the 2CH browser.
[SPEAKER_04]: And really the first version of it can only visit the site 2ch.jp or some Japanese site.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Snuff with the 2.0 browser, which actually supports Java and downloads and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, one of the really cool games that came out this week for the PSP Homebrew was actually a port of Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_04]: No way.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_04]: GP, which was actually for the console GP32.
[SPEAKER_04]: They made it for that portable system, but now they've ported it and you can put your own characters in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Does it look like the GameCube one, though?
[SPEAKER_05]: It has the look and feel.
[SPEAKER_04]: It has the feel of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not exactly the same detail and look, but hey, homebrew, come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's still fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that came out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, Sony is letting everyone know not to upgrade your US PlayStation portables to the 2.0 because that's meant for only Japanese PlayStations and it could harm your PlayStation and turn into a brick.
[SPEAKER_05]: Will that stop you?
[SPEAKER_04]: No!
[SPEAKER_04]: No, that won't stop people.
[SPEAKER_04]: But anyways, as far as the DS stuff goes here, there's been a few things being worked on.
[SPEAKER_04]: A brand new Super Nintendo player for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But honestly, emulation on the DS is tough, especially when you have to get all those external cards and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_04]: Antlion Trooper's Deuce Antlion Trooper's Deuce
[SPEAKER_04]: The Cardboard Showdown with Cardboard Tube Samurai
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh god, I can't remember what game it's for now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Unreal Tournament, that's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you can check this out at ObeyTheTube.com Very cool, very cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you for following up on the mods, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: A couple quick news items here, then we're going to get to the advice column.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Matrix Online is going down from nine servers to three.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're scaling back to three servers starting August 2nd.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know, that's probably a sign that it's not doing as well as they thought it would.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, they said that the reason why they're scaling back is because there wasn't a lot of players on it one time or whatever, so they're cutting them back.
[SPEAKER_04]: Two of the servers are going to be standard servers, one of them is going to be a PvP server.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's kind of sad to hear that Matrix Online, or the Matrix franchise in general has just been going downhill.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I don't know, maybe their servers can handle more people, and so they want more people cramped into the city, because the city was huge, so it might just be the world's too big.
[SPEAKER_05]: D.D.R.
[SPEAKER_05]: Namco Museum 50th Anniversary Arcade Collection
[SPEAKER_05]: to go with this game.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're going to license Come On Eileen, Loverboy's Working for the Weekend, Fine Young Cannibals, She Drives Me Crazy, The Romantics with Talking in Your Sleep, and Daz Band's Joystick are just some of the titles that are being announced for the upcoming Namco Museum.
[SPEAKER_05]: And by the way, Namco Museum is going to be a budget title.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to be out for only $19.95.
[SPEAKER_05]: But my question... Where's Pac-Man Fever in all of this?
[SPEAKER_05]: Where is it?
[SPEAKER_05]: The quintessential Namco 80s tune, come on people.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh yes, let's get to the one and only.
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, speaking of Namco, there was a 7-Up commercial in the 80s where someone was playing Pac-Man and it played this song that sounds almost like Betty Davis' eyes, except it's Pac-Man chasing the ghost, stopping, getting all out of breath, dehydrated, and drinking a 7-Up on screen.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can you download that on one of those retro commercial websites?
[SPEAKER_01]: I think so, but I think my fiance has it on his computer, which is still not hooked up because our house is still being unpacked.
[SPEAKER_01]: But if I can, I'll try to rip the audio out of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: That would be cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, we here at Orange Lounge Radio, we're not just here to talk about video games all day long, which should be pretty evident tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: But we're here to better your lives as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because if we stayed home and played video games all day long, we'd have no time to go out and film commercials.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which we've never done, but I just thought I'd throw that out there.
[SPEAKER_05]: We were willing to.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was nicer than what I was thinking.
[SPEAKER_05]: What were you thinking?
[SPEAKER_05]: Forget it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's DarkSakura's advice column, you know it by now.
[SPEAKER_05]: What are you going to talk to us about tonight?
[SPEAKER_01]: Tonight's bit of advice is how to escape from a sinking car.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is like if you happen to drive your car off into the river or something.
[SPEAKER_01]: Number one.
[SPEAKER_01]: Open the window as soon as possible.
[SPEAKER_01]: Opening the window allows water to come in and equalize the pressure.
2.
[SPEAKER_01]: If you cannot roll your windows down, break the glass.
[SPEAKER_01]: Use your foot, shoulder, or heavy objects such as an anti-theft steering wheel lock, the club, the cops say use it, to escape from your car when it's underwater.
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting.
3.
[SPEAKER_01]: Get out as soon as you can.
[SPEAKER_01]: Floating time will range from a few seconds to a few minutes.
4.
[SPEAKER_01]: If you are unable to open the window or break it, wait until the car fills with water.
[SPEAKER_01]: When the water level reaches your head, take a deep breath and hold it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now the pressure should be equalized inside and outside, and you should be able to open the door and swim to the surface.
[SPEAKER_01]: But, you know, my number one thing is, you know, you know, don't drive after having that adios motherfucker.
[SPEAKER_01]: I had one of those.
[SPEAKER_01]: You don't drive after that.
[SPEAKER_01]: You will end up in the bay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, don't drive into the bay, people, unless you're playing Driver 3, because that's about the only fun thing to do in that game.
[SPEAKER_01]: And just in, I should go ahead and now, since it's very obvious that I have a source for my advice.
[SPEAKER_01]: The Worst Case Scenario Survival Handbook is a wonderful thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: It teaches you all kinds of ways to keep from getting trapped in an elevator and controlling runaway camels.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: They sell a calendar or something?
[SPEAKER_01]: I have a calendar.
[SPEAKER_05]: We should really plug them so they don't sue you.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, I've been getting my advice, but this is all stuff I knew anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: You never know when you have to cross a piranha-infested river, okay?
[SPEAKER_01]: or Navigate a Minefield.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to laugh one of these days when someone actually... I was on this runaway camel and you saved my life.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you, Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, I'm waiting for the podcast alley votes this month because we usually have a couple people that leave these smart-ass comments that say, like, Orange Lounge taught me how to have a baby.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, like, all these crazy things, which is cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'm looking forward to seeing those types of things come up this next month when people can vote again.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, vote for us.
[SPEAKER_05]: Vote.
[SPEAKER_01]: Every second.
[SPEAKER_05]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rumble Roses XX.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a sequel to Rumble Roses and it's coming out on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why didn't they call this Rumble Roses XXXG?
[SPEAKER_05]: Let me think about this one for a little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because that's basically what it will be.
[SPEAKER_05]: I saw pictures.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's pretty.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's going to be customizable.
[SPEAKER_05]: None of the existing characters will be replaced.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fans of the series should check out changes to the known roster before inquiring about new characters.
[SPEAKER_05]: So they're going to kind of change, but none of the characters are leaving, supposedly.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it should be very interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: It needs customizable characters.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're saying, though, that they're not thinking about mud wrestling.
[SPEAKER_05]: They want to do something else that's stunning.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I guess they haven't thought of it yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Cream Corn!
[SPEAKER_05]: Kids, Cream Corn.
[SPEAKER_04]: Braun Panty Match.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wasn't that what the whole game was?
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, it's a completely different side of the spectrum here.
[SPEAKER_05]: WB Interactive will be putting out a game on consoles and PC, and it's called Friends, the one with all the trivia.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right, it's a game dedicated to Friends trivia.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, I saw this.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's sad.
[SPEAKER_01]: Joey is your best friend.
[SPEAKER_05]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_01]: You will make him a ham sandwich every morning.
[SPEAKER_05]: Please watch Joey.
[SPEAKER_05]: Somebody, please watch it.
[SPEAKER_01]: And buy him hundreds of dollars in pants.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm sorry, that's the only episode I remember was the Subliminal Message episode.
[SPEAKER_05]: I remember Smelly Cat.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I don't want to give that show any more time on this show.
[SPEAKER_05]: Midway!
[SPEAKER_05]: Midway's putting out a sequel to The Suffering.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a sequel to the popular shooter called The Suffering, The Ties That Bind.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they just wanted to let you all know that they landed some major Hollywood talent to be doing the voice acting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Michael Clarke Duncan.
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember that guy who was in The Green Mile and The Planet of the Apes and Daredevil?
[SPEAKER_05]: He will be doing a villainous character in the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Rachel Griffiths, who is in Six Feet Under and Hillary and Jackie and probably nobody that listens to this show remembers this movie, but I remember her at Muriel's wedding.
[SPEAKER_05]: She's going to be doing a role in this as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: So some big Hollywood talent coming to The Suffering.
[SPEAKER_04]: Might add also The Suffering starts in three different ways depending on how you ended the first game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or The Suffering starts if you choose to buy a Mary-Kate and Ashley Olsen game instead.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bad joke.
[SPEAKER_05]: Forget it.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, you had another story for us?
[SPEAKER_01]: I sure do.
[SPEAKER_01]: I actually wanted Yahoo!
[SPEAKER_01]: UK put up the top 100 computer games of all time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ah, very interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, now we don't have time to read all 100, but... But I'll give you the top 10.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, top 10 works.
[SPEAKER_01]: Number 10, Elite for the BBC Micro, which is a system I need to get because I don't have one anymore.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hope I will have heard of some of these games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, UK listeners, I just don't know that one.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's very Vectory.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: Then we have GoldenEye 007 for the Nintendo 64.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know that one.
[SPEAKER_01]: That game makes me violently motion sick.
[SPEAKER_05]: But for shooter fans, great game.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was a great game, but it did make me violently motion sick.
[SPEAKER_01]: Next up, we have Street Fighter 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, definitely.
[SPEAKER_01]: Arcade version.
[SPEAKER_05]: Revolutionized arcades, absolutely.
[SPEAKER_01]: Super Mario Kart for the Super Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_05]: Old favorite of mine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Love it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Monkey Island 2, LeChuck's Revenge for the PC.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hell yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's an interesting one to have in the top ten.
[SPEAKER_05]: A good choice, but that's kind of like that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, that's number five.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, what else?
[SPEAKER_01]: Number four, Legend of Zelda Ocarina of Time for the Nintendo 64.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know the hate mail is going to come in, but Ocarina of Time was not as great of a game as everybody says.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, it was.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, it wasn't.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Super Nintendo one was leaps and bounds better, in my opinion.
[SPEAKER_05]: But maybe I just can't get the 3D Zelda thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, I apologize.
[SPEAKER_01]: That one was number five.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, sorry.
[SPEAKER_01]: And listeners, never mind Rob, because he's on crack.
[SPEAKER_05]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hated it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Super Nintendo one was the best.
[SPEAKER_05]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Moving on.
Number four.
[SPEAKER_01]: Pro Evolution Soccer 4 on the PlayStation 2, put out by Konami.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whoa, soccer and not football?
[SPEAKER_04]: Your mic's going out again.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know what's going on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_01]: Konami published it with Sakura in the title, but it is football.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: Number three, Pokemon Red and Green.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a big audience for that, and it reaches a lot of people.
[SPEAKER_01]: Pokey Pokey.
[SPEAKER_05]: Top two.
[SPEAKER_01]: Number two, Super Mario 64 for the Nintendo 64.
[SPEAKER_01]: That game was fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Again, the most overrated... This is the thing with Nintendo 64 games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Their franchise games were incredibly overrated, in my opinion.
[SPEAKER_05]: Goldeneye was a good game.
[SPEAKER_01]: I like how it's described.
[SPEAKER_01]: It says they're a childhood hero able to go anywhere and do anything to an extent that is purely magical.
[SPEAKER_05]: And doesn't hold a candle to Mario 3, but that's just my big, fat opinion.
[SPEAKER_01]: The number one game of all time... Tetris for the Game Boy.
[SPEAKER_05]: No Pac-Man anywhere in the top ten, which is considered the granddaddy.
[SPEAKER_01]: However, DDR was number 49.
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right, well, Tetris... And it was right above Afterburner, which I honestly like better than DDR.
[SPEAKER_05]: Everybody plays Tetris, so I can't argue with that as the number one choice.
[SPEAKER_05]: I really can't.
[SPEAKER_01]: Tetris is the ultimate game to take on an airplane.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Couple more stories for you guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: Codemasters
[SPEAKER_05]: Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: on the product, and Konami is bringing a good game to the American Idol name.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, they're not confirming that it's going to be a karaoke revolution marriage, the American Idol game, but come on, what else is it going to be, people?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be karaoke.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's got to be some type of karaoke.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then you're going to see DDR, Think You Can Dance.
[SPEAKER_04]: Please, please, no.
[SPEAKER_05]: End there, end there.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to happen.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, and... Wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um...
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, moving on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Field of Magic.
[SPEAKER_05]: You remember that game on the DS?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's kind of like a dating sim type game, but it was like WarioWare mixed with Sprung, I guess you could say.
[SPEAKER_05]: Field of Magic, even though it wasn't the most hugely popular game, it's actually getting a sequel.
[SPEAKER_05]: Famitsu Magazine mentions that Field of Magic XXYY is going to be getting a sequel.
[SPEAKER_05]: Guess what the sequel is called?
[SPEAKER_05]: This is all we know about the game so far is the name.
[SPEAKER_05]: Akachan wa doko karakuru no?
[SPEAKER_05]: Which means, where do babies come from?
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Where do babies come from?
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, um...
[SPEAKER_04]: You got another quick story before I get to tonight's last story?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like I hinted at earlier about the Nintendogs thing, selected members of Nintendo.com who are registered there will receive their copies of Nintendog on August 22nd.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or before the August 22nd release date, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: And rumor is it's probably going to be the people that have the most usage of their forms.
[SPEAKER_04]: Lucky you people.
[SPEAKER_04]: Send me a copy.
[SPEAKER_04]: and also one more thing and it's not too much of a surprise since there's a lot of instant messaging on the Xbox 360 they're going to have a QWERTY controller as well one of those ones with a stupid little keyboard on the bottom fun fun interesting
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, one more story for you guys tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: I promised you a Mac story.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's your Mac story.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you are a OSX user, you must check this out.
[SPEAKER_05]: MikeZornik.com, that's M-I-K-E-Z-O-R-N-E-K.com slash Coco, C-O-C-O-A, slash Mega Man Effect.
[SPEAKER_05]: And what this is, this is an application so that when you launch an icon in OSX, it actually does the Mega Man Effect from Mega Man 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it's gonna be like, calculator!
[SPEAKER_05]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: So every time you launch an application, the icon comes out, and you get the little Mega Man 2 anthem.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my god, that'd be so annoying, but I gotta put, I would totally put that on my computer at home.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you saying you're gonna buy a Mac?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not gonna buy a Mac for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck that, he'll port it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, that would be so annoying.
[SPEAKER_04]: They should do that with everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hamburger!
[SPEAKER_04]: Dude!
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow!
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, guess what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's at the door?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Pizza Man!
[SPEAKER_05]: Mailman!
[SPEAKER_05]: No!
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, God.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: And now it's time for the final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, just kidding.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just kidding, people.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, Loki, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_04]: My final thought is I must play more Star Soldier, and goddammit, they better have my copy of Graffiti Kingdom.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, besides getting your mic fixed, what's your final thought?
[SPEAKER_01]: Sometimes, the reason why I say I don't play any games during the week is because I have a life!
[SPEAKER_01]: I work and I go to college!
[SPEAKER_01]: Sue me!
[SPEAKER_05]: Somebody ruffled your feathers this week, didn't we?
[SPEAKER_05]: And my final thought, I'm hungry, so I'm going to go have a pizza.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe you should call the pizza man!
[SPEAKER_05]: Goodbye, everybody.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for tuning in.
[SPEAKER_05]: See you next time on the Orange Line.
[SPEAKER_05]: You guys are going to do a cast next week, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Ow!
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: Your table got all GTA on my elbow.
[SPEAKER_05]: She got beat up by Pizza Man.
[SPEAKER_05]: Put down the joke.
[SPEAKER_05]: Step away from the joke.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey, at least it's not, you know, cake pie anymore.
[SPEAKER_05]: You guys are going to be here next week even though I'm not, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: We will be taking over the podcast.
[SPEAKER_05]: That should be interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: It'll be anger chat for 30 minutes.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, I could always call in on Skype or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: We could always set you on fire.
[SPEAKER_05]: Until next time, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the end of another Orange Lounge Radio To Go edition.
[SPEAKER_03]: This podcast is a proud part of www.orangeloungeradio.com See you next update.