[SPEAKER_04]: Tonight, June 2nd, 2013, One Country has a strong statement about the Xbox One.
[SPEAKER_04]: Blizzard postpones its next MMO, and could legendary buried game cartridges in the desert soon be unearthed?
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura or Jamie Summers
[SPEAKER_03]: Can we call this one a go-to-mix instead?
[SPEAKER_11]: Whatever you want it to be.
[SPEAKER_03]: Can we have True Kiss Destination?
[SPEAKER_11]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: Club Append!
[SPEAKER_11]: They weren't that good, let's be real.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, if their career didn't last that long.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dreams Come True lasted longer than them.
[SPEAKER_11]: Also say hello to Tech Master Loki.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hi, how you doing, Loki?
[SPEAKER_11]: Pretty good.
[SPEAKER_11]: Excellent.
[SPEAKER_11]: And of course, my name is Rob Roberts, and we do join you live every Sunday night at 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern, right after the Bobby Blackwolf Show at the Voice of Geeks Network, vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, so last week was a little weird.
[SPEAKER_11]: We weren't actually here live on Sunday.
[SPEAKER_11]: We did a special show earlier in the week, which we called episode number 506, but then it was brought to my attention.
[SPEAKER_11]: You're going to ruin all the tracking of the classic game of the week and all these segments you usually do if you give a special episode a regular episode number.
[SPEAKER_11]: So I broke it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just put a blank in there.
[SPEAKER_07]: How damn hard is that?
[SPEAKER_11]: Give it a letter.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's fine.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's episode R. We'll just have 506.
[SPEAKER_11]: Second mix.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's a do-over!
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll do it live!
[SPEAKER_03]: Because it's not an episode unless I'm here, let's face it.
[SPEAKER_11]: So episode two was not an episode?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, it wasn't.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was when I was sleeping in the Harry Potter room at the Gay Frat House.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, so last week you were in Alabama, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_11]: And you were taking care of mostly some family stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: But you did get to hang out with, like, you met at least one OLR listener, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: I got to hang out with Jammer J, who I have known for quite some time, and there's a little bit of background.
[SPEAKER_03]: About 10 years ago, we met up and played DDR together, and I got his games, and I think I got him dinner.
[SPEAKER_03]: So this time he paid for my games and got me dinner, and took me to McGuire's in Pensacola, and I got shit-faced.
[SPEAKER_03]: I drank, okay, Meguiar's is like a small microbrewery, and they do their own stouts and porters.
[SPEAKER_03]: I had a good porter, but then they served me this drink called an Irish Wake that's very green and served in a mason jar, and I consumed it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I was very dizzy the rest of the ride.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then I got a sunburn in the shape, well, my tan line is in the shape of a seatbelt because we were riding in a convertible and I stopped caring about the sun.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: But we did go to Pace, Florida and play a lot of DDR and played some Addams Family Pinball at another arcade at the Pensacola Beach.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then I spent some time with my mama's son and papa's son and their roommates Kristen and Bobby, a different Bobby, of course.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I got to see Derek, who is one of my very good friends.
[SPEAKER_11]: And all these people none of our listeners know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: and my good friend Donovan who, they're both fixtures at DragonCon.
[SPEAKER_03]: You may run into them.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I got to see my very good friend Jen.
[SPEAKER_03]: She picked me up when my flight was changed from Gulfport to Mobile.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do not get me started on American Airlines because fuck them.
[SPEAKER_11]: I heard about your drama going.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, fuck them.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm on an airplane tomorrow and you got me a little worried.
[SPEAKER_03]: Are you doing American?
[SPEAKER_11]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good, fuck them.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't care if I can wear it or not.
[SPEAKER_11]: Is there a hot topic in Alabama?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, we had Gadzooks, I think.
[SPEAKER_03]: But at any rate, I bought a Charlie the Unicorn shirt at a Goodwill in Daphne, Alabama.
[SPEAKER_11]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shine the non-believer!
[SPEAKER_11]: If you do get dumped from the stream, just click pause and play again.
[SPEAKER_11]: If you're at live.vognetwork.com and it should reconnect right away as soon as we come back.
[SPEAKER_11]: Unfortunately, I don't know what to do about it.
[SPEAKER_11]: The joys of live radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: I might have upset the cosmic balance by my sewing.
[SPEAKER_11]: Possibly.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm doing matronly things.
[SPEAKER_11]: Can you sew the internet back together?
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_11]: Get a really big needle.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have really tiny needles.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I keep poking myself in the thumb.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's not gonna work.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, so you missed our X-Bone special.
[SPEAKER_11]: Excuse me, our XB1 special.
[SPEAKER_11]: All the stuff about the Xbox One.
[SPEAKER_11]: Did you hear anything about Xbox One?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, and fuck all of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not getting it.
[SPEAKER_11]: No.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, now, wait a minute, DarkSakura, and I think I said this on the show.
[SPEAKER_11]: Isn't it too early to make up your mind on this?
[SPEAKER_03]: Right now, going by what I have, fuck them.
[SPEAKER_11]: And why so strongly?
[SPEAKER_11]: Why the F-bomb?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I don't want to have a microphone and or a camera on all the damn time.
[SPEAKER_03]: The whole used games thing, fuck them.
[SPEAKER_03]: The whole downloading games, fuck them even more.
[SPEAKER_03]: If I'm going to download a game, it's going to be on my PC.
[SPEAKER_03]: Where, you know, if I buy another PC...
[SPEAKER_03]: Guess what?
[SPEAKER_03]: My games will transfer.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, well, to be fair, to play devil's advocate, what's the difference between getting a digital copy on your PC that you can't sell back and a digital... Because I can upgrade my video card.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can upgrade everything on my PC and make everything look amazing.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, in a way, you're saying a PC is pretty much guaranteed to be backwards compatible, no matter what.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pretty much.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, I guess that's fair because the Xbox 360, anything you downloaded... I've been playing Loom.
[SPEAKER_03]: If I can play Loom, thanks to Steam, if I can play all kinds of old PC games, if I can play text-based games, if I can play Oregon Trail on my PC, I have no problem.
[SPEAKER_11]: um going to our chat room at live.vognetwork.com or of course again we do tape live every Sunday night right after Bobby Blackwolf at 6 Pacific 9 Eastern on Sundays uh Gamer Girl says thank you Dark Sakura clap clap that's exactly why I don't want one either uh Koopa Kid Jeremy says I think it's too early to decide that it's not for you I kind of agree could anything but could anything at E3 end up swaying your mind that's what I'm curious about what if they come out and say the big rumor is Killer Instinct it's gonna be one of the games what if one of these 15 games is like OMG gotta have
[SPEAKER_11]: What if there's a Homestuck game, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_11]: What if there's a Homestuck game?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I know for a fact already that I don't think it's... Well, I think it's going to be PC anyway.
[SPEAKER_11]: What if Mass Effect 4 is an Xbox One exclusive?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's already going to be running on PC.
[SPEAKER_11]: What if, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_11]: What if?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know that that would be enough because fuck EA.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_03]: Time to change it!
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that for him it's going to be more of the next Gran Turismo game, of course it's just going to be PS3, but he's going to probably stick Sony.
[SPEAKER_03]: Especially if they say something that's going to counter all of the crap that Microsoft is saying.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's sort of a wait and see kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, well I'm going to check in with you again after E3 and see if anything that has happened may have changed your mind.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, and to tell Ragenator about Fuck Activision, I did quit WoW before I went to Alabama.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now that everybody is reuniting in our guild.
[SPEAKER_11]: Two people came back to WoW, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_11]: Two people.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's not everybody.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, we better do like an old raid or something before my account expires.
[SPEAKER_11]: I thought your account already expired.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I've got a couple days left on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll find out when it expires.
[SPEAKER_11]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then let me do, like, Ice Crown Citadel.
[SPEAKER_11]: You should go to Karazhan and get the pets.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want pets.
[SPEAKER_11]: There's new pets in Karazhan.
[SPEAKER_03]: Stop it!
[SPEAKER_11]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_03]: Stop it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I stopped paying for it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wow, crack.
[SPEAKER_03]: I did delete the beta, so that did free up a lot of space.
[SPEAKER_03]: But then I filled it up with, like, more games on Steam.
[SPEAKER_11]: Isn't that how it always goes?
[SPEAKER_03]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_11]: I just cleared off 100 gigs from my hard drive.
[SPEAKER_11]: God damn it, Steam sale.
[SPEAKER_11]: God damn it, Humble Bundle.
[SPEAKER_11]: God damn it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Which is funny.
[SPEAKER_11]: You don't have to install all of them.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I don't have them all installed.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, you do.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have a bunch.
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually have the majority of them not installed.
[SPEAKER_11]: How dare you?
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know when I might want to play.
[SPEAKER_11]: You just never know.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I can never uninstall something because the minute I uninstall it, what happens?
[SPEAKER_03]: And TigerClaw, Gran Turismo 6 has already been stated to be for PS3.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, anyhow Keep me strong, tie me to the mast I will hear the song but I shall not succumb This is my finger Well, I've got a needle in my hand This is my finger raised at Activision and Blizzard Sit and spin, motherfuckers Or pay for my account Oh boy Is there anything in gaming you do like this week?
[SPEAKER_03]: I started playing Mass Effect again
[SPEAKER_03]: And guess what, Rob?
[SPEAKER_11]: God, I just can't.
[SPEAKER_07]: She won't get an Xbox One if it's Mass Effect 4.
[SPEAKER_11]: Right, exactly.
[SPEAKER_11]: It totally answers my earlier question.
[SPEAKER_11]: Totally answers my... Who is she?
[SPEAKER_11]: Fucking kidding, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: No!
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, I can resist playing another Mass Effect game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_11]: LOL, nope.
[SPEAKER_03]: The minute Garrus in HD... There will not be a Garrus in... They already said Mass Effect 4 is a different story.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, here we go.
[SPEAKER_11]: Here we go, guys.
[SPEAKER_11]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, this is the first OLR comic strip I need somebody to draw, okay?
[SPEAKER_11]: You can bite my ass along with Activision and Blizzard and EA.
[SPEAKER_11]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_11]: First panel, DarkSakura holding a microphone saying, I will not buy an Xbox One.
[SPEAKER_11]: Fuck them.
[SPEAKER_11]: Fuck them and their stupid asses.
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, ready?
[SPEAKER_11]: Second panel is a picture of the E3 press conference where EA and Microsoft are holding hands on a stage saying, Mass Effect Garrus Edition, Xbox One exclusive.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then the third panel is DarkSakura walking into a Best Buy with a balloon that says, LOL, nope.
[SPEAKER_11]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_11]: LOL, nope.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, first of all, I'm fairly certain that with a franchise like that, they will not make it an exclusive.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm only saying this to get you ruffled and it's working you know what you are about to earn yourself the mother of all girl
[SPEAKER_03]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_03]: And... Okay, this is... To go ahead and put the blanket thing out there, yes, I will get Mass Effect 4.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I love the universe.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't care how shitty the story is.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't care how sparkly the turd is.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love the turd.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will buy the sparkly turd.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because I am a fangirl.
[SPEAKER_11]: There's her little quote for the next show intro.
[SPEAKER_11]: I love the turd.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: I have pointy things.
[SPEAKER_03]: You see all these little pins?
[SPEAKER_11]: answering your questions as you direct him on the show floor.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's all explained for you at e3.vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_11]: Check it out.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's get into how was your gaming week and we'll talk about the types of video games you've been playing this week.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, why don't you start us off?
[SPEAKER_03]: Lol, Mass Effect.
[SPEAKER_11]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: Guess what?
[SPEAKER_03]: I bought Dramamine so that I can do the makeup missions.
[SPEAKER_03]: God, I'm awful.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have ginger pills and Dramamine.
[SPEAKER_11]: You bought drugs so you can play Mass Effect.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because last time I played... Okay, last time I had a nice two-hour session of getting side missions out of the way, and I literally had to stop playing after... Stop it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do not YouTube me, Rob.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rob!
[SPEAKER_11]: Have you ever played... Don't watch what I'm doing over here.
[SPEAKER_11]: Keep talking.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I decided that I didn't want to get motion sick again, so I have plenty of things to keep me from getting sick to my stomach.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hopefully, just because I get super motion sick, I'll make omissions.
[SPEAKER_03]: I also downloaded a bunch of high-res, it's called the Ultimate High-Res Mod or something, for...
[SPEAKER_03]: For the first Mass Effect That has made my game look absolutely freaking gorgeous Like, pretty And so I have been I'm still on the stupid first mission Right after Dumbass gets shot Which we all know who Dumbass is Jenkins, sorry So I am right after that part in my game And it kind of doesn't like all the mods But I don't care Because it makes my game pretty And I play DDR
[SPEAKER_11]: So again, to clarify, you bought drugs so you could play a drug?
[SPEAKER_00]: No!
[SPEAKER_00]: I had the gender on it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Have you ever played Mass Effect?
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: And for the record, anyone who's a fan of the first Mass Effect that is interested in this mod, talk to me.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I played a lot of DVR, my calves hurt for the next two days, and my skin did.
[SPEAKER_03]: You gotta stretch.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh no, I stretched.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was freaking doing yoga in an arcade, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: But it was very fun, and so if you go to the one and only DDR machine in all of Pace, Florida, and you see D. Sakura Explanation Point, that is me.
[SPEAKER_03]: On two whole songs.
[SPEAKER_03]: Two.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I passed Superstar.
[SPEAKER_11]: Until they reset the leaderboard at night.
[SPEAKER_03]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I was feeling old, so I passed Superstar, and it made me good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Congrats.
[SPEAKER_03]: So yeah, I... Oh yeah, I also played a lot of Midway Arcade for tickets on my iPad.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, oh, I was like, like the classic midway games like Joust and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, well, yeah, but I was playing pool.
[SPEAKER_03]: I could not stop playing stupid pool.
[SPEAKER_11]: If you just want tickets in that game, just play the skee-ball.
[SPEAKER_11]: You can just, you just go like this, fling, fling, fling, fling, fling, fling, fling, tickets, fling, fling, fling, fling, fling.
[SPEAKER_03]: You play one game of pool and you get 200 points.
[SPEAKER_03]: Even if you scratch it on your first one, you still get 75 points.
[SPEAKER_11]: I didn't know that.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I was like, pool, pool.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was so mind-numbingly bored.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: When I laid down on my grandmother's bed, for a moment I was like, oh, the bed's kind of crooked.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then it was daylight.
[SPEAKER_03]: So my time completely reset while I was there.
[SPEAKER_03]: But still my night owl thing was like, it's 8 o'clock and I'm not out doing stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is not me.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it was very bizarre.
[SPEAKER_03]: So yeah, I played a lot of Midware Kid and Blazing Star.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I have Blazing Star on my iPad and that game is awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: The end.
[SPEAKER_11]: The end.
[SPEAKER_11]: Loki, how about you?
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, this week I played more Saints Row the Third, just trying to finish up my last few achievements on there.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then also played...
[SPEAKER_07]: A bit of track mania.
[SPEAKER_07]: We tried to do VOG Gaming Night on that.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was weird because I did everything correctly.
[SPEAKER_07]: One person was able to join my game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Everybody else was not able to join my game.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then we decided, hey, let's play on a third-party server.
[SPEAKER_07]: So we just picked a server at random that we were able to connect to.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then it just had the weirdest fucking tracks ever.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just these giant maze tracks everywhere.
[SPEAKER_07]: that were impossible to figure out where the hell you were supposed to go.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was ridiculous, but we had a little bit of fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then I played a little bit of Cave Story Plus and a very little bit of Call of Duty because everyone was flaking the entire week.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_11]: My gaming week.
[SPEAKER_11]: Over the Memorial Day weekend, I was staying with Captain Spike and Tim, who were on a previous episode a few weeks ago at their Memorial Day soiree.
[SPEAKER_11]: We played a few video games.
[SPEAKER_11]: I watched them play Trivial Pursuit on the Xbox, which was kind of frustrating how long that game was going on because it's Trivial Pursuit and LOL.
[SPEAKER_11]: and uh we went out to GameStop one day randomly to go find a cheap game to play and we ended up buying Wheel of Fortune I should say Spike ended up buying Wheel of Fortune on the Xbox 360 and many lulls ensued uh what can I say about it I'm like you you know exactly what you're gonna get with a game like Wheel of Fortune because you've seen the game show at some point in your life yes although I have to admit the characters are a little bit derpy and some of the unlocks are a
[SPEAKER_11]: For $20, hey!
[SPEAKER_11]: It provided a little bit of entertainment and some really, really hilarious instances where we were solving puzzles incorrectly and throwing each other off and so forth.
[SPEAKER_11]: So that was fun.
[SPEAKER_11]: As far as other stuff I've been playing during the week, I was keeping it retro.
[SPEAKER_11]: And thanks to some conversations I was having on Twitter with not just Spike, but Jeremy from Koopa Club and some of the other people I talk with on Twitter...
[SPEAKER_11]: I was reminded that Mario 2 came out on Virtual Console for Wii U and I was like, oh, I had that on the Wii so I should just spend the dollar or whatever to upgrade it and play it.
[SPEAKER_11]: And not only did I play it, I played it from start to finish.
[SPEAKER_11]: Granted, I cheated and I used warps, but I used only Luigi the whole way through the game.
[SPEAKER_11]: In my nod to Year of Luigi, I beat Mario 2 using only Luigi.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I'm going to tell you what, those ice stages that you have to play even when you warp,
[SPEAKER_11]: Suck with Luigi.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, they do.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because I'm used to using the princess to just float through those little, you know, not the shy guys.
[SPEAKER_11]: What do you call the flying ones with the pitchfork?
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't remember their names.
[SPEAKER_03]: The flurries?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, the flurries are the guys on the ground.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, the little dudes on the ground that look like little jigglypuffs.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't remember what they're called.
[SPEAKER_03]: I call them bastards.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, they're little fuckers.
[SPEAKER_11]: So the little fuckers are flying in the air and the princess is easy.
[SPEAKER_11]: You just float in between them.
[SPEAKER_11]: But not so easy when you're Luigi.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I did it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I did it.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I beat the game.
[SPEAKER_11]: And that was fun.
[SPEAKER_11]: So yeah, I was keeping it retro this week.
[SPEAKER_11]: I gotta say, there's something about Wii U Virtual Console and I'm totally having to eat my words from what I said earlier on this program about a year ago when I was like, Wii U Virtual Console is gonna be stupid and why would I pay money to upgrade and da-da-da.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's just a better experience and I can't put my finger on it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know if it's the HDMI, I don't know if it's the sound from the tablet and the sound from the speakers at the same time.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know, but it is a better experience.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, oops, I was wrong.
[SPEAKER_11]: It happens.
[SPEAKER_11]: So yeah, I was having fun with Mario 2 on Virtual Console.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then I was playing Warcraft because, you know, I'm addicted.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, I hit 90 with my Hunter, my Blood Elf Hunter, my PvP character.
[SPEAKER_11]: So I've been playing more PvP.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you get sassy to 90... Sassy is 87.
[SPEAKER_11]: In a row?
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: When you get sassy to 90, I will redo, I will re-up WoW for one month.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just to play with sassy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I like the braids.
[SPEAKER_03]: They float.
[SPEAKER_11]: Jeremy is coaching me in chat, I guess, saying, you warped.
[SPEAKER_11]: I said I warped.
[SPEAKER_11]: My next goal is to do it without warping, but unfortunately I'm on a work trip this week, and then I have all the E3 stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, I'm not going to E3, but there's other stuff going on.
[SPEAKER_11]: So it's going to be a little while before I can get through the game without warping, but that's on the list, except for the fact that Animal Crossing comes out Sunday, and then the list will be shot, because yay, Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: It actually comes out on Friday.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it is Sunday.
[SPEAKER_07]: Last of Us is coming out on Friday.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, is it this Friday?
[SPEAKER_07]: Uh, next Friday.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, the E3 Friday?
[SPEAKER_07]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_11]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, I mean, if no other big games are coming out, then why not?
[SPEAKER_11]: Most of America doesn't go to E3, so it doesn't really matter.
[SPEAKER_11]: Why Friday, Street Day?
[SPEAKER_11]: Just put it out on Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_11]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_11]: Just in time for the weekend.
[SPEAKER_11]: Why do movies sometimes open on Wednesday?
[SPEAKER_11]: They just, they do.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rob?
[SPEAKER_11]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you sometimes just wonder why?
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you ever feel not so fresh?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: First of all, I am incredibly crescent fresh.
[SPEAKER_11]: And second of all, the answer to why?
[SPEAKER_11]: Because.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then deal with it.
[SPEAKER_03]: See if that works with a six-year-old, by the way.
[SPEAKER_11]: With the floating sunglasses.
[SPEAKER_11]: Did you tell the child to deal with it and then have sunglasses land on your face?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, but I'm going to do that next time.
[SPEAKER_03]: You should.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would be hilarious to see Julian's reaction.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, housekeeping.
[SPEAKER_11]: Visit our Twitter, twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_11]: And we are on Facebook as well, facebook.com slash Orange Launch Radio and on the Google+.
[SPEAKER_11]: And of course, you want to visit our network, vognetwork.com, home to lots of great geeky podcasts and geeky content, including video game reviews.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know Actdeft just reviewed Dust and Elysian Tale.
[SPEAKER_11]: was on the site this week.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then, of course, as I mentioned before, lots of exciting stuff going on for E3.
[SPEAKER_11]: So check out e3.vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_11]: We will be the second site that you check.
[SPEAKER_11]: Not the first.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll be the second.
[SPEAKER_11]: And that's okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're number two.
[SPEAKER_11]: Silver medal for VOG.
[SPEAKER_11]: It'll be great.
[SPEAKER_11]: Xbox One, Xbox One, Xbox One, Xbox One
[SPEAKER_07]: 1 billion dollars into putting games on the Xbox One.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I'm assuming a lot of that has to do with the 15 exclusives that they, I guess, paid for and will be coming out the first year.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then didn't really hint at a whole lot of what's coming other than, you know, we know there's a Rare game coming and apparently Black Tusk Studios is working on something.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um...
[SPEAKER_07]: Microsoft Studios is obviously working on stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: We know that there's going to be a new Forza.
[SPEAKER_07]: Remedy's got that Quantum Break game and EA's got some stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not necessarily exclusive, but features that are somewhat exclusive, I guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're spending quite a bit of money on that stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: uh of course you know we're gonna have to figure out what that is and um you know maybe one of these announcements has to do with a bunch of these you know domains that they're registering including domains pertaining to a title called Halo Spartan Assault which doesn't sound like a you know it almost sounds like an arcade game or something like a spin-off so I guess we'll have to wait and see could it be maybe an upgrade or something
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm hoping it's not that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Remember, wasn't there supposed to be like a Kinect-powered game or something like that?
[SPEAKER_07]: Remember, they were doing that with Gears of War, I remember.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe it's like a Kinect Halo game or something?
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Joy, I can flail around and choose weapons.
[SPEAKER_11]: Didn't one of the Halo games, like ODST or something, incorporate Kinect?
[SPEAKER_11]: Um, well... Like you could shout grenade and it would throw a grenade?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, that was the Halo Combat Evolved HD thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh yeah, that one.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Combat Evolved Anniversary.
[SPEAKER_07]: They had where you can shout grenade.
[SPEAKER_07]: There was a lot of Halo games.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry, can you shout grenade faster than you can press a button?
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, you cannot.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that's assuming that the Kinect hears you and understands what you ask for.
[SPEAKER_11]: It would only be useful as if what you're yelling is, how do I throw a grenade?
[SPEAKER_11]: And it just does it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh hey, it worked!
[SPEAKER_11]: How do I throw a grenade?
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, anyway, the German Federal Commissioner for Data Protection and Freedom of Information.
[SPEAKER_11]: I did not know such a position existed in Germany, but I guess it makes sense.
[SPEAKER_11]: Certainly, you want to make sure that everything is regulated when it comes to those exchanges, but to a fault.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyhow, he calls it the Xbox One Connect, a monitoring device.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's because it is.
[SPEAKER_11]: It is.
[SPEAKER_11]: And he goes on to say, under the heading Game Device, this is through a translation that he mentioned with the website Spiegel.de, but this is through a translation.
[SPEAKER_11]: Spiegel.
[SPEAKER_11]: Under the heading Game Device, Microsoft pushes a monitoring device in the market.
[SPEAKER_11]: The Xbox continuously records all sorts of personal information about me.
[SPEAKER_11]: Reaction rates, my learning or emotional states, these are then processed on an external server and possibly even passed on to third parties.
[SPEAKER_11]: Whether they will ever be deleted, the person cannot influence
[SPEAKER_07]: It absolutely is.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's what it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's marketing metrics is what it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're going to be listening to stuff that you're talking about.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they're going to advertise to you.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're going to target advertising.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's just like on Facebook where they try to target advertising.
[SPEAKER_07]: But they're going to also make sure that, hey, are you paying attention to those ads?
[SPEAKER_07]: What ads are interesting you?
[SPEAKER_07]: That kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: So they're going into greater detail.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that information is worth a ton.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_11]: Microsoft is a leader in the world of privacy.
[SPEAKER_11]: We aren't using Kinect to snoop on anybody at all.
[SPEAKER_11]: We listen for the word Xbox on, then switch on the machine, but we don't transmit personal data in any way, shape, or form that could be personally identifiable to you unless you explicitly opt into that.
[SPEAKER_11]: What's interesting about that is that basically he's saying it is there.
[SPEAKER_11]: You just have to opt into it, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: And I remember their excuse was, well, but you can turn the console off.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can power the console off and unplug it.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's stupid.
[SPEAKER_11]: So it sounds to me like Microsoft is going to have to really clarify this.
[SPEAKER_11]: And it's a valid concern about this.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, when I got into this last week is that I don't want no Xbox filming me when I'm running around in my underwear trying to get coffee in the morning or whatever.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, I don't need that.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, who knows?
[SPEAKER_11]: Who knows what might be said when I yell to Alan in the other room and suddenly I'm calling DarkSakura on Kinect and things are awkward.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_07]: All I got to say is you're going to be getting a lot of targeted Pinkberry advertisements.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: and Keurig.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pinkberry and Keurig.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll be there with you except for the Keurig part.
[SPEAKER_03]: You said to buy enough of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just saying if I ever get the console I'm just talking about pornography whenever I'm in front of it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Here's what I was thinking about, though, with the Xbox One, is that if I get one, which, you know, I'm still on the fence.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't feel as strongly as Jamie does, what she said earlier in the show, but I kind of have very similar concerns to what she already said.
[SPEAKER_07]: To me, it's very similar to how I felt with the Wii U. It's like, okay, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do I feel like buying one right now?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I don't feel like buying one.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_11]: And if I wanted to cover the little camera on the little device, or I can just flip it to the wall or whatever, and it still works just fine.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, no worries, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: So here's my thing is that I think Microsoft needs to clarify some of this, and I think they will.
[SPEAKER_11]: But in a way, if it's just left at what Phil Harrison is saying, he's basically saying, what?
[SPEAKER_11]: Don't you trust us?
[SPEAKER_11]: We're a leader in privacy information.
[SPEAKER_11]: What are you talking about?
[SPEAKER_11]: No one got hacked before.
[SPEAKER_11]: Money wasn't stolen.
[SPEAKER_11]: Fact, guys.
[SPEAKER_11]: Fact.
[SPEAKER_11]: You want me to trust a company that, fact, sold a bunch of broken Xboxes that would break after several days of use.
[SPEAKER_11]: My Xbox 360 Red Ring two days after I bought it.
[SPEAKER_11]: That is a fact.
[SPEAKER_11]: fact I had money stolen from my Xbox Live account by a hacker and to this day Microsoft will not acknowledge that there was a breach and instead they deflect blame on the user that is a fact and you want me to trust you you need to be a little bit more transparent with what's going on that's the reality
[SPEAKER_11]: And if I want to turn that fucker off, then I should be able to turn it off.
[SPEAKER_11]: Period.
[SPEAKER_11]: It should not require that thing to be on for any reason.
[SPEAKER_11]: Here's my other question.
[SPEAKER_11]: What if I just unplug the fucking thing so it doesn't have a power source?
[SPEAKER_11]: What if I just unplug it when I don't want to use it?
[SPEAKER_11]: Is that going to cause it to malfunction?
[SPEAKER_11]: Because I could just put it on a switch and have a little on-off switch.
[SPEAKER_07]: They said, no, you don't even have to do that.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just like the PlayStation 3 where there's a power switch on the back of the console and you can flip it off.
[SPEAKER_07]: But they're just saying, though, if you're going to leave it in standby mode or whatever, that the microphones are going to be always listening to you so that you can say on and it will turn the Xbox on.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: I read 1984.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, did we leave the Xbox on?
[SPEAKER_07]: Ah, fuck, it's turned on again.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ranma in our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com says, Say what you will about Microsoft, but they handled the security breach a hell of a lot better than Sony.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes and no.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sony at least admitted there was a problem.
[SPEAKER_11]: I didn't actually have any money stolen from my Sony and that whole thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: Nobody hacked into that or stole anything.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sony did have to give a lot away with that and the whole free games and everything.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm not saying that makes it right.
[SPEAKER_11]: What happened with Sony was not cool and was something they needed to have their feet to the fire held to.
[SPEAKER_11]: but I kind of feel like that was done and they paid for that in the court of public opinion I'm not so sure Microsoft ever had to pay for that but they're gonna pay for this in the court of public opinion and you're starting to see it in you know what Germany is I mean this this is much bigger news than you guys think Germany is freaking crazy when it comes to privacy laws which
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't think anybody here is going to really have a problem with, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: Germany is a leader in some regards when it comes to the privacy.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, you know, if it's going to come to the point where like, yo, the Xbox will not be sold in Germany unless they allow you to turn it off.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's going to cause policy change.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's going to have to.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's stupid anyways to have... I understand that the interface stuff uses the Kinect.
[SPEAKER_07]: Whoop-dee-shit.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do I need to use that?
[SPEAKER_07]: Is that really something I need to use?
[SPEAKER_07]: Why even bother with it?
[SPEAKER_07]: Just have it where you can unplug it, and if it's a game that requires Kinect, and I mean requires it, not like...
[SPEAKER_07]: Shouty and Grenade or some bullshit like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: But if it requires Kinect, then have it plug in.
[SPEAKER_07]: That way they can still program the games because they know that there's going to be a Kinect there.
[SPEAKER_07]: You just plug it in.
[SPEAKER_07]: But the whole thing is, if it's not going to work with the Kinect, what if a cat knocks the Kinect off your shelf and it breaks?
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck, now you can't play your console because your stupid Kinect that you weren't using anyways for stuff is just broken.
[SPEAKER_11]: In the interest of time, I'm going to go ahead.
[SPEAKER_11]: Final thought.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wasn't it also Germany that sort of had Nintendo by the balls for legalities?
[SPEAKER_11]: Didn't the whole zombie you sell late at night thing, wasn't that a Germany-rooted thing?
[SPEAKER_03]: And we saw how they had to work out a deal to get that to go.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I think that whatever comes out of Germany, if it doesn't fly legally on the international stage, they're going to have to make changes.
[SPEAKER_11]: all right regardless admittedly we are making a lot of opinions here based on cloudy information so Microsoft I look to you to clear up some of this cloudiness at E3 and we will reformulate our opinions at that time if need be but this just shows there are questions that have to be answered let's hope Microsoft answers them in a week we'll know a week and a half in a week and a half we'll know
[SPEAKER_11]: Hopefully this will all be over and it'll all be just a dream.
[SPEAKER_11]: It'll be like that one season of Dallas.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyway, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, speaking of international stage, the Xbox One is going to be region locked.
[SPEAKER_03]: So everything that comes out must match the region and this is something Microsoft told Digital Trends.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, we've already pretty much seen this anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not a big surprise.
[SPEAKER_03]: But they are going to keep everything to country-specific guidelines before they're cleared to sale.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think before they were saying that it was up to the developer or the publisher, whatever, if they wanted it to be region-locked or not.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_03]: If it is up to the studio, that's one thing, but the quote here says, must match.
[SPEAKER_11]: Here's where I'm at with this.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's one of those things where I hear this and I'm like, okay, yet again, it's something that's a little unclear and it's a little disappointing.
[SPEAKER_11]: But sadly, I can't go, well, Microsoft, I totally blame you for doing this, because it's a real unfortunate trend.
[SPEAKER_11]: The only thing we saw that really bucked the trend recently was the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_11]: And what, the original DS was region-free?
[SPEAKER_07]: The DS, the PS, all the handheld systems up to the 3DS were region-free, and then the PS3 was region-free as well.
[SPEAKER_11]: So I can't fault Microsoft alone for this, but I think it is worth saying.
[SPEAKER_11]: We've said it many times on this show, being that this show started out of a very Japanese-centric video game.
[SPEAKER_11]: A bunch of games, including Beatmania and Dance Dance Revolution and all that.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think there's going to come a time when companies need to realize...
[SPEAKER_11]: Gaming companies tear down this wall.
[SPEAKER_11]: Why do we keep separating?
[SPEAKER_03]: We are a global community.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, yeah, we're becoming more and more this global economy.
[SPEAKER_11]: There's a lot of people here who would like to play some of the shit that's out in Japan.
[SPEAKER_11]: There's a lot of people in Europe that would like to play some of the stuff that comes out here.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's like, when are we going to get a global console?
[SPEAKER_11]: Why does everything still have to be separated?
[SPEAKER_11]: I know you're all sitting there answering the question for me that, well, it has to do with licensing, especially when you get into those music-based games.
[SPEAKER_11]: A lot of it is licensed by region.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I'm just saying, you know, the internet has got to force some of our ways of thinking in this dealing to modernize.
[SPEAKER_11]: And we need to globalize some of this stuff a little more and make more games region-free because...
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm going to be open and honest.
[SPEAKER_11]: Region locks on the PlayStation 1 is what drove me to piracy.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't think there's really a whole ton of region locking on iOS games or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I mean, let's be honest here.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's not all these iOS games that have great soundtracks and high development costs, that type of thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: But there are a few.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I know there are some music games out there that...
[SPEAKER_07]: aren't region locked, so why can they get away with it when the consoles can't?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you know, this is what I think.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you leave everything completely region-free and then just impose import taxes, you know, it's the same thing like I've sort of suggested being done for companies that outsource, you know, tax the crap out of them so that they'd be more inclined to keep jobs over here.
[SPEAKER_03]: But other than that, if a company is going to have, you know, say that everything's region-free, will then make it a little bit more expensive to import.
[SPEAKER_03]: Have an import, you know,
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, I always thought it was really cool that, you know, there was a handful of games on the 360 that were Japanese where they didn't bother to translate them.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like Death Smiles?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, they just put them up on the marketplace.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like, if you want to pay 40 bucks for it, here you go.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_03]: We bought, like, that Death Smiles Special Edition, which was pretty much the exact same.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: I wish more game companies did that stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, they just did that.
[SPEAKER_07]: They had a new Dawn of Apache game that came out.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, I mean, if they are going to region lock the Xbox One or whatever, I hope we see more stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I just think region locking is kind of a dated thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyway, more news.
[SPEAKER_07]: So let's see.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's talk a little bit about Sony.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can get away from Microsoft here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sony is going to be forcing all publishers and developers to have their titles that are going to be on the PlayStation 4 compatible with remote play on the Vita.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think that's kind of cool actually more reasons to buy a Vita it's a smart little jab at Nintendo and the fact that a lot of the whole Wii U is the whole off screen play Nintendo won't be able to claim exclusivity to that anymore although granted the Vita is a separate device it's probably going to cost you more to do it via the PS4 it's a logical movement of the chess piece if you will
[SPEAKER_07]: But it's even better than just off-screen play with the Wii U because if you're in a Wi-Fi hotspot somewhere else, and I'm assuming that this is all going to be streamed through their Gaikai stuff now, you're going to be able to play your games away from home.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, interesting.
[SPEAKER_11]: I didn't even think of that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was just assuming it would be very... And I didn't even think it would necessarily be Wi-Fi, but that's very interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, so I think it's just going to be wherever you are.
[SPEAKER_07]: That'd be kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: That would be really cool if it would work, but if you have an internet connection like what we have here trying to do the show, it might drop out.
[SPEAKER_11]: LOL, game over.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what that makes me think of, though, just as a concept?
[SPEAKER_03]: Back in the days in Neo Geo where you had the memory card where you could play on the arcade and then take it home if you had the system, wouldn't it sort of be almost the same thing?
[SPEAKER_11]: Especially if you incorporated the share function?
[SPEAKER_11]: Actually, Jamie, now that I think about it, you know, the PS3 and the PSP, yes, PSP, do this today.
[SPEAKER_11]: We talked about this on the show, how this is a horribly underlooked feature of these consoles.
[SPEAKER_11]: But if I'm at a friend's house on their Wi-Fi, if I have my PlayStation 3 set to listen for it, I can power on my PlayStation 3 from my friend's house and over the Wi-Fi navigate my PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, all this technology is there right now.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's just that it's slow as shit and you can't play games through it.
[SPEAKER_11]: You can only do things like watch movies and even then they're going to be a little bit shoddy.
[SPEAKER_11]: Maybe music.
[SPEAKER_03]: But look at where the technology is going to be in two years.
[SPEAKER_11]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_11]: Now that Sony has Gaikai, what if PlayStation 4 and Loki, I think you hit the nail on the head, what if the PlayStation 4 is a Gaikai box and they're leveraging that technology to oomph that up a lot?
[SPEAKER_03]: We're already looking into these massive...
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it's always harder to look ahead in a way because honestly, think back to when we were like 9 and 10 years old or...
[SPEAKER_11]: or even, we'll even go a little later, you know, something that, you know, because I know a lot of our listeners are younger, something that maybe a lot of you guys remember.
[SPEAKER_11]: So think to the time that was like 1990, 91 or so when the Super Nintendo was big and the Super Nintendo was first coming out.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was like when you first saw that Mode 7 for the first time, it's like, oh my God, I'm really flying.
[SPEAKER_11]: This shit is real.
[SPEAKER_11]: Or Star Fox.
[SPEAKER_11]: Stunt Race Stunt Race
[SPEAKER_11]: Who knew that we would be replacing all of our TVs?
[SPEAKER_03]: Who knew we wouldn't have to change sides?
[SPEAKER_11]: Who knew that the government would come in and say, everybody must switch from analog to digital?
[SPEAKER_11]: Like, we are going to switch as a country from analog to digital signals for TV.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like, that's just, you know, you don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: So who knows where we're going to be in 25 years?
[SPEAKER_03]: Who knew?
[SPEAKER_11]: It's exciting and scary.
[SPEAKER_03]: Back when I was playing Kangaroo on the Atari 2600, that I would be playing Mass Effect today.
[SPEAKER_11]: Who knew three years ago on this show when you were like, I don't want to play that game.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's like a stupid shoot-em-up.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't want to play that.
[SPEAKER_11]: More like dumb effects.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't want to romance the blue chick, which I did once just so I could dump her, which was hilarious.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, in about 25 years, that might be the time when you can actually play Blizzard's next MMO.
[SPEAKER_11]: They've been working on a new game that's called Titan, but that's a codename.
[SPEAKER_11]: That is not the final name of the game, that's just the codename internally.
[SPEAKER_11]: But it came out this week from a site named VentureBeat that there have been some big changes with Titan.
[SPEAKER_11]: Blizzard internally has postponed this game there were 100 people working on the project but this has been reduced to 30 the other folks have been put to work on other games Titan never had a release date it was never really confirmed by Blizzard but again rumor and all this you know speak is saying that now the game will not be ready until 2016 well now usually I would just say whatever it's a rumor you know I don't know what to think about this
[SPEAKER_11]: But the network ZAM, which runs some popular World of Warcraft sites like Wowhead, if you've played Wow, you probably know that site, wowhead.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, Wowhead.
[SPEAKER_11]: They reached out to Blizzard, and Blizzard actually said, quote,
[SPEAKER_11]: They kind of confirmed it by saying that, which is really weird.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like, you just would not expect Blizzard to be that transparent, but they said that.
[SPEAKER_11]: So...
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_11]: I, for one, can't get upset about a game I know literally nothing about
[SPEAKER_11]: Maybe that will be that much better and will actually come out sometime soon.
[SPEAKER_11]: Maybe we'll see that at BlizzCon.
[SPEAKER_11]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_11]: So I can't say I'm going to get upset about this news, especially hearing that they're going to shift the resources elsewhere.
[SPEAKER_11]: But, you know, it's a little bit, you kind of want to go, I wish I could see what Blizzard's going to do that's not Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_11]: And granted, this could be World of Warcraft 2.
[SPEAKER_11]: It could be.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, it took Ragnarok Online long enough to get to a sequel.
[SPEAKER_11]: I sort of think, I don't know, tinfoil hat maybe, but I sort of think that the next WoW expansion is going to finally give that big graphical upgrade that's going to modernize it, and they're not going to need a World of Warcraft 2.
[SPEAKER_11]: I just don't see Blizzard trying to make that happen because it doesn't always happen so well for other MMOs.
[SPEAKER_11]: But...
[SPEAKER_11]: Then again, Guild Wars and Guild Wars 2 coexisting fine.
[SPEAKER_11]: Final Fantasy XI, Final Fantasy XIV Reborn, too soon to tell, but looks promising.
[SPEAKER_03]: Final Fantasy XIV, sorry, pretty.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, no, I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Cannot wait.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, that's the importance of technology.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, anyhow, one more story and then release dates.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, in other news, and God, what a disgusting ad on this page.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, who remembers the rumor, the big urban legend, about a bajillion Atari 2600 ET cartridges being buried?
[SPEAKER_11]: I've definitely heard that.
[SPEAKER_11]: But they were melted down before they were buried.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's what I heard.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think that's important to know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, there is an Ontario-based production company called Fuel that has signed a deal with the... Basically, it's a town in New Mexico.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to ruin this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alamogordo?
[SPEAKER_11]: Alamogordo.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alamogordo, thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: were the landfill that supposedly not just E3 cartridges, but a ton of Atari prototypes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Prototype games, prototype systems, anything that was in development that they ended up not releasing going into this dump.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the city has given this production company permission to go digging through the dump.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're going huge dumpster diving in a landfill.
[SPEAKER_11]: This is digging up a dead body to see what the real cause of death was.
[SPEAKER_11]: This is what this is.
[SPEAKER_11]: To do a DNA test.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, and you know that there are people who have, I'm saying escaped with prototypes, just in jest, but you find a lot of 5200 prototypes online for sale, where people have gotten legit ROM dumps and reconstituted them for sale.
[SPEAKER_03]: Our copy of Millipede for 5200 was a prototype.
[SPEAKER_11]: But they crushed these.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, I'd always heard they melted them down, but crushed makes a lot more sense.
[SPEAKER_11]: You put them in the trash compactor and they crush down.
[SPEAKER_11]: They did that so that looters wouldn't dig them up and try to sell them.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, I mean, but then what's the point?
[SPEAKER_11]: You're going to dig up literally garbage that doesn't work.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's 25 years old.
[SPEAKER_11]: Those things, if a board is sitting outside a case that long, it's not going to work.
[SPEAKER_03]: But if a memory chip happens to have been compressed within... Good luck.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know, but the whole thing is that...
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a chance that exists.
[SPEAKER_03]: And people who especially big video game history buffs, Atari fans, they're going to drop the opportunity to see if there is anything salvageable.
[SPEAKER_11]: Dungeon Buster in our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com says, I hope that doesn't turn into another Capone's vault.
[SPEAKER_11]: Will Geraldo Rivera be there when they unearth the big massive ET cartridges?
[SPEAKER_11]: Will he be there live?
[SPEAKER_03]: Does he have a career still?
[SPEAKER_11]: No?
[SPEAKER_11]: So yes, he will be.
[SPEAKER_03]: Didn't the angry video game nerd, like that was like the basis of his movie, was going to the dump to find if the game exists?
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't even know.
[SPEAKER_11]: I never saw it.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, if we're done with the Atari story, I want to go back real quick to the Titan thing because Technus in our chat room at live.vognetwork.com made a very good point about this.
[SPEAKER_11]: I want to throw this out there.
[SPEAKER_11]: Technus says, I would speculate that Bungie beat them to the punch with Destiny and they needed to reset after Activision picked up Bungie.
[SPEAKER_11]: that's a really good theory because again rumors and whisperings and you know who knows how much we can lend to this but I did hear that Titan was quite a bit like what Destiny sounds like it's going to be that it was less of a shooter per se but that a lot of the same stuff they're talking about implementing with Destiny was supposed to be the types of stuff they were doing with Titan too you know take with a gigantic grain of salt take with an entire can of salt actually take with all the salt in the ocean salt lick salt lick
[SPEAKER_11]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have to quote Queen Semia in chat.
[SPEAKER_03]: They find Hoffa under the pile.
[SPEAKER_03]: Plot twist.
[SPEAKER_11]: Masked Bishop with some strong opinions on Realm Reborn.
[SPEAKER_11]: By the way, Final Fantasy XIV Realm Reborn will succeed.
[SPEAKER_11]: If you think Square Enix will let the Final Fantasy franchise fail, you're sadly mistaken.
[SPEAKER_11]: Final Fantasy XIV Realm Reborn will be the next game changer.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'll say this much.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's impressive that they...
[SPEAKER_11]: The second half of what he said at least is true because Square Enix put a lot of money to basically redo the fucking game from scratch.
[SPEAKER_03]: and you can see it.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can really tell.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's going to be interesting.
[SPEAKER_11]: Free to play Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_07]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_11]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wouldn't that be something?
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's check out some games that will be coming out a little bit sooner than Final Fantasy XV or whatever else we're thinking about here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Release dates.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: So this week we've got PlayStation 3 or on PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_07]: Remember me?
[SPEAKER_07]: Coming out from Capcom.
[SPEAKER_07]: Receiving kind of mixed reviews but whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: Animal Crossing on the 3DS or Animal Crossing New Leaf on the 3DS because there's one single new leaf in the game and the rest is all the same as the last one.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Skyrim Elder Scrolls V Skyrim Legendary Edition cover re-released the game with the DLC on PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, and PC.
[SPEAKER_07]: and at long last if you don't have the internet and you want to play Minecraft Minecraft on the Xbox 360 the Xbox 360 version is coming out as a disc version that might be a good one for the Xbox 360 in the kids room that's not hooked up to the internet I could see that being a plus because Minecraft's a pretty friendly kids game it is an awesome game so there's that and that's pretty much it this week
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, coming out in Japan on the PlayStation 3, Gal Gun gets a price reduction into the best series.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ha ha, yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: And there's another game called Narawatera Gakuen...
[SPEAKER_11]: Geki Joban Anime, and Complete Setting Book Hybrid Disc.
[SPEAKER_11]: So I think this is actually the anime and a game based on the anime all on one disc.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because you see this happening more and more in Japan where you get the bundled Blu-ray that has a game and a movie or at least two separate Blu-rays or whatever in a bundled collection.
[SPEAKER_11]: On the Xbox 360, Halo Origin Pack this week in Japan for all you Halo fans in origin.
[SPEAKER_11]: Also, Minecraft Xbox 360 Edition, the standalone game, is out in Japan as well.
[SPEAKER_11]: And a new Camouflage 360 wireless controller in Japan.
[SPEAKER_11]: I guess this is to go with the Halo Origin Pack.
[SPEAKER_11]: Which, by the way, quickly while it's on my mind, do you think Microsoft at E3 is going to have anything to kind of throw something at Japan to try and make it work there?
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't think they're going to try.
[SPEAKER_11]: Really?
[SPEAKER_11]: I thought I read somewhere that they did say they are committed to Japan, but that could have just been smoke up my ass.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's smoke up their ass.
[SPEAKER_03]: They'll release a game with a pillow and a clock.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think the market's so small there now.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're just more focused on the larger market.
[SPEAKER_11]: Microsoft's market is small, but certainly handhelds is really what it seems to be about.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Nothing of note on the PlayStation Vita this week.
[SPEAKER_11]: Looking at... Oh, I already did Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_11]: Way to go.
[SPEAKER_11]: Seeing if there's anything on the Wii U. Actually, yes.
[SPEAKER_11]: Rabbids Land is supposed to be out in Japan this week.
[SPEAKER_11]: The game that got delayed here is supposedly coming out in Japan.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, Rabbids Land was a launch title for the Wii U. Oh, I'm thinking of the other Rabbids game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, you're thinking of Rayman Legends.
[SPEAKER_11]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_11]: On the 3DS in Japan this week...
[SPEAKER_11]: Nothing of note.
[SPEAKER_11]: On the PSP this week, God Eater Burst gets a price reduction.
[SPEAKER_11]: So lots of price reductions this week, but really not a lot of new games until we get to about June 20th.
[SPEAKER_11]: Seems to be when the next batch of big games comes out.
[SPEAKER_11]: Really nothing to say on Nintendo 3DS either.
[SPEAKER_11]: Japan gets Donkey Kong Returns 3D next week on the 13th and a Metallic Red DS to go with that.
[SPEAKER_11]: I did pick up Donkey Kong Country Returns, by the way, for my DS.
[SPEAKER_11]: I haven't really played enough of it yet to review it, though.
[SPEAKER_11]: On my plane ride this week, I plan to play some more of it, so I'll let you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did I tell you we might finally be getting three DSs?
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because there's going to be a new massive... I know Apollo Justice is in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm trying to remember.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, Phoenix Wright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Phoenix Wright, thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: A new game coming out and Fire Emblem.
[SPEAKER_03]: and then I've won Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, how about the UK?
[SPEAKER_11]: What's coming out over there?
[SPEAKER_03]: Some stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: On the 3rd we have Gunpoint for PC and Scrolls for PC and Mac and on 7th we have Remember Me PC, Xbox 360, PS3 and that would be it.
[SPEAKER_11]: To register participation for this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio at vognetwork.com use the passphrase OVEN
[SPEAKER_11]: Just a couple more stories for you guys, and then the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_07]: But first, Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, this is kind of, I guess, the best news that could come out of the situation, because we know that this is only alluding to worse things to come on the next-gen consoles, but EA is eliminating... They already went ahead and said that they're not going to have the online pass in any future games, and now they're going back and retroactively taking away the online pass...
[SPEAKER_07]: from all the old games as well so the online pass now is free so if you want to you know play a used EA game that had the online pass you buy the game and then you activate the online pass for free so that's nice
[SPEAKER_11]: There's just something about this.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know what it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: As we discontinue online paths for our new EA titles, we're also in the process of eliminating it from our existing EA titles.
[SPEAKER_07]: We heard the feedback from players and decided to do away with the online paths altogether.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't trust them.
[SPEAKER_07]: I totally believe that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, what we're doing is wrong.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know what it is I don't know what it is and maybe I am just being a jerk but it's like one of those things where it's like are you sure that when you download the free thing it doesn't say but you are giving us your soul like are you sure there's nothing in there like that I just worry I'm sorry but I know better it's just it's so much bullshit I just don't believe any of that crap I roll my eyes
[SPEAKER_07]: We've made too much money, America and the world.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're just going to stop making extra money now because we have all the money that we need to run those servers now.
[SPEAKER_07]: So we don't need any of your online passes anymore because servers all of a sudden got cheaper to run.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is a company that makes money.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're not going to say, hey, we hate money all of a sudden.
[SPEAKER_11]: Right.
[SPEAKER_11]: No.
[SPEAKER_11]: There's just something I don't trust.
[SPEAKER_11]: Call me a conspiracy theorist.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or maybe if I take this as an actual legit sign, maybe it's them trying to get away from the business tactics of the former CEO.
[SPEAKER_11]: Now you're being nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've decided to play Angel's Advocate.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or it could be in-game purchases in Dead Space 3 in future games.
[SPEAKER_03]: But if I want to put it at a non-conspiracy theory point of view, even though I trust...
[SPEAKER_11]: EA as far as I can pick up the entire building and nudge it maybe it is trying to separate themselves from former business practice or it's trying to get people to install Origin which I will not fucking do no TigerClaw with a theory in chat at live.vognetwork.com says EA removes the online pass so people can play the used games online and then a few months later EA shuts down the online servers to those games
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, that is kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_07]: But here's the thing with some of these games.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're not online games.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was the thing that was kind of the funny part about the online pass.
[SPEAKER_07]: Remember like Dragon Age Origins, Dragon Age 2.
[SPEAKER_11]: Mass Effect 2 had that Cerberus pass and it wasn't really, you didn't play online.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was DLC.
[SPEAKER_03]: My hope is that with all of this that it means I won't have to fucking be online for my DLC in Mass Effect 3 to load because I paid for a lot of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, I'm a consumer whore.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_11]: And how?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, mister, I'm gonna buy Mass Effect 3 Trilogy and own it on Xbox and PC.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: You're worse than me, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, well, okay, maybe I play more than you do.
[SPEAKER_11]: I play other games too, though.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're seriously like my dealer, you and Shane I blame you for everything that happens in my life Shane's worse though, come on Shane is worse Shane is far worse And I haven't started on Persona, so There you go, don't resist I will resist, my will is strong My will is titanium By the way, there's now music from Persona 4 in rotation at vognetwork.com I just put some in today You know what, I actually kind of I'm playing too much shit already
[SPEAKER_11]: Going to one more story here.
[SPEAKER_11]: This actually came up last week, but it's too good for us to skip completely on our show.
[SPEAKER_11]: We've got to mention it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Actually, maybe it... When did this finish?
[SPEAKER_11]: I think it finished on Saturday or Sunday of last week.
[SPEAKER_11]: But anyhow, here's the deal.
[SPEAKER_11]: So did you guys ever check out the iPhone and Android game Curiosity?
[SPEAKER_11]: What's in the cube?
[SPEAKER_11]: It's Peter Molyneux's Dick in a Box.
[SPEAKER_11]: Remember this game where you tap the little keyboard?
[SPEAKER_03]: If this was last week, this was me not having much in the way of internet access except for Tumblr.
[SPEAKER_11]: Finally, what was in the box was revealed.
[SPEAKER_11]: Some dude opened the box.
[SPEAKER_11]: You win nothing!
[SPEAKER_11]: You're so stupid!
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, here's what's amazing.
[SPEAKER_11]: The guy who won is an 18-year-old guy, Brian Henderson.
[SPEAKER_11]: He lives in Edinburgh, and he won.
[SPEAKER_11]: And the great thing about it, he ended up tweeting or saying in an interview, I don't remember where it was, but he said, yeah, I just downloaded the game an hour before I won it.
[SPEAKER_11]: So what was in the goddamn cube?
[SPEAKER_07]: See, I would have played to the very end too if I had remembered that it was ending, but I just like, I don't fucking care.
[SPEAKER_11]: Here's, guess what was in the goddamn cube?
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm sure many of you have heard, but here's what was in the cube.
[SPEAKER_11]: You, again, now 22cans is, they did Curiosity.
[SPEAKER_11]: Their next project is like a populist reimagining called Goddess.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, Brian will be the god in Goddess.
[SPEAKER_11]: at the Stardust.
[SPEAKER_11]: No.
[SPEAKER_11]: But he will be in... You don't know shit.
[SPEAKER_11]: I can't believe this.
[SPEAKER_11]: Some new kid from the street won this.
[SPEAKER_11]: You don't know shit.
[SPEAKER_11]: You are a whore, darling.
[SPEAKER_03]: A show where we can fall into showgirls quotes is a good show.
[SPEAKER_11]: That game is called Goddess and it just makes me think of showgirls.
[SPEAKER_00]: Sorry, Nomi Malone.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Nomi Malone from Edinburgh.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm sorry to this kid.
[SPEAKER_11]: This poor kid didn't ask for this, so I'm very sorry.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I'm going to make the joke anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm doing the hand flashies in my head.
[SPEAKER_11]: Nomi Malone from Edinburgh.
[SPEAKER_11]: Open the cube and we'll get to be the god and goddess.
[SPEAKER_11]: and apparently not only will he be the god but he will have a hand in creating the rules that will govern the game so it's his rules or get out and Brian gets to share in the revenue generated by goddess but they're saying in one year he could be pushed down a flight of stairs or slip on ice and a new goddess could emerge here's the thing
[SPEAKER_11]: When did this whole thing, this cube thing launch?
[SPEAKER_11]: Like what, seven months ago, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: Didn't Goddess get kickstarted midway through this project?
[SPEAKER_03]: Kickstarted?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, that's my new verb.
[SPEAKER_11]: Didn't it get kickstarted?
[SPEAKER_03]: Where would it be kickstarted?
[SPEAKER_11]: Kickstarted.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because the website is Kickstarter.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: Not Kickstart.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Are you going to kickstart my heart?
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_11]: So Goddess got kickstarted halfway through the run of Cube.
[SPEAKER_11]: What if it hadn't gone through?
[SPEAKER_11]: Then what would have been in the Cube?
[SPEAKER_11]: I got you.
[SPEAKER_11]: No.
[SPEAKER_11]: You are making this shit up as you go along, Peter Molyneux.
[SPEAKER_07]: I got you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Was it Schreudner's box or whatever?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's basically... There's a dead cat who's not dead.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, so it's Goddess, but not Goddess.
[SPEAKER_07]: We won't know because it was Goddess in the box and not Goddess dead having eaten the poison.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what it would have been?
[SPEAKER_07]: It would have been a dog.
[SPEAKER_07]: He would have adopted a dog for you.
[SPEAKER_07]: It would have been life-changing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or, guess what?
[SPEAKER_07]: I've got this boy named Milo and you're going to adopt him.
[SPEAKER_07]: Having kids is going to change your life.
[SPEAKER_07]: Milo will change your life.
[SPEAKER_03]: Milo needs his diaper changed every five seconds and you'll want to die.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, well we reached out to Peter Molyneux for comment on Goddess and this is what he had to say.
[SPEAKER_05]: Must be weird not having anybody come on you.
[SPEAKER_11]: What does that even mean?
[SPEAKER_02]: What does that even mean?
[SPEAKER_07]: That was a quote from Showgirls.
[SPEAKER_07]: Get it?
[SPEAKER_07]: I will give you the best Fable game ever made.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's Fable the Journey.
[SPEAKER_07]: It uses Kinect.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's fantastic.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not on Rails.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh shit, alright, let's go to- Hey, I'll tell you what, you know what would have been inside the box if perhaps Peter Molyneux wasn't backing this and it was the Steam box?
[SPEAKER_07]: Hats!
[SPEAKER_07]: Would have been fucking hats.
[SPEAKER_07]: Lots of hats.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hats, hats, hats.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's travel back- Do they have like a gif?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's funny that we both grunted at him at the same time.
[SPEAKER_11]: Near?
[SPEAKER_11]: Far!
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's travel back to a time when gaming was so much simpler.
[SPEAKER_11]: When you know what?
[SPEAKER_11]: Elizabeth Berkley was Jessie Spano and you hadn't seen her boobies yet.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's a much simpler time.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, what is the classic game of the week?
[SPEAKER_03]: Sonic R.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, it is Sonic R. I have finally decided to do fucking Sonic R. So, Sonic R was done by Traveler's Tales and Sonic Team, and it came out on the Sega Saturn and Windows.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was out for Windows, which actually, if you've got a decent graphics card, the Windows version actually looks a lot better and plays better.
[SPEAKER_03]: It came out in the US on October 31st, 1997, and then later it came out in Europe, Australia, and Japan all at the same time, and was re-released for PlayStation 2 and the GameCube as part of the Sonic Gems Collection.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is basically the last of the two, I'm sorry, the third Sonic racing game, and the last of two games that was done by Traveler's Tales and Sonic Team.
[SPEAKER_03]: So basically, it's a huge foot race.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what the game is.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's single or multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can race.
[SPEAKER_03]: You have ten different Sonic characters.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you can pick up, like, you have to collect rings on the way to open up different parts of the racetrack.
[SPEAKER_03]: You also can get, like, different shields, like what's in Sonic 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, you can actually get a lightning shield that attracts rings to you.
[SPEAKER_03]: and you have different areas that are sort of based off of various places in the different Sonic games like you have a place that looks like the Green Hill Zone a place that looks like the Chemical Plant you have those item panels like I was talking about that give you different abilities as you go like you can run on water or attract rings and then you get Sonic Tokens and Chaos Emeralds and the Chaos Emeralds help you unlock secret characters
[SPEAKER_03]: You also have different kinds of weather.
[SPEAKER_03]: You have clear, you have rain, you have snow.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the snow does make the water free so you can run over it instead of being slowed down by it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you have a time attack mode to see basically who has the fastest time.
[SPEAKER_03]: So the characters in this one is you are, let's see, you have Sonic and he has double jump.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's also the fastest.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tails actually has the ability to fly.
[SPEAKER_03]: Knuckles can glide.
[SPEAKER_03]: and then you have Amy Rose who actually drives a car and she can hover over water and gets extra speed boost for your secret characters you have Robotnik also known as Eggman he has a hovercraft and can resist terrain you have Metal Sonic you have a Tails doll and you have Metal Knuckles you have Egg Robo and Super Sonic so basically when you have all the Chaos Emeralds you can play as Super Sonic and you just sort of float over everything
[SPEAKER_03]: The game actually came out after Sonic 3D Blast when Sega was working with Traveler's Tales on a different Sonic game.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they'd also been working on a 3D graphics engine that they didn't really have anything for, so they decided to work with Sonic Team to make the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pretty much just everything that came together.
[SPEAKER_03]: So there's actually even a Sonic R that came out on the Tiger handheld system.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, like I said, there was the Sega Saturn version that actually had some really bad problems with draw distance and clipping.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the PC version let you use better rendering and 3D acceleration, and you could adjust the draw distance.
[SPEAKER_03]: So basically, like today, you could have no draw distance at all in the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It would be gorgeous.
[SPEAKER_03]: The music was done by Richard Jacques of Sega Europe, who also did the music for Sonic 3D Blast.
[SPEAKER_03]: And he basically worked with Yuji Naka to basically design the musical feel of the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's where we got the Super Sonic Racing.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then the singer in this one, now this I didn't know, her name is TJ Davis, and she did all of the singing in it at Yuji Naka's request.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, basically, it was done by a London studio.
[SPEAKER_03]: The music came out of London.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's a fun game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's sort of, you know, not like the world's best Sonic game, but it's a really fun game.
[SPEAKER_03]: And from that, we also got the two games, well, there were two games that came out before Sonic R. There was Sonic Drift and Sonic Drift 2 for Game Gear.
[SPEAKER_03]: and then after that we've gotten Sonic Riders, we've gotten Sonic Riders Zero Gravity, Sonic Free Riders, Sonic and Sega All-Stars Racing and the Transformed version as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Those are all pretty much born out of the Sonic R franchise.
[SPEAKER_03]: and, of course, the music is, you know, pretty much the big iconic thing about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not the most gorgeous game, but it's super fun, like we said.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, we say a system is only as good as the games that are on it, but the games are also, can be absolutely amazing without having to look, you know, absolutely gorgeous.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_03]: And this is one of those that falls into that category.
[SPEAKER_03]: So my game of the week is Sonic R.
[SPEAKER_11]: This is one of those games that to me just made sense.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like Sonic in a racing game.
[SPEAKER_11]: Why did it take so long?
[SPEAKER_03]: Kinda right.
[SPEAKER_11]: And it did have some good music.
[SPEAKER_03]: Super Sonic Racing was in Sonic R, Tiger Call.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: There it is, your classic game of the week, Sonic R. Good pick.
[SPEAKER_11]: Have you done every single Sonic game yet?
[SPEAKER_11]: You gotta be getting close.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've done a few of them.
[SPEAKER_03]: But keep in mind, there's a bunch of crap out there in the Sonic franchise.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I would get Sonic herpes or something.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're going to take a break.
[SPEAKER_11]: And when we come back, there is still more news to come in the Fugo Question of the Week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, and to tell what up, G, same music in Japan, all out of the London studio.
[SPEAKER_11]: So there's none of this whole No, there's not.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, just making sure.
[SPEAKER_11]: Good, at least we can all agree on something.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, plenty more to come when Orange Launch Radio returns with this episode number 506, Second Mix J Append, Part B, right after this.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hola, this is your friendly neighborhood Mexican, Actdeft, and you're participating with Orange Nouns Radio, the show where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I want to use my voice to tell you that Kirby does not suck.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, literally he does suck, but not figuratively.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyways, play more Kirby!
[SPEAKER_11]: That's right, play more Kirby.
[SPEAKER_11]: They have that whole Wii U virtual console thing going on right now.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was tempted to get the Kirby's Dream Course that they had on Super Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was like the miniature golf game.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_11]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_11]: You too can leave a bumper.
[SPEAKER_11]: Go to vognetwork.com and check out the forums for Orange Lounge Radio and more information on there.
[SPEAKER_11]: If you want to use your voice to tell the gaming world something, maybe you want them to play less Kirby.
[SPEAKER_11]: You could tell us that in a future bumper.
[SPEAKER_11]: That was the last one that I had in the queue, by the way.
[SPEAKER_11]: So you're going to start hearing repeats if I don't get any new ones for the next show.
[SPEAKER_11]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's my little threat.
[SPEAKER_11]: During the break tonight, before we get into rapid fire news, I noticed some of the chatters were talking about Civ V, and I don't know how this got brought up, but apparently the Mass Effect mods for Civ V I thought I mentioned this on the show before Yes, they exist, and they're awesome Fun fact, you once said that about Mass Effect I have never liked that type of game
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't even, I mean, I admit that, shit, what game is it I'm thinking of now?
[SPEAKER_03]: Pop, not Populous.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I didn't like Populous either, but... SimCity?
[SPEAKER_11]: Are we?
[SPEAKER_11]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, I thought I hit all the buttons.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what, I just happened to look over and saw that we were muted, so all of this conversation that's happening...
[SPEAKER_11]: Professional radio folks.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: Rob was giving me crap for not wanting to play Civ even though there's a Mass Effect mod.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I was telling him how I did not like Civ.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't like SimCity.
[SPEAKER_03]: I do not like SimCoaster.
[SPEAKER_03]: Although I do like watching the coasters that people have made on SimCoaster.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't like SimPark.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like the Sims, but really I like building houses and dressing them up and murdering them.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't like SimAnt either.
[SPEAKER_11]: Actraiser
[SPEAKER_11]: Two things about Actraiser.
[SPEAKER_11]: A, the soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_11]: B, when that angel flies around, you can see his butt.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was butt.
[SPEAKER_11]: And this is how Rob first learned.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, it was butt on the Super Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_11]: So it made you giggle a little bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_11]: It was butt.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_11]: Butt.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's what.
[SPEAKER_03]: From now on, instead of chicken butt, it's angel butt.
[SPEAKER_03]: Guess what?
[SPEAKER_03]: Angel butt.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's go around and talk about rapidly what's happening in the world of gaming.
[SPEAKER_11]: Some quick stories.
[SPEAKER_11]: Rapid Fire News.
[SPEAKER_07]: This may be a bit of a spoiler, but...
[SPEAKER_07]: We think maybe Mirror's Edge 2 might be coming to the Xbox One.
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently there was first off a listing on the German and Italian storefronts for Amazon.
[SPEAKER_07]: And those are removed.
[SPEAKER_07]: Listing it was for the Xbox One and
[SPEAKER_07]: and then on EA's own website in the help section their help center had a page for Mirror's Edge 2 and now it's gone so makes me think that maybe that's going to be one of the announcements perhaps
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, please.
[SPEAKER_07]: Last but not least, El Shaddai.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know if you guys remember that game.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's kind of an artsy action game from Ignition.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, now the rights have been transferred to the creator.
[SPEAKER_07]: El Shaddai is now back in the creator's portfolio as far as the rights go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe that means it's going to open up an opportunity for more games.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what's making me cry right now?
[SPEAKER_03]: Every time anyone talks about that game, I hear Amy Grant.
[SPEAKER_02]: Baby, baby.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, no, no, because when she was heavy into her Christian singing mode, she did a song called El Shaddai.
[SPEAKER_11]: Keep in mind, I was raised Baptist.
[SPEAKER_11]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: The references on this show are getting more and more obscure.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, well, the full title was El Shaddai, the Ascension of the Metatron.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did she do a song called Metatron?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, but I just finished watching the season of Supernatural and there was Metatron in it Lordy So, let's see Metatron Yeah
[SPEAKER_03]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, sorry, Brad, I adore you to death.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was a decent song, but her Hebrew was awful.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm shocked that so many people know that Amy Grant song.
[SPEAKER_11]: I only remember, baby, baby, something, something lyrics.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, there's one song that she did that I really like, and that was the duet she did with Vince Gill, who she married.
[SPEAKER_11]: Just saying Whatever happened to her?
[SPEAKER_03]: She's still recording and still married to Vince Gill She's still recording?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I actually, believe it or not, the only site I could get working was Wikipedia And I was reading up about, actually Vince Gill, but it linked to Amy Grant, so I was like Isn't that amazing how on Wikipedia you could just She married him She's married to Vince Gill I believe you
[SPEAKER_03]: Mama's watching that Oklahoma relief thing and Vince Gill was on it, so we looked up Vince Gill and it led to Amy Grant.
[SPEAKER_03]: She's back to doing super Christian stuff and singing with Vince.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jamie, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_03]: For the record, she does have a gorgeous voice.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey!
[SPEAKER_03]: I remember I got...
[SPEAKER_07]: I remember I got dragged to an Amy Grant concert at the State Fair.
[SPEAKER_07]: I got dragged to one of those, and it was just not fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did you sing along?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I didn't.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not a fan of Amy Grant.
[SPEAKER_07]: I recognize that song, but I don't know any of her other songs.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know the only concert I've been taken to at a fair against my will was Michael Damien.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think literally that is the only concert I have seen at the State Fair is the Amy Grant one.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I don't remember who opened it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was another Christian artist.
[SPEAKER_03]: You haven't been to Sea Weird Al?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I sadly haven't.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's coming this year.
[SPEAKER_03]: I see Weird Al.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a hundred and some degrees outside.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't go outside for anybody.
[SPEAKER_07]: He can come to my house.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jamie, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_03]: I went to Fresno to see Weird Al, so...
[SPEAKER_11]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_11]: Hotline Miami, and Proteus.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm going to get this just because I like indie games and I've pretty much gotten every other indie bundle.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's already got it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Did you?
[SPEAKER_11]: Have you checked out any of the games yet?
[SPEAKER_11]: They'll just sit there in my Steam library.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have now in my Steam library 126 games.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that's not all of them because I haven't bothered to put all of the Sonic the Hedgehog games in.
[SPEAKER_07]: I only because I bought the Sonic collection with every single Sonic the Hedgehog game that's on PC and I only put in Sonic and Sega All-Stars Racing and Sonic Generations.
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't bother to put the rest of the ones.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sonic Generations is a damn good game.
[SPEAKER_11]: They also have, well you saw, I don't know if you saw They have a mod that actually, it's Sonic It converts it to the other Sonic 3D game that they had I don't remember I see TigerClaw in the chatroom saying Hotline Miami has a good soundtrack And the good news is you will also be able to get the soundtracks with these games DRM free downloads, Steam keys, Windows, Mac, and Linux versions For the record, for the record Whatever games that I don't keep out of this I'm more than happy to share with some of our listeners
[SPEAKER_07]: And, and, and, I should mention that they also have a humble weekly bundle that's going on right now that's all the Telltale series.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh yeah, I saw that too.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which I also bought.
[SPEAKER_11]: Those are some great deals right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Walking Dead, Sam & Max.
[SPEAKER_11]: Walking Dead alone is worth it if you don't already have it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, if you pay more than average, it's Walking Dead.
[SPEAKER_07]: You get Sam & Max.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also great.
[SPEAKER_07]: Back to the Future.
[SPEAKER_07]: Great.
[SPEAKER_07]: Puzzle Agent, which I've never played, Waltzing Gromit, Poker Night, The Inventory, and... That's a lot.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jurassic Park?
[SPEAKER_07]: No Jurassic Park.
[SPEAKER_07]: Probably because of licensing.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_11]: So look at stupid kids ruining everybody's fun.
[SPEAKER_11]: Stop DDOSing MMOs and kicking everybody off.
[SPEAKER_11]: This is trying to have a good time.
[SPEAKER_11]: By the way, speaking of DDOS attacks, Bobby asked me to relay the following along.
[SPEAKER_11]: Should we lose the stream at some point during the show tonight, don't hit F5 to refresh the entire page.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because when you all do it at once, it's like a little mini DDOS attack.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because we're not on the servers as big as EVE Online or Dust514.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're running off a tin can that has some...
[SPEAKER_11]: Pause, unpause.
[SPEAKER_11]: And that will not do a DDoS attack on our little website.
[SPEAKER_11]: If you are a Vita owner, you'll be excited to know that Flower is coming to the Vita.
[SPEAKER_11]: This is awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: I love Flower.
[SPEAKER_11]: I played it on the PlayStation 3, but I would say it's the best racing game I've played in a long time.
[SPEAKER_11]: Even though you would not think of Flower as a racing game.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's really great.
[SPEAKER_11]: Flower is going to be on the Vita.
[SPEAKER_11]: It will be one of the IndieCade games coming to E3.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Hold on, I'm saying that I only care about R-Type.
[SPEAKER_11]: What, in the chat room?
[SPEAKER_03]: Talking about Irem games.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, okay, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because R-Type is freaking great.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, tell me that R-Type does not have the best first stage music of almost any game ever.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you said it doesn't, then you're lying.
[SPEAKER_03]: So...
[SPEAKER_03]: You Don't Know Jack is going to be on OUYA on June 11th and the Jackpad app will make your phone a controller.
[SPEAKER_03]: So folks who have OUYA's and an Android phone or an iOS will get to have a controller out of their phone.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_03]: Aren't you special?
[SPEAKER_03]: Square Enix registered Final Fantasy Agito.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which is something that we heard at E3, what, five years ago?
[SPEAKER_03]: Six years ago?
[SPEAKER_03]: Eventually?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because they were supposed to do Final Fantasy Agito 13.
[SPEAKER_03]: So now they've got Final Fantasy Agito.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hooray.
[SPEAKER_07]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Perfect question for Bobby Blackwolf.
[SPEAKER_07]: So where's Versus 13?
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, a question for the screeners?
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: Either that's going to be answered once E3 starts.
[SPEAKER_11]: I kind of think it's a game that has to show up in one way or another.
[SPEAKER_11]: Whether it's true that they moved it to 15 or what, I kind of think you'll have something on that well before the show starts.
[SPEAKER_11]: But let's say they do announce Final Fantasy Versus XIII and you want to know, is lightning in it?
[SPEAKER_11]: Or something that they don't say.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: You could go ask that question.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_03]: It's getting a Steam release date.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to be out today already.
[SPEAKER_03]: July 2nd.
[SPEAKER_03]: As announced by developer Two Tribes.
[SPEAKER_03]: And in the PC version is a Steam workshop integration and achievements.
[SPEAKER_03]: So there's also a level editor that was promised for Wii U and well, they don't have that yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Gee!
[SPEAKER_03]: Nintendo and online?
[SPEAKER_11]: It's coming soon, trademark patent pending.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what else is coming soon?
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey, you know what, though?
[SPEAKER_11]: At this point, if the Xbox One Connect is going to watch me poop, then, like, give me the Wii U and its outdated technology, all right?
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just going to go home and hook up the Turbo Duo and play me some freaking Dracula X and not worry about my system watching me in my pajamas.
[SPEAKER_03]: The end.
[SPEAKER_11]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_03]: The Connect did while it was watching you poop.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, seriously guys, I don't have my theme music.
[SPEAKER_11]: Help me fill time.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, not by singing.
[SPEAKER_03]: You don't want to hear me sing anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want that game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Go to Square Enix and tell them to give it to me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tell them to give me the zero.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Can't you just import it?
[SPEAKER_03]: So what exactly is the downside for... I don't think I can read it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not voting on Steam Greenlight titles.
[SPEAKER_07]: I never understood that.
[SPEAKER_07]: You don't get your little mini-achievement?
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyhow, I would love to answer Loki's question, but I found music.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, anyhow, although I'm not going to get into all the details on Final Fantasy IX because it sounds complicated, this had us thinking about rediscovering things in classic games.
[SPEAKER_11]: Have you ever revisited an old game years after its release to find something new?
[SPEAKER_11]: Go back and complete it at 100%?
[SPEAKER_11]: What classic game did you revisit after many years, not necessarily to play it for the first time, but to try and discover new things inside it?
[SPEAKER_11]: DRAGON BOSS GRAPPLING BEAM
[SPEAKER_11]: Pretty neat stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: I guess it's common knowledge to many, but I had no idea.
[SPEAKER_11]: And he linked us a little YouTube.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, there's a lot of ways you can kind of trick that game.
[SPEAKER_11]: You can do like wall jumps and get past places you're not supposed to.
[SPEAKER_11]: There's lots of little ways you can kind of like trick it and beat the system.
[SPEAKER_11]: So that's one of the really cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's what makes part of what makes Super Metroid the best ever.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, that's where you could get to the top of the castle by doing the double jump and get your final star in Super Mario 64.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyway, Tiara responds and says, I've actually been replaying Final Fantasy IX for the past several weeks and I never knew about this side quest until I stumbled upon the info while looking for Chocobo hot and cold treasure locations.
[SPEAKER_11]: You're going to be one of the first to see it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sorry for the Facebook noise, but I'm actually on Facebook trying to read these answers.
[SPEAKER_11]: Trust me when I say it is harder than the first quest.
[SPEAKER_11]: Really?
[SPEAKER_11]: That is true.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, a lot of people go back and beat retro games.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is harder than the first quest.
[SPEAKER_03]: And for the record, for anyone who wants to do it without beating the game first, just type in Zelda for your name.
[SPEAKER_11]: That is true.
[SPEAKER_11]: Zelda's another one of those games where you don't have to have every item.
[SPEAKER_11]: You can get around some of this stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like, you could get through the whole game with a wooden sword, I think.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't forget to walk headfirst into walls because you never know which one's invisible.
[SPEAKER_11]: You never know.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_11]: Andy R. replied and said, I replayed Okami earlier this year thanks to the HDification version and I found a lot of things I didn't find the first time.
[SPEAKER_11]: Things such as the hidden spider bosses or some of the advanced forms of the brush techniques.
[SPEAKER_11]: Also, knowing what happens in the story before I started made me more cognizant of the foreshadowing I missed the first time I played the game, which was kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: Mary B. replied with another Final Fantasy answer.
[SPEAKER_11]: Final Fantasy VIII learned how to crazy attack with Squall's two-hour, whatever it was, and that it was stronger than his summit.
[SPEAKER_11]: Did they have two-hour abilities in Final Fantasy VIII, or was that your Final Fantasy XI addiction talking?
[SPEAKER_11]: after getting stuck on Bahamut.
[SPEAKER_11]: I had to come back to a save down to Bahamut after not playing for months.
[SPEAKER_11]: Final Fantasy X and X-2 just for fun because I like them so much.
[SPEAKER_11]: Use strategy guide to get 100% though.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ragenator said, well, at least prior to my PS3 being stolen, I regularly went back and played older classics.
[SPEAKER_11]: The closest thing to discovering something new was in terms of tactics for situations where I got stuck in the past.
[SPEAKER_11]: GameFAQs
[SPEAKER_11]: I knew fatalities, not sure all, were possible without the blood code, so I tried it out with Kano.
[SPEAKER_11]: To my surprise, Kano managed to do his finishing move.
[SPEAKER_11]: However, instead of a heart, he pulled out an organ that was dark colored.
[SPEAKER_11]: I can only assume that he pulled out his opponent's liver.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's an evil thing and must be destroyed.
[SPEAKER_11]: Even with no blood code, Mortal Kombat surprised me with the amount of gore it was still able to show on the consoles.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, going over to Google Plus and some of the answers there.
[SPEAKER_11]: Were there no answers on Google Plus?
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, no, there's two, sorry.
[SPEAKER_11]: Google Plus changed and now I can't find things.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, Red Entertainment says, I remember me and my best friend as a kid trying and failing to beat Mega Man 2 on the NES.
[SPEAKER_11]: No matter how many different times or many different ways we tried to beat the game, we could never get past one particular part in Dr. Wily's Fortress at the end.
[SPEAKER_11]: It wasn't until I was older...
[SPEAKER_11]: Bought the Mega Man Collection on PS2 and had access to online walkthroughs that I finally got the item you needed in order to proceed past that one particular part.
[SPEAKER_11]: When I finally beat that game, it felt like I was giving my eight-year-old self a figurative high-five.
[SPEAKER_11]: Not a literal high-five because that would break the space-time continuum.
[SPEAKER_11]: and lastly Travis H on Google Plus says I found myself overjoyed with the amount of PS1 and PSP games I can replay on my Vita.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm right now in the middle of playing Wild Arms trying to complete it to its fullest and find things that I missed the first time around.
[SPEAKER_11]: It is very refreshing to go back in an older age and enjoy the simple things as the dialogue and some humor you may not have got when you were younger.
[SPEAKER_03]: Talk about a good soundtrack by the way.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh my gosh, alright, there you go Thank you to the folks that answered the Facebook question of the week and the Google Plus question of the week Answer in a future week I want to say quickly though about that last answer was very similar to one of the Facebook answers and a couple things we were hearing is that these HD remakes really seem to get people to go back and play them again and I kind of find that to be true too is that when the things get re-released it's like a reason for me to go back I had never tried to beat Mario 2 with just one character before
[SPEAKER_11]: So that was something I kind of did that was new this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Try doing it with Toad.
[SPEAKER_11]: The desert levels would be manageable.
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually, I only use Toad in the desert levels for the most part, but I did, now this was, keep in mind, when I was a kid, I did a full playthrough with Toad.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you would be surprised at the number of coins you get.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was playing the stupid bonus game for ages.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because you have a faster dig.
[SPEAKER_11]: SSJ100, Matt to the rescue in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_11]: A-B-A-C-A-B-B.
[SPEAKER_11]: That was the blood code.
[SPEAKER_11]: ABA, CABB, Abacab
[SPEAKER_07]: The next Kickstarter for Double Fine has been launched.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're a brand new game called Massive Chalice.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's kind of a cross between a feudal fantasy tactical strategy game with this weird...
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess they're saying there's like permanent death in the game so you have to create new characters by breeding them I guess so yeah that's gonna be coming I guess and it looks interesting they're most likely gonna hit their goal since they're at 677,500 right now and their goal is 725,000 and they've got 24 days to go so most likely they're gonna make it so yeah
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Looks interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's being headed up, I guess, by the guy that did Iron Brigade, Brad Muir.
[SPEAKER_11]: Speaking of Kickstarter stuff, by the way, the Zelda Kickstarter we had, that guy on the show a couple weeks ago, didn't make it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Didn't make it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Bummer.
[SPEAKER_11]: He says he has some other plans, though, and good luck to him with plan B. I think you gotta have a plan B when you go into this Kickstarter thing, because I think it's like...
[SPEAKER_11]: I think it's like going viral.
[SPEAKER_11]: These ad agencies will hire people saying, we need you to make a viral ad.
[SPEAKER_11]: But sometimes, either it's going to catch or it's not.
[SPEAKER_11]: And it's not that it's necessarily bad.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sometimes it happens and sometimes it doesn't.
[SPEAKER_11]: Now, when you're double fine and you have that name recognition, well, the money's going to come to them pretty easy.
[SPEAKER_11]: But unfortunately for the Zelda movie and all that, it just didn't catch on for whatever reason.
[SPEAKER_11]: And that's going to happen sometimes.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Good luck to him with whatever he decides to do with his plan B. That makes me quite sad.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, it's unfortunate.
[SPEAKER_11]: Very unfortunate.
[SPEAKER_11]: I had put in some money, but I got it back.
[SPEAKER_11]: Or I should say they never charged it, because that's what happens.
[SPEAKER_11]: They don't charge you until it goes through, so...
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, going to some news for the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_11]: The 3D Sonic that I remember we talked about was rumored a couple weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_11]: Apparently it is something that's happening because the Australian Classification Board issued ratings.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, you gotta love when the ratings board spoils games.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, not only did they roll out a 3D Sonic the Hedgehog rating, but they also rolled out a 3D Altered Beast rating.
[SPEAKER_03]: apparently 3D Space Harrier, 3D Super Hang-On Space Harrier these are all out in Japan already but the fact that they're rated in Australia means they're probably coming around to the rest of the world too which by the way if I am right and they're the same as the Sega Ages what was it I imported like three of them I had the Phantasy Star, the Phantasy Zone and Space Harrier they're really good if it's in the same line
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, these will be 3D.
[SPEAKER_11]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm all about Space Harrier, Super Hang-On, yeah, Sonic, yeah, Altered Beast.
[SPEAKER_11]: Look, Altered Beast is one of those games that is... Everybody remembers that, and in people's memories, it's awesome, but I played through the game not that long ago.
[SPEAKER_11]: It sucks.
[SPEAKER_11]: Altered Beast sucks.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm sorry to say it.
[SPEAKER_11]: It is not aged well whatsoever.
[SPEAKER_11]: When I was 12, that game was the shit.
[SPEAKER_11]: When I'm 34, not so much.
[SPEAKER_11]: We need a Marvel Madness.
[SPEAKER_11]: We do need a Marvel Madness.
[SPEAKER_11]: That wasn't Sega.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't care though, it would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wasn't it Williams or Midway?
[SPEAKER_11]: It was Atari.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, Atari.
[SPEAKER_11]: Which their arcade division got snapped up by Midway, I believe.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that's what I'm thinking of.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which in turn then got snapped up by Warner.
[SPEAKER_03]: The game's great if you've got a trackball to play it with.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, it could do something with the touchpad, who knows.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, DarkSakura, what do you have for us?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, as soon as I can get it up, there we go.
[SPEAKER_03]: Gianna Sisters Twisted Dreams developer.
[SPEAKER_03]: We like them, don't we?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because they gave us that wonderful series back, didn't they?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's Black Forest Games.
[SPEAKER_03]: They've announced another game called Ravensdale.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a four-player co-op side-scrolling platform shooter set in a medieval oil rig city.
[SPEAKER_03]: Looking at the screen capture here, it's pretty grimy, very oily looking.
[SPEAKER_03]: They wanted it to be an action RPG, but publishers were saying that Steampunk doesn't sell.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's why they are... It looks like they've changed the method of this.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, has anyone else heard anything about this?
[SPEAKER_11]: No, not this particular game.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, it was...
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, there are likelihoods saying that we're going to see a Kickstarter in about a month or two.
[SPEAKER_03]: Since they're not finding a publisher, they're going to go the Gianna Sisters route.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I mean, if judging by Gianna Sisters, it's probably going to be good.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, they got a good track record.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, yes.
[SPEAKER_11]: I still need to play that Twisted Dreams.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's one of those games that's like in my queue waiting to play, but I loved the Commodore 64 one, even though, yes, it was kind of the Mario Brothers ripoff, but soundtrack is part of what I remember most fondly, but
[SPEAKER_07]: It's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have it downloaded, but I played it like once.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then I went back to Saints Row the 3rd.
[SPEAKER_03]: I did not like Saints Row the 3rd.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's wrong with you?
[SPEAKER_03]: I just didn't like how the game started off.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's so funny.
[SPEAKER_11]: I laughed and laughed.
[SPEAKER_11]: Did you get to the part where they're skydiving out of the plane?
[SPEAKER_11]: You gotta at least get that far, because I died.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was so funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just found I didn't like the control, that's all.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, I didn't like Mass Effect the first time I played it, just saying.
[SPEAKER_11]: Loki, what do you have for us?
[SPEAKER_07]: So there's some more announcements coming from Japan for the Wii U. First off, the Wii U is now going to be available in white for the 32GB premium set.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's starting July 13th.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I guess it'll be available in black and white since they already have the black to begin with.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then, of course, they're going to be...
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess doing some sort of... And I'm surprised it's taking so goddamn long for this.
[SPEAKER_07]: But they're doing... Well, first they have a larger capacity battery for the Wii U gamepad.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it's going to be 2500 mAh instead of 1500 mAh.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which will, I guess, equal to 5 to 8 hours of gameplay.
[SPEAKER_07]: As opposed to 3 to 5.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then on top of that...
[SPEAKER_07]: They're having official Wii Remote charge battery packs for it.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_07]: Crypt of the NecroDancer Crypt of the NecroDancer
[SPEAKER_11]: It is a rogue-like game, which is, you know, like a dungeon crawler, like if you think way, way, way back to the old Terminal Game Rogue.
[SPEAKER_11]: But it's mixed with a music game.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's a hardcore rhythm-based roguelike.
[SPEAKER_11]: Notable game composers Danny B and Alec Holowaka are working with Crypt of the NecroDancer, which I think is awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: And you can also load your own MP3s into the game if you want.
[SPEAKER_11]: Although, I don't know how well that will work.
[SPEAKER_11]: But there you go.
[SPEAKER_11]: That looks awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: And you can check that out at NecroDancer.com Very cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: I like both those types of games.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's like a game made for Rob.
[SPEAKER_11]: Dungeon Crawler meets DDR.
[SPEAKER_11]: Love it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I just need my dance pad.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, let's get to our mailbag.
[SPEAKER_11]: Every week you guys send us emails and DarkSakura reads some of her favorites here on the show.
[SPEAKER_11]: In fact, she's got a couple weeks to catch up on with no official show last week and so forth.
[SPEAKER_11]: So...
[SPEAKER_11]: Unfortunately, she was trying to sew.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, one of my stitches came out.
[SPEAKER_03]: It actually broke when I flipped the foot inside out.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I was trying to fix it real quick.
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought I had time before mailbag.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, well.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, a freaking ton of mail.
[SPEAKER_03]: And a lot of it's in Mandarin Chinese.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, let's skip all those.
[SPEAKER_11]: That was the spam.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was the spam.
[SPEAKER_03]: Except for the stuff in French, which I could actually read, but I don't really care about boobs that much.
[SPEAKER_07]: Spam-durin'.
[SPEAKER_03]: Womp womp.
[SPEAKER_03]: So this comes from Rababababa.
[SPEAKER_03]: I noticed the Curiosity game from 22 Kansas approaching the center.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, there's a countdown on each cube and I believe it was at 13 when I wrote this on Monday.
[SPEAKER_03]: I made my final cynical conclusions about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, we've already done a big reveal.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I like reading this stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: It appears the cubes do not get smaller as you get closer to the center.
[SPEAKER_03]: It isn't fun, not even as bubble wrap.
[SPEAKER_03]: It gets boring easily, and after I toyed with it once or twice, I'm content to just see it end.
[SPEAKER_03]: The payoff at the end will be disappointing.
[SPEAKER_03]: The life-changing promise is way too large a nebulous.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love the word nebulous, by the way.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hope the center is remember to drink your Ovaltine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Stay pound zero zero zero zero zero zero.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, you know what that is.
[SPEAKER_11]: Stay Black.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then I realized simply Xbox was literally the last name I expected, so they chose the pen's ultimate name of all I could come up with.
[SPEAKER_03]: Overall, the name is pretty good, as it conveys multiple meanings, is easy to remember and understandable, unlike Wii and Wii U, which sound dumb, even repulsive, and conveyed no obvious meaning.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't expect a lot of debate over what a terrible name 1 is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Does it have good games?
[SPEAKER_03]: At this point, I don't really care.
[SPEAKER_03]: All I know is that there aren't many good games coming out for any system at the moment.
[SPEAKER_03]: They'll stop making games for PS4 and Xbox 360 very soon, and new consoles will be my only choice for new games on console.
[SPEAKER_03]: Used games?
[SPEAKER_03]: If I can't trade or give used games away, I will probably not buy discs at all.
[SPEAKER_03]: I also believe this is how EA will implement Game Pass.
[SPEAKER_03]: The game DVR is interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: It requires online to share, so I suspect this will be an exclusive gold feature.
[SPEAKER_03]: I also expect that certain games will not be allowed on this feature, even GASP not allow certain parts to be recorded.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's all I'll bug you with today.
[SPEAKER_03]: And this comes from Elliot B. It's the Oculus Rift report.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dear OLR, this week I was lucky enough to get some hands-on time with the most exciting hardware release of the year.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, not the PS4 or Xbox One, I'm of course talking about the Oculus Rift.
[SPEAKER_03]: For those who don't know, the Rift is a VR headset with low-latency head tracking, providing an immersive 3D experience, in theory at least.
[SPEAKER_03]: While the reality doesn't quite yet live up to the hype, it's still an impressive device, even for a prototype.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oculus have got the basics down pat.
[SPEAKER_03]: The headset is easy to set up, weighs nothing, and lag is unnoticeable.
[SPEAKER_03]: Unfortunately, there is still a pretty major issue standing between the Rift and the mainstream success.
[SPEAKER_03]: Movement with standard FPS controls produce instant motion sickness.
[SPEAKER_03]: Even the peaceful Italian villa demo is nauseating, let alone a fast-paced shooter.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, you have been warned.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: My thinking is that rather than adapting existing games for the Rift, devs will need to keep in mind its weaknesses as well as strengths.
[SPEAKER_03]: Still experiencing the Rift for the first time is a breathtaking experience, even despite its teething problems.
[SPEAKER_03]: To be any more than a novelty, it now needs some equally breathtaking custom-built games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yours virtually, Elliot B.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you, Elliot.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good lord, everybody, why are you writing me novels?
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dear OLR, I would like to take this moment to thank Microsoft from the bottom of my heart for the Xbox One announcement.
[SPEAKER_03]: The amount of money I'll be saving by skipping their draconian, unattractive Kinect mandatory disaster is enormous.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, it's funny, I was worried about skipping this generation because I was afraid the PS4 was going to blow major chunks.
[SPEAKER_03]: I even bought a Wii U out of that fear.
[SPEAKER_03]: Instead, it seems Microsoft is going into the junior year slump that seems to happen with any successful console manufacturer.
[SPEAKER_03]: Seriously, first it was Nintendo with the N64, then Sony with the PS3, now Microsoft with the Xbox One.
[SPEAKER_03]: By the way, lamest name ever.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're getting quite a bit of...
[SPEAKER_11]: The PS3, though, it started off like a great comedy of errors, but after a couple of years, it got better and better.
[SPEAKER_03]: It grew into itself.
[SPEAKER_03]: It did.
[SPEAKER_03]: It fits its big boy pants.
[SPEAKER_11]: Nintendo 64 had its moments.
[SPEAKER_11]: I wouldn't call Nintendo 64 a flop.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pokemon Snap.
[SPEAKER_11]: Among others.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, Mario 64, some in Ocarina of Time, some considered to be the greatest games ever made, so it had that, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: and even Treasure did a couple of games for it and we know what we think of Treasure okay this isn't to say I'll be completely sitting out on gaming hardware this generation obviously I have my Wii U and actually already have a bunch of games for it and I'll be picking up the Retron 5 and Ouya when they're commercially available also since Sony doesn't appear to be restricting used games or mandating internet connections the PS4 seems to be a viable option unless something disastrous turns up at E3
[SPEAKER_03]: Honestly, if Sony isn't looking at the Xbox One and saying, this is what we don't do, I'll be surprised.
[SPEAKER_03]: However, I can say with absolute certainty that I've got more than enough... You know, that was the first typo I found.
[SPEAKER_03]: He said, then and so than.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I was just thinking I was impressed, so good on you.
[SPEAKER_03]: More than enough gaming ready to go for the next five or so years, and that doesn't include GOG or Humble Bundles.
[SPEAKER_03]: However, almost as troubling as the DRM encumbrance on the Xbox One is Microsoft's continued commitment of trying to pimp the Xbox to people who don't give a crap about video games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Does Microsoft not understand that there are cheaper alternatives for those who want set-top boxes?
[SPEAKER_03]: Seriously, media centers like Boxee and Apple TV are $80 to $100 and modern Blu-ray players are having more and more of those features put into them for about the same price or less.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's ignoring the obvious
[SPEAKER_03]: plug a cheap PC into your television through HDMI option I shit you guys not I can do the whole Netflix YouTube multimedia thing on my Blu-ray player my PS3 my Nexus 7 tablet and my PC and most of those options are also on my Wii U Microsoft goes full bore with the living room takeover thing at their own peril while I hesitate to wish them ill I do hope they're awakened soon
[SPEAKER_03]: Failing that, however, I'm good to go.
[SPEAKER_03]: Emulators on Ouya, Retro Goodness on the Retron 5, and Modern Gaming on the Wii U, and potentially a future on the PS4.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Japanese developers will likely be able to go right back to ignoring Microsoft, and all's right with the world.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, there's my thoughts on the Xbox One.
[SPEAKER_03]: Have I mentioned it's a stupid name?
[SPEAKER_03]: I have.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't care.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a stupid name.
[SPEAKER_03]: Seriously, it's worse than Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: Regards, RollStillUT.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for the best written email I have ever read in my entire life except for your one typo.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's T-H-A-N, not T-H-E-N.
[SPEAKER_11]: And also... That is totally a lie.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well written.
[SPEAKER_03]: Shut up, Rob.
[SPEAKER_03]: No offense.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mr. Kickstartered.
[SPEAKER_11]: No offense to the emailer.
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you know it's my job to completely fuck up everyone's grammar.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think maybe it's a little bit overly cynical, but I will give until E3.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's see what happens.
[SPEAKER_11]: And just like Bobby said in the chatroom at live.vognetwork.com Sony never said they weren't doing any of that.
[SPEAKER_11]: They just never answered the question.
[SPEAKER_01]: True dat.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're not going to be able to dodge it much longer.
[SPEAKER_03]: One foot.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have one scale mate foot.
[SPEAKER_11]: In your behind.
[SPEAKER_03]: In your angel butt?
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, this comes from Jay, who I was hanging out with.
[SPEAKER_03]: And just let me hop back into the chat long enough to keep from getting logged out.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: This email comes from Jay, Jammer Jay, who I was hanging out with on last Monday.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, is it gossip all about your experiences?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, it's not.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's pictures of me being sunburned.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um...
[SPEAKER_03]: The highlight of my gaming week was playing DDR with the legendary DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, she did a fine job for getting back into DDR.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's time for Sky and Loki to brush off the rust and join her back into DDR.
[SPEAKER_11]: Played at Roseville Golf Land a couple months ago.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think when Spike and Tim... That show that Spike and Tim were here.
[SPEAKER_11]: We've gone to Golf Land earlier in the week.
[SPEAKER_11]: I have a pile of tokens, which they don't... Which they don't even use anymore.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's all like a card.
[SPEAKER_11]: Maybe you could trade them in.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't think they'll do that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, they had to for a certain time.
[SPEAKER_03]: My summer advice for gamers, be sure to have light sunscreen if planning to be out in the sun a bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, why?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, because the thing is I'm not supposed to wear sunblock at all because I don't make enough vitamin D normally, so I didn't wear any.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then I forgot what humidity and sunlight really does, and I'm still peeling.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, it was nice seeing you again, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was good to see you too.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I look forward to meeting up with Sky and Loki for California DDR one day.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, we would love to have you out here and you are more than welcome to crash at my place.
[SPEAKER_03]: And last email.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hello all!
[SPEAKER_03]: Just thought I would drop a line to say hello to the gang.
[SPEAKER_03]: I am in the middle of reading an amazing book called Ready Player One, which we've discussed on the show, by Ernest Cline.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know I'm a little late to the party since the book has been out about two years now, but it's so good.
[SPEAKER_03]: So much gaming culture and influence as well as a lot of great pop culture references from the 80s and 90s.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have two questions.
[SPEAKER_03]: To anyone who has read it, what did you think?
[SPEAKER_03]: No spoilers.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which I think we've discussed in depth.
[SPEAKER_03]: I haven't read it yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to be borrowing it from Becky, I think.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, good.
[SPEAKER_11]: I still haven't read it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I still need to read Catching Fire, y'all, before the movie's out.
[SPEAKER_11]: So I got a long book queue.
[SPEAKER_07]: You don't need to read the book to watch the movie.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, but like when I... See, reading the book makes the movie better because when I went to see The Hunger Games, like every time they changed something from the book, it was like... And then Alan would know that that was something that changed in the book because he could hear me huffing.
[SPEAKER_07]: So the fact that you got pissed off that they changed things in the book made it better?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, it made it a more interactive experience.
[SPEAKER_11]: Who won The Hunger Games?
[SPEAKER_11]: I did.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's kind of funny doing that with Battle Royale now that I've read the book.
[SPEAKER_03]: and seeing how the movie is just complete blood fest and not really political it's very different the manga is great though so anyway I'm only halfway through and my second question is to Loki when you were doing that challenge a while back this was the book you were doing it for wasn't it yes
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyone who hasn't read the book, stop what you were doing after the OLR show, of course, and go pick it up on Kindle or your local bookstore.
[SPEAKER_03]: You will not be disappointed.
[SPEAKER_03]: Keep up the great work.
[SPEAKER_03]: You three make my Monday at office a lot less miserable.
[SPEAKER_03]: Your friend, Travis.
[SPEAKER_11]: You make our Sunday mailbag a lot less miserable.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you, Travis.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: and you know there's pictures that Jay sent but I think they're the same ones that he put up on Facebook and they're not wanting to look yeah my butt playing DDR your butt on a DDR machine lol see I'm not showing any of you in the chat room because no all right well as long as you have fun that's what DDR is about because I'm the diva that's why fun uh speaking of diva moments it's time to get into that segment we do here every week on the show where we get a little bit angry
[SPEAKER_03]: F you to smoking in your house and making all of my clothes smell like smoke and then on top of it okay this is me going into some family shit okay my mom smokes in the house her husband smokes in the house while my grandmother has vasculitis and I was reading about just how badly secondhand smoke can aggravate vasculitis aggravate a lot
[SPEAKER_03]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then my mom's like, my mom has asthma, and she's saying that my shampoo is aggravating her asthma.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, it was not.
[SPEAKER_03]: Your smoking is aggravating your damn asthma.
[SPEAKER_11]: When I smoked, I would always go, which was a long time ago, but I would always go outside.
[SPEAKER_11]: Most smokers I knew would do that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Especially in this state.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like, it's illegal to smoke anywhere that's not outside.
[SPEAKER_11]: And most outdoor places are also banned at this point in time.
[SPEAKER_03]: They actually banned it in Daphne.
[SPEAKER_03]: I had the most pleasant experience in a Waffle House that I've ever had in my life because you couldn't smoke inside.
[SPEAKER_03]: You could actually smell your food.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was amazing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, I love you, Daphne Waffle House.
[SPEAKER_03]: Your peanut butter waffles are so freaking good.
[SPEAKER_03]: And even though you're kind of racist assholes, Blue Bell Ice Cream, I love your ice cream too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for the banana pudding ice cream.
[SPEAKER_03]: And also, F you to Attention Horse.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks.
[SPEAKER_11]: Three hour show, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_11]: Three hour show.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck you to hot.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because it's going to get hot.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was like 95 today or something, and next week it's 105.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like the winter.
[SPEAKER_07]: Winter, it's cold.
[SPEAKER_07]: You put more layers on.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can only take off so many layers in the summer.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's going to rain.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, it's going to be hot.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's it?
[SPEAKER_11]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_11]: My F.E.
[SPEAKER_11]: of the Week just goes to the whole, like, when it rains, it pours syndrome.
[SPEAKER_11]: I have a lot of good things going on right now.
[SPEAKER_11]: I can't really complain.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like, there's nothing I'm doing where I'm like, argh, I'm so angry about this, which is like, did Robbie bite off more than he could chew?
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: But it's actually one of those things where I'm like, okay, when I have some days off next week, I have some time to catch up on some things, then I can go have fun in L.A., even though I'll have to be driving down there by myself, but...
[SPEAKER_11]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, let's get to a couple more news stories for you guys and then Twitter topics at twitter.com slash OLR and the Skype line at 1-877-GAME-OLR or username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: Not just yet though, a couple more stories.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, unfortunately we got some depressing stories.
[SPEAKER_07]: The first being that unfortunately there was a tragic event that happened this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: One of the engineers for the Oculus Rift, Andrew Scott Reese, was killed in a
[SPEAKER_07]: Basically, a hit and run during a police chase.
[SPEAKER_07]: He was crossing the street in a crosswalk and got hit by a car that the police were chasing and killed.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's awful.
[SPEAKER_03]: That sucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Especially after we just had an email.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, after that email and everything.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's crazy.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, what's really horrible about that is it's like, you know, dude was crossing the street and... Well, didn't it happen to Gunpei... Fuck, I can't remember his name.
[SPEAKER_03]: The dead Metroid?
[SPEAKER_11]: I think he died in a car accident.
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought he was getting out of a car and got hit.
[SPEAKER_11]: He, yeah, yeah, yeah, that sounds familiar.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's on Wikipedia somewhere.
[SPEAKER_11]: But yeah, it was really sad.
[SPEAKER_11]: And it's just, you know, obviously people, car accidents happen every day and we lose great people.
[SPEAKER_11]: And people, pedestrians get hit every day, unfortunately, and we lose great people.
[SPEAKER_11]: It just, it just really sucks that A, this was such a great, you know, young mind that was inventing these things that everybody wanted to play.
[SPEAKER_11]: And B, totally preventable.
[SPEAKER_11]: This guy was not at fault.
[SPEAKER_11]: He wasn't crossing the street in a drug-induced stupor or something.
[SPEAKER_11]: He was hit by a guy who was running from the police.
[SPEAKER_11]: Totally preventable.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's awful.
[SPEAKER_11]: But what can you do?
[SPEAKER_11]: When it's time to go, you're gonna go.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know?
[SPEAKER_07]: But at the same time, it's important not to...
[SPEAKER_07]: If there's a police chase going and there's cars with sirens coming your way, you can hear those sirens and, you know, you always want to look.
[SPEAKER_07]: Especially when I'm driving and stuff, even though there's a green light, I'm always looking.
[SPEAKER_07]: I give it a couple seconds before I go because there's always someone that's not paying attention that's going to run the light.
[SPEAKER_07]: So you've got to be defensive and always kind of keep your eye out, even though it may be green or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: I remember, actually, it was funny.
[SPEAKER_07]: The last time I went to E3, even, a bus ran out of control and smashed into a Walgreens.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, so here's the deal with Gunpei Yokoi.
[SPEAKER_11]: And if you don't know that name, he's the guy who produced... He worked for Nintendo for a long time.
[SPEAKER_11]: Producer of Kid Icarus and Metroid, which is huge right there.
[SPEAKER_11]: Designed Rob the Robot.
[SPEAKER_11]: Designed the Game Boy.
[SPEAKER_11]: So you all know that one.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, he designed the Virtual Boy 2, for which, you know, there was a lot of shame that came with that, and he left Nintendo, but...
[SPEAKER_11]: They say that he had always planned to leave Nintendo at a certain age.
[SPEAKER_11]: Virtual Boy was not the reason for that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, unfortunately, in 1997, he was in a fender bender accident where he rear-ended a truck.
[SPEAKER_11]: He got out of the car to inspect the damage, because, you know, same thing happens here, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: You take the pictures, send them to the insurance company, all that stuff, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: And the passing cars hit him.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I remembered it was something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's similar-ish, yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's very tragic.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, and Yokoi.
[SPEAKER_03]: I knew it was Yoke, but I didn't remember.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, I hope... I really, really hope this story doesn't have a sad ending, but, you know, somebody in the gaming community is missing right now, and his name... I'm hoping...
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_11]: and he was missing in the Vancouver area his bike and helmet were found in Stanley Park but before he left he closed his Twitter account his Xbox Live account reportedly he left his wallet, computer and phone at home and there's really just not a lot of information unfortunately they have been assembling groups in Vancouver to try and find him unfortunately no luck yet I think they were going to search the Waters area next
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: He could have... So he took himself off the grid.
[SPEAKER_11]: Essentially.
[SPEAKER_11]: And who knows where he could have gone.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hopefully, he is safe and sound somewhere.
[SPEAKER_11]: Just, you know, for whatever reason, just got away.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I highly doubt he would be listening to this podcast.
[SPEAKER_11]: But if by some strange string of luck he was...
[SPEAKER_11]: A lot of folks miss you, dude.
[SPEAKER_11]: Please call your family.
[SPEAKER_11]: And a lot of people are out looking for this guy, and they really miss him.
[SPEAKER_11]: So if you are in the Vancouver area, please... Even I would say, honestly, if you're in the Pacific Northwest at all, honestly, he could be anywhere at this point.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's not that hard to get on a plane and go somewhere else.
[SPEAKER_11]: or get in a car and go somewhere.
[SPEAKER_11]: He could be in the US.
[SPEAKER_11]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_11]: FindKnuckles.com is the place to go.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's Knuckles like Sonic and Knuckles.
[SPEAKER_11]: FindKnuckles.com.
[SPEAKER_11]: This guy, by the way, you might have seen his work in the gaming community before.
[SPEAKER_11]: He was pretty well known because he got the one achievement a day on the 360 for like three years.
[SPEAKER_11]: He was really big in the Xbox achievements community.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know I heard his name before.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think he was working with other indie podcasts.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know he did stuff with Rooster Teeth.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, um, I hope they find them and I hope, uh, I hope all as well.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: Uh, that was two really horrible stories back to back.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm sorry we have to end on that note, but, uh, you know, we want to do our due diligence and get some puppies and kittens.
[SPEAKER_11]: Could you, we just need, we need like a kitten playing video or something to play the baby monkey writing backwards on a pig song.
[SPEAKER_11]: Is there a, okay, hold on.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's literally, it's called baby monkey writing backwards on a pig.
[SPEAKER_11]: this will make us feel a little better that will make us feel better yes it will
[SPEAKER_11]: 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_11]: Cheer me up.
[SPEAKER_11]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: If you want to give us a call and comment on anything you've heard about on the show or maybe you didn't hear about on the show tonight but you want to.
[SPEAKER_11]: Again, that's 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: Meanwhile, we will get to Twitter topics.
[SPEAKER_11]: I got to pull those up.
[SPEAKER_11]: Loki, do we have any last minute news while we're working on that?
[SPEAKER_07]: There's a Kickstarter for some sort of vest haptic device or something that they're trying to get off the ground.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's supposed to be the as-close-as-it-gets Kickstarter, and it's like this thing that's supposed to tie in with first-person shooters and stuff like that to make it more immersive, where you actually feel like the bullets are hitting you and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: Ragingator
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, that makes me feel better.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's a kitty.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wait, put it back on the cat.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't want to see you.
[SPEAKER_11]: I want to see the cat.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_11]: Much better.
[SPEAKER_11]: What's kitty's name?
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, that's a good name.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hopefully that will be better than the Anakin that was in episodes one through three.
[SPEAKER_11]: What's on your mind tonight?
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, not a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um,
[SPEAKER_09]: Just kind of a generic question for tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is there any upcoming games that have been announced that you're possibly looking forward to?
[SPEAKER_09]: And not only that, but as a secondary question, if you have a wish list or something that you would love to see on Steam, like if it was you see on Steam right now,
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, I stole that money for that game and said, buy it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like anything?
[SPEAKER_11]: Or are you talking about like ports from consoles or something like that?
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, either or.
[SPEAKER_11]: Whatever direction you would like to take the question.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, I would point you to the OLR Dream Games page on the OLR Wiki because things like WhatTheyPlay.com, Snap, those still have not come to fruition and I think we'd like to see some of those.
[SPEAKER_11]: But on a serious note, things that are on console that I would like to see on Steam...
[SPEAKER_11]: I could be a total fanboy and say Mario, which also wouldn't happen, but
[SPEAKER_11]: Then again, on the keyboard, it wouldn't be the same experience.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'd have to think about that one.
[SPEAKER_11]: You guys, anything that jumps to your mind?
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll come back to your other question though.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anything that jumps to your mind?
[SPEAKER_11]: Something that isn't on Steam that ought to be?
[SPEAKER_03]: there's so many things that I could come up with to make the list especially in this short of a show let me check in with DarkSakura and Loki I want SNES collections like Genesis collections even better, TurboGrafx I want the revamped Dracula X Alien Crush HD I want to see the whole Crush series up through Jackie Crush Loki?
[SPEAKER_11]: Minecraft
[SPEAKER_11]: You just won Minecraft in Steam.
[SPEAKER_11]: Makes sense.
[SPEAKER_11]: It'd be cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: I run my Minecraft through Steam.
[SPEAKER_11]: I guess it can be done.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, you can do that.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, let's get to the meatier question that Ragenator asked.
[SPEAKER_11]: What are you personally looking forward to this year, if anything?
[SPEAKER_11]: Let me guess.
[SPEAKER_11]: Loki, Saints Row 4.
[SPEAKER_07]: Grand Theft Auto V. Oh, of course.
[SPEAKER_07]: Both.
[SPEAKER_07]: Come on, both.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is that it?
[SPEAKER_07]: And Earth Defense Force 2025.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the new Call of Duty.
[SPEAKER_11]: For me, the Kingdom Hearts 1.5 remix is something I'm definitely looking forward to.
[SPEAKER_11]: Final Fantasy XIV Realm Reborn.
[SPEAKER_11]: So I know I'm sounding like a total Square Enix fanboy, but it is what it is.
[SPEAKER_11]: Disney Infinity, although I'm totally expecting that game to be a flop.
[SPEAKER_11]: That whole collectible figurine thing, I have to admit, if I'm going to get into a Skylanders game, it's going to be this one.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm cautiously optimistic.
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually do have to tell you something.
[SPEAKER_03]: Julian does not have any Skylanders games, but he has toys that he plays with.
[SPEAKER_07]: There are people that collect Disney commemorative plates.
[SPEAKER_07]: They will buy this game.
[SPEAKER_07]: People will buy this game.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not going to matter.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not going to flop.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm still holding hope that Phantasy Star Online 2 will make it out this year at some point, although I'm losing hope.
[SPEAKER_11]: E3 is kind of the make or break for that.
[SPEAKER_11]: I kind of want to see the South Park Stick of Truth game, too.
[SPEAKER_11]: the toilet humor potty humor guy in me wants to see that Pokemon X and Y believe it or not I'm loving what it looks like the revamp battle system is going to be or not system but the graphics and everything and how they're making everything 3D it looks really cool I don't usually get into the Pokemon games quite as much as other people I know like Shane but if there's going to be one that's going to win me over it'll probably be X and Y
[SPEAKER_11]: How about you, Spazinator?
[SPEAKER_11]: What do you want this year?
[SPEAKER_11]: What can't you wait for?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, stuff that would probably run on my PPS computer, probably Magic 2014.
[SPEAKER_09]: Of course, of course.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, well, that's probably one of the few upcoming games that will run on my computer for sure.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Some of the other stuff, like GTA 5, I know for damn sure it won't run on my computer.
[SPEAKER_09]: If I were to go replace my consoles, I may go get that, but it's not really within my budget right now, but...
[SPEAKER_09]: The short answer is just the next Magic the Gallery.
[SPEAKER_11]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_11]: There's sometimes those reliable series, and we're always waiting for the next entry in them.
[SPEAKER_11]: Some people only get Madden every single year.
[SPEAKER_11]: And if we were like 10 years ago, I would have said, oh, whatever new DDR game is coming out this year.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's what I'm looking forward to.
[SPEAKER_11]: But times have changed.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ragenator, I'm going to let you go so we can get more calls.
[SPEAKER_11]: But take care, buddy, okay?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yep, you too.
[SPEAKER_11]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_11]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, and bye to Anakin as well, if you hear that.
[SPEAKER_11]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or use his name on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: We didn't get a lot of Twitter topics tonight, but I will read this one from Tigerclaw, because this does look interesting.
[SPEAKER_11]: I didn't know about this.
[SPEAKER_11]: Tigerclaw tweets us, the Tetris creator, Alexey Pajitnov, I totally said that wrong.
[SPEAKER_11]: I haven't heard that guy's name in a long time.
[SPEAKER_11]: But he created Tetris, and he came out with a new mobile phone game.
[SPEAKER_11]: This is where everybody go on iOS.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's an iOS game called Marbly.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's the first title he's ever designed exclusively for a mobile device and that you play with colored balls.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hence the name Marbly.
[SPEAKER_11]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: Are they blue?
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, someone had to go the five-year-old route.
[SPEAKER_11]: Why are you giggling over there when I mentioned balls?
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because balls are funny.
[SPEAKER_11]: Balls are funny.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's go to the phones and see who's there.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, another video call.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm loving this.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love your shirt and I want it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Take it off and send it to me now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Your chest is impressive.
[SPEAKER_11]: Keep it on for the rest of this call, please.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's a family show.
[SPEAKER_11]: You guys are cheating me.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't see you on video.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, you've heard how many times the stream has gone down tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: We can't afford the upload.
[SPEAKER_11]: Who is this for the listeners?
[SPEAKER_11]: This is Osfer.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hi, Osfer.
[SPEAKER_11]: How are you doing?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm pretty good.
[SPEAKER_10]: You mentioned earlier about how you were really getting into the Wii U virtual console.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: I, uh...
[SPEAKER_10]: I also went and I got Mega Man X because, I don't know, a lot of people seem to really be into the series.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've never played Mega Man X before, but I've played the other games.
[SPEAKER_11]: Now's a great time to catch up.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, it seems pretty good.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm pretty bad at Mega Man games in general, too, but I have a lot of fun things.
[SPEAKER_10]: I like the dashing and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, a lot of Mega Man games are really freaking hard, too.
[SPEAKER_11]: You say, I'm not that good at Mega Man games.
[SPEAKER_11]: Nobody is that good at Mega Man games, but you learn.
[SPEAKER_11]: You learn.
[SPEAKER_11]: You get better at them.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I was actually really mad earlier because I was fighting some mini-boss against... I can't remember the robot's name.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was some electrical guy.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I couldn't even beat the freaking mini-boss.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was getting so angry.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then I fight the actual boss.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm like, wow, that was the easiest thing I'm going to fight.
[SPEAKER_10]: What did you think of Super Metroid?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I actually own it on Super Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I've played it before.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_10]: But you're very...
[SPEAKER_10]: you're very well thought out and it being your favorite game ever because it is pretty amazing that is the right answer sir I will side with you in your whole Chrono Trigger debate that I think Super Metroid is a far better game than Chrono Trigger it's comparing apples and oranges though I don't care how many times you F5 the site tonight you get a gold star for that comment if you're comparing RPGs Chrono Trigger is up at the top next to Final Fantasy 6 but action games
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, Jamie, in the RPG department, I will say that I like Chrono Cross better than Chrono Trigger.
[SPEAKER_03]: But if we're sticking to just SNES?
[SPEAKER_10]: Just SNES?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Final Fantasy VI versus Chrono Trigger, I think, is the great SNES debate.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, for me, then that would be Super Mario RPG.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, good answer.
[SPEAKER_10]: Fair answer, fair answer.
[SPEAKER_10]: Also, you mentioned this shirt earlier.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can tell because it's like backwards, but it's the Symphony of the Goddesses shirt.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not backwards on our end.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess the camera flips properly.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, that's weird.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, we see it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, on my end, it is backwards, so I'm like...
[SPEAKER_10]: That's weird.
[SPEAKER_10]: Have you guys made it out to see Symphony of the Goddesses yet?
[SPEAKER_11]: No, but I want to.
[SPEAKER_11]: But you know what I said earlier about a lot of stuff going on?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think...
[SPEAKER_10]: What was that?
[SPEAKER_10]: Sunshine.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think he mentioned something about it coming back to California soon.
[SPEAKER_11]: I believe I heard it's going to be in Oakland or somewhere in the East Bay soon.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I honestly think it was like early June.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's probably when I'm in L.A.
[SPEAKER_11]: Just my luck.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, as for anything you want to share with our listeners tonight, anything else?
[SPEAKER_10]: That's about it.
[SPEAKER_10]: All your listeners should go drink coffee.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's what they should do.
[SPEAKER_11]: But don't drink crappy coffee.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, you're drinking coffee right now.
[SPEAKER_11]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_03]: Your mug is like the size of mine, except mine says the queen is not accepting an audience today.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is just like some cheap Walmart mug.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it's Starbucks blonde dress, so it's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_10]: I like Starbucks.
[SPEAKER_11]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, Osprey, you take care.
[SPEAKER_11]: Have a good night.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thanks for calling.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, you too.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, bye.
[SPEAKER_11]: Everybody's beautiful in their own unique way.
[SPEAKER_11]: Everybody's beautiful.
[SPEAKER_03]: Was that, who was that?
[SPEAKER_03]: That was Ray Stevens, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_11]: Was it?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, it's funny, I told, when I was on the way back to Gulfport to get on the plane, I texted Dan from Pascagoula, so he asked if there were Skrulls going berserk, because that was another Ray Stevens song.
[SPEAKER_11]: You guys are such nerds.
[SPEAKER_03]: So?
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, let's go to another call.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio, who's this?
[SPEAKER_11]: This is Legend of Zaku here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Three video calls in a row, look at that.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's up, Zaku?
[SPEAKER_08]: Nothing much, just trying to stay dry, high and dry right now with all this thunder outside.
[SPEAKER_11]: I've already heard a few rumbles.
[SPEAKER_11]: Which, by the way, I hope everybody's... I know Codeman lives in Oklahoma, so I checked in with him earlier in the week.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know who else of our listenership is in that area affected by the tornadoes, but I hope y'all are okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hope your stuff's hooked up to surge protectors, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my god, he's got a shirt I want!
[SPEAKER_03]: I freaking love Dream Theater.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dream Theater's freaking awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, Zaku, surely you did not just call in tonight to get complimented by DarkSakura, although I wouldn't blame you if you did.
[SPEAKER_11]: What's on your mind tonight?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I guess, well, to put it bluntly, I think we're approaching the next video game crash.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, call me cynical, but if you look at the rumblings of how Microsoft announced to the world about the Xbox One, how they're basically...
[SPEAKER_08]: You're not getting a straight answer from them regarding used games since each answer is contradicting one another.
[SPEAKER_08]: Kind of like Heisenberg's rule of uncertainty principle where if you study something long enough its properties change dynamically so it keeps shifting around.
[SPEAKER_08]: In other words, you're still left with so many unopened questions and
[SPEAKER_08]: and it's getting to the point where we don't own things anymore.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's kind of like the Steam model being pigeonholed into the console even though it's not the appropriate medium.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wait, do you blame Steam for what Xbox... Let's say worst case scenario is true with Xbox One.
[SPEAKER_11]: Do you blame Steam for that?
[SPEAKER_11]: Do you think that everybody's looking at Steam going, well, they get away with digital downloads?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I mean, it's expected that a console which for the...
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: is physical, it's tangible.
[SPEAKER_08]: Even though they do exist as game downloads and that's already accepted as a standard where you only own the license to that particular digital copy.
[SPEAKER_08]: But if you buy something tangible, wouldn't you expect that the first sale doctrine would apply to it?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not going to disagree with Zaku.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wait, hold on, hold on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Zaku, Zaku, Zaku.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not going to disagree.
[SPEAKER_08]: Zaku, hello?
[SPEAKER_11]: Zaku, Earth to Zaku.
[SPEAKER_11]: Come in, Zaku.
[SPEAKER_11]: Zaku, stop talking.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, Zaku, I've got to ask you this.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because I want to play devil's advocate, and this is important, because you say that we expect something tangible.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm not going to disagree with you.
[SPEAKER_11]: I like having the tangibleness.
[SPEAKER_11]: I've been very disappointed that manuals are going away, and instead we're getting these inserts.
[SPEAKER_03]: Me too.
[SPEAKER_11]: N64 N64 N64
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, that is true.
[SPEAKER_08]: However, even with the disc error, starting with PlayStation and anything slightly earlier than that, you're able to lend it out to anybody, to your friends.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, all of a sudden, Microsoft wants to impose paying for that game all over again.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, when you buy something, you're presuming, it's pretty much common presumption that
[SPEAKER_08]: You pretty much own it.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're able to do what you want to lend it out.
[SPEAKER_08]: But in this case, for the Xbox One, it's a much tighter grip.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's equity.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's equity on your value.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like this huge wall of DVDs I'll never watch.
[SPEAKER_11]: They at least have equity.
[SPEAKER_11]: I could get 50 cents at a dimple or something.
[SPEAKER_11]: which is a local chain that buys these things per those discs it's like a house you buy a house and then you sell it for hopefully more money later on it's like a car you buy it and then you hopefully can sell it later on and I know a lot of people are saying a video game is different than a car but until now our games have had equity and now we're saying we might lose that and that is not good when you're asking me to pay $60 for a game that will be worth zero when I try to resell it
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a rumor.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's an exchange, so to speak.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's almost similar to how the Yankees basically opted out of StubHub to create their own ticket exchange.
[SPEAKER_08]: Up until last year, me and my girl were able to get home tickets for really good seats at below face value.
[SPEAKER_08]: and I think this is what's happening.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're taking the same approach where they want to cut out any other middleman and basically set their own terms and set their own prices for certain games.
[SPEAKER_11]: Holy crap, I just saw lightning in the background.
[SPEAKER_11]: That was crazy.
[SPEAKER_11]: Did you guys see that?
[SPEAKER_11]: Like totally flashed in his window there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it's definitely the... This is why we don't do a video show.
[SPEAKER_11]: I get too distracted.
[SPEAKER_11]: There's something shiny behind you!
[SPEAKER_11]: Something shiny!
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, yeah, that too, and then mobile, which those issues were never a moot point to begin with.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, they were never an issue to begin with.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, everything on mobile is pretty much digital, so it's the same rules that apply to PC.
[SPEAKER_08]: And if it turns out that Sony's basically pulling the same tricks as Microsoft, then
[SPEAKER_08]: and God help them if they find a way to spin it really well, better than what Microsoft was able to, then yeah, there might be a crash long overdue.
[SPEAKER_08]: It might even happen a lot sooner if they flop at the end of the year or early next.
[SPEAKER_08]: People will still clutch
[SPEAKER_08]: to their existing 360s and PS3s like myself.
[SPEAKER_11]: I hope it's not an all-out crash because I know a lot of people in the industry that would be affected.
[SPEAKER_08]: As I said, I may have exaggerated when saying crash without adding context and scope.
[SPEAKER_08]: It will be a crash with traditional consoles.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mobile and any other casual aspects of gaming will be unscathed because they appeal to a broader audience.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Zaku, I got to let you go so we can wrap up the show.
[SPEAKER_11]: But thank you for your opinion.
[SPEAKER_11]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_11]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_11]: You too.
[SPEAKER_11]: Don't get hit by lightning.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love when we get like really in-depth discussion like that, though.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Zaku does, you know, love Zaku or hate him when he gets on his train where he won't let me talk.
[SPEAKER_11]: But he's very passionate.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I love that.
[SPEAKER_11]: I love all your guys' passion.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's what this show is all about.
[SPEAKER_11]: All you guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I love Utada Hikaru's passion.
[SPEAKER_11]: I do, it's a good song.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes it is.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you guys for putting up with our internet up and down fuckery tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: We really appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll be back next week.
[SPEAKER_11]: Next week is the big pre-E3 show.
[SPEAKER_11]: That is the week to lock in our predictions and guess what guys?
[SPEAKER_11]: You know we gotta use this as an excuse to bring back Listless and the thing we most wanna happen, wanna see happen at E3 2013.
[SPEAKER_11]: So be thinking about it now.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll be back one week from tonight to do all that.
[SPEAKER_11]: But in the meantime, it's time to end tonight's show.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just wanted to let you know that there was a mention of a very old joke when I was hanging out with Jammer J. Oh God.
[SPEAKER_11]: Pantsless Rage.
[SPEAKER_11]: Of course, of course.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, look.
[SPEAKER_11]: Loki, any other last minute stories before we wrap it up and say print?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, Shadow Warrior.
[SPEAKER_07]: You remember it's being remade?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, the classic is available free on Steam forever.
[SPEAKER_07]: So go play it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then finally, the Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_07]: movie has celebrated its 20th anniversary.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, and one other thing that Steam does better than the Xbox One, the Alan Wake series on the Xbox 360 right now is $20.
[SPEAKER_07]: $4 on Steam.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's why people don't mind DRM, because you can get a series of games for $4.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or the Humble Bundle, where you can get the entire franchise, like 20 games for $5.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, that is going to do it there for another episode of Orange Lawns Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you guys very much for tuning into our show, whether it be live and putting up with the connection issues or listening on the podcast feed, taking the time out to download us or through an app like TuneIn or Stitcher or one of those.
[SPEAKER_11]: We really appreciate it no matter how you listen to the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I would like to give a shout out to somebody who said she would be downloading the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: To Blue Sigma from Tumblr.
[SPEAKER_11]: More people that I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_11]: So just spread the word about our show.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's all we have.
[SPEAKER_11]: Don't spam, but spread the word about our show.
[SPEAKER_11]: Tell a friend.
[SPEAKER_11]: Tell somebody who might appreciate what we're doing here.
[SPEAKER_11]: And spread the love of independent podcasting.
[SPEAKER_11]: If you think our show is shit, then thank you for at least listening to the whole thing before you decided it was shit.
[SPEAKER_11]: Go download another great independent podcast.
[SPEAKER_11]: There's lots of great content producers out there.
[SPEAKER_11]: We've got a whole ton of them here at the Voice of Geeks Network.
[SPEAKER_11]: Everybody from Bobby Blackwolf, Understation Live, Girls Gone Wild, Anime Jam Session, PodCulture.
[SPEAKER_11]: Everybody, everybody.
[SPEAKER_11]: E3.vognetwork.com
[SPEAKER_11]: And I think that's really it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Now we can go around and get everybody's final thought.
[SPEAKER_11]: So my final thought tonight, I'll start, is that it's time to check in for my airline because I want a good seat.
[SPEAKER_11]: Loki, your final thought tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: AC's not working.
[SPEAKER_11]: Boo.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_03]: And when I am done with him, hopefully, because I never sleep, so it might be tonight, I will post pictures up.
[SPEAKER_11]: Are they happy feet?
[SPEAKER_03]: They're kind of deflated because they have no stuffing.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I could put them on my fingers and pretend they're real feet.
[SPEAKER_03]: See, look.
[SPEAKER_11]: Real feet.
[SPEAKER_11]: You need a little picture of that for OLR.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: I am scale mate feet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Little pictures of your happy feet.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think I'm going to name my scale mate Sir No Stuffing or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll name him Stouffer.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, that's it.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're done.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're out of here.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you guys very much for tuning in.
[SPEAKER_11]: Again, if you like the show, please help spread the word.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're an indie show.
[SPEAKER_11]: We don't have big money to be selling ads.
[SPEAKER_11]: We don't have the type of listener base that's going to give us a quarter of a million dollars on Kickstarter.
[SPEAKER_11]: All we have is word of mouth and we appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Have a wonderful night, everybody.
[SPEAKER_11]: See you next week for Pre-E3-ness.
[SPEAKER_11]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Lounge Radio is a production of OLR Studios.
[SPEAKER_04]: To join us for a live show, tune in to vognetwork.com Sunday nights at 6 p.m.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pacific, 9 p.m.
[SPEAKER_04]: Eastern.
[SPEAKER_04]: The views and opinions expressed in this program do not necessarily reflect those of the staff of Orange Lounge Radio or VOG Network.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you know they were all still true See you next week