[SPEAKER_00]: Tonight, June 30, 2013, Microsoft reportedly drops Xbox Live patching fees, the Dave & Buster's chain is searching for the next big game, and Nintendo fans start a petition to end region locking on the Wii U.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hello my friends out there on the internet and welcome back to another week of the show where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is Orange Lounge Radio for this episode number 510, June the 30th of 2013.
[SPEAKER_06]: My name is Rob Roberts and I am here to talk with you guys about video games and gaming culture and gaming roles and gaming WTFs with my co-host, joining me as she has faithfully for the past 11 years,
[SPEAKER_06]: Say hello to DarkSakura or Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bleh.
[SPEAKER_06]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you still sick 11 years later?
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_11]: It's funny.
[SPEAKER_11]: My voice is getting a little bit better, but I still have the cough, so.
[SPEAKER_06]: Aw.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ricola.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm living on a steady diet of Ricola, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_11]: I've gone down a size.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thanks to my diet of Ricola
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm doing alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, for those that... Loki has a bubonic plague.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it's a good thing it's not a video show because if you guys could see Loki, he's got like chicken pox on his hands or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it's not really chicken pox.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I don't know what chicken pox look like because I've never had it, but it's an extreme... Well, it's not extremely rare, but it's rare.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's hand, foot, and mouth disease.
[SPEAKER_04]: Usually something that, you know... Is that where you keep putting your foot in your mouth?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because you do that a lot on this show.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: The listeners do not want to catch foot and mouth disease or whatever it is you have.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it's only contagious.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's mainly if you're dealing with your children or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can catch it from changing their diapers or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can catch it from...
[SPEAKER_04]: She had baby butt disease
[SPEAKER_04]: I wouldn't expect you to do anything different any other day.
[SPEAKER_11]: We could set up a quarantine.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think we've got some canvas somewhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: Should we drape a plastic sheet over Loki?
[SPEAKER_04]: You'll be the Loki in the plastic bubble.
[SPEAKER_04]: But other than that, I've been just staying at home, just doing a lot of watching of instructional videos for Unity stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Your programming stuff is...
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I finished, well, I don't know if you'd call it finished.
[SPEAKER_04]: I finished slash quit my C++ thing because I was just like, listen, I don't really care about all this stuff that they're talking about.
[SPEAKER_04]: And really, it doesn't, when you work with Unity and stuff, it doesn't really apply.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, you know, some of the very low-level things they're teaching you in C++, and sure, I'll go back to it someday, but for right now, I just wanted a basic understanding of, like, programming languages, and that's what I got, and that, you know, now when they're showing Unity stuff, I can understand what they're doing, and I'm not like, what?
[SPEAKER_04]: What's he mean by that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I look forward to seeing whatever project, especially the one you were telling me about before the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sounds very ambitious.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like an OLR dream game in the future.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's Peter Molyneux crap.
[SPEAKER_06]: Can you imagine if Peter Molyneux had Loki's ideas?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because this is where we're headed now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki's learning programming.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki's going to come up with these games.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to be crazy.
[SPEAKER_06]: So a couple quick things and then we'll get to our guests because we have a guest here in the studio.
[SPEAKER_06]: First off, I know much of the country is under a heat wave right now, but it is hotter than Satan's taint here in Sacramento right now and just as sweaty.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like it's humid and we bitch here in Sacramento about the humidity when it's like above zero.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not East Coast humid.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know that, but it's bad for West Coast.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was one thing I was going to say.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then I think I was going to say something gaming related, but I forgot because I was thinking about how fucking hot it was.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I guess with that, speaking of Satan's taint, let's go introduce our guest.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_06]: Say hello, everybody.
[SPEAKER_06]: Joining us live in studio tonight, a good friend of mine.
[SPEAKER_06]: We go way back years and years, and he hosts another show that you all should be listening to.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's First Mate Slidekick from the GameBooey.org podcast.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ahoi!
[SPEAKER_06]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_07]: Pretty well, aside from the roasting like a chicken part.
[SPEAKER_07]: More like a pig at a luau.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it's pretty bad here in Sacramento, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: You're visiting us for the weekend from, where do you live usually?
[SPEAKER_06]: The Bay Area.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: The big nebula of the Bay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, welcome.
[SPEAKER_06]: So Spike, your co-host at Gamebuoy.org was here about, I think it was about, actually it was about two months ago at this point.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: So assuming we've picked up any new listeners between now and then, tell us a little bit about Gamebuoy.org.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's your show all about?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, we're your port of call for gaming news and views that maybe aren't on your radar, but definitely should be.
[SPEAKER_07]: What we kind of focus on are left of center news and...
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_07]: Not really, but we think it's important for people who are interested in this type of content and these sorts of games to have a place to go to hear the news.
[SPEAKER_07]: We find all this stuff on all the big news sites, but with all the big news that happens, it sometimes gets lost, so we try to...
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, sure, like, all this fuckery about the Xbox One, I mean, that whole talk dominated E3, and I'm sure there's lots of great, and I use my quotey fingers, Kensha Hall games, in memory of the hall that used to be there, that kind of fall off the radar, because, you know, everybody's too preoccupied with all this crap about Xbox versus Sony and Nintendo out of left field and all that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Right, yeah, and I mean, we talk about Xbox One and some of the bigger stuff, too, but, you know, we just try to keep our fingers on the pulse of the stuff that you might not hear a lot about, so hopefully we succeed with that.
[SPEAKER_07]: And where can folks hear your show?
[SPEAKER_07]: We're over at GameBooey.org, and you can get all of our episodes there, and also links to all our social networks, so...
[SPEAKER_07]: Hopefully some of you, all our peeps, will come and listen to us and say hi.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's like Game Boy, but you have a U before the O, like a buoy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, like a boat buoy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hence why you're pirates and first mates and all that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry, the listeners are complaining that you're too quiet, so I'm trying to turn you in.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow, that's a first.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, especially since back when we were raiding, I'd have to turn you way down.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then I'd have to turn Rob even further down, because...
[SPEAKER_11]: Rob would be like, okay, everybody on the main... Tank, move!
[SPEAKER_11]: Tank, move!
[SPEAKER_06]: I like to yell at people when I play WoW.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't help it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just the way I am.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, you got some fans in the chatty room over at live.vognetwork.com because this show, you know, the one that does all the mainstream stuff here where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_06]: uh we uh read along with you guys in the chat room you guys can participate live.vognetwork.com Sunday nights at six o'clock pacific nine o'clock eastern right after the Bobby Blackwolf show although sadly he was not live tonight due to a last minute technical glitch those things happen and but poor Bobby's had a string of bad luck lately with the lightning and everything else so uh
[SPEAKER_06]: our thoughts go out to him for like a good week somebody needs to take Bobby Blackwolf on a cruise y'all somebody needs to put him on a cruise you know he likes cruises he's a cruiser guy he needs to that's not good luck at all come on oh yeah with everything that happened with the carnival and everything just stay away from cruises he'll end up on the poop cruise we don't want that somebody needs to get him on a good cruise no we just need to like win the lottery go to Georgia and give him a big hug
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Going into our chat room at live.vognetwork.com, Osfer says, I've been recently listening to Game Buoy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Happy face.
[SPEAKER_06]: Aw, thanks, Osfer.
[SPEAKER_06]: And ClericalError404 says, Game Buoy is great.
[SPEAKER_07]: Aw, lots of love.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: He has to say that, though, because we're doing the stuff with Koopa Club and Game Bar and Gamer X. No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_06]: What a great bunch of guys all around the internet doing those podcasts.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: ClericalEra404 also suggests a cruise to Alaska.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi!
[SPEAKER_06]: And Codeman says, I love Bobby.
[SPEAKER_06]: We all love Bobby here at the Voice Geeks Network.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's why we get pissed when all this bad shit keeps happening to him.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um...
[SPEAKER_11]: How about an open letter to bad shit?
[SPEAKER_11]: Knock it off.
[SPEAKER_06]: Stop it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not love, OLR.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought of the other announcement I wanted to make real quick, and then I'll get back to John, or excuse me, First Mate Slidekick.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ooh, I just said your real name.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then we'll move on with the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow, back to First Mate Slidekick since I'm supposed to be talking to you.
[SPEAKER_06]: What are some of the topics you've talked about on Game Buoy lately?
[SPEAKER_06]: One thing I kind of like about your show is that since you do a central topic, you pick a lot of stuff that's not necessarily tied into the news.
[SPEAKER_06]: Your April Fool's show was all about Tingle, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, it was our Tingle cast.
[SPEAKER_06]: and what you did another show about I know you did an LGBT show you did what was your most recent one?
[SPEAKER_07]: The most recent one we did was like the recent full episode was our E3 blowout which is a yearly thing now second year actually a new thing that we've done on the site is introduce Game Buoy Micro which are little tiny podcasts and by tiny I mean like a half hour because our podcast is
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Since you did, I know one of the micros you did, because I actually listened to it, you guys went and saw the Best Buy Nintendo E3.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, we actually took some YouTube video as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: How was that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Not to steal the thunder of your show, but give us the Cliff Notes version.
[SPEAKER_06]: How was it?
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, it was kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: I feel like any time you go to a Nintendo event, whether it's just camping out for a Wii or going to something like this, Nintendo crowds are usually pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was a really long wait, but to Nintendo's credit, they didn't cut it off right at 6 or whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: How long was long?
[SPEAKER_07]: We were in line for about five and a half hours.
[SPEAKER_07]: We got to play one game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just like the real E3.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_06]: Authentic experience.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what they were actually saying.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Nintendo representatives there were saying it's an authentic E3 experience.
[SPEAKER_07]: They give us pizza.
[SPEAKER_07]: P-I-Z-Z-A Did they give you whipped cream pouring like waterfalls?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, they didn't.
[SPEAKER_07]: Cheap bastards.
[SPEAKER_07]: But yeah, I thought it was really cool that they put it on and that they were so cooperative in that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Best Buy, to their credit, was really cooperative too.
[SPEAKER_07]: They could have just been like, nope, it's five.
[SPEAKER_07]: Everyone who hasn't played yet doesn't get to play.
[SPEAKER_07]: But they tried to get everyone to play what they wanted and they had little Mario Kart 8 flags to give you just for waiting in line.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I mean, it was really cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I still think the best way, you know, approach to E3 was like Xbox.
[SPEAKER_04]: I only got Xbox.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, 2005 or 2006 when they did that, we're bringing E3 home and they had like demos for games, like same demos that were out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm like, why don't they do that?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't understand why they can't do that now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I know a lot of that doesn't run on like final hardware and stuff, but...
[SPEAKER_06]: I think the reason why they don't is there's too many people that make their final judgment of the game based off the E3 demo, and it's too risky in that regard.
[SPEAKER_06]: I honestly think that's a big part of it.
[SPEAKER_06]: E3 builds are usually really early on in the development, and there's too many people that make their decision like, oh, this game sucks, based off the demo.
[SPEAKER_06]: Demos carry a lot of weight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but these people, though, are the same dumb people that will buy a game based off of a review score from one outlet.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, I mean, they're very fickle anyways, so I don't know why we should punish them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Considering that, you know, it's going to get a good review and they're like, well, I guess I'll buy it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, because, you know, iGen liked it or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: Quickly, also about the Nintendo experience.
[SPEAKER_06]: What did you play?
[SPEAKER_06]: You got your hands on with... Spike did Mario Kart 8.
[SPEAKER_06]: You did the Mario... I did Mario 3D World, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Mario 3D fused with Super Mario 2 game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Cats.
[SPEAKER_07]: Super Mario Cats.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's why you need to know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Super Mario Cats, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, it was kind of chaotic, and I've actually... I think it was over on US Gamer, which is Jeremy Parrish's new...
[SPEAKER_07]: Outlet.
[SPEAKER_07]: They were describing it as chaotic too, but I mean like in a good way.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it was fun, you know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mario Party's chaotic if you play with me.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mario Party's always chaotic.
[SPEAKER_11]: Everything is chaotic if they play with you, Rob.
[SPEAKER_11]: Shut up!
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_11]: I've been here 11 years.
[SPEAKER_11]: I have the right to say whatever I want to.
[SPEAKER_06]: But did you have fun?
[SPEAKER_06]: I did, I did.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you make your judgment on the entire game based off that demo?
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, I mean, I kind of made my judgment on that game based on the Nintendo Direct, honestly, so... You're like, it's Mario and Princess Floats, I'm in.
[SPEAKER_07]: Pretty much, you know, I'm a shameless Nintendo fanboy, but, you know, it was good to get a chance to play it and to be able to, like, speak to that, and...
[SPEAKER_07]: And just being able to see the games that I didn't play, like watching Captain Spike play Mario Kart 8 and Wind Waker HD.
[SPEAKER_07]: Towards the end, people were starting to just get really annoyed when people were like, oh, I want to play Wind Waker HD because it's actually what they did is they redid the...
[SPEAKER_07]: Original GameCube demo, so you could either do the bird battle, boss battle, or run around Windfall Village.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which is cool, but compared to doing two races on Mario Kart or two levels in 3D World, it was just a little too long.
[SPEAKER_07]: It looked gorgeous, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: Donkey Kong Country Tropical Freeze looked good.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was cool to actually get a chance to see it, not just based on E3 videos, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was worth it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Going to the chat room for some comments at live.vognetwork.com ShadowNextGen says, Gamers rush to decisions.
[SPEAKER_06]: A lot of them don't understand the concept of an alpha or beta build that will be buggy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, there's a lot of people playing the Final Fantasy XIV online beta right now that are basically like, oh, this is just a game trial, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: And not really.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a lot still missing.
[SPEAKER_11]: We've already seen big changes from the last build to this one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, God, yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oscar says, I also did Mario 3D World at the Nintendo E3 experience.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was pretty fun playing the cat form.
[SPEAKER_06]: The dive mechanic is really awesomely integrated in some of the levels.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I agree.
[SPEAKER_06]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, we'll take it a step back and just kind of getting to know you as a gamer a little bit before we get into tonight's news.
[SPEAKER_06]: I always ask the guests this.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's your favorite video game of all time?
[SPEAKER_07]: That's always a really tough question to answer.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can name a couple if you have to.
[SPEAKER_07]: One of your favorite video games.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have to say, if I'm going to just pick one favorite, it would probably be Original Legend of Zelda for NES.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just because I grew up with that game, I know it inside and out, and that's the game that I can just put on a virtual console or whatever and play through in a weekend, and I just know where everything is.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not that over-familiarity is always good, but it always feels like going home again.
[SPEAKER_07]: What do you love about video games?
[SPEAKER_07]: What possessed you to want to do a podcast?
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, I've known Captain Spike for actually longer than I've known you, so... Yes, you have.
[SPEAKER_07]: You guys have been besties for a long time.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, we were just always talking about games, and we just thought, you know, why not give it a try?
[SPEAKER_07]: We were inspired by y'all here at OLR, so we just thought we'd give it a go, and we've been going for over a year at this point, so...
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a great compliment, though, so thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, anytime anybody says, like, oh, I mean, you guys did it, so that helped me learn that, like, I could do it, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm always like, that's, like, actually, like, a great compliment.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_06]: You guys rock.
[SPEAKER_06]: Aw, you guys rock.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, you.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, love fest here at OLR.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not in this heat.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anything else you want to plug?
[SPEAKER_06]: Ew, sticky.
[SPEAKER_06]: Any other shows, Twitter, things like that you want to plug?
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, they can find all of our social links on our website, GameBooey.org.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess I just would like to shout out to Gamer X Convention in San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, it's for gamers of all genders and that sort of thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: You don't have to be gay to enjoy Gamer X.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Rob and I and Captain Spike and our friends from Game Bar and Koopa Club are going to be doing a podcasting panel there.
[SPEAKER_07]: So if you happen to be heading out there or you didn't really know about it and you think that sounds like a cool thing, you should go over to gamerconnect.com.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura.org.com
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, well thank you and of course, please continue commenting on tonight's news slide kick.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's why we're here.
[SPEAKER_11]: For the record, it's 68 degrees in San Francisco right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: For all you in San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, but tomorrow it'll be 80.
[SPEAKER_06]: For all of you in San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_06]: Grandpa, if you're listening, kiss my butt.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow, let's move on into how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_06]: We always like to start off the show with a little bit of what types of video games have you been playing this week in Dark Sakura?
[SPEAKER_06]: I know you've had a big week in gaming.
[SPEAKER_11]: I played old stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: We hooked up the Super Nintendo last night for my friend Amanda's 30th birthday.
[SPEAKER_11]: Happy birthday, Amanda.
[SPEAKER_11]: And we played Turtles in Time.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_11]: And if you are whored, though, you can kill them, which is pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_11]: I always liked doing that when I was way past level.
[SPEAKER_11]: So I played a little bit of Final Fantasy XIV just because I only played a little because of all the stuff going on, especially with being sick and having to clean house and having a party.
[SPEAKER_11]: I finally got to play Cards Against Humanity.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's not a video game, I know, but it's totally wrong.
[SPEAKER_06]: All the nerds are playing it.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I got the best win ever.
[SPEAKER_11]: I might say it on air, but it's really horrible.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I did say that it's like an M. Night, whatever his name is.
[SPEAKER_11]: The plot twist was that Nickelback was really the perpetually handicapped.
[SPEAKER_06]: and Night Shyamalan.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Shyamalan Dean Dong.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's what Dan calls him.
[SPEAKER_11]: So we had the old school SNES stuff last night and I have played some...
[SPEAKER_11]: Mass Effect 3 3DS
[SPEAKER_11]: Thanks to my husband not wanting me to make puppy eyes and whine at him, I have Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_11]: He also got himself the last Fire Emblem game for the DS.
[SPEAKER_06]: So there's a little something in it for you both.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's good, though.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're probably going to sell my old DSi.
[SPEAKER_11]: We only need to have one of each system.
[SPEAKER_11]: We have my pink GBA.
[SPEAKER_11]: I have the clear pink one.
[SPEAKER_11]: We have the Nintendo SP, whatever they were called, the one that was done up by the NES.
[SPEAKER_11]: Usually it's like when the new stuff comes out, we'll have one each of us and then sell off one of the old ones.
[SPEAKER_11]: Right now we're poor.
[SPEAKER_11]: Um, so, uh, I've been playing, what, six hours of Animal Crossing today.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I've already, uh, made the down payment on my house and bought a phone booth.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then, uh, one of my friends on Tumblr, who, uh, I have to say thank you to my name twin if she's listening.
[SPEAKER_11]: Um, we, uh, I got a Dave Strider shirt for anyone who's into Homestuck.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was really cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: So my character's running around in it wearing pink glasses because, ew, pink, but glasses.
[SPEAKER_11]: She looks kind of weird hipster.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a lot for just one day.
[SPEAKER_06]: You've probably done more in a day than I've done in the three weeks I've owned this.
[SPEAKER_11]: I have all the fruit now.
[SPEAKER_11]: I do not have a watering can and I do not have a slingshot yet.
[SPEAKER_11]: You'll get it.
[SPEAKER_11]: It better be tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't forget to buy the fortune cookie every day.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, shoot.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, don't you have to have coins or something?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, you get those from walking around.
[SPEAKER_06]: So if you've been walking around with your 3DS day, you have coins.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_07]: Up to, I think, seven times, I think is where it maxes out.
[SPEAKER_11]: I thought you guys would just run amok through my game.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I'm just like, look at my pretty penguin hat.
[SPEAKER_06]: Isn't it awesome?
[SPEAKER_06]: I love your penguin hat.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is why I stopped playing Find Me, because I don't need a better hat.
[SPEAKER_11]: Rob, I honestly like Slakic's hat better.
[SPEAKER_06]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Mario hat.
[SPEAKER_11]: I want to have a propeller hat, because that would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: So yeah, Animal Crossing, that's going to be my life from here on out.
[SPEAKER_11]: I did name my town Normandy, like I said I would.
[SPEAKER_02]: Congrats.
[SPEAKER_11]: So either that, so either all of my townsfolk are going to call me Commander, I mean my character Sakura, because every Animal Crossing character I've ever had is Sakura.
[SPEAKER_11]: Either that, or they're all going to have like French words, they'll be like Merred or Ulala or...
[SPEAKER_06]: or Zoot today I made my crappy recreation of the VOG logo in my Animal Crossing town because we finished the custom signboard so right when you enter the town you see now a big little VOG logo my ghetto logo I have a goal for this game though to find Dina you want to be reunited I want my lesbian back ours is a love long denied Dina was an aardvark I don't think she was an aardvark I thought she was a duck whatever no Mallory was a duck
[SPEAKER_11]: There were several ducks, Rob I don't give a duck We have diversity You and your only aardvarks can be lesbians
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, I know you haven't been playing Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_06]: What have you been playing?
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't been playing very much at all, actually, this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: The two things I did play this week, one being Final Fantasy XIV, the beta.
[SPEAKER_04]: I played about an hour of that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was actually going to play more, but then I just kept getting distracted.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was supposed to play LittleBigPlanet Karting, but I forgot.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hands are too much anyways to play anything, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm like, okay, I guess I will.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then I get killed because I don't notice that my health is going down because it's too much on the screen.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's a tip I have for fates if you happen to find yourself overwhelmed.
[SPEAKER_11]: Run through a big crowd of people.
[SPEAKER_11]: The thing will not follow you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it wasn't that at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't even notice it was doing a lot of damage to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's because I'd get done with one and immediately target the next thing and immediately go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also, many people don't realize the UI is completely customizable, even on PS3.
[SPEAKER_06]: So if the health bars are not in a unique place for you, try to move them.
[SPEAKER_04]: I should.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then the other thing I played was a little bit of Excite Truck this morning because we wanted to entertain Josh.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I was trying to get Mario Kart to work, but my disc wouldn't read in my Wii U, which is weird because it did before and now it's not.
[SPEAKER_04]: and then so it's just like okay well I guess we'll do you know we play and then he couldn't understand we play so we did excite truck and he just kind of let it sit there and just coast in a circle so that was kind of fun but I actually did get to play a couple races and stuff and man that game looks really basic now that actually like you know now that you're not zooming through the landscape you know at a high rate of speed it's just very basic looking I'm like wow
[SPEAKER_04]: S, Actdeft, Drew,
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks to one of our old listeners of the show and also one of the old players that used to play on the Minecraft server that we had, Lord Gally.
[SPEAKER_04]: He has actually provided or said, hey, you know what, I have a server that not a lot of people play on.
[SPEAKER_04]: You guys want to come play on our server?
[SPEAKER_04]: So he gave me full access to the admin stuff for it, so we'll be able to set it up.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's actually a lot more flexible than the old one, so I can actually do all the kind of mods I want to do.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, somebody needs to build a shrine to Lord Gally first thing for that, because that's an awesome gesture.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you, Lord Gally.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have to check with him, because right now it's set to survival and stuff, so I have to see if he wants to switch it off of that and put it on bucket and everything, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: but now that I have all the tools to do that I just got to sit down and actually research what I want to do I wanted to put a spout craft server on there because spouts pretty awesome because you can create all the custom shapes and stuff like other materials that are unique to the game so you can have new enemies you could have planes cars guns you know all sorts of crazy stuff so I'll see how hard that is and may do that but it looks like it'll be a lot of fun and hopefully we'll get to play it again
[SPEAKER_06]: Codeman is bouncing off the walls in chat.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's very excited to hear that it's back.
[SPEAKER_04]: So soon, I'll have the details in the VOG Minecraft forum.
[SPEAKER_06]: Slidekick, are you a Minecraft player?
[SPEAKER_06]: You ever tried that out?
[SPEAKER_06]: I've actually never played Minecraft before, so I probably should.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's different.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a game, but it's more like Legos on the computer.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's hard to explain.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've watched people play it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's clever.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just never really been a high priority for me, but I should check it out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Give it a chance.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, if that's it for Loki's Gaming Week, then I will move into my Gaming Week real quick.
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't have a lot to play.
[SPEAKER_06]: Honestly, I OD'd on Final Fantasy XIV this weekend during the beta.
[SPEAKER_06]: I played damn near nonstop.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, I had a couple other things to do here locally, but when I wasn't out and about, I was trying to stay out of the heat and I was playing the crap out of Final Fantasy XIV beta.
[SPEAKER_06]: For those that would understand that they've been playing the beta too, my Thaumaturge is level 16 and then my main... I started with Thaumaturge and I switched to Conjure.
[SPEAKER_06]: And my Conjurer is now 17.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I've got both those jobs going.
[SPEAKER_04]: So is Conjurer like the 14 version of a Summoner now?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, that's going to be Arcanist, which isn't in the beta yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: So there's still stuff to add.
[SPEAKER_06]: Arcanist will lead to Summoner and Scholar eventually.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then Conjurer leads to Black Mage.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or no, excuse me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Whoop!
[SPEAKER_06]: Thaumaturge leads to Black Mage Conjurer leads to White Mage but like you don't ever get stuck with just one job it's kind of more the final it's not like 11 system of sub jobs it's Final Fantasy 5 more system where you choose traits like because my Thaumaturge is level 16 when I play a Conjurer I can have Thunder and Surecast from my Thaumaturge in my bar so that's kind of like and like if I were to play a Gladiator or something I could actually get like maybe weapon skills if they're usable if they're compatible with my class but
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: In many ways, some of the combat I realized when I was healing a dungeon the other night, I'm like, you know, this game doesn't really have the complexity of World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_06]: All I'm doing is Cure, Cure, Cure, and occasionally I'm doing Medica, which is the group Cure.
[SPEAKER_06]: And sometimes I'll get to nuke the mob, but I don't have the diversity that I have in World of Warcraft spells.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now granted, World of Warcraft wasn't always like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: World of Warcraft's five expansions in right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's going to take time for Final Fantasy XIV to build up to that, and I see the potential there, but I love that the combat is so fast-paced, but it's Final Fantasy.
[SPEAKER_04]: I also like how the combat, well, you can kind of utilize your terrain as well, because now that you can jump and stuff, you can actually, you know, okay, I'm going to...
[SPEAKER_04]: Hop up on here and, you know, shoot stuff from, you know, cast spells from up on top of here and the monster can't really get around to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or, like, I found with, like, it doesn't work all the time with goblins and stuff, but when they do the bomb toss or whatever, it'll show where the bomb's going to be and you can run around behind them and you don't take any damage, which is pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_11]: I actually liked that, too.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like, that one duty I was having a problem with, I ended up just sprinting and kiting him the whole time, but it was really neat.
[SPEAKER_11]: It actually worked a lot better than it did in WoW.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_11]: It's just... Everything is there.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought I was going to have to get a new system, but there has been such a jump in performance from the last beta to this beta.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm like, oh my god.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, this game looks great on my not-so-great computer.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm so thrilled.
[SPEAKER_11]: It really sets it to optimize to what you have.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Been loving Final Fantasy XIV.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, one of the other fanservice-y things I have to talk about.
[SPEAKER_06]: The last boss in Tamtara Deepcroft, which is one of the instances...
[SPEAKER_06]: it's a it's a mage with a tentacle face and I didn't catch it at first but Alan looks over and goes dude that's one of the mage mobs from Final Fantasy 1 and I'm like oh my god it is like there's just all these little like subtle fan service things they change something by the way um when you start off in Gridania did you remake a character there
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_11]: Your intro is different now from how it was in the last one.
[SPEAKER_11]: You have moogles.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I started an olda this time.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, I went ahead and made another conjurer because I wanted to see if they had a new quest.
[SPEAKER_11]: And there's moogles.
[SPEAKER_11]: And it's really funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's cute.
[SPEAKER_06]: Techness in chat says, Oh, and where's the VOG link shell for Final Fantasy 14?
[SPEAKER_06]: I accidentally rolled on one of the JP realms.
[SPEAKER_06]: My assumption is that Horde House being the online gaming show will kind of pick up the VOG link shell thing and create.
[SPEAKER_06]: Right now we're on Behemoth, but that's subject to change for Beta 4.
[SPEAKER_06]: We will let you know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Behemoth is busier.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_11]: If it's lower, then that's even better.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I had the impression it was going to be the $14.95 thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm assuming somebody in chat will yell it out, or if Shane Alinko is listening, he'll join shortly and yell it.
[SPEAKER_04]: See, the thing is, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hate paying for an MMO month-to-month because I want to play so much other stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: I feel locked into having to play that to kind of get my money's worth each month.
[SPEAKER_04]: and that's the thing it's like that's why I quit Final Fantasy XI because I just wasn't playing it enough and I kind of afraid to get into something like that's why free to play or you buy the game and you can play whenever you know works well for me it's just I like the game I like it a lot better it seems to be a lot easier to level up and stuff than XI which is nice but
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, so anyway, Final Fantasy XIV.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then the other game I've played a lot of this week, Marvel Heroes, the free-to-play MMO, although it's a little more like Diablo.
[SPEAKER_06]: Free my ass.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, well, it's got little transactions up the wazoo.
[SPEAKER_06]: Little?
[SPEAKER_06]: I started a storm, of course, because I love storm.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I started playing a storm, and then after I beat the first boss, I got the Scarlet Witch token, so I can play a Scarlet Witch now, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's who I started with.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, so apparently all the characters will drop in the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: It just might take forever.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I'll give a cheap plug to this week's Horde House because we had Mihail on this week and he talked about Marvel Heroes and a lot of League of Legends, which I patched this week so I could play with Mihail later this week when Final Fantasy XIV is not running.
[SPEAKER_04]: HordeHouse.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not running this week?
[SPEAKER_04]: Only on the weekends, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, Final Fantasy XIV is only running on the weekends, but the rumor is there's going to be a longer stress test before Beta 4.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_07]: anyhow uh slide kick first mate slide kick what have you been playing this week what's a week of gaming look like to you it's pretty much been all animal crossing uh you know it's funny because i picked it up actually at the nintendo experience because you know they had a display sitting out so i was like oh i probably should get it and for the first couple of days i only played a little bit but lately i've just been playing for like hours at a time and i'm like oh i've got to sleep now
[SPEAKER_06]: I also played the shit out of Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_06]: That one night we were doing the Google Hangout with everybody.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I just built the upstairs to my house.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've been going to the island a lot, catching bugs.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, I got Reggie's house in my spot pass in the Happy Home model homes gallery.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I've been buying a lot of stuff out of Reggie's house.
[SPEAKER_07]: And when you look in his little profile card, it says my body is ready.
[SPEAKER_07]: So...
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, you know it was an intern that did it, people.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not Reggie's actual house.
[SPEAKER_06]: An intern did it for him.
[SPEAKER_04]: I did notice in some of the screenshots or whatever they were showing of the game that they have a lot of cool niche Japanese arcade stuff you can get.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if they have a Japanese arcade set, but they have a candy cab, a claw machine, some actual table cabinets and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: They look pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not sweet enough for me to buy a 3DS for the game, but sweet enough.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a claw machine in my Animal Crossing house.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you know what I loved in your town was the animal that had the chocolate fondue fountain.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what I want.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who doesn't want a chocolate fondue fountain?
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's be real.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: And some McCroons.
[SPEAKER_06]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_11]: First thing that I bought wasn't making a down payment on my house.
[SPEAKER_11]: I bought a phone booth.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that the thing that looks like a TARDIS but red?
[SPEAKER_11]: It's the current British style phone booth.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like one of those was for sale in my town the night of the Google Hangout.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Spike was like, open your gates right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm coming to town.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that just started this whole like wave of Animal Crossing fuckery.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Except then he didn't take my virtual boy that I was saving for him.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's a virtual boy fanatic.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I'll have to get it to him.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now you're no longer friends.
[SPEAKER_11]: If they put in like virtual boy games, it would totally work with the lenticular game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, as like a 3DS Virtual Console thing?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I don't even know about like Virtual Boy emulation, if that's actually a thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought there were early rumors it was going to happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: They just need to make Animal Crossing like the Nintendo version of PlayStation Home.
[SPEAKER_04]: Done.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, rumors are it's going to go free to play at some point.
[SPEAKER_06]: System seller right there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Makes sense.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anything else?
[SPEAKER_07]: Slide kick.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, actually just Animal Crossing this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've been meaning to get around to some other stuff, but I'm actually in the process of moving.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I've been kind of trying to pack up my console games.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I'm like, oh, my 3DS is right here.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's why I've kind of been focusing on 3DS for the most part.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not to give out your home address for all the stalkers, but you're moving to Daily City, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, which is Alan's old digs, kind of.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, just Alan's old digs and just a quick part right away from the city.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because you're having fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good thing you missed this weekend because I hear it was crazy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, yeah, with all the festivities.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, lots of extra festivities.
[SPEAKER_06]: Lots of stuff in the news to be festive about.
[SPEAKER_06]: But we are going to move into gaming news.
[SPEAKER_06]: But first, I want to go over some housekeeping.
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course, I always like to plug our Twitter, twitter.com slash OLR, and Facebook, facebook.com slash Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I was going to plug this during housekeeping.
[SPEAKER_06]: We already mentioned it at the top of the show, but I'll plug it again.
[SPEAKER_06]: GamerX, catch me.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll be there live August 4th.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: You get there and you just look for Podcast Cross Zone and you're going to go to it because it has the word podcast in it and that's where you're going to see me and Slag Kick and all the kids from Koopa Club and Spike and Game Bar and it's going to be fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: Come up and say hello.
[SPEAKER_06]: It will be great times.
[SPEAKER_06]: And earlier today before the show, I was talking about cosplay because I think there is a costume I can pull off that's tasteful.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're going to pull off your costume?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, this is tasteful, Slag Kick.
[SPEAKER_11]: He's going to do the gladiator armor from Final Fantasy XIV.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I'm going to wear the, what is it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Subligar, the panties.
[SPEAKER_06]: The leather mantis.
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: You'd probably be very popular if you wore that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, right.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, no.
[SPEAKER_06]: They'll be like, okay, that guy does not have the body to wear something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, all right.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I will wear something that will keep me covered.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just turned 35, you know, so I don't need to be showing all my wrinkles.
[SPEAKER_06]: Such a press.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, anyhow, let's for real get into some of the gaming news this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is the gaming news that may not be on your radar, or it's pinging huge on your radar, one or the other, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Slidekick?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, start us off, Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, so Index Corporation, the, I think, pretty recent parent company of Atlas, they are having some problems.
[SPEAKER_04]: They are basically filing for civil rehabilitation and maybe selling off assets, I'm assuming.
[SPEAKER_04]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: and they also have some other titles that they're publishing including the movie tie-in for RIPD and I guess Daylight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah, Daylight.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't even remember what Daylight is.
[SPEAKER_07]: Daylight is the survival horror.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're thrown in a haunted house, I think, with only a flashlight and the PlayStation Eye records your scares so that your friends can laugh at you.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: So yeah, so
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe they're not in too much trouble.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's hard to say with Atlas because Atlas, they kind of deal with a lot of niche properties, so money seems to be very tight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very small production runs, very small everything, budget, so it's hard to say if
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I've seen a lot of people worried about them, but I mean, Atlus is well-loved enough that they'll find a home.
[SPEAKER_07]: A lot of people think that Sony or Nintendo would snap them up, but I wouldn't be surprised if, like, GungHo or somebody snapped them up.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would think, like, Marvelous... And a lot of people are afraid that EA might snap them up.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would think it would be more like Marvelous or...
[SPEAKER_04]: What else?
[SPEAKER_04]: Axis, I don't think it's too big to do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But those are kind of the three companies that bring over localized Japanese product nowadays.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I don't think they're big enough.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, XSEED's, I think, quite small compared to Atlas.
[SPEAKER_04]: Atlas was kind of growing quite a bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought they were going to be branching out more into, like, Western development stuff as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because they tried, you know, with, like, Game of Thrones and they have a few Sherlock Holmes games and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's just nothing's really taken off.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which is too bad, because Game of Thrones could have been good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Except it was a really bad game.
[SPEAKER_06]: That PlayStation 3 game you're talking about, the horror game, sounds really good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sounds interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Better than what they have.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sony had a PlayStation Move game, although I don't know if it's Move anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: What was it?
[SPEAKER_04]: That one was supposed to be a teen horror genre type game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't really know how that was going to work.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't even remember the title of it now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because it was that memorable.
[SPEAKER_06]: Shadow Next Gen in our chat at live.vognetwork.com says, what if Microsoft bought Atlas?
[SPEAKER_06]: They would have a lot of Japanese content on their platform then.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that won't do them any good since they're not putting out the Xbox One in Japan at launch.
[SPEAKER_06]: It would be an interesting strategical move, but I think for Microsoft also a risky one.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've heard a couple people say that could be a thing, but I don't think Microsoft really would do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think a lot of Nintendo fanboys would just eat it up if Nintendo would do it, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: That kind of only exists in fanboy imagination, I think, but you never know.
[SPEAKER_06]: So...
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, well let's move on to another story, and this is about Saints Row 4.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, Loki's looking forward to this one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, it's a good thing Loki doesn't live in Australia, or he might be waiting a little bit longer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, please, like an Australian, stop me from getting this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, right, and I'm sure there's a lot of people in Australia that are saying the same thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: However, Saints Row 4 is now the first game to be refused classification in the country since Australia released their R18 plus rating at the start of the year.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which doesn't make any sense to me.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know how they're going to do that, but good luck.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's going to be a mod immediately after it comes out that'll put it all right back.
[SPEAKER_06]: Especially on PC.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: How cute that Australia thinks it could regulate some of that because on the internet this stuff will just come over instantly.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just don't understand.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just encourages piracy too.
[SPEAKER_04]: But did you hear the reason why it got... I didn't hear the specific reason why, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: What was it?
[SPEAKER_04]: They have an anal probe.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_07]: See, I was wondering where they would take the dildo vat next.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, they have a... Does it have a big satellite?
[SPEAKER_04]: It basically looks like a giant dildo with a sword hilt or something on it, and you can shove it up the ass of your enemies.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm like, this makes me want to buy the game even more.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't wait.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, I gotta find... Yeah, you just finished talking there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm gonna find the exact description was hilarious.
[SPEAKER_06]: Didn't an episode of South Park have the anal probe, though?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, wasn't that the first episode?
[SPEAKER_06]: Cartman gets an anal probe?
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it was.
[SPEAKER_11]: The moment he said anal probe, like, the whole, I like to sing about the moon and the trees popped into my head in that episode.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, also, I guess games are getting hit left and right in Australia now.
[SPEAKER_06]: State of Decay is another game that's been refused classification in Australia.
[SPEAKER_06]: This was just not even that long after word of Saints Row 4 happened.
[SPEAKER_06]: So this was Microsoft is evaluating the options with regards to the title's classification.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Australian classification system plays an important role in ensuring that Australians can only access age-appropriate games and content.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that was one day after Saints Row 4.
[SPEAKER_06]: The game includes a weapon referred to the applicant as an alien anal probe.
[SPEAKER_06]: The applicant states that this weapon can be shoved into enemies' backsides.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sold!
[SPEAKER_04]: That's not a probe.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's more like a bottle rocket.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're such a teenager.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's an ass-launcher.
[SPEAKER_04]: an ass launcher ass launcher ass master apparently after the probe has been inserted into the victim's anus the area around the buttocks becomes pixelated highlighting that the aim of the weapon is to penetrate the victim's anus the weapon can be used during gameplay to enemy characters and civilians so the weapon
[SPEAKER_04]: as long as they don't leave a blood trail that would just be wrong and also alien narcotics was the other reason why I guess smoking alien narcotics equips the players with superpowers awesome do they actually get superpowers or do they just think they have superpowers who cares alrighty then let's move on with something else I don't want to be on this planet anymore
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, well, a lot of people are not happy with Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_11]: And among the people who are unhappy with Microsoft is the creator of Fez, Phil Fish.
[SPEAKER_11]: Try saying Fez and Phil Fish together three times fast.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fez, Phil Fish, Phil Fish, Phil Fish.
[SPEAKER_07]: See?
[SPEAKER_11]: You lose.
[SPEAKER_11]: But basically he's saying that Microsoft was doing nothing to help sell his game on Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_11]: He complained about it on Twitter.
[SPEAKER_11]: He said Microsoft was our publisher on the Xbox 360 and they did nothing.
[SPEAKER_11]: No promotion, no festivals, not a single mention.
[SPEAKER_11]: In a newsletter or conference, they put us up on their shitty dashboard and somehow fucked that up too.
[SPEAKER_11]: They put us up on the game marketplace with no cover image.
[SPEAKER_11]: The file was missing for a week.
[SPEAKER_11]: So basically, he's also saying that Microsoft has stopped charging developers $10,000 for patches and updates.
[SPEAKER_11]: And there's a lot of crap going on between...
[SPEAKER_11]: with misinformation going from Microsoft not telling them about corruption within the file system or anything like that so basically they're like oh we don't really care indie developer we just want you to put your game up there we're not going to promote it just put it there we're not going to put any money behind you
[SPEAKER_06]: Actdeft in chat says, Phil Fish, I hate the guy, but he's right in this one.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, yeah, because Microsoft doesn't let people self-publish to the... I mean, they have XNA for self-publishing, although they're not going to be supporting that anymore.
[SPEAKER_06]: And this is part of why people are mad, because you can publish under Microsoft, but then, you know, there's all these other complaints.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, yeah, and Microsoft was charging $10,000 for them to put in a fix in corrupted files.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, Fez really got screwed by all that business.
[SPEAKER_11]: and on top of that Microsoft did confirm that they automatically charged developers for resubmissions of games was scrapped in April is what they're saying but they never told any of the developers about that they said that the new policy was retroactive but they never said anything
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, didn't you have more information on that, Loki?
[SPEAKER_04]: Nope, I had exactly that information.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, of course, on top of that, you know, Phil Fish is still pissed off about the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: See, this is kind of funny, I think, because he was complaining that, oh, well, you know, I don't know if he had a patch or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: First, he put out a patch for the game, and it fucked up the game even more than without the patch.
[SPEAKER_04]: And so then they pulled the patch, I guess, and he couldn't resubmit the patch or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: But now that it's free, why isn't he resubmitting the patch?
[SPEAKER_10]: Perhaps by this point it's just done with the fuckery.
[SPEAKER_04]: But if he had it done already, if he had that fixed patch done already, I'm assuming he still has the data, why can't he just resubmit it instead of being a complete douche?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I know, because he wants to sell Feds 2, which will be coming out to platforms other than Xbox One.
[SPEAKER_11]: Unless it's seriously trying to distance himself from Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_11]: Which I can see that, trying just to remove any association between your product to Microsoft...
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, you keep in mind the bottom line of development is money.
[SPEAKER_11]: If he's trying to market a next game, it's a smart move to separate it from where it's already been screwed over.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, Shadow Next Gen in our chat says Sony was charging for updates too, I believe.
[SPEAKER_06]: It wasn't Microsoft specific.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know if they were charging that much.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to say I remember hearing something like that too because I remember it was a big deal when Wii U first came out is that's why indies were embracing it is because Nintendo wasn't charging.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that was like a huge selling point.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm pretty sure Sony has to have gotten rid of that since, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: They might have just done it a lot quieter than Microsoft did, because look at all those indies they lured to their E3 press conference.
[SPEAKER_06]: To register participation for this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio at vognetwork.com, use the passphrase, EARTH.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, well speaking of Microsoft, a very interesting patent revealed out of Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was a patent filed back in December of 2011.
[SPEAKER_06]: This would have been around the time Halo Combat Evolved Anniversary or the Halo remake came out.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was a patent for a video game that would, quote, have a plurality of game engines running concurrently.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you might remember the Halo Anniversary game lets you go between updated visuals and original Xbox...
[SPEAKER_06]: Back and forth.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently, this is what the patent was out there for, is that it was for remakes of games where you could have original graphics and, I thought this was interesting, leveraging player emotions tied to the original experience.
[SPEAKER_06]: However, this may be lost as modern graphics may cause the gamers to lose that feeling of nostalgia.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it was because of an emotional connection.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess I could see that.
[SPEAKER_06]: There was a whole bunch of these games on Xbox Live Arcade when that first came out, like all the Konami remakes.
[SPEAKER_06]: You could play like Gyruss.
[SPEAKER_06]: You could play it with the original graphics or the HD graphics.
[SPEAKER_06]: You have to play with the original graphics.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't play with the new graphics because they're not that good and it's hard to see the bullets.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that's a different thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's not that you're nostalgic for the old graphics.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just the new ones are really lame.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sounds like you're smoking some alien narcotics here because I don't see the point.
[SPEAKER_11]: Weren't we having that discussion, though, about voice acting today?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, a little bit, yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: With Metal Gear, how they updated the voice acting.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, it was all the same people, but they didn't put the same cheesiness into it, I guess.
[SPEAKER_11]: I wonder if it's sort of along the same lines.
[SPEAKER_06]: SILENT HILL 3
[SPEAKER_06]: Slidekick, are you emotionally tied to retro games?
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what this actually made me think of is when they put out the Star Wars DVDs that had the original video.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it might have been like a laser disc transfer or something because that's all they had that wasn't destroyed at that point.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which one?
[SPEAKER_07]: The original Star Wars trilogy.
[SPEAKER_07]: They put out a DVD set that was like two discs.
[SPEAKER_11]: Which I have that set.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, me too.
[SPEAKER_11]: That were the theatrical releases.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_11]: And those I think were redone off of film prints.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, film prints, okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: So like hand shot first on the Laserdisc?
[SPEAKER_11]: I have a version of it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I have the THX remasters on Laserdisc, where yes indeedy, he shot first.
[SPEAKER_11]: We call them the non-fucked up remasters, because they actually had the whole THX sound, they did all the cleanup, they had the extra, you know where you see the X's flying in the air, instead of X-wings flying in the air?
[SPEAKER_11]: They had all of the corrections made, but they didn't do any of the changes.
[SPEAKER_06]: and I got it for 11 bucks that's a good point though that people are definitely tied to that emotionally because you bring up the new Star Wars with anybody is there anybody out there anybody that prefers Lucas's changes in the original trilogy anybody people with brain damage I mean I'm sorry don't offend you know what diversity DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_11]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's still wrong.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think people are that nostalgic for Xbox One graphics, to be honest.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, and if they're redoing the game with, you know, I think it was like Halo 3 or Halo Reaches Engine, which is not bad and definitely the graphics look way better.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't see the point of having to tax the system that much by running two copies of the game at the same time.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's a little ridiculous because you either...
[SPEAKER_04]: sell a copy of the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I wonder if they have the actual data of how many people actually play that game with the new graphics versus old graphics.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then also a subset of that, how many people play the game with the new graphics and old graphics and use the Kinect to old graphics, new graphics, old graphics, new graphics.
[SPEAKER_06]: The same people that sit there and yell grenade to throw a grenade.
[SPEAKER_04]: Grenade, grenade, grenade, grenade, grenade, grenade, grenade, grenade, grenade, grenade, grenade, grenade, grenade, grenade.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you know, HD remasters seem to be pretty popular, so I mean, I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_06]: But some of them are so good.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, I am so there for the Kingdom Hearts and Final Fantasy X. Oh, that was gorgeous.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm running up to the feeder bar, give me pellet, give me pellet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, you know, some of that, you know, I'm a sucker for some of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know who I wouldn't want to go up against, you know, using the Kinect and the Halo thing?
[SPEAKER_04]: The guy that used to do the Micro Machines commercials because, my God, he would fucking own online.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think he should be relieved that he's dead.
[SPEAKER_04]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_10]: And John Machida.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: Did any of you play Mega Man Powered Up for PSP?
[SPEAKER_07]: It was the remake of Mega Man 1.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: It wasn't bad, but they replaced the original Mega Man 1 music.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's awful.
[SPEAKER_07]: One has good music, but it's not 2 or 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: The GameCube one, too, I think of.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think it had the re-dunk.
[SPEAKER_07]: They just had this cutesy music that I was like, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it had the new music in it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was just too cutesy.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can understand the nostalgia thing at times.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, let's move on with some more news.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura's got something for us and then we're going to get to release dates.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was trying to find out when John Machida died.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh well.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was a while ago.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hate to say it, it was a while ago.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think it was sometime while I was still in high school, maybe?
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyway, there is some good news for people who were going to put some stock into the Xbox One.
[SPEAKER_11]: They've actually improved the memory performance for the console.
[SPEAKER_11]: Basically, they... Let me see if I can't find exactly the amount.
[SPEAKER_11]: Um...
[SPEAKER_11]: They've actually have now a 32 megabyte of embedded static RAM that's going to make up the difference in processing speed between what was previously announced for the Xbox One and the PlayStation 4.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I don't know if it's still going to be as good.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're saying that right now that 192 gigabytes a second is theoretically possible.
[SPEAKER_04]: 32 megabytes of RAM.
[SPEAKER_04]: Man, that console must be worth thousands of dollars, said somebody in the 90s.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, they're saying it's this embedded static RAM, which I think just means it's a new chip.
[SPEAKER_07]: It just kind of sucks because launch games always are not going to look as good as games later in the console's lifespan.
[SPEAKER_07]: Especially now that they're like, oh, right away we're shipping with more memory.
[SPEAKER_07]: So the games that are prepared for launch probably won't be able to take advantage of that, and that kind of sucks.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, they were saying right now that their original calculations, just as a base calculation, came up to 128 bytes per block multiplied by 800 megahertz.
[SPEAKER_11]: And that now that they've been able to reasonably get in their simulations 133 gigabytes a second, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, then I want no excuses if the Xbox One versions are inferior to the PlayStation 4 versions.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all I'm just saying.
[SPEAKER_11]: Now that you're not going to get your games online, we got more speed.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hold on a second there.
[SPEAKER_04]: You said you added 32 megs of RAM.
[SPEAKER_04]: This should be night and day difference, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: On my 486.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Womp womp.
[SPEAKER_04]: I honestly think this is a bunch of just... It's a bullet point to report on and no one knows what the hell it means.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why, if they're just going to add this RAM, why can't the developers just go back and turn up the graphics on level 3?
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't they just take a big dial and turn up the graphics?
[SPEAKER_11]: What they're basically saying this means is that for some of the games that they showed at E3 that kind of stuttered along, that it should improve performance dramatically.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, I'm not sure what this 32 megabyte thing is going to do.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, it has to be something involved with another calculation, like maybe a buffer or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's to save more pictures of you masturbating.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: On its Kinect.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's the fat box one.
[SPEAKER_04]: The 32 megabytes is basically just to put it in its actual, so it runs off an actual console.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tigerclaw in chat says, yeah, he's right.
[SPEAKER_06]: The first crop of games won't take full advantage of the hardware until, whoa, what the hell?
[SPEAKER_06]: Until, don't paste five lines at once when I'm trying to read.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tigerclaw says, the first crop of games won't take full advantage of the hardware until like a year or so later when the developers finally figured out how to push the hardware to its limits.
[SPEAKER_06]: But that happens with every console.
[SPEAKER_07]: What was that Rome game?
[SPEAKER_07]: Rise from York Wave.
[SPEAKER_07]: They were saying that it looks choppy right now and that this might smooth out some frame rates or something, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow, a fifth dream in that big post he put says the Micro Machines guy is not dead.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_06]: But seriously though, if he was in that... I could have swore he was dead.
[SPEAKER_06]: I swore he was dead too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I mean, I didn't like swear like, God, I hope he's dead.
[SPEAKER_04]: He'd be dead within the first 15 seconds of that, you know, Eddie Murphy movie, One Thousand Words.
[SPEAKER_11]: So... Well, maybe, maybe not.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm looking at the Wikipedia article and sure enough, Wiki says he ain't dead.
[SPEAKER_06]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_11]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, that's good.
[SPEAKER_11]: Then maybe I'm thinking of somebody else.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, it was... What was his name?
[SPEAKER_11]: Chris Latta.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was thinking of.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, he just needs to come back and do something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_04]: I need him talking in something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Trailer, TV, movie, it doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was thinking of Chris Latta.
[SPEAKER_06]: At least that urban legend, I can understand someone falling for that because I could swear I've heard that that guy's dead too.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not like you came on here and said the kid from The Wonder Years is Marilyn Manson.
[SPEAKER_06]: People believe that?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, it was Chris Latta that died in 1994 and he was the voice of Starscream in Cobra Commander.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: I have the stupid Transformers analogy in my head.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, look, we're getting way off track, so why don't we talk about some release dates, some video games that we could play this week and get our mind off of dead celebrities.
[SPEAKER_04]: There is not a much coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's basically just one 3DS game, and it's Crash City Mayhem.
[SPEAKER_04]: The only reason I think it's kind of cool for the 3DS is it's based off a really old series called Runabout, which is on the Sega Dreamcast and PlayStation 1.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or, you know, if you played it over here in the United States, it was Felony 179, a racing game where the whole point of the game was to crash in the shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it was awesome and super glitchy.
[SPEAKER_04]: I remember one time I took a full-size bus, a tour bus, and I tried to go through the train tunnel
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't even know how I got it in the train tunnel.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I tried to turn around like you know you do in the Austin Powers movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it got stuck in there in such a way that it started spinning like a helicopter until it got enough speed where it shot straight up through the roof.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hilarious.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's all that's coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, let's go over to Japan.
[SPEAKER_06]: And on July 4th in Japan on the PlayStation 3, Loki's really excited.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Earth Defense Forces 4 is out.
[SPEAKER_06]: I may have to import that.
[SPEAKER_06]: It'll cost you $71.49.
[SPEAKER_06]: You could also import for much cheaper a Smart Headset 3, which is also released on the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who cares, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: How about on the Xbox 360?
[SPEAKER_06]: Also, Earth Defense Forces 4.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's also a limited edition with gold membership for $86.99.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm assuming that's like Xbox Live Japan, because you know who's paying for Xbox Live over there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Very few people, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nothing of note on the Vita this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm just looking at my other releases.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, nothing really on Wii U either.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you know they don't have new Super Luigi U until July 13th?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I bet that's the retail release, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: They probably have the download version, just not the retail release.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, how about on the Nintendo 3DS?
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a couple games there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Toriko Gourmet Battle comes out, as well as Mame Goma Happy Sweets Farm.
[SPEAKER_06]: That sounds nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to see... God, I hope it's not another game starring scantily clad characters.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, it's the little seal cute thing!
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, that stars a little seal cute thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: I love the plushies of the little seal.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh God, these things are adorable.
[SPEAKER_06]: It looks like they just kind of wither on the ground.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're so adorbs.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they run a farm.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's Farmville and they also make sushi rolls.
[SPEAKER_11]: Rob, that's a sweet roll.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a sweet roll, my bad.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's a Swiss cake.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, it's a little Debbie roll with the strawberry.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's called a Swiss cake.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like I said, a little Debbie roll.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a strawberry shortcake.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want them to localize that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want a fucking strawberry shortcake, damn.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know we have strawberry cheesecake ice cream at my house.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who's going to my house after the show?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, because that would involve going outside, I'm sorry to say.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's it for Japanese releases.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, how about the UK?
[SPEAKER_11]: Some stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: Stuff and things are coming out.
[SPEAKER_11]: What we have on July 3rd is we have Limbo for iPad and iPhone.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh my god, I need that on my phone.
[SPEAKER_11]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_11]: Mortal Kombat Complete Collection.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sorry, Complete Edition.
[SPEAKER_11]: They should have called it Complete Collection, but no, I see why, because then they would have been racist.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's on PC.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, you know what I mean.
[SPEAKER_11]: Too many, too many...
[SPEAKER_11]: and we have a Scourge Outbreak on Xbox 360 and on July 4th we have Trackmania 2 Valley and on the 5th we have Dark.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sakura?
[SPEAKER_11]: No, just Dark.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a vampire stealth action game.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know why but that made me think of Craig Ferguson.
[SPEAKER_04]: Being published by Atlas because they publish Calypso games now.
[SPEAKER_11]: It made me think of Craig Ferguson talking about damp being a color.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just a couple more news stories for you guys and then the classic game of the week, Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or don't.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there's some cool stuff being added to Steam.
[SPEAKER_04]: First off, the Source Software Development Kit now is including native support for the Oculus Rift.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you have the dev kit, you got more games to play it on, or at least hopefully soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: So they're really embracing that, and that's going to be kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then finally, the Steam trading cards.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's out of beta.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now it's available to everybody.
[SPEAKER_04]: So far it supports 30 games, including Team Fortress 2, Faster Than Light, Grid 2, Monaco, Trying 2, Super Meat Boy, Counter-Strike Global Offensive, Portal, Half-Life, Don't Starve, and Borderlands 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, so at the risk of sounding like a complete moron, can someone explain to me how the trading card thing works?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because it's not based on achievements.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's based on time playing the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, yeah, I think it might be on achievements.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's just based on time playing the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I noticed I have a Steam level now, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you get, like, XP, and I think some of that's from the trading cards, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: But I got a lot from participating in old sales and things like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which, by the way, July 4th is next week.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what that means.
[SPEAKER_06]: Barbecue at my house Hide your wallets Hide your wife, hide your kids Cause steam sales is gonna happen I ain't got cash for that shit And they slashing all the prices on up here See, here's the thing though, I've already bought so much stuff I don't really know if there's much more I need All I need is that Civ 5 expansion That's all I need No, Rob, you want it
[SPEAKER_06]: You need air.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I fucking need it.
[SPEAKER_04]: The new expansion?
[SPEAKER_06]: Which expansion?
[SPEAKER_06]: Will you die without it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, you need me to get it because otherwise you will not want to be on this program with me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, we'll have grumpy Nick Trump.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you talking about the new expansion coming out in July or the one that's... The one that's like a couple weeks.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know July is tomorrow, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: I understand that, but no, you're talking about the one that's coming out in... Brave New World.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not going to be on the Steam sale, but it's something on Steam I need to get.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, Brave New World.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't remember if that's next week or if that's going to be the week after next.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's the 8th.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think they're releasing it just in time for my boyfriend's birthday.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think there's like all of two games on Steam right now I'm interested in.
[SPEAKER_11]: And one of them is that Miami.
[SPEAKER_11]: I can't ever remember.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hotline Miami.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because I want to go around shooting people in bloody messes with weird synth music.
[SPEAKER_04]: Should have gotten in on that with the Humble Bundle, man.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good prices there.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I have Bill's.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, Bills.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, let's see.
[SPEAKER_11]: I just had to do something like go to Alabama.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, one more story for you guys here, and this is a follow-up to something we had talked about before.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently, Nintendo may have been easing up a bit on the whole Let's Play video thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Remember that they were really unpopular for a week there because they didn't shut down Let's Play videos, but they were like, we're going to take the money and use it for us if you have a Let's Play video that features our newer games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you, OuyaLaunch.
[SPEAKER_06]: You think that's part of it?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: Since you mentioned analytics and stuff like that and getting paid on stuff, I just happened to check my... Well, here's the timing on this.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's part of the revenue reports because on May 14th, his ad earnings ceased, but then they started again on May 23rd.
[SPEAKER_06]: So he made a leap of faith since he saw the revenue return and no other claims have been made on his videos since.
[SPEAKER_06]: So Nintendo may have given up as fast as they implemented it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, that's what?
[SPEAKER_06]: Two weeks, if even?
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, when we talked about this on Game Buoy, this kind of was an unpopular opinion, actually.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I just didn't really understand people actually making a living off of Let's Plays.
[SPEAKER_07]: It happens.
[SPEAKER_07]: If it works for you, I guess more power to you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, as I mentioned before, because I started monetizing some of my YouTube videos just...
[SPEAKER_04]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm in the wrong fucking business.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is the last episode of OLR, everybody.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was wonderful these last 11 years, but we're moving to YouTube next week in our little five-minute chunk segments, which will just be Loki and I arguing and DarkSakura crying.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_11]: Dan and I were actually talking about doing this with our TurboGrafx games.
[SPEAKER_11]: It'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, there's money to be made.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I'm not looking to make a living off of putting YouTube videos out there, but...
[SPEAKER_04]: It's $36 I didn't have before.
$36?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's about halfway to the Earth Defense Force 4.
[SPEAKER_06]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you know, and I'm kind of actually, Slidekick, I know you said that it was an unpopular opinion, but I think when we talked about this on the show originally, I actually kind of voiced a very similar thing where I'm like, really?
[SPEAKER_06]: You can make a living off this?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, no shade to those that do very well with Let's Play videos.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have a respect.
[SPEAKER_06]: It takes work to do this podcast.
[SPEAKER_06]: It takes a lot of work to do those Let's Play videos.
[SPEAKER_06]: But you have to admit you do owe some of the success to the game that you are featuring.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, if they want to come in and get a cut... But I think Nintendo just kind of did a dick move by cutting it all off, you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, there should have been some type of sharing, you know?
[SPEAKER_06]: The Let's Play content gets something, but Nintendo gets a little something-something too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or, you know, they get their own commercials in there, you know, things like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, they need to take a smaller cut, you know?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, circumcision, not Lorena Bobbitt.
[SPEAKER_11]: What is wrong with you?
[SPEAKER_11]: That is a great analogy.
[SPEAKER_11]: Bump.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thanks.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't want your hand disease.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't fist bump him for that.
[SPEAKER_11]: I did.
[SPEAKER_11]: I didn't high five him because I don't like... I hope you get the blister thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's not going to happen.
[SPEAKER_11]: Here, Rob.
[SPEAKER_11]: Don't touch me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't wash your hands.
[SPEAKER_11]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can't get it from touching my hands.
I'm not afraid of germs.
[SPEAKER_06]: Clearly you're not afraid of germs.
[SPEAKER_04]: If she starts handling my feces, I can't make any promises.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you have a diaper fetish, Loki?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I do not.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, that's good.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's good.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought that was just your dinner that smelled.
[SPEAKER_11]: For the record, if you would pay attention, the more you expose yourself to germs, the stronger your immune system gets.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's very good chance if you were a kid that went to preschool or something like that, you probably already have had this and you won't catch it again.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, for the most part, when kids have this, they don't even develop the blisters.
[SPEAKER_11]: They'll run a fever and have a sore throat.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: ShadowNextGen says, YouTube also has a policy where you can't monetize videos for content you don't own.
[SPEAKER_06]: So this whole thing is a bit confusing to me as to how it was allowed to happen in the first place.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a comment from live.vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: And ClericalError404 follows this up with, it's been about 15 years since I heard a Lorena Bobbitt reference.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Keep it classy and old school here at OLR.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's way too long.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that the whole YouTube policy originally was just to prevent people from, okay, some dude makes a video and then I copy said video, put it up on my channel and monetize it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's me humming along to this new movie that's out in theaters, Man of Steel.
[SPEAKER_06]: Man of Steel, Man of Steel, Man of Steel.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's my little, you know, that would be very bad, I think.
[SPEAKER_11]: I paid good money for this hue card and I own all the data on it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I paid an entire $5 from the garage sale for this hue card.
[SPEAKER_11]: I own it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, DarkSakura is clearly stepping into a time portal over there so you know what that means.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's time for the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Every week, DarkSakura goes into the gaming vault and finds a game that she thinks, hey, you kids and your YouTubing and making careers off of Mario U, you know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: You need to go back to my day when we used to pay $400 for a frickin' Neo Geo game and we liked it.
[SPEAKER_10]: and really weird games were really cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, well, really weird games are kind of still cool, let's be real.
[SPEAKER_06]: But this one was weird.
[SPEAKER_06]: This one was weird, and it's not in the OTO, it's a little newer than that.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, what is the classic game of the week?
[SPEAKER_11]: The classic game of the week is Mr. Mosquito.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's weird.
[SPEAKER_11]: I figured to go for a PS2 era, you know, finally moving up a little bit.
[SPEAKER_11]: Mr. Mosquito was... This is Rina's room again.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oops.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_11]: and the following March in everywhere else.
[SPEAKER_11]: And it was distributed by Eidos.
[SPEAKER_11]: Basically, you play as a mosquito who has taken up residence in the Yamada family's house.
[SPEAKER_11]: I wonder if they were voiced by the Japanese voice actors because the accents are really thick.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, they're legit accents too, so...
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyway, you have to stock up on enough blood in the summer so that you will survive through the winter ahead, which is funny because don't mosquitoes only live for like a week?
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyway, so you can collect these spheres to save extra blood.
[SPEAKER_11]: and you have to suck the blood from them while they're going about their everyday business but you can only get it from certain body parts at certain times like this scene here with the girl on her bed you can only suck it from her upper thigh he's getting a little close to the no-no spot so this is a little bit of a scandalous game he's actually close to the femoral artery
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyway, if he is swatted while sucking, then instant death occurs.
[SPEAKER_11]: Basically you have a stress meter so you have to balance your suck with your stress.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't we all?
[SPEAKER_11]: and then to calm them basically they will try to battle you too like a big boss battle like what we're watching right now on this video where you have stress points that you have to I guess sting them on or bite them on that are meant to calm them so it's like you're doing acupressure on them you're doing mosquito shiatsu there you go you can get smacked all over the room and it's really hilarious
[SPEAKER_11]: So you have different stages.
[SPEAKER_11]: You can go through different parts of the house.
[SPEAKER_11]: And you have different items, different things to help you.
[SPEAKER_11]: The fun thing about this game too is that your ending depends on how much sucking you did.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like how successful you were.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because for the Yamada family, they're going to have their family portrait taken at the end of the summer.
[SPEAKER_11]: And it's like if you completed all the missions and everything, they're all puffed up and swollen all over their faces and the picture's horrible.
[SPEAKER_11]: and it's really funny the voice acting is actually super hilarious too um as for the game it was voted one of the top 10 weirdest games of all time in 2008 by Game Informer and um G4 put it on its list of weird games and uh
[SPEAKER_11]: It was really weird, but Famitsu said it was the fifth best-selling video game in Japan during its release.
[SPEAKER_11]: It sold 41,006 copies.
[SPEAKER_11]: It also got a release on PlayStation 2 the best, and it led to a sequel in Japan on July 3, 2003 called K2 Let's Go Hawaii.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_11]: but this game was just wrong and like you could do other stuff too like you could distract the people in the room by like turning off the light switch or changing the music or doing all this other stuff it's just bizarre but it works it's a very strange game but it's awesome like it's you just you have to see it
[SPEAKER_11]: and like this week I wanted to pick games that were all in the same vein of Incredible Crisis because that game was fucked up and this game I'd have to put it's fucked upness level somewhere near Incredible Crisis so alright
[SPEAKER_06]: There it is, your classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mr. Mosquito on the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, very good pick tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: A little bit edumacational, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, don't go anywhere, guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: We've got plenty more OLR to come tonight with more Slidekick.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Fugle Question of the Week coming at you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Going to talk a little bit about Ouya in the Fugle Question of the Week as well as some news.
[SPEAKER_06]: And also we'll talk about the upcoming Moley Jam.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's always hilarious.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we're going to talk about that.
[SPEAKER_06]: All that and more including your phone calls, CFUs of the week, Twitter topics and all that when we come back with more of Orange Lounge Radio right after this.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hola, this is your friendly neighborhood Mexican, Actdeft, and you're participating with Orange Noun Radio, the show where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I want to use my voice to tell you that Kirby does not suck.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, literally he does suck, but not figuratively.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyways, play more Kirby!
[SPEAKER_06]: Play more Kirby.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do it now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, not now, because you're trying to listen to LLR.
[SPEAKER_04]: Poor guy, man.
[SPEAKER_04]: We put forums in chat that it was like 112 degrees or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're here bitching.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's like tomorrow, though, by the way.
[SPEAKER_11]: I did look up Phoenix.
[SPEAKER_11]: Phoenix was at 116.
[SPEAKER_11]: So Phoenix is like on fire.
[SPEAKER_06]: What about Needles in Death Valley?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's always the lousy place to look at.
[SPEAKER_06]: Didn't we say 122?
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow, that was a repeat bumper there.
[SPEAKER_06]: That means we need more bumpers.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, I'm sure Actdeft is happy to have his voice played on the show all the time, as well as some of our other repeats we'll get into.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're Orange Lounge Radio, the place where Actdeft has a voice.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you want to get your voice heard, go over to our forums at vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: Click on forums and check out the Orange Lounge Radio forum.
[SPEAKER_06]: The call for bumpers is there, and it's very easy.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can even Skype them in if you don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, don't...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: We did.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you sure love to rub it in how good at game show video games you are, huh?
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess I just have a natural talent.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you practice Wheel of Fortune a lot as a kid?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I played a lot of Wheel of Fortune as a kid.
[SPEAKER_07]: 5,000 paths.
[SPEAKER_11]: We've had a Wheel of Fortune winner on the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, I know, yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: I kind of think I need to actually go on Wheel of Fortune.
[SPEAKER_06]: Our buddy Mel, who needs to come back to the show, by the way, actually won a car on Wheel of Fortune like years ago.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was during Price is Right.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it was on Wheel of Fortune.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was on Wheel of Fortune.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because he even put up the clip of him winning.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, his Facebook cover photo is him solving the pumpkin pie or whatever his final thing was.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I have been in that Camaro, and it was a bitchin' Camaro.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a co-worker that won a car on Price is Right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, he won a car and like a China cabinet.
[SPEAKER_11]: And the sucky thing they never tell you about winning prizes like that is that you have to pay taxes.
[SPEAKER_06]: All these game show winners.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, Alan's here to lend his commentary.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, Alan.
[SPEAKER_12]: Talking about prices right just reminded me of something.
[SPEAKER_12]: There's going to be an all Plinko episode in September.
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, all Plinko.
[SPEAKER_12]: August or September.
[SPEAKER_12]: Google it.
[SPEAKER_11]: If I'm working, I'm just going to quit and watch.
[SPEAKER_07]: Viewing party.
[SPEAKER_06]: Kidding, kidding.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've never heard of a better reason to quit your job.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you get Plinko, and you get Plinko.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everyone gets a Plinko.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm surprised it's taken them 35 years or something to think about Plinko.
[SPEAKER_04]: If they want, see, PopCap, telling you, if you're smart, you market that son of a bitch on that show right there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Peggle 2, Plinko.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rob, you were getting a little pressed during Press Your Luck, weren't you?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I was getting very pressed during Press Your Luck.
[SPEAKER_06]: How many whammies did you have?
[SPEAKER_06]: I had three whammies in the first round and fucking... Okay, so I actually uploaded to my Twitter, twitter.com slash S-K-I-E, that's Sky, twitter.com slash Sky.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've always liked more followers.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I actually posted a picture that's like, Slidekick, I hate you so much.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because it's me and I have three whammies and no money.
[SPEAKER_06]: And he has no whammies.
[SPEAKER_06]: He has like $7,000.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I ended up with over $50,000.
[SPEAKER_10]: Were you like the unemployed man who memorized the patterns and just sat and watched it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, he was.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know what happened to that guy, by the way?
[SPEAKER_06]: He died.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, besides that.
[SPEAKER_11]: What?
[SPEAKER_11]: He went on all the trips and everything and ended up investing the money in this scheme.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh yeah, he lost it all.
[SPEAKER_11]: And he lost all of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, poor guy.
[SPEAKER_11]: If you come into money, be smart.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, you can have one of my two trips to Rio, Rob.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, shut up.
[SPEAKER_06]: It wasn't real.
[SPEAKER_06]: It wasn't real as the lengthy disclaimer when you boot up the game lets you know that the prizes are not real.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not a contest.
[SPEAKER_07]: If I could make money winning game show video games, I'd just quit my job and do that in Let's Plays.
[SPEAKER_11]: We could get you a string of pearls and an apron.
[SPEAKER_06]: OK, that's a little bit awkward.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: What were you going to say, DarkSakura, before I rudely cut you off?
[SPEAKER_11]: I forgot.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's for the best.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: No whammies.
[SPEAKER_11]: Stop.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkTetsuya says, I was just going to ask, are the patterns in the video game version like the old game show?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're a lot more randomized.
[SPEAKER_06]: I highly doubt Slidekick had the time to memorize them.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you hit X as fast as you can, you seem to never hit a whammy.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Slidekick figured that out in about five seconds.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, one thing... Cheater.
[SPEAKER_11]: One thing, too... Cheater!
[SPEAKER_11]: ...is that after this guy basically broke the system, earning all that money, they changed the patterns and added in an extra randomizer.
[SPEAKER_06]: So... Oh, yeah, he made them change the game show.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, and basically, they couldn't actually call him out on cheating because he did what anyone could do.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, no, he didn't cheat.
[SPEAKER_11]: They just told him he's not allowed to play again.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um...
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm gonna take all your money
[SPEAKER_06]: I would love, like, an uncensored game show on TV.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not necessarily that they have to have all the TNA and stuff, but, like, I'm just saying, you know, we're just like, fuck!
[SPEAKER_04]: God damn it!
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_04]: Why did I say that?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's like the wrong answer completely.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is motherfucking Jeopardy.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then you also get bonus points based on how well you're judged.
[SPEAKER_06]: Where all the trivia answers have to start with what the fuck.
[SPEAKER_06]: What the fuck is I don't care, Alex?
[SPEAKER_12]: That makes me think of The Price is Right where you're the really hard ones where you have to step on the floor to step out the price of the car.
[SPEAKER_12]: They always look to their family members and they can just be like, I fucking hate my family.
[SPEAKER_12]: You're all fucking walking home.
[SPEAKER_12]: Fuck you.
[SPEAKER_12]: And like Drew Carey's all really uncomfortable.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh god, alright Moving on, we're talking too long about game shows Actually you can never talk too long about game shows Is that the Press Your Luck game that I got you like ages ago?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, the DVD game, I still have that I was gonna say I've talked about before how badly I need to go on a reality game show And I don't think I could do Survivor Because if I didn't eat for 13 days I would be the biggest bitch I would get voted out so fast If I didn't eat for one day I'd be a bitch, let's be real
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't go on Big Brother.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, you would be a big bitch if you didn't have Pinkberry near you.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't go on Big Brother anymore because I don't know if y'all are following this season, but what a bunch of racists.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it's pretty sick in that house right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Paula Deen ain't got nothing on some of those people in the Big Brother house this season.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I was going to say there's a new show on ABC that's pretty fucking hilarious.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's called Whodunit.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's like Clue meets The Mole Which by the way, I know a lot of you judge reality TV shows And that's fine, a lot of it needs to be judged But The Mole was the best reality game show they ever had I'm like, if you're gonna try any reality TV, do The Mole So somebody decided to adapt The Mole into a Clue game called Whodunit But here's the great part Is that at the end of the episode Whoever scored the lowest on the quiz dies
[SPEAKER_06]: They become the victim in the next episode So the episode, literally, like the first episode aired, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: And so the guy who lost and didn't get the case right and got the lowest on the quiz He runs out at the very end, somebody set him on fire and he falls into the pool dead And he's all like, obviously it's all fake, it's makeup and all that stuff But all these people on Twitter were like, did they start killing people on TV?
[SPEAKER_06]: What the fuck?
[SPEAKER_11]: Ratings, oh my god Right?
[SPEAKER_06]: But I was like, dude
[SPEAKER_06]: He lost this game and he literally had to die in a fire.
[SPEAKER_06]: That is amazing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, did DarkSakura write this game?
[SPEAKER_11]: It's the closest we're going to get to Battle Royale.
[SPEAKER_06]: Happy Hunger Games.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's supposed to be a Hunger Games game show on CW this year.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, but it's not Hunger Games, but it's so fucking obviously a thirsty ripoff of the Hunger Games.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like, what?
[SPEAKER_11]: Wait, let me hear your book.
[SPEAKER_06]: What, the Hunger Games?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's on his Kindle.
Okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: This is why I hate Kindle.
[SPEAKER_11]: Shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a thing called the internet where it's probably there.
[SPEAKER_10]: I like books where I can smell paper and ink and cry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Somebody in chat has to know this show I'm talking about.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's on the CW.
[SPEAKER_06]: The CW doesn't have anything except the Whose Line Is It Anyway reboot starts in a couple weeks.
[SPEAKER_06]: Really soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll have to watch that.
[SPEAKER_11]: And it has the lady.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just googled CW Hunger Games show.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's called The Hunt.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Hunt.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not The Hunger Games.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's The Hunt.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just like it, though.
[SPEAKER_11]: I tell you, 10 years from now, Battle Royale.
[SPEAKER_06]: The one I can't wait for on ABC is called The Quest, which is supposed to be The Amazing Race meets a LARP.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh my god, that sounds awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: I would watch that one.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was like, how do I get cast for this show?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I would want to fucking go on the quest as a LARP.
[SPEAKER_11]: LARPers of the world unite.
[SPEAKER_06]: It would be amazing.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyway, it's like the producer of... I was a proud former LARPer, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's the amazing... Well, I did Rocky Horror Picture Show, which is really close, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's...
[SPEAKER_06]: The Amazing Race producers and the Lord of the Rings producers or something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Making it.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's when you go to a live action vampire game and you see the people actually rigged up with the fake blood and everything spraying it everywhere.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've seen the people throw the magic bags.
[SPEAKER_06]: The little bags that are supposed to be like, I'm throwing ice at you.
[SPEAKER_11]: You can't see me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh my god, oh my god, we need to have an OLARP.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, and for anyone... Who would pay money to charity, of course?
[SPEAKER_06]: A charity.
[SPEAKER_06]: If we did an OLARP, who would pay money?
[SPEAKER_06]: I would.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm broke.
[SPEAKER_11]: For the record, what I did to Rob was I did the Obfuscate thing, which is also stolen by John Cena if you watch wrestling.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wrestling Reference Bobby, uh, anyway.
[SPEAKER_11]: He does the waving his hand in his face and it's the you can't see where I am type thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, Melody was just asking me how she could raise money for her team and training thing that she's doing.
[SPEAKER_06]: O.L.
[SPEAKER_06]: Flarp.
[SPEAKER_06]: Larp.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, are you gonna do it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Come on, Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sounds so ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah!
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm so fucking excited.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_11]: And Rob?
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_11]: Here's the rule.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, here's the rule.
[SPEAKER_11]: We each pick a video game character.
[SPEAKER_11]: And we have to cosplay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_06]: You don't have to do Tingle.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can do your Sackboy.
[SPEAKER_11]: You should walk around in Sackboy.
[SPEAKER_06]: I already have a costume.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll do it when it's cold.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: We have to go out to Vacaville and the Nut Tree.
[SPEAKER_06]: and play in the 112 degree heat.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, for anyone who doesn't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's dead.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's on the ground.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's not moving.
[SPEAKER_11]: Behind the nut tree is where the old Wren Fairgrounds used to be.
[SPEAKER_11]: That would be perfect.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know where we used to do LARP, Rob?
[SPEAKER_11]: We used to do it in the courtyard at my college at the University of South Alabama.
[SPEAKER_11]: And because that's the only thing there is to do that's exciting in Alabama, it's still going on probably.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actdeft wants to know what does the F in FLARP stand for?
[SPEAKER_11]: You only know if you like Homestuck.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, of course, Ragenator says Loki should LARP his tingle.
[SPEAKER_06]: He won't.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's do some rapid-fire news because we're 12 minutes into Part B and haven't even touched rapid-fire news yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks, Slag Kick.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is all your fault.
[SPEAKER_04]: It would be potentially cooler, though, than wearing that Zack Boy costume because that thing is like two or three layers of sweats in the summer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, anyways.
[SPEAKER_04]: So Nordic Games, they've been acquiring and acquiring and acquiring.
[SPEAKER_04]: They bought up a bunch of the old THQ properties and now they're buying up some of Atari's properties including Desperados and Silver.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, and you may remember, Atari, you know, they've been selling off parts of their company.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, I wonder who's buying Marvel Metas, seriously.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, and I guess they, um, I'm not sure what they're gonna do with it, but, you know, make some westerns, I guess?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh, Silver, I've not really, I'm not familiar with, but I guess that came out, um, was an action RPG in, uh, on the PC and Dreamcast back in 99, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: Retro City Rampage has been adding some new updates, including mod support, which is pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can create your own vehicles and characters, fonts, color palettes, etc.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have a new Retro Plus mode, which adds some more visual effects, including soft shadows and doubling the number of colors on screen.
[SPEAKER_04]: and also I guess this is going to be coming on Steam via automatic update and then on Good Old Games you have to log in and just re-download I guess grab the 1.11 update
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: And then last but not least, Project Anarchy, a brand new mobile development toolkit from Havok.
[SPEAKER_04]: And did I mention it's free?
[SPEAKER_04]: So you'll be able to use it to create some pretty awesome 3D games and freely publish on Android, iOS, Tizen.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not sure what Tizen is.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I guess it also has a provisional license to develop for but not publish on Windows.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, and I guess it will support low-level C++ access, Lua scripting, debugging, and other fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: It includes tutorials and sample projects as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you want to check that out, I would imagine you just go to Havoc's website, and it should be there.
[SPEAKER_04]: What the hell is Tizen, though?
[SPEAKER_04]: I've never heard of Tizen.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like an operating system for some smartphones, tablets, and vehicle infotainment, smart TVs.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have not heard of that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Something else to build a console out of.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, well, the potentials of this could have been epic, but it was unearthed an old ad from the Consumer Electronics Show from years ago.
[SPEAKER_06]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_06]: Final Fantasy 2 was supposedly going to come out here at one point, but we all knew that.
[SPEAKER_06]: One of those big Lost Levels website or whatever kind of chronicles what happened with that game, and it didn't come out.
[SPEAKER_06]: But a lot of people didn't know this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Final Fantasy 3 was apparently planned at one point, but it clearly didn't get very far along.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's even some mock-up box art that shows the Nepto Dragon possibly there, some sea monsters clutching wood on a broken ship.
[SPEAKER_06]: Final Fantasy 2 and 3
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: That's really cool because, God, I can't wait to play this game all over again in HD.
[SPEAKER_06]: So pretty.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm just, like, so excited about this.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, very cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm less excited about this, but it's not going to stop me from getting the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Final Fantasy X and X-2 HD Remaster.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently, GameStop could be getting some type of limited edition exclusive or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a flyer out there that was dated June 26 that talked about a free limited edition upgrade if you pre-ordered the HD thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: However, this is saying this could have been an error on GameStop's part because they apparently removed said mention and Square Enix has not said anything about it and it's not on GameStop.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: So don't freak, y'all.
[SPEAKER_04]: It must be reparations for the whole Deus Ex issue.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that's right.
[SPEAKER_06]: That wasn't that long ago, all things considered.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow, also, this is cool, a lot of people don't even realize there was a Game Gear Mega Man game And it was out there, it had some different bosses too, I don't recall Or was it some of the ones from 3, it only had like 4 bosses in it There was a whole series of different portable Mega Man games Like there was the WonderSwan one, and there was one other that I can't remember But there was the Game Gear one
[SPEAKER_06]: The Game Gear version is on its way to the Nintendo 3DS eShop.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, we do have, well, Xbox One, as far as headsets, they have to be wired and they're going to be sold separately.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're not going to be packed in.
[SPEAKER_11]: And they're basically saying that the only thing that you're getting with it is going to be the Kinect sensor and the microphone in there, but no actual headset.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, trying to screw us out of more money, huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it was sort of like that, though, at the launch with the Xbox 360, only the premium set had a headset.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're basically saying that you can still talk to people, but you can't have a headset.
[SPEAKER_04]: Honestly, I don't like the standard headsets because I wear headphones, so you can't wear two sets of headphones at the same time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I've tried.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, that's how I do it on my headset.
[SPEAKER_04]: I tape a headset that I ripped apart, and I just have the boom part of the microphone on there, and I tape it to the side of my...
[SPEAKER_04]: on my headphones.
[SPEAKER_04]: It works just fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess I could use Kinect, but then I'd be yelling across the room, so that wouldn't be fun.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, in other news, and this has to do with the Wii U, the Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_11]: release may actually lose some characters.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're saying that they're working on getting as many characters in it as they can, but they may not have the full intended roster, although they will have, of course, the Wii Fit trainer fighting you with yoga.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love her.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, it's just like, if I knew that I could punch somebody with the warrior pose and have them go across the room, I'd be doing that more often.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's one of those things I never realized how much I loved the idea until it was announced.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm like, she should have been a character.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love the memes.
[SPEAKER_11]: Have you seen this already, cosplay?
[SPEAKER_07]: of the Wii Fit Trainer of the Wii Fit Trainer that's amazing and then of course the Villager and our Mega Man I almost wonder if we'll see something like not really like a Ultimate Marvel vs. Capcom you know but like a DLC Ultimate Smash Ultimate Smash with like new characters or something
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, what they're saying here is that, I mean, the other big reason they may have to cut people is time constraints.
[SPEAKER_11]: So they won't be able to bring everyone back.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I mean, then again, there was like, what, Solid Snake before and Sonic and some Fire Emblem characters that no one cared about?
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dan cared about.
[SPEAKER_06]: A lot of people care about.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some people will miss them.
[SPEAKER_06]: But yeah, I think some of those more like like I bet Captain Falcon will be in there with Roy and Mars or or no Star Fox will be in there.
[SPEAKER_06]: But like his little buddy, like Falco won't won't be there.
[SPEAKER_06]: It'll be the more secondary characters in some of those games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like Lucas from Earthbound.
[SPEAKER_06]: You mean like the palettes?
[SPEAKER_06]: I know people who would probably throw a fit if Lucas wasn't there.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll throw a fit if Ness isn't there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you know what?
[SPEAKER_11]: People throw fits for any reason.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because gamers hate everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe just get rid of the palette swap characters.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, the ones that are basically the same moveset and everything.
[SPEAKER_11]: As long as Zelda still has the chic transformation, I'll be happy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a must.
[SPEAKER_11]: But they need to put Daisy in there and have the back of her head eye laser.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know about the eyeball in the back of her head, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: I heard about that, yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, in the original Smash Bros., if you look at the Daisy trophy, if you happen to scroll in super close to the back of her head, there's an eyeball in the back of her head.
[SPEAKER_11]: And so now it's like this thing that like, you know what Mugen is, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: The fighting game creator?
[SPEAKER_11]: So for people who put Daisy in Mugen, they actually gave her a back of her head eyeball laser.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_11]: Which is the big, grandiose eyeball laser.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think it's hilarious.
[SPEAKER_11]: And people have tried to say, oh, well, it's not there in Mario Kart.
[SPEAKER_11]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_11]: She has a great big eye on the back of her head like a tumor.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's why her hair is so big.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's full of secrets and eyeballs.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's full of secrets.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm going to use that for anybody else, especially when my hair frizzes out into fro mode.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm just going to say it's full of secrets.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can thank Mean Girls.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, I haven't seen that.
[SPEAKER_06]: You should.
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_11]: Doesn't it have Sarah Michelle Gellar in it?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it's Lindsay Lohan before she was on with the drugs.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Rachel McAdams, is that her name?
[SPEAKER_11]: What was the one that had Sarah Michelle Gellar in it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Buffy?
[SPEAKER_11]: No, she was in another movie.
[SPEAKER_06]: Cruel Intentions.
[SPEAKER_11]: Cruel Intentions, that was it.
[SPEAKER_11]: That movie had a song that I liked, but I've never seen it either.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that's the one where you can see Sarah Michelle going, but I wanna fuck.
Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Were you volunteering?
[SPEAKER_11]: Sarah Michelle Gellar is an attractive lady.
[SPEAKER_11]: If you're Freddie Prinze Jr., then yes.
[SPEAKER_11]: So anyway, you know what, though?
[SPEAKER_11]: She does not look as attractive as she did on Buffy because she's all bone thin again now.
[SPEAKER_11]: And not, you know, in good shape.
[SPEAKER_11]: So anyway, okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: Former King of Fighters developers are having some issues.
[SPEAKER_11]: They were basically... They have an original 2D fighting game that they were...
[SPEAKER_11]: Looking to have some development on.
[SPEAKER_11]: It says that right now, and the game is called Yatagarasu, that they want to have it crowdfunded so that they can release the character in the game, and they're wanting it to be 10 playable characters at launch.
[SPEAKER_11]: They have a funding goal of $68,000 right now, and it's on Indiegogo, and it can go up if it needs to be.
[SPEAKER_11]: If it's not sucky like The King of Fighters 12 was, then go for it.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, I guess that does it for Rapid Fire News.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm a little opinionated when it comes to bad King of Fighters games, Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you?
[SPEAKER_06]: I would have never guessed.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: I figured it was appropriate, though, considering you just did a King of Fighters, or, well, sorta.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorta.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fatal Fury.
[SPEAKER_06]: King of Fighters prequel-ish.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, I'm going to do Art of Fighting next week, ew.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you really?
[SPEAKER_11]: No.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm going to do World Heroes Jet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you know what I'm going to do is the Fugle Question of the Week right now.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's Radio Fugle.
[SPEAKER_06]: Take Facebook and Google+, slam them together, and you get one clusterfuck of a social networking site.
[SPEAKER_06]: You also get the word foogle, which we ask a question every week of our Facebook and Google fan communities, and we read some of the answers here on the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: I might read them all tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see how I'm feeling.
[SPEAKER_06]: I haven't looked.
[SPEAKER_06]: How many are on Facebook?
[SPEAKER_06]: There's not a ton.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, I can probably get through them all tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Ouya officially hit shelves this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you get one?
[SPEAKER_06]: Why or why not?
[SPEAKER_06]: What do you think about these mobile platform consoles, especially considering there are more to come, such as Mojo and the rumors of an official Google Android console?
[SPEAKER_06]: And GameSick.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh yeah, I said and more.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, Red Entertainment says, unless the Ouya is something that'll make it so it's not so damn fucking hot outside, I will not be buying one right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe I'll buy an Ouya in the future when the outside world is not trying to cook me alive.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, to be fair... That answer wins.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're done.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, to be fair, one thing I do like about the Ouya controller is the face plates are made of metal, and so they're nice and cool on your hands.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll read other answers then.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, so moving to Evil, E3VL.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, unless I see more exclusive content for the system.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also, the Ouya seems to have had bad customer service as of late, having shipped their console to retailers before providing all their Kickstarter backers with one first.
[SPEAKER_06]: At least provide the backers with some store credit or free games instead of just apologizing.
Excellent.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll get into that in a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're definitely going to be getting into that in a little bit.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nietzsche says, Between the reports of horrible controller input lag and poor performance due to outdated hardware, I have no desire to get the Ouya.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was a fun idea, but in my opinion, didn't work out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Travis H says, Asus transformer tablet plus HDMI cable equals an Ouya I can take on the go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Honestly, the only thing that I think that piqued my interest about the Ouya is having a system to throw emulators on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Kind of like an all-in-one super nostalgia machine.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I already have that with my tablet, so I'm out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow, lots of hate for the Ouya on Google+.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see if Facebook's any different.
[SPEAKER_06]: Gally89 says, Nope, I don't see the need.
[SPEAKER_06]: Juan, not for me at least.
[SPEAKER_06]: Daniel S says, Everything I hear about the Ouya is that it's a piece of crap.
[SPEAKER_06]: And putting more Android-based platforms is exactly what they need because market confusion and dilution is great.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think there's a slash Sark in there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Clover Nikon says, My wife and I enjoy playing games on our Google Nexus 7-inch Android Jelly Bean tablet.
[SPEAKER_06]: My wife playing Simpsons Tap Game, I play Star Wars Pinball, and my father-in-law playing those Pokey Magic slot machine games when he borrows it.
[SPEAKER_06]: If a shop here near me sold the Ouya, I would definitely buy one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, there you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Finally, an answer we can say is a positive one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Degenerate Johnny says,
[SPEAKER_06]: says, it all seems oxymoronish to have a stationary platform for mobile games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Honestly, I don't very much care for mobile games, 3DS and Vita excluded.
[SPEAKER_06]: They don't offer the same amount of excitement and enjoyment that the big three consoles offer.
[SPEAKER_06]: Console developers, including Valve, should take a lesson from the auto industry, and this is my Michigan side talking, there can be only three, and that's currently Nintendo, Sony, and Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_06]: Otherwise, you are doomed to walk the unfortunate path of the 3DO, Jaguar, and God rest its soul, the Dreamcast.
[SPEAKER_06]: Aww.
[SPEAKER_06]: Aw, that answer made me sad.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, but the difference between the 3DO and the Jaguar and the Dreamcast is that the Dreamcast wasn't shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: Word.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also, the 80s called and would like to tell you that there is room for more than three consoles, although then again it might lead to another crash.
[SPEAKER_06]: We had the whole home computing wars, but that's another episode of the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, we talked about that a lot last week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, ClericalEra404 left a pretty long answer here, but...
[SPEAKER_06]: Since I like them, I'll read it.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I did not get one.
[SPEAKER_06]: It has clever ideas, offering digital copies of games to first demo and then decide to upgrade to the full version, having an easy setup of plugging in an HDMI cable, a library of 200 games and counting, being able to run emulators to play games from older systems.
[SPEAKER_06]: Almost a retro gamer's dream come true.
[SPEAKER_06]: But the old saying is true that a system is only as good as the software.
[SPEAKER_06]: And unfortunately, so far, it has been able to really wow... I'm thinking it hasn't been able to really wow anyone yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: and more.
[SPEAKER_06]: Code Man says, no, I don't have a justification for buying one.
[SPEAKER_06]: It would just make my wife more addicted to Candy Crush, and I definitely don't need that.
[SPEAKER_06]: LOL.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's so much confusion with the platform, I think.
[SPEAKER_04]: And there's no Candy Crush on it, thank God.
[SPEAKER_04]: First off, okay, so what?
[SPEAKER_04]: The console runs Android.
[SPEAKER_04]: It doesn't make it a fucking mobile console.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's...
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's an operating system that runs Android.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just like Android runs on some of those smart TVs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Does it mean your TV is a fucking mobile console?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it's not.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a TV.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's just an operating system that you're developing games for.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, a lot of the first games that are coming over are going to be ports of games that are on the Android marketplace because you're porting an Android game to Android with some additional APKs in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, of course, it's going to be like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that's the thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: The whole draw of this console is that it's an indie console.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, I'm not saying that there's everything that's positive about it, because yes, there's issues with the controller being, well, especially the first backer controllers, which I'm going through an issue right now where I'm trying to get mine replaced, because the analog sticks don't work correctly.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's on Ouya.
[SPEAKER_04]: They need to fix that shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, you know, since we're getting into some topic about, you know, Ouya...
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, can I read the rest of the answers here?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_04]: You still want to yell at people.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, no, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll save that for a second.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkCharger says, I have a main cabinet for my emulation needs and everything else that I want can be handled by my consoles or smartphones and tablets.
[SPEAKER_06]: An Ouya would be the epitome of a superfluous purchase.
[SPEAKER_06]: AZHP says I didn't get one because I didn't realize it came out this week if there's no advertising how can I know when it's coming out I might pick one up soon for emulation purposes though and lastly Osfer says I'm just not interested the new consoles from the big three are the only ones that really have my attention that's all the answers from Facebook and Google thanks to y'all for answering join us on Facebook and Google Plus for next week's question alright slide kick you gonna get a new yeah
[SPEAKER_07]: I was actually a very early backer.
[SPEAKER_07]: Honestly, if I saw how it played out, I don't think I would have backed them.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: You heard about all the mess with E3 and how rude they were.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was there.
[SPEAKER_06]: I took a picture of the big truck parked in front of the booth.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Ouya thing at E3 was more of a developer showcase than it was the console.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's too bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's better than last year's Yu-Gi-Oh!
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like, you know, I just don't know if that's a good precedent to set for gaming consoles.
[SPEAKER_07]: Even though it's not directly trying to compete with the big three, but, you know, I just, I don't...
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I actually, mine did arrive, and I've yet to unbox it, so I probably should at some point.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_07]: But Captain Spike also backed on Kickstarter before I did, and he hasn't received it yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, I'll hook mine up eventually.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hope that I don't have any controller issues.
[SPEAKER_07]: When did yours arrive?
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, it arrived in late April or May.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, your controller's fucked.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was late May is when they fixed that shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: See, I didn't back this for that reason.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's all fixed now.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's fixed now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, but not for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well...
[SPEAKER_04]: It's fixed if I don't use the NUYA controller.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank God I can pair a PlayStation 3 controller to it, but the only thing is, not all games, you have to account for that, so they have to program in those button mappings as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can, you know, for a lot of things, like emulators, I can play with the PlayStation 3 controller and it works great.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's how I knew it was the controller, not the console.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know,
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm gonna get into it in just a second.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some of the customer service things.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, if... Why don't we go back into the gaming news?
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, why don't you start us off with a possibly related topic?
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's talk about this.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is great.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is fantastic.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right when they launched, there was two Kickstarter updates.
[SPEAKER_04]: First there was one like, Hey!
[SPEAKER_04]: We launched our console!
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, we couldn't have done it without you.
[SPEAKER_04]: To which there was a bunch of replies, Hey, you fucktard!
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't gotten my fucking console yet that I backed last year.
[SPEAKER_04]: Where the fuck is it?
[SPEAKER_04]: And then...
[SPEAKER_04]: Julie comes out and says, I'm pissed!
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm so pissed that we haven't been able to get some of those consoles to you.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I promised that we'd ship them all, and I don't know what's going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have people in, you know, Hong Kong that are checking into it and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll tell you what's going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: You shipped it via fucking DHL.
[SPEAKER_04]: DHL Global, first off, so slow-ass ship...
[SPEAKER_04]: in the first place, and then you had to pass off to, because it was their global logistics mail or something like that, where they pass it off to the U.S.
[SPEAKER_04]: Postal Service.
[SPEAKER_04]: It takes so fucking long.
[SPEAKER_04]: They didn't know what the hell was going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: It basically said, oh, yeah, you're going to get an update on your tracking number.
[SPEAKER_04]: It'll become active within a couple days.
[SPEAKER_04]: It took a week.
[SPEAKER_07]: My tracking number was never active.
[SPEAKER_07]: It just showed up one day.
[SPEAKER_04]: You were lucky if that thing showed up in the first place.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then on top of all that, you had the issues where you were getting bummed controllers with the earlier backer additions, which I did.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's annoying because it doesn't work correctly.
[SPEAKER_04]: And so I replied.
[SPEAKER_04]: I sent a ticket for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm like, hey, I need this shit fixed.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I sent them a ticket.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I understand that they're a little busy with their console launch and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I sent it on Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_04]: They got back to me today.
[SPEAKER_04]: And here's what their response was.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like, as we continue to evolve the OUYA, making constant improvements to our product and blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_04]: You got a copy-paste from an outsourced customer service company.
[SPEAKER_04]: I bet anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not even outsourced.
[SPEAKER_04]: It took so long.
[SPEAKER_04]: And basically saying, you know, the goal is you should look into the fact and see if you can solve your problem there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm like, I have a fucking defective controller.
[SPEAKER_04]: Your fact doesn't help me there.
[SPEAKER_04]: It doesn't say anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I sent a reply.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm like, listen, I have a defective controller.
[SPEAKER_04]: I need to replace this shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because you know what's going to happen if I can't get it replaced?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to go to the store.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to buy a controller.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to replace it with my controller.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm going to return it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a good idea.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, shame on you.
[SPEAKER_06]: But that's kind of...
[SPEAKER_06]: It's clever.
[SPEAKER_06]: I should not be supporting that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I did something similar to that, but not really.
[SPEAKER_07]: When Sonic Spinball came out, I got it for full price, and then Target had it for like $5 or $7 less, so I bought it at Target and returned it to Toys R Us.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, I mean, it's not really like repackaging it, but I was like 10, and I felt like, ooh, what if they find out that this is actually from Toys R Us?
[SPEAKER_04]: and Defective Allowments.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's all right.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're used to Defectives, but seriously, if they're not going to solve my problem because they're claiming that they're too busy right now, well, I'm sorry, but it's going to be hard for me to continue supporting your console if you're not going to give me a controller that fucking works since I only have one controller anyways and your additional controller is $60 fucking dollars.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nope, not going to buy those.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_11]: So you're saying most of the cost of the system is the one controller that doesn't work?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's their claim.
[SPEAKER_04]: But here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like I don't understand why the whole thing was a clusterfuck to begin with.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I know it's going to get better.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I actually haven't touched my console since May.
[SPEAKER_04]: I did loan it to a friend, a co-worker.
[SPEAKER_04]: He wanted to check it out for stuff, and so he did my updates and everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess the interface is a lot nicer now.
[SPEAKER_04]: But a lot of the things that they promised, obviously, they didn't come through with.
[SPEAKER_04]: One of the major ones, this console can be easily rooted.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're going to be able to root it immediately once you get it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can't do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can't do that at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's very hacker friendly.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it's not.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not hacker friendly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Aside from the fact that you can sideload.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why not channel this energy into a complaint with the Better Business Bureau?
[SPEAKER_11]: Because they're not going to do anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's not that whether they do something or not, it's still going to hurt their reputation and prevent them from being able to do business.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure there's tons of people who have already done that just for their backers.
[SPEAKER_11]: Or is that just an excuse not to do it?
[SPEAKER_04]: It is an excuse not to do it because I just don't care.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't care enough.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not like I dropped a ton of money.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was $100 a year ago, and I just don't care.
[SPEAKER_11]: And that's why companies get away with this because people don't care.
[SPEAKER_04]: He wants to internet rage.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want my controller to work and that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then that's fine.
[SPEAKER_11]: So write them about it and tell them you're going to file a complaint and see how long it takes them to reply because trust me, they will reply.
[SPEAKER_04]: They won't reply.
[SPEAKER_04]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_11]: The moment you bring up the three, you know, the Better Business Bureau, especially for any company that wants to continue to do business, they tend to jump on that, especially if they've got other people doing the same.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: The next time I send them an update, I'll say I'll contact the Better Business Bureau and we'll see them do nothing because, you know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let me read some of the written word in our chat room at live.vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: Burr says, even the positive reviews are like, I like mine, but I haven't bought a game for it yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just played the demos.
[SPEAKER_04]: Seriously, a lot of the games on there are free to play right now, and everything has a free version of it, so yeah, a lot of it you don't need to necessarily buy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Codeman says this is just a huge shit on the people who backed.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is really inexcusable that they, you know, they got limited supply of the stores because they wanted to make sure they had that retail presence or whatever, but at the same time, they made a promise to everyone that backed them to, you know, deliver on that.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if they can't deliver to, you know, people that ordered their console, I'm sorry, backed their Kickstarter and got a free console, however the fuck you want to word that, because you're not technically ordering anything, but, you know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: They made a promise and they couldn't even fulfill that.
[SPEAKER_04]: They didn't give any firm numbers to what was shipping.
[SPEAKER_04]: They just did this really generic line graph thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: At a point at the beginning of June or something, they were like, all the consoles have shipped.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: They've all shipped because no one's gotten them yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, yeah, it was really weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm kind of curious to see what it's going to look like in three months' time.
[SPEAKER_04]: If they're going to follow through with everything they promised about this console.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because right now...
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, well, I gotta move on.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sure Loki could do an entire episode just about his hatred towards this whole thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Lesson learned.
[SPEAKER_06]: Would you back another console after what happened to this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I would, but it would have to be a lot more research done into it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's how I feel, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not that Google's gonna put a Kickstarter out there for a console, but it would have to be like if...
[SPEAKER_04]: It would be different.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a different console that I keep seeing that they're trying to pitch.
[SPEAKER_04]: This guy is kind of doing this, oh, it can do everything and stuff that you can't imagine.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's amazing.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Oton or whatever, it's like this autonomous console is basically supposed to procedurally generate games.
[SPEAKER_04]: and that sounds neat I guess but it's just like the stuff that he's promising is ridiculous and so like it's just like yeah I'm not gonna back in any of this but he's planning on doing a Kickstarter so you'll probably see that at some point because he tried to get in unfortunately it was we got in and then they started requiring that anything that's electronics or something like that has to have an actual prototype a physical prototype made not just a concept so that's a problem
[SPEAKER_07]: I think I would be reluctant to spend as much on Kickstarter anymore.
[SPEAKER_07]: Usually I just put in about $15 to $20 for a game or something, but that was the first big Kickstarter amount that I put in, and I don't think I'd be as likely to do it anymore.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, well, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Speaking of people who aren't likely to do certain things anymore, Bethesda, the vice president of PR and marketing, Pete Hines, in an interesting statement with, I believe it was Eurogamer, talking about, quote, We don't have Facebook stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: We don't have mobile stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: We feel like we really know who we are and what we're good at.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, you know, you don't see Skyrim mobile or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: A while ago it was social games that were all the rage and people were asking, why aren't we doing Facebook?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's not what we do and that's no longer a big deal.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we didn't run after it and now we're not running away from it.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're just going to kind of stick to what we feel is best.
[SPEAKER_06]: By the way, it doesn't just extend to Facebook and mobile.
[SPEAKER_06]: Quote, we have nothing announced in development for Wii U. It's not something we've done anything for previously.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't even remember the last time we've done a Nintendo title.
[SPEAKER_06]: I do.
[SPEAKER_06]: What was it?
[SPEAKER_04]: It was Brunswick Bowling.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm serious.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what it was.
[SPEAKER_06]: We don't have anything.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that was just everybody trying to run off of the popularity of Wii Sports, of which bowling was huge.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was.
[SPEAKER_06]: We don't have anything now whether or not we would in the future is to be determined.
[SPEAKER_06]: As for why, I guess I'd rather not go into that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, well, shit, now we all have to sit here and make it up, because he won't go into it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, what it is just that the Wii U is a... They don't believe in it?
[SPEAKER_06]: They don't think something like Skyrim is capable of running on Wii U?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's just, once again, it's cost-risk type thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: The cost it's going to take to develop a game or port a game over to that platform versus the amount of money you're going to make with the limited marketplace for it right now because there's just not a lot of people that bought the console.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's going to change.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're going to hear a lot of people more willing to develop for it when there's more people that bought the console.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's going to take another year or so with some of these first party games to kind of drive some console sales to get more third parties involved, but if it doesn't work, if the third parties, or I should say the first party games don't drive enough console sales, then yeah, you're going to hear a lot more of this.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think it's a huge loss because, I mean, what, there hasn't really been a Bethesda game, like I said, since Brunswick Bowling, so it's not like
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, I do, and I found it on Game Politics, which I love Game Politics.
[SPEAKER_11]: If you want to see what goes on in the world around video games, it doesn't necessarily have to do with release dates, then that's the place to go.
[SPEAKER_11]: But there was a conservative political website called The Daily Caller that said that a Texas teenager was making a joke while playing League of Legends.
[SPEAKER_11]: and the joke was and I'm going to quote oh yeah I'm real messed up in the head I'm going to shoot up a school full of kids and eat their still beating hearts followed by a JK and lol well there were people who took this seriously actually a Canadian lady
[SPEAKER_11]: Who looked up the teenager's address and noted where he lived and reported it to the police And he's been in jail ever since He actually spent his 19th birthday in jail And if he's convicted, he's going to spend up to 8 years in prison And this is basically for making a terrorist threat
[SPEAKER_11]: It just goes to show what this is.
[SPEAKER_11]: Basically, it's an ignorant kid.
[SPEAKER_11]: His dad said he doesn't watch the news, he doesn't read up on any current events.
[SPEAKER_11]: He's just a dumb kid making a threat.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry, but if you're on the internet, how do you not hear about stuff?
[SPEAKER_07]: Hearing about stuff that other people are talking about.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, even apart from that, there's people...
[SPEAKER_11]: Who will all the time say really horrible things.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, trying to threaten somebody or exert their own personal dominance over somebody else.
[SPEAKER_11]: And there's actually a petition out.
[SPEAKER_11]: I hate change.org just because when you sign any petition there, you get a bajillion emails.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I hate it.
[SPEAKER_11]: But there is a petition up on change.org right now to try to get him out of jail.
[SPEAKER_11]: Which, I don't know if it's going to work.
[SPEAKER_11]: But the whole thing that this boils down to, and it's sort of almost an epidemic when it comes to online play.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: And it's not just the whole terrorist threat type statements.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because they're saying that there's kids everywhere being gotten in trouble for this.
[SPEAKER_11]: But for the ones who go, oh, I'm going to rape you.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I'm sure they're not meaning they're going to go out and take somebody against their will.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's a means of exerting dominance.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, it's, you know, a top of the ones says, you know, I will... Just relax and let it happen.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_11]: Rob, I am disgusted.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, you know, like the whole... I'm just the G-rated version of that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, but on top of that, there's also ones going, well, I'm just going to beat the shit out of you or... I mean, just with all the cyberbullying that's been in the recent... Or the tits or GTFO.
[SPEAKER_06]: A lot of people say stupid shit on the internet.
[SPEAKER_06]: What a shock.
[SPEAKER_11]: But what we're looking into now is that people actually taking some of them seriously.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I firmly believe that this kid was just being a stupid kid.
[SPEAKER_11]: Just saying something that he thought was going to make himself sound a little more puffed up and a little bit more of a badass.
[SPEAKER_06]: You have eight years in prison.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, I mean, I would even think by now, even if they dropped the whole thing, he's fucking learned his lesson.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, send the cops to his house to scare the shit out of him.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, like, that's how you learn your lesson.
[SPEAKER_11]: If I had a way to do that with everyone who said anything that out of context could remotely be taken as threatening or any type of bragging of said threatening action, I would do it in a heartbeat just to scare people into behaving even though it shouldn't take scaring people into behaving.
[SPEAKER_11]: They should just fucking know how to behave like a human being.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's asking a lot from people.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's asking a lot, I know.
[SPEAKER_11]: and I mean and it goes without saying that when you know you put these people behind a mask of anonymity that they think that they've got fair you know fair game to say anything that they want that there's no repercussion in this case the lady knew who he was and called on him you know I actually my point with this is that I would actually even express this as a cautionary tale
[SPEAKER_11]: Put it out there for any of these people who are going to be douches online.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not that our listeners would ever do that.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, because our listeners are kind, intelligent, beautiful, handsome.
[SPEAKER_11]: non-bigoted lovely people.
[SPEAKER_11]: And if you are bigoted, don't tell me or I'll beat you up.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, I wouldn't beat anybody up.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think I hear sirens heading towards your house, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_07]: A po-po is coming for Jamie.
[SPEAKER_11]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_11]: I would just judge them really harshly.
[SPEAKER_11]: But, you know, you should never bring up something that you know is going to be
[SPEAKER_11]: Triggering.
[SPEAKER_11]: I hate to use the word, but something that's going to be triggering to somebody.
[SPEAKER_11]: There are people who lost family and friends in any number of terrorist attacks.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know people personally who have lost family members.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's a really awful thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: And when you bring up something like that, when there's such a volatile environment around just that concept, then you are really asking for a pile of shit.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, I think, like, games included, but, you know, just as everything moves more with more online communication, I mean, I think people just need to really be more mindful, and, like, we need to, you know, educate people of, you know, but, I mean, again, that's asking a lot.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm going to quote my granddaddy, and my granddaddy was a great guy from, you know, Bridgeport, Connecticut.
[SPEAKER_11]: He was our Yankee when I grew up in the South.
[SPEAKER_11]: He always said, put brain and gear before mouth in motion.
[SPEAKER_11]: His other catchphrase was, don't be an instigator and an agitator.
[SPEAKER_11]: But, I mean, those are two really good pieces of advice.
[SPEAKER_11]: You don't want to stir up the hornet's nest.
[SPEAKER_11]: You have to gently remove it to where you don't get stung in the process or no one else get hurt.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, it's the same thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I think that with this kid, yeah, he doesn't deserve to be locked up, but he did deserve to have a stern talking to, at least.
[SPEAKER_11]: To have some sort of repercussion.
[SPEAKER_06]: Scared straight.
[SPEAKER_11]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_11]: Or maybe he's scared gay, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Whatever, whatever.
[SPEAKER_11]: You're the one who told me to go gaily forward.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: So anyway, I think that in any of these cases, yeah, they need to drop it with Kid.
[SPEAKER_11]: He's clearly learned his lesson.
[SPEAKER_11]: But to everybody, just think before you speak.
[SPEAKER_11]: And instead of reacting to something that someone has said or something that you've seen or losing a game, boo-hoo, go cry me a fucking river.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_11]: Don't react.
[SPEAKER_11]: Think and act.
[SPEAKER_06]: End of story.
[SPEAKER_06]: I apologize after our press our luck game slide kick for threatening to kill you and leave your corpse out on the porch for the crows to pick at.
[SPEAKER_06]: Didn't you say you were going to pee on my corpse too?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I probably did.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I was going to hit you with a bug net repeatedly since you like Animal Crossing so much.
[SPEAKER_11]: I hear the sirens again, they're coming back this way I'm sorry, I shouldn't joke about that I would actually still like to encourage our listeners to keep a level head Don't react, think and act
[SPEAKER_11]: That's my new catchphrase.
[SPEAKER_06]: You should have a little McGruff the Crime Dog saying at the end of every episode.
[SPEAKER_06]: You should make some YouTube gaming PSAs.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like Jamie's Gaming Stern Advice.
[SPEAKER_06]: I almost said gameys.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like Wanda Sykes' Knock It Off.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then you know what's going to happen is I'm going to get a ton of people commenting on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_11]: Show Me Your Boobs, Get Back in the Kitchen, Rape, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_11]: And so I'm going to have to just single out each and every one of them, trace their IPs, and send them a letter.
[SPEAKER_07]: Backtrace them through the internet, through the cyber.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or just disable comments.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what I do.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I've actually done that before where I got one of those stupid, you know, so-and-so rape.
[SPEAKER_11]: But it came through a source that I was able to track back as IP.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was on a forum.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think it was a DDR Freak back in the day.
[SPEAKER_11]: I love all those people who say, oh, well, I just found your Facebook.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm posting it back where your mom can see it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, but then some trolls make it really successfully and it makes me very bitter.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm having a drink as I say that.
[SPEAKER_11]: In some cases, it's when you remove that mask of anonymity that they really straighten up.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_06]: Degenerate Johnny in chat says, go to shitsenders.com and send them a cow pie.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a real thing?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh my god, that's great.
[SPEAKER_06]: Captain Spike, if you're listening, happy birthday.
[SPEAKER_11]: Actually, you know what I want to do?
[SPEAKER_11]: And I don't know if something like this exists, because you know how there's like the National Sex Offender Registry?
[SPEAKER_11]: I want to do the Internet Offender Registry.
[SPEAKER_07]: National Gaming Douchebag Registry?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, well, if you can do... Slander, slander, lawsuit, slander.
[SPEAKER_11]: If you can do soandsoparkslikeanasshole.com, then you can do shitpeoplesaidontheinternet.com.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, I'm just saying.
[SPEAKER_06]: Captain Spike is in chat, by the way, and says, rude.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sure we have lots of other thoughts on this.
[SPEAKER_06]: I invite you guys to email us, mailbag at orange lounge radio dot com.
[SPEAKER_06]: Although we are definitely going to change that email address in the coming weeks.
[SPEAKER_06]: But for now, you can still use that.
[SPEAKER_06]: There'll be plenty of announcement when we flip it over.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mailbag at orange lounge radio dot com.
[SPEAKER_06]: Meanwhile... Everyone's doing emails these days.
[SPEAKER_11]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, Queen City has a national douche burr registry, and Fifth Dream says dbagshaming.com.
[SPEAKER_11]: I am all for that.
[SPEAKER_11]: I would do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: We have to run it through Sweden so that we don't get... Loki, we need something a little less serious here.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_04]: So...
[SPEAKER_04]: Molly Jam, Part 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: This one's going to be a little different.
[SPEAKER_04]: Instead of basing it off of the fake Peter Molyneux Twitter account and those kind of ideas, these are based off of actual quotes from Peter Molyneux.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's really weird.
[SPEAKER_07]: Can you read the one that was included in that article?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I can do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: In fact, here is some of the stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think a lot of this is going to be very dirty.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's you Americans.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's something about nipples you hate.
[SPEAKER_04]: If this were Germany, we'd be romping around naked on stage here.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that could become a game.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Neckbreaker!
[SPEAKER_04]: I like it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're explorers who have just discovered this new continent of emotion.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'd actually play that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It would probably be very cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wish I had some time machine and could go back two weeks.
[SPEAKER_04]: You live by your mistakes for sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: When you rip your fingers on the screen, you tear the landscape apart with your physical hands.
[SPEAKER_04]: It just feels amazing, man.
[SPEAKER_04]: It feels amazing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_06]: They have 48 hours to make a game out of these quotes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, there's like 22 quotes here.
[SPEAKER_07]: The one about ripping the screen would have to be an iOS title.
[SPEAKER_04]: I remember hearing about this last year.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can eliminate starvation or you can double it.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can empty the treasury or you can fill it with gold and rub it all over your body.
[SPEAKER_07]: That game sounds hot.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, another Atari adult game.
[SPEAKER_04]: will the first female nudity give you a success or will it turn off an audience what is that gonna be I gotta see that I'm not punishing you for button mashing I'm rewarding you for not button mashing and that's a really big distinction that could be a rhythm game alright anyhow show me the games when you're doing it in multiplayer it feels incredible I love that so the theme is gonna be adult games then
[SPEAKER_07]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, well, maybe some of these games that come out of Moley Jam could be pitched to Dave & Buster's Arcade Chain.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, Dave & Buster's, of course, it's Chuck G's results.
[SPEAKER_11]: It used to be the annual site of my birthday every year where I would play Chuck.
[SPEAKER_06]: It stopped for some reason.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, because they got rid of Battletech.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, anyhow, Dave and Busters, along with Comedy Central, VH1, and MTV, that whole network thing, is putting on this contest called the Next Big Game Search.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you can see this at nextgame.cc.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can fill out a form.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can do its ideas, their pitches for a mobile app, larger-than-life arcade game, or simply some improvements for an already classic game.
[SPEAKER_06]: you'll be judged on originality, ease of play, family fun it has to be suitable for people of all ages so some of those nudity games won't be eligible gameplay experience and difficulty the prizes the grand prize is Dave and Buster's Create Your Game and Free Games for Life
[SPEAKER_06]: First runner-up, $5,000 in gameplay at Dave & Buster's, and second runner-up gets $500 in gameplay.
[SPEAKER_06]: The contest runs through July 15th.
[SPEAKER_06]: You have to be a resident of the U.S.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm telling you what, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you go and submit an OLR Dream Game and you win this competition, patent pending, and you owe us a chunk of your winnings.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're going to buy us a hell of a nice meal at Dave & Buster's.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's all I'm saying.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can record live from Dave & Buster's.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, that's right.
[SPEAKER_06]: We should go submit some of our favorite dream game ideas.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just do them all.
[SPEAKER_06]: This will be fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: Can you imagine if the winning game out of this was WhatTheyPlay.com, Snap, or Puzzle Sluts?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it has to be for all ages.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't think that the Roseville Dave & Buster's has the DDR anymore.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's sad.
[SPEAKER_11]: Answering Misty in chat room because she asked.
[SPEAKER_11]: Besides that, the Roseville Dave & Buster's is the size of a closet.
[SPEAKER_11]: No one goes there anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, when you have a Dave & Buster's that's smaller than Times Square Dave & Buster's, it's a problem.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, let's go to the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_06]: Every week you guys email us, mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com and we sift through the emails that are mixed in with all the Asian spam that we get.
[SPEAKER_11]: and... We have a lot of Asian spam this time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh my god, and Russian spam.
[SPEAKER_06]: And French spam.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like, just when we thought the French spam and Russian spam was done with, now it's... Zoot le porn!
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mailbag at orangeauntradio.com, DarkSakura, dive in the mailbag, pull out some emails.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, um... Hello, guys.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_11]: OLR, the video game podcast where every gamer has a voice, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, I'm gonna offer up mine to say, girl, please.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ocarina of Time is not an overrated game.
[SPEAKER_11]: It is as deserving of praise just as much as Link to the Past is.
[SPEAKER_06]: Next email.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey, Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_11]: To quote a video game, sit your ass down in that chair and drink your goddamn tea.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hearts, hearts, hearts, hearts.
[SPEAKER_11]: It is, okay, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, the major thing that determines which you have an affinity for is the one you grew up playing first.
[SPEAKER_11]: Mine obviously was Ocarina, but I also grew up playing A Link to the Past on Game Boy Advance.
[SPEAKER_11]: I have many fond memories of playing through that game, just as I do with Ocarina of Time, but Ocarina moved me on a deeper level and made me into the gamer I am today.
[SPEAKER_11]: For the record, I actually really like both of them about equally.
[SPEAKER_11]: It depends on the mood I'm in.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I really like them both.
[SPEAKER_07]: I really like Majora's Mask too.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's like, I really love lasagna, but I also really, really like sushi.
[SPEAKER_06]: I really like Link to the Past, and that's the end of that sentence.
[SPEAKER_11]: This brings me to two questions about your opinions on Ocarina of Time specifically for Rob.
[SPEAKER_11]: 1.
[SPEAKER_11]: You mentioned that you really like Twilight Princess.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hell, I did too.
[SPEAKER_11]: I caused a flood warning for all of Northeast Ohio with how much I came buckets over Link turning into a wolf.
[SPEAKER_06]: Came buckets?
[SPEAKER_11]: I thought I was thinking cried, but it's came buckets.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sexy chat.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sticky.
[SPEAKER_11]: But why are you so fond of a game that took a lot of cues from Ocarina of Time?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, Rob, why?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, Rob, why?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because, next question.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, especially with all the waggle technology being new and it was something that was a little bit outside of Wii Sports.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I think also kind of getting to see the game with more, like, you know, in Ocarina of Time, the 3D was still so early on.
[SPEAKER_06]: You had a lot of very blocky textures and very solid colors and, you know, things.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I realized at the time there were a lot of people that were very imaginative and it didn't matter.
[SPEAKER_06]: But you have to remember, there were a lot of us
[SPEAKER_06]: and my generation that grew up on the 2D games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like you say that, you know, Ocarina of Time was from your generation.
[SPEAKER_06]: We were a little more stubborn when it came to getting into the 3D.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like I was cool with Mario Kart.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like Mario 64.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think it deserves all the praise that it gets.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you an N64 hater?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not an N64 hater.
[SPEAKER_11]: So you're saying you didn't pee your pants when Star Fox came out?
[SPEAKER_06]: Ocarina of Time Ocarina of Time
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright Number two, a while back I remember you mentioning that you're not a big fan of Metroid Prime You didn't like the direction Nintendo took the series and that it just didn't have the same feeling of the older games like Super Metroid Do you think that this has to do with why you didn't like Ocarina of Time and the fact that both games were a shift to 3D?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, but I like Metroid Prime 3 for the record Did you just not like that change and wish the game stayed as top-down Zelda or side-scrolling Metroid games?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes and no, because I still stand pretty hard for Zelda 2, which even Miyamoto himself has issues with.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't like Zelda 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that shifted back and forth, but I'll defend that game as pretty fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: Dan will agree with you, just saying.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's hard as hell, but beating that game when I was a kid, I'm not going to be able to do that again.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've tried.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's tough.
[SPEAKER_07]: What do you think about Wind Waker?
[SPEAKER_06]: I honestly didn't play enough of it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't play enough of it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Dan beat Wind Waker and he really liked it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I just couldn't get into it.
[SPEAKER_06]: If I can borrow the HD one or get it on Gamefly or something, I'll give it another try.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, Rob, I can lend you mine.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you know, there's the HD remake coming out on the Wii U. I'd like to try it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, you and your HD.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_11]: Thanks for reading and sorry for the slightly longer email, but I just got to defend my first and favorite gaming love that is Ocarina of Time, and that's from Osfer.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I don't need to know about you, Coming Bucket.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a PS.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, that was Osfer?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not surprised about the Coming Buckets.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, because Twilight Princess has, like, never mind.
[SPEAKER_11]: I actually just finished a playthrough of Ocarina of Time last night with one of my close friends.
[SPEAKER_11]: We took turns playing through the dungeons and reminiscing on how we grew up while playing it as kids.
[SPEAKER_11]: After the end credits, we were both pretty teary-eyed.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, she played again.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_11]: I actually, not too long ago, played through Ocarina on the GameCube Redo disc.
[SPEAKER_07]: You need to get the 3DS version.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's really good.
[SPEAKER_11]: I still wanted $40 for it, and they're charging a premium for it because it's out of print now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_06]: By the way, I just want to make sure this is very clear.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't hate Ocarina of Time.
[SPEAKER_06]: I never have, and I've never said that word on the show in regards to Ocarina of Time.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just don't lavish all the praise upon it that many other people do.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's a good game.
[SPEAKER_06]: In fact, I think it's a great game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just don't think it's in my top 20.
[SPEAKER_11]: Rob, you like it, you just don't like like it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_11]: You wouldn't date it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wouldn't eat at S.H.I.E.L.D.
[SPEAKER_11]: You'd go to Pinkberry with it, but you wouldn't date it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Get it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I don't like like it?
[SPEAKER_06]: That was a Zelda joke, people!
[SPEAKER_06]: I try.
[SPEAKER_11]: Last email.
[SPEAKER_11]: This is from Sam.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hi, Sam.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hello, OLR crew.
[SPEAKER_11]: I love the show.
[SPEAKER_11]: If the devs stop making single player games, are we really any better off than we were before Microsoft's change in plans?
[SPEAKER_11]: What do you all think?
[SPEAKER_11]: First of all, I don't think single player games are going away.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, single player games won't go away.
[SPEAKER_06]: There will always be a demand for single player games.
[SPEAKER_11]: There are always antisocial people.
[SPEAKER_06]: However, I can see where this guy, unless Sam is for Samantha, it could be guy or girl, but I'm going to assume guy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Way to assume, Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: Where this individual...
[SPEAKER_10]: Our lovely writer.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Where this individual is getting this from, because it does seem like a lot of single player games that have come out lately have a multiplayer mode suddenly in it.
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: Just within the past few months.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tomb Raider.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tomb Raider, Uncharted 3, Last of Us, Mass Effect 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: All the Assassin's Creed ones, even though it's a little bit older.
[SPEAKER_06]: Assassin's Creed 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: They all have multiplayer modes in them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, I don't think in any of these cases they've necessarily detracted from the single-player game, although some people kind of resented that you kind of had to play multiplayer to get the edge in Mass Effect 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_07]: But Mass Effect 3 multiplayer is great.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that's the thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, it also gives the games more replay value, I guess you could say.
[SPEAKER_07]: I still have yet to... Although, for Mass Effect fans, replay value is going and making another Shepard, let's be real.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, and this is the funny thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm now on my third playthrough of the first game because I'm braving the motion sickness.
[SPEAKER_11]: I've beaten two and three 27 bajillion times.
[SPEAKER_11]: The fun for that for me is making a new Shepard and completely hacking everything I can possibly hack about the appearance.
[SPEAKER_11]: I have one wearing Ashley's face like it's ripped off of her flesh as she died on Vermeier.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_11]: And wearing Warren's outfit.
[SPEAKER_11]: She's been referred to as Hobag Ashley.
[SPEAKER_06]: So in my discussion there, the original question was Xbox One something.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, you closed the email, huh?
[SPEAKER_09]: I did.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you think that single players are going away?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think it was necessarily going away, but I think it has something to do with as they fade more and more.
[SPEAKER_11]: Is Microsoft's decision a bad one?
[SPEAKER_06]: Um...
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I still think if Microsoft wanted to do... Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: If Microsoft wanted to try and push digital, then there's no reason they can't run two separate license systems, your disk-based license and your digital-based license.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why not enhance the digital license?
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, Nintendo dipped their little pinky in the water when they said, well, if you buy the game digitally, you'll get 5%, what is it, 10% back in points, which you can trade in for cards, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: A little bit of a tiny-ass incentive, but it's some incentive to get the game online.
[SPEAKER_06]: What if Microsoft said, okay, we're going to one-up that.
[SPEAKER_06]: So when you digitally buy the game, here's the perk you get over getting it on disc, is that you can now share this digital game with a friend.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can loan it out to a friend across the country instantly.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the perk you get with it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, why can't they run both licenses?
[SPEAKER_06]: They can do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It will take time to develop and so on.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think if Microsoft really wants to, for the Xbox...
[SPEAKER_06]: S2 or whatever their next generation system is called after this, assuming this box doesn't kill the company, but I don't think it will.
[SPEAKER_06]: They could start getting people used to the idea of digital and why it's better as opposed to, nope, we're going to change the whole fucking thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Right now, we're turning your world upside down.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, even though I don't approve of a lot of what the Xbox One was trying to do, I do think it's a shame that we didn't see how it could have developed.
[SPEAKER_06]: The positive was never clearly communicated, only the negative.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, lesson learned, hopefully.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow, that was it for Mailbag, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: That means we get to the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Every week here on this show we let out a little angst.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because we're just really angry people.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, I hate bringing up traffic, but this was really fucking stupid.
[SPEAKER_11]: When I was driving over that same bridge over across the American River coming this way to your place, Rob, someone was freaking tailgating me while all that road construction was with a cop expecting me to speed.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I'm like, no.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I know everybody and their twin goes 20 miles over the speed limit over that bridge, but I wasn't about to do it while there was a CHP parked off to the side.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sorry, your convenience isn't worth me having a $300 ticket.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: Fuck you to hand, foot, and mouth disease.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't like having blisters on my hands and feet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or my mouth.
[SPEAKER_06]: Slide kick?
[SPEAKER_06]: Why don't you go next?
[SPEAKER_07]: I want to say F you to the lady in the Target parking lot who gave me a very pressed look when I was trying to leave.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry that I delayed you like 10 seconds getting to your car so you could go home and eat your Panda Express.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sure it just ruined your day.
[SPEAKER_07]: That orange chicken just fucking... She glared at me.
[SPEAKER_06]: She's like, fine, go.
[SPEAKER_06]: The orange chicken would not stay warm in this weather.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, by the way, I'd like to add a thank you to you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Aww.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you so much for facilitating the crack.
[SPEAKER_06]: And thank you for the Groupon for brunch.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, hey, hey.
[SPEAKER_06]: No rainbow and sunshine shit in the FU segment.
[SPEAKER_11]: You better watch it.
[SPEAKER_06]: FU, Rob.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, FU, Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just kidding, I love you.
[SPEAKER_06]: I-L-U.
[SPEAKER_06]: F-U both.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's my finger.
[SPEAKER_06]: You should do an I-L-U section.
[SPEAKER_06]: You want to do an I-L-U's of the week?
[SPEAKER_06]: Wait, hold on, because I've got to get my F-U out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fuck you to this goddamn shitty fucking hateful heat.
[SPEAKER_11]: Amen!
[SPEAKER_06]: TimTRP in chat agrees.
[SPEAKER_11]: It is hateful.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's a good word for a robot.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's very hateful.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sliding on the chair.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, it's time for the ILUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, I'm using the same music bumper twice.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's the ILUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love you, KBB.
[SPEAKER_11]: Dark Sakura.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you for the 3DS!
[SPEAKER_11]: Slack kick, you are my hero forever.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I have Animal Crossing now, thank you, because you facilitated it.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I'm glad you enjoyed your sausage.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, I always enjoy my sausage.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I have to say ILU to DarkSakura for the Groupon, for brunch, and for sharing her French toast with me.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was so good.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sam's should be a sponsor and I'm going to give my ILU of the week to Alan because he's over there in the kitchen clearly making dinner you can't hear the foil in the background you've got an ILU right?
[SPEAKER_06]: you know the quickest way to a man's heart is through his stomach no, it's through the rib cage Loki, what's your ILU of the week?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't have one, sorry
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: You grumpy cat.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love the fact that it's really sweltering hot in here.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's nothing I can do.
[SPEAKER_06]: You don't have ILU to breadsticks?
[SPEAKER_06]: ILU to these five fans.
[SPEAKER_06]: One, two, three, four.
[SPEAKER_06]: I made one up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Five.
[SPEAKER_09]: And all your fans in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_11]: Aww.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oops.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was not meant to be followed by holic.
[SPEAKER_11]: Everything is meant to be followed by Holic.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, if you could possibly do the next story.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, so unfortunately there was a little bit of an issue with the precursor games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently, writer, game designer, and artist Ken McColl, he was arrested for possession of child pornography.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's not good.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, that's definitely not good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, the company is now distancing themselves from their co-founder, and he doesn't have anything to do now, obviously, with Shadows of the Eternals.
[SPEAKER_06]: Every time I hear Shadow of the Eternal, now I hear this as the theme song.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, as if Precursor needed any more bad press, honestly.
[SPEAKER_03]: Right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, that sucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh well, what are you going to do?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's all you can do.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, for one, don't download child pornography.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's not good.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's gross.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's beyond gross.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're nasty.
[SPEAKER_11]: By the way, Rob, did you hear about the 12-year-old girl who shamed a guy in her room drinking off over her?
[SPEAKER_11]: Ew!
[SPEAKER_11]: What?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, it was kind of unpleasant.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was on the, I read it on like some news thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was like a legit news thing where this 12 year old girl says, you need to be ashamed of yourself, leave.
[SPEAKER_11]: And he did.
[SPEAKER_06]: The internet's disgusting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Disgusting place.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, no, this was a real life thing, but.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, moving on to a campaign about something that really pisses people off about the Wii U, and that is region locking.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, I guess some of the fans out there are hoping, you know, if Operation Rainfall worked, and Microsoft ended up reversing course on a lot of their shit, maybe, just maybe, we can get Nintendo to end region locking.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they're taking to Twitter, you know, because Twitter is a very effective way of protesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: It worked for the PlayStation 4 and Xbox One.
[SPEAKER_06]: and region locking and Nintendo region free are some hashtags there's let's see some posts on Miiverse as well which are actually kind of funny like I love some of these Miiverse posts I love the one of Monita with region free please that's great and then like a picture of Reggie Fils-Aim or I guess that's supposed to be him my body is region free so it's kind of clever that they're taking to Miiverse to put some of their opinions it won't happen no it probably won't happen
[SPEAKER_07]: The thing is that Nintendo seems to be trying to bring over a lot of stuff that maybe in the past they wouldn't have.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fire Emblem is a thing that we can basically expect at this point, but also Bravely Default, that was kind of uncertain, but Nintendo is helping bring that over.
[SPEAKER_07]: Even though it would be nice if the Wii U was region-free, I think that Nintendo is really trying to listen to gamers and know that they want these games that are...
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: SimCity has a wonderful new piece of DLC for $9.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Zeppelins.
[SPEAKER_04]: You get an airship and a hot air balloon park.
[SPEAKER_10]: Is it piloted by a guy named Sid?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hot air balloon park and an airship mass transit option.
$9.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all you get for $9.
[SPEAKER_06]: Will it explode like the Hindenburg did?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, not to be in poor taste.
[SPEAKER_10]: Too soon, Rob.
[SPEAKER_10]: Too soon.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thanks to the power of cloud processing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Part of SimCity is disasters, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, SimCity was a disaster.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh boy.
[SPEAKER_11]: It wouldn't be the same without the reporter.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, let's go to the phones because we do have calls coming in.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, you're on Orange Sounds Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's Codeman.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, Codeman.
[SPEAKER_06]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_06]: I haven't called in in a while.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was going to say, long time no talk.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you know, it's busy everywhere.
[SPEAKER_06]: Real life is not allowed to get in the way of OLR.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, thanks.
[SPEAKER_13]: It never does.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hardly.
[SPEAKER_13]: Good answer.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_13]: No, I was just calling about the whole YouTube thing earlier because I'm your friendly neighborhood YouTuber, I guess.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes, you are.
[SPEAKER_13]: But they're actually starting to monetize for minutes watched now.
[SPEAKER_13]: So it's not so much your video anymore as it is the minutes of how long somebody watches your video.
[SPEAKER_13]: so I mean it's really I don't know they keep changing it but to say something about I believe Square Enix or Squeenix as a lot of people say is they did that for a really long time they wouldn't let anyone put any of their games up which I always see it as free advertisement for the company but I mean you're playing their game people are watching it they say oh you know this is a really good game I want to buy it so then they go out and buy it and then
[SPEAKER_13]: That's free advertisement.
[SPEAKER_13]: So to me, that's the way.
[SPEAKER_13]: But I see where everybody's coming from, where you're playing this game, you're claiming it as your own video, but it's actually just your voice over something else that somebody else made.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I can understand that, but...
[SPEAKER_13]: I just wanted to call in because I missed that whole conversation.
[SPEAKER_13]: I had to go put the girl down to sleep.
[SPEAKER_13]: I just wanted to call in and talk about that a little bit.
[SPEAKER_06]: No worries.
[SPEAKER_06]: You probably aren't surprised to hear that people make a living off those Let's Play videos though, right?
[SPEAKER_13]: Um, there's a lot of people out there, a lot of really, really big YouTubers that make a huge, huge killing off of just doing Let's Plays and doing... Minecraft's real big right now.
[SPEAKER_13]: There's just tons of people out there making so much money off of that.
[SPEAKER_13]: And, yeah, to an extent, you make a lot of money, but I don't really think, unless you partner with a third party...
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't really think, which sometimes you kind of get screwed out of that money too.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, you know, either way, if you manage yourself correctly on YouTube, I think you can make a good amount of money.
[SPEAKER_13]: But other than that, I do it just to do it and, you know, to show people what I'm playing and, you know, all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, I don't do it for the money, obviously, because I'm not making anything from it.
[SPEAKER_13]: But it's just fun to do to me.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I love video editing and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: that's what's got it's like podcasting I've said this before on an earlier show if you don't love it what the hell are you doing
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, exactly.
[SPEAKER_13]: If you get into YouTube to make money, you're getting into the wrong reasons.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like those companies that are like, we need to hire an agency to make a viral video.
[SPEAKER_06]: You don't force something to go viral.
[SPEAKER_06]: That has to happen.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, no.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, that's totally true.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, and I also wanted to say, you will have a buffer from a one-year-old... Well, actually, from a...
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, she'll be two probably by the time that I make the buffer, but I got her to say orange today, but she has to put all of them together.
[SPEAKER_13]: I haven't got... Adorable!
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, so that should be fantastic.
[SPEAKER_06]: Excited to hear it.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, I think that's about it, really.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, I mean, yeah, I was up late tonight, so I thought I'd give you guys a call because I haven't talked to you in a while.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm glad you did.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, always good to hear from you.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's good to hear from you.
[SPEAKER_06]: You take care, and I hope everybody's doing well out there in Oklahoma.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm glad to see you've been okay throughout all the  I mean, here I am bitching about the heat.
[SPEAKER_11]: Rob, that was a bad pun.
[SPEAKER_06]: At least I don't have  what?
[SPEAKER_11]: I didn't even  Please, okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: God, shut up.
[SPEAKER_06]: At least I don't have these tornadoes running through my backyard, so I'm glad to hear you're alright with all that.
[SPEAKER_13]: We're getting the heat right now, too.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think today we got probably a high of 101, which is not a whole... I mean, it's not big here, but I mean, we're not getting tornadoes, and that's all that we care about.
[SPEAKER_13]: Although I am getting a shelter put in in September, I think, so... Phew, that's good.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, buddy, I'm gonna let you go so we can get more calls, but stay safe.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right, you guys, keep making the podcast for another 16 years.
[SPEAKER_13]: How about that?
[SPEAKER_13]: We'll try.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, we'll see you.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, bye.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_06]: In 16 years, I will be 50.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know about that.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, let's go to some more calls.
[SPEAKER_06]: Phone's ringing tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, you're on Orange Lawns Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_06]: This is Zorme.
[SPEAKER_06]: Zorme.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, Zorme.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think... Have you called the show before?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't recognize your name.
[SPEAKER_06]: I call him a few times back in the day.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, back in the day.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, welcome back.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_08]: I know you guys are average gamers of Final Fantasy XI, and now that Final Fantasy XIV has come out...
[SPEAKER_08]: It looks like it's going to be pretty good.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've been playing it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Have you guys?
[SPEAKER_06]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_06]: You might have missed the beginning of the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was talking a bit about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_06]: We actually, all of us, except Slidekick, you haven't been able to play it, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, not lately, but I did play in like an earlier phase.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, we've all been playing it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I especially have been playing it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I really love it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have two classes at 16 on my character that's going to get deleted in a week anyway, but I'm having a lot of fun just exploring this gorgeous game that's very fanservice-y.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, you said that they're going to delete your character.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think that's official.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's out there that right now we're in what's called Beta Phase 3, and they have said that they're going to wipe the characters at the end of Beta Phase 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: We just don't know when the end is.
[SPEAKER_06]: But before the official release of the game, there is another character wipe slotted because there's going to be Beta Phase 4, which is open beta, where everybody's going to get to play.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they did say about Beta Phase 4 that they're going to try...
[SPEAKER_06]: and let those characters carry into the live game but they did clearly say so that people don't bitch about it if it happens another character wipe at the end of all the betas still may have to occur so we may still be looking at two character wipes so don't get too attached to your character but that's I mean considering they haven't even opened up Arcanist as a job yet and I mean you have to I think have a 1.0 character or something I mean considering we don't have all of that in there yet I'm okay with them I mean it is a beta it is a beta not a demo
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, yeah, that's the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think I've been enjoying playing different characters and it's been quite fun because there's just so many different customizations.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that whole, what do you think about the free company?
[SPEAKER_08]: That's what I want because a lot of people...
[SPEAKER_08]: See that you have link shells as well, but there's no need for them because you have free company.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I haven't been able to test that yet because I don't even really understand it.
[SPEAKER_06]: You have the link shells or the little sub guilds, but then the free company is like your huge chat channel, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like you have big guilds and little guilds as a part of that, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Right.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's basically like you're able to go ahead and
[SPEAKER_08]: Make a group of people a little bit more organized where you can have like cadets and I'm not too sure, but like people who are in your officers, you have like cadets and you have like commanders, some sort of thing like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: And they can basically distribute money and kill and.
[SPEAKER_08]: based off of like their prestige inside the link shell, I mean inside the free company.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know exactly on too much detail about it, but it's more than just a glorified link shell though.
[SPEAKER_06]: My understanding, especially coming from World of Warcraft, which I've played for a long time and I'm still continuing to play even throughout Final Fantasy XIV,
[SPEAKER_06]: You had a lot of big guilds in World of Warcraft that had several raiding groups in it.
[SPEAKER_06]: In fact, my own guild for a time that I was raiding with had, infamously to an extent, two raiding groups in it, Raid Group 1 and Raid Group 2, and that actually is what kind of drove that guild apart.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I would think that maybe with a free company set up, you would still have that, but then each raid team would have its own little link shell in it for raid nights and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's interesting, though, the way they're doing that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I do think it's going to be great for organization, because I don't know how... Well, I do know, actually.
[SPEAKER_08]: You played Final Fantasy XI, but you didn't play it to the extent where you were in an endgame.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I never got that far.
[SPEAKER_06]: I played for years and never got a character past 56.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it was the highest I ever got.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's crazy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Me, I had a couple of jobs, like level 75, and it was kind of difficult distributing...
[SPEAKER_08]: Skill and prizes and drops throughout the several instances like Dynamis and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I think it'll make it a lot easier for people to just know who is who going forward.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm a little bit worried because it's a lot of jobs and things can get nerfed, like how Lancer got nerfed when Samurai Dragoon tend to go out of hand.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think you remember that with the Pentathrust.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yep, I do.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, so it's...
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know, I'm still waiting.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, we'll see how things go.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did you play the first one?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, I did play 1.0.
[SPEAKER_06]: I played at the very, very beginning.
[SPEAKER_06]: I played the beta for 1.0, and then I played the very, very early version, or when it first came out, and I hated it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I tried playing later after they opened it up and said, all right, we're not charging a monthly fee anymore.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to say it was like January, February of the next year.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it was still like it just wasn't  it made me go back and play 11 for a little bit.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I felt the same way.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, it was kind of weird the way the auction house wasn't available, and there was no direction.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's no chocobos.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's no direction.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's crazy.
[SPEAKER_06]: But okay, quickly, before I let you go, since you were a player of XI for so long, what do you think of XIV, having come from XI?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm excited.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm taking my time, you know, because, you know, when I played XI, I didn't really know what I was
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm playing as many jobs as possible on several different servers and just trying to get a basic understanding of the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm pretty sure I want to be a scholar, so I'm hoping Arcanist is open soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm hoping they open soon so I can see it before the real game goes live, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: But anyway, I have to let you go, but thank you so much for the call.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good to hear from you, and I'll always talk MMOs with people.
[SPEAKER_08]: No problem.
[SPEAKER_06]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_06]: Take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good call.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love hearing from people.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tonight is people we haven't heard from in a while, apparently.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: You all right over there, Loki?
[SPEAKER_06]: You're giggling.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love these Battlefield 3 animated GIFs because it just... I kind of want to play it even... GIF.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to play it even more because it looks so glitchy sometimes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like this guy snipes a jet and makes it blow up in front of his face and nothing happens.
[SPEAKER_06]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or a username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio, all one word.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll try to squeeze in at least one more call.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wanted to do a Twitter topic that came in here from Tigerclaw.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sent us a tweet.
[SPEAKER_06]: What is it here?
[SPEAKER_06]: Nintendo defends the rapid release of new Mario games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Although our phone lines are lighting up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, I'll come back to this in a minute.
[SPEAKER_06]: For now, let's go to the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, you're on Orange Lawn Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, we have a web.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, hey.
[SPEAKER_09]: How's it going?
[SPEAKER_09]: We have a web.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's DT and Gigi here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh my gosh, you guys are together.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a cam thing, though, although all I see is like half of Dark Tetsuya's head, but that's okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's up, you guys?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, not a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, just been hanging out, playing a lot of games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like what games?
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, I got sucked into Unepic.
[SPEAKER_09]: That game was so fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: Unepic?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tell us a little bit about that one.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like a dungeon crawler.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's actually like a Metroidvania type thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm here for that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that free or is that like a Steam game?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's $7.99 on Steam.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, that's not bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll have to write that one down.
[SPEAKER_06]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, I'm looking at pictures, actually, it does look kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_11]: It is very Castlevania-like, with big dragons.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, and you can level up your character with each, there's a bar at the top that has a leveling system, and with each level you can put it into weapons or yourself to get more stamina and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: That looks super fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think I am going to check that out.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: So did you guys just call in to get me sucked into a new game and make me spend $8?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, congrats.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, that was a plan.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're like, we need to suck him into another game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, because I haven't been talking about how I've been playing Final Fantasy XIV literally all weekend long.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just updated League of Legends.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: I got time for another one.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Bring it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was trying to get into the beta, but I don't think I made it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good news.
[SPEAKER_06]: Beta 4 is going to be open.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyone who wants to play can play it.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then I heard about the pricing system.
[SPEAKER_09]: Have they already fixed it?
[SPEAKER_06]: You don't have to pay for it yet, but when the game goes live on August 27th, I believe it's $12.95 a month is the lower tier and then like $14.95 for eight characters or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't quote me on that.
[SPEAKER_09]: That seems pretty legit.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think I can work that into my budget because I want that game so bad.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, it's going to be fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: I started playing Final Fantasy back when VII came out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Unfortunately, I was never able to really play the online ones, but I've been a fan ever since VII.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, there's a lot of fan service in 14.
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's Moogles.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, well, you guys, you have fun, and go find another game for me to get addicted to.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, take care, guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, you too, bye.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_06]: Video calls are always fun, even though I can only see like half of each of their head, but it worked.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: 1877GAMEOLR, our username on Skype is OrangeLoungeRadio.
[SPEAKER_06]: What do you say it's like?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, can we try to fit in one more call?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Someone new needs to call.
[SPEAKER_06]: Someone new?
[SPEAKER_06]: Someone new.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_11]: I challenge you.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Listeners of OLR, be somebody new.
[SPEAKER_06]: Be quick because there's been a lot of people trying to get through.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's why I'm going to allow one more call to squeeze in here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I was going to read the Tiger Claw tweet that said Nintendo defends the rapid release of new Mario games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Quote, who's this quote from?
[SPEAKER_06]: Nintendo of America Senior Director of Corporate Communications We think we're putting out the right number of Mario games based on what fans are asking for Based on what our own developers' creative visions are The key to that is as long as there's innovation occurring within the gameplay As long as there's new features Then marrying the characters and the IPs that people love is the right call from our standpoint But the phone is ringing again, so let's go to it Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio, who's this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Uh, Name and Lights Name and Lights!
[SPEAKER_06]: Although, it's ironic, because your icon is just a solid black square It is?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, at least that's what I'm seeing, I don't know, maybe it's not supposed to be But yeah, I do not see your name in lights That's not supposed to be Oh, oops, oh well Alright, well, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_06]: This is the first time I've listened to the show live Well, I was gonna say, I recognize your name, but I don't think you've ever called Well, DarkSakura, there you go, you got your new person Yay, thank you Well, uh, what do you think?
[SPEAKER_14]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_14]: I've been listening to the Orange Lawns for years.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, well, and you just now were able to make it to a live show?
[SPEAKER_06]: Usually busy on Sunday nights?
[SPEAKER_14]: Normally I'm sleeping.
[SPEAKER_14]: This is flipping late for me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_06]: We have a lot of people.
[SPEAKER_06]: Codeman said earlier he was staying up late.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess a lot of people maybe for the 4th of July week kind of have a lot less going on.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: You may remember me from a couple of the messages I sent you privately.
[SPEAKER_14]: Perhaps.
[SPEAKER_14]: My wife passed away.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, that's right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, yes, yes, I do, I do.
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course I recognize that, and I'm very sorry to hear that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because, yeah, we're Facebook buddies, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, we're all Facebook friends.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, well... I just got back in the gaming again.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_06]: And what have you been playing?
[SPEAKER_14]: Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like old school Warcraft or World of Warcraft?
[SPEAKER_06]: World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm in the Horde House Guild.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I knew you were over there in the Horde House Guild.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you for being loyal to the Horde House Guild because unfortunately a lot of people have quit WoW for things like Final Fantasy XIV or League or whatever it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or real life.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean... I was off a month.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, understandably so, but... I was actually sort of thinking about rebuilding my subscription except that
[SPEAKER_06]: Now you have Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_06]: What would you like to do in World of Warcraft?
[SPEAKER_14]: Right now I'm leveling a new monk.
[SPEAKER_14]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_14]: I deleted the monk that I was... Because my wife used to play.
[SPEAKER_14]: And she wanted to play, but when she had the stroke she couldn't see.
[SPEAKER_14]: So I spent three solid weeks...
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: to get your minds out of the gutter, people.
[SPEAKER_06]: They can ride on your back and, like, you can fly them to places.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's really great.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like if you have a low-level character, you're like, oh, you need to get to Thunder Bluff or a town that might be far for you to walk to.
[SPEAKER_06]: Get on my back.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's go.
[SPEAKER_11]: And it was 300 flying, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: So if you had a lower-level character, you could still take him at, what, epic speed, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: You could.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, so when I was off for five weeks taking care of her after the stroke...
[SPEAKER_14]: I upped my warcraft, and the only thing I did was farm archaeology to get the recipe.
[SPEAKER_14]: Right.
[SPEAKER_14]: And she passed away three days after I got it.
[SPEAKER_06]: But at least you got it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, I did, but I never had a chance for her to use it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm sorry to hear that.
[SPEAKER_14]: So I pretty much stopped WoW.
[SPEAKER_14]: I deleted the monk that I leveled with her.
[SPEAKER_14]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_06]: and it was tough to get back in yeah has kind of getting in I mean I hate to dwell on what might be a difficult topic but has this been a way for you to kind of help get back into you know after such a tragedy as video games kind of helped you a little bit in getting back into what might have been your routine before it took a while to get back into it because
[SPEAKER_14]: I was trying to play after she passed away, but I just couldn't play more than a few minutes without getting irritatedly bored and just shutting it off.
[SPEAKER_14]: So I didn't up my account until very recently.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I named a character after her.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a great way to memorialize somebody.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know of other people that have done that in WoW.
[SPEAKER_06]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know that even the developers, when people that they were close to that were involved in the game, they've immortalized them in the game too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, there's some really great memorial.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, usually this is more for people that were really part of the WoW community and heavy raiders and stuff that...
[SPEAKER_06]: But they have set up tributes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Blizzard has kind of done that in the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: And there's some really great compilations out there on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know somebody that had this for somebody that they were married to.
[SPEAKER_06]: And yeah, really great when the companies kind of do that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it just really emphasizes the community that an MMO game and what really makes those games great is the community.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, it's been hard.
[SPEAKER_14]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_14]: The last couple months have been ridiculously hard.
[SPEAKER_06]: Right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not even going to sit here and try to imagine, but you know you got friends here at OLR and at the Voice of Geeks Network and out there in Facebook land and on the internet that are trying to help you through it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hope it's getting a little better every day.
[SPEAKER_14]: Except for today.
[SPEAKER_14]: I got my eviction notice today.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know what to say.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bobby should start a support group.
[SPEAKER_06]: I need bad news to stop happening to our listeners.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: Gosh, I don't know what we can do to help.
[SPEAKER_14]: I knew this was coming.
[SPEAKER_14]: I knew when she passed away I wasn't going to be able to afford the house that we have.
[SPEAKER_14]: Sure, sure.
[SPEAKER_14]: What goes around comes around.
[SPEAKER_14]: So I got the eviction notice that opened a beer.
[SPEAKER_06]: When in doubt, when in doubt, why not?
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, buddy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, we're all thinking of you, and good luck pulling through.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, I love the show.
[SPEAKER_14]: I love listening.
[SPEAKER_14]: I love Horde House.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm an avid listener.
[SPEAKER_14]: This is the first time I've actually had a chance to be up this late.
[SPEAKER_14]: My buddy was helping me pack up some stuff tonight.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's the only reason why I'm still up.
[SPEAKER_14]: He took off.
[SPEAKER_14]: I just decided to turn the show on.
[SPEAKER_14]: I know you guys don't usually end around 12, 1 o'clock Eastern Time because I am on the East Coast.
[SPEAKER_14]: But I listen to you guys on a regular basis for years now.
[SPEAKER_14]: I just never have a chance to listen live.
[SPEAKER_06]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_06]: I ended up getting a career I've been at for 12 years now.
[SPEAKER_14]: Not to get all preachy and everything, she was happiest ever as a teacher.
[SPEAKER_14]: She was teaching CNAs, which is Certified Nursing Assistants.
[SPEAKER_14]: She loved her job.
[SPEAKER_14]: She was an RN.
[SPEAKER_14]: She was two credits away from being a bachelor's.
[SPEAKER_14]: And, you know, when she lost that job because they changed the qualifications for the job, I just simply told her that it's like, you know what, I'll support you.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'll do whatever it takes.
[SPEAKER_14]: Just, you know, go back to school, get your education and get more education than the person that just fired you.
[SPEAKER_14]: And that's what she was going to do.
[SPEAKER_14]: She was... Sorry, but... No, I understand.
[SPEAKER_14]: Cinco de Mayo.
[SPEAKER_15]: She wanted to go back to the school.
[SPEAKER_06]: She was supposed to start school on the 5th and I told her that the module wasn't going to open up on the 5th because it was a holiday Um
[SPEAKER_15]: She went to school on Monday and passed away on Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you're getting the world's biggest hug from our chat room right now for this, you know, all over the place.
[SPEAKER_06]: But how great that you were helping her to achieve this and, you know, come out of the circumstance better.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I know wherever she is right now, she's thanking you big time for it.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's been a really horrible two months.
[SPEAKER_14]: I was glad May was over with, but June is just... June's gone.
[SPEAKER_14]: It is July, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, today for East Coast.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, it's just... She went back to school one day.
[SPEAKER_06]: But you helped her get back to school.
[SPEAKER_06]: You did.
[SPEAKER_14]: All she wanted to do was become a teacher.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: My mom was a teacher.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a great profession.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm actually a corporate trainer.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's an admirable thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love my job.
[SPEAKER_06]: Absolutely love my job.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, I'm going to let you go.
[SPEAKER_14]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'll try to listen again live again when the dust settles.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I'll stay in touch.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, please do stay in touch.
[SPEAKER_11]: Message me on Facebook.
[SPEAKER_06]: I will.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, you take care.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're all thinking of you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ooh, how's that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Tough call.
[SPEAKER_06]: I need someone to cut... Quick, Loki, I need a fart joke.
[SPEAKER_06]: Quick.
[SPEAKER_06]: Help me.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_11]: I have happy-happies.
[SPEAKER_06]: because look at the chat room I mean yeah for real seriously for real and you know there's even I'm sure a lot of people are like wow that was a heavy call and yes it was a heavy call but when we say we're there for people we kind of like mean it and shit so
[SPEAKER_11]: and you know the biggest thing that me that I like to do for people is I like to find if there's a tough situation I like to find research everything that has to do with it and offer options because especially when you're in the middle of a situation
[SPEAKER_11]: There's not always things that occur to you when you're in that situation.
[SPEAKER_11]: And when Dan and I were... Because you know when we got our notice for the house that we were staying in rent-free, we had to move in a week.
[SPEAKER_11]: And it was people helping us and giving us options that opened the door for us, too.
[SPEAKER_11]: So...
[SPEAKER_11]: If you need to bounce any ideas, if you need just someone outside the situation to help you see it clearly, let me know.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm happy to help.
[SPEAKER_06]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Some people are playing video games to kind of escape reality such as the very difficult thing that he just shared with us which is not an easy thing to get on some radio show and talk about what happened so you know I commend him for being able to do that and keeping it together even as much as he did.
[SPEAKER_06]: but you never know who's going to be on the other end of that game you're playing in that MMO or on that Xbox Live so you know have a little decency for each other and you know anyway just think do you want it being said to you and even more do you want it being said to someone you care about so because there's people who can take it but they don't take it when it's somebody that they care about so just think about it that way alright
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, anyhow, do we have any other last-minute stories to try and transition us back onto the video game news we were talking about earlier?
[SPEAKER_06]: I think... Oh, yeah, I got through the Twitter topic, which was the only one that we got, but...
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh, they're selling an Earthbound Zero Reproduction NES cart.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gimme.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's, uh, an English translated ROM of, uh, you know, the game Mother.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, uh, of course it never came out over here.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I guess it's being, um...
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know who's doing the reproduction of it or if it even works.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wasn't that the one that had the anti-piracy thing that would shut down the game?
[SPEAKER_06]: Earthbound.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, no, I know that would get harder, but I thought Earthbound Zero even had the prototype ROM was infamous for having these game-breaking bugs in it, but maybe the hackers fixed that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's been so long.
[SPEAKER_06]: It seems like it was so long ago that that all happened.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not sure if it actually does anything or if it's just a reproduction of the original.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I never played Mother, but I always thought it was kind of a glitchy game to begin with.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actual version.
[SPEAKER_06]: Uh, like, you mean the Earthbound that was on the SNES here?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mother.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mother Earthbound Zero.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think because it wasn't finished, it was still glitchy, yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, um, that does it for the Skype line tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: That does it for our Twitter topics.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that did it for the, um, uh, last minute stories as well, unless you have anything else to surprise me with over there?
[SPEAKER_06]: No?
[SPEAKER_11]: I, um, no.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: I love all the Hello Kitty everywhere.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, you can thank Slidekick for some of that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Slidekick, I want to thank you for being here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you so much for having me.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, I've been listening for years, and I'm so glad that I finally was able to come up and get on the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: It'll take you 11 years.
[SPEAKER_06]: and you really got to run the gauntlet of an OLR show tonight from the dick and fart jokes and the stuff at the beginning to some real heavy stuff there at the end so it's like you got a whole two years worth of OLR emotions in one show so congratulations.
[SPEAKER_07]: We know every gamer has their voice here so.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you, yes that's what we strive for.
[SPEAKER_06]: Best of luck with your project.
[SPEAKER_06]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_06]: You've made it a year on Gamebuoy.org.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: I look forward to sharing the stage with you at GamerX.
[SPEAKER_06]: It'll be a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: It'll be my honor.
[SPEAKER_06]: Everybody else, aw, shucks.
[SPEAKER_06]: One more time with the plugs.
[SPEAKER_06]: How can they find your fine show?
[SPEAKER_07]: GameBooey.org GameBooey.org GameBooey.org
[SPEAKER_07]: We love OLR.
[SPEAKER_07]: We love all our OLR listeners.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're usually in chat when OLR is going on.
[SPEAKER_07]: So if you haven't checked us out yet, we'd love to hear from you and hope you enjoy what you hear.
[SPEAKER_06]: We love indie podcasts, period.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, I don't want to sound shady or anything, but do you think some of the corporate casts out there could have done some of these calls we did tonight?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the difference, y'all.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the difference.
[SPEAKER_07]: We might have to get Alan in here because TimTRP in chat says we demand a Fabulous Flames reunion show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Where's Alan?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I think he ran outside or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: Damn.
[SPEAKER_06]: Braving the heat.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe he's trying to figure out how to make it cooler in here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here he is.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alan, when's the Fabulous Flames reunion show?
[SPEAKER_06]: Definitely look that up on iTunes, y'all.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's one week after I win $50 billion in the lottery.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to win the lottery.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alan, did you have a final thought for the listeners tonight before you run out?
[SPEAKER_12]: I still think it may actually be a few degrees hotter outside than it is in here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sweet Jesus, when did I move to Phoenix?
[SPEAKER_11]: You know what's happening, by the way, next Sunday for me?
[SPEAKER_11]: We are on the house hunt.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, good luck.
[SPEAKER_11]: Which may end up being a new dedicated studio.
[SPEAKER_06]: That would be nice, I'm not going to complain.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wish us luck.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's go around and get everybody's final thoughts so we can wrap up and head on out of here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Again, Slykick, thank you for being here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you have an official final thought for our listeners tonight?
[SPEAKER_07]: I want a burger.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh my god, so do I. I'm so hungry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Burgers are pretty fucking good, I gotta say.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm gonna hit the drive-thru on my way home.
[SPEAKER_06]: Get it, girl.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, you got 30 minutes to get to Pinkberry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ooh, girl.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, you're packing up.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're ready to go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good luck with all your disease and everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hope you're cured by next week.
[SPEAKER_10]: Make sure that you find those rats that gave you the bubonic plague.
[SPEAKER_06]: okay all right at least it's not herpes uh your final thought tonight and here's only with weather it's hot uh my final thought is that if you live in northern California you should make plans to come see Clue at the Colonial Theater in Sacramento on July 27th I'm playing Colonel Mustard it'll be fun yes I do other finally find a tie
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, your final thoughts tonight?
[SPEAKER_11]: I actually have an appetite tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: I had French toast this morning and I thought I wouldn't be hungry all day.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm actually hungry right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Get some pinkberry, girl.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's it, you guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you very much for listening to Orange Lounge Radio and supporting independent podcasting.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's much more than just some silly little radio show with a bunch of dick and fart jokes.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hope tonight's show proved that for you all.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have a wonderful night and we'll see you next time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good night.
[SPEAKER_00]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_00]: Orange Lounge Radio is a production of OLR Studios.
[SPEAKER_00]: To join us for a live show, tune in to vognetwork.com Sunday nights at 6pm Pacific, 9pm Eastern.
[SPEAKER_00]: The views and opinions expressed in this program do not necessarily reflect those of the staff of Orange Lounge Radio or VOG Network, but you know they were all still true.
[SPEAKER_00]: See you next week!