[SPEAKER_01]: Tonight, June 9, 2013, Microsoft's controversial announcements could change the industry forever, Zynga layoffs affect a developer they recently acquired, and E3 is next week, and we're making our predictions for the big show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello everybody out there on the internet and welcome back to another week of the show where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is Orange Lounge Radio, episode number 507 for this June 9th of 2013.
[SPEAKER_04]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_04]: Joining me as always, say hello to DarkSakura or Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_09]: Greetings and salutations.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I hope you're doing well, Ms.
[SPEAKER_04]: Summers.
[SPEAKER_10]: I am.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm caffeinated.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good to hear.
[SPEAKER_04]: And also joining us tonight, Tech Master Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, definitely working in that Tech Master moniker this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: How so?
[SPEAKER_04]: Quickly.
[SPEAKER_03]: I had to fix my laptop.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hard drive crash.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I've been following your tweets, your Twitters, and all the hard drive drama.
[SPEAKER_03]: But now it works pretty much like it did before.
[SPEAKER_03]: All it needed was a little reformatting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, all the non-essential stuff's not working, like some of these touch buttons up the top here that I never use, or the icon's different now for the volume up and down, but eh, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Big week this week, E3 obviously coming up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Unfortunately, none of us attending this year.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bobby Blackwolf from the Voice Geeks Network at vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: He is attending.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if you haven't already checked it out, do check out the interactive coverage of E3 presented in an all-new way at the Voice Geeks Network at e3.vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or at least we think it's an all-new way.
[SPEAKER_04]: The internet's a big place.
[SPEAKER_04]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't seen it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's get into it, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, after the whole... Well, I guess the promise was, after the Xbox One press event thing that they did back in May, that there was going to be some answers about, or clarification, I guess, on the big hot topics that they were getting grilled on after the event, basically.
[SPEAKER_03]: What is the deal with, you know, the online connectivity?
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, how often do I need to connect to the internet?
[SPEAKER_03]: How is the used game thing going to work?
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, and, you know, what's up with the Kinect having to be online all the time or attached to your system at all times of work?
[SPEAKER_03]: So, on Friday, I think it was Friday.
[SPEAKER_03]: Was it Friday?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, the 6th.
[SPEAKER_03]: On Friday, no, it was Thursday.
[SPEAKER_03]: On the sixth, they released a three-page document called Xbox One, Details on Connectivity, Licensing, and Privacy Features.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's go through each one, shall we?
[SPEAKER_03]: Xbox One, a modern connected device.
[SPEAKER_03]: And to kind of spoil everything, none of this stuff is actually sounding any good.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's pretty much just...
[SPEAKER_03]: The Xbox One will deliver new benefits for gamers that are only possible with a system designed from the ground up to be ready and connected.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here are a few examples.
[SPEAKER_03]: Make your game more powerful or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: Your Xbox One is always ready.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's designed to run, I guess, low power state.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, let's get to the good part.
[SPEAKER_03]: Network technologies and network requirements.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_03]: For an optimal experience, we recommend a broadband connection of 1.5 megabits.
[SPEAKER_03]: And also, if in areas where, I guess...
[SPEAKER_03]: An Ethernet connection is not available.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can connect using mobile broadband.
[SPEAKER_03]: Lucky you.
[SPEAKER_03]: And also, while a persistent connection is not required, the Xbox One is designed to verify if the system application or game updates are needed and to see if you have acquired new games, resold or traded in games, or have given a game to a friend.
[SPEAKER_03]: Games that are designed to take advantage of the cloud system may require a connection.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then, of course, with Xbox One, you can game offline for up to 24 hours on your primary console or one hour if you're logged into a separate console accessing your library.
[SPEAKER_03]: Offline gaming is not possible after these prescribed times until you reestablish a connection.
[SPEAKER_03]: But you can still... Oh, oh, and this is the best part.
[SPEAKER_03]: But guess what?
[SPEAKER_03]: You can still watch live TV, enjoy your Blu-ray and DVD movies.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, thank you, Xbox One!
[SPEAKER_03]: I can still enjoy TV that you are connected to.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dearly beloved, we are gathered here today to mourn the loss of the gaming industry.
[SPEAKER_10]: Rest in peace.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, let's get to the next thing here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, so, um...
[SPEAKER_03]: Next, how game licensing will work on the Xbox One.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'm glad that they have to tell me how it's going to work.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, so basically you buy the games the way you want, disc or digital, and you'll be able to buy them through traditional retailers or online through Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it says, discs will continue to be a great way to install your game quickly.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, to install, not play off of install.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can access your entire games library from any Xbox One, no discs required.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can share access with your games to everyone inside your home.
[SPEAKER_03]: Your friends, family, guests, and acquaintances get unlimited access to all your games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyone can play your games on your console regardless of whether you are logged in
[SPEAKER_03]: or their relationship to you.
[SPEAKER_03]: In other words, a feature that's been available on console gaming since the beginning of time.
[SPEAKER_03]: That yes, if I bring a friend over, that they can play on the Xbox One without it going, hey, who are you?
[SPEAKER_03]: What are you doing trying to touch my controller and play this game?
[SPEAKER_03]: Get your hands off my controller.
[SPEAKER_03]: I need an adult.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, you could share access, oh, let's see, uh, give your family access to your entire games library anytime, anywhere.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, this is kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Xbox One, I guess, they're going to have a way where up to ten people of your family, or whoever you're saying is your family...
[SPEAKER_03]: can log in and play from your shared games library on any Xbox One.
[SPEAKER_03]: So if I buy a copy of, say, Forza Motorsports or something like that, someone else can go to a friend's house or whatever or from their own location and play that copy of Forza as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: But only one person can play at a time.
[SPEAKER_04]: And not at launch.
[SPEAKER_04]: None of this is available at launch.
[SPEAKER_03]: All the good stuff, all the pros, not at launch.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know if that's available at launch.
[SPEAKER_03]: Doesn't say.
[SPEAKER_03]: Trade in and resell your disc-based games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Today, some gamers choose to sell their old disc-based games back for cash and credit.
[SPEAKER_03]: We've designed the Xbox Ones so game publishers can enable you to trade in your games at participating retailers.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's an optional feature.
[SPEAKER_04]: So no eBay, gone.
[SPEAKER_04]: No flea markets, gone.
[SPEAKER_04]: No garage sales, gone.
[SPEAKER_04]: Authorized retailers only if the publisher allows it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's now not my choice on what I'm going to do with my game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's now Microsoft's choice or the publisher's choice on what I'm going to do with my game.
[SPEAKER_10]: But we don't own it.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're licensing it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was never ours to begin with.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't sign a form when I'm playing these games, although I'm sure you're going to have to agree to it when you install your game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: Press A to agree to the 500-page terms and conditions, or you won't be able to play anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: This thing's a brick.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see, Microsoft does not charge a platform fee to retailers, publishers, or consumers for enabling transfer of these games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which, I don't know, kind of goes against what I've heard, what we've been hearing rumors-wise, but maybe it's not Microsoft charging them, maybe it's the publishers charging these guys, I don't really know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whatever, that doesn't...
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: So what are the key points out of this whole thing?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because we got to get to the bottom line here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, a couple more.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're going to allow you to give your games to a friend.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you can enable your disc-based game.
[SPEAKER_03]: You give it to a friend, basically.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's no fees.
[SPEAKER_03]: But there's two requirements in order to transfer this to your friend.
[SPEAKER_03]: they have to be on your friends list for 30 days and you can only give it you can only give the game once once it's been transferred to them I don't think that they can give it back to someone else now I don't know if that's clarified if there is so no wishing for more wishes
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, but I mean, if it is where you can give it to somebody, you know, the friends listening is kind of annoying, but like say you can give it to them and then they can give it to somebody else, you know, that's not so bad, but it's still annoying.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: I will give credit where credit is due.
[SPEAKER_04]: It sounds like Microsoft's trying to implement the Kindle book borrowing thing, which just sounds a lot like.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm like, all right, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I know I lend out a lot of video games I never get back.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: They can be handled all digitally.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, you know, what am I having to give up?
[SPEAKER_04]: What's the minus for this plus, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: And last but not least, I'll just breeze through this.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Kinect stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: They say you're in control of what the Kinect can see and hear.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I guess you get to adjust your privacy settings or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: So the system will navigate you through key privacy options like automatic or manual sign-in, privacy settings, and clear notification of how data is used.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wait, how is data being used?
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'm assuming this thing is just going to be listening for advertising purposes and stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: If they hear a lot of wank, a lot of porn.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're in control of the Kinect sensor sensing on, off, or pause.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can turn off your Xbox One.
[SPEAKER_03]: They say it's only listening for a single voice command of Xbox On, but come on.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're in control of your personal data, and you can use other inputs to control your games, TV, and entertainment experiences.
[SPEAKER_03]: So once again, why do I need the Kinect?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm gonna be honest, and I'm not trying to be that snarky kid on Twitter, but this is really kind of like a vague answer that they kind of gave to this.
[SPEAKER_04]: So does it have to be on or not?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it's basically, it has to be connected to your system, but I think you can... Point it at the wall and cover the mic?
[SPEAKER_03]: You can turn your system off or something and it won't be listening.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just don't underestimate the value of privacy and all that.
[SPEAKER_04]: And this is really badly timed for Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, again... There's a lot of news that's great.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a lot of news out there right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not trying to get political.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not going to take the show there.
[SPEAKER_04]: But there's a lot of news right now about privacy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Microsoft's name's involved.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: So this is not a good time to be requiring anything with that connect.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they're saying that some of the examples, of course, they've mentioned before, a fitness game can measure your heart rate, give you feedback about your exercise routine or whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: You'll be able to tell if you're a communist.
[SPEAKER_03]: A card game could allow you to bluff your virtual opponent using your facial expressions.
[SPEAKER_03]: But once again, the Kinect could allow you to scan in your objects and use them in real games.
[SPEAKER_03]: That never happens, so who knows.
[SPEAKER_03]: But yeah, okay, so that's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's basically the information.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: You ever seen that show Shark Tank?
[SPEAKER_04]: You ever watch that show?
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's the premise of the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: These guys pitch their ideas to all these big executives.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like Mark Cuban's one of the executives that sits there.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's actually, as far as reality TV goes, it's one of the better shows because it's a little more like these guys are real business makers and you kind of see, like, I don't know, there's less of the pompousness that comes with the Donald Trump business show and there's a little more, like, you know, reality, I guess, for lack of a better term.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, anyway, the whole pitch is that as you're given these ideas, if one of the executives says, I'm out, that's their sign that they are not going to put a bid.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if all four of them say, I'm out, the guy loses, walks away, doesn't get the financing they want.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I got to admit, after listening to this whole detail thing that's gone on this week, I'm kind of sitting in that chair.
[SPEAKER_04]: And when I'm hearing about the whole, here's the minuses, here's a plus in the game trading and all that, but here's all these minuses that suddenly these $60 games may not be worth anything anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: But...
[SPEAKER_04]: I do not have... That's what I hate the most.
[SPEAKER_04]: I no longer have the power to sell this game on eBay.
[SPEAKER_04]: If I want to do it, I have to go to a GameStop or a comparable store.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you kidding me?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's not what I want.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's the point where I said, I'm out.
[SPEAKER_03]: And on top of that, the plus is like, oh, you can loan it to your friend.
[SPEAKER_03]: Something I can do already right now with all these fucking restrictions.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why do I even... And that's the thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's so sad that this has to happen because I want to be excited about this new console.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to be excited about the games that they're coming out with.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I'm sorry, even if there's like a new Crackdown game or whatever the big awesome game they're going to show us, all this stuff is just like right in front of me.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's like, well, that sounds cool, but nope.
[SPEAKER_03]: To me, it's very much like how I treat Origin.
[SPEAKER_03]: Battlefield 3 looks fucking amazing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I really want to play that game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not installing Origin, so therefore I'm not going to play the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it's unfortunate.
[SPEAKER_03]: These games look awesome, but all this stuff stands in my way, so I'm not going to do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: For me, a lot of it is kind of about control.
[SPEAKER_04]: Control.
[SPEAKER_04]: and I feel like what's happening this console generation that I just don't fucking like is that the publishers are trying to take all these things away from me that I used to get as the investor in the game you know what I mean like I used to be able to sell the used games and you know trade the games I wanted to and they could put in the disc or whatever like
[SPEAKER_04]: The publishers have been slowly thinking of ways to take that away, and I just don't like it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And look, I understand the cost of developing a game is super expensive and all that, but the line's gotta be drawn somewhere.
[SPEAKER_03]: It doesn't have to be super expensive.
[SPEAKER_03]: They decide to go big and, you know, big and bold, I guess, for their games.
[SPEAKER_03]: It doesn't have to be.
[SPEAKER_03]: Indie games that come out are still just as good.
[SPEAKER_03]: How much did it cost to develop Minecraft?
[SPEAKER_03]: Granted, it's not as visually stunning as something else, but
[SPEAKER_03]: It doesn't have to be visually stunning.
[SPEAKER_03]: It just has to be fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: It has to be fun to play.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's all it has to be.
[SPEAKER_04]: I understand that, that this is the way the industry wants to move, but I have a right to say I'm not moving with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think we all have that right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, the industries don't determine what the consumers do.
[SPEAKER_10]: The consumers determine what the industry should do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I want to make an analogy to where I think this is all going, but actually first I want to address, because I see numerous people in chat rooms saying, well, that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: PS4 is for me this generation.
[SPEAKER_04]: But...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_03]: and I mean look at all the stuff that's happened you know before all this this this whole three-page thing came out there was reports going Microsoft canceled their after you know conference Q&A session they canceled their one-on-one interviews they just don't want to talk to people then they put this stuff out and that's it they're just leaving it at that but on top of all this
[SPEAKER_03]: So, first off, the whole game sharing thing with your family and stuff, don't assume for one second that they're not going to expect each one of those people to have live, you know, a paid subscription to live in order for that to happen.
[SPEAKER_03]: So why am I having to pay money for this console, pay money for live?
[SPEAKER_03]: and like it's like I have to pay for the privilege to be like fucked over because you want to start you're feeling greedy or something that you feel like we're just not giving you enough money I also just don't like the fact that the Xbox has to talk to the servers once every 24 hours because you know
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not that I have a problem with it in theory or on paper.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, you know, I play a lot of MMOs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course those talk to the servers.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not so much caring about it in principle, but the reality is what's going to happen when those servers go down?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because they will go down.
[SPEAKER_04]: And history has shown that this is what happens.
[SPEAKER_04]: PlayStation Network down for months due to a hack attack.
[SPEAKER_04]: You don't think there's kiddies out there that want to hack this new network the minute it goes up because they're angry too?
[SPEAKER_04]: What happens then?
[SPEAKER_04]: You're not going to be able to convince me otherwise.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because history has shown it will go down and what is going to happen.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wank.
[SPEAKER_03]: There is no server on the face of the earth that has not gone down for any period of time.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I know they're saying that it's going to have a ton of servers or virtual servers or whatever, but they're going to have to perform maintenance on these things.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's got to go down for maintenance for a certain amount of time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um...
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it's just... It's gonna lock people out at some point.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can we go back to PlayStation 4, though?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I do think there's a distinct possibility at least some of this is gonna be true about Sony's system as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: And to which parts, not sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it seems like maybe the game registration, especially... And you told me before the show...
[SPEAKER_04]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think they wouldn't have gone all in if they didn't know that it was a guarantee from both console manufacturers.
[SPEAKER_03]: And honestly, we have to see how similar it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: If it's very similar, there's some serious antitrust concerns there because these guys just sit down and make...
[SPEAKER_03]: Decide, hey, we're going to do this.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is how we're going to do this system.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're going to both be on board.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're going to both benefit from it because they're going to have no choice.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're going to get rid of options for them.
[SPEAKER_03]: I... Like, you know, even though there's all this negative information, I have to wait until when the consoles come out before I can make my decision, because they could very well, hopefully, you know, say, fuck you guys, you know... Seriously, to EA, okay, what are they gonna do?
[SPEAKER_03]: They gotta kind of get some balls here, because...
[SPEAKER_03]: What's Microsoft gonna do?
[SPEAKER_03]: They can say, fuck you, EA.
[SPEAKER_03]: What are you gonna do?
[SPEAKER_03]: Not publish games on our console?
[SPEAKER_03]: And if Microsoft and Sony does that, what are they gonna do?
[SPEAKER_03]: Publish PC only?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, they're not.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have to kind of agree on some sort of partnership here.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just...
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, if Sony, let's just say in a perfect world, Sony would say, okay, listen, we're not going to put up with this bullshit.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're just going to keep things kind of the way they are right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they could totally have this in the bag easy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Easy this generation could come out on top and just totally rule everything.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I have a feeling that's not the case.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think Microsoft would take a risk like that without knowing that both parties are going to do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: but yet you know there's going to be some little differences in policy because for instance we heard last week about how Sony is mandating that there be off screen play or whatever for PlayStation Vita so there are going to be little twists in the rules so maybe
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe Microsoft implemented, just theorizing, tinfoil hat here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe Microsoft invented the whole game sharing, Amazon Kindle thing to try and put a little positive in a negative that they agreed to with Sony.
[SPEAKER_04]: And maybe Sony's not going to have that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe Sony's only got the negative.
[SPEAKER_04]: And their positive is the PlayStation Vita Play.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you think there might be some of that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: but so what you can do that anyways just you know you loan your games to your friends if you really want to I just don't I don't want to like just say well at least they have this okay well that's good but no they're taking away all this stuff from us I'm sorry I'll just stick with what I've got right now and if I have to I'll just go PC because at least there there's flexibility with I know I know there's DRM with Steam but
[SPEAKER_03]: There's also mods with Steam.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's also all sorts of customization.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's indie games.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's just insane sales on stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can honestly say, yes, I use Steam, but I really think I maybe ever bought one game.
[SPEAKER_04]: One game in the years I've owned Steam, I've bought one game full retail price, and that would have been Civ V. You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: A PC-only game.
[SPEAKER_10]: I never have.
[SPEAKER_10]: And even when I could have gotten... Yeah, the stupid Origin bullshit.
[SPEAKER_10]: But when I bought Mass Effect 3, for example.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I bought it new, but I went and price matched somewhere so I didn't pay full price for it and didn't go through Origin.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: If Microsoft were to announce at the end of their press conference, by the way, we're going to be lowering the price of games from $60 to $30.
[SPEAKER_04]: I...
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm in.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm back in.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because if that's the plus, that the games are now going to cost half as much, you know, so okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: They have to have an incentive to make people win.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll be back in in a heartbeat.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not going to happen.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because here's what it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: You think that you're going to get better prices because now they're getting rid of the used market, so to speak.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not going to happen because on PC you have multiple storefronts that are competing with each other.
[SPEAKER_03]: And yeah, it may be all Steam DRM and stuff, but they're having sales all across the board.
[SPEAKER_03]: With Microsoft going this route, not only are you going to be limited where you can trade your game in, so right there you're not going to get a really good deal as far as trading value goes because hey, where else are you going to go?
[SPEAKER_03]: We're your only option.
[SPEAKER_03]: So your trading value is going to fucking suck to begin with.
[SPEAKER_03]: And on top of that, you think they're really going to mark down prices of games?
[SPEAKER_03]: Hell,
[SPEAKER_03]: There's games on their Xbox games on demand service right now that are still way above what you can actually get them in a disk space format.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, no, you're kidding yourself.
[SPEAKER_04]: A couple great comments in our chat room I want to get to.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ahamkara in our chat says, I noticed Japan is not porting some of their best games out of the country, offer good games to themselves for cheap or free, and don't seem to care.
[SPEAKER_04]: Funny how Microsoft is giving them the finger now by focusing on TV for Xbox One and not caring about Japan as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I mean, we've all kind of sat here going, well, clearly Microsoft's written off Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: But if Sony were to adopt these similar measures, how would that impact Japanese gaming culture?
[SPEAKER_04]: Are Japanese gamers... I mean, I honestly don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are Japanese gamers as willing to buy into all this?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think... Go ahead.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think that it's not necessarily going to work because from what I've seen, and of course we need somebody who lives there to confirm this, there's a big culture around having collectibles being one of the campers to get the game the first day, like the big lines around the Capcom store for whenever a Monster Hunter game comes out.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a different type of culture.
[SPEAKER_10]: We may have a few people standing in line for a new system release or for having maybe one super special game, like the Madden ones, but it's nowhere near the crazy levels that it happens in Japan.
[SPEAKER_11]: Right.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, and then, like, for example, I mean, I keep bringing up my stupid Cardcaptor Sakura Dreamcast game.
[SPEAKER_10]: It had a pillow, pillowcase, and a clock, and a fork, and a spoon.
[SPEAKER_10]: And a dish.
[SPEAKER_10]: And a dish, yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: But, I mean, and there was a Sakura Taisen game that came out in the same type of bundle.
[SPEAKER_10]: But, I mean, there's lots of crazy-ass special editions that come out, and people like their packaging.
[SPEAKER_04]: Akuma JP like clockwork shows up in chat when you said we need somebody from Japan to be listening, but he just turned the station on.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're talking about the Microsoft Xbox One DRM restrictions.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I was just kind of wondering if Sony's going down that same route.
[SPEAKER_04]: How does that impact Japanese gaming culture?
[SPEAKER_04]: Are the Japanese going to be as willing to buy into some of these restrictions?
[SPEAKER_10]: I still think there's going to be physical packaging.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's still going to be copies you can buy and sell.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because there's a big part of the economy around that and there's a big part of the culture around that.
[SPEAKER_10]: You even see a few people over here who like to get their import special editions and everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, one more comment I want to get here from chat, and then I do kind of want to move on with the show, because we have a lot of news to cover in this pre-E3 week, and I know we're going to get back to this topic during phone calls tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I want to get this comment here from Koopa Kid Jeremy says, Thankfully, Nintendo isn't smart enough with online to even be able to implement these types of features.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, this is something I've kind of referenced in past episodes on the show when we were all worried about this, is that could Nintendo end up as the...
[SPEAKER_04]: right now they're the dog in the corner chasing its tail looking a little silly and everybody's like what a weird dog but now all of a sudden it's like it's the most attractive puppy in the room and everybody might want to adopt it has Nintendo's failure to embrace online which granted probably is what drove EA does that suddenly make them the most attractive option to Japanese gamers to people like me that feel like I'm out I don't want all these
[SPEAKER_04]: and Draconia Measures.
[SPEAKER_10]: Honestly, I would... If they put an Xbox... Actually, as I've been calling it, the Xbox in front of me versus a Wii U, giving me money and said, pick one to buy.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can buy one.
[SPEAKER_10]: I would go for the Wii U.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, do you have a thought?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because then I'm going to ask Jamie a very tough question.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, Lord.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I still don't want a Wii U. And the reason it goes back to the original reason why I don't want a Wii U is because there's nothing I want to play on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I don't really consider it a next-gen console.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, honestly, the stuff you're going to see on the Wii U, especially coming out of new games, is stuff that's going to be ported to the Xbox 360 and PlayStation 3 already.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't need to buy another console for games that I can play on my console that I already have.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, the only advantage I see, and it's been kind of, I've been thinking about it more because my wife has been really hogging the TV, is that off-screen, or the, you know, second screenplay stuff is kind of cool, because I do want to play console games a lot of times, and my wife wants to watch TV, so, you know, that is the only positive, but once again, it's, I don't want to buy a new console just for that, because I have my laptop, I can play on my laptop if I'm really willing to, so...
[SPEAKER_03]: No one's holding a gun to my head to force me to buy a new console.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't have to.
[SPEAKER_03]: If that's the thought process that they're going in with it, saying, well, that's why EA can get rid of their online passes because, hey, they've got to buy another console at some point.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I don't.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't have to do anything.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't have to follow what you want me to do.
[SPEAKER_03]: And don't think for one second that no one's going to figure out a way to put some sort of device in between your console and the internet to fucking spoof that authentication server.
[SPEAKER_04]: I kind of think that's what's going to happen too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hackers going to hack, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: it's gonna happen they will and this will be a focus uh YYR in chat says all these draconian restrictions aren't going to send most gamers to aren't going to send most gamers to Wii U the Nintendo fans will already buy one and everyone else will just not buy a console I think if anything I think people will still buy a next gen console even though they hate everything because they're like well I gotta play Killer Instinct or I gotta play whatever
[SPEAKER_04]: I always try to gauge this.
[SPEAKER_04]: In the years I've been doing this show and the commentary and everything, I find that the best insight comes from non-gamers, truly.
[SPEAKER_04]: If I want to really get a feel for where America's head is really at, I'm not going to look for it on Twitter.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, guys, I'm not going to look for it with you because we're a very unique, smaller sort of subset fan base.
[SPEAKER_04]: and I look to general people, people that don't consider themselves gamers.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you know, this week I was on a work trip in Phoenix and I was with a couple co-workers and the subject of video games came up just randomly.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think somebody had asked about my podcast and I was talking about it kind of casually and he mentioned, yeah, oh yeah, I really like Assassin's Creed and yeah, I heard about that Xbox One but...
[SPEAKER_04]: I heard it's not going to play any of the used stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think I want to get one.
[SPEAKER_04]: It sounds like it's too restrictive.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm kind of just thinking in the back of my head, I'm like, I wonder if there's a lot of people that when they just kind of hear what a friend of a friend says to them, they're going to run with that.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_04]: Gamers will buy the console.
[SPEAKER_04]: There'll be something on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: There will be PlayStation 4s that sell.
[SPEAKER_04]: There will be Xbox Ones that sell.
[SPEAKER_04]: Will they sell more than Wii U?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know the best time to buy an Xbox One is going to be the end of the generation when they do eventually shut down those authentication servers and let's assume that they go the Steam route and they unlock it so that you don't have to call in every 24 hours.
[SPEAKER_03]: It just works.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or they can be fucking dicks and say, well, fuck, none of your shit is going to work now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me ask Jamie the difficult question, then we'll move into our gaming week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I open this up to the chatters as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: For the 11 years this month that we've been doing Orange Lounge Radio, we've always had a mantra on this show.
[SPEAKER_04]: 11 years.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we're actually having a show on June 23rd this year, which is the birthday.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: but Microsoft's about to unveil 15 exclusives which might include some of the things we've been clamoring for for a long time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Killer Instinct, perhaps that Banjo-Kazooie thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to fanboy wank here.
[SPEAKER_04]: But now because of all these things that the system is doing, I'm coming back to question, is that mantra still true?
[SPEAKER_10]: I think we may have to evolve it.
[SPEAKER_10]: because we've got a system now that's doing things that systems didn't do in the past.
[SPEAKER_10]: We have a new restriction being placed on how they're trying to change how the system works.
[SPEAKER_10]: And so with that, I believe, I'm trying to think of how to phrase this.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think that the games themselves should speak for themselves, but they have to be made accessible.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you don't have access to the game, it does you no good.
[SPEAKER_10]: If it's not going to give you a way to play the game that's... I hope I'm making sense of this.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a tough question I just unloaded on you.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's tough to phrase.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I just kind of feel like the golden rule of gaming may finally have shown a blemish this week.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think that to be able to appreciate the game being on the system, you have to have a system that's going to allow you to enjoy it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Does that make sense?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_10]: It has to work.
[SPEAKER_04]: It has to, like, for the Nintendo, you put the cartridge in the system and you know it's gonna work.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even if you blow on the cartridge a hundred times, you know, it has to just work, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: But now we're calling into question, is this really gonna work?
[SPEAKER_10]: I have to quote Queen Semia, sprinkles on a turd don't make it any more tasty.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because actually, that's pretty much how it is.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think that...
[SPEAKER_10]: Ugh, God, it's hard for me to say.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me try this from ClericalEra404 in chat.
[SPEAKER_04]: At live.vognetwork.com, ClericalEra404 says, I think the mantra needs to evolve in that it needs to have the games, but also the versatility, the more games that are accessible by more people and potential players.
[SPEAKER_04]: Power to the players, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: Agreed.
[SPEAKER_10]: The evil G there.
[SPEAKER_10]: But...
[SPEAKER_10]: here's really where my thought is on this one and I hope this makes sense because I've been trying to the thoughts clear in my head but it's kind of hard to bring into words a system is only as good as the games that are accessible on it
[SPEAKER_10]: Preach.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I'm using an example here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Back in the day, I'm going to use Symphony of the Night for Saturn and for PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because I've got them both.
[SPEAKER_10]: I like the Saturn version better.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was accessible to me at the time because I could import it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Other people, but say that I had no means of importing the game and all I had was a $20 copy that I bought used at GameStop because you could buy them used at GameStop.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well then I would say, well of course I like the PlayStation version because I haven't been able to play it on the Saturn.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have no basis of comparison.
[SPEAKER_10]: So say that you've got this system here that you don't want to...
[SPEAKER_10]: Invest in because of its practices around the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Say the PS4 comes out and it's fully open and everything's nice and lovely and the same games come out for it, you're still going to go with the one that's more accessible to you because that's what you have.
[SPEAKER_10]: You have no basis of comparison.
[SPEAKER_10]: Saying X version is better isn't necessarily fair because you can't compare it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that the reason why I tend to buy games on the PlayStation 3 over the Xbox 360 for the mere simple fact that I like the controller better?
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, that's really the same thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not always.
[SPEAKER_04]: But then I go, if I want to play the game online with friends, I go to the 360 because it's got the better network.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you, ClericalEra404.
[SPEAKER_10]: As said, I loves you for preferring the Saturn version.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just because I really like playing as Maria, okay?
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, all right.
[SPEAKER_10]: But anyway, the whole point is that the games being good to play is also determined by the other factors that go into actually playing the game itself, like for you, the controller.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, for me, I love playing Saturn games because the dual analog controller does not hurt my hand, even to this day.
[SPEAKER_10]: But playing, like, I'm better with RPG, like, I like playing RPGs better now because I get to move my hand.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't have to keep moving my thumb around and, you know, pulling at my scar on my hand.
[SPEAKER_10]: All the scar tissue I've got.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it's really going to be a matter of how you play it as well as the content itself.
[SPEAKER_10]: And if it's not allowing you to access that content, then why bother?
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it's a complex issue.
[SPEAKER_04]: Any quick last words, Loki, you want to get in before we move on here?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, it's just, I'm just disappointed that this news came out now and not after, because I wish I could be a little bit excited about what Microsoft's showing, but once again... You sound like a tweet I made earlier this week that every year I'm so excited about E3 and like, yay, new games, yay.
[SPEAKER_04]: This year, I really have a sense of dread about E3.
[SPEAKER_04]: This year, it's about, how am I getting fucked over this year?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, and I'm sorry to sound like that jaded gamershateeverything.com guy, but...
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not gonna lie to you, that's where I'm at right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whether I'm overreacting or not, it's a lot of money.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're asking me to drop on a console where it's not even really my console.
[SPEAKER_04]: At some point, I've got to put my foot down and say, I love video games, but no, I'm done.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here's another question, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: How are they even going to enable this with the first sale doctrine and stuff?
[SPEAKER_03]: I just don't know if they're going to say, well, you're licensing stuff from us now.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know if they're going to be able to.
[SPEAKER_03]: Considering how sue-happy everything is, I think we could very well see that this is going to be a lawsuit within a year or so.
[SPEAKER_03]: I forgot to make my analogy, so I'll make it quick.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I thought you did.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I didn't.
[SPEAKER_04]: I make a lot of crazy analogies.
[SPEAKER_04]: There was one I was sitting on all week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who remembers DivX?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh my God.
[SPEAKER_10]: When they had the DivX players?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not talking about the codec on your computer that lets you watch movies and things like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm talking about when there was actually a DivX player at Circuit City.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it always had to be connected online because you could rent the movies at the store and the thing ended up flopping.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why did the DivX flop?
[SPEAKER_10]: because of all the restrictions on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: There weren't any games on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, there weren't any movies for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, there was the same movies that were on DVD and Laserdisc.
[SPEAKER_10]: And for the people who don't know what DivX is, just think of the little mascot from Penny Arcade.
[SPEAKER_10]: They have that little DivX player character.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's a DivX machine.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm sorry, but right now what I'm hearing out of Xbox One sounds very DivX to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: People rejected DivX because they wanted to own their shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they didn't want to have to keep dialing this server that was Daddy Steven Spielberg, who was a co-owner in this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Daddy Steven Spielberg, may I watch this movie?
[SPEAKER_10]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_10]: People want to have control in the end.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: GameGuru in chat.
[SPEAKER_04]: DivX, the disc player that killed Circuit City.
[SPEAKER_04]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_04]: It brought down an entire chain with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't think that the DivX didn't have a lasting negative impact on Circuit City.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, and also keep in mind, there...
[SPEAKER_10]: I just completely lost my train of thought.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, it was the fact that you still have people today that even though we've got iTunes and we have all this digital distribution, there's still people who like to physically go out and buy a disc, who will prefer to buy their music on CD.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's quite a few people in chat agreeing with you, yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, I'm not necessarily one of them, but...
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Lots of passion behind this topic.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure we'll hear more about it during our phone call segment later, as well as the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mailbag at OrangeLaunchRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be a very interesting E3 week.
[SPEAKER_10]: Rob will answer it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be a very interesting E3 week.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all I have to say.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm really looking forward to next week's show when Sony will have to put it out on the table because they didn't cancel their media stuff, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: So they're going to have to answer this question.
[SPEAKER_04]: And finally, we'll have a clearer picture to what things are going to look like come this fall.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: But I had a really good time doing it.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I really liked what it added to the, as I'm calling it, the main timeline lore.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was really good.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I've actually been enjoying that.
[SPEAKER_10]: And they kind of set the skill trees back to how they used to be.
[SPEAKER_10]: Not necessarily exactly the same, and I kind of respect my Vice Admiral incorrectly, but still, they did a lot of really cool stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: And actually, I'll tell you what was funny, because I was just running around on my Vice Admiral, because I have her pretty much permanently parked at Deep Space Nine.
[SPEAKER_10]: They put Morn in Quark's bar, and like, as a big DS9 fan, that made me stupendously happy.
[SPEAKER_10]: It even had him quote telling a story even though he never talks.
[SPEAKER_10]: It just sort of did a fade out and him shaking his head forlornly and everything.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_10]: I did start Marvel Heroes.
[SPEAKER_10]: I do not care for it.
[SPEAKER_10]: It reminded me a bit of playing Marvel Ultimate Alliance without the fun part of having other people to play with.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting because you're the first one I've heard say something negative about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, everybody has their opinion, it's just interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm not saying it wasn't fun, and yeah, it's free to play, but if I wanted another character, I pretty much have to buy 20 bucks worth of points for one character, or if I bought $40 worth of points, that would get me, you know, maybe three characters, and the one that I really wanted to play, she had a sprite for it, but she wasn't accessible to buy, because as I've made no...
[SPEAKER_10]: No secret of this, my favorite Marvel character is Jessica Jones because she's badass.
[SPEAKER_10]: So anyway, I played through the whole first mission as Scarlet Witch and it was just like a not quite as fun version of Marvel Ultimate Alliance and I would rather play Marvel Ultimate Alliance.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm gonna check I want to check out this Marvel Heroes game I just I was busy this past week so I didn't get a chance to check it out but it wasn't bad I'm gonna say it wasn't bad but it wasn't enough to make me want to spend any amount of money on it I mean I might play it a little bit more I've got Scarlet Witch she's pretty cool I almost picked Hawkeye because you know Hawkeye but I went for her you just wanted to stare at his booty no I'm you know what that's objectification Robin I take exception to that
[SPEAKER_10]: um but uh it was all right it was all right and as a male I am totally okay with the objectification of Hawkeye just saying
[SPEAKER_10]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft
[SPEAKER_10]: and then um yes Claire Claire it's because it's Jeremy Renner and I think he's pretty um and intelligent and intelligent um but uh
[SPEAKER_10]: What was I saying?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I actually, I have a high-res mod.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, it's really, you have to sort of manually mod your INI files yourself and then use text mod for the high-resolution textures.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I figured out that why my game kept shutting down is because I didn't have this, there's like a little program you can run to make it accept higher memory usage.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Which, I mean, I've got a card that, you know, gives me two extra gig of VRAM, so I don't know what's going on.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I ended up getting that working, and...
[SPEAKER_10]: It was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I actually, I can tell you this, that I don't get as sick as I did with some of the higher res textures.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I'm pretty much just running through the game and trying to get all the stuff I missed.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm actually also doing a different background than what I used to do, because I always used to do either a colonist or a spacer, but I would always do Soul Survivor, and now I'm doing a war hero, which is...
[SPEAKER_10]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_10]: and um god I was playing something else too and I don't remember what it was
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't remember what it was.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll come back to you if you think of it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, Dan is really irritated with Grid 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because he says that the collision detection in that game is just really shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't played it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, you know, he has that driving rig.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, no, I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: He loves his driving rig.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's a manly man.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, Loki, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_03]: Unfortunately, I did not play, I don't think, anything, actually.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it's just...
[SPEAKER_03]: Boss has been out all week, so they haven't played any Call of Duty, and I didn't really play anything in the week, I was working on my laptop for most of the week, and then my laptop broke, so then I had to fix my laptop, so I've been busy with that, so yeah, I did buy the Serious Sam bundle thing that they have on the Humble Bundle Weekly thing, so that's kind of cool, so hopefully I'll play some of that soon, and just watch the Watch Dogs trailer for E3, the E3 trailer in
[SPEAKER_03]: Looks fantastic.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't wait for that game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did that just release tonight?
[SPEAKER_03]: It leaked out, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything else?
[SPEAKER_04]: That is it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm only really going to talk about one new game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was in Phoenix for a lot of the week for the day job, so that kind of kept me away from most of my games besides iPad and portable games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've talked a lot about on the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: My random game to play on the airplane.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank heavens for the Game Boy Advance games and the NES games and all that on the 3DS for the early adopters.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mario Kart Game Boy Advance.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know why, it actually is one of the weaker Mario Kart games, just control wise and everything, but I was like, I want to unlock the special cup, so I did it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, the real game I've been playing a bit of at least the past couple days is Animal Crossing New Leaf.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the 3D version of Animal Crossing that just came out.
[SPEAKER_04]: What can I say?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some of the differences, though, I noticed that they put a lot of the stores that used to be sprinkled throughout your town.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not really the mall thing like the Wii did, but there's other side of the tracks now, like a Main Street, where all the Nooks, the Able Sisters, Tom Nook, who's now the realtor because he gave the convenience store to his kids.
[SPEAKER_04]: and some other stuff is all that stuff's on the other side of the tracks the museum's there too so it's kind of neat to have kind of everything in that one place that really opens up your town to have a little bit more of your design when it comes to the trees and the flowers and all that all the online experience is pretty much similar to what I noticed in the previous games you open up your train gates and people can come visit in fact I should open mine up and see if anyone comes to visit
[SPEAKER_04]: and then you can close them when you're ready for people to get out so a lot of that hasn't changed but I know they brought the island back and there's a lot more fruits available thanks to the island some of the other things I noticed is that the story is a lot different because now you're the mayor so you have an assistant Isabella who kind of helps you or I'm assuming everybody has the same one I don't even know
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's just kind of fun to grow your little neighborhood and interact with the people.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then the online element provides a lot of fun with that.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's $35 since it's a handheld game, not $60 like a lot of console games cost.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I think that's priced pretty good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sometimes you just want to do a little bit of fishing, donate it to the museum, make some bells.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's get into quick housekeeping.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mentioned this earlier in the show, but do keep an eye on this week, e3.vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is our interactive E3 experience at the Voice of Geeks Network that's going to be led by VOG Network's Bobby Blackwolf, who will be on the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Show Floor at E3 and he will be getting answers to your questions.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because once Bobby's done these appointments and played some of the games, he wants to see what you guys want to hear about.
[SPEAKER_04]: But all we ask, don't ask the obvious things that are already in the press releases and don't ask about this stinking Xbox used game thing because we all know they're not going to comment further on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: but you know whatever it is you want to hear more about it uh go take a look at e3.vognetwork.com it has all the information you need question submissions open up after the Sony press conference tomorrow when we're really going to know where things stand okay um we'll hear from Bobby Blackwolf on that a little more later because we are going to have a list list later tonight uh the thing we most want to see happen at E3 2013 that'll be in part b later in the show but first let's run through some gaming news and Loki start us off
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, so there's a rumor going around that GameStop is discontinuing the Wii U Basic after June 18th.
[SPEAKER_03]: And basically, the rumor comes from that they've been getting, like there's an internal email saying that they're going to be sending back all the basic units and that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, Nintendo has followed up with this, saying that there's a current misperception about the Wii U hardware.
[SPEAKER_03]: To clarify, Nintendo is working with its retail partners to simply rebalance the stock of white 8GB systems and black 32GB Wii U models in the market.
[SPEAKER_03]: Consumers looking for either model will continue to find them available.
[SPEAKER_03]: That doesn't make any sense to me, but okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then, of course, there's a follow-up to that where another retailer was saying that they received an email that they're going to be recalling all the 8GB systems.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think, if anything, this has to do with the fact that they're talking about putting out a white 3GB, 2GB system.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm wondering if they're just going to get rid of the 8GB system altogether because...
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe that's not as popular.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know a lot of people that buy Wii U's, at least as far as my customers are concerned.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's buying the basics?
[SPEAKER_04]: Not a lot of people.
[SPEAKER_04]: They want the pack-in game.
[SPEAKER_04]: They want the stuff that comes with the deluxe.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wouldn't blame Nintendo at all if they're phasing the basics out of the market.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think the 18th coincides well with being after E3, so maybe an announcement in the new
[SPEAKER_04]: That's my fingers.
[SPEAKER_04]: My real hope is that they're getting rid of the basics because they're going to drop the price of the deluxes down to where the basics are.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be phenomenal news.
[SPEAKER_04]: And what a great opportunity for Nintendo to kick their competition in the balls while all this other talk about the usage restrictions and all this is going on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nintendo could really strike them in the jugular and you might still hate everything that Nintendo has to offer but you gotta recognize that there's gonna be a lot of people that are here for Mario Kart and 3D Mario and all this stuff it wouldn't be that hard for them to refurbish all those old systems to pop that 8 gigabyte storage chip off there and put a 3 gigabyte chip there in place so it wouldn't be that hard very well could happen
[SPEAKER_04]: Alan Alchemy in our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com says, 8 gigabytes is just an embarrassingly insufficient amount of memory by today's standards, period.
[SPEAKER_04]: Budget console or no?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's very true.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not a lot.
[SPEAKER_04]: So Nintendo's got to catch up.
[SPEAKER_04]: But don't catch up too much to what else is going on in the world.
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on to other news out of E3, Square Enix mentioning what they're going to be showing at their E3 booth.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sometimes things get left off of this, but I'll say what there is so far.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kingdom Hearts 1.5 Remix on PlayStation 3, Final Fantasy XIV A Realm Reborn, which makes sense because I believe Beta 3 starts next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it comes out in August.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, so they're counting down there.
[SPEAKER_08]: They've also changed restrictions on the beta stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, NDA is lifted.
[SPEAKER_10]: But still, you're not allowed to say anything on the previous betas.
[SPEAKER_04]: Final Fantasy X and X-2 HD Remaster for the Vita and PlayStation 3 Deus Ex Human Revolution Director's Cut for Wii U
[SPEAKER_04]: and Thief, another big title on its way.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, there are rumors that there could be something additional there as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently, the future of Final Fantasy being teased for Tuesday, June 11th, 9 a.m.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rumors and rumblings suggesting it's Final Fantasy XV.
[SPEAKER_03]: uh whether that is what 13 versus has been put through a remodel and that's now 15 or maybe this news is just 13 versus no it's gonna be something new for the playstation 4 and the probably the xbox one because remember the playstation 4 of it they showed the same fucking trailer that they had before and they're like and we'll have more to announce 33 you know so it's it's gonna be something new for next gen it's probably gonna be using their new engine that they have
[SPEAKER_04]: It is sad to me though that Dragon Quest X just probably isn't going to happen over here, is it?
[SPEAKER_04]: I was kind of hoping that maybe they would announce that at E3, that maybe they were just going to solely back Wii U. I really wish they would try with Dragon Quest X, but...
[SPEAKER_10]: Dragon Quest 9 Dragon Quest 9
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Quest Swords, that's what it was.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, this is purely rumor, okay?
[SPEAKER_10]: So I'm just going to go ahead and spit it out there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Allegedly stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: There is a rumor going around that Microsoft has been paying off third-party developers not to show off anything for PlayStation 4 either on stage or at their booths.
[SPEAKER_10]: That Microsoft has resorted to paying them off for this.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now, I don't know if this is true or not, but the report came from a source on NeoGAF that's done a lot of true research.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here is your nice big salt lick to go with this.
[SPEAKER_10]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it did come from someone who in the past has been reliable.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, now this would put weight in the column of maybe Sony isn't in the same camp as Microsoft because otherwise it's, what are you so afraid of, Microsoft?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, the whole point is that the theory is that if this is really what's going on, that Microsoft is trying to give the illusion that they're going to have more games available than the PS4 will.
[SPEAKER_10]: Which would make them look more attractive.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's not that Microsoft and Sony haven't struck at each other financially before.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Microsoft got a lot of DLC agreements.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sony got the whole Valve tie-in portal like everybody bought Portal 2 on PlayStation 3 because everything well not everybody but a lot of people did because of you know their agreements with Valve and the Steam integration which was really good I got mine on Steam yeah well you got you bought it it was a gift but still well you bought it on PS3 and you got it on both no I didn't no no I you did but I mean I didn't care about it on PS3 at all I got it on on Windows yeah
[SPEAKER_04]: So paying for exclusives and paying off for stuff like that, that's not really... But it's just in light of everything else going on in the gaming industry is what makes a lot of people kind of leech onto this news.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, and it could just be something that was thrown out there for the purpose of, you know, making Microsoft look bad too.
[SPEAKER_04]: But at the same time... They don't need a NeoGAF thread to do that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know that at this point that I would put anything past past them right now especially since this type of shit goes on all the time in the corporate world so saying but isn't it weird how Microsoft and Sony would have had to agree to this thing and then now they strike at each other in corporate warfare in these other ways it's really it's kind of sick
[SPEAKER_04]: in some ways.
[SPEAKER_10]: Welcome to corporate America.
[SPEAKER_04]: Welcome to the world corporation.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not just America, honey.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know, I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I'm saying it's business.
[SPEAKER_10]: And in the end, what companies most care about is their bottom line.
[SPEAKER_10]: And they will do what they can to increase it.
[SPEAKER_10]: End of story.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, so let's see, let's talk a little bit about Plants vs. Zombies.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you may remember they had an announcement for Plants vs. Zombies 2, it's about time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well now there's some actual banners being spotted at E3 showing Plants vs. Zombies Garden Warfare.
[SPEAKER_10]: I am excited.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which is, rumors to be true, I think they were saying that it's a multiplayer first person shooter game.
[SPEAKER_03]: So...
[SPEAKER_10]: I am no longer excited.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, there's still the Plants vs. Zombies 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm excited about that, but first person shooter, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, so I remember actually hearing about that before, so it'll be interesting to see what that's like.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm thinking maybe a little bit like that Batman, what was it, the...
[SPEAKER_03]: The Batman game that they had on Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_03]: Gotham Impostor.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: That one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, the Gotham Kids or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it's like... Somebody in chat will yell it out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, neat.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess we'll have to hear about it during EA's press conference.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess they're going to have that on Monday, so...
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm watching all of those.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would be fantastic.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, me too.
[SPEAKER_03]: You want to hear something kind of funny off topic here a little bit?
[SPEAKER_03]: I was looking on NeoGAF just a second here.
[SPEAKER_03]: They put out a reminder that there was this thing that leaked last year.
[SPEAKER_03]: Remember about their kind of game plan?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the actual marketing position that they had for 2013 is this one box input one.
[SPEAKER_03]: So...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Akuma JP in our chat room with a very interesting comparison we were talking earlier the whole corporate warfare with Sony and Microsoft Akuma JP in our chat says look at Apple and Samsung that's another good comparison because those two they have to work together for some things but then they're at each other's throats
[SPEAKER_04]: with courts and lawsuits and everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's fascinating how that all works.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, so here's, if you remember that whole thing, the PDF that came out last year.
[SPEAKER_03]: So here's what the next game plan then would be.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fortezella glasses, digital glasses that allow you to see 3D objects in your living room.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's augmented reality stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's going to be next year, apparently, according to their road map.
[SPEAKER_04]: What about the Illumina Room?
[SPEAKER_04]: When's that supposed to be a thing?
[SPEAKER_04]: Next year too, I think.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_04]: I talked earlier in the show about Animal Crossing and I know one reason everybody loved the GameCube version of Animal Crossing and some people arguably say it's their favorite is because it had all the classic NES games in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember how you could play Punch Out and Clue Clue Land and all these Nintendo games in Animal Crossing?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, this will probably be a bit of a duh, but in an interview with Katsuya Eguchi, he basically, and this is an interview that he had out there, he said that please consider it's not happening ever again in regards to Virtual Console.
[SPEAKER_04]: At the time of Animal Crossing on the GameCube, we didn't have a virtual console system.
[SPEAKER_04]: We thought that playing games inside of a game is kind of funny, and we wanted to do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But now there's a virtual console where you can play classic games, so we don't think we'll be doing that in future titles.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, kind of confirmation that, yeah, they're not going to bring those NES games back in the other systems, and it's really virtual console's fault because they can make money selling those games separately.
[SPEAKER_04]: However, part of the reason I wanted to bring this up is because when I was reading this article on Destructoid.com, who ran with this article, I really liked an idea that was proposed.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I wanted to kind of put this out there by the author at Destructoid.com, who said, "...there's more that could be done to appease those looking for retro flavor in a new Animal Crossing adventure.
[SPEAKER_04]: A nice compromise would be to include some special 8-bit Animal Crossing-themed games."
[SPEAKER_04]: in the next entry of the series.
[SPEAKER_04]: In the GameCube title, Tortimer might give you a fake NES game called Super Tortimer on April 1st.
[SPEAKER_04]: What if Super Tortimer were playable?
[SPEAKER_04]: A little 10 minute long platformer starring a turtle mare and maybe a few other fake but fun lo-fi NES on Animal Crossing minigames.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm like, I love that idea.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a fantastic idea.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's a fantastic idea.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, you know, just silly little flash games to be collectible.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that would be a great thing for the series.
[SPEAKER_04]: Granted, you know, it's going to be a lot of development costs and somebody's got to design all that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Design it as a contest.
[SPEAKER_03]: You have a bunch of indie devs.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was just going to say, crowdsource the fucker.
[SPEAKER_03]: You just have a bunch of indie devs just creating 8-bit shit for it and you could even market that as a reason to buy the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just don't see Nintendo as somebody who would crowdsource like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_04]: but yeah that would be awesome it's too bad oh you know Nintendo if you're thinking about that Wii U version of Animal Crossing here's a oh oh this could this could really bring a lot of people back or just you know maybe just give us you know those NES games because come on you've already made your money back and then like who the fuck's gonna buy Clue Clue Land let's be real it wasn't that good or Donkey Kong Math or yeah who's gonna buy that shit come on um
[SPEAKER_04]: I have memories of Clu Clu Land, don't judge me
[SPEAKER_04]: YYR in chat says but I do have to buy a third party hack disc to unlock them all this time yeah because remember Super Mario Brothers and Zelda were in the original Animal Crossing but you couldn't get them without a code like they were never actually given out you had to code them to do it or use the link from Hyrule website that was big back in the day where everybody had the same character name so you could just gift yourself all this stuff pretty funny
[SPEAKER_04]: what else do I want to say with that oh here's one other thing I would say is that if they do these whole like little flash games that they put inside Animal Crossing they could almost one up virtual console and like how about little achievements within Animal Crossing and leaderboards within Animal Crossing suddenly Animal Crossing is what we all thought PlayStation Home was going to be think about it womp womp
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, anyway.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, how about something that's a little bit happier, Rob?
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: How about something that has nothing to do with Nintendo?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if that's going to be happier this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nintendo's kind of my safe room.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nintendo is my safe word this week.
[SPEAKER_10]: Remember, if it gets a little bit too hard for you, just say...
[SPEAKER_10]: I want my Wii U This actually has to do with an exclusive for PS3 that will be launching on Tuesday
[SPEAKER_10]: Tekken Revolution is going to be on PS3.
[SPEAKER_10]: It will be free to play.
[SPEAKER_10]: And you know me and my Tekken.
[SPEAKER_10]: I worked for Namco.
[SPEAKER_10]: I remember Tekken 3 and trying to predict who the next character would be.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I have special, special love of anything Tekken.
[SPEAKER_10]: Especially anything that has Gene Kazama in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but isn't this just going to be the dumb trading card game?
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: It says that basically it's going to be... I'm trying to see what it says it's going to be.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, it's being referred to as a new version of Tekken card tournament.
[SPEAKER_10]: Which, you know what's funny?
[SPEAKER_10]: I even had the stupid Tekken card game on the Wonderswan.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I will go to Lynx to play anything Tekken.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I'm just saying.
[SPEAKER_10]: Don't judge me.
[SPEAKER_04]: At least this one's free.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like free.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who doesn't?
[SPEAKER_04]: Especially because I'm broke.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, if you hate free and you want to buy something this week... Get the X-Bone!
[SPEAKER_04]: If you hate freedom, buy an Xbox One.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, seriously, what is coming out this week around the world?
[SPEAKER_04]: US first, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nothing, really.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, one game.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Last of Us on Friday.
[SPEAKER_03]: On Friday.
[SPEAKER_03]: Arguably a big fucking game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, great reviews, but Friday?
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you know, gotta get down on Friday.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess, you know, they want to make sure... Gotta get down to Disneyland!
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to make sure that it doesn't release on Tuesday with all that E3 news getting lost in the shuffle there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well, traveling to Japan and seeing if there's anything additional this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not so much on the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: PlayStation 3 is looking pretty empty this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Xbox 360, you'd be surprised.
[SPEAKER_04]: There is a game on Xbox 360 this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's called Ginga Force and...
[SPEAKER_04]: Eschatos Wonder Pack.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if that's just like a combination two-for-one thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it is definitely a two-for-one pack.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm looking at the box art.
[SPEAKER_04]: These look to be 3D spacey shooter games, like mechs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, it's got classic games in there, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: I see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Judgment, Silver Sword, Cardinal Sins.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you're a shmup fan, this might be the compilation for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is out on the Xbox 360 this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just me or does Xbox 360 get so many shmups over in Japan?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the shmup console.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, that's good to know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, but especially bullet hell games?
[SPEAKER_10]: Please.
[SPEAKER_04]: Looking at the other systems, sadly not a lot this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: 3DS is really the only other thing that's seeing some releases.
[SPEAKER_04]: Donkey Kong Returns makes its way to Japan this week and there's a Nintendo Metallic Red 3DS to match.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, one other game from Square Enix this week, Chusoku Henkai Jairozetter, Albatross no Tsubasa, comes out this week.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wings of the Albatross?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, it looks like another mech fighting game slash role-playing game type thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Aren't albatrosses usually associated with bad nautical things?
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe they're mechs that swim, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't think albatrosses can swim.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think they just die and hang around your neck.
[SPEAKER_04]: Speaking of dying and hanging around your neck, I'm done with Japanese game releases this week.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, we have a few things for the UK.
[SPEAKER_10]: On the 11th, we have Tekken Revolution, as I brought up earlier.
[SPEAKER_10]: On the 12th, we have Xenoclash on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_10]: And on the 14th, Animal Crossing 3DS.
[SPEAKER_10]: Chemical spillage simulation for PC, which actually just sounds hilarious without knowing anything about it.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then The Last of Us on PS3.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Stick a fork in it, speaking of dead things.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: There is some interesting controversy with this game, Vampire Smile, which was one of those... It originally started off as the dishwasher, one of the first Xbox...
[SPEAKER_03]: Indie games that they showed off.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, I think while they were introducing indie games or what they used to be called?
[SPEAKER_03]: Community games?
[SPEAKER_03]: Way back in the day?
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, so the sequel, The Dishwasher, The Vampire Smile, was coming to PC.
[SPEAKER_03]: But originally, the first way it came to the PC was a hacker, I guess a developer, Barbarous,
[SPEAKER_03]: He really wanted to see the game come to PC, so he cracked the version of it and uploaded it, I guess, to the internet.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so he kind of ported it to PC.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well now, it's actually coming officially to PC as well, because they weren't too happy with the fact that he cracked the game and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: New Director's Cut is going to have some enhancements to the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's not a good precedent to set, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hack our game and we'll put it on the console you want.
[SPEAKER_03]: I remember with Sonic Generations, they had the Sonic... What the hell was the crappy one with the werehog?
[SPEAKER_03]: They had all the daylight missions from that game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ask this one.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't tell all those Sonic games apart.
[SPEAKER_04]: She can.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which Sonic game?
[SPEAKER_03]: Sonic Unleashed, I think it was.
[SPEAKER_09]: I didn't play that one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sonic Unleashed, they had the daytime levels from that ported over to Sonic Generations for the PC because it never came out on PC.
[SPEAKER_10]: I do have Sonic Generations and I haven't even played it yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: To register participation for this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio at vognetwork.com use the passphrase TICKET
[SPEAKER_10]: To answer a code man, I don't acknowledge that in my universe.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: Acknowledge what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't have a one-sided conversation here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Kiefer Sutherland.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, that's coming up later in the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stop spoiling things.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stop spoiling it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I still don't like thinking about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Spoiler.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what, Rob?
[SPEAKER_04]: Spawning
[SPEAKER_04]: and I thought that meant maybe like a new enemy unit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Isn't that what Zergs do?
[SPEAKER_04]: They spawn a lot of Zergs.
[SPEAKER_04]: But anyway, what happens, you get free access to gameplay features when somebody who doesn't own a certain version of the game parties with someone who did.
[SPEAKER_04]: So in other words, when you go into multiplayer, you play the most current version of the game owned by at least one person in the party.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you have the free starter edition, but you come play with me and I have StarCraft II Basic Edition, we're now both playing StarCraft II Basic Edition.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's like...
[SPEAKER_04]: DS One Cartridge Play or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: If I party up with somebody playing Heart of the Swarm, we both get to play Heart of the Swarm.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's been rolling out globally since June 4th when this was announced.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know what regions do and don't have it at this time, but this is something that is planned for everybody.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's some...
[SPEAKER_04]: that's kind of awesome actually because if you if you have like a core group of four friends that you just want to do nothing but play Starcraft with maybe one of you is a big Starcraft nerd but the others aren't so much one person buys the game everybody mooches off it and you just don't play otherwise
[SPEAKER_03]: That's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's almost like if you had a game and then you load it to their friends and then they got really excited about the game and bought the sequel when it came out at launch.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, we can't have that.
[SPEAKER_03]: We can't do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: It cuts into developer money.
[SPEAKER_04]: To be fair, although I love your tongue-in-cheek point there, let's not forget StarCraft II does require an always online connection just because that's the nature of the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're right, because the PC marketplace is completely different than the console marketplace.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_10]: I cut you all with my razor sharp wit.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, what is the classic game of the week this week?
[SPEAKER_10]: Star Gladiator.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or as it was called over here, Star Gladiator Episode 1, Final Crusade.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, Episode 1, Final Crusade.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's up with that?
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: So anyway, it came out in 1996.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was a 3D fighting game done by Capcom for the PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, actually for the ZN1 arcade, which was basically a glorified PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was their first polygon fighting game.
[SPEAKER_10]: It actually came out before Street Fighter EX, so this was kind of a big thing for them.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was a pretty neat little game, I mean, as far as a 3D fighter goes.
[SPEAKER_10]: It...
[SPEAKER_10]: It didn't use the six button thing, it used a four button configuration that was a lot like how the Soul Edge and Soul Calibur games went.
[SPEAKER_10]: You had a 3D plane, you could do ring outs, it was that type of game.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it wasn't really anything that was special.
[SPEAKER_10]: as far as 3D fighting games at the time, but the fact that it was Capcom's first makes it notable.
[SPEAKER_10]: It also had these things called plasma reverses that are guard moves that you have to release at a particular point in time in the battle where it will enable you to deflect an incoming move and stun them so that you could actually attack in reverse.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it also does extra damage as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: It also had a combo system so that you could basically just pommel people to death and then in the arcade mode it was ten fights and depending on who you chose as your character you had a specific set of opponents that you would fight.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it was actually a pretty good game.
[SPEAKER_10]: You see some notable characters in there that showed up in other Capcom games, like Hayato showed up in Marvel vs. Capcom 2, and he had an appearance in Tatsunoko vs. Capcom in the Tekken Man Blade ending, which actually kind of made me giddy at the time.
[SPEAKER_10]: and there was June who was also in the background stages of Gem Fighter and in Capcom vs. SNK 2 and in one of the wind poses of Hayato in Marvel vs. Capcom 2 and she was also in Hawkeye's ending in Ultimate Marvel vs. Capcom 3 as a member of the West Coast Avengers which actually that was pretty crazy because I beat my game with him.
[SPEAKER_10]: There was Saturn Dyer, Gammoth Gogri, Franco Garrett, Vector Rimgal, who was June's dad, Zelkin Diskay Krogan, there's a bunch of people in the game anyway.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was a really neat game in that it used both English and Japanese voice acting for the characters.
[SPEAKER_10]: It also spawned a Dreamcast game that was called Plasma Sword Nightmare of Blissin, which is... Actually, me finding my Dreamcast copy is what made me think of the PlayStation version.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it was a really neat game.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, for all of the stuff that it did, it may not seem a big deal today, but when it came out, I thought it was a really cool game.
[SPEAKER_10]: So...
[SPEAKER_10]: Star Gladiator.
[SPEAKER_10]: You win Classic Games of the Week.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have to admit, I didn't know a lot about this game until I'm kind of watching the... As with a lot of these classic games you pick, I didn't know a lot about this one, but I'm watching it and I'm like, wow, this looks pretty good for a PlayStation 1 game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: It looks a little more Dreamcast level to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it late PS1?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'd say it was late PS1.
[SPEAKER_10]: But you should see Star Gladiator was actually a really fun little fighter.
[SPEAKER_10]: It had its issues, I mean, just about with any PlayStation 1 game at a time.
[SPEAKER_10]: But you should really see Plasma Sword, because that was really fun, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: This character here, June, I really like her, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: With the chakram?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, well, she reminds me of that Chicken Soul Calibartina, I think it is, with a similar deal.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: The big disc, yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: And actually, that's who I played this game most with, was Jean.
[SPEAKER_10]: But you should, one of these days we'll have to hook up the Dreamcast and I'll bring over Plasma Sword.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have a Dreamcast.
[SPEAKER_10]: So do I. But I have Plasma Sword and I will bring it over.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is why I need to get game streaming on my TV, because we need to do some classic NES game streaming through the Dreamcast emulation.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_10]: That would be wrong, but funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, there it is, the classic game of the week, Star Gladiator.
[SPEAKER_10]: Star Gladiator.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, actually, I need to point out, ClericalHero404 did remind me, she's using a combo attack of Chun-Li and Puzzle Fighter 2 Turbo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who was?
[SPEAKER_10]: June.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't remember that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, there were cosplay...
[SPEAKER_04]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, we got plenty more show to go here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Coming up with Part B tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have a list list coming up tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: A few surprises in store with list lists tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all I'm going to say.
[SPEAKER_04]: You are definitely going to want to be here live for this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry to the podcasters in advance.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very cool live feature tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the Fugle Question of the Week as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Rapid Fire News, the Mailbag FUs of the Week, and your calls at 1-877-GAME-OLR and username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: All when we come back after this with more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi there, this is Flaco Jones, and you're participating with Orange Lounge Radio, the show where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I want to use my voice to tell you, you should all play Ni No Kuni.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rob, you should beat Ni No Kuni.
[SPEAKER_06]: And now that I've said it in a bumper, you have to beat Ni No Kuni, or you have to play this bumper forever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, if you're actually going to play it, then yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think you'll like it, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: So yes, you may borrow it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm fun employed.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think Flaco would approve of that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, we did recycle a message this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: That means we could use some new bumpers.
[SPEAKER_04]: I did get one today, to be fair, so I'll put that in for next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: But if you want to submit a bumper as well, you can get all the information at the Voice Geeks Network, vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Click on Forums.
[SPEAKER_04]: and look at the ULR forum.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's right there at the top in a sticky thread how you can get your voice in a bumper on the show and you can tell the listeners whatever you want within reason.
[SPEAKER_10]: I even did one in not that great Japanese, but thanks to Kuma JP for correcting my grammar.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I'm talking about the ones that, not the ones that play on the network, but the ones that bring us back here.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I'm planning on actually doing one.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you're on the show.
[SPEAKER_10]: I can do a bumper.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, you can't.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I can.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do a bumper for Bobby's show.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll do one for Bobby.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll do one for Bobby that says, Hey, listen to this show, damn it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, listen.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I'd have to make it high-pitched.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, listen!
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, plenty more to come here on this half of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: But first, some rapid-fire news.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's take care of a lot of news this week in rapid-fire news.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, so it sort of leaked out, and then it got announced.
[SPEAKER_03]: Halo Spartan Assault is coming out for all your favorite gaming platforms, including Windows 8 PCs, tablets, and phones.
[SPEAKER_03]: and those are Windows 8 devices by the way.
[SPEAKER_03]: Windows phone, Surface tablets.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, and apparently it's gonna be set between Halo 3 and 4 and is a twin-stick shooter.
[SPEAKER_03]: Totally the title you were looking for.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's some free-to-play games coming to the PlayStation 4.
[SPEAKER_03]: Planetside 2 and DC Universe Online have both been confirmed for the PlayStation 4.
[SPEAKER_03]: Although I'm not surprised because it's Sony Online.
[SPEAKER_04]: Those are Sony Online games.
[SPEAKER_04]: But somewhere I hear Brad from PodCulture squeeing about the DC Universe Online.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just call it a hunch.
[SPEAKER_04]: If his internet's back up.
[SPEAKER_03]: so those will both be coming out and also Warframe is gonna be coming as well as a free-to-play title and yeah so I guess we're gonna see a lot of free-to-play games on PlayStation 4 so that could be good or bad I don't know free-to-play is not I like that business model so we'll see you like free?
[SPEAKER_03]: I like free yeah it's awesome do you think there'll be a lot of free games on Xbox One?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think there's got to be some.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the world we live in now.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just wondering if there's going to be any MMOs on Xbox One.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because remember, there wasn't really much on the Xbox 360 aside from Final Fantasy.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I guess there's some pay to play MMOs, like the Defiance and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: But none like actual traditional MMOs beyond Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it'll be interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: and last but not least new Harmonix title was announced last week and that was Fantasia Music Evolved and I saw the trailer and I'm like that has very little to do with Fantasia here's the thing
[SPEAKER_04]: I love harmonics.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love Disney.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do we get elephants and tutus?
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, I love harmonics.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love Disney.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hate Bruno Mars.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why was that in the trailer?
[SPEAKER_03]: Why?
[SPEAKER_03]: But they're going to have pop music.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're also going to have... That's not Fantasia.
[SPEAKER_03]: But they're also going to have the classical music as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Bohemian Rhapsody is going to be in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything with Queen is instantly better.
[SPEAKER_03]: Queen is one of the artists.
[SPEAKER_03]: Instant fantasticness.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just add Freddie Mercury.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here's the tracks announced so far.
[SPEAKER_10]: Does that make him a Disney queen?
[SPEAKER_03]: So, Bohemian Rhapsody, Kimbra Settle Down, I don't know what that is, Fun Some Nights.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hold on, just in case DarkSakura hadn't seen this yet, I'm playing this in studio, the little teaser trailer for this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me skip ahead a little bit.
[SPEAKER_10]: So basically it's Sorcerer Mickey mode.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it's like you're Sorcerer Mickey, but it doesn't really tell you what the game is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Where's the game here?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm left to think it's Rhythm Party.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it looks like Rhythm Party.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which I said Rhythm Party should have just been a retail release with all the tracks, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't care, because I don't really like Kinect games.
[SPEAKER_03]: The thing that's kind of unique, I guess, about it, supposedly, is you can control the tempo of the song, and it changes depending on stuff you do, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's going to be kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_03]: One of the tracks in there was it, AVI, what was it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Black Wolf in chat says game trailers actually showed gameplay it's Elite Beat Agents Connect oh so it's Rhythm Party like I said and you see this face that no one in the chat room can see this is my no one Kerr face I'm willing to give it a shot just because I really love Harmonix and they always put out quality I love Harmonix but I hate Kinect games fair
[SPEAKER_03]: and Levels is also one of the songs in there, which if I remember correctly, I think that's... Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_10]: If I wanted to get up and dance, I'd take a Zumba class.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, I do like Levels.
[SPEAKER_03]: Levels is awesome because that was one of the songs that was in Forza Horizon, one of my favorite ones on the dubstep thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm digging it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it'd be kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Harmonix, can't go wrong with them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bobby gave me a link to this and I hadn't seen it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Where's the actual gameplay?
[SPEAKER_04]: I just hear a dude talking.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to see gameplay.
[SPEAKER_13]: Is that under the sea?
[SPEAKER_13]: Down where it's wetter under the sea.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, see, there it is.
[SPEAKER_13]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, so this is not a rhythm party.
[SPEAKER_04]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like curious.
[SPEAKER_10]: Put out a demo.
[SPEAKER_10]: It seems like a game that you... I want a new Para Para Paradise.
[SPEAKER_10]: Then I would play my Kinect.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what they really needed to have?
[SPEAKER_03]: Is they needed to have Q games and fucking Harmonix come together and do like a new like Child of Eden type of game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because Child of Eden was fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_04]: ClericalEra404 in our chat quickly wants to know, DarkSakura, why do you hate Kinect games?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because usually they show you what you're doing and I don't like to watch myself.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can sometimes turn camera off.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, if I can turn the camera off, I have no problem with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I would have just thought you just don't like the whole flailing around.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I don't mind flailing around as long as nobody else is over.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was going to say, to be fair, the original Kinect games, not exactly very accurate a lot of times.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was that, too.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, the only fun I've ever had playing a Kinect game was doing Parapara on Dance Masters, which is why that's still the only Kinect game I will play.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let me move on with some other news.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe DarkSakura instead would rather play Injustice.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know she loves DC Universe.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do I like DC Universe?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: But apparently Injustice is pretty good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Somebody said Injustice is the best thing going on in DC Universe right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_03]: Why?
[SPEAKER_04]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't care.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because they have a whole bunch of other DC superheroes that they could put in the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Scorpion's a superhero.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, he's not.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, he's like fucking, it's like, oh, hey, it's Scorpion, but I can't do any of my bloody moves because it's fucking teen rated.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, that's what happened with the whole Mortal Kombat versus DC universe.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, sorry, I can't behead Batman because it's fucking teen rated.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: It sounds lame.
[SPEAKER_10]: I honestly did not find the game fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: The end.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, information on the new voice of Snake, because you know, a certain co-host of mine didn't ruin this earlier in the show, but Kiefer Sutherland confirmed as the voice of Snake in Metal Gear Solid 5, not David Hader.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, I think this was just like buzz earlier.
[SPEAKER_04]: We didn't have confirmation, but now that it's in the trailer, because the Konami whole thing, which we haven't even brought up in the show yet, but Konami had their whole little movie thing come up, and this was part of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, that's that.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, that to me sounds like the whole situation where, you know, it's the How I Met Your Mother situation where you have, you know, Bob Saget as the narrator, he's supposed to be the father, but yeah, his voice isn't obviously going to change, you know, over the default Ted Mosley voice that, you know, the characters have.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just different.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I wonder if we ever get a movie, if we'll have, you know, Kiefer Sutherland playing Snake.
[SPEAKER_04]: EA, hopefully giving some final clarity to some of the shady things they've said about the Wii U in the past, courtesy of EA president Frank Gabow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, I'm going to admit, I think we brought up something similar to this last week, but this is coming from EA president of labels.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is somebody else.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, they have nothing coming.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's nothing coming.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're really excited about the Xbox One and the PlayStation 4, and that's a pretty big endeavor in and of itself.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wonder why.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have four titles out on the Wii U that are active right now, so looking at how things unfold, that's where our focus is right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gen 3 is an awesome platform.
[SPEAKER_04]: It has a huge audience, has a lot of capability, and we're going to continue to publish games on Gen 3 for as long as there is an audience there.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have a tendency as a company to support the last gen platforms for many, many years.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can tell you we have products planned for next year, the year after that, and the year after that for Gen 3 for sure.
[SPEAKER_03]: well yeah because they keep pumping out Madden sequels and stuff like that on like PlayStation 2 and Xbox up to like way past the console's life cycles and stuff but it doesn't necessarily mean you're gonna see like big games on there the honest blunt way I could say this is that third party games aren't really what a lot of people go to Nintendo for anyway I mean they'll help of course I mean certainly the Sega partnership with Sonic which is so weird
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura I'm sorry, I was just getting out my DC hate out of my system
[SPEAKER_03]: Can't we all just get along?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, Marvel all the way.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, listen, if it's any consolation, Deadpool comes out in a couple weeks anyway.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know!
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm so happy.
[SPEAKER_10]: So happy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway, well, how about some other really quick news, okay?
[SPEAKER_10]: Diablo 3.
[SPEAKER_10]: We've seen an announcement before that it's going to be on the PS3 and PS4.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're also bringing it out on Xbox 360, but have no plans to bring it out for any other system, which is a polite fuck you to Xbone, as I'm still going to call it forever.
[SPEAKER_10]: Honestly, a lot of us have been playing it on PC already, so who cares?
[SPEAKER_10]: and then this makes me really happy is that Hatsune Miku Project Diva F is going to be coming out in North America in August and I'm gonna get it there's a demo on June 11th and so excited because I love the Project Diva games and then last but not least Metal Gear Rising Revengeance
[SPEAKER_10]: If anyone likes stories about Raiden, well, you get to play more Raiden because it's going to be on PC.
[SPEAKER_10]: The end.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're also bringing, I think, the original Lords of Shadows to PC as well, so that'll be interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, let's go to the Fugle Question of the Week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Every week we ask a question of our Facebook and Google communities.
[SPEAKER_04]: You put it together and it's Fugle!
[SPEAKER_04]: We had a fun idea for this week because, you know, E3 really kicks off tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_04]: The show floor doesn't open until Tuesday, but there's a shit ton of press conferences tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_04]: And so everybody's going to be talking about this tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we thought we would go to Facebook and Google and ask.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's that time of year to ask everyone, what's your E3 predictions?
[SPEAKER_04]: However, we at OLR, we like to do things a little differently and maybe a little bit silly.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we only want your E3 predictions in a haiku format.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be five, seven, five, remember?
[SPEAKER_04]: Guess, OL Army, what will occur at E3?
[SPEAKER_04]: Games of win or fail?
[SPEAKER_04]: That was my haiku to the listeners.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, you look so impressed.
[SPEAKER_03]: That wasn't bad, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some haikus.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, DarkSakura, I want you to count the syllables and tell me who failed.
[SPEAKER_04]: For the record, Rob?
[SPEAKER_04]: There are some fails in here.
[SPEAKER_10]: For the record, Rob?
[SPEAKER_10]: The plural of haiku is haiku.
[SPEAKER_04]: Haikuzis.
[SPEAKER_04]: The haikuza.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's go to the haikuza.
[SPEAKER_04]: Haikuzerzis.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: Bite me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Haiku gaggle.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: And all in good fun about those of you that fail, by the way.
[SPEAKER_04]: Edgar R. says, Call of Duty Ghost, Dogs of War, X-Bone exclusive.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think Dogs of War.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's wrong.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's not a haiku.
[SPEAKER_10]: You lose.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's also already confirmed that as an exclusive to the Xbox One.
[SPEAKER_04]: I appreciate the effort.
[SPEAKER_04]: Porkchop sends this entry.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't really mind as long as they don't release more shit EA games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bravo!
[SPEAKER_04]: Tiara.
[SPEAKER_04]: All I really care is about... Excuse me, I fucked that up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: All I really care about is Dragon Age 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love Bioware.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, she loves Anders.
[SPEAKER_10]: She loves Sir Pounce a lot.
[SPEAKER_04]: So she gets a fail for lying.
[SPEAKER_10]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Honestly, that's about... She named her cat Sir Pounce a lot.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, this is from Mason D. Want more Pokemon?
[SPEAKER_04]: Pokemon versus for Wii U. Pokemon get hype.
[SPEAKER_10]: With a big white smiley face underneath that, no less.
[SPEAKER_04]: Blood Drunk submits the following.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's a great name.
[SPEAKER_04]: Blood Drunk.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if Blood Drunk is a newer listener, but I've noticed his name on the VOG leaderboard.
[SPEAKER_04]: So he is a big participant.
[SPEAKER_04]: So a win to you, no matter how good or bad your haiku is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: From Blood Drunk.
[SPEAKER_04]: Connect watches you fap.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that's six syllables.
[SPEAKER_04]: Six syllables.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_04]: We still like his name.
[SPEAKER_04]: Connect watches you fap.
[SPEAKER_04]: LOLPS4DRM.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nintendo shows games?
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Not quite a haiku, but hey.
[SPEAKER_04]: Close enough.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a haikuga.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a haikuger.
[SPEAKER_04]: Degenerate Johnny submits the following.
[SPEAKER_04]: Predicting prices.
[SPEAKER_04]: Xbox, five bills, four with subs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sony, $450,000.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good way to put your predictions in.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think you might be highballing it a little bit, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Haseo Sumiwagawa submits the following.
[SPEAKER_04]: Xbox One fucks up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nintendo might steal the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: PS4, ooh pretty.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was six syllables.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Liam C. submits the following.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Last Guardian, a brand new Uncharted game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kinect flops badly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Codeman says, what will E3 bring?
[SPEAKER_04]: Nintendo surprise maybe?
[SPEAKER_04]: Xbone will has sports.
[SPEAKER_10]: This one just got sent to me, which I have to read.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: From who?
[SPEAKER_10]: From ClericalEra404.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sony has less trust.
[SPEAKER_10]: Nintendo rules us all, but it all ends well.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ragenator says, E to the three.
[SPEAKER_04]: E to the three.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's four syllables.
[SPEAKER_04]: You lose.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why can't people count?
[SPEAKER_04]: E to the three.
[SPEAKER_04]: MS.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, no, they didn't.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, they done screwed up.
[SPEAKER_10]: He could do E fucking three, yo.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, Captain Spike.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's Captain Spike's submission.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yay, Spike.
[SPEAKER_04]: We love Spike.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's full of win, no matter if his haiku is fail or not.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nintendo no show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sony and MS hate us all.
[SPEAKER_04]: The worst E3 ever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Worst E3 ever.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love Spike.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's HitStun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Next Gen Consoles, Meh, Nothing PS3 Can't Do, Game of Show, DuckTales That's a good one.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's my favorite one so far, I think.
[SPEAKER_10]: Did you watch the last trailer they put out?
[SPEAKER_10]: Not since... It's the side-by-side.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, no, I didn't see that one.
[SPEAKER_10]: They did one comparing the old DuckTales to the new one.
[SPEAKER_10]: Somebody on Tumblr posted it a while back.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll see if I can't find it and repost it, but it was pretty neat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, here's SSJ100 Matt Sentry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anticipation.
[SPEAKER_04]: Elated disappointment.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gamers are winners.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wouldn't that be losers if we're disappointed, though?
[SPEAKER_04]: And I got excited because when he said anticipation, it made me think, oh, maybe that's the Rare franchise they're bringing back.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because y'all know I could give two fucks about Killer Instinct or Banjo-Kazooie when Rare could remake Anticipation.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know you want to play as the ice cream cone again, bouncing around the board.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want ice cream right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is from Steven M. What about another cameo?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hell no.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, Steven M. says like I had to think about what the fuck game is he talking about?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh god.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, Steven M. Must be online Xbox.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wii U will die.
[SPEAKER_04]: We finally get Last Guardian.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think you did 557.
[SPEAKER_10]: I like especially since you gave them how to do a haiku.
[SPEAKER_04]: I put right there, as a reminder, a haiku is 575.
[SPEAKER_04]: We can't read.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's a syllable?
[SPEAKER_04]: We love our listeners.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're just giving you shit.
[SPEAKER_10]: I give everybody shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: We just want to educate you all this week on haikuses.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, study some damn literature.
[SPEAKER_10]: Fuck.
[SPEAKER_04]: Was that a haiku?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, not quite.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll make one, though, if you like.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: You think of one while I read the rest of these.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Andy R. says, I don't really know.
[SPEAKER_04]: A giant enemy crab?
[SPEAKER_04]: Ridge Racer 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ridge Racer 2 is four syllables.
[SPEAKER_04]: Andy, you're killing me.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would have been great for 2006.
[SPEAKER_04]: What I want this year is to see really good games and VOG to hit big.
[SPEAKER_04]: Somebody kissing a little VOG behind in that response.
[SPEAKER_04]: Love it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you, Actdeft.
[SPEAKER_04]: Flaco Jones says, Xbox and Sony.
[SPEAKER_04]: Their DRM kills gaming.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's a Nintendo?
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, I got one.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let me make sure I have it right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, let me read.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll do yours last.
[SPEAKER_04]: We do the rest of these.
[SPEAKER_10]: Forget it.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, go.
[SPEAKER_10]: Use the internet.
[SPEAKER_10]: There are haiku examples.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Really use Google.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Technus says use some fucking Google.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, no, it doesn't work.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Technus says people still complain.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rare shows next gen Battletoads.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why are you still hating?
[SPEAKER_04]: Never know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Redertainment says, oh, it's a double haiku.
[SPEAKER_04]: Redertainment's always got to fucking show everybody up.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Redertainment says, gamers hate everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everything will receive scorn.
[SPEAKER_04]: Twitter will explode.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gamers will not see a wanted not seen project.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Last Guardian.
[SPEAKER_10]: We got it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Since he did two, we got another one from Clerical Error.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, wait, let me read this last one from Google+.
[SPEAKER_04]: From Travis H. Sony is epic.
[SPEAKER_04]: Xbone will be eaten up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Long live PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see how that press conference goes.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm approaching it with cautious optimism, Travis.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cautious optimism.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, last but not least.
[SPEAKER_10]: Nintendo has props, but Sony has some issues.
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess we should wait.
[SPEAKER_10]: That one was good.
[SPEAKER_04]: YYR in chat can't you people count you have offended Jamie study some damn books you win the internet YYR Xbox One console TV TV TV sports what's wrong deal with it that's good did you do that one by yourself I just did that I love it I love it
[SPEAKER_04]: after I posted the question use that Mensa thing for something there you go Jamie came to me tonight she said you should make every week be a haiku because they're short alright
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, and SSJ100 Matt bringing some clarity.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anticipation because gamers are anticipating a lot for E3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Elated disappointment because people will be either happy or disappointed.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gamers are winners because no matter what gamers win because we have all these new games to play.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, I know we gave some of you a bad time, but that was a really fun topic.
[SPEAKER_04]: So thank you everybody for trying.
[SPEAKER_10]: I love you, YYR.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do I need to give you two a moment?
[SPEAKER_04]: Should I sit back?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't love you in that way.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, just a few more stories and then listless tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: But first, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Codeman is reminding me that I need to play more Borderlands 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I haven't touched it on PC yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Even though I finished the game like three times on 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: So yes, unfortunately there was some massive layoffs at Zynga.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also including the closure of OMG Pop.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so they closed the office there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, they closed the Zynga office in Los Angeles, Dallas, and New York.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know there was layoffs in all of their offices.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think about 520 or 540 or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: People were laid off.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, I was reaching out to one of my friends.
[SPEAKER_03]: She's a concept artist and artist over at Zynga in San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think, though, she's pretty high up.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think she's affected by it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, that kind of sucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, of course, a lot of horror stories coming out about how things were run and stuff like that and how they were talking about the terms they used for cloning things, like taking games like Tiny Tower and turning them into Dream Heights or whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's kind of sickening.
[SPEAKER_03]: So maybe this is the beginning of the end.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is surely not too good for them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I mean, I don't like to poke fun or tease or celebrate layoffs, especially like Loki says, he has friends that are at Zynga and so forth.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I mean, we always knew Zynga had a really questionable business model.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think people bought into that way too fast.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Zynga expanded way too fast over Farmville.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think it just goes to show Farmville was kind of a one-hit wonder, I hate to say.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some would argue with me that, well, there were other Facebook's games and blah, blah, blah, blah, but... Well, it's like this.
[SPEAKER_04]: When the news came out about them copying games, I mean, that was just shitty.
[SPEAKER_10]: A-ha had good albums and good music, but the only song anyone ever cared about was Take On Me.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is quite possibly the best possible comparison somebody could have made in this scenario.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because, remember, I had that thing of Dan singing the lyrics to the synth part with One Hit Wonder instead of the...
[SPEAKER_04]: By the way, before I get to the next news story, I just got a text message, and I'll let you guess where this is from, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you ready?
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, here's the text message I just got.
[SPEAKER_04]: Haiku game is weak.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sometimes we just can't even.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura mad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Girl.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's from Alan.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought that was good.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Going into some news about the Ouya.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sonic the Hedgehog 4, Sonic CD
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I mean, still, though, it's Sega support for the Ouya, so that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: How about some Phantasy Star Online?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe that's wishful thinking.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're coming out on June 27th in the Ouya store, $7 each.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is Sonic the Hedgehog 4 Episode 1, Episode 2, and Sonic CD.
[SPEAKER_04]: No idea if the Ouya version will include fun for Sonic the Hedgehog 4, because unfortunately that was missing in the earlier versions.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anybody?
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Ouya ports, they say, are optimized for the console's Tegra 3 processor and free trial versions will be available.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sega of America director of mobile business, David Zemke, interesting where this is coming from, was praising Ouya's, quote, disruptive technology and, quote, they want to see what these technologies can do and be a part of it from the beginning.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're always looking for other titles and there may be some future titles that we'd like to bring over.
[SPEAKER_04]: For us, we're always trying to bring the best gaming experience to the right platforms.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a delicate mix of how and when to do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right after the launch of the OUYA, by the way, which is June 25th.
[SPEAKER_04]: The day before my birthday, y'all.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, one more story and then we'll get into Listless tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry, we were just having a discussion about Turian's mutt.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, not really.
[SPEAKER_10]: Something from Double Fine, the game Massive Chalice, that basically, as they were saying that there was going to be a gay relationship in the game that had been taken out, and now the project leader feels shitty because people on Kickstarter say, no, we want it.
[SPEAKER_10]: So he's putting it in.
[SPEAKER_10]: As of today.
[SPEAKER_10]: All that from feedback.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's what you want.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're putting it back in.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's kind of cool though because that makes it seem like Kickstarter really is a place for like... Not to say they're investors or whatever because Kickstarter is with the backing or whatever but that they get a say.
[SPEAKER_04]: That these people really had a say.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, if you look at it this way, it is probably the best type of board meeting you can ever expect because you've got real-time feedback going in.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I think it's good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is this something that you would consider backing or a game that you might think you're going to buy?
[SPEAKER_10]: I told you what I'm waiting for for my first backing.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, what?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, unless he's already put it up, I'm waiting for the understanding video games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can you refresh my memory about this?
[SPEAKER_10]: That Seg's doing?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wanted... There was another name it was, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yeah, he hasn't put it up yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I think he's going to.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to give my Kickstarter cherry to Seg.
[SPEAKER_10]: Love, love, love, love.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a fair place to give your Kickstarter, Terry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm trying to get this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, we're going to do listless now, except I'm having a little problem with the connection.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see if we can get it there.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to call an old friend of ours here at Orange Lounge Radio to help us out with Listless tonight, and hopefully the internet will hold up.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I think we're connected now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you there, old friend?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, Bobby Blackwolf, how you doing?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm doing good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rob called you old.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shouldn't he be like old chum?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I'm not Adam West in Batman, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: How you doing, Bobby?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm doing good.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've been playing Animal Crossing since I got off the air.
[SPEAKER_04]: Finally have time to get into that, huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you think so far?
[SPEAKER_10]: it's Animal Crossing I'm very sad because everybody else has this and I don't even have a 3DS so whatever you gotta bug Dan no because I don't have a job so we're not buying one you have to have a J-O-B to have a 3DS you're gonna need to get on MTurk I've even already been in someone else's town so my fruit collection is growing wow
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: I used Pico.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Pine was the male.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, one was email and one was Pico.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shows you my knowledge of Unix.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't used it in a while.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you coded away in VI this new E3.VOGnetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: What are you hoping comes of this?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is me saying, this is an idea I have.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wonder if it'll work.
[SPEAKER_05]: And in the past, I've had these ideas, and they didn't work, and then two years later, everybody's doing them.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we'll see if this is another one of those.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: So be sure to check it out, guys, if you haven't seen it yet, e3.vognetwork.com, especially those of you listening on the podcast.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everything will open up on Monday night for the question and answer.
[SPEAKER_04]: But tonight, live, you can at least watch the video.
[SPEAKER_04]: and learn everything you're going to need to know for when everything goes live with the question asking.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've already been given the blacklist against asking anything about Hello Kitty games, so I'm not going to do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you're leaving for E3 tomorrow, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Correct.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tomorrow morning.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: And what's your very first appointment?
[SPEAKER_05]: Bethesda, I think.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I think it's Bethesda.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's at two o'clock.
[SPEAKER_05]: That way I can get there and see things from noon to two and kind of get my way to land.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I think, yeah, it's Bethesda at two.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know we're about to get into the listless here about thing I most want to happen at E3 2013.
[SPEAKER_04]: But seriously, off the record, what are you personally like looking forward to getting your hands on yourself and checking out?
[SPEAKER_05]: This is my standard answer, and everybody calls it a cop-out, but I don't care.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh no, I know what you're going to say, and I think it's a great answer.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the game I haven't heard of yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: Catamari Damacy
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: All seriousness though, we are going to play listless here, but there's one other reason I have you here tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: And there's been a theme here at VOG Network the past couple weeks, and that is that the game is always changing.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the game is changing again tonight, isn't it Bobby?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: What is new?
[SPEAKER_04]: What did you do for us this week?
[SPEAKER_05]: I hope you're logged into the site.
[SPEAKER_05]: Everybody, because you no longer have to learn how to private message Rob to play listless.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you've ever done any of the live polls here on VOG, then you kind of know where to look.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's where you're going to want to look.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: So with that, it's time to start some listless.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: at E3 2013.
[SPEAKER_04]: And once everything is up on the list, then we will go around and this is what has to happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have to strike the items that are not worthy of the list.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a very difficult, painful process, but it must be done.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember, there is a new rule that is still in play, however, and that is that when a host has two items eliminated from the list, the third gets immunity.
[SPEAKER_04]: So a person's list cannot be completely decimated.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, here it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: The topic, thing I most want to happen at E3 2013.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's put it up on the board at live.vognetwork.com For those of you that are logged in right now, you will start to see the board and our answers as we fill it in.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hopefully, right Bobby?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's also part of the reason you're on the line.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, I made it live.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm keeping a watch on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I'm going to say the easy answer, a new F-Zero.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I think that's a very good, safe answer.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think that is one that can't possibly get eliminated no matter what happens.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, that's always famous last words.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, thanks for dooming that answer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's put it up on the board.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bobby locks in a new F-Zero.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, DarkSakura, what is the number three thing that you want to see happen at E3 2013?
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, it's probably, it won't happen, but I would love to have Sega announce that they're back in the console business.
[SPEAKER_10]: It won't happen, but it's what I want.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, Sega is back in the console business.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's put it up on the board.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dreamcast 2?
[SPEAKER_08]: They should call it the Sega Utopia.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Sega Utopia.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, my turn for a number three answer.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to say... I'm going to have to figure out how to fit this in the board, but my number three answer is the Microsoft server crashes at the show causing all the Xbox Ones to stop playing games after Wednesday.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: because you know every 24 hours it's got to check in, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: So the Microsoft server crashes for 24 hours.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess that's how I'll shorten it.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, putting that up on the board right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Boy, Bobby would be very sad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bobby, wouldn't you be sad if you didn't get to play an Xbox One and then all of a sudden the servers crash for 24 hours?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but then I'd laugh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then you'd laugh.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, your number three answer.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, just because I want to get this out of the way, Microsoft and Sony go back on their plans for DRM.
[SPEAKER_03]: It stays the way it is now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love how you threw in and Sony when we don't really know yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, we know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's be honest.
[SPEAKER_04]: No one's kidding themselves.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's put that up on the board.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki says MS and Sony go back on their DRM plans.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, Bobby, we're to you for your number two answer tonight for Listless.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thing you most want to see happen at E3 2013.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to see E3 announce that Kensha Hall will be returning next year.
[SPEAKER_10]: Damn it, you stole mine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_04]: You had that on your list.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_04]: I did.
[SPEAKER_04]: These things happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: You better check the chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bobby just threw that up on the board.
[SPEAKER_04]: E3 announces the return of Kensha Hall.
[SPEAKER_04]: And maybe a new ex-Tango that goes with that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, DarkSakura, what's your number two answer?
[SPEAKER_10]: Sony uses Final Fantasy VII to display an engine without a release of Final Fantasy VII Remake.
[SPEAKER_04]: So basically they're going to repeat what they did with PlayStation 3 and show a Final Fantasy tech demo that never happens.
[SPEAKER_10]: Final Fantasy tech demo that never results in a game.
[SPEAKER_03]: That'd be awesome if it was in a new Final Fantasy engine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey!
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it looks like Advent Children.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nope, never gonna get it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, I'm gonna put this up on the board.
[SPEAKER_04]: Final Fantasy VII PS4 tech demo that never is a real game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that should fit within the confines of our shiny new board.
[SPEAKER_04]: Live.VogNetwork.com Again, if you are listening live on this Sunday night, be ready to participate because you're gonna vote through the site as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: Live.VogNetwork.com I mean, granted, if Final Fantasy VII was remade, yeah, I'd play it.
[SPEAKER_10]: But, let's be realistic.
[SPEAKER_04]: My turn.
[SPEAKER_04]: My number two answer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nintendo announces their plan to win the new generation of gaming by adding porn to Miiverse.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_04]: The Miiverse porn channel.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it's WiiWiiverse.
[SPEAKER_04]: Come on, that's how you win the console wars.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, I'm gonna throw that up on the board.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, Loki, your number two answer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Super Mario RPG 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: That'll never fucking happen, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why, though?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's such a fantastic game.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'm sorry, I understand that there are the Paper Mario games.
[SPEAKER_03]: And granted, Super Paper Mario was actually a pretty fun game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was actually one of the games I liked the most on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I would just like a sequel.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, Square Enix, come on.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, we'll throw that up on the board.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, it's time for the number one answers.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's go around and collect them for the thing you most want to see happen at E3 2013.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bobby Blackwolf, our guest.
[SPEAKER_05]: So picture this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Somehow, Valve does some kind of event, goes on their own stage, press conference.
[SPEAKER_05]: Everybody's in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Gabe Newell walks out on stage.
[SPEAKER_05]: Half-Life 3, available right now, drops the mic and walks off stage.
[SPEAKER_10]: That would win E3.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm typing that up as Half-Life 3 announcement followed by mic drop.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sound fair?
[SPEAKER_05]: Release.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, excuse me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Excuse me.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, what's your number one answer?
[SPEAKER_04]: The new Mass Effect announced with good writing
[SPEAKER_04]: New Mass Effect announced, but with good writing.
[SPEAKER_04]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's up on the board and I totally know which answer Bobby's going to strike.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: If Bobby touches it, I will get... Never mind.
[SPEAKER_10]: I won't even say it.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: You leave my Mass Effect alone.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a scientific process, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: My number one answer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Take faith in this, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think you will be okay with this as a backup.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know you will because my answer is... If Bobby doesn't get rid of it too.
[SPEAKER_04]: He might.
[SPEAKER_04]: My answer is...
[SPEAKER_04]: The Guardian Legend 2 on Wii U. Technically, there was a Guardian Legend 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's the one that we got in the US.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was Guardic 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: You shut up.
[SPEAKER_10]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Preferably WayForward would somehow be involved because they're really good at retro boots.
[SPEAKER_10]: RageFader said Garrus gets his own game.
[SPEAKER_10]: That would be like a Silent Scope Turian edition.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, last but not least, Loki, one spot left on the board.
[SPEAKER_04]: What are you going to put in the list tonight?
[SPEAKER_03]: Grand Theft Auto or Saints Row Online.
[SPEAKER_03]: An MMO for a sandbox game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess we already have... They have a free-to-play MMO right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: ATB or whatever?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, ATB.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not the same.
[SPEAKER_04]: A GTA or Saints Row MMO.
[SPEAKER_04]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's recap before we get to the very difficult part.
[SPEAKER_04]: A new F-Zero Sega is back in the console business Microsoft server crashes for 24 hours Microsoft and Sony go back on their DRM plans E3 announces the return of Kensha Hall Final Fantasy VII PlayStation 4 tech demo that it never is a real game Porn to Miiverse Super Mario RPG 2 Half-Life 3 released followed by a mic drop New Mass Effect announced but with good writing The Guardian Legend 2 on Wii U
[SPEAKER_04]: and Grand Theft Auto or Saints Row MMO.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a lot of answers tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's getting crowded up here, so unfortunately it's time to ask which of these is not worthy of the list.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bobby Blackwolf, I know you don't want to do it, but you're going to have to make one of us mad by eliminating something off the list.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's it going to be?
[SPEAKER_05]: Porn to me-verse.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, Bobby, you're killing me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why are you getting rid of porn, though?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because... Because the Wii U is a wholesome system?
[SPEAKER_04]: Think of the children.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: It has been stricken from the list.
[SPEAKER_04]: Porn to Me-verse is gone.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's next?
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's the various answers.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which one of these is not worthy of the list?
[SPEAKER_04]: Tough one.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a lot of good answers up here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, there are.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm probably going to have to axe the Microsoft and Sony going back because I don't think Microsoft is going to.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're eliminating it because you're just like, it's not happening.
[SPEAKER_10]: And we still don't know what Sony's going to say.
[SPEAKER_04]: You might want it to happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's all speculation.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: It has been stricken from the list.
[SPEAKER_04]: As sad as that is going to make some of you.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I understand.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, my turn to strike something from the list.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh gosh, these are all actually really good.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hate to do this, Loki, but I'm removing Super Mario RPG 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Before you get mad at me, people, it's the same reason DarkSakura got rid of hers.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not fucking happening.
[SPEAKER_04]: So let's not even get our hopes up.
[SPEAKER_04]: So Super Mario RPG 2, I'm sorry, but it has been removed from the list.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the good news is GTA or Saints Row MMO gets immunity going into the final removal, which is yours, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, that's fantastic news.
[SPEAKER_03]: And since it's not really going to happen either, new Mass Effect announcement.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey!
[SPEAKER_03]: Because there's just not good writing in that series.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, if they got the first game writing team, it would be good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I'm sorry to say that it has been stricken from the list.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, Dark Sakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess while we're talking about things that will never happen...
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, there it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is now your turn to vote for your number one and your number two answers.
[SPEAKER_10]: Did EA pay you off?
[SPEAKER_04]: But guys, no longer do you send your answers to me over private message.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now there's a little button on the site that says your turn.
[SPEAKER_04]: Select your first and second choices now.
[SPEAKER_04]: It just popped up there in the corner.
[SPEAKER_04]: And when you click answer, you will be able to answer right now and we will get the answers tabulated.
[SPEAKER_05]: What you do first, you click on the answers and your first answer and your second answer and then you click the answer button.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Run through that one more time, Bobby, because I'm a little slow.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you'll click on one of my answers and you'll see it say one.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then you'll click on one of my other answers and you'll see it say two.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then you click answer.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: So click on answer one and then answer two and then click answer.
[SPEAKER_04]: What if they screw up?
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't have five, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: if the if but well once you click answer it's done like it's in but if you decided oh I didn't want that to be my number one you can click on it again and it takes it away oh okay good good to know all right there it is so um Bobby amazing work on the site I loved watching that all pop up as we were going and I bet you're breathing a sigh of relief seeing it actually work right yes awesome well I'll let you know if the votes come in here I'm wait oh there they go they're coming in oh nice oh it's even tabulates it for me Bobby I love it
[SPEAKER_04]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_04]: You the man, Bobby.
[SPEAKER_04]: A coding god.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, well, Bobby, any other plugs like maybe for your show or something you want to get out here before I let you go?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, E3.VOGnetwork.com Alright, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now how do I end this poll when it's done?
[SPEAKER_04]: Do we just uncheck answerable?
[SPEAKER_04]: Uncheck live.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uncheck live and that gets rid of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I actually see a bug on this too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh really?
[SPEAKER_04]: What's happening?
[SPEAKER_04]: Is the scoring wrong?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you notice how it's
[SPEAKER_05]: That's weird.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know why it's doing it.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's wrong, Bob?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, it's not sorting it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's not a big deal.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, it is sorting it, but it's sorting it by the first number and not the entire number.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_05]: I get it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's sorting it as a string instead of an integer.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's coding terms.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I see what it's doing.
[SPEAKER_09]: We can still count, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I can count, Bobby, believe it or not.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Your last chance to vote, live.vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do I uncheck answerable as well or leave that?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, because then you won't see the live answers.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, that would be bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: You keep it answerable.
[SPEAKER_05]: We uncheck live.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll let you know the results shortly, but we want to give a few more moments for everybody to vote.
[SPEAKER_04]: Once again, e3.vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for playing listless with us tonight and kicking off the new generation of listless.
[SPEAKER_04]: Appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you so much guys
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, we'll let you know the results here shortly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Again, you can vote for about five more minutes at live.vognetwork.com in tonight's list list.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's go to the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess now's a good time for us to... Do we gotta... Of course!
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: What, you don't like to hear from listeners?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com is the place to send us emails.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura's gonna dive in head first and find some emails that she thinks are worthy of reading on the show tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: First email.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's also subject line is, now they've done it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I looked up hubris the other day to make sure it meant what I thought it did.
[SPEAKER_10]: Microsoft definitely has an overabundance of hubris.
[SPEAKER_10]: They revealed Xbox One and the consumers on the internet made assumptions.
[SPEAKER_10]: Then Microsoft denied the rumors, but last Thursday confirmed all the rumors to be true.
[SPEAKER_10]: And the consumers are not happy.
[SPEAKER_10]: See Major Nelson's blog comments to see the shitstorm.
[SPEAKER_10]: The Xbox One seems to be defying the consumers who use the internet.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh wait, those are the target demographic.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's really stupid business-wise to ignore your customer base and punish them in the process.
[SPEAKER_10]: I hope they change.
[SPEAKER_10]: And that comes from Robaba.
[SPEAKER_10]: Agreed.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to apologize.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can you summarize that for me?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because Alan just got home and I was talking to him.
[SPEAKER_10]: and basically Microsoft denying the rumors, then confirming the rumors and a big shitstorm.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, what's up with that?
[SPEAKER_04]: They totally did, like, say no.
[SPEAKER_04]: But then they were also saying, like, at one point, what, like, that it was going to be $60 for the license or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't... Sometimes the left hand isn't talking to the right hand, is it?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, and I'll repeat this line.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's really stupid business-wise to ignore your customer base and punish them in the process.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know why I don't sign up for porn No one signs up for porn, porn happens
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, this is another one from Rabababa.
[SPEAKER_10]: You should probably avoid my other emails for reading out too late.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is about the Xbox How It Games letter I slash we got via email.
[SPEAKER_10]: Here is one quote feature.
[SPEAKER_10]: Your games keep playing even when you're not.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just because you're not playing doesn't mean your games have to stop.
[SPEAKER_10]: With living games technology and the power of the cloud, game worlds are persistent.
[SPEAKER_10]: So the things you do in a game will stay that way.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wait, the living games continue to play without you like an MMO, which is the opposite of things you do in the game will stay that way.
[SPEAKER_10]: We call that technology save files.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you, Rababa.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some good emails from Rababa tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: I like Rababa.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's a good man.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, that's it for emails tonight, huh?
[SPEAKER_10]: I just came back into the chat room to see German Dungeon Transmidget Porn.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you guys know how to party or what?
[SPEAKER_10]: I love the chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, last call for votes, guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Again, this is the last call for votes.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you're participating with us, live.vognetwork.com The listless answers will be read after this.
[SPEAKER_04]: The FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's time to get angsty.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why?
[SPEAKER_04]: Cause E3's this week and none of us are going.
[SPEAKER_04]: I get to go to the OUYA booth.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ooh, lower your expectations, that's all I gotta say.
[SPEAKER_10]: F you to me forgetting that I brought chocolate that's in the fridge and I'm gonna go get it now.
[SPEAKER_04]: F you to just realizing that you're going to give me a bunch of chocolate.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not that, like, I'm sad to have chocolate.
[SPEAKER_09]: I waited for Alan.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alan, chocolate.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have to do my laptop for the hard drive failing and then having, you know, these things that they put in place, like a recovery partition just not doing anything.
[SPEAKER_03]: It got so bad that, like, Windows could read the hard drive because I was able to boot in the Windows and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: But then it's like, oh, you want to fix that drive?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I can't read that drive to fix it.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that kind of sucked.
[SPEAKER_03]: But at least I got a new hard drive in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: That had to take out all of my JTAG, which I'm not using.
[SPEAKER_03]: My Xbox of fame, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um...
[SPEAKER_03]: and then also F you to Steam actually just for this weekend because I was trying to I installed Steam on my new installation of Windows and it asked me hey I haven't played on this PC before you need to authenticate with us and then they wouldn't send me the email.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm like, what the hell?
[SPEAKER_03]: It ended up being that their server was all fucked up this weekend, and so it was sending the email like two hours after you sent them the confirmation.
[SPEAKER_03]: Normally it's like immediate, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I feel that.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: My IP of the week, it goes to The Heat in Phoenix, Arizona.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can only imagine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Except for Grand Avenue.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alice Cooper owns a bar there and I totally went there and it was amazing and I got to see his big unit or whatever that that that 22 no seriously it's like a 22 inch hot dog it was on man versus food or whatever I got to see somebody order that that was cool um otherwise F you to the fact like I can deal with 110 degree heat like I had to deal with that yesterday but at nine o'clock at night it cools off here in Arizona nope
[SPEAKER_04]: So F you to the heat in Arizona.
[SPEAKER_04]: And F you to the fact that I'm not really going to E3, but... Phoenix, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, what's up with that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, I think it's time to read the results of this list.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you guys think?
[SPEAKER_11]: Chocolate.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right, I think chocolate too.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, here it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: The results of tonight's list list at live.vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you didn't vote now, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is too late.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, so let's... Oh, son of a bitch.
[SPEAKER_04]: It doesn't still show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, there's the table.
[SPEAKER_04]: Phew.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was like, Bobby, I found a bug.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it showed up again after a second.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: The answers for tonight's list list.
[SPEAKER_04]: Number three.
[SPEAKER_04]: And this is it.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is what you want.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is what will happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, what you really want to will happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: Scientific Process, The End.
[SPEAKER_04]: Number three answer.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Microsoft server crashes for 24 hours and none of the games are playable after Wednesday.
[SPEAKER_04]: Unfortunately, that's not possible because they're running off PCs anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stop being a realist.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Number two answer, Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: It should make you happy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Grand Theft Auto or Saints Row MMO?
[SPEAKER_04]: I wish.
[SPEAKER_04]: Number two answer.
[SPEAKER_04]: and the number one answer with over the number of points of number three and two combined.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if that's ever happened in Listless history.
[SPEAKER_04]: The number one answer, Half-Life 3 released followed by a mic drop.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be fantastic.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know everyone wants it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would love to see that in just like a really crappy just like stage that he has in like he built in his house.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's just like not even a stage.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just like half.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm pushing a giant button.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just have the button.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, he can lift up the button and the little case covering the button.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hit the button and the little thing in the back says Half-Life 3 release.
[SPEAKER_03]: Drops mic, leaves.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Video done.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It worked very well.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, ooh, it even shows me how everybody voted.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now I know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now we know who the traitors are.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now I know who to judge.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did Loki vote for his own answer?
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_03]: You always vote for yourself.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Again, just to recap.
[SPEAKER_04]: Number three, the Microsoft server crashes for 24 hours.
[SPEAKER_04]: Number two, Grand Theft Auto or Saints Row MMO.
[SPEAKER_04]: Number one, Half-Life 3 released, followed by a mic drop.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you and good night.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, and BlackWolf is celebrating in chat.
[SPEAKER_04]: A winner is me.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think he hacked the system.
[SPEAKER_04]: Couldn't he have done that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Couldn't he have hacked the system to give himself more points?
[SPEAKER_04]: He may have.
[SPEAKER_04]: The game has been hacked.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, just a couple more news stories for you guys, and then we're going to get to the Twitter topics and our Skype line at 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: But first, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: So Minecraft is getting some updates on the portable version, or the pocket edition, including Alpha Realms support.
[SPEAKER_03]: And if you remember correctly, Minecraft Realms is that new Mojang-run private servers, basically.
[SPEAKER_03]: Cake?
[SPEAKER_03]: Cake.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I'm glad to see that the Android version is getting some updates.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wish that, I know one of the things that they're working on, and I don't think it's happened yet, is controller support for that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because if that's the case, then I can sideload that onto my Ouya and play with the controller, and it'd be fantastic.
[SPEAKER_03]: and oh, god damn it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I knew there was something.
[SPEAKER_03]: I forgot nephews of the week, but I'll mention it real quickly since we're talking about Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_03]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_03]: The fucking VOG Network Minecraft server host is absolute shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's been down for five days now.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I've sent a bunch of support tickets to them.
[SPEAKER_03]: No fucking response back.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's not cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: But they sure as hell took out the money out of my account this weekend to pay for it.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I'm looking... There's three magic words that will get...
[SPEAKER_10]: Action.
[SPEAKER_03]: Better Business Bureau.
[SPEAKER_10]: Better Business Bureau.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'm going to be probably, I'm going to either switch the server to a new host or I'm just going to shut it down because no one's really playing on it.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, I tried to log into it this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it's just.
[SPEAKER_10]: I played last week.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's just not a lot of people on there.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's, you know, even though it's $10 a month, it's just, you know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll give you $5.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_03]: No one plays.
[SPEAKER_03]: It goes down.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that doesn't mean no good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, and they have announced...
[SPEAKER_04]: They have announced that this game is inspired by, and this is why DarkSakura is excited, it's inspired by Konami's Parodius series.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's some gameplay, a little flying hamster.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: And if you want to play it, though, they do have flying hamsters.
[SPEAKER_03]: The original game is on iOS.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you can play that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like the little Egyptian penguin.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's super cute.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to fight the owl.
[SPEAKER_04]: So this is super cute.
[SPEAKER_10]: It is cute.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you gotta love somebody who says they're inspired by Parodius, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: Parodius is like one of the best games ever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Online leaderboards, unlockable trophies, and all that fun stuff on the PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_04]: The game is also on the PlayStation Minis service.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my god, Fat Mermaids.
[SPEAKER_04]: The original Flying Hamster is on the Minis.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: It has Fat Mermaids.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's also a great little indie... You might not have noticed that otherwise title, so I'm really glad we're getting a little bit of a spotlight on that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: So DarkSakura's thinking about getting a Vita for that.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I'm not.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just download it on your iPad.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's about time to open up the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because, I'm sorry, nothing is Pentaro.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's open up the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_04]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is time to get some calls here on this Sunday night.
[SPEAKER_04]: We want to know, what are your E3 thoughts?
[SPEAKER_04]: You don't have to give them in a haiku form, but bonus points if you do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe you have something to say about all this Xbox One business.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure some of our regular callers have an opinion or three or five or ten on what we talked about at the very beginning of the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or maybe there's something else completely different we've missed.
[SPEAKER_04]: We want to hear from you guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: And look at that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's already ringing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Already got calls coming in tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's go to it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd say sobered up Ranma.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry to hear that.
[SPEAKER_04]: How are you otherwise, Ranma?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm doing pretty good.
[SPEAKER_04]: How about y'all out there in California?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hot.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, today was better.
[SPEAKER_10]: I had chocolate, and I'm happy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I've calmed down a little bit.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yesterday was 110.
[SPEAKER_10]: Tomorrow's going to be 80.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_10]: Go fig.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, what's new with you, Ranma?
[SPEAKER_04]: Why'd you call in tonight?
[SPEAKER_02]: A couple of things, but before I get into it, hey, Ukchan.
[SPEAKER_02]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: Looks like at Otakon this year we may be bringing Ranma 1.5 back.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, a few of us are doing like a quick impromptu group photo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, send me a copy of it, definitely.
[SPEAKER_10]: Too bad I can't come with my spatula.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, and if we have to, we'll pack you in a box.
[SPEAKER_10]: I wish I could go, I really do, but unfortunately money, blah blah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is a real reason why I called.
[SPEAKER_02]: Number one, I understand what everyone says about the Xbox One, but truth be told, it's still going to sell because they're going to have these top-tier titles.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you have to forget, half the gamers in the video gaming fandom are lemmings.
[SPEAKER_02]: They will say one thing, and then after the presentation, you see all these games, it'll be like, shut up and take my money.
[SPEAKER_04]: Couldn't you say the same thing about Nintendo's Wii U, though?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, I could say that about every single gaming console.
[SPEAKER_04]: But then what happens after that?
[SPEAKER_04]: The Nintendo fanboys have bought the Wii U and they're still calling it a failure.
[SPEAKER_04]: I still think the jury's out on that, given another holiday season before we build its coffin.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why do you think that is?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the way people think.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm kind of reminded from back in the days of everybody was importing the DDR into Beatmania games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then when Konami started bringing over DDR and people got pissed that certain titles were not in the US releases, they were like, I'm not going to buy it.
[SPEAKER_02]: The game comes out, they buy it anyway to support their fandom.
[SPEAKER_02]: As for these next-gen consoles, one of the reasons why people are going to buy them is to support the console they think it's going to work.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: You don't?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think Blizzard or EA thought so either.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's my worry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I don't know how many servers other manufacturers have, but I have this feeling Microsoft's going to have the most.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they said straight up they're going to bring up all these servers ahead of time.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'm guessing some of the mistakes with EA and Blizzard we're doing with servers.
[SPEAKER_02]: So who knows?
[SPEAKER_04]: So where's your head at with Xbox One after all of this?
[SPEAKER_02]: I said before, shut up and take my money for a PS4, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to wait until after the presentations and see what everybody has to say and then make my decision.
[SPEAKER_04]: Based off games are most important?
[SPEAKER_02]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like games, technology, functionality, a little bit of everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me ask you one more question, because I know you're a long-time listener of the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Were you here at the very beginning of the show, or did you come in late tonight?
[SPEAKER_02]: I was here at the very beginning of the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wouldn't judge you if you were late, but I just want to know, earlier in the show I asked DarkSakura about the golden rule of gaming, and we kind of came to a consensus that perhaps the golden rule of gaming, a system that's only as good as the games that are on it, could be evolving.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think so, too, because that golden rule is the reason why I got a 360 before the PS3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because people are going to argue, why did you get that next-gen console?
[SPEAKER_02]: All these cool games are on that one.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the answer is, well, those games are not games I would particularly like to play.
[SPEAKER_02]: The games that I've played and I've enjoyed are on this console.
[SPEAKER_02]: This console is going to offer these games I am interested in, which is why I'm going to buy it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I still remember when I was working at Staples, I looked outside the long line of people across the street at Circuit City for the $500 and $600 PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_04]: There'll be an audience somewhere, but will it be big enough?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the question.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, Ranma, I gotta let you go to get more calls, but any other thoughts before I let you go?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I'm sorry, but this is the thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if you heard, but GameStop had a special this week on Injustice Gods Among Men.
[SPEAKER_02]: You mean Gods Among Us, but yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: $10, one hour sale only.
[SPEAKER_02]: So many people flooded the site to try to buy it online.
[SPEAKER_02]: What I found out about this, I went and I printed out the paper.
[SPEAKER_02]: When I got out of class, I went down to Best Buy and I got them to price match a $60 game for $10 that happened about two and a half hours after the sale ended.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice work.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you enjoy the game?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, it's one of the few games where I actually enjoyed it because I was playing it more for the story than anything else.
[SPEAKER_02]: Asking for someone who does not believe in paying retail price for a game unless you can get it to knock down, I honestly say...
[SPEAKER_02]: The game is worth $50 at least.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't see myself paying $59.
[SPEAKER_02]: I see myself paying $49 or maybe $54.
[SPEAKER_02]: But full retail, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is a tricky line once you break that $50 barrier.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's something psychological about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But we could do a whole other episode on that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I should let you go for now, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everybody listen to Anime Jam Session.
[SPEAKER_02]: You got it.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll be talking about Denver Comic Con and Anime Next on Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow, you guys got a busy show.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, have a good one, buddy.
[SPEAKER_04]: You too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even though we've been talking a lot on this show about E3, there's lots of other nerd shows at the Voice of Geeks Network talking about other stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there's anime conventions going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure somebody's going to be talking about Apple stuff on Monday.
[SPEAKER_04]: So stay tuned for that and all the great shows at the Voice of Geeks Network at vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's go to the phones which are lighting up and take another call.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_07]: This is YYR.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just called to drop this rhyme.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ha ha, I'm a troll.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to have to have haiku call night at some point and everybody will have to do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well played, my friend.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well played.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm tipping my hat to you.
[SPEAKER_04]: You just can't see it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because Rob's head is invisible and intangible.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, that's really the only reason I called in.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, since I have a captive audience, how is Bungie Ferret Tossing going?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's beer money.
[SPEAKER_07]: Beer money is great because it buys beer.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I don't think you've seen the last of Bungie Ferret Tossing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Deep in other projects right now, such as Ports 2,
[SPEAKER_07]: The smartphones and tablets I like to complain about, but I think at some point I would love to revisit that universe, yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow, okay, very cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you think about the way, you know, there's been a lot of news about like Xbox One is kind of shafting indies or whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, as somebody who developed, you know, quite a bit, you did several games, not just Bungie Fair Tossing, but I know you had Snake 360 and Falling.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, you did a few games for the...
[SPEAKER_04]: XNA, or Xbox Live Indie Games.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you think about all this news about Xbox One?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I mean, as far as indie games in general, specifically, Microsoft already said they're not going to allow anyone to self-publish on one at first.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I think that's a game changer, especially when Sony has come out and said, yes, if you want to self-publish, come to us.
[SPEAKER_07]: PS4 will
[SPEAKER_07]: will be happy to host your self-published game.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, of course, Nintendo is welcoming self-publishing on Wii U as well to some degree.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think you still need a business address to be a developer for a Nintendo platform.
[SPEAKER_07]: But besides that, yeah, it seems that Microsoft is going to be the least indie-friendly next-gen console out of the gate.
[SPEAKER_07]: So with that in mind, I think that, you know, depending on how much indie games influence the next console generation, that may not matter at all or it may matter a lot.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, it's all going to depend on how big of a blip on the radar indie games are over the next console gen.
[SPEAKER_07]: Before I let you go... The rest of it, it's crazy.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's absolutely crazy.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I think...
[SPEAKER_07]: All eyes are going to be on Sony at that after-conference presser.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, is PS4 going to be like this?
[SPEAKER_07]: Is it going to be like that?
[SPEAKER_07]: Is it going to allow us to do this?
[SPEAKER_07]: And the answers given there are really going to make a big difference as far as how people perceive not just the Xbox One, but all of the new consoles, really.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tomorrow, I mean literally tomorrow, what, 12 hours away is a huge day in gaming.
[SPEAKER_04]: Huge.
[SPEAKER_04]: One of the biggest ever.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll be on the edge of my seat, and I know probably all of us will be to some extent.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to take a nap.
[SPEAKER_04]: Before I let you go, buddy, I always kind of like to ask this.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know you just called in to give a haiku, and here we are with an interview.
[SPEAKER_04]: But just outside of developing your own stuff, what games are you playing?
[SPEAKER_04]: What are you enjoying playing lately?
[SPEAKER_07]: I've been playing a lot of Tekken lately.
[SPEAKER_07]: I actually bought the Wii U version just out of curiosity.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I can say Tekken Ball, I don't know who remembers the Tekken Ball minigame in Tekken 3.
[SPEAKER_11]: I love that game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Totally do.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, they basically, you know, they updated it graphically and now you can actually select different balls to use.
[SPEAKER_07]: and the difference is basically in how fast they move how quickly they charge up damage so it's a little bit more customizable than it was before and of course you can use tag teams which is for Tekken ball mostly useless but it's fun anyway so that is pretty much the major addition to the Tekken on Wii U the mushroom battle that everyone made such a big deal about and looks like so much fun in videos it's really not all it's cracked up to be
[SPEAKER_07]: It's fun for like five minutes, but after the novelty wears off, because basically it's like the poison mushrooms that shrink you and the super mushrooms that grow you, the poison mushrooms also hurt you, and the damage is really high to begin with.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it's like you get a couple mushrooms and already one more hit and you're dead.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it's over way too quickly, and you can't play it online, and you can't use tag teams, and it's just, it's not that great.
[SPEAKER_07]: And also, online, not too many people playing, for reasons that you could probably guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: Other than that, it's the same game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I haven't played a lot of Tekken in a while, so maybe I should rent Tekken on Nintendo Wii U, since my Wii U will allow me to do that.
[SPEAKER_08]: The actual last one that I bought was Tekken 4.
[SPEAKER_07]: I am warning you, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: Tekken has gotten extremely complex over the years.
[SPEAKER_07]: The learning curve is as steep now as it ever was, or possibly steeper.
[SPEAKER_07]: As long as you're okay with that, enjoy your rental that you can actually do.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, all right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to let you go to see if we can get one more call.
[SPEAKER_04]: But enjoy all the E3 stuff this week, and we'll talk to you later.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, we'll either enjoy it or not enjoy it.
[SPEAKER_07]: One of those.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_04]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_07]: Have fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: You too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, this is the first year where we can't necessarily say we're going to enjoy it, are we?
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, 1-877-GAME-OLR, our username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: We got time for about one more call here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Any last-minute stories while we're waiting for calls?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then we'll get to Twitter topics?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, actually, I do have one.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a hack that was done for New Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_03]: on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's just been released.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a total conversion for the game called Newer Super Mario Bros.,
[SPEAKER_03]: 120 all new levels remixed and original graphics to the game themes and music classic power-ups also new bosses and that kind of stuff and you can get it if you have a homebrew enabled Wii there's no piracy or hardware mods needed so I believe it's just a file like a save file that you put on there and you can download that at newerteam.com that's where you can find that hmm
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that it?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm trying to pull up Twitter here.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've been looking at the Xbox 720 checkpoint thing that came out last year.
[SPEAKER_03]: Remember the whole leak about VR and stuff?
[SPEAKER_03]: And a lot of it sounds exactly what they're talking about right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: So who knows?
[SPEAKER_03]: Next year maybe we might see some sort of Xbox glasses or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because, I mean, straight up even to their slogan that makes no fucking sense.
[SPEAKER_03]: Next generation entertainment, one box input one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why would you even do that?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's take another call.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_00]: Hi, this is Raginator.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, Raginator.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was going to say I didn't see the cam come on at first.
[SPEAKER_04]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's up, Raginator?
[SPEAKER_00]: Just a quick question.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's kind of a loaded one.
[SPEAKER_00]: You kind of touched on something, albeit briefly, earlier during the show.
[SPEAKER_00]: Rare has kind of hinted that they're working on something, and everyone's speculating that they're going to resuscitate an all-franchise.
[SPEAKER_00]: Most people seem to think it's going to be either Conker or Killer Instinct.
[SPEAKER_00]: What are your thoughts on that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, well, we had a screenshot that was leaked, but I, you know, again, this is one of those anybody could have with a Photoshop.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, did they prove it fake?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Proved it fake?
[SPEAKER_04]: You're talking about the one that has... That had, like, Banjo-Kazooie and Halo 5.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's because that stuff that they got on there was either as wishful thinking and trademarks that they had already done.
[SPEAKER_03]: It wasn't anything new.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was fake.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's not going to be Banjo-Kazooie.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think it would be Banjo-Kazooie anyways because it wouldn't be that big a deal.
[SPEAKER_03]: It would be just kind of like, eh.
[SPEAKER_04]: whatever because they had a new banjo game and it was just it was all right but I'm gonna go with the easy answer and say Killer Instinct based off the whole trademark dispute that they got settled um there wouldn't have been a reason to do that otherwise I don't think if they didn't want to keep that door open for some reason and I think they know that's what everybody wants and especially with where they're going with all this you know DRM debacle um
[SPEAKER_04]: it's gonna take a franchise like that to make people you know what's it gonna take for you to sell your morals up the river essentially and it I mean honestly if Xbox could come out and say you know what we're gonna have we're gonna have Rob's fantasy games Mass Effect 4 the Guardian Legend 2 you know and the things I want to see it's gonna be hard for me to even go god I fucking hate what they're doing but I really really really want these games it's gonna be hard it's easy for me to sit here now and go
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't need Halo 5.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't need a new Killer Instinct.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't need some of this other stuff they're talking about because I can kind of be satisfied with PlayStation 4.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, and technically, we don't need any of it.
[SPEAKER_10]: We need air and water.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I need Guardian Legend 2, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_04]: I need it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: I need it!
[SPEAKER_10]: Intervention!
[SPEAKER_04]: What about you, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_10]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: Rare franchise.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's coming back.
[SPEAKER_10]: Killer Instinct.
[SPEAKER_04]: How about you, Ragenator?
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, I would love to see another Killian State God only knows I played the Jesus out of the SNES port along with the N64 game but I'm a little concerned because now history has shown that both first priorities and third priorities tend to really
[SPEAKER_00]: Goverbard screw with a proven formula, and when they screw with a given formula that's proven to be a winner, a lot of people tend to revolt.
[SPEAKER_00]: Cases at point, Capcom is screwed with
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, they had a final fight with Streetwise for PS2.
[SPEAKER_00]: Turned a 2D brawler into a 3D brawler.
[SPEAKER_00]: They didn't do too well.
[SPEAKER_00]: Street Fighter EX3 was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to say with Capcom too, since you brought up Mega Man, I think there's a very strong possibility Mega Man fans will finally have something to celebrate this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if that'll just be a little victory or something, but I just think the timing is right for Capcom to unveil what they're going to do with Mega Man.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would love to see it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just don't screw it up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Make minor tweaks here and there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe
[SPEAKER_00]: and new characters, maybe a mechanic here or there, but don't go radically changing the game to the point where
[SPEAKER_00]: It's basically a totally different game.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's only related to previous games by name only.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not going to say it the other way.
[SPEAKER_04]: I asked because I just wanted to type Uranus.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: And now I read it there on air.
[SPEAKER_04]: So congratulations.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if I remember right, it would be three warps to Neptune and then three more to Uranus.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Six warps to Uranus, Ragenator.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, I know it's corny.
[SPEAKER_00]: I came up with something.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's all right.
[SPEAKER_04]: So is the show, Ragenator.
[SPEAKER_04]: So is the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, have a good one, buddy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have a good E3.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, have a good one.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: I feel like that's like wishing people a Merry Christmas or Happy Hanukkah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I feel like you should wish video gamers a happy E3, even when E3 is going to be bad news.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, you're our linguist.
[SPEAKER_04]: What should the greeting be to other gamers?
[SPEAKER_10]: Blessed E3 That might be a little too much Blessed E3 How about Blessed E3
[SPEAKER_10]: How about WankFreeE3?
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, maybe I'll throw that question to the chatters and see what they come up with.
[SPEAKER_04]: But for now, I am going to close the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you do have further thoughts on any of tonight's topics, mailbag at OrangeLawnTrader.com or Twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_03]: So a screenshot leaked from a brand new unannounced game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, we kind of assumed it was coming.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just Dance, the new Just Dance game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's gonna have the Ghostbusters theme in it because they have a screenshot where people are dressed up like Ghostbusters.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's in Just Dance 4, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_03]: You sure about that?
[SPEAKER_10]: Rob is up going to look, by the way.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now in the chat room, by the way, we have a call for a new Rival Schools series.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, what are you looking at?
[SPEAKER_10]: Just Dance 4?
[SPEAKER_10]: He's reading.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's going to take us a while because Rob's reading.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry, YYR, I can't click YouTube.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe not.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought it was in this.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, it's official because it's actually on Xbox's website.
[SPEAKER_03]: So if you go to Xbox's Just Dance 2014 and they've got... Well, I mean, what a duh they're going to do a new Just Dance game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: These games sell like crazy and it's not a bad game.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Tiger Claw talking about Mad Catz readying an Android console of their own.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is this like an Ouya type response?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, we are, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not like the Ouya.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, I like the idea a lot better than the Ouya.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's basically going to be a console that plays Android games.
[SPEAKER_03]: It has the Google Play Store, and it plays any Android game, and you can actually map buttons onto stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: so games that don't support touch or whatever you can use a mouse with them or do support touch you can use a mouse or you can use analog sticks to emulate touch but the fact that it doesn't require any special games it's just the games that you have or the games that you buy for like a dollar or free or whatever so I like that and their controller looks nice too it looks like an Xbox 360 controller
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, it looks exactly like their Xbox 360 controller, their MLG controller.
[SPEAKER_03]: It looks exactly like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: And one other tweet from Tigerclaw tonight about Interplay getting an IP from THQ for $7,500.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's how much they paid for Free Space.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a good deal.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a great deal.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interstellar Combat Series that was developed by Volition and published by Interplay.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's back in Interplay's library after getting it back from THQ.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interplay, by the way, it should be noted, they never did lose the rights to sell Descent Free Space and Free Space 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want another Descent that is awesome that required more buttons than the other Descent games.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: That required telekinesis to play.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, well, thank you guys very much for your tweets at twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_04]: Lots of great stuff tonight, but it's about that time.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've got to wrap up the show and get everybody's final thought and all that.
[SPEAKER_10]: We have a consensus in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_10]: Rival Schools is awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rival Schools is awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: You should have put that on your list list.
[SPEAKER_04]: Too late.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, okay, you know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: I actually, when I had a lot more disposable income, I paid 99 bucks to import the Justice Gakuen Evolution.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I played the hell out of it for days.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it's like, every time they would bring out, like one of the games for home, they'd take out something from the Japanese version that made it awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like the board game mode in Project Justice.
[SPEAKER_10]: After you played through the board game, your custom character that you played the board game with would have stats based on how you played the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: And they just took that out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, guys, before I let you go tonight, I just want to say happy three, and let's hope the news isn't too terrible.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's hope there's a lot of good surprises and things that we will be excited about.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will be here during the day tomorrow during the press conferences, and I'll be around Tuesday, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will make a point to be in chat.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you want some folks to talk about the conferences, you want a live blog post,
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not really live blogging because I kind of think everybody's kind of watching it, but more like live discussion.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you want to talk about what's going on at E3 with some like-minded individuals, I urge you to be at live.vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll be there during the big preface conferences tomorrow, and we can talk about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll be there as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you going to be there too?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, because my boss is gone, so I don't have to really work there.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's all work-related anyways.
[SPEAKER_04]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll be there at least for Microsoft and Sony but in the middle of the day DarkSakura and I might go on a friend date to take care of some stuff around town.
[SPEAKER_10]: YYR left another haiku.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah?
[SPEAKER_10]: Happy E3 guys.
[SPEAKER_10]: Look forward to no prices and no dates either.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think we'll get those tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think we'll get prices and dates tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: It would be a first if we did because remember what was the infamous thing a few years ago from Sony?
[SPEAKER_04]: $599 US dollars.
$599.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I think we will get it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll try to wake up tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: to care about the press releases.
[SPEAKER_04]: To get in chat as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've already got my popcorn.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just stale, but I already have my popcorn.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to go to Popcornopolis.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: So yeah, if you want a place to just chat with some other folks and kind of just get some live banter going on what's going on at E3, join us in chat, live.vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: You never know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bobby might hop in on a plane for all we know from his plane.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Check out E3.VOGnetwork.com I'm really excited about what this week is going to bring and it's going to be a great week I guess that's it We'll be back next week to do it all over again as we lead up to our 11th anniversary on June 23rd It's time to go around and get everybody's final thought DarkSakura, we'll start with you tonight, your final thought I wish I hadn't eaten all that chocolate so quickly
[SPEAKER_04]: And my final thought tonight is no regrets.
[SPEAKER_04]: I did eat it that quickly, and it was good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, your final thought tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm looking forward to this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think I'm always excited about E3 stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just disappointed I don't get to play it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And also, I'm not going to be able to make it out to Best Buy on Wednesday to play the Wii U games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because it's at a weird time.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like at 4 o'clock.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, if it was in the middle of the day, I could sneak out and do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the middle of the day one's on Saturday, and I'm not going to drive all the way to Elk Grove.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you guys for listening to Orange Launch Radio and supporting us for all these years.
[SPEAKER_03]: We really appreciate your support.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is a free show.
[SPEAKER_10]: All we ask if you enjoyed the show is
[SPEAKER_04]: tell a friend or two about the show help us spread the word because we don't get a big booth at E3 to help spread the word or any big fancy advertising budget any advertising you do see comes out of our own pockets so please help spread the word and grow our family here at Orange Lounge Radio and the Voice of Geeks Network support independent podcasting have a terrific week good night
[SPEAKER_01]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: Orange Lounge Radio is a production of OLR Studios.
[SPEAKER_01]: To join us for a live show, tune in to VOGnetwork.com Sunday nights at 6pm Pacific, 9pm Eastern.
[SPEAKER_01]: The views and opinions expressed in this program do not necessarily reflect those of the staff of Orange Lounge Radio or VOG Network, but you know they were all still true.
[SPEAKER_01]: See you next week!