Do you want to hear the most annoying sound in the world?
You're listening to Orange Lounge Radio, the Monty Talk, and then some.
Orange Lounge may contain adult content.
Orange Lounge may contain many four-letter words.
Orange Lounge may contain a scene of nudity.
Orange Lounge may contain hot monkey sex.
Just kidding, Orange Lounge will not contain hot monkey sex.
In this episode...
Hey, are there any balls down there?
About the biggest bear you've ever seen, Dingleberry.
What's your favorite scary movie?
Showgirls.
Absolute fright.
What's yours?
There are no stupid questions, just stupid people.
Don't torture yourself. That's my job.
Now's the time on sprockets and we dance!
I'll get you, my pretty. And your little dog, too.
I know kung fu.
I'm sorry, but all questions must be submitted in writing.
Why did they have to take the word gang?
No! What he expects for Spanish expression is ken-to.
Hey!
Dark Sakura
Shut up! Where's my gun? This is my boomstick!
Skye
Come on girls, it's time to drop the bomb!
Loki
I can't, for the life of me, get the hooker to have sex and leave.
What kind of war human being would find that funny?
Orange Lounge Radio
We are live, and this is episode number 35 for March the 2nd of 2003.
into the Le Mani Scene's most crowded radio station of all things, Beeee, Le Mani.
My name is Rob Roberts. You might know me as Skye. I'm a poet and I don't know it.
But your feet show up because they're long feathers.
My feet are big. You know what that means?
Attention guys out there, Rob wears big shoes.
Joining me as always are my awesome co-hosts in this corner, the happiest and most loud-mouthed
bunny on the farm, Miss Jamie Summers.
you know her better as Dark Sakura?
In that corner, say hello to our tech master Loki.
Also with us tonight, we have a whole ass load of guests.
Say hello to Sharks Girls in the house.
Everyone else is in the other room playing Animal Crossing, I'm thinking about joining
them.
Hey, traitor.
Hey, I gotta get Bones back.
And also with us, say hello to Mel B.
I believe that children are our future.
Say hello to Dave.
And there's a whole bunch of other people. Oh, say hello to Brad!
Bawk, bawk, bawk, bawk, bawk, bawk.
Why are you bawking?
Ah, shit!
Oops, I had a little technical difficulty there, sorry about that.
Hi. Say hello. Oh, hi Brad. And then in the back is the Ice Queen.
Say hello to the Ice Queen. Come on in.
Wow, that's twice this month I've been called a douchebag.
Tell me Rob, do you feel
not so fresh? Oh yeah, so we're in a new month now.
So that means that somebody else has to call Rob a douchebag.
Who wants to take the turn this time? Okay, you can do it. Don't forget. April 1st.
I'm getting reports that all of our listeners might...
The beauty of silence
Turn the steps wide to orange flags This PDR stops all of us
Apparently, Dave knows what camel piss tastes like.
Tastes just like it smells.
Alright, we're back.
Unfortunately what happened just before the break, for some reason, we didn't show ourselves
this going down off the air, but all our listeners got dropped, so they're slowly coming back
on the stream, and it's kind of ironic that they should come back to the beauty of silence.
So, today is a little bit of a buzz show, I'm downing a Smirnoff Black with Mel, a toast,
to a non-crappy show for once, no I'm just kidding.
Who's all here?
Dang.
It sounded like five people just got here.
Who got here?
We have Brandon, Brian, Anita, Johnny.
Oh my god.
Full House today.
Today it is kind of a Full House.
Okay, so.
Full House?
Everywhere we go, everywhere you look.
Okay, after what we were watching today that showed what's-her-face from Full House.
Candace Cameron.
Yeah, Candace Cameron.
Oh, she looks kind of slutty.
What the hell ever happened to Candace Cameron?
She's very pretty.
Candace Cameron met a hockey player by the name of Valie Bure and got engaged in Paris
and got married and has two kids, go fig, and she looked like a slut for a long time
because she had platinum blonde hair.
But now she looks a little bit more respectable.
She kind of reminds me of that B-movie actress Beverly Lynn who did this really awesome movie
called Babes II, Lost in Beaver Creek.
Anyone who's down with Skinimax, it's a must-see and a must-hape and all that.
Okay, wait, hold on, hold on, I found some information on Candace Cameron, here we go.
at age twenty six candace cameron beer has accomplished a lot
i'm gonna shove a parade right up your ass in a minute
all hello to our other guests is not your what's up
and say hello and introduce yourselves are much
room on the mike's here
hey what's up everyone knows me i'm zero how's it going
what's up
this is uh... johnnie
a cable bay
Okay, and now I'm going to finish talking about Candace Cameron, Biaray.
Oh, Billy the big fat queer is here!
Say hello, Billy!
Hi.
How are you, Billy?
Peachy keen.
Wait, before I tell the story about Candace Cameron, no, because Billy would enjoy hearing
about Candace Cameron.
I would love to hear about Candace Cameron.
And then we're going to have a segment called Story Time with Billy, because I want Billy
to tell about all his experiences last night at Mardi Gras.
I gave some guidance.
Wait, no, no, no.
Hold on.
First, first, Candace.
Then your story.
Oh, hi.
You're listening to Orange Lounge of Omani Radio.
Sometimes we talk about the game with the arrows.
I hear it's popular.
Anyway.
And we talk about porn a lot.
Since her years as DJ...
B-Ray.
Hello.
Rob, if you need to throw up the bathrooms down the hall.
I'm going to throw up in your lap.
Since her years as DJ Tanner on the long-running sitcom Full House, she has had the lead role
in six movies, guest starred on four television shows, and executive produced an entertaining
child safety show.
She is married to ice hockey player Valérie Biré, who sucks ass and has three children.
I don't want to know what their association is.
Their names suck, ass, and who?
Come here suck, come here ass!
Since I was ten years old, Candace has been a distraught role model for me through her
varied acting roles and admirable participation in organizations like the Starlight Foundation.
Which sucks ass.
Hey!
That's a charity!
It's an ass-sucking charity.
Her openness and love for Christianity is refreshing in the church of ass-sucking.
So she sucks little boys' asses then.
Refreshing is this nice malt beverage right here.
And then it talks about growing up with Candace.
So if you want to visit all about Candace Cameron, go to www.candascameronbure.net.
If you want to suck some ass.
Okay.
Speaking of sucking ass, let's get to story time with Billy.
Wait, hold on.
Okay, Billy.
Yeah, I'm going to pull up some storytelling music just for Billy.
But yeah, I just want you to tell, you know, why you came down to Sacramento this weekend
and what you did last night and how it went and, you know, make it really long and exciting
because we have three hours to fill, okay?
I have to go soon. It's going to be short and sweet.
Well, try.
It was Mardi Gras night.
Wait, hold on.
Story time with Billy!
This better be the Jerry Halliwover.
It is the Jerry Halliwover. It's the DDR Jerry Halliwover game.
Tell your tale, Billy.
Well, it was Mardi Gras night, and we had quite a bit of fun, and I got a couple beats here and there.
Wait, and now how did you get beats?
How do you think?
Did you show your titties to some lesbians?
I did show my titties since I'm a lesbian, and then some cute boys just walked in and gave me these items to show me.
So anyways, on the way out, there was a cute drunk boy, and he's all,
I didn't give you these, so I'm like, what are you going to give me?
Billy just cut right to the chase! What are you going to give me?
He's all, I'll let you stick your hand down my pants, and I'm like, well, okay.
Not that I'm complaining. I've got quite a handful.
And then Matt got a C.
I got a hold of it and see it, so it was a wonderful fun night.
Oh, Matt's here. Matt, come here, come here. Do you have anything you want to add to this story, Matt?
Or, I'm sorry, the Ice Queen?
When he got the grab, I got the C.
He wanted some more beats, and he came up to me and said,
Well, what do I got to do to get some beats? And I said, Well, you know you got to do some of your stuff.
and
you know he asked for a piece for me to some michael's what do i get he said i
did the same thing
so i can simply
and make you know you open up his pants
and you know i thought i started looking at another and i'm like
no no honey i've got more class billy does
for
I was trying to start fights in the parking lot.
Yeah, sometimes we talk about some Arrow game, I don't know.
Build your gay sex quota, now it's time for...
Yeah, the show is getting too gay. Pussy, cunt, clit, cock...
Alright, quick, the chat room is getting restless because we haven't talked about anything but
Emani yet. So, Loki, give us a topic we can have a roundtable about.
Oh god, okay. Starting off this week, well obviously everyone knows that DDR Max 2, the
Japanese version, is coming out April 25th, I believe.
Which means that somebody has to buy that for me for my birthday.
Yes, April 25th. Also announced with it is going to be a brand new V-Rare CD, V-Rare
number 5. Which I don't get because once they mass produce
the CD, it's not really rare anymore. Shut up. Anyways, well, some of the things that
are going to be on it, obviously, is going to be the ability to make linked data for
DDR Extreme, which will be nice because you'll be able to actually record data for all the
songs instead of like half. And also, it's rumored to be that there's over 70 songs,
including some from DDR Extreme. Whoo! Which means you're going to see Dynamite, Rave,
Downbird Soda Mix, Look to the Sky, True Colors Mix, Do It Right, the Harmonize Two
Set Mix, Drop the Bomb, System FS Mix, and AM3P 303 Bass Mix. And that's it from DDR
Mac or DDR Stream. If they have La Copa de la Vida, I'll be like so happy, because that's
the best song ever.
Did you say it was a foreign language until Ricky Martin's song?
No. That's right, Billy, that's going to be...
I said it was like a foreign language until someone said Ricky Martin's song.
So yeah, that's what's coming out April 25th.
Okay, discuss.
Well, I for one am super excited about this, except I'm fucking broke and I have to move to the end of next month.
But, you know, I'll probably scrape some money out of the couch and buy it anyway.
That's okay, you can play mine. It'll be my birthday month.
Oh, gee, I can come over and play. That would be great.
Like hell, we're gonna buy one, dammit!
I was I was brought to you by we're gonna buy one so I can rip the songs and put them on the Internet
Okay stuff. Well, the thing is I don't know what if Konami happens to like be spying on me
But every time the game comes out my birthday's around there
It's just for me that affected you just released games I roll in a world
Okay, I have the tie into my life and know to release games around my birthday CDR max to
USA, November. Of course. Any idea what's gonna be on that? Are they gonna give us anything
special? Probably just like, you know, same thing as last time, maybe some more new exclusive
songs and whatnot. So, you know, nothing yet. Of course, we'll know more after E3, so. That's
true. If we can get into it, wink, wink, nudge, nudge. Mel's got his hand raised, hold on.
Why can't Orange Lounge get the hookup like what?
People who are engaged to Gamestop employees get the hookup?
Well, um...
Yes, Jason Enos actually hires a lot of DDR spot bemoniacs and other people to dance for him at the boots.
That's pretty much how we get our hookup.
extremely fashionable maybe that could you know go for something
but i'm surprised how everybody at e three looks good for some reason or
another
you can model a dance
i could be a dance mat
hey i want to dance pattern three
i've kicked everyone's ass at britney's like dance beat
uh... there's my claim to be released
your billy's new hero for being the britney's answer that
which also is about what he was kinda like last year is a lot of us can only
dream to go there Mel you've been there so what's it kind of like you go in the
doors is just like oh my god Disneyland for me pretty much you walk in there
it's like someone took Vegas and put it inside a convention center it's nothing
but neon lights everywhere you see like you know every brand name out there has
a billboard the size of like a freaking street you know the street billboards
everybody looks good not just the people who model off games but like even the
business exec women and guys I don't know you know it's like everyone's just
There's celebrities that roll through there like my boy Henry. He saw Robin Williams in there got you know a picture with him
I almost got was able to flag down Gary Coleman for an autograph, but he was in a rush. What you talking about Mel?
Our friend Ryan goes there every year and brings back a videotape, but this last year
He went and saw Bruce Campbell again and got Bruce Campbell to record his answering machine message
Wow
That's a serious hookup and yeah other celebrities like at the
THQ I think it was that Stacy Kubler freaking like
Come on Bruce Campbell on the goddamn radio show
Hey, just tell me tell me who I have to blow to get in the door and we're there. Okay?
Sorry, I didn't want to cut off your story
But yeah, pretty much III is just a blast and not only do you just see like what's new
It's all about the free stuff, man. It's all about just nabbing posters, friggin' demo discs.
Inflatable Morolians from Space Channel 5.
Oh, Inflatable Morolians from Space Channel 5. Those are great.
And just like all the stuff, and like, it's crazy because Nintendo's booth just gets like the biggest freaking line because everyone is just all about winning free stuff.
And that's where my boi, a couple of my bois won Wave Burt's from there. You know, right before they were out in the public and, yeah, that was the hot item.
I have to cut in really fast because Billy the big homo has to go, but I wanted to ask him if he has any final thoughts.
No.
Not even one?
Not even one.
A song lyric, maybe?
Final thoughts? Is this like Jerry Springer?
I just can't get you out of my head.
That's all I think about.
Alright, get out of here. Later.
Bye, Billy. Thank you.
Na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na. Oh, hell yeah. Later.
Oh, you guys are going too? That sucks.
Wait, where's Anita? Bring Anita in here.
it's only become the good I know this is like it's the oh my god who walks into
the studio next show it's steedy or Holik ladies and gentlemen say hello hi
everybody what are you doing in town today actually I'm moving in here you're
moving in here well hello and I know you're kind of in and out but do you
have any final thoughts for the radio show or anything you want to say any
Any shout outs?
Let's see.
I don't know.
I don't know too many people anymore.
Shout outs to all the DDR people out there who love DDR and all the money.
Alright.
Well put.
Thank you.
Alright.
Take care.
Be safe.
Have a good move.
Alright.
So.
We should be able to get E3 tickets because we have word in the industry, right?
We want to go!
Well, probably the best thing you can do is just talk to Jason Enos, you know, because he gets, you know, for all his pull, he gets a lot of guest passes, so if nothing else, you may not get, like, the perks of media, which means you get to have, like, exclusive views of, like, say, you get media guides and, like, kits and all that stuff.
But you still get to go around and go everywhere else, you just don't get to go inside, like, behind the wall and get free food, but...
Oh, well. Bummer.
You know what? You'll take what you get and you'll like it.
I want free food!
My God, I feel like there's a party going on in the hallway.
If you've received tickets to your home address once, you will always receive tickets.
Even if you are no longer in the industry, you will always receive tickets.
I know, I got my thing in the mail about two months ago saying,
yeah, re-register for Ethereum, like hell yeah.
okay
now was leaving
uh... what is the three
i'm wondering if i could
met one of my old and
you know you're going to come to have a decision
how do you still work for namco look might you may six of namco they've just
asked the a question of the hour and there which is actually kind of funny
because you know
a lot of people may actually not know this and here we are sitting
talking about a three what exactly is the three of those of them
electronic entertainment expo
uh... yeah that goes on in l a basically it's
the you know big all be of all video games computer entertainment such
vegas in a nutshell it's every key extreme to go up in there
and fan service for the guys
and some of them
it's when all the big game companies get together to show off their new toys
and had seen it there a couple years ago today
all every like everybody's up in there
just walk up to him i mean you know
monday
my back up with the am i correct
i wanna go
and i don't like my work in a rather go
So I guess I'll talk to Mel B and Sharksko a little bit while you guys are still here.
Mel, how was Cyber Beat? What did you think of the tourney and all that?
Cyber Beat was, I guess personally, just one of the most fun weekends all together.
There's something to be about going to a tournament and yeah, it's fun if you win or it's fun for whatever reason.
But just being there and being able to go through just the whole competitive experience and seeing some of the people who've been just working their way up finally get to the top or get some recognition.
It was cool for them, definitely. I was happy to see, I guess, well, a lot of people are referring to the torch being passed.
You know, it's like the old school's kinda like making way for the newer, the new jacks, the new generation.
And I'm totally fine, because most people out there, like Bruce Lee or AJ and such, they've busted themselves pretty hard, and it's good to see them get some recognition for a change.
I mean, I wanted some, I wanted a slice of the pie, but it was cool. I'm glad people still, you know, like to see me out there and whatever.
Cool, cool deal.
I have to ask you guys, Sharkskroll, I know you are huge on the Derby Owners Club.
I'm trying to break myself up, but I haven't played it since the last time you were in the Bay.
Oh no, I was going to ask if you went to that tournament that they had in Milpitas.
I kind of didn't even realize it was happening because I thought it was the following week.
What have you been up to lately then, girl?
Work, I see MLB and then I go to sleep, and that's about damn near it.
Well, you know, gotta do what you gotta do.
Sucks for the record, but that's okay
On a side note okey actually won the Derby on how the hell did that happen? I coached him in the final match
See Ross actually was kicking a lot of ass
He had the most wins and had the most money, but the last match was a g1
Which is like the big high stakes and I know he was just asking me for advice
I'm like do this right here hold the horse right there whip it right there BAM wasn't even close Wow. That's pretty cool
Doesn't Derby Owners' Club handicap you if you're behind or something?
Only in one certain race.
But everything else is skill to the player.
I wonder how well Polteri would have done.
Yeah, because the last time I raced I remember Polteri won like her second race.
And I was actually racing, I think I was racing Ross in that one, I don't know.
I was racing some of the better players and I won.
And I was like, how the hell did I win that? My horse sucks.
And somebody was telling me, oh, they handicap it.
And I still have the picture, I still have the picture that says Pollotary is very happy.
Pollotary, the horse, rules. I'm sorry, hot man sex still rules.
Okay. So, alright, how about we take a quick break, and then we come back and we're going
to do the FUs of the week before the people have to go, because I know we certainly have
a lot of angst. Yeah, we're going to have another three hour long FU segment. No, well
This is what we'll do.
Everybody in the studio can F you as much as they want.
But everybody in the chat room will limit to like three FUs.
OK.
So chat room, send your FUs on to me over a private message.
But three at the most.
Because we don't want this to go on forever.
All right, so.
OK, so yeah, we're going to, somebody turn the mic off.
uh-oh
that was uh... the other line
uh... yes i would like to call the other line
we're going to let me see that when i had a phone that had a pause that would
meet the line
i would
and people that i had call waiting since i got tired of talking to them at the
i'm sorry that was from a grandma that has let you go
uh...
it's cool like when you have
when you have to be fun
he just was it
and see how long it takes people to actually think you've hung up on us.
Whoa, whoa, yeah, yeah, yeah
He made me feel like I was lost in the circle of time
Who said
Yeah, baby, this is my home, so come on
We can touch it, hold us to your feet I know you feel it, but I ain't no fool
You need to make a man you hate You need to have the power
And you make me feel high, and you defend the power
who are in everything else. I just like that one because I like the background.
And it's really easy to PA, I think. That's why I like it.
You know what I want to say? What?
I want to say is, where's 2MB? We need some more 2MB remixes.
There's Trip Machine Survivor? That's not 2MB.
Isn't it? I don't know. That's just Desire.
We need 2MB. You know what the next song is going to get the 2MB treatment? It's going
to be fucking Bag. Bag sucks ass, okay? It's just like a rhyme.
I'm trying to make a trans version of Bag, The Legend of Bag, or The Legend of Haggis.
They already have The Legend of Bag sucks.
Do they really?
Yeah.
Okay, the worst fucking remix I heard this week, the Legend of Max unlimited 300 or something like that, is not even a remix.
It's like, okay, let's just stop it, start playing Max 300, stop it again, it's not a remix. It's just awful.
Oh, cool!
No, I haven't heard Climax.
Also reading the chat room, and if you're not in her chat room, you should join it.
Just go to her website, orangelounge.skie.cx and click on chat.
She's playing Snake.
And I'm just reading some things that are going on in the chat room right now.
We have someone who hates Polteri almost more than we do, it looks like.
We have Satome Ranma says, you know what's great?
The songs that are credited in Aoki All Stars and all it is is Polteri, with little voices
the background. God damn her taking over DDR. I swear she's like a cancer.
Paula Terry. I have to say, to her credit, lately she's been able to hold a key, but
I think that's just because someone's been beating her over the head more and more. You
know, it's like, okay, it's like, for anyone who's ever been in band, you know, you can
buy an instrument and it can be built out of tune. Well, I think that Paula Terry has
been built out of tune. So they did what they do with some instruments and beat them into
shape
Brad would be so mad at you right now
actually you know what they've got right now it's pretty cool I saw this on tech
TV today
for when you're doing like karaoke and stuff what will happen is you can sing
all out of Keith but when it comes out of the speakers it makes you in Keith
it like compensates
what was that machine in Josie and the Pussycats the
the one the big machine they had that would make them all in tune
not the Mr. Movie Phone there was something else and then it had the subliminal messages from Mr. Movie
Phone you know
Purple is the new orange.
You know, he's talking about that machine that you can sing out of key and sing in key.
That's probably how you got a hundred points on that.
Hey, hey, hey, I don't like where you're going with that, mister.
I don't like where you're going with that.
I actually, you know what, maybe I can find it later.
No, I couldn't play it during the actual show, but I do have Irene and I.
I taped Irene and I singing Boys.
I remember.
We got a hundred on it too.
One day at Rob's old apartment in Roseville, when I had laryngitis,
Rob's standing, tall while everyone was sitting, with his hand to the side, diva-style singing
that I'm Like a Bird song, with his eyes skyward, and I'm sitting here going, God damn I'm glad
I have laryngitis.
I have a very vivid memory of just this, like, Rob's on stage with the spotlight on him,
and he's got a feather blood.
Now, that's going to be DDR Idol.
The only thing that any of us from Sac-Bimani are doing is admin work and running the 2DX
portion of the tourney.
It's going to be pretty intricate.
Rules will be posted within the next few days, possibly as soon as tomorrow, and it's going
to be cool.
I think you guys will like it.
A lot of people are coming from out of town to do it.
As far as Perfect Attack goes, there's rules posted on DDRSpot.com, DDRFreak in the tournament
forum.
They're going to be on SACBimani as soon as we get the site up.
As we all look.
I'll put something together then.
Do you have any answering questions and then beating people with bats?
Actually, you know, I'm thinking about auctioning off my bat.
What's it about you're going to put your bat on the new DDR Freak Marketplace or something?
No, I'm just going to go around and hit people in the head with it and go,
Hi, you've been beaten by some of the most famous people in the big money world.
You've actually hit yourself with a bat?
Question for Loki from the chat room, and I already think I know the answer.
But, apparently the rumor is you can triple-A Fuhurata's theme. Is that true?
What?
Somebody in the chat room is asking if you can triple-A Fuhurata's theme. Ninzapro.
No? I can't triple-A shit, man. I totally suck at PA.
Somebody claims they played DDR with you and you triple-A'd it.
Okay! I wish I was there because I only played doubles.
So, how much drugs were these people doing?
I don't know.
I only played doubles, and if I triple-a'd that, I mean, that would be pretty sweet, but no.
I might have triple-a'd it on basic.
I double-a'd Rhythm and Police on my new pads that suck.
You know what fucking sucks? Again, one great on all these EX songs.
I can't get my fucking triple-a on heavy. I always get one fucking great.
Oh, that brings me around to the FUs.
I can't even get one grade. I'm five is my best, I think, but no.
Back to March Madness.
Oh, hi, yes.
I've played for about the same time.
4th place?
Yeah, but where's their 4th place in the red?
I don't know, the guy's in Iowa, so that's a really good question.
Where was I in Iowa?
This is actually turning into a pretty good story.
Holy crap, you have a job now?
On the dream plane, no.
Now back to March Madness, hello.
The dates for the tournament are March 29th, March 30th, it will be at Scandia in Sacramento.
There's addresses, there's directions, everything's going to be posted in one form or another.
But we're going to be giving updates throughout, and like we were saying, we should have rules
for the 2DX tournament posted this week.
And it's going to be fun, right?
Yeah, it's going to be fun.
Fun.
It'll be exciting.
exciting it will it will make people's heart race it'll bring a couple of
thrills oh yes I still want my home run derby tournament for March Madness we
are actually working on that I did I actually did leave the suggestion for
doing the I just we didn't get to talk about it in depth but I did leave the
suggestion for this is the this is the bummer no bang a ball for dollars I had
suggested that we possibly at scandia's have bumper boats of scandia that we
have a wet t-shirt contest in the bumper boats however unfortunately they can't
do that it's a family environment because I work there okay you got you
got the inside on the bumper boats all right I can make that happen trust me
there my my my co-workers would probably in fact you know enter a couple people
they know in the contest I'm totally serious too this is the problem from what
What I told, a big radio station here in Sacramento, the rock station in Sacramento, did a big
as I hear the grunt from the former intern, they used to do a undie 500 on the raceway
where they would get all these strippers to go out in their underwear and race in the
race cars and they would have the tarp that goes around so that people can't look in because
what happens ten minutes after the green light goes on, the clothes come off.
So, unfortunately, some little kid decided to rip a hole in the tarp and look through
it and go home and tell his parents and ruined it for everybody.
Mommy, mommy, I saw boobies!
Dad's going to park his car in your garage!
Why would you, why would you go run home and tell your mom?
It's like, mom, look, I saw boobies!
Oh, okay.
Don't tell your mom that.
Since I, like, used to be the intern there, I'll tell you right now, 95% of the contests
they have are all horrible ideas.
like that one because they don't ever think of what can happen they just think
what's gonna get the most like 40 year old dirty guys out there that's all it
is people doing it in the church that was good radio so what can we go like
hire people to go to go to the Presbyterian Church down the road and go
hey you know it's gonna be interesting though because we will be broadcast
The Orange Islands Radio will be broadcasting live all day long, both days.
We're going to have a lot of help this time.
We're not leaving one person in control of the night.
We're not going to be constrained in the corner.
No, this is going to be great.
If things...
That was your trial by fire.
If things work out like we're hoping, Orange Islands Radio is going to have its own little
freaking temple.
That day.
It's going to be awesome.
Can I get a squirt gun to shoot people with?
Yes.
Okay.
I have a squirt gun that looks like an Uzi.
March?
No, it actually it actually is just a water gun, but it looks exactly like an Uzi
It was part of my Jill Valentine costume for a Resident Evil ax the first time I played DDR was just as Jill Valentine
That's very on a DDR machine. Did you play Silent Hill? I know Steve no
Actually, my first song that I ever played on third mix was dynamite. No with Xanadu
of course and then and then dynamite rave in
In army boots! Never play Gen. Raven army boots, by the way, especially ones that aren't broken in.
Ah, 23rd Magus has a zing here. We'll be broadcasting from the Temple of Butt.
Come inside the Temple of Butt!
We should hang a little side. It's too bad Scandia is the family fun center. It'll have to be the temple of...
So what are we going to do, Barbecued...
Rob, what are we going to do, Barbecued Fried Clams?
Oh all right okay that goes in pride class y'all are dirty
to do for a while we're going to buy a hundred tacos at from Del Taco just
because we can and we're gonna give them to everybody at March Madness just
because we can here have a taco yeah exactly you're like hey we're gonna
bought a hundred you like one by like a hundred of them and then just start
hand in mouth to people as they walk in for no apparent reason.
You guys have to come if you're in the area.
I can't say anything officially on this yet, but keep your eyes on all the boards.
Keep listening to us.
Because there might be a little bit more to this tournament.
Are you talking about the power station bit?
Because that has been official.
It's official.
It's a twist greater than Joe Millionaire.
Look out.
Our tournament is also...
It's an all new tournament.
That's a twist.
The tournament is also going to serve as qualifiers for that other one.
It's going to serve as qualifiers for the big power station tournament,
Which is this chain of arcades, I believe, and maybe you know a little more about this,
Mel?
I don't know.
I think there's going to be somewhere around three qualifiers, I believe.
Two in SoCal, I think one in Resume, two in SoCal, and one in NorCal, and this of course
being the first.
Yeah, it's going to be an invite-only contest.
Yes, I believe top three from each competition will be invited to the big power station for
a thousand bucks in prizes or more.
Then we do have a twist.
At March Madness, ladies and gentlemen, top six will be qualifying, so if you want a good
chance of qualifying...
I think I better get on the bus then.
Is this for PA or something?
Or freestyle?
Freestyle.
And PA.
Oh, you've got to enter PA, Dave.
You might qualify for the power station.
You could walk away with fabulous casting prizes.
Oh, boy.
I don't know if a fourth makes giving away.
If you don't enter the 2DX tournament, I'm going to kick you.
But I'm not good at 2DX.
Brad and DJ Syndrome are good.
DJ Syndrome can't enter.
is helping us run it so are you going to enter fine all right they were asking
me if I was gonna enter I got a chuckle out of that one well there might be
incentive for even the bad people to be entering the people who don't consider
themselves good at 2dx there's even incentive for you guys to enter it's
It's just a surprise.
I look like a fucking retard going,
Ahhh! Ahhh! Buttons! Ahhh!
You know what's funny? It's the way the 2DX machine is at Scandia right now.
Like, you know how the buttons light up and they flash?
On the one player's side, the 2 key and the 6 key are burned out.
So you have the 4 on the bottom and then the middle one.
It looks like a giant middle finger.
Because you have these 4 ones on the bottom and then one that's kind of raised up above the others.
So, it's kind of cool.
and little does everybody know, but all the right side players had a hand in that.
Right side pride!
whatever whatever
whatever
Am I the only one that plays left side in here? I think so. Shit! Shit!
I'm outnumbered!
I'm not the cheese, I'm the princess. Alright, anyway.
I'm also a model and an actress! I'm also a model and an actress, so fuck you two!
Black Lab says, and he's making a pretty big claim here, Black Lab is going to enter Perfect
Attack and beat Tigger. He doesn't say he's going to win, he just sees he's going to beat
Tigger.
We need this on film.
Puppy's making a call.
And sadly enough, about 90% of the whole world is kind of, you know, hoping that would happen
too.
No offense, Tigger. Good guy. Just god damn it, lose for once.
You know, I still got giddy when you beat me. I still have a smile.
I tried to be humble about that because I know it was a luck. It was just total luck. One great, it was luck.
You know what? I only lost the Tigger by like 32 greats.
I was close.
Good job!
It was like, that's like, you know, fingers, toes, fingers, and a couple toes.
I mean, we were playing Can't Stop Falling in Love, Speed Mix, and he got like 9 and I got like 40. It was close.
But he had it by a little bit next time.
You know, just for the fun of it, I think that even I would enter this if I wasn't running
half of it, you know?
I would enter this condo, actually, I know somebody that's going to be entering and I'm
helping this person train, so, you know, I'm pretty close to, so we'll see what happens.
But this person will be entering DDR Idol and it will be fabulous, I guarantee it.
Oh.
So, anyway.
Do we want to do the FUs of the Week?
Yes, I need angst.
We need you to explain the FUs of the Week, because we have some new folks listening.
How much do you have to explain what the fuck you mean?
Just give the brief rundown of the, Jamie I'm going to do it for you, the fuck yous
of the week.
Alright, that made me happy.
Basically this is where we talk about stuff that pisses us off.
The end.
Love, Jamie.
Alright, then on that note, let's get to it.
This is fucked up.
My first fuck you week goes toward people who drive slow in front of me.
As in, like, the grandma from earlier today.
She had around her license tag,
Quilting keeps grandma off the road.
Why was she on the road? And why was she taking off her wig in her car?
She's like, oh, I'm driving 20 miles an hour, I'm going to take off my wig and scratch my head. Oh, let me adjust it.
You know, I have nothing against old people.
Except the way they drive.
But I have things against old people who can't drive.
I think that when you reach, like, maybe 60 or so,
you need to retake your full driving test to make sure that you're capable of operating your vehicle
like the rest of the world
the other thing on the other part of the week is for speed limit
why is it
is it like forty just a suggestion
cause everybody else who goes down el camino or arden
goes fifty to five
or pharaohs in the morning on my way to work and the other thing goes toward the guy who told us our car couldn't heal and shit
i still don't have my title yet
Um, all the way back to Trent.
Um, my other one goes toward, um...
Um...
I forget.
Jeremy for being a butt all weekend.
My cat.
My sweet baby.
Who's been a butthole all weekend.
I mean, she's been a butthole to me, too.
And my other one goes toward, um, our Neo Geo.
I've been trying to apply for a position at my old job as an internally posted, and under
the terms of my displacement, I am eligible to apply for this job until March 17th, because
I'm still considered technically an employee of the company, just not officially. I'm a displaced employee.
Well, Julie, who was kind enough to send in all this stuff for me, gets an email or a call or something from one of the HR people and says,
No, she can't apply for this because she has dysplasia.
Whoopsie, what the hell, that completely contradicts my dysplasia.
So I'm going to call them and say this,
Okay, if I can't apply for this job, then you need to create a petition for me like you did with, I won't say her name,
But they had another employee there who quit.
Two weeks, she actually, the day after she started this new place,
she gave her notice there and came back there.
They created a job for her, which completely goes against HR policy.
So I'm going to bring that up, and if they don't give me a job,
then I'm going to report them to the employment board.
And then after, if I don't get a job by May 17th,
I'm going to report them to OCC and the health board.
Health board for the state of the breakthrough.
Don't fuck with Jamie.
Oh, no.
And you know, and you know this, after working in customer service, it's like, you know,
they give you this example where every one person complains there's eight more people
who's pissed off, and then they're going to tell people, but the only people who ever
get anything done are the ones who do something about it.
So, screw it.
If somebody gives you a hard time anywhere that you've been, bad service, you name it,
you make sure someone knows about it and you get it fixed, because nothing changes until
you make a change.
You're going to do something big enough to cover for those other eight people.
Exactly.
I'm sorry.
And I want to do what I can to make sure those other people get off their asses and take care of the business.
You know? I don't stand for that. If I can help it.
Pre-challenge system.
What?
I got a face. F that face.
I'm done now!
Okay. Let's move on to Loki!
I think this court's long enough.
Um, well first one, first FE I have has a story behind it. Now I read on Yahoo News there's this guy, he's suing the movie industry for all the trailers that they have on, um, before the movie and the commercials.
Because, you know, most of his time is like, say, $4.45 to $6.21. Or, in this case, it would be like $5 million.
Well, F you to that guy because you suck! You can't wait fucking 5 minutes to see the damn movie! I had to wait fucking 15 minutes!
No wait, no wait, no, I agree with that guy. F those commercials.
Hey, hey, hey, I'm not- Shut up, trailers are fine!
Shut up! Okay, I haven't even gotten there yet.
Hey, F you! No, listen, this is my- this is- this is my time, okay.
So F you to that guy because you can't wait fucking five minutes,
and F you to the fucking thingers for putting commercials.
Then trailers! In which case, then you've got UK-
Okay, before Daredevil today, there was two fucking trailers for X-Men 2.
right after each other hello no it's different trailers but it's not the point the whole point
is there's two fucking trailers of the same goddamn movie i didn't forget they just saw a
trailer right before the last one god and f you the super movie industry for continuity issues
hello make your movies make sense when you see a reflection someone's glasses the exact same way
as looking at it it doesn't make sense and they have like a part in daredevil okay where they've
got this chick and uh... mlecra and daredevil fighting for no apparent reason he met her
hi how you doing i don't like being attached so they get in this fight scene and stuff
happens for no reason which fight scene are you talking about when he first met her in
the park that was because like um don't spoil no spoilers it was that they're like hey let's
It was tight, they were like, hey, let's have a fight scene for the flight.
It made no sense! Made no sense!
Okay, so enough with that movie industry thing.
F.E. to Wells Fargo for not sending me a fucking replacement card when mine expired,
and I had to wait. First, I had to wait in line for 30 minutes,
while some stupid person's like, I don't want to wait in line for five minutes.
So, you know, he left, and then he came back and made another scene
saying how he wants to get his money, and they said no, and then he left.
So I had to wait in line for that then to tell me to call an 800 number to get my card.
What the fuck's the bank for if everything I need from the bank is through the 800 number?
Why the hell does the bank exist?
This is why Jamie makes it safe.
So that's just stupid, so I called the number and yeah, they were nice at least on the phone number.
Um, F.U. is stupid old people, just because you're old and stupid.
And uh, and F.U. is the Burger King,
Because no, I don't want to donate a fucking dollar to help children get wheelchairs.
They can rot in hell.
They were born defective and they should die defective.
Oh my god, you're awful!
So, enough of that.
And...
Oh my god!
I wonder if this means in the future when everyone has test tube babies.
You know, I'm sorry my child arrived, you know, with this part wrong.
Can I just have order replacement part?
part
and you know what i don't care about like all the stuff that's going on with the news
how they're talking about saddam
you know disarming, arming, doing whatever in korea
well seriously, does korea want to get blown out of the sky? I mean seriously
there's like, hey we're building nukes now, oh sorry we don't care about you, we're talking about Iraq
well we just fired a missile
see we can do that now
We don't care about you. Well, we're amassing an army. What? You want us to come over and
nuke you? Is that what you want? Are you asking us to do it? I mean, because I'm sure we'd
be just fine at doing that. I mean, seriously, it's like, hello, I'm here. Hello, North Korea!
Hello! I mean, it's so stupid. It's like, you're not even a full country. You're north
part of a continent. Or part of a continent. God.
You're more like the toenail of a continent. Seriously, North Korea. That's like North
Dakota attacking us, I mean, it's stupid! God dammit! The views and opinions expressed
on Orange Lounge Radio do not necessarily reflect those of the entire staff. And there
is a missile silo in North Dakota. Look, he has funny angst. God, I had other things,
oh, oh yes, an F-B to my stupid Cypher V Nation pad, whatever the fucking stupid pads I got!
that's it, because they bend after one fucking game.
These nice pads, you know, fucking bend, like, instantly.
They're supposed to, you know, support 300 pounds.
I think if someone stepped on those 300 pounds, the pad would just, like,
just disintegrate and reject you.
Oh, yeah, and one final F.D. to the movie industry.
I mentioned this before, and I'm gonna say it again probably every week
until this movie comes out, and then after I see that movie,
just because I have to go make fun of it. Listen, this whole continuity thing, the fucking
movie The Core makes no fucking sense. Okay, okay, The Core. Here's The Core, basically
a brief summary. We developed this weapon to cause earthquakes to, you know, attack
people. Then, oh, somehow we stopped The Core from spinning, which causes weird electrical
storms and shit that destroys the world, and we have to jump start The Core. Well, how
How else do you think you'd jump to the core?
Oh well, let's design this vehicle to drill into the middle of the core, and everything's
solved with nuclear weapons, so why not detonate a nuclear bomb and hope that everything's
fine.
And then ride the giant shockwave with the molten lava that's gonna engulf the whole
thing and magically fly out through the surface of the earth and be fine.
While this magic guy who's played by DJ Qualls or whatever his name is, that stupid nerdy
guy from Road Trip, he's gonna hack the planet, cause he's the best hacker ever, he can hack
the planet.
going to hack the information coming out of the planet. Fucking stupid movie! Come on!
Seriously, movies like this get fucking budgets, yet awesome movies like fucking Bubba Hotep.
Bruce Campbell is an awesome Elvis in that movie, but Bubba Hotep can't fucking get picked
up by all these studios. We're getting stupid movies like that, another Chris Rock movie
where he's gonna try to run for president. You know, stupid, out of, you know, fish out
of water movies. I hate him. I hate him, and I wish you'd die. We need more midget, uh,
vampire movies. I have one, yeah. Midget porn. Fuck midget porn. Anyway, vampire midget porn.
Carpool of midgets! Uh, are you guys having a go? Is that why you're up and ready to go?
Did you want to do FUs really fast? I'll let you go first.
Did you want to do some FUs?
Alright, Mel B and Sharkscroll are having a get going pretty soon here, so I thought I'd let them step in and do some FUs of the week if they want.
Well, I'll make this one real short and sweet. Apparently I'm just not as passionate as these other people, but I do have an FUs of the week.
To those people who are totally anti-against this upcoming Pony campaign, I don't know if any of y'all heard of it, but I guess Pony wants to have Jenna Jameson of all people be their spokesperson model.
Now, and like, they're gonna put billboards and everything all around Snokel and all that stuff,
and there's just like this total, yeah, touching against it. I don't know why.
I mean, yeah, porn stars just get normal credibility like everyone else,
they wanna be real actors, they got feelings too.
Hell, I would.
I mean, I can see it right now. After that, sign Ron Jeremy, he can be up on TV.
You know, me and a pony have one thing in common.
Pah!
Whips him right out.
And then, of course, you know, it comes down right to the shoes.
I don't know, personally, I just don't get mad at the world very much, just when people hate porn, you know?
Hopefully I'm not ruining what I should be doing this year, so this will be the last game I can see for a long time, so I've blown off two different games to come see you guys, so...
I can't do it this third time. I have to check.
Okay, good.
Moose are so near-sighted, but they often try to mate with cars.
Wow, I did not know that. Did you know that, Jamie?
God bless C.R.A.M. Go wash C.R.A.M.
and we need to call the C.R.A.M. We are gonna be on C.R.A.M. and we're gonna cover it for
Orange Lawn's radio. I can't wait.
They're gonna put us in a storefront and make us stay up for 24 hours. That's gonna be freakin' entertaining.
I could never do that because that would be like
reliving all of middle school, high school, and college.
That accounts for 10 years of my life.
I'm not going to relive that ever again.
The concept is this. It's a trivia show. They give you all the books, all the information
you need, and you have to stay up for 24 hours straight. You're not allowed to sleep. You're
in a storefront. People can see in. You can see them. I've seen people making faces and
doing entertaining things to the people outside.
You have to read all these books and all this information and remember it, and then they
quiz you on it when you get on the show and make you do entertaining things like stand
on balance beams and stuff, but mind you, you haven't slept in over 24 hours, so it's
pretty fun to watch these people.
Then at the end, if you actually make it and you're the winning team, they have this lovely
woman who will tuck you into a nice warm bed and put a nice black eye cover on you and
Read you facts, and she reads you facts in a voice like this.
Adolf Hitler and Mussolini both had venereal disease.
You are getting so sleepy.
And I'm just like, oh shit, I'd be gone.
And if you win, you have to answer five questions in a row,
right, and you get $10,000.
And I think we'd be fabulous.
Oh, I think Melody and I would take it all.
So we've got to get on there.
I think I would do OK at this, except that I don't want to.
Because, when I was in college, every time an exam would come up, I wouldn't sleep for
four days.
The most I stayed awake was five days in a row.
I worked during part of this.
I stayed up one night running D&D, actually two nights running D&D games while people
were studying.
And I took all of my exams, did not make less than a B on them.
The last day, after all my exams, I was sitting at my friend's house watching them on their
computer next thing I know I'm in my dorm room in bed sounds like a bad
sorority party I loved college anyway you know whenever there's an opportunity
that comes up to make an ass out of myself I'm there so you know melody yeah
money money money
i feel like they'll be asking questions
all right well bye guys thank you for coming
yay we're so happy you guys came
so um... we'll get back to the angst in just a minute here but first some
lovey-dovey hugs all around
hug hug hug awwww
thanks for coming
bye have a safe trip back
big hug from lbe
uh... mandy hug
mel B and sharks girl have left the building
okay so back to the fuck yous then
where's your booze?
you don't get booze you're driving
you can drink the drop sitter at the bottom of here
haha
alright
moving on
All right, I have some FUs of the Week.
Let's see, my first FU of the Week
goes to
Irene,
because Irene was rooting against me today in Mario Party 4
because she was just pissed off that I whooped her ass last night at Mario Party 4.
So of course I won the game again, just to show you not to fuck with me in Mario
Party,
because I rule.
Anyway,
uh... my other day
my other if you the week goes to party girl last night because i'm not willing
to do that for peace
and i guess it's really a i guess that's all my
sadly enough
out you guys almost convinced me to go with you
really
almost
until the beach there is a good one and i thought the whole beat
really
and of quality working on our website will be the last time we go will go get
we'll be loaded i've never been there and uh... on i've been hit on by gay
guys before down and uh... sunday night at uh... the race
you would probably get hit on by less people at this club
with their honestly does not free people
like it
my other thank you
this is not reminded me of what i thought it
earlier today
thank you to everybody who
the word Mardi Gras is an excuse to throw a party because first of all Mardi Gras means
that Tuesday that's the day before Ash Wednesday right right okay Mardi Gras is
the real ones are held in Mobile which is where it started where I'm from Mobile
Alabama New Orleans which is you know basically crap Mardi Gras and then
fraternity and sorority girls to end up on girls gone wild yeah oh I forgot to
You know, actually, Guys Gone Wild was supposedly already out. I've been trying to get the video, but I've had it on Backward for two months, or Guys Going Crazy. I've had it on Backward for like two months now, and apparently the studio that we ordered it from is such a small studio that they won't be able to get it.
I've had it on backorder for like two months now, and I have apparently the studio that we ordered from is such a small studio that they won't take orders because we have so many titles on order.
And so I had another one also, Girls Going X, what was it? It was Girls Going XXX Wild, Extra Wild or something like that.
But the guy's going crazy from what I heard. It's just a bunch of like video of like guys getting head and stuff from like women and stuff, I think.
I want to see guys getting head from other guys.
Jamie don't hold back. Well, you know what? You know what? We can get you some...
I can try. I know that they have some of those Vivid DVDs.
I had one at one point in my possession. I think I ended up throwing it out when I moved.
But, um, we had one, it was like...
They had, like, a bunch of, you know, guy fucking scenes. They had one guy getting fucked by a machine type of thing.
I don't want a guy on Robot Jam.
I want to tell you about the site that I found by accident, Man Machine.
Accident, huh?
No, it's real.
Okay, I was looking at Bill Jenchi, but I found this one.
It was a link to this, and I think this site is down, I thought it was manmachine.com.
But it was these guys, like the first thing you see on this page is this guy attached to a machine
with like this
is that like the flashlight
that
i have my body a mardi gras
last night
i can't
no it was a mardi gras was um... show your dick get to be tonight
I would only show any of my body parts if there was a lot of money involved, and nobody else was there.
Turn off all the lights, give me a million dollars, and flash!
You know, flash in the night. There you go.
I'm glad you brought the show back to Bamani, because we've kind of forgotten our roots there for a minute.
Flash in the night, in the dark where no one can see.
Oh, yeah, yeah, cuz we got to finish the same now cuz it's already been going for about 40 minutes, so
Loving let's uh, let's start with the intern Ryan. What's up?
Shut up, I'm saying an F you
F you oh
no, like what I got is a
F used all the little kids and the one adult who decided it would be a good idea to run across the crosswalk on DDR
And for people who don't know what the crosswalk is, we gave it the name basically because there's the machine and a lot of places have that wood piece between the panels and the machine.
So kids decided to run across there over and over and over again. And we had an adult. Last night I was playing over at Scandia and some little kid got up on there when I was doing doubles and I knocked the kid four feet off the panel.
eke
uh... that's cool
as i said i feel really bad and he's all
no don't worry about it i told him not to go up there
so that guy gets the parenting award of the week
it was really cool
all right
right
this is not miss america stop balancing things on your head
it kind of goes along with your movie thing
one about a story about a story about this movie that i just saw a movie about a guy with those people brat
that is the weirdest idea ever
One more F U and this goes to Scandia, actually this goes to the kids at Scandia.
Alright, if I have to listen to you go WOO WOO every time the fucking whistle song comes out, I'm gonna kill you!
They did that for like four fucking hours.
We were in the top secret meeting room and we heard WOO WOO and Keith is like, oh yeah, they'll play the whistle song.
They did that every game, like twice.
oh my god I wanted to go have my lunch break and these people I came in like
three hours later to take my 20-minute break these people were still in there
doing this shit it was driving me crazy I remember yeah that's about it yeah
like like okay I thought it was really really stupid it's like okay you can do
like maybe twice but then don't do it ever again like a week just don't do it
I agree you know what song though you remember but qua you remember but qua
when everybody used to clap and everybody and would do the chicken noises
and people were like what the fuck are those people smoking I don't know anyway
oh wait I'm sorry look you read them don't make fun of us because no I do not
See, back in the day, it really wasn't me or anything. Here.
I have a couple fuck yous to make.
Wait, I had one more I needed to do, and then we can go to yours. Okay.
Here's my FU. My other FU of the week. This was a good one.
A bunch of us were standing all around just outside of the party room by the 2DX machine.
Myself, Jamie, Irene, Brad, and Keith, the Scandi of Tech.
We were all sitting around outside the party room.
kind of all standing there, and we're talking, da da da da da, you know, we're having a good
time, and then all of a sudden I hear this voice behind me.
Excuse me?
Yeah, this lady just all of a sudden out of nowhere, she's like, excuse me, and we all
turn around, and she's just, she's trying to get by, she didn't try to like tap anyone
on the shoulder, just kind of like, even kind of like go, and trying to get by, she just
went, excuse me!
And so she walked away, and when she was, when she was kind of like out of sight, but
still within hearing distance i went
you're excused
uh... and she turned around and give me the dirtiest look at the world anyway
means that the best thing
are you in your period
i'd like to know it must be the day before
uh...
i have
all right johnnie yes
johnnie johnnie bombay has a couple of fuck you's to make
That are really like legit. These are these are legit. Fuck you. It's not something that I thought you're taking me
He's like legit. Fuck you. I have a fuck you
Okay a couple at Scania
No, yeah, no, not so much at Scania
But there are a few employees there that I need to say fuck you to for I bought a while
I was in LA like a couple days ago and I bought a watch there and I took it I took it
I took it to I took it to my job. I had it in my backpack
I put my backpack down in our break room. I go in there when I get off to get it and my watch is gone.
The only people allowed in the break room are employees.
Now, one of my fucking co-workers took my fucking watch, and I will kill you!
If it's my fucking manager, I don't give a fuck! I will kill you! I don't care if it's Paul!
p0k3smot42o
drive it's like it's so it's so weird how people do not know how to drive a
go-kart all you have to do is gas and break gas and break some we had we had
fuck you to see senior citizens that came and rode go-karts at my job they
were the slowest go-kart riders in the world it was so funny you should have
finished it I know you think you think they would have might have sped up but
knows all it was all slow
that's pretty much it
they've given some f he was really fast as chapters get restless okay
uh...
well i don't have that many just a few dole things that make me have to drive
slow
like speed limits
all people
the fear of cops
fast turns
shitty tires
and stoplights, all that stuff. They're bad.
Because I tried... Yeah.
Okay, that's a lot of people.
Hey, I'm not one of them. I'm not one of them. Okay.
No, um...
And, fuck you to not being able to turn fast enough, because, like, I was trying to go
50 in a residential area,
and the tires started squealing hella bad.
I couldn't go 60.
No, and so, um, that's basically it, and, and F.U. did not being able to see into Jamie's car,
cause there's, the light didn't seem to be working or something.
And so I just search around in the dark for like two minutes to try to find what I was looking for,
and then how to lock the car, cause I couldn't figure it out.
But that's it, okay Rob.
Alright, Chat Room F.U.s, I'm gonna run through these.
Muhymer
I play we will rock you on step mania see nine feet then go to scandia own it and cross a cata off my list
Fuck yeah, fuck you to international toll charges
I cannot talk to my love girl and fuck you for making me accidentally calling DDR. Holic a kid
There's my three. You don't like him. Fuck you
That was four
Fuck you to myself for making like one of the hardest DW eyes ever because I'm an asshole I made
I did a DWI to Hot Limit that is really impossible, so fuck you to myself.
It makes no sense.
And stop making bad remixes, please!
Just because you know how to chop samples and put them next to each other, doesn't mean you know how to remix.
Fuck you to this song because I just started doing the Samba de Amiga stuff to it.
Dude, this song rules and you still need to give me my porn from like a long time ago.
The chat room, okay, chat room actually said, shut up, it's our turn.
Dude, my, dude, no, no, uh, Garret, no, SkylineDC505 needs...
No, he didn't say that, he just, somebody else did, but it's funny.
No, look up farther, look up farther, it says it, uh, he needs...
Moving on, moving on.
Anyway.
DarkTetsuya, hello, DarkTetsuya says fuck the fact that girls don't want to talk to him.
Aww, girls want to talk to you.
Dark Tetsuya
You bitch!
I'm sorry. You know I'm teasing.
I like dark Tetsuya.
Uh, fuck the initial D machine at CCL for being broken again.
What?
You are so mean. Alright.
You know some jokes.
Soutome Ranma says, hey, I have-
You pronounced it right.
What?
Holy shit.
Rob pronounced something right in Japanese.
God, my eyes are slanting as we speak, okay.
Loki in the back's going, Rob, you're getting shorter.
I only have one F-you, and it's to everyone that lies about their DDR
accomplishments. Pisses me off.
Everyone who lies about their DDR accomplishments.
You mean like Triple-A and We Will Rock You? I'm just kidding, I'm kidding, I'm kidding.
uh...
sorry about the whole more typing thing i'm sleepless all i have a second fuck
you it's all these secret spy camera pop-ups
that had a nearly a m
but not nearly naked women
as in they're not close
nor naked but painfully in the middle
go to jail is if you want to see food
if you would be good things like this on the site that's not even a porn site
just go to jaylist.com and look at the DVD section.
Just go to Persian Kitty for Christ's sake.
All those hidden camera sites, OK, the hidden camera things
are for security only.
So I never knew that I had naked models or close to naked models
on my lawn, like hours of the day that I don't realize.
But if I had a hidden camera, I would.
I'm done.
I actually do have one more fuck you, and that is to jaylist.com.
I'm looking for a copy of Battle Royal on jaylist.com.
Instead, I have to look through so many pictures of boobs and twat,
Okay. If I want to see boobs and twat, I'll actually go looking for porn. For real porn.
Alright. Uh, here's, okay, here's another one. Let's see if I get this right.
Ninja Usagi Koi. Did I get that right?
Close. Ninja Usagi Koi.
Oh. Says, I want to send an F.U. to whoever broke the fan in our arcade. A big F.U. to our arcade manager for raising the price and not fixing the machine so it breaks for two weeks.
When it does get fixed, have to dish out two dollars and die after the first round from the sheer ease.
That is way too freakin' much for DDR.
You must be playing at the Metreon or something.
Yeah, at either the Metreon or at a convention or something.
Okay, uh...
Snugdismoid says,
Fuck anyone that sees the magical invisible crosswalk of space between the DDR paths of the machine. I failed an Oni.
Matchhead got fucked up and Zero accidentally ran into a kid just because people have a fascination with fucking us up.
I don't care if I look stupid or if I suck, I just don't want to step on a kid. Or do I?
That really sucked, too, because he was doing really good on the Oni.
Then some stupid little girl walked in front of the screen. She didn't run, she took her sweet time and stood there like a friggin' moron.
What you guys doing?
We're going to have to take to the tactics that we used to have at RBGL, where people would stand on either side of the machine.
That's actually what we started doing in the last half. Matchhead was there, and he was there, and I was there, and we were just standing on both sides of the machine.
I think we should get, like, caution tape or something, and put it right there, and have the only way you can get in between the bars, because that would save a lot of trouble.
I will give another Scandia shirt to somebody, and I'll just give it to everybody, and we can just stand on each side while they're wearing a Scandia shirt.
With your arms folded, looking intimidating.
Yeah, exactly.
I didn't expect this to fix the machine. I don't remember how to...
Hi, guys!
Hi!
DAS Square says,
F you damn Cali bastards who get all the awesome Bhimani stuff,
while we Easterners take it in the butt as far as Bhimani goes.
I'm jealous of you lucky sons of bitches.
Then move out here like I did.
Hey, I gave up my life and got on a plane.
Of course it was before there was Bhimani out here.
But the East Coast has hurricanes and snow.
And planes are going to skyscrapers.
Paris
lower gas prices though
snow
lots of snow
at least we don't have to pay like twenty bucks just to get to the arcade
but also keep in mind that food is taxed there
alright moving on
cancer off look you're off the hook tonight
okay
black lab says fuck the horrible dining hall food
but the boring city of davis davis davis
i was a danish republic of davis
and fuck cheaters in online games
and fuck boredom
that was the purpose of online games
yep but he's also part of staff so he's allowed
remember he's a jay b justin circuit says f you to airplanes not being the
speed of light so i can get my customized cd quicker
Fuck Sky for playing the not full version of Irresistible Mint.
Fuck you too, I'll do what I want, bitch.
FU to my mom for making me clean my room that's still messy.
FU for making the FUs only three.
And then he says play a song.
The song I'm sending now is an excellent cover of I'm Like a Bird.
I don't know, we might have to try that.
Alright, we'll try that. We'll try that. We'll play that next break.
OK, Vidpawa says, F you to dumb workers who can't properly put up a restaurant sign and have only 3 fourths of the letters light up while practically the rest of the entire mall has a perfectly lit up sign.
Jay Kinetic, our favorite.
Jay Kinetic says, fuck you to Stone Cold Steve Austin for coming back to the WWE. I can't watch Raw or is it SmackDown, the more suited show for Stone Cold?
He got tired of beating his wife and now he has to beat on wrestlers.
Hold on. For coming back, slapping your wife in anger is never okay.
Fuck you to every scrub at Southland Mall tonight who couldn't play any song besides Orion 7-8.
Dang, that's like a year ago. With Orion 7-8 getting played all the time.
Fuck you to the guy who made pop-up porn. I don't give a shit about your sister getting ass raped violently by a horse while you shit on her face.
If I wanted prawn, I'd go to persiankitty.com.
That's what I recommended earlier.
Jkinetic also says, fuck you to bitch-ass roommates who don't do their dishes, I work 40 hours a week and I still have a way to work out, wash dishes, and bullshit on the internet. Fuck you to world discounters for some of the most ghetto, fake, crass, and bullshit stuff for high prices.
An FU to HappyHackers.com for taking down their back door sections, so now I can't get free porn from them.
And on that note, I think we finally exhausted the FUs of the week.
I have a request.
Oh, Jesus.
No, no request for a song.
Oh, what?
And this is important.
Later on, later this week, we have lost one of our most beloved childhood entertainers.
Mr. Rogers died this week, so it was very sad.
Do we have the Mr. Rogers theme? I think we should play it during the break.
Let's see. Let's see if we have it. Let me look.
No, I do not have the Mr. Rogers theme, but if somebody in the chat room has the Mr. Rogers theme
and wants to send it to me, that would be fabulous, and we'll play it later in the show.
Okay. Okay, well, I'll sing it. Okay, here we go. Johnny will lead.
okay I think I remember this I don't know the whole thing I know the first
part okay let's just repeat the same thing over and over again. Ready?
It's a beautiful day in the neighborhood. A beautiful day in the neighborhood.
Hahahaha
Won't you be my name? Won't you be my...
Won't you be my neighbor? Come on now!
You were already fucking it up.
It's a beautiful day for a neighborhood.
The second part is a beautiful day for a neighborhood, would you be mine?
Yeah, it's not a beautiful day for a neighborhood.
And then could you be mine?
All right, chat room, send it to us.
Would you be mine?
First of all, I have perfect pitch, and hearing this many people off key is giving me a headache again.
If no one brings it, then I'll just bring it next time.
Okay, all of you are now voluntary, so shut up.
Before I beat you like voluntary.
Okay
One last comment one last comment before we go to break and as the chat room is saying we're disgracing the memory of a living
Let's see
Tell me Rama says hey look. It's me. I just wanted to comment that Battle Royale is the most traumatizing movie
I've ever seen I recommend it wholeheartedly it made me cry
I don't know how they based a movie on kids killing each other, but they did it, but you should buy it anyways
Battle royal is actually and I found out more about this is basically was sent as a statement to Japanese children
Because actually school violence has gotten to be at a pretty big high
In Japan, so they made this to show the extreme side of violence in school
Yeah, just like series 7 said Fe to the reality shows and after series 7 came out
So did tons and tons and tons and tons and tons and tons of reality shows.
So it didn't work. And they're making a second battle royale.
Number two, coming up soon.
I have the first one, and it was awesome.
Especially the guy that goes around and kills everybody because he's awesome and he gets killed in the end.
Jay Kinetic says we fucked up the Mr. Rogers song so bad it's as bad as George
Bush not knowing the words to Jingle Bells.
Strong Matt forgives the lyrics to his favorite songs.
Okay, we're gonna go to a break. We're gonna play that song. JB says should be dedicated.
JB says we should play and JB says should be dedicated to me. This is Sheldon with I'm Like a Bird, the dance remix.
That loud popping noise was brought to you by Propel.
Ow!
Alright, we'll be back.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Your people, that's for sure
They'll never, ever fade
You're lovely, but it's not for sure
All I need for you to know is your faith in me
It gives me disease
Even after all these years
And it pays me so much to tell
That you don't know me that way
I'm gonna say goodbye Just every time you try
To tell me me that you love me Oh, oh, it's every single day
I know I'm gonna have to eventually give you, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Don't my love be a chariot Don't my love be a shrew, yeah
Hey, I'm just sayin', fell with me for a rule
I'm not the brother, I only run away I don't know when my story will end
They call me but slowly, but slowly're away
I don't know where my story it away
I don't know where my hope is
They call me but slowly, but slowly're away
I don't know where my story at away
I don't know where my hope is
They call me but slowly, but slowly're away
I don't know where my story at away
I don't know how
All right everybody, now thanks to Akuma GM, we have the real thing, so since you guys
fucked it up so bad, myself included, sorry, here's your chance to study, so there will
be a quiz later, so now in memorandum of a living saint, here you go, a moment of silence
Please.
It's a beautiful day in this neighborhood.
A beautiful day for a neighbor, would you be mine?
Could you be mine?
It's a neighborly day in this beauty, would a neighborly day for a beauty?
Would you be mine?
Could you be mine?
I have always wanted to have a neighbor, just like you.
I've always wanted to live in the neighborhood with you so let's make the most of this beautiful day
since we're together we might as well say
could you be mine, could you be mine, won't you be my neighbor
Can't you please, won't you please, please won't you be, my neighbor, my television neighbor.
I'm glad we're together again.
One day when I got hungry, I told them who to help
I had to be Chef Uncle Ghandi, who let's think of who to help
Uncle Ghandi, he is rich, he is the freshest kind of man
And I know that he will help me, as much as he can
The freshest kind of man is what I want to be
But there's all of us who want to ride with me
I don't know why it's okay that I'm always by
But every speed in kazoo-ta is a fight
Kazoo-ta, I am a sexy-cyber
Kazoo-ta, I play my little sexy
Kazoo-ta, sexy sexy sexy
And I won't stop
When the texture comes flying
I love to fly the klaxy
I like it very much
Even though I have relations
I always panic, but
I can't buy me off my hands
I can't buy me a copy
I am the sexy clown of Mayen
Cali cali gutta guta guta yo yo
Cali cali gutta Cali cali gutta Cali cali gutta guta guta
I am a taxi driver's man I am a taxi driver's man
I am a taxi driver's man
Easier to dance to than that freaking catch-up song, Orange Lounge Radio
Hi, we're back. I have food in my mouth.
I'm eating these combos.
Everybody left.
I haven't had combos in a long time.
And I swear to God, this is some of the most addicting shit in the world.
You know what's more addicting than those to me?
Actually, when I was in middle school, do you know what the snack was?
What?
The Everlasting Gobstopper.
No, but we used to take them out to see what color they changed.
That was the coolest.
And you know what, I love all of you from Starman.net because I want Mother64 to come
out.
I was just about to say, we have all these new people in the chat room tonight, I was
trying to figure out where the hell they were all from.
And then I looked and somebody mentioned a site that they were all from, Starman.net.
And then it's like, oh my god, it's an Earthbound site.
I love Earthbound.
Like seriously, I almost love Earthbound more than I do DDR.
Earthbound was the shit.
You know what?
By the way, for people who actually have emulators, I've heard this, because I know that the guy
who did Robotech Crystal Dreams has as much as a game that they had programmed out in
ROM format for these emulators.
I have been hearing that there was a prototype ROM for Mother 64, and I've been looking for
it.
So if any of you have it, please feel free to send it to me.
They have a little section here on EB64, let me click, I'm clicking here, that they were
We're going to plan a sequel and there's little cute little screenshots.
Why the hell didn't this come out?
F Nintendo.
Why aren't we getting one of these on GameCube?
See, you know what frustrated me is every time I started Earthbound, someone would interrupt
me when I was playing my game and I've never gotten to get further than the first town.
You know what?
No, I never got further than like, Foresight I think was like the furthest I got.
I hope I didn't fuck that name up or I'm going to really get shooed out now that all the
fanboys are in there but you know that's I think the furthest I ever got and I
never did get to be that but really that's cool now that's that was the shit
when Ness was ended up being in Smash Brothers because I own with Ness and
Smash Brothers all you have to do is sit there and you just PK fire the shit out
of everybody which reminds me they're having a sale on Super Smash Brothers
right now for like 29 bucks at fries I'm so excited this oh guess what they sent
us the biggest joke in the universe for free what a request for ps2 see that's a
great thing about like my man managing GameStop because we get free crap games
for free like we got we got BMX triple X for free and then they sent us ever
I want to borrow a PMX Triple X from YouTube.
Can I borrow a PMX Triple X?
I'll buy it.
it's cool actually no unless you've been going playing the demo at GameStop
but no it's actually I thought that I was gonna I see I was still feeling you
know a little bit weird about that game just because link looks like a dork but
when you see the game in action it's so freaking cool and like you're in the
dungeon and the you know to cross like the lava you throw bottles of water at
the lava, and it cools it. And you can ride them up jets of lava, it's so cool.
I was telling you about Dark Cloud earlier, that was another thing I was cool about, is
all the dungeons are randomly generated throughout the game.
Of course, right now I'm still trying to go back and finish Final Fantasy X, because I
have this habit with any Final Fantasy game that I rush all the way through it just because
I play really smart when I play. Now I'm at the first Unileska battle, and well, you know,
Auron is at 4,000 hit points, Tidus is at 2,100. And you know what? That's way too little.
I'm supposed to be like, what, 6,000 hit points by now.
No, no, I never got that far in 10. As long as you have haste, Dega, you're all
good to go. Uh-uh, not yet. I only have haste. I'm slow
right now. Big news in the video game community this
this week, and Jamie, I think you're the only one that's played it. Maybe anybody else who's
played it wants to chime in. Xenosaga?
I saw Xenosaga last year at March Madness, come to think of it, when I was staying at
Tyzone. I saw the incredibly long cinematic intro to Xenosaga, and I was absolutely uninterested
in it. I thought it was pretty, but I'd never played Xenogears, so Xenosaga means nothing
to me.
Xenogears rocked.
Xenosaga's nothing like Xenogears, though.
Another big news is uh Konami changed their logo and they lost their stupid little red
yellow flag.
It was cool like the little walkie guy was cool.
It was like at the beginning of Dracula X2 also known in the US and none of us who ever
had the game in the US knows about this for Castlevania Symphony of the Night for the
Japanese one the Japanese Konami logo the two little squiggly lines walk across the
The screamer goes doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo
That was also the salmon in BeatMania II also.
Yeah.
That's where I saw it.
I thought it was a cool thing.
And actually a little Beymani reference to this.
The song, what was it?
Make a Jam?
Mm-hmm.
The effects in that song are taken from the little walking Konami logo thing.
That's cool.
Yeah.
Like, Konami's new logo is about as exciting as Namco's logo.
Okay, Namco all by itself is cool because of Pac-Man.
I know, but the logo is so boring.
Um, Konami's new logo is about as exciting as watching cheese ferment.
It's about as exciting as the, uh, Jaguar.
It's about as exciting as this radio program.
Virtual Boy! Okay, Virtual Boy is more exciting than the new Konami logo.
Because, at least, because, because, okay,
The Virtual Boy gives me a headache. The New Konami logo makes me want to throw up.
In other news, Poppin' Music 9 came out and it's cool. Poppin' Music Best Hits also is out with brand new V-Rare CD number 4, which is also cool.
The absolute guitar version is supposed to be on new popin' music and also there's some new Desero songs. Desero being the person that the die can tie.
I did get the long version of that rock version of absolute so we'll play that next break.
Oh, yeah. Okay, dead air, dead air, dead air, dead air, dead air, dead air, dead air, dead air, dead air, dead air.
Can somebody download the Desro songs and, like, set me up with them? Because all I have is Die Can Guy and I want to hear more stuff by them. But I can't download thirty megabytes on a 56K.
Let me know where and I'll do it.
Yeah.
Yeah. They've been putting them on B Mani style. There's one up right now for here I think it is or whatever. They're my favorite now for some stupid reason. I'm their fanboy now.
I want more Deval. As in more dancer. We had crumpling noises. What the hell was that?
I keep moving the fucking cord over goddamn food that's in the middle here because it's about to tip over, and so I just move the food instead, you know.
Being proactive.
NES for president.
You poor deprived child.
dude whatever happened to that guy
whatever happened to the guy that used to be in the Nintendo
show that guy
the Nintendo show the guy at the zapper
Captain N. Captain N? Whatever happened to him? I downloaded
the episode of Captain N where he went to the Zelda universe
and it had Link and Zelda but they were like much taller
and but it was the same voices that was cool
but the episode sucks because I cannot go back and watch Captain N
Now that I know so much more about the background stories of these characters, because Simon Belmont, okay, they had him as being this pretentious asshole, when he was really supposed to be all honorable. I'm a vampire hunter, and I'm a Belmont, and damn, I'm cool.
Fuck that, dude. You know what's going to be awesome? Is that fucking movie.
Mega High, by the way.
Van Helsing, the movie. It's going to be awesome.
Ooh.
Like, wasn't, the Captain N, didn't they play that during that horrible show where they, like, they'd have the two people compete in video game contests?
No, Captain N was its own show.
Oh, because I remember they had a show where they would do some of that.
And Captain N was even okay for a while, but they jumped the shark when they introduced Game Boy.
Oh my God.
As a person.
No, it was a Game Boy, and they would ride the Game Boy like a flying carpet.
And Mega Man would always talk Mega High, and Kid Icarus was stupid.
That was pretty bad.
They'd have Pit there, and he'd be like, hi, I'm Kid Icarus, but I'm not Pit.
john fields when it's blood captain in dot net
did i'm gonna go to that site
okay i think there is to do the cage match now
that's game you know i don't think i remember that from the eighties
kid video
freaking kid video was the best
you know what i haven't understood one topic
that like discussed as you a baby
the whole night
jay kinetic actually says here he says
He married Kid Video. That's what happened to Captain Eddie. He married Kid Video. They live in the cast store now and run a small book store.
Kid Video was the name of the band.
Maybe he married the whole band. I don't know.
See, I remember the intro to that song. Yeah, I agree. Let's get to the cage, man.
And they would play, you know, horrible 80's videos afterwards.
do not play track 1 or 2, do not play track 2. It will blow out your speakers. One of
the tracks will show up as the game. You want to know what's really cool is if you put in
the Japanese version of the Dracula X2 and then put in Castlevania of the Night. He actually
says exactly the same thing, just one's in English and the other. They did a perfect
There is no track 14.
Is it the last track?
It's the last track.
So there's a track 13.
Whatever.
Okay.
We'll try that.
It shows up as track 14 on mine.
If it ain't it, then I'll just get bitch slapped and we'll see.
That's right.
Track 13 plus a data track.
So track 14.
Alright.
Okay.
We got that settled now.
Good.
Then let's get it on.
The cage match, everybody.
Hooray.
Rob, did I get to play live at the K-Trap song?
I have a really good one.
No, I'm too lazy to get there.
But I've been to this one before. Where's your house?
Tell people on, tell people.
The Chat Room has some weird taste sometimes, but no, this is actually a pretty good song.
This is a good one to win.
But man, against, come on, Legend of Trance?
I thought for sure that would win.
And then we had the Love of the Angel, I thought the Dedication would have votes built into
it, but apparently the Chat Room had other ideas in mind because this is the winner.
This is Wild Side with Heaven is a Place on Earth, and this is the first song you can
vote for in tonight's cage match, the reigning champion.
Here's a clip.
All right, that's the first song you can vote for is Wild Side with Heaven is a Place on
Earth.
way the cage match works by the way for those of you who are kind of new to our
chat room in the show we're gonna play three songs first off we play a clip of
last week's winner then we'll play two full-length songs two new songs that are
chosen by the hosts and you guys vote on your favorite and the winner goes into
rotation on Orange Lounge Radio's music show that plays all week long when we're
not here with all your favorite DDR 2DX dance medium music and the cage match
winner so that being said you can't submit your votes till the end of the
third song though so don't send him yet because we've got two more to go
including Loki's Choice. Loki, what'd you pick for us tonight? Tonight we have one
of the, well, one of my most favorite Grant songs. This is Sasha with his very
I think pretty famous expander. All right and let me know if this is the wrong one
on X-Tickles. We're kind of trying to pull this from CD. This might be the wrong
track. Here we go. This is Sasha with Expander, Loki's pick.
Sasha
Alright, that was Sasha with Expander. That was
Loki's pick for tonight's cage match. Let's go around the room and get our thoughts on it. Jamie?
Repetitive, but nice. I give seven and a half.
Seven and a half. Johnny?
you're eating are all come back to you johnnie
i give it
any reason why
i wasn't really listening and i don't know that are good
but i'll let you judgment
i say and i agree with him he was a little bit repetitive i give it a seven
I'll go around the majority and pick the average. I'm going to say 7.
Alright.
Yeah, it was.
Okay, so that's two down, one more to go.
This is the last pick for tonight's cage match. This is a song I download.
Actually, Billy, the guy that was here earlier, Billy the big homo who told us the Mardi Gras story,
suggested I download this song, and it ain't too bad, and I could totally see it in DDR.
So I thought you guys might enjoy it.
Excuse me.
Is this? No, I should put Kylie Minogue in though, huh?
You know what? Fuck that. Fuck this pic.
I've changed my mind. I have done a last minute change my mind pic.
I want Kylie in the cage match.
I know something I want to hear.
So, my pick for tonight's cage match.
God, I hope I can find it. Hold on, I gotta...
No, no, no. It's a different one. It's really fucked up.
But I'm kind of going really random.
Kylie, I need you dirty.
Okay, this is my pick.
I downloaded something for Billy and I forgot to bring it.
I got the lingerie commercial to download.
I downloaded it for Billy and I didn't give it to him.
You know, okay, I'm being told that I don't get it, that that track is one of the
mainstays of trans and all that. It's been around for eight years.
So what? It's still repetitive, that's my opinion. Eight years is old.
Eight years is old.
Okay, I changed my mind. This is my pick instead, because I want to get really random.
The other one was too mainstream. This is Kylie Minogue
with a song that Robbie Williams helped her co-write and it's really messed up
and the video's cool and it looks like Xanadu, it really does, that's what Billie told me
This is called Your Disco Needs You, and this is my pick for tonight's cage match, enjoy.
Your disco, your disco, your disco, disco, disco, disco, disco
Desperate, be seeking someone, willing to travel
You're lost in conversation, at your best last revel
Happiness will never last
So just come, kick your ass
So let's dance to all of this
War is over for a bit
Your whole world should be moving to your heart
You're a lonely heart
Your disco, your disco needs you
Your disco, your disco, your disco needs you
Disco, disco, disco, disco, disco, disco
We're sold on vanity, but that's so easy
Take your body to the floor
Your disco needs you
From soul holes to sing of war
From the mainland to the shore
So let's get to all of these
More is all the fire up here
You're a flame to the rhythm through your heart
You're a lonely heart
Your disco, your disco, your disco needs you
So let's dance through all of this
For it's over for a bit
You should be moving through your heart You're a lonely heart
Your disco needs you
Your disco, your disco, your disco needs you
Your disco, your disco, your disco needs
All right, Hil 1978 N Sensei with your disco needs you, going around the room starting
with jimmy's
i'm going to care for a happy baby
that's something to talk a little
it
uh...
all you know is that there is a really good
all yeah
highlight
highlight robin
robbie williams is different
whatever
okay
they are looking for anything
and you know
but that would be
yeah i'd like to think it is a good
both
dot
that's all
it's active badly as people sucking on that bottle
and i was pretty bad
uh... not as hard as camera camera camera
uh...
that uh...
if you don't like so that's that
yeah but i give it to you right
i give it a night to write it
all you don't know the music
moving on yeah well that's all i'm hearing and yeah
can just check on that i love the 80s thing on vh1
that was so
the last thing i remember her in was that stupid movie where she got high high
high page match kylie disco
i lost interest in that song in like the first ten seconds
if i could give it negative i would but i'll just say like one
we were holding a whole conversation here in that song
we started off talking about like
the dreamcast stuff
yeah we were talking about dreamcast and zibriven
that's how bad that song was i give it a one
uh... whatever whatever
i'm gonna retract
a ten
I'm gonna retract mine and give it a half a point.
I give it a 30 then! Compensate!
Alright, alright.
You know what?
I'm gonna give you the wafer.
Okay.
That song, you guys, just, you don't understand quirky music.
You guys just don't understand quirky music. That's what it is.
I understand it!
Rob?
Olé, olé, olé!
I understand quirky music, and that wasn't quirky, that was vomiting.
I give it a 10, because Kylie Minogue owns all of you.
Alright, so let's review. Here's what you can vote for tonight.
You can vote for last week's winner, Wild Side, Heaven is a Place on Earth.
Or you can vote for Sasha with expander
Or you can vote for Kylie Minogue with your disco needs you
All right send your votes in now for the orange lounge
cage match send those votes over private message to sky and
And we shall tally those votes up and have them for you in a few more minutes.
So, alright, we got a good chunk of time left in the show.
What are you talking about here?
Okay, alright.
Yo, yo, I go to McDonald's.
I should check the email box to see if we have any new messages here.
We have dead air here.
The cheat is grounded.
We had the light switch installed so you could turn the lights on and off.
Not so you could throw light switch waves.
We actually did have this big Homestar Runner fest over the weekend while Mel and Melody
were at my house.
Yeah, I sat down on that site for like 45 minutes, just going over the stuff.
My favorite one was-
I'm freaking Carmen Miranda!
My favorite one was to the guy with the long name, to the song, and he said, for how long
it took me to say your name, I could have painted a picture, and he goes out in the
backyard and starts painting a picture, and he's all, this looks good, like put it in
the art gallery or painting for some guy's dad.
I don't know that a lot of people haven't got this particular section of homestarrunner.com
the marzipan's answering machine. Yeah I did.
But I haven't talked to a lot of people who have. I went, like, there's a third thing I did.
This call is...
This call is not
your boyfriend.
That was the coolest thing ever. I actually sent an email. You have been diagnosed
with serious problems. I sent Strong Bad an email. Leave your stereo on the front porch.
Yeah, that's what he had to cut back later or something.
Yeah, I sent one to Strong- I sent an email to Strong Bad. It was one that's saying if you were-
There's something RPG about you, what would your character be?
That'd just be interesting to see what he says to that one. You know what, though? That actually brings up a point.
If you were suddenly list to the worlds of Dungeons and Dragons, what would your character class be?
My character would be like...
Some retard-
I would be some, like, retarded wizard, like, orc from He-Man.
No, would you be, like, a wild mage then?
Yeah.
Wild mages are cool.
What about you? What would your character class be?
I was an evil jester last time I played.
An evil jester?
An evil jester who had playing cards that turned people into stuff, like jackasses.
That's cool.
Yeah, if you were suddenly list to the worlds of Dungeons and Dragons, what would your character class be?
You know what? I never played it, so...
Lesbian.
lesbian is not a character class
although i played a lesbian ninja once
the one time i played D&D
i was a lesbian
i want to play a lesbian ninja
oh wait wait i'm sorry i was a beautiful lesbian
isn't D&D like that game where you just kind of make up shit and be like hey what's up
we all switched to it and never got into D&D either
i was probably D&D
cool
Like yeah, I'm Tigger. I can play any song just describe what your person would do
my person
He wouldn't do much like do they have like magicians or whatever. There's wizards clerics
Wait major wizard. This is good. This is good. Loki's got a good idea here or there was zero that had the idea intern
I don't know. I guess back in there
They were kind of thinking is we should do this live on Eris to segment four
So we're desperate were coming up for new segments because you know, we can only there's only
after some time we're gonna have done every listless topic we can possibly do
so thinking of starting a D&D DDR game and we can play live on air DDR D&D you
know what actually actually no I'll tell you what let me sit down with freaking
white white wolf rules and I can make up the Pokemon style you know like in the
Just bring in Mario Party and listen to us play that live on air. That would be great.
Should have heard me earlier today. I choked Irene.
She was being mean to me.
We need to seriously get enough bandwidth to do a video feed because then what you could do is you could do a picture of what's on the TV as a video feed and hear us talking over it.
I used to sit and play D&D with my friends and I would always wear my black cloak over
my head.
So you'd see this like, see me huddled over with a black cloak over me and all of a sudden
this hand would creep out, throwing dice and then go back and write something down.
That would be fun to have a Super Smash Brothers tournament and have people watch us go on
about that forever.
I would win all of it.
Two characters.
adult link
i would be necessary
come you know you know if you have to do with the back
that's how i guess
i have another kid i'm actually really good with a bunch of characters on that
one of the other good one
who is my best one from the and sixty four one was kirby
kirby will never die
you know we should do is have the home under contest
if you can get the first
Home Run Derby on Rival Schools.
You know, I can't play that game. I care if we get damn big.
Okay. We actually, you know what, on another show, play DDR Live on Netcam. It's actually
funny. The show that kind of
preceded this, I guess some would consider Orange Lounge a spin-off of
understudationlive.org. Which still plays Saturday nights. Which still does play on Saturday nights,
6.30 to 9.30, Pacific Standard Time, over to understudationlive.org.
We actually did do a DDR show, which was kind of
where this all came from, kind of, Orange Lounge actually kind of was birthed by that
show. I was a guest more times than anybody. And we did play DDR Live on air and we had
the cam and everything, it was pretty crazy. Who was around for that? I don't know if anybody
is listening to Orange Lounge was around for that show, who knows. Ask, oh, we have...
That was Orange Lounge in the fetal stage. Black Lab, save your question, we're gonna
do Ask Orange Lounge when we come back from the break, cause we have some new people listening
You want some more points? Let's take a quick break because I want to get the cage match
finished up so I'm going to give people a chance to send in the last votes. We're just
going to do a one song break because this is a five minute song but JB's been begging
and begging me to play this so fine. This is the sign with words, the dance mix, so
I don't know what it's like, we'll hear it live on air. If it sucks, blame JB. Oh yeah
we've got to get to the absolute. Well we'll do absolute before the end of the show I promise.
the absolute guitar mix. We'll do that. So this is the last chance to get in your votes
for the cage match. If you haven't voted, you have 60 more seconds and then voting is
closed or you die. So, we will be back. Enjoy.
Wait
C'mon
Don't come easy to me
How can I find a way to make you see?
I love you, birds don't come easy
Birds
Don't come easy to me
This is your only way for me to say
I love you, birds don't come easy
Why don't you start music playing?
My love keeps up all my wrestling
But my world was calling on one another
I will hold on to you
And I hope that you believe
Cause world
Wait, feel this on me, babe
Let your complete day
Wait, wait
Calling out, calling out, calling out, calling out
Where are you?
I wanna, I wanna, I wanna, I wanna, I wanna
I wanna, I wanna, I wanna
Wave
Don't come easy to me
How can I find a way
To make you see
You are my own
That I'm here to meet
And you know and I
When I say I love you, honey
Please believe I really do cry
Call it nice, call it nice Call it nice, call it nice
Alright, some kind of mixed reaction from the chat room on that one, the sign with words
sent to us by JB by request.
Okay, this is going to be the part now, we're tallying up your votes for the cage match,
However, when we come back, we're going to do Ask Orange Lounge, or ask Johnny, ask the
intern, zero, or ask Dave.
You are delinquent.
Bombay, you can ask Bombay.
And Bombay, what kind of questions would you want to answer, like things about freestyle,
things about...
Yeah, freestyle.
Because I'm trying to get in more to freestyle.
Okay.
I'm trying to compete more and get more experience and all that.
And then you guys know Dave and the intern by now, this is Johnny for sure.
Yo, yo, I go to McDonald's, not Delta Co.
Yo, yo.
Burkayfo!
Anyway, okay, so send us your questions over private message to sky and we'll get to those or if you're too lazy to be
In the chat room, just send them over email orange lounge radio all one word at yahoo.com
and you can also
Always send us your comments or whatever else so something bimani related for you guys that I promised earlier. Here you go
So we'll be back after this with Ask Orange Lounge.
Please listen to Orange Lounge Radio, because real radio makes Captain Jack cry.
Let's go, Racco! Pick up the set, go! Let's go, Racco! Yeah!
a damn good fake and I want more by that faker.
Seriously, I seriously doubt that that's a fake because, I mean, hold on, it's absolute
and guitar, I mean, it doesn't sound like shit, and unlike M, you know, which obviously
could have been made by anybody, but this is a lot better. I don't see how this is a
fake.
Okay, well, there you have it. Like it or not, fake or not?
It could be quite possible that it's one of those special editions like the.59.
Very true, like the 0.59 live mix and stuff?
Well not the live one, but the really goth-y sounding one.
I have a DWI I'm making to like the second remix or whatever of 0.59.
It's like half done, and it actually has a backbeat to it instead of like how 0.59 originally was.
Well there was, the original one had a beat to it.
Well it's, I can't explain it, it seems more, it's a lot more fulfilling.
You hear it better the more that you play it in 2DS.
The thing about that remix that you're doing, it's like the piano, it makes sense at first but then it just goes into a different song after that.
So do you guys want to know who won the cage match?
Alright.
The cage match winner was, and I was surprised because Kylie did manage to get at least one
vote.
So not everybody sucks, alright.
But the winner was Sasha by quite a little bit of a landslide, ladies and gentlemen.
So Sasha takes it and is the winner of the cage match.
to think of something new next week. That means what I was talking about in here is
going to get played next week.
Alright. Well, you know, at least Loki can't bring in one of his remixes and win it for
sure because, you know, it's Loki.
No, never mind. Never mind. I will bring it next week. I'll bring something really good
next week.
Yeah, I'm going to fuck it up next week, too, and bring something really psycho. What? We'll
talk later we'll come up with a plan you know I'm thinking I'm thinking I'll get
that chick from American Idol that'll be my that'll be my cage might fix the
children of the world I found my child what about you know my you know remixes
my era CDs oh the chick from Sacramento and American Idol is a bitch anyway not
that I know or anything she's a bitch on the show all right okay we're gonna do
ask orange lounge now you guys ready okay ask orange lounge here we go for
those that don't know ask orange lounge this is your opportunity to ask us
anything you've ever wanted to ask if you're sick that we don't happen we
don't talk about the money enough on this show ask us but money related
questions would be happy to answer you want to know something about Loki sex
life and ask it maybe he'll answer it or maybe he'll come up maybe he'll come up
with a vicious lie. Who knows? Ask it and we'll answer it.
Alright, here we go. Black Lab has the first question because I made him hold it over until
this segment because this was kind of the inspiration. Oh, we should do Ask Gordon last
night. It's a question for Jamie. Black Lab would like to know, whatever happened to the
Orange Lounge quiz? We were going to do a live journal quiz. You know how live journal
quizzes all the...
Okay, this is what happened. Jamie got a job, okay? End of story. I don't know, if you want
to help me make one, then we'll get on that, you know, Quizilla.com and put one together.
Maybe that'll be a project for this week. We'll see. But that's a good idea. I like
the idea of doing an horizontal quiz. I have to play P.S.O. Tuesday night P.S.O.
That's true, Tuesday night P.S.O. night. But you know, which reminds me, if you guys want
to, you know what, if you guys want to play P.S.O. with Jamie and I, we're looking for
a few good players. So come to the chat room, come to the chat room Tuesday night, and we'll
let you know what block and zone we're playing in. This is PSO GameCube.
First of all, remember that Jamie played her game all at once, and she actually needs to
get past level one. Well, I think what we're going to do, this
is the other stipulation. Tuesday night, if you come, new character. We're all going to
start with new characters for Tuesday night. Mine, even though I made her when I first
got the game, I've only played it once, so I'll leave her as she is.
Okay, that's fine. But it's got to be low level, so we all start at the same and progress
Nothing higher than level one.
If you're into PSO GameCube, come on the chat room Tuesday night, we'll let you know where we're at.
Okay, what do you guys talk about back here?
I've never played PSO, I don't know what that is.
Sucks to be you.
Fantasy Star Online.
Don't play it though.
Get a GameCube and a broadband adapter.
I'll show it to you sometime.
Alright.
I think I might play my game tonight.
Here we go.
How about our simulation mean no one over level three?
Okay, that's fine.
Cause I'm gonna play tonight.
Alright, moving on.
jaykinetic wants to know
can i kill the intern on a show
can i kill you
although you know if i would like to get back to you
who's everyone's favorite superhero
juman
uh... they've says juman uh...
I'm gonna have to go with Dave and say Jewman.
Jewman for Bombay 2.
Loki.
Superhero.
I'm not fucking seeing Jewman, ass!
Dude, one of my friends is like...
If you're gonna say Jewman, I'm gonna say Nazi boy.
It's my arch-rival!
Loki! Jesus!
We are gonna have to tape his mouth shut.
What is he's like Nazi boy the protector of the duty Loki is worse than t-shirt held calm tonight
Yeah, it's all about fuck. Oh my man. I'll hide all right blunt man much better man much better blunt man
Thank you
Okay, I gotta apologize for my killing you comment, but um I would say orgasm. Oh orgasm. Oh
Excellent you want me to go you want to go all right Jamie?
The handyman and the tiny avenger.
Nora and my cradle power and stuff totally sounds like Paul is that like
super solid all do you have spinning action I don't know but wait Paul is
dead I know he's gone orange lounge ask the world your action figure needs
kosher sent power I love you too I'm changing I'm changing my vote from Jew
man I'm changing it to lightning day like all right anyone that knows me this
This should be a dub. My favorite superhero is Catwoman, of course.
She's a hero to some. She's a hero to me.
She's a hero to me and she's going to have her own movie.
Are the interns...
More questions from Jaheem. More questions from Jaheem.
Are the interns related to Godden?
No. He's a guy in SoCal.
Mel told me I should emcee a tournament with him, but I'm not related to him.
He seemed cool. I didn't really talk to him at all, because I was kind of introverted and clicky at Cyberbeat, unfortunately, because I'm a bitch.
I'm not really an intern, by the way. I'm just kind of sitting in, I guess. I guess.
You're a guest.
Monica Lewinsky was an intern.
That means we make him go do stuff.
Alright, next question. Is Orange Lounge for the children?
I don't know, but I think that...
The children of the liking to listen to crazy monkey sex?
Nope. JB will agree with me. You know, we actually are the founders of the Cup of Child
Foundation. You know, the new flavors of ramen, Cup of Child.
I'll answer that question.
There's skanky RVGL flavor. There's, you know, spicy scandia flavor. Then there's, you know,
There's CCL ass flavor.
No, no, remember that? That's drug and alcohol flavor.
And then crud under the machine, uh, crusty flavor.
No, that's good.
Um, Orange Lounge...
Laser Force is non-existent flavor.
Orange Lounge is not for the children, but they listen to it anyway.
We think...
It's like porn.
We think that children are...
I can relate anything to porn.
I love how everyone thinks I'm a racist, porn addicted, crazy psychopath when I'm totally opposite in person.
Next question is for Loki.
And frosted with sugar and fortified with vitamins.
Next question is for Loki. Here we go.
Does Loki have a sex life?
Damn right I do!
Oh man, dude, seriously, you think I sound horny on air? Imagine my girlfriend, she's about ten times as horny as I am, so...
It's just like, holy crap.
It's a good... It's damn good.
For your birthday, we'll get you vitamins.
Seriously, I do need vitamins because I don't eat well at all. I eat like one meal a day, and it's normally junk food, and I'm tired, and...
Oh, do you need vitamins for Halloween?
Okay, but nah, that's alright.
SkylineDC505, Dave, do I still get prawn for my birthday?
Well, that depends on if I get my prawn from Loki.
I got two mics.
Anyways, I can get you both prawns, so that's no problem.
Where's my man from?
I'm trying! He's not coming!
The men aren't coming in the prawn?
No, I haven't.
but i'm interested in reading it
i bet it's porn
no it's not
it's c o s f v b come on
second question is for dave
you wanna ask it?
i'm leaning back i aint reading it from here
second question is for dave
did you ever beat that ancient boy game
no i never actually beat it i never played it after that one day
i just played it and i got to one bone left with two cracks in it
A bone and some crack. I think it was a bone.
I think that's what... No, no, you were throwing a bone. First you take crack, then you take bone.
Insert bone into crack.
Repeat as often as necessary
until you obtain desired results.
The end. Next question, and it's Bomani related, and it's an excellent question.
Satome Ranma wants to know, I ask Orange Lounge this, why is it so hard to find
Poppin' Music MP3s? Seriously? Not a house, pyramid, melobunk, or tromobunk anywhere,
dammit. Poppin' Music MP3 is hard to find.
First of all, Poppin' Music is really cool, but it does have a limited fan base, honestly.
You want Poppin' Music MP3s? Good for my style. Serious. Tons of MP3s for Poppin' Music stuff
there. Or, if you can't find them, look for Feeling Pomu, that's their sim, and I'm sure
if you find sim files for that, you'll probably find the MP3s as well.
You know how much of a pain in the ass it is to find sim files for that? I have it. I found all but two. Anywhere.
That's why you use the Japanese sim files.
I was going to actually suggest, if you're looking for pop and music mp3s, go download sim files because people make sim files to all these other Bomani game mp3s and pop and music happens to be made into files a lot.
Also, there's WinMX.
Very good.
and eBay they have three of the pop music soundtracks on eBay right now for
about five bucks a piece okay so tell me Rama also wants to know as a follow-up
question have you guys seen the original Japanese the ring scary shit Ringu I've
been wanting to because I want to see it before I see the u.s. one guess what it's
actually coming at the same time in the u.s. one they're releasing on dud ring
you yes so it's coming out the same time in the u.s. it's going to be subtitled
I believe.
I won.
Actually, Billy.
We were just talking about this earlier today.
Billy's seen it and he says it's very good.
I guess it's a three-part series there.
There's three of them.
Actually, I have a question for our chat room.
What's that?
I don't remember hardly anything about this movie, but I've been trying to find it.
I've been putting in all these clues trying to find this one movie.
I wonder if anyone's ever heard of it or knows what this is.
It had to have come out in the early 80s or late 70s.
It was this movie about these people who move into this house that's possessed by three
Japanese spirits and these people back then each killed themselves and then the
movie the people end up recreating the fight that led to the three there who
killed themselves and they kill themselves the same way this was this
is an old movie and I've been trying to find the name of this movie no it's not
Brady Bitch movie interesting and it's like these you know and it's like these
super cracker people too
and i don't think the beach house it's a it's a house the stairs leading up is by
the water
no
but for anyone who happens to know the name of this movie or anything please
let me know cuz i've been trying to find this for like
years
all right we still got a ton of questions to go through so let's move
right along here
alright jimmy john fields wants to know
favorite non-standard bdr mix i e euro disney
uh...
all i still have a bomb a
i have to say
jimmy i want to go play in orange county and it's like
this have ever played
your makes you
stuff but i'll probably say hostel because it has a lot of fun
or or
say your answer to all
all right he's a lot of time
i'd i'd say i'll pump it up
uh...
that
it's korean bd r same damn thing
expression
all right next question
snub disloyal says
first off what's the easiest only
i've gotten halfway into a few only seen even got to stow it on road attack once
but i haven't passed anything
easiest only
since i've barely ever played them
i would have to say i'm not the standard
way are you talking about extreme or
on max to ensure that you pass some of them like
soul six and shit
i'm so so thick is easy dot now he standard we had no use standard and uh...
that first one
yet nearly thirty but if you're talking about extreme which i think that you are
yet dance mania and then you know if you think
does not dance anyone have written the police in the phone
but it did
dot pop force
an easy one but that's not stop here
uh... your second question will have to answer offline because uh... we ban that
topic from discussion on the show so will answer your question offline
for you though. So, we'll get to that later. Alright, Japan Man wants to know, Dave, how
long is your shaft? That was a few months ago. Snip the tip, baby. No, I don't, I'm
I'm not going to answer that, like...
Yeah, more than you can handle.
Never.
It's above average, and that's all I'm saying.
Ah, above average.
It is!
Are you...
No, don't do that, please.
Are you comparable with Run Jeremy?
Comparable with Run Jeremy.
I have never seen it.
He's nine and three quarters.
What?
Anyway, moving on, Daf Square wants to know, when is Sky's voice the game coming out?
We have that one that Stressa made, and I don't know if Angel helped them with that
or not.
No, I think it was all Stressa, because I know Stressa did the lyrics, and he made this
sim file of a parody that I did during a fuck-off show to Bumblebee.
And it's really embarrassing.
I can't believe...
I played it on the show last week.
The damn thing is actually being pretty widely distributed right now, which is pretty scary
to me.
I played it on the show last week.
Yeah, I know.
And you played it on the show.
I've been doing it before.
We need to do it the wrong show and just sing.
Sing to the music.
Like, you know, sing lyrics to Afro Nova.
Ehh, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah.
I will promise you guys, there will be another MP3.
There will be another MP3 of me singing on the site.
Sometimes, on the Orange Launch Radio sometime in the next week.
You know what everyone missed, though?
This was a few weeks ago.
She's been on the show a couple of times, Iguana Girl.
We were at, um, at Scandia doing our own version of Kuchimuda V.
Black Lab wants to know, is there a boba in your immediate future?
not tonight but maybe sometime this week just because I'm really personally I'm
really tired I was up until 5 a.m. last night and he's fault is that mine but
that means I ain't going to Boba tonight but maybe sometime this week because I
do I do kind of crave it I haven't had Boba at all this week or why I mean I
haven't had Boba in a while so I think we need to go we need to take a Loki
then Loki we need to go apartment hunting and then look for Boba all right
Dark Tetsuya wants to know, how do I let someone know I'm interested, if you know what I mean?
Excellent question. It's a pretty serious one.
You go up to them and go, you know what, I'm interested in you. Would you like to date? That's what you say.
To me, I mean, I'm a shy person too, honestly, and it's so hard for me to just go up to somebody and ask that. That's really bold.
Okay, I'm the worst at doing that type of shit ever. I like go up be like you're hot
What are you okay? What you okay? Here's what you really have to do you have to keep cereal in your pocket to feed them
Right Ryan back me up
Yeah as the resident woman okay first of all I
I'll be right back. I got to get this
as a resident woman
let Jamie speak let Jamie speak I think it is absolute bullshit to drop hints
that you like somebody you know because I mean it's like guys start acting
really weird when they're interested in you and you think that they have a
disease and so they start creeping you out you don't want to be around them
okay if you like somebody fucking tell them get them by themselves and go you
You know what? Do you want to hang out? Or you don't even have to say it right away.
Say, you know what? Would you like to go to a movie or go anywhere?
Now that's a little more along the lines of what I was saying.
I wouldn't say you just come out and say, I like you.
But like, you know, find out, talk to the person. People are going to talk to you.
They're always talking to the person.
And you talk and you find out what you have in common.
And then you go out and do that common thing.
But see, me and maybe I'm different among women because I don't like bullshit.
I'm like, if you want to go out with me, ask me if you want to go out with me.
Jamie, can I go out with you?
Of course.
I mean, I've gone out and said, hey, I think you're cool, I want to go out with you.
No, see, I'm too honest.
I'm like, you're hot, your face could use a little work, but you're still pretty hot,
so you want to go out, and then you'll be like, fuck you!
I think Jay Kinetic sums it up very nicely here.
Dude, try to get her to laugh at a joke, talk about a common topic, and then casually invite
her out to have lunch sometime.
Two simple things.
First of all, don't tell, don't have any of your friends do it for you.
Don't write a letter.
Just walk up and call them.
Remember it.
Talk to them.
Don't have your friends there when you ask.
If we've learned anything from Olimore, it's basically to go, I have money.
No, but actually, seriously, what you want to do is you want to definitely go up and
tell them because if you waste time by just like beating around the bush and stuff, you're
not only going to waste time, make yourself more stressed out and, and yeah, that might
happen in the meantime, but it's better to like, you know, instead of waiting forever
and then telling her and she's saying no to find out, you know, beforehand, you know,
say, Hey, I like you, hi, I'm not interested or hi, I'm interested, you know, whatever
she says, whatever she says back. And never casually make out with somebody you're not
interested in. What are you talking about, man? That's fun. No, because then they might
expect that you are interested in. Here it is. I have the greatest pickup line. Believe
it or not, I have the greatest pickup line for women. No, no, this is it. It's like,
no. You go up, you say, hey, I like peanut butter. Wanna fuck? Actually, the best pickup
The best pickup line that I've heard of is, um, what was it, is like, uh, do you like jogging?
And, well, the thing is, is, is it's gotten you in the conversation. It's not some awkward,
you know, some pickup line or whatever, and you should probably respond to that, you know,
then you're like, hi, my name is, you know. Did you realize, like, photography?
You like casual sex?
Kind of take pictures of you accidentally.
It's like, no.
Okay, bye.
It's like, hey, do you like casual sex?
No.
Hey, do you like casual sex?
Yeah.
Hi, my name is Dave.
I love casual sex.
This is Bimani Loveline.
I think that we should get together and have some some time because, you know, common interests.
We both like casual sex.
And yeah, go from there.
And by the way, never ever try to hit on somebody when they're working in an arcade.
This one really scary guy came, when I was working at Labs Castle, this one really scary guy came up to me and like, tried to pick me up.
I was like, oh, I'll come see you after work. I'm like, um, I have a boyfriend. Oh, well, that's okay. After you hang out with me, you won't want to be around him.
I'm like, sir, just being around you right now makes me very appreciative of my boyfriend.
Let me ask Neil, because he just walked in the room. Neil, what's the best way to pick up chicks?
I said, hi, I like peanut butter, what a fuck. What do you think?
Nice shoes.
the best way to pick up a girl is with your arms and then with your knees.
because girls fucking love shoes. I can't explain it.
Would you like some pizza and then go fuck? No? How about we can skip the pizza?
The best way to pick up a girl is with your arms and then with your knees.
All right, all right. No, no. I think we got the serious answer out.
The best way I ever hooked up with a guy one time, and actually this is an incredibly nerdy
way but I thought it was pretty funny,
We played D&D, and our characters hooked up, and then we started dating.
Because we started dropping the hints through our characters, and then we went out.
You flirted virtually, that's so interesting. Alright, alright.
Better living through roleplay.
Here we go. Moving on, moving on, because we've got to wrap up the show pretty soon here.
Okay, that wasn't a question, that was a yay, but we appreciate those two.
Okay. EOSFBB wants to know, which female targeted cartoons that most would be ashamed to admit they watched are your favorites?
For instance, oh, okay. EOSFBB says, is the movie Jamie talking about called House translation, which is from 1977 put out by Toho, I think.
I don't know. See, I don't remember the name of it, but I knew that it was late 70s, early 80s.
And it had three people who ended up killing themselves in the end of the movie.
Look at that. Look on Internet Movie Database. Try that. House.
Save that. Actually, email that to me.
her the unico
yes of course you know how we don't need it
you know i think it's cool
well anyway
is that guys can only get away with really watching guys cartoons but
we can watch what the hell we want well what would be your favorite then jamie
it's kind of a moot point for cheeky stuff? yeah cheeky girly things
no not hello kitty
well i'm trying to think of stuff that's not anime because there is shoujo and shounen
anime
I think as far as anime is considered, I would have to go with Pre-Tier, The Legend of Snow White, which none of you have probably ever seen.
Loki?
As far as guy stuff goes, it'd freakin' be Berserk.
I don't watch freakin' girly cartoons, so there!
Yeah, me neither!
I don't know what Unico is.
I have the answer. When I was a kid, when I was younger, when I was in junior high,
it was all about the Beverly Hills teens.
Yes! Oh my god!
Jem and the Holograms.
Yes!
I didn't really watch Jem, but Beverly Hills teens, every damn day.
I have a friend who has every episode of Jem on tape.
Are they good college?
Or, or, and, or, and this is the gimme.
This is the one I'm sure everybody thought we would say.
She-ra. Hello.
Okay, She-ra.
But that was with He-Man.
Yes, Shiro was kind of a zenith.
Anybody can answer this, though. Anybody that has freestyled in the past, Francis.
Yes.
How do you face your fear against the crowd?
How do I? Okay.
Excellent question.
Okay, wait, Ryan.
Ryan.
Okay.
All right, well, how I face my fear is, I basically, when you don't think, like, when you're up there on the stage, it's like the same as PA.
When you PA, you think of PA, right?
The same thing with freestyling. When you're freestyling, you think about having fun and, you know, just having a good time. You try not to think about, oh, what are they going to think? You just have a good time. Just be yourself, basically.
Here's the simple thing I realized about freestyling altogether when it comes to the crowds is, first of all, just imagine or pretend that you're practicing alone. There's nobody around you, and when you turn around, just don't see anybody there.
Because that way, you're not going to feel nervous at all because it's just like you're practicing and having a good time on your own.
No, what I do is, first of all, if you never want to feel nervous again, just first go
up there naked, and then everyone will laugh and bust out, and then every other tournament
you'll just be like, man, this won't be as bad as the last time when I was naked.
Honestly though, that one and only freestyle that we did, I forgot that there was a crowd
going together.
No, and mainly, most of the time, the more outrageous stuff that you do that you would
think would be embarrassing people love it like like like Ryan in his and all
the women would stand up cheering and so would Rob anyway a grass skirt and a
tiki mask holding a spear doing Afro Nova that was my suggestion my
suggestion for the freestyle because Jamie and I have done one freestyle
there's pretty infamous by the way you can find that video still on DDR
forgetting yes I've yet to watch that and I won't ever I might have it
Anyway, my advice, get up there and don't give a flying fuck what anyone in that crowd feels about you.
Just don't care what anyone thinks.
Go up there for yourself to have fun, to just do it and forget about everybody else,
because their opinion doesn't mean shit.
And one thing too, is when you freestyle, don't really give a fuck about the arrows.
Hit a few, but mostly all people are watching is you dancing, they're not watching the arrows.
All you have to do is pass. You're not in the game. All you have to do is pass.
Good. You may or may not remember at Shaft when Tran actually failed his routine the first time, crowd demanded he go again, because well I mean there was also the other circumstance going on where he meant to do fourth mix and the fourth mix was broken so we had to do the sim, but he ended up taking second place, not too shabby.
That was nice.
That was my bad for not turning auto fail off. Dope.
It's all good, we all make mistakes.
Ask Orange Lounge
I work there and on weekends they have a policy, Friday after 5 o'clock is considered weekend, I'm not allowed to be there on weekends.
So Friday after 5 o'clock I'm not allowed to be there. Saturday and Sunday I'm also not allowed to be there. At all. There, the end.
Pretty much. Just goes along with the freestyle thing. It's one last thing. Just have fun with it. Don't even care how you look. And for everyone else playing DDR, just go and have fun with it and don't even bother what other people think of you.
I'd like to add something to that. Also, just like, you know, look like you're having fun. If you're up there concentrating too hard, it's not going to look good.
Absolutely. Bruce Leroy, many say he won Cyberbee on his expressions, period.
Well, and also when I was making up the grading sheets for Shaft, that was the big thing I
had in their face, you know, how well they react with the audience.
It counted for a quarter of their score.
Okay.
Oh.
And, hey, DVR Colic's back. Have comments?
Well, I missed most of the show, but if you guys were talking about freestyling, my input
would be to just have fun because it seems like no matter what happens, the crowd likes
freestyling, even if you suck. They don't want to see you just stomp. They want to see
you do something. Find the closest person to the stage and go try hump their leg. Winner!
Do anything and don't have any fear because there's nothing to fear. That's it. One last
If little kids run across the crosswalk, feel free to kick a little leg out there and let them just do cartwheel right off the side of the thing after you kick them.
I'm wondering if anyone in here remembers Big Cans?
Yeah.
Rob's half-finished edit to kick the can started off really hard and then there was like nothing else.
I remember when the fourth mix was there at Goughland.
Yeah, it was Rick and Paul just ran off and started running all over Goughland.
No.
They were like doing bar hops and slapping hands across it.
No, they hopped off and started running around the arcade too.
Yeah.
Oh, wait, wait.
Me and Pat also healing, uh, I wear orange beanie.
We have, uh, we also have a freestyle to, uh, Sugaru.
No, Master Ride Japan.
I'm sorry.
Where, where we just run around the arcade and just like, that's about it.
Would you, uh, would you love to meet Maniac Little?
Really?
There's like, what is it, 32 measures of no steps?
All right.
Anyway, your final thoughts?
My final thoughts is we didn't cover it.
The step chart site went down, just so everyone knows,
because that's kind of major news and stuff.
So the step chart site went down.
There's a new one coming back up, so look for that.
My site, I'm working on it.
There's actually going to be a complete,
I'm going to redo all the graphics again, actually,
because I don't like the way they are right now.
and I'm going to make it simpler. And if you're lucky, if you're very, very lucky, I might
upload Second Style through Fourth Style, all the MP3s, all the DWIs I have for that
tomorrow, if you're lucky.
All I got to say is that me and Johnny, like a few weeks ago, we started, like it was at
like 3 o'clock in the morning in my car, and because we were like parked outside someone's
house and anyway and so we were like really late and we were trying to like
rap and shit he's like okay David go and some like yo I went to McDonald and like
we started making all these weird names to like to fast food chains so now we
have we have it's called our ghetto slang for fast food chains yes yeah
We have McDonald's, Burger King, and Delta Cup, which is Del Taco, and Jack in the Box is Jack in the Box.
I still prefer Jack in the Box.
Anyway, that's, that's what we have.
Delta, come out!
Blink, blink, blink.
Alright, my final thought is that choking when you're drinking water live on air really sucks.
Does that just happen to me? Jamie?
My final thought is that scars are cool.
Scars are cool.
They're sexy.
Thank you everybody much for listening. Thank you all the guests for being here tonight.
Lovely as always.
Next week, we'll either be coming to you from the studio of Jamie or we'll be pre-taped. We don't know yet.
We'll think about it.
Most likely studio of Jamie, but we don't know yet.
And maybe I'll do a fuck off on Thursday.
Alright, and the Cyberbeat special was delayed so it's going to be this Friday and Saturday because we got lazy.
Alright, alright dude. Anyway, some of the requests, I have some requests, some things you guys requested us to play.
We'll get to those after the show wraps up and everything, so stay tuned if you want to hear those songs you requested.
Good night everybody, thanks for listening.
Come on for Hogwarts guys, come on for Hogwarts guys
QQ
for Hogwarts Guys
Say. Come on for Hogwarts Guys
Everybody to the limit
Everybody come on for Hogwarts Guys
I say. Come on for Hogwarts Guys
Say. Come on for Hogwarts Guys
Everybody to the limit
Who's that?
At least to the limit
Everybody come on for Hogwarts Guys
Come on for Hogwarts Guys
I see you jockin' me
Tryin' to play like
you know me
I'm like
Come on for Hogwarts Guys
I say
Everybody to the limit. The Cheek is to the limit. Everybody com'on for
Hoag-Wag-Gaz I said, Ooh,ahh, for Hoag-Wag-Gaz, say Ooh,
ah, for Hoag-Wag-Gaz People say, Ooh, ah, for Hoag-Wag-Gaz
They say, Ooh, ah, for Hoag-Wag-Gaz, Ooh, ah, for Hoag-Wag-Gaz
for hover guys. Man for hover guys, you're just making yourself look worse you know.
I mean, everybody's just gonna feel sorry for you. I mean, I do.
Thank you very much for listening, and we'll see you next week.