message for you sir, attention!
do you want to hear the most annoying sound in the world?
you're listening to orange lounge radio, the monty talk and then some
orange lounge may contain adult content, orange lounge may contain many four letter words
orange lounge may contain a scene of nudity
Orange Lounge may contain hot monkey sex.
Just kidding, Orange Lounge will not contain hot monkey sex. In this episode...
Hey, are there any balls down there?
About the biggest berry you ever seen, Diggleberry.
What's your favorite scary movie?
Showgirls. Absolutely frightening. What's yours?
There are no stupid questions, just stupid people.
Don't torture yourself. That's my job.
Now's the time on Shrock, it's going to be dogs!
I'll get you, my pretty, and your little dog, too.
I know Kung Fu.
I'm sorry, but all questions must be submitted in writing.
Why did they have to take the word day?
No! What I expect for punishing positions is gentle.
Hey!
Dark Sakura.
Shut up! Where's my gun? This is my boomstick.
Sky.
Come on, girls, it's time to drop the bomb.
Loki.
I can't, for the life of me, get the hooker to have sex with me.
What kind of warped human being would find that funny?
Orange Lounge Radio
We are live, and this is episode number 37 for March 9th. No, it's not the 9th, it's the 16th of 2003.
Rob's doing the time warp again.
Hello. You're tuned into Mamani Scene's most buzzin' radio station of all things Mamani.
Sounds like a fart.
Heim is Rob Roberts, but you might know me as Sky.
Joining me as always are my awesome co-hosts. In this corner, the happiest bunny on the
farm is Jamie Summers. You know her better as Dark Sakura.
I'm not happy. In that corner, say hello to our Tech Masoloki.
Hello. And with us here also in the studio tonight,
we have? Here!
Nobody! This is amazing! There is nobody else here tonight. It is just the three of us.
This is craziness. Zero's not even here. He was supposed to be here tonight.
Yeah, I guess.
subwoofer and then we won't hear anything but I think they still get the
buzzing even subwoofers off but I don't know so life sucks and you'll just have
to bear with us tonight we'll do what we can but in the meantime we're gonna play
some break songs and what songs are we gonna hear this break these are songs
songs that no one listens to, but you're gonna do now, so enjoy. We'll be back.
are
Hey!
Now let's go, now we're free
Hello, hello, is this thing on testing?
Testing one, two.
I'm looking in the index, but I don't see anything for how to run a radio show.
Hello? I don't understand this. This thing works.
This thing reads like stereo instructions.
Is this on?
What the hell?
Orange Lounge Radio. Broke-down ghetto bimani radio.
WHAT THE F***
I'm a
I'm
we're supposed to be back before that was over positive about that now it is
is that irony or what
that you know broke down ghetto ass radio and then we can't even get our
fuckin' volume to work
We can't get it up! We're impotent!
we actually what's funny is that during the break I was trying to fix the buzzing
problem we've got tonight
and I went behind the computer and kinda unplugged the splitter cuz
Loki said, hey, look at the splitter, maybe something's wrong with that, and lo and behold,
I went and I plugged it back in the wrong hole.
I stuck it in the wrong hole!
Okay, Rob, do you have hole priorities here?
Yeah, I have hole problems.
I think I'm dyslexic!
Anyway, in that break of little-played Bimani songs, pretty controversial in the chat room,
because every time one of them would play something, they'd go, hey, I play that!
We had Changma...
How many people really play Minimillion?
Thank you.
We had Chang Ma, would love this feelin', and then Minna Melon from 4th Style, which
was also the background music in 3rd Style, if I'm not mistaken, blink blink.
Yes, I think so.
And then after that, the sampling masters with tablets, from 5th Style.
And then Usama Kaboto with Presto, which is somewhat debatable, because actually a lot
of people play that song, but what happened is I was actually looking for Five Regrets,
and I couldn't find it.
So then I tried to find, I was gonna put 1989 in, but a lot of people would have beat me
up if I played 1989? And then we played about half of Sanctus before we decided to spare
you all and come back. Which is interesting because Sanctus is in Dance Maniacs. If there
was ever a song that just doesn't make sense in a Bomani game, Sanctus in Dance Maniacs
I don't get every Kubota song could have been in keyboard mania yes presto was
you are listening to Orange House radio and again we apologize for having some
buzzing issues tonight we don't know what's causing it we've dissected
everything going on about the only way I think I'd be a bee is angry for you know
you to facing its song so I don't know what we can do about it we'll just have
zero the orange lounge intern had a little get-together at his house
and we decided to do a little bit drinking because it was mostly older folks who were
there over 21 so we
we decided to bust out a little bit of liquor. I had my one triple shot of
that imported tequila. I had about half a glass of aftershock
not a shot but half a glass. I had half a glass of aftershock. I had whatever it was that Irene
made me do. Irene knew, you know,
what I've been needing for about the past year and Irene made me a cocksucker which is
Irish cream mixed with butterscotch schnapps and again, she didn't make me a shot. It's supposed to be a shot drink
I was made a full glass
Yeah, and I drank just about the whole thing except for a couple sips
So needless to say after half a glass aftershock and that I was pretty fucked up
So, I don't know. I was running around the house yelling things. I don't know what I was doing
And then I fell asleep too after about 45 minutes
And that was it.
It wasn't long at all.
I'm like, Rob's drunk, and I'm like, oh, ready?
Shit, man.
I didn't even finish sitting at the pads yet, and you're already drunk.
Hey, wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
That's not fair, because you guys ran to the store.
They did.
Poor Ice Queen spent a bunch on liquor.
Which reminds me, he's not here, and he's supposed to be.
I need to call him and see where he's at.
What did I do with my phone?
You dropped it over the side of the desk.
Did I?
Oh, I sure did.
Yes, you did.
Let's call Ice Queen and see where he's at.
On the air.
We're not Broke-Ass Ghetto.
Well, we've got nothing else to talk about tonight.
Yeah, we do.
We don't really ever do phone calls on the air because myself...
We have two weeks till tournament.
Do you want to talk about tournament while I call Matt?
There's nothing going on at all.
It's just dead.
It's been like this for like the last three months.
Nothing is happening.
Well, March Madness isn't for two weeks.
Yeah, I mean, we can talk about that next week because nothing's going to happen next
week anyways.
If one were you, Diggy?
Sad. Nothing is happening.
Shit, it went out. My phone sucks in here.
Mine got three bars.
You call Matt then.
No. You can use my phone.
Okay.
Rob's gonna use my phone.
I'm gonna use the phone.
What else is new in your sim this week, Matt?
That we were all playing on last night?
Uh, just more stuff I downloaded.
I've been trying to work on it.
and stuff, but yeah. I've got up through Fifth Mix all ready to go. So, you know, it's ready
for Monday. I'll probably upload this Monday. So, up through Fifth Mix. Pretty much everything
you'd see in Bimani is stellar right now. I'm trying to get Max and Max2 done before
maybe tonight. Have those up and maybe submit everything else. But, yeah, I ran into some
problems with the DDR Extreme files because not just one person's making them, but actually
a whole bunch of different people are making them and they're all out of sync or just awful
and so I have to like, you know, fix those two and that sucks and I don't really want
to and I probably won't, but yeah, there'll be more stuff and you know what, I don't have
like no, I don't have a hidden page this week because I'm lazy and I just didn't get around
to it and you know what, I don't care.
Here's a shot.
and uh...
well shit man i mean
well oh let's go to make let's make a hidden page of one sim file or uh... i
don't know i'll release release like three hundred tomorrow
yeah decisions
so you can have the one or the three hundred one
fine that's all i know what sim file i'm going to upload then let them move and that's it
yay just to be the single sim file
no i don't know i've got more stuff
What else has been going on this week?
Loki and I are planning a move and we decided on the apartment we want to go to, so the
show is going to be moving.
Yes, we have an orgasmic fountain at the new complex.
Multiple orgasms.
Yeah, it's like a multiple orgasm fountain.
It flickers a little bit of water and then all of a sudden it's like gush, gush, gush
and then back to a little bit.
I lost my job.
That sucks.
Like Sierra Pacific Mortgage, there are 11,000 Olson Drive Rancho Cordova, CA, Suite 202.
Go there with a grenade launcher aimed at the office of the shipping department.
Why did you lose your job?
I don't know.
They never told me.
It's a temp assignment.
I think it's because I was being paid more than the other temps because I'm cooler than
they are.
So like, we don't want to pay her.
She costs too much money and she's too damn good.
Megamix?
I've never heard of it.
What the hell are you talking about?
Let's see.
I've never heard of what you're talking about here.
There's a link, I think.
I don't know.
I don't know what the hell they're talking about.
Megamix.
Is this it?
Here we go!
Konami is, in fact, hard at work with a new dancing stage game, and this time it's for
the PS2.
They have licensed new songs for it, and the data is set to a May release in Europe.
There are ten licensed songs in the mix, some of them are as follows.
Ms. Dynamite, It Takes More Elvis, A Little Less Conversation
Kylie Minogue, Love at First Sight The Sugar Babes, Freak Like Me
Christina Milian, When You Look at Me The Cure, Love Cats
That's crazy.
It will also feature twenty original tracks created by the Konami development team.
It will also have the normal features like Arcade Mode, Practice Mode, and Workout Mode.
It will also feature a tutorial mode for beginners.
Once again, I've been saying this before, it really sucks that Euromix stuff gets better
music than our fucking U.S. mixes.
They started putting licensed tracks in our first one, but ever since the get-go for Dancing
Stage they've had licensed tracks that are exclusive to them, and I think that sucks
ass.
But yeah, the one day I'm not on the internet, there's stuff happening, and I hate that.
It's like I'm on the internet all the fucking time. All day long on the fucking internet.
Waiting for something to happen. Nothing ever happens. Then I turn it off, boom! Something happens. I hate that.
Let's see what else. We're just leeching news right now from ddrmaniax.net.
Oh yeah, DDR Big Brother.
Giving a little credit where credit's due. What'd you have? You had a suggestion, Jamie?
Failing lists work. I have their address. That's what I should do.
Never mind. I was thinking of ways of getting revenge against that woman.
Oh, Jamie's plotting revenge on her work.
Former work.
Also, DDR Media X is reporting, and this is kind of neat.
DDR was on Big Brother.
Oh, Dancing Stage.
I'm sorry, Dancing Stage was on Big Brother.
Not Big Brother in the U.S., but Big Brother because Big Brother in the U.S. only airs in the summer.
but it was on Big Brother in Norway.
They had their very own dancing stage machine, and they have this little picture here when
they're all playing on the machine, and one chick in the back says, fuck the machine,
I'm going to play on the Nordic track.
That's what she's doing.
And then there's this bald guy looking on going, what are they doing?
And then there's these two chicks kind of dancing, and it's obvious that they're...
It sucked, and then coming onto message boards today, guess what? It sucked.
Shock? MTV programming sucks? Wow.
Shock of shocks.
Oh my god.
When did that happen?
Who knows? Maybe y'all. And knowing MTV, don't worry. If you didn't see it, they'll re-run it 50 times.
So just, you know, look in your TV guide.
The downfall of MTV began with the banishment of Martha Quinn.
The loss of Kennedy, I concur.
You know what sucks about Road Rules though?
It's old.
It's fucking old.
They do the same thing every year.
Same shit, new location.
There's some fag, there's some bitch, there's some black guy, and they all fight all the
time.
That's what they do.
The show's getting old.
And then there's like the one person who goes, okay.
Yeah.
And then there's the virgin.
You know, the chick that's like, oh, I'm a Mormon and I'm never going to do anything
bad.
And she gets fucked three ways from, you know, yesterday.
I still want to be on the real world.
I want to be on the real world, so I should be on the real world.
See, I wouldn't start fights with anyone, but I'd just be totally strange.
I'd just be the weird guy.
The guy that sits in the corner like, dude, that guy's weird, man.
I don't know what it is, but it's weird.
Like, they come to talk to me, and you just, like, start screaming, you know, weird shit
like that.
Anybody that listens to this show knows that you'd be the crazy racist and homophobe.
I'm not the crazy racist, homo-folk guy.
Fucking A man.
Hello man, I'm going to be living with you.
Shit man.
That's why they have auditions for these shows.
See, if I were on any of these programs, I would be sitting in the back of my Game Boy.
And the Game Boy reading a book.
We should do something though.
We should do our own reality show.
Orange Lounge Reality Radio.
This kind of is reality radio because it's not like we talk about Bimani ever.
No, I mean we should get a video camera and go on a weekend road trip or something and
videotape it and post it on the internet.
This is what we do.
This is the thing is I tried to do that for Cyberbeat and it came out really really bad.
Did you have a video camera?
I don't even think it ever aired.
No, I didn't have a video camera.
See if we can get a video camera and go.
I'm so excited.
So we'll see.
Well, you realize that if we get to go, you know who else is going to be there?
Who?
Dan is going because he's a manager.
Woohoo!
Well, that's cool.
Then you'll get to go.
For all the people who remember my fiance on our lovely radio show here, you get the
Dan experience.
Very cool.
So if that happens, we will do an E3 reality show, but we're still kind of hanging out
to see if it's going to happen or not.
I mean, I don't know.
I don't know, that sounds hopeful but I'm kind of like I don't know, but we might have
an in.
And it's very exciting so I'm moist with anticipation, as should all of you, because the E3 rules.
Why are you messing with my shoes you're like-
So yeah, DDR on Big Brother.
I think you should try out for Big Brother.
I would try out for Big Brother.
I think I'd be awesome on the show.
I'd f***ing win Big Brother.
Big Brother is the one where they have no computers, no news, no TVs or nothing.
just in a house with cameras watching them 24 hours a day, and they just all have to
like co-exist.
I would do nothing but read the whole time.
I'd have withdrawals.
Ahh!
Shaky!
They don't let you bring books.
So...
I'll bring a book somehow.
I'll write a book.
You sneak a book in your bra.
I draw the arrows on the ground.
What are you doing, man?
You know, and what's funny about Big Brother, at least in the U.S. anyway, Big Brother in
the US, the first season was shit. It was absolute shit because it was totally not cast
well at all.
Interviewer2. Did they make them do anything?
Man 2. Yeah, they have to do stupid little challenges every week, but like in the first
season some of their challenges were having to make papier-mâché. It was shit. But then
the second season it started to get a little better. I didn't watch the second season because
the first season was so bad that I wouldn't watch the second season. But I heard that's
what started getting better. And then this last season was really good, last season was
good.
finally got some... you're a bitch! You made Pippi Longstocking out of my shoes! Anyway,
yeah, the last season of Big Brother was pretty good. And I could see, totally see them doing
something like this, where they bring it, then that's what they do, is they just kind
of drop a toy on them, like, and then in the next week, they would probably have to do
like whoever's the best at DDR gets to win, gets to go out for dinner.
Oh man, I would love that. It's like they do the same thing for that show and you're
on the show. Dude, NC, I would... They're all playing in there all, okay, who's the
best of all start busting up like oh my god I just don't even try you know I'd
fake it like for that whole week I'd fake it that I really suck at DDR and
then like the last day of it I just go fucking nuts win the dinner and
everybody would hate me and I'd get voted out suddenly dawned on to me as
you're there you know paying back yeah it's like it just clicked I don't know
oh my god it's not like I don't play this oh oh yeah Jamie's gonna fix my
shoes. I have some more really important Bahmani news, or Bahmani related news. It's not really
directly Bahmani news, but it's about a Bahmani artist. I have some really important Bahmani
news that we need to take care of. And it's about a lady who is in Max 2, and you probably
know this song. She's Ginger Spice, and she did a song called It's Rainin' Men. You all
know that song. She's not a Spice girl, but she used to be. But there was big revelations
about Jerry Halliwell this week.
And this is the way the story goes.
Ex Spice Girl Jerry admits she had a lesbian fling.
So former Spice Girl Jerry Halliwell says she has had a brief encounter with another
woman but denies she's a lesbian.
So she's not joining tattoo or anything.
Remember, try it but don't like it.
The singer who was dated, fellow pop star Robbie Williams, told Thursday's Sun tabloid
that after the fling she quickly realized that she was not gay.
I had a little lesbian thing, she said, adding the encounter with an unnamed woman had been
part of experimenting.
She refused to pinpoint the date, but said it was somewhere between the ages of sixteen
and thirty.
Yeah, it's sometime between now and never.
It was just a drunken moment.
She also says, you wanna go home and have sex with me?
The singer also said she was not in a relationship but present.
I would like to be in a loving relationship, but it has to be with someone who is trustworthy
and kind and sweet, and also my equal, she said.
And a man.
Halliwell or Ginger Spice, as she was known during her time with the band, left the Spice
Girls in 1998 amid reports- Or the only cute Spice Girl that wasn't Butch.
Amid reports of her squabbling.
She looked like a drag queen.
Whatever.
The 30-year-old singer is currently hosting the U.S. television beauty and talent show
All-American Girl, which, by the way, funny enough, All-American Girl was the name of
Margaret Cho's show, a much, much different program, also on ABC.
Can you believe they blatantly just took that name, especially after Margaret Cho's movie
about the hell she went through on that show?
Well, you know what's funny is they're having a...
There's a microphone in my face.
Howard Stern is actually, you know that show Are You Hot?
Yes.
the producers of that show because it was his idea.
If you go to SmokingGun.com, which is my favorite website on the entire internet, you can read
the court documents of Howard Stern filing the lawsuit with ABC because apparently he
used to do this bit on his show and it's been a long time since I've listened to Howard
Stern in it.
I never even saw that.
I used to watch the E-Show and I used to listen to it in the morning, but I never saw this
segment.
But I guess it's been on for a while.
Was the Examiners or the Examiners, what was it called, the, I don't know, but they would
I think it was called the same thing, actually No, it wasn't called Are You Hot, it had something
else Still, I even thought that they were ripping
that off of that website, Are You Hot or Not, I mean, it's exactly
They suit them too, because they have that, I've never watched the show because I don't
watch crap, but like, they have this big sign from a picture I saw that says hot or not,
and then the contestant is standing under it and I guess it lights up if they're hot
or not, and I guess, uh, uh, what's his name, that one guy, oh god, what's his fucking name,
that guy, he was on chips or something I think? Eric Estrada? I think he's a judge. I don't
know. Well they have, uh, Lorenzo Lamas as a judge. Oh, him, nevermind, I'm getting Eric
Estrada mixed up with Lorenzo Lamas. I don't know how or why, but I do. Yeah, I don't like
women with fake breasts. Uh, wait, wait, hold on, let's flashback for a second here. Uh,
Weren't you just, weren't you dating, or say, married to a Playboy model, uh, you know,
just to fill you in?
Guess what?
They weren't real.
Not real.
Fake breasts.
Breasts aren't supposed to be like solid plastic.
I mean, when she hits the wall, they're supposed to kind of like give a little bit, not like
crush through them.
So-
It's a surgical flotation device.
It's a bath toy.
In case of Wanderlanding, the bosom may be used as a flotation device.
So this begs the topic that we need to do a new segment here on OrangeLawnsRadio, called
DDR Hot or Not.
And basically the way this would work is you're going to send a picture, but it has to be
a picture of you playing DDR.
Not just a generic picture, it has to be a picture of you playing DDR, or any bimani
I guess would work.
And no, I don't know.
Are we not accepting any nude photos of people playing DDR?
I don't want to see that shit unless you really are hot.
Only if you're really, really hot, and people tell you that on a daily basis.
Then nude photos are okay.
But if you don't get told that every day, don't send it.
So you're just going to send it to orangeloungeradioatyahoo.com, and we'll let you know how you rank, okay?
And Howard Stern can sue us if he wants, but you know, you can't get blood out of a turnip.
So send your photos, graphs of you playing DDR and we'll let you know if you're hot or
not.
And what we'll do, huh?
And remember that all pictures submitted become the property of Orange Lounge Radio.
We say that because we're going to put your pictures on our website.
Because this is radio, obviously, other people are going to need to see these somehow.
So we're going to put your pictures up on the site so that people can access them.
Brilliant, huh?
And Jamie says, it reminds us of an old segment from Undersedation Live, the kind of show
that came before this.
Have anybody ever listened to Undersedation Live?
You need to listen or we'll shoot you.
There was an old segment that also included pictures submitting.
Oh, excellent question.
USFVB asks, what if he whips his cock out at the end of the routine?
Good question.
You want to know what?
What?
No offense to any of our guys listening, but I think that as far as organs go, that the
penis is the weirdest looking thing ever.
Why do you think that?
They just start ugly.
Just because they're just like there?
I don't want someone to whip out their cock on film, I'm sorry.
Well what if somebody whipped out their cock and then in an amazing yaoi fetish film another
guy started sucking it.
Would that be okay?
Okay.
Oh, you hypocrite!
What?
If you want...
Okay, so send those pictures to orangeloungeradio at yahoo.com.
They have to be of you playing DDR.
And no nudes unless you're told that you're hot every single day.
And you have to have proof. Somebody has to send us an affidavit.
I am not retarded. I think that it's the strangest looking...
I didn't say I didn't like cock.
It's just funny looking.
I can just see it now.
You know, that's really weird looking.
Oh yeah, thanks. Whoa, that does it for me.
Oh come on, even Dan agrees with me.
It's like Carrot Top.
He's funny looking, but everybody loves Carrot Top.
No wait, nobody loves Carrot Top.
How about Yahoo Serious?
Yahoo Serious funny looking.
But everybody loves Yahoo Serious.
I like it because he's Australian. He's funny. He plays with the Tasmanian Devils.
It's funny Australian stuff.
Excellent question. What if you tell yourself you're hot every day?
No, it doesn't work. Sorry, dumb fly.
It's just like those people that tell themselves they can sing.
Alright, so that's something we'll look forward to doing either next week.
Probably not until next week because we'll have to upload those photos, but, you know, something you guys should do.
Yeah, if anyone actually sends them. I think we'll get a couple.
I'll post on the forums that we're doing it to. That's always a good way of getting people to participate.
So, moving along. What else do we have to talk about?
I don't know. I'm just not happy today.
You're just not happy today? What's up, Logan?
Ah, there's microphones coming every which way. Well, actually, in two weeks,
We're probably going to see the last, I think, of the DER Extreme Unlocks.
I think. I can't remember our off-hand.
I think there's thirty, well, number-wise, as far as the unlocks go, there's a total of thirty different unlocks.
I mean, even though, like, number thirty is, like, three different songs or three different whatever.
But there's only, like, thirty total, and we're up to twenty-four right now.
So, in two weeks, we're going to have the rest of the songs, supposedly.
So, which ought to make it very interesting because in two weeks from now is March Madness.
Yes, March Madness.
So, I wonder if we're going to see any last minute routines to some of these new songs.
March Madness will be broadcasting live, by the way, on Orange Lawn's radio.
For those of you not in NorCal or SoCal driving up here or whatever,
if you're too far away to come to the tournament in person, you can attend online.
Just visit our website and we'll be doing a live broadcast all day long, both days.
So that does mean in two weeks, the normal live program here on Orange Lounge will be
preempted by that coverage, so we won't be on live.
And chances are we're actually going to finish up over there probably around seven o'clock,
so there won't be a show in two weeks.
But we'll be here next week, of course.
Yeah.
If anyone expects me to do a fuck off afterwards, you can fuck off.
Because I'm going to be dead.
Had a tournament here last night, says Ninjosakekoi.
It was interesting.
Was that the tournament in Albany by chance?
Because I know there was a big one that was supposed to go on the East Coast yesterday
and I haven't heard anything about that.
I'm wondering how it went.
If somebody wants to tell me about how that went.
Certainly.
I'll fill you all in on that.
This particular tournament was in Hickory, North Carolina.
Cool.
You know, if any of you folks out there on the East Coast, other places, mid coast, basically
anywhere outside of California you want to do some tournament coverage you want
to maybe take a tape recorder over and talk to some people there talk to the
winners talk about the tournament put together a little bit like 10 minutes
long little package about the tournament well we'll air it here on the Orange
Lawns radio we put a call out a while back on live journal but nobody sent us
anything, so fuck em!
The last time I actually looked at GameFacts.com was back in April when they had Xbox.com.
XboxFacts.com.
Oh, the April Fools joke? I think right after that, during the summer, they did the top 64 characters of all time.
No, what I don't like is this new show on Tech TV, it's like this Microsoft-only show,
it's like all Microsoft propaganda, stupid Nazis.
What is it about?
I've never seen this.
It's like extra tips for Microsoft products and Microsoft this and Microsoft that, and
it's all about Microsoft and how wonderful Microsoft is and how Microsoft heals the world
and what not and it sucks ass. Remember that parody they put out by the Microshaft corporation
Whimblows? Yeah. They suck. Anyways, I think what we're going to do is go to a quick break
and then we're going to come back and get to the FUs of the week. And it will definitely
be short this week because there's only three of us here in studio. There's lots of you.
But there's lots of you, so you can go ahead and send those FUs over to Sky via private
message in the channel.
Let's see.
Question, we have another Hot or Not question.
I only have a video of me playing Legend of Max.
Is that acceptable?
Sure.
Sure, but please don't email that.
If you could put that on the web somewhere and give us a link and email us the link,
that would be great.
Don't send us...
Or there's programs out there that take screen caps of videos that can cut a frame right
out of it.
You can use that too.
Yeah, so please don't email us video, but email us like a link to the video or take a screencap of it, because we don't want any files over like 200k or something or else our email box will fill out too damn quick!
Alright. What do we want to hear this break? What do you guys think?
Entrance.
Entrance. And we already... No, we didn't do entrance. Entrance is the one you said I should have played that we didn't do.
Okay?
Evan is the metallic 57 gray? I don't even know if I can find that one. I'll see if I can find it.
What style was Entrance on?
I think someone else might have just showed up. We had the door go. Let's see who opens up the door in a little bit.
Tengo no kis, Tengoku.
All right, we'll be back in a little bit. Send us your FUs please
Make me do it any way
I don't know what to do
Kishine ga takigatou gozaimasu
Kissing the heavens, kumono hanenu
Kissing the heavens, no te deii tenemori
Please
Please listen to Orange Lounge Radio, because real radio makes Captain Jack cry.
That's the coolest thing ever.
I haven't seen a Bjork video.
We can fix that after the show.
Oh, great. Thanks.
Human behavior, the one with the bear.
I saw the one where she's jumping around and just being stupid, though.
It's like, she's just bouncing off her couch or something like that.
I don't remember a Bjork video with a couch in it.
I don't know. We'll see.
Like, I know.
Okay, so, also here we have DDRholic. Say hello.
Say hello.
Hello, good evening everybody and always fashionably late, here I am.
It's alright we forgive you because we know it was a lot of partying the night, or last
night there was a little bit of a party.
No, it was so cool, it was great.
How late did the party go till?
Because we left about 3.30.
It probably went till about 4, 4 o'clock.
Yeah.
Okay, cool.
I would have stayed by 4 this morning.
I got cold because his house has no heating at the time.
There is a little story to this.
Oh, okay. The heater was on last night at like 100 degrees, so I went and turned it down and then I wake up this morning and somebody turned it all the way off.
It was comfortable and I turned it down to like 80 and then I wake up and it's just totally off because some stupid moron turned it off.
Probably one of the jerks in the back.
Yeah, because it doesn't help that the heater is in the back of the house and there's none in the front.
And you know when you're at a party, you know when you're at a real party, when like all
these people are showing up that you don't fucking know.
That was happening last night.
All these people were showing up, and what's even weirder, they know you, but you don't
know them.
Oh, that's weird.
I took a nap.
Sorry.
Oh, no problem.
I think most everybody took a nap at some point.
I took like a three hour nap.
I like took over that that love seat and didn't move for a while except like to
wake up every so often and when I woke up I'd be fully awake and then I'd be
certainly tired again. Well like okay it was it was kind of retarded at the end
because all the kids in the back were screaming and being dumb and coming over
and taking the couch so none of the adults had places to sit like Shane
slept on the damn couch after you left so nobody could sit there and then Loki
had his spot and I had my couch and that was it and it was they were still yelling at five
o'clock in the morning those damn kids and then that was funny that call it preceded
the party from that stupid bitch oh yeah hold on okay this is like the best thing which
is actually pretty funny that Loki bitched it up okay Matt and Loki are at my house we're
We're setting up Lucky's Pads for a sim, and this girl calls.
I won't say her name, but she knows who she is because I know she's listening right now.
She calls, and she's just trying to lay these guilt trips on me, and I'm like, I want to
get off the phone right now.
And she's all, no, I don't want to let you.
Then she tells me about how some truck drove by her and threw porn at her or something.
That's a bad thing?
I want someone to throw porn at me.
And so I'm like, okay, and then she's like starting to get mad at me so I just flat-call her a bitch on the phone like four times and they're over there laughing.
Language, now now.
I'm sorry.
Bitch.
Thank you.
Anyways, so they're over there laughing and I'm trying not to laugh and then she's, and I'm like, I just want to go.
So you get annoyed with me.
I said, I want to go because I'm about to have a party and I need to get ready for it.
So you can hang up anytime.
And I said, oh, I can?
And I just hung the phone up.
That sounds worthy of me.
That's interesting because it's like really mean, yet kind of humorous at the same time.
I don't know.
Also here, hiding in the corner, snacking on food, eating a lot, getting really fat.
Eating a lot, getting really fat, of course, well, I have some catching up to do with that.
Say hello to the ice queen, cold as always.
That's right.
Or as I should say, frigid as always.
Well, that too.
Of course, you know, it's odd though because I don't really seem to remember much about last night except getting home at like 5 o'clock in the morning. Go figure that.
He picked up a prostitute on the way home.
I was very interested in driving while I was asleep.
So, we're going to catch you guys. Oh, I'm sorry. Go ahead for your shot.
We're going to catch you guys up on what you missed so far.
There's not a whole lot of Bahmani news this week, so we don't have a lot to talk about,
surprise, surprise.
However, it did come out in the news that Jerry Halliwell, who did It's Raining Men
from Max 2, admitted she had a lesbian fling.
Ooh.
It's Raining Boobs and the ever-important Dancing Sage Megamix coming out for the PS2.
This, The Cure.
Joe, by the way, we have to offer a word to our sponsors.
This episode of Orange Jones Radio is brought to you by Propel, by Pizzeria Pretzel Combos, and the El Sebroso Guata Chip, Guacamole Chips.
They're tortilla chips with guacamole already in them.
They're chips that are the color of boogers.
For those of you... What did you say? Loki made it funny.
It's the guacamole-dilt chip.
For those of you too lazy to dip your chips, that's amazing. Only in America.
We will play Gamelan a couple in a little while.
Alright, let's do the FUs of the Week. You guys ready?
Alright, we got a whole bunch. Chat room sent me a whole bunch.
So, plenty of things to rant about tonight. Let's get it started.
My first recipe of the week is for what I mentioned earlier towards Sierra, Pacific Mortgage, and in particular, Shanda, who is the supervisor. Her name is Shanda Ramsey-Wallace and I don't care, I'm not a professional.
She can go burn in hell.
Because I had been asking for feedback.
How am I doing?
What do you need me to do differently?
What can I do to improve what I'm doing?
She's like, oh, no, you're doing fine.
No, no, no, no, no.
Just like that, by the way.
And then I get a call at 9 a.m. today
saying that I lost my assignment with my job.
And I'm going through 10 pages to see if there's anything new.
And the other thing about this,
I need to go to the doctor really bad, and I've needed to go for practically a year now.
And I was really, you know, counting on being made permanent this week so that I could go to the doctor and get all that crap taken care of.
But no. So, you know, I have to say this, is that what I'm going to do when I finally find out what's wrong is I'm going to send her my medical reports and I'm going to say,
You can pay for half of this. I should probably sue her for, uh, you know, for damages. And, you know, with our current court system, I'd probably win. But, um, I'm not that petty. Um, but no.
I like how you add that in there, but P.S. I'm not that petty.
No, I'm not petty and fake like she is.
But anyway, her office is toward the front on the opposite side where the UC Davis Medical Center is at 11000 Olson Drive in Rancho Cordova.
It's upstairs on the right side of the building, and her office is the window office.
She can go in there and set it on fire.
Although I am intentional making a bunch of those very bot-speed, like her vomit flavor, and dirt, and sardine, on her desk.
I am going at five in the morning to pick up my stuff.
Of course she's there, so that I don't have to see her ugly, lying face.
But guess what?
They said the temperature apparently likes me so much they're giving me another salmon instantly.
Yay.
They're done shaking back.
Next?
Moving on, uh, Loki, what do you have to say?
I had some dumb bitch in front of me today, actually I don't know who it was, but it was
some dumb bitch driving a 30 and a 45, and there was no red lights or anything, it's
not like you're slowing down for anything, you're just slowing down for the hell of it.
So I got pissed, and drove by them and flipped them off, and yelled at them and stuff because
I couldn't hear you, but it felt good.
Um, have you the stupid teenagers that were at this gandhi last night?
Um, okay, let's see.
Number one, you're a nerd.
Okay, yeah, that's acceptable, okay?
Number two, you're not goth.
Don't try to be...
I don't know what the hell they think, but what's the step of coolness?
Okay, let's see here. I'm at the bottom rung, so the next thing I gotta be is goth.
Oh, wait, um, you know, the whole goth trend, you know, that was so ten years ago.
And now you're just annoying and you look stupid and then the guy with the wannabe mohawk
I'm gonna spike up my hair in the middle and it's gonna look like shit, and I'm gonna be all coop because I yeah
So there's all these kids there are like wannabe punk
which is sad because it doesn't take much to be punk, but they're not quite there yet
And then they're playing DDR, and you'd think okay these wannabe punk guys
Maybe they listen to rock maybe they're you know trying to get through the whole punk thing and that kind of thing
They start playing nori nori nori and fucking like, you know shit like that. It makes no sense
I'm just you're annoying and you're in my way
So then I had my turn coming up on the machine to get a coin line of all fucked up
So I have my turn this dump this dump dumbass kid comes up to me. He's like, you know, what's my turn?
I'm like, fuck you, man. I was waiting for people. I you know, I counted it and everything
Well, I don't know if I've been on here waiting here for two minutes of 15 minutes
I'm like, oh, it was my fucking turn, get out of here.
So, it was annoying.
So basically just stupid people at Scandiac because they suck.
Um, F you to...
Would you like to take a nap, by the way, because you're a stupid kid in that place with your hair.
F you to the stupid bastard that was there also last night that wanted to do some improv turning.
He's like, dude, let's have a turning man for people. Yeah!
I know that kid, and he used to try to hang out with me because he thought I was so cool because I played PDR, and I was teaching him little stuff, and now he thinks he likes PDR guys because they're trying to get tournament going everywhere he goes, even if he's by himself. He'll ask random people.
what else we've got on the list here i know there's a bunch of shit um
at the police because i don't know why it takes about eight people to you know
if you uh...
patrol the fucking like
greenback lane i was driving here and i thought the police cars
drive-by not take after anything
what he's doing thank you for giving out my address on there
I'm kidding, God.
I took a street.
What the hell, man?
Fucking A, dude. It's stupid.
Yeah, so, so they're just...
I don't understand, they're like complaining, we don't have enough money to, you know, support our police force, and it's understaffed, and...
What the fuck? You have like eight people traveling around here, you know, pulling over speeders in a traffic area.
You're not gonna speed up those cars in front of you, you dumbasses.
want to do something important like stop robberies or drive-by punchings or
something like that
something like
do something
uh...
at the my website
that's close
and uh...
uh... i don't know that that's all i have right now because my memory
uh...
all right my turn
uh... my nephews of the weaker pretty short
uh... my aunt per step you the week goes to a low-key simp
smoky simp
because last night the party i didn't play at all
because i was too drunk
why did my since i really wanted to play it to let me get to
with an f everybody else who played because i didn't get to play
oh oh oh wait thank you for reminding me. I even remember saying in a drunken stupor
I wanna play!
I have one more, I have one more, I just remembered.
F you the cypher game pads because they suck ass
okay what the hell's the point of putting frickin
they've got not even no kind of gauge of sheet metal they have underneath them but there's no fucking way it's gonna hold any sort of weight whatsoever
I took the feet off the bottom of these things so they wouldn't bend and they still fucking bend
and the wires are coming out of what you know it's it's like
jim and my i'd thought might have to build really shitty
i mean i look at that point all my god man with i'd just fully fuck those up
but now these are just really fucked up so
yet don't buy safer game pads if you're going to buy my mind by anyone else is
not there
uh... a quick question in the chat room wonder what someone would like trying to
play d r when they're really really drunk
last time i was in vegas i did that a circus circus i got really fucked up at
the star trek experience
which i know it's like the nerdiest thing i've ever said on the show but i
swear to god it's true
i got drunk at the star trek experience then walked back
to the circus circus
and then played uh...
played afro-nova
afro-nova trick i remember the song even though which is amazing is there no
struck
i played afro-nova trek on the machine that's right in the middle of like the
little kid area
No, I realized when I was in Reno and I was at the Atlantis and I played their Max 2 machine. I play better when I'm drunk than when I'm not drunk.
I was, uh, I was, it was the DDR Freak Moderator strip. Me, an iguana girl, an islander. All three of us and two of my friends were there who lived in Las Vegas.
At the Star Trek experience, between the three of us, we had three warp core breaches. And, uh, no, two and a half. Two and a half.
And we went on the ride, went on the ride again, and then we took a cab over to Circus Circus and played on the USA machine that was up there with the broken, I mean broken arrows on the left side, I'm sorry, on the right side, and I was trying to do love to me.
And then, like, we called, um, Understanding Live, the voicemail, because we were drunk.
And, um, one more after you, just remember it again.
Fuck you to the stupid DDR stream roulette.
Seven times yesterday, I got one away from the Legend of Max, and it wouldn't fucking give it to me.
I've got the timing down perfect, yet you won't give it to me.
Why even fucking have it in the roulette if you're not gonna give it to me?
You stupid assholes, I can't wait two weeks to play this damn song.
I wanna play it now!
I wouldn't play roulette so you know I can get cutie chaser five times for freaking white lovers or whatever the fuck that stupid
Song is it sucks ass
Shouldn't be in there
Tell us what you really think logy. Oh
Yeah, cutie chaser morning mix. Why did they take anything from OHA?
You know DDR. It's just dumb, but did you say Omaha DDR? Oh, hi dumbass
That's not Omaha. I swear to God, I thought you said Omaha. I'm like, hey, we got friends there.
Yeah, do you know of a DDR Omaha mix? Do you know of one? Because, you know, I'm...
That's what I thought you said, and I'm like, in my mind, I'm like, God Loki's a retard. There's no Omaha mix.
Rob's still drunk in his head, like, Rob's still drunk. I'm taking over.
No, Rob's too drunk to be over her host.
No, I'm, uh, I'm not doing my FUs yet, lady.
If you even think about it, I can hear you.
Also, um, I forgot to finish that story. When you play DDR drunk, it's like, every time you jump, I remember,
I remember you jump up and it's like, I'm flying and then you come down like a rock.
That's how it's different when you're drunk.
That's all I remember.
When I do this, I always spin on them and I get really dizzy.
I played drunk on your old pads.
I would also like to give a nephew the lack of sex.
Thank you.
by the way, I played drunk on my pads and he fell over and that was funny.
Alright, let's get to the rest of the room, shall we?
Who's first?
Who else is first?
You're first, go.
Okay, a couple of FUs, one of them is to these guac-a-chips because they taste like guac-a-shit.
I don't care if anybody else likes them, I think they taste like crap.
Combos are fucking good. Eat one! Okay, eat like eight, okay?
No, anyways, another F.U. I have is, of course, to the little punk, wannabe punk brigade over at Scandia.
They're stupid and annoying. They don't know what the hell a coin system is.
And they think they're really cool because they can pass, like, exotic ethnic on light.
Are you trying to get Legend of Max on roulette?
No, not at all.
And yeah, especially that little mohawk kid comes up to me four fucking times after I tell him every new time.
So how does a token line work?
I'm like, just put your damn token up.
And the fourth time, I just walked off. I didn't even say anything.
Whose tokens are those? Because I want to take them.
And I just said there were some guys who didn't take them.
Another F.U. I have is to, we'll call them drunk kids.
last night. I've already seen kids are trying to get drunk and stupid and I'm going to kill
them whenever I find them. And another one is those fucking pads because they should
be registered as lethal weapons. I moved the fucking pad twice and I got cut four times
because the sheet metal is so sharp on the side. I was sitting there on the pad and all
of a sudden I just noticed I was bleeding off my hands for no reason. Not to mention
Not to mention that, but the fact that the pads are bent in half, that the one side doesn't really work too well.
It got bent in half just from one game of playing on them.
And then that and the fact that the wires are coming out, and yeah, that's up.
And one last one is to Bel Air for having fucking two things left of the Sharanov Triple Black,
And one of them is missing a fucking bottle, and so we can only get one and have to resort to, like, substituting.
That was the worst thing ever.
And that's all, because I don't want to talk no more.
Next.
Okay, it's my turn.
Uh, first, hi DarkSessia, thanks for saying hello.
Uh, hi Irene, how are you? Are you out there?
Not angsty enough.
Okay, my fuck yous aren't that great, but here we go.
Well, yeah, okay, we'll start with that.
Fuck yous to Laundromat, because going to Laundromat is not fun.
Today was my first experience in years to go to a Laundromat, and it wasn't too bad.
I was in a hurry, though, so it just kind of sucks having to share your laundry with the whole world.
So anyway, back to other things.
Uh, fuck you to my computer.
It's not working properly.
I can't get it to work hardly at all.
Oh, yeah, okay, thanks to me.
I did my good deed for the week.
I gave 0x my extra 32 megabytes of RAM for this computer,
which only had 32 megabytes of RAM,
so I gave him an extra one, and now it has 64 megabytes of RAM,
and now it works nicely.
So, that's my good deed for the week.
I know, it was like, yeah, it was extra.
What's that?
You have 512 megabytes of RAM.
512 of my old computer.
My current one's like 80-something DDR RAM now.
Whoa, that's nice.
This is how it came.
Yeah.
Well, yeah, right now my computer is not functioning,
and I think there's a virus on it, and I can't tell,
I can't get online yet, but I don't know, I'll have to figure it out.
Your computer has never had a virus scanner?
Yeah, I think I got something stupid on there, but I'll have to figure it out.
Anyway, and fuck you to the Kmart on Stockton Avenue, because they have... Stockton Boulevard, excuse me.
There are people that work there that really suck. They can't do anything, and they never have enough people at the cash register.
It's a Kmart.
Yes, I know. It's a Kmart. It's going downhill fast.
And fuck you to guys, and I won't say why. I just hate guys. You know, guys suck. Sorry to all you guys out there who are decent guys.
But guys who really suck, fuck you.
And yeah, fuck you to lack of sex.
Guys who suck, here's my number.
And I'm done. Let's see your fucking math.
I have to agree with Rob, fuck you to lack of sex.
It's been so long I don't even remember what a penis looks like, except my own.
Oh, great, that's lovely. Thank you.
Also, I have to back up Jamie's fuck you to her boss, because bosses everywhere suck, and they should all be frickin' tarred and feathered and thrown out into a street naked.
Well, with the exception of Lokai's boss, because I guess Lokai's boss is wrong, but other than that, fuck not having a computer and fuck not having...
Well, actually, fuck having a job, period.
Having to have a job to make money.
And that's about it this week.
You say fuck having a job. Can I say fuck not having a job?
I should rephrase that. Fuck having to have a job to have money.
Or say fuck having your job.
Well, that too. That works.
People need to pay me because I'm cool.
Pay me for the privilege of being in my presence.
I'm just going to become a porn star. You know why? Because you're getting paid to have
sex. That's two of my big problems right there.
I don't want to go buy porn to see Robin. Well, you'd see my dick on the cover, so you
know, you'd be all, I better stay away from this. Rob's naked on the cover.
What if you're one of the extras? And you're not on the cover.
I am much better than a fluff boi.
We're gonna start with Ninja Usagi Koe.
Our first F.U. goes to rocks in the woods that aren't fat people friendly.
The second will go to Namco for no free play. They suck.
The third will go to all politicians for being so fucking stupid and sending us to war and just ignoring other possibilities because they're so fucking power hungry.
Arigato ho hanemate.
F.U. to Freedom Fries.
what that used to be like.
people who get in Jamie's way when she drives.
I'm sorry, this is from Skyline DC-505.
Fuck you to the DMV for failing me during the drive test for a dangerous maneuver.
Stupid, stupid bitches, and fuck you to little kids in Scandia.
I would like to request more information on what that dangerous maneuver was.
So send that over, please.
Dr. Tuya says, continued F.U. to being single.
I need a date, dammit.
Fuck banging my foot on the vacuum, it freaking hurts.
And fuck the United States Postal Service, Angel Snail Mail didn't arrive yesterday.
I haven't gotten any either.
Oh, God, here comes Snub Dispenoid.
Okay!
First off, fuck drivers training once again, fuck it up the peehole.
I'm fucking sick of Red Asphalt 3 and that sick fuck that treated human beings
like they were fucking toys.
I swear to God, I don't want to hear some child-raping 40-year-old say,
Oh, what a waste, when the person's fucking brains are plastered on the freeway.
I thought it was hilarious. I was laughing my ass off during that video.
Well, you're a sick fuck.
If you ever want to see a good comedy, watch any of the Red Ass Waltz.
It's, like, better than Spike and Mike.
They're all, Oh my God, it's so horrible!
And they just show a dead person on, like, me, not a steering wheel.
True.
little kids who told the people at my table to shut up. The only person that can tell
me to shut up is the fucking teacher, not some stuck-up, cousin-humping piece of shit
that lives in Natomas. Fuck them. Also, fuck you to that stupid shitwad that thinks Judo
is kicking someone in the nuts as hard as you can and throwing their limp body over
you. That's not Judo, that's fucking mental retardation. That's ghetto Judo, man. My ball
still fucking hurts, so fuck you, buddy. And fuck you to the fucking asshole bassoon player
that left me all alone in my orchestra. I have to play all of my parts alone and I can't
play contrabassoon because we won't have a regular bassoon if I did.
Hey, if your band has a contrabassoon clarinet, I'll play it. I'll volunteer.
Fuck him right in his little bitch-ass ear. I fucking hate his worthless ass. Fucking
shack of shit. Fuck it. Fuck it all. Fuck. Like bloody fucking hell, fuck it all.
23rd Magus says, Fuck you to being broke. Probably can't enter March Madness. I cry.
you to Angel being in Japan and not here in SAC. I cry again. Fuck you to my parents not
getting me and having their heads stuck up their asses. I cries more.
Rice says, fuck you bad mic with buzzing. I agree. Fuck you slow, weak, move faster.
Fuckity fuck fuck fuck, that is all. Black Lab says, more FUs. Did I even get the
first ones? I don't remember reading Black Lab FUs. Well, he says number six. I don't
Remember seeing one through five, but whatever
Fuck the shitty internet connection in the dorms and fuck chipotle burritos. They're damn too. Damn good. I had them four times this week
Like this whole chipotle trend, okay
I like the chipotle burritos, but you know what they make me sick every time I eat them. Isn't it pronounced chipotle?
Chipotle or something like that, okay
Anybody seen that um that one check in the box commercial great
D.D.R. Mike would like to say, fuck you to Concord.
Skyline says that his dangerous maneuver was that he messed up in a left turn.
What did you do, you turned right in a left turn or something?
Or did you try to turn left from the right turn lane?
When you turn left and you're with a driving instructor, you're not supposed to powerslide.
Yeah, I would just like to remind everybody out there that real-life driving is not like Initial D. You don't want to drift.
You know what? Everything that I learned, it was funny the whole time I was taking JB home, I'm like, okay, what I just did, don't do that.
that
jonah sent us some uh... lovely a fuse
over e-mail
explicit
might know by the show forces fuck you too
yes definitely
But he would like to help console himself through that by doing a little bit of venting.
He says, F.U. to my Calc teacher, and he draws a little asky middle finger.
She does not understand what I was going through and told me there's no chance I have to pass
the class, so I decided to withdraw.
I can't believe this.
This is just sick to fail a person whose, well I guess this is what I'll say, whose
dad just passed away and missed a midterm, so fuck her for that.
And another F.U. to the asshole who was pissing me off so badly at a situation like this.
Like I told him I wasn't in the mood to get pissed off that he intended to do so anyway.
That's just disgraceful.
As much as I want to rip his skull so bad the teacher was there and I don't want to
get in trouble from the cops.
Oh yeah, F you to the cops because they won't let me rip this asshole apart.
Saying I'd be arrested.
He'll be gone for a little while but not retired.
Well you know what the whole deal with midterm is, I'm assuming that's college courses.
take that up with the dean of that particular college and they should take care of it.
Alright, some good advice from Jamie because Jamie knows how to kick ass and take names.
Flak Lab, we got the other FUs. He says, Fuck my upcoming finals, they suck. Fuck legal
battles. My girlfriend's plans to visit me during her spring break are currently fucked
over because her aunt is in legal trouble with her business. Fuck the engineering two
building computer labs for closing at 10pm on Friday nights. I had a project due at midnight
that I couldn't finish because they closed early.
Fuck flat bike tires. I got one on Friday night and on my way home from working on my
project thus forcing me to walk a good distance in the rain and dark.
Fuck power outages. One happened Friday night and it screwed up my computer and iPod settings.
Oh and Skyline says he didn't see the oncoming traffic when he made the left turn.
justin circuit wants to add FU to comcast for still not fixing my email if this next
request doesn't fix it
i told you what you need to do with them you just let me call them okay i'll get your email
back let me call them
and last but certainly not least we have uh mennequin ego jazz for saying fuck you to
teachers who complain about noise in the hallways. If you want quiet, close your fucking door.
Yeah, if you don't like noise, you probably shouldn't be teaching because you're loud.
Well, that remark about teachers not teaching, if they didn't teach, they wouldn't be able
to do anything because you figured there are teachers because they can't make it doing
what it is that they teach. Oh, my God. One of my high school teachers,
She would always go, this is so chaotic, didn't you have any Christmas the whole time?
And she would always, every time anyone would say anything, and someone in the back of the
hall said something, she always blamed it on the front three people in the row, but
the funniest thing happened like two years after I left.
She left the classroom, okay, and see everyone really didn't care for her just because she
was so nuts already, but she left the classroom to go take care of something, and when she
When she got back, all the students had turned their desks around backwards.
And if I remember correctly, they even moved her desk to the opposite side.
When she came in, she had a breakdown.
And apparently went on hiatus.
No, it's funny. I've never really had any teaching experience, even though I think that'd be fun.
But I used to do marshaling for Cuzar, which is obviously pretty much no work at all.
But you have to do a little brief, which is kind of funny.
I did one for this one girl who was losing her voice. This is after I quit working there.
But my favorite way I entered the brief, because everyone was talking, was,
Shut the fuck up!
And then everyone was like, Huh? What?
And then I did my brief, yelling at them.
It was cool because I couldn't get fired because I never worked.
The best teacher thing I ever did was when I was in eighth grade.
You knew she was a big drug, you could only tell because she would eat sunflower seeds
in class and then just fall asleep.
One time we made a big old packaging tape, we made a big ball out of it, threw it at
the chalkboard right behind her head.
She jumped like 10 feet and my friend and I personally made it our mission to get her
out of the class and we drove her to rehab.
We drove her nuts and we found her drug buddy one day in class and that was all the evidence
we needed.
This one, I don't know what prompted me to do this, but some girl in 4th grade that I used to talk to, I would only talk to her, no one else, I'd talk to her with a fake Spanish accent.
And then at the very last day of the year I'd talk to her and she'd be like, what happened to your voice? What are you talking about?
It was hilarious.
That's so stupid.
the
you're telling me about this yesterday back in late sixth grade when i was like
parent even
he was sixth grade
are very late it was like after they built this one is going to raise the
risk of being like bright
neon like god-awful i don't even know what was on them
sixties
and things they're almost like empty air pants with his role i kind of like
Silk, so they weren't like silk or anything, but I used to wear those all the time
I think they were like the coolest thing and I used to be awesome at German dodgeball
I was just like yeah, look at me in my pants
I remember
In 11th grade I took advanced English
And I laid my, I would sleep all day in my classes and my teacher wouldn't care
there, because I would always pass my tests, and I never read the book. I just happened
to retain everything that she said in class while I was asleep. Proof that the subliminal
learning tapes might actually have worked. Of course, I could learn in my sleep, and
again high school is a joke. In Spanish class, when we'd watch a movie, we'd steal the tests
for the next two or three months, and we stole midterm and sold it at the beginning of the
In chemistry class, I took the later afternoon chemistry class, and we would go whenever
we had substitute teachers and were left busy work to do, you know, just those forms fill
out.
We would go into the assignment box, because we would have to, we had this little stack
of inboxes that we would put in our papers, we would take the early, the morning class
as papers, and take the person who we know always got the answer right, and copy off
The only thing I can remember from high school that was funny was one time, this is a very
short story, I was in class, I was in ROTC in high school and my best friend Becky, she
gave me, she was like, come here Anita, come here, come here, let me show you something.
She had a Playgirl magazine.
So we were looking at this in class and we were both sat in the back of the classroom
and we were all giggling and everything and checking it out and one of the other girls
that was sitting in front of me, she was like, what are you guys doing?
She's all checking it out and she saw me and she was like, ooh, I'm going to tell, I'm
going to tell, I'm going to tell.
And we started making those big ruckus because I was trying so hard not to get caught because
I was one of those kids that never got in trouble.
And here I am with a Playgirl magazine in ROTC class.
Well luckily our teacher...
What grade was this again?
This was like, I was a sophomore in high school.
I'm gonna tell him, I'm gonna tell him, I'm gonna tell him.
Dude, that bitch should have fucking gotten slapped aside.
I'm gonna tell him, cause I'm the teacher's pet 911.
I want to be the teacher's best friend.
And if she would ask me, I would sleep with her.
Oh my god, I don't know if it was quite like that, but she was just acting up.
If she bent over to kiss my ass, I would be sold there.
Well, anyway, what happened was nothing. I didn't get caught. The teacher came close to check him what was going on, but he looked, and I think he realized what was going on, and he was like, I don't want to go there, and he just walked away.
He walked up to the girl and was like, let me tell him, let me tell him!
I used to read comic books and geometry.
I have a story about a geometry teacher, and I have a picture of him actually with me,
not here with me.
I should guess they're in the car, I can't find them.
My teacher looked like a treasure troll with no hair.
What color was the hair?
Oh, no hair.
Well, he had, you know, he was bald on top.
Well, how do you look like a treasure troll?
He had the face of a treasure troll.
Same shape.
And the other class called him Jolly.
Jolly?
No, his name was Mr. Jolly.
The other classes either called him Dolly or they called him Elmer.
Like Elmer Fudd.
That was the one but ugly man.
But I would just read comic books because I didn't care.
And then there was the one time in class where, to confuse him, I asked him, can you truly
square infinity because any number, the only numbers that you can multiply, you've said
this yourself, it's a proven mathematical fact that the only numbers that you can square
and have them equal themselves are one and zero.
Right?
Right.
Well, you can't square infinity, because if the only two
things that can equal themselves are zero and one,
infinity squared cannot equal infinity.
That just disproves that, though, because infinity is not
even a number, though.
So I guess it doesn't disprove anything.
It's not a number.
It's an idea.
Exactly.
But I was using it in mathematical terms,
and he was like, oh, of course you can.
I feel like I'm in school right now.
Can we stop?
Okay we can stop.
I was a little brat.
Okay then we're school.
We're going to take a quick break and then we're going to come back and I think we want
You are listless when we come back for the break?
Sure.
Okay.
Tonight's listless.
So, who wants to participate tonight?
Okay.
Oh, everybody?
Six?
We could do it.
Yeah.
Okay.
But this is the interesting thing.
Okay, the list tonight.
Top three things that Konami needs to apologize for.
Okay.
So think about that during the break, and we'll be back.
alright
Come on, shake your body, baby, do the come down, no You can't control yourself any longer
Everybody makes a deal that comes out Don't you pick a choice that's in it
All you're building up are the music getting stronger
Don't you fight it, please, let the deal that comes out
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Everybody gather round now, let your body feel the heat
Don't you worry if you can't dance, let the music move your feet
Put the bread down on the island, and like sugar cane so sweet
But if you want to do the contest, you've got to listen to the beat
Come you, shake your body, baby, do the combo
No hit the charges, can you come along?
Come on, shake your body, baby, do the combo
Come you, shake your body, baby, do the gunfire
No hit the charges, can you come along?
Come on, shake your body, baby, do the combo
We are what we're supposed to be
Illusions of our capacity
Out of the light you speak and face
What you do is what you wish to do
We are the god of symphony
We do the things you want to see
Bring my friends to the extreme
Our friends are so unreasonable
They do the unpredictable
I don't like to speak and say
What we do is what you wish to do
That's all I know, that's my friend
Going on a little bit
Bring my friend to the extreme
One by one, we're making it fun
We are the actual heroes of the world
We are the ones who've gone there forever
You say bye-bye, crazy-bye
Oh, the ones that'll never be forever
You can fly fast, or I can hold your hand We're going to go to the party
We're going to the party We're going to go to the party
That's a long way to go, huh?
I know, but I'm afraid I'll be going.
into the dark black forest.
Into the dark black forest.
easier to dance to than that freaking catch-up song, Orange Lounge Radio.
So, you just want to duplicate something because you really believe it's true, then fine, do
it.
With all due respect to Konami, because of course the show wouldn't exist without DDR,
but you know, there are a few things they could fix.
I would find another reason.
There are a few things they could fix.
If it was not for Paraparaparadise.
Alright, go for it, Jamie, you want to start?
Oh, let me, I'm sorry, I have to bring up the list, my word document where I can actually
make lists here.
I noticed how I've never erased that Erotic one, because that was the greatest one we ever did.
Alright, Jamie, your number three pick.
They have not done any more Super Konami World games.
Super Konami World, they had done two of them on the Nintendo.
And you could, like, play as Boy or Girl and go to the Castlevania universe,
and then go to the Gradius universe, and then it's like a bunch of Konami games in one, and it was neat.
And they haven't done any since.
We need more Super Konami World!
One I just put basically was shitty steps for hella good songs on Xtreme.
Sink steps suck, Frozen Ray sucks, V sucks.
I mean, the list could just go on. Colors sucks.
I mean, I'd even need to say more about that.
shitty steps for good songs on Xtreme.
They should have had... I think it sucked that they didn't have any Korean songs on there, because that was what made...
Yeah, well, I know. That made the first, second, and third mixes fast, though, I thought.
They didn't? Whoops.
Maybe the first ones you played or something.
Yeah. Okay. Well, I just like Korean songs. Okay, thanks.
Okay, Ice Queen.
I'd say they need to apologize for not making any more keyboard mania.
The number three thing they should apologize for, you know I actually had DDRPC on my list,
So I'm going to say the number three thing that Konami should apologize for, and I apologize
in advance to some folks in our chat room because they're really going to hate me for
saying this, but they need to apologize for the whistle song.
Yes, that song fucking sucks.
And I know there's fans of it in the chat room, but you need to understand, I had no
problem with the song until other people ruined it for me by like chanting along to it and
all that stuff it's now ruined and now it needs to be apologized for so all
right my number two pick is they should apologize for the bad voice acting in
Castlevania Symphony of the night
they came had atrocious voice acting in comparison to the Japanese version it
It was not by my hand that I was once again given flesh.
Die, monster! You don't belong in this world!
Oh yeah? Well die, Richter voice actor! You don't belong in this game! Ha ha!
Alright. Loki, your number two pick.
Um, let's see. I would have to say they need to apologize.
This should almost be a number one, but they need to apologize for B4U.
I hate the group. I hate the group B4U that can all die, okay? All of them.
Jamie had that written as her number one, now she's thinking.
All right.
Your number two pick, zero.
Um, basically fucking over the U.S.
When it comes to any DDR releases, or pretty much any Beemani releases,
we get, like, the total shit end of the stick.
The Japanese one was good but the US one was totally just raped.
They know they have the following here now, so why don't they do something about it instead of keep screwing us over?
Okay.
Oh, I guess it's my turn. Okay.
Let's see, where am I here?
Oh, I think we should apologize for not making more mixes of Para Para Paradise arcade game.
I mean, I know Para Para Para itself kind of died in Japan, but shoot, you know, it's
one game, huh?
Yeah.
Was it?
Really?
Is it getting big here?
The Para Para craze is actually starting to pick up here a few places, like about places.
Like in the dance clubs kind of thing?
Well, they've had Para Para All Stars Touring in the US.
You're kidding me.
At the Anime Expo, they had them giving out flyers and doing instructions at Anime Expo last year.
That's fly! Awesome.
Don't go to Anime Expo, by the way, because it's the worst convention ever.
So, yeah.
Well, more Para-Para, please.
Anyway, I'll pass the microphone.
Yes.
Okay, Konami really needs to apologize, and this is kind of an addition to Zero's earlier statement.
Just, they need to apologize for Konami USA, period.
I'm just, I'm elaborating on his, that was my original idea.
Konami America is just, I'm sorry, it is just not limited to Konami.
Everything they made in Japan that has been transferred over to the US through Konami USA
Sucks! They raped it up the ass and started punching it. What is that, donkey punching?
Yeah. I'm like, I'm sorry, but that's just it. Period. Next.
Alright, my number two pick that Konami needs to apologize for. I would say Castlevania 64.
When I first started playing that game, I thought it almost started off as a good game and then like halfway through the first level I was like ehh.
They need to apologize for the Super Nintendo version of Dracula X because I have the PC Engine version.
And you know what? Where I actually really like the Super Nintendo one, if ever you've played the PC Engine version, then that's like, where the PC Engine version is like eating a feast, the SNES version is like vomit. So, yeah.
So Dracula V gets a...
Five!
Isn't that what they called it here?
No, it was Dracula X on the Super Nintendo.
I thought they called it Dracula V. Or Castlevania V or something.
No, it's Dracula X.
Oh, okay. My bad. My bad.
So it's actually cool because, you know, actually Symphony of the Night was Dracula X2.
All right.
So you're Loki. I'm sorry. Loki's number one pick.
Okay.
Um, they need to apologize.
Propolitary.
Because, uh, you know what, she wouldn't have a career if it weren't for DDR, and I would hope that she wouldn't have a career if it weren't for DDR, and, you know, I wish she would just go, you know what, uh, yeah, we were hoping that you would get better, you never did, so bye.
Zero, your number one pick?
All right.
Anita.
I have a question, Zero. How come you named your cat, Naoki, then?
Ha ha ha! Touché!
Because I was actually drunk when I named my cat.
And I just got too lazy trying to think of something else.
And my cat makes the name Naoki sound cool.
Well, your cat was also answering to Nao-chan, too.
Anita, you're number one.
Okay, my number one. They should apologize for
let them move!
Excellent suggestion.
Matt, or Ice Queen, your number one pick. They need to apologize.
Oh yes, yes.
Is that your answer or what do you want to say? You know what, I had something in mind, but I'm going to change it to Loki's.
Bag. Period.
Who wants to hear a freakin' bagpipe screeching as loud as you can get it?
Oh my god, Jamie. Oh my god. No comment.
They really need to apologize for that.
Okay, very controversial topic in the chat where we have a lot of people arguing with this. This is interesting.
Alright, but my number one, and I'm surprised nobody's said this yet,
No New Super Konami World Games, DDRPC, Shitty Steps for Good Songs on Extreme, Not Making DDR USA Arcade Better, Discontinuing Keyboard Mania, The Whistle Song, Bad Voice Act 2 in Castlevania 2 The Night,
fucking over the U.S. No new Parpar games, konami USA,
Castlevania 64, SNES version of Dracula X,
Politary, Naoki and his 150 aliases. Let them move, bag, and new logo.
Probably Naoki.
Because before I had heard many tac things, I really liked Naoki's mixes.
Remember, I was a big fan of Brilliant To You O.D. That was my favorite song ever.
I would agree to some extent because some of the Naoki aliases are bad, like Naoki
featuring Politary and Naoki NMR, like Let Them Move and stuff, those are bad, but Naoki
Underground who did Insertion, that's pretty cool. Although I do agree he needs to get
over the identity crisis okay uh next yeah loki what are you taking off um i'm gonna
take off not making ddr usa arcade better because you know what i just don't care if
that machine doesn't exist to me anymore so whatever
you know the other i almost took off that one but for one reason it sort of opened the
door for all the new stuff we're getting now, so, yeah.
It's red and has Konami on it. It's okay. Okay. Zero, what's coming off the list?
Even though I totally agree, I would say let them move. Take that off. Even though I, I
mean, I absolutely agree with it because it's horrible, but the other ones are better.
The song sucks.
Anita.
Uh...
Jeez. Where does the list begin?
I'm sorry. It starts with...
Ladies Night to Get Out was from a couple weeks ago.
It starts here. There we go.
Okay. Um...
Ah, gosh.
Alright, I'll just say shitty steps for a good song sitting straight.
Okay.
Yes, exactly. That is the reason I am attacking Zero.
I don't know, I just think you have a very good point, but it just doesn't seem like as much of a bitch as the rest of the stuff.
Alright.
Decision's final. Matt, what comes off the list?
I'll have to take off the new logo just because, you know, there's so many other things on there that are so much better.
It sucks, but it's lesser of evil.
I'm going to get slapped for this, but it's so bad that it's good.
I'm taking off the bad voice acting in Castlevania 6 days at night.
No!
Because, you know what, it's one of those things where it's like, I love mimicking it.
Die, monster! You don't belong in this world!
And I mean, it's so bad that I love to mimic it, so for that it's redeemable.
and it said true of all religions. Dan and I used to quote that game.
And I'm not doing that because Brad is jumping in the chatroom up and down asking me to,
but I really do think that it's so bad it's good, so there you go.
Alright, so I have to close out all the windows first before I can start taking votes here.
Somebody had suggested, because of no new remixes by the T-word...
What were some of the suggestions? I missed them. Oh well.
I find it funny that he's been reduced to a four-letter word.
Alright. We're going to post that list and you guys can send in your...
Sort of like Twat.
Send in your votes right now over private message to Sky.
Jamie, you want to read the final list?
No new Super Konami World games, DDRPC, Discontinued and Keyboard Mania,
Whistle Song, B4U, Fucking Over the US, No New Para Para Games, Konami USA, Castlevania 64, the SNES version of Dracula X, Politarian Bag.
Vote now or die.
too so I do that when we come back so we will do a quick break and which one you
want the old-school one you want the new one okay let's go on we'll be back send
Put your votes in now, please, please, please.
I will do ya
Don't wanna play a game
I apologize because that was mislabeled, so that wasn't the old school one, but I found
labeled so that wasn't the old-school one but I found the right one so enjoy a double shot
Ha! Ha! Ha! Ha! Ha!
Yari koya ni koyo de uni ka da da da daro
Yahanara hayo!
Ah!
Get up, stand up, stretch up on your suction bowl
How you gonna be the attraction?
And why don't you, if you wanna stay to the wall
Ride yourself a piece of reaction
Got you, get out, let's make big fails
Get up, you know when you got to go
Get up, get up, dancing all the time, come on
Here we go, here we go
Get up, stand up
Stretch your body, stretch your neck
Let's just use it there in a corner
Sitting by yourself in the top
You don't really wanna be no, no, no
Come on now, get up and dance, dance, dance, dance
Dance, dance, dance, come on, get your feet
Wreck my feet, you the most it's gon' be
Get up, stand up, touch up from the shoulder
Hi, this is Mel B of RTF. Looking for an extra $1.99 a minute, my girlfriend Mel B can join us on all the fun together.
But hey, if you're a broke-ass like I am, why don't you come to the one place that costs absolutely nothing to go to and still the fun is just as great?
It's Orange Lounge Radio, Sunday nights.
Kick it with me and you just might realize the best things in life are free.
Howdy, kids! We're back, and we're being a little slow
because the listless votes aren't fully tallied yet, so we're going to go right into this week's cage match.
Uh, last week... oh, I've got to get all this stuff cued up, though. I'm not even ready.
Is there anything, uh...
Wait, wait, wait, but you said you wanted to make a stipulation before this week's cage...
Are you pulling out about what you wanted to do in your song last week?
If I withdrew mine, I'd want to put in a new one, which means I have to go to my car real quick.
Oh, so you have last week's winner in here.
I put it in there, but I kind of want to withdraw it and put in something new if I can.
What do you guys think? Well, let's ask the chat room what they think.
Let's hear a little bit of last week's winner.
Because Jamie's having second thoughts.
I hated it. Okay.
Jamie doesn't really like that song.
I picked it because it was hyper.
Okay, then we're going to play a little clip of it.
This is Link's theme, the Heave Dance Remix.
And if the chat room says it's okay to bend the rules a little bit this week and let Jamie
take it out and give us something new, then we'll do it.
so here we go
Alright, by an overwhelming vote in the chat room, it's out of here. It's gone.
Alright, I'm going to go get a CD out of the car. I'll be right back.
Alright, so I'm getting suggestions for what to put in this week, too. That's great.
Okay, so we're going to start this week's cage match, except I'm short a few songs.
So, Clean Slate. We have no winners coming over from last week because we're deleting that because it sucked.
I don't know how it won. I guess the other two songs. I put in Fable, and everybody has something against that song.
Alright, so I guess I'll start. This is the way, since we're starting with a clean slate tonight, let's refresh everybody on how the cage match works.
We have this little segment that reoccurs on the show called the Orange Lounge Cage Match. The way it works, each of the hosts puts in one song that they want to put in there.
And the chat room votes on which is their favorite.
And the winner gets to go into regular rotation on the station during the Bamani Music & More program.
So, I'm getting votes for stuff. This is interesting. Oh no. Don't tell me what to put in.
And like half the ones you're mentioning either suck ass or have already been in there.
No, actually another song by that artist is in there. I get what she was saying.
I already have I already have a song for this week, but I'll do that for next week. Oh
I'm so tempted to put that song in just J or whatever you're called this week, Justin
I really want to put that first song in there you sent me, but I'm not ready to yet
We'll do that next week. Okay, because I really want to do this song this week. So I'll start
My song this week that I'm going to do is by a group that you know from 2dx
They were in seventh style and they have a pretty popular song in there
the song they did in there was called the beauty of silence and the group is
svenson and guilin and this this is another song by them i have this song
well cool this is uh my pick for tonight's cage match this is a song
called twisted by the same group that did beauty of silence svenson and
leland enjoyed
that kind of has an abrupt ending oops that's because it came off a non-stop mix that was
the actually that was the energy mix of Twisted by Svensson and Geedle in the same group the
beauty of silence and what y'all think
beauty of silence it ain't
sorry that was really boring
what do you give it on 110?
well poop on you
i give it a 5
right down the middle
zero
i kind of give it
i have to mix it up
i guess i give it a 6
because i really like beauty of silence
and that seemed to have been really well
more real repetitive
I've heard better cuts of that same song, and that was a pretty bad cut of it.
Like you said, it's repetitive, and it does kind of, you know, do something ill with the middle, because in the beginning, it might make you feel bad, but it's not good for the core.
On all of you.
You're really not gonna like it.
Ice clean.
Yeah.
I don't like repetitive notes, and that was all that was, and I've never heard any other version of that, so that's all I have to go on. I have to give it a three.
I can't really do too much of a judgment as far as cast history on this one goes.
I feel like this one's gonna be with stylists.
But this one was like, well I'm just going by an overall judgment and I have to give it about a 5 because it was kind of repetitive.
But I kind of liked it too.
It just sounded kind of nice.
Alright, and personally I give that a 150 so that way it averages all your votes to a 10.
Yeah, that's great.
you saw next week that if you will see i'm gonna come back i'm gonna save this clip of the show
and after i play what he sent me next week i'm gonna remind you all that you asked me to play
that okay that's all i have to say all right come on and all your balls need to yeah i don't have
All right, Jamie, what's your pick tell us about it?
of people calling my eyes
they're praying to shake it down
saying, oh, dear, dear
they're really saying, I'm
hi
I don't know what happened
I don't know what happened, let me have a sip, sorry.
Okay, I'm going to abort this real fast because we're going to try switching it around a little bit.
We're having issues with that CD.
I burned this like three days ago.
Let's see, I'm going to put it in the other drive and see what happens.
It's a pretty big scratch right there.
Yeah, it's a pretty big scratch right in the middle.
Well, let's try it.
Okay, we're going to restart this.
This is the burner.
Sorry about that.
I don't have the three of that with me.
Thank you everybody.
Oh
Now what?
I see trees of green, red-rooted tombs I see them bloom, poor me and you
And I think to myself what a wonderful world
I wanna see the skies of blue
And clouds of white
The brightest light of day
The dark state of night
I've got things in my hand
What a wonderful way
What a wonderful land
I'm also a little lazy
Of people going by
I can feel shaking hands
Staying for the reason
That everything is being
All I love is
I hear a baby cry
One second cry
There ain't much more that I ever know
The things in my head
They're a wonderful world
But I don't want you to go away
kostjamrh Alrighty, that was Beatbox from The What A Wonderful World.
Alrighty, tell us what you thought, give it a scale of 110. Jamie?
Oh wait, oops, I have the volume way up too loud. Sorry about that. Jamie, tell us again. Sorry, I had the volume way too loud on that. Tell us what's out of that.
Twenty-four.
Okay.
Um... I didn't like it very much. I... It was... I'm sorry, I don't like club mixes of, like, songs like that. It's just... it just doesn't fit.
Everyone thinks that the formula for a dance song is let's put a beat to it and add lyrics from an old song.
No, it's not gonna work.
So, um...
And then that part in the end where it starts kinda doing this little thing where it starts changing the pitch a little bit,
where it starts getting way out of key and then coming back in, I don't know what the hell that was either.
So I go to six.
Better than the other song, but still.
Alright, zero.
Generally, I don't really care what it is.
I personally liked that song. I liked the variety, I liked how it wasn't the same goddamn beat the whole way through.
So they'd be faded out, in a faded bag, different kind.
And yes, I like this one too, the original, so I'm going to have to give that one a 10.
Just because that's a happy song.
This one's a happy song. Very, very happy, happy.
I liked it. I wasn't too crazy about how the rhythm kind of reminded me of Beauty and Silence
and there's a little hint to that.
But overall, it's a very nice sounding song, a little on the long side, but not too bad.
I'll give it an 8. It's nice.
That song makes my heart happy whenever I'm in a rotten room.
That's one of the few songs that just makes me happy all over.
Night Angel Mix, it's Loki vs. Steve Reiner, featuring a Solaris or something like that.
Okay, here you go
It's a long way to go, honey It's a long way to go, honey
It's a long way to go, honey.
I know. But I'm awake. How are we going?
Into the dark, black forest.
Okay, what did y'all think of that one?
How is Steve Rider vs Loki featuring Solaris with Dark Black Forest?
Keep in mind that I'm trying to bypass my bias against Dark Black Forest.
Because I'm utterly sick and disgusted with that song.
However, it was nicely done.
So I'm trying to bypass my bias with that song.
I give it a seven, plain, seven, seven, seven, seven, seven, eight, eight.
Okay.
Loki?
As mentioned in the chatroom, it doesn't sound very remixed.
There's actually a lot of subtle stuff, and there's a few more synth things added to the actual main synth of the song.
So it's kind of hard to detect that there.
It was a mix between one song by Sinaris, I don't remember exactly what the song was called,
And uh, Dark Black Forest, uh, long trip, so there's a lot of stuff that sounds the same, but you know, overall it is really mixed, not just like, oh, here's Dark Black Forest, I'm just going through that.
But um, I give it an 8 because the Legend of Trance is way better, but you know, I'm getting better, working on it.
Alright, Zero?
I don't know how many more trips to the dark black forest we need to take, but it was pretty good.
And look, he's right, there's a lot of slow stuff, so for you people who didn't hear it, turn your
stereos or headphones up really really loud and you'll be able to hear it.
But I guess I'll give it an 8 because I still did enjoy it.
I have to agree with the last two clips, I give it an 8 just because I liked it.
The beginning was kind of a little bit slow, but it was very repetitive.
But then it picked up and I liked it again.
I think I'll give it an 8, because I...
Oh, wait a minute. I'm thinking backwards. I'm giving it a 7, because...
The previous song, I thought that was a bit better. I like that one. This one is good, but it does sound a little bit like the original, so I like the first or second entry the best.
It was just Dark Black Forest's long trip with some subtle synth.
The next one is going to be totally different than the trance remixes I've been doing.
It's going to be an even more hardcore version of Sligo Works.
You're going to love it.
Okay, let's recap.
I'm getting happy thinking about that.
Quick recap, here we go.
These are the three things you can vote for.
You can send your votes now over private messages to Sky in the chat room.
First one you can vote for,
Second one you can vote for, Beatbox, right, is that Beatbox?
Beatbox with What a Wonderful World is the other one you can vote for.
CD Fire's out.
All right, and the third song you can vote for, Steve Reiner vs. Loki featuring Solaris
Cenaris with Dark Black Forest.
Alright, again, first song was Svensson and Gleelan with Twisted, second song was Beatbox
with A Wonderful World, third song was Steve Reiner vs Loki featuring Cenaris with What
I just thought of my next week's song. Damn it, that sucks.
Oh, you just thought of the song you really wanted to do?
I just thought it was in my car, too. It was like, ehh, next week.
Alright. So, there you go. Send your votes in now to Sky.
In the meantime, we don't want to go right to a break, because we just played a bunch of music.
So, let's try to chat it up a little bit, shall we?
Who has something they want to talk about?
Loki.
Well, let's see. Uh, Jackie? Wait.
I haven't made a racial comment this week yet. Oh dear god. Okay, good, because I'm
not going to. I'm not going to, but I was just thinking back to when we were talking
over food at TJ Friday's about my blank owner's club game where you have to train your people
I still like mocap bakery.
And then what was yours, mocap hansel and gretel, where you shove the little children
into an oven?
Well, let's see, big news, this week opening up was Dreamcatcher, and for all the, yeah,
yeah, I agree Dreamcatcher looked like ass, but you know what was before it? It was the
Final Play of Osiris, and that kicks ass. I would go see it just for that.
I would pay matinee prices just to go see that, that, and I'd just walk out of the movie.
Q. Ever since Puppy introduced me to BitTorrent, I've been loving downloading things for free,
like movies.
And I downloaded that movie Foam Booth, which Brad and I were telling me that it was actually
just a rip-off of an old movie with Wesley Snipes in it. I was getting that and what
sucked is I left it on for about 18 hours to get the goddamn movie and then it wouldn't
even burn because it told me I had the wrong type of burner to do it. I'm so mad. I'm gonna
just burn off those files and take it to someone else's house. But I'm like, how cool. I can
have like a movie like two weeks before it's out in the theater and then I was
getting phone booth it's um this new program it's called bit torrent and if
black lab has a link to that site he gave me that would be cool it's this
it's I I would say it's like win MX or something like that but it's not it's a
little different because it's not a separate client it's a download tool you
install into your browser, so when you start downloading a file with a.torrent extension,
what you do is you start downloading this file from, I guess, I don't know, it tells
you where everybody else has the file, and you start downloading from people, and then
as you're downloading it, when new people start downloading, they start downloading
from you. So the key is to make it work, you have to leave your thing on for like a couple
hours after you finish so other people can finish their stuff too. But it's a way of
just basically file distribution. It's mass leeching and seeding and all that. But it's
cool. How I've used it so far, I've gotten like a couple CDs in a movie, and I'm working
on getting Final Fantasy Origins, but it's not finished yet. And I had to stop it because
we had to start the show. The Final Fantasy I and II for America? Yep. That'll be fun.
Okay, so what else is on y'all's minds? How was your week? How was your week, Anita?
My week was pretty good. On Saturday, we went out to the store, did a little browsing at a game shop.
I bought.hack, the new PlayStation 2 game.
And how's that? How'd you like it?
I haven't started yet, but it looks really, really cool. I just got it.
But if anybody out there has any advice or any experience playing.hack,
Well, actually, I think Ice Princess has many good comments on the series, right? No? Yeah,.hack? No?
Who was that? Some people are saying that this series was great.
I don't remember.
Loki.
I heard it was good. I've never seen it. Actually, to be honest, to be honest, looking at the game from the screenshots I've seen, it looks like ass, but, you know, I don't know.
It's good enough to spawn two more sequels.
Whoopity-doo!
I'm sure the summoner did have one good thing about it and that was that
previous thing that they did based on the attention to dragons thing got any
dr. pepper no Mountain Dew got any Mountain Dew like yeah it's in the
fridge am I in the tavern yet no why cuz if there's any hot chicks there I want
You have to do them!
of their original tension, but it's a lot more realistic, and the cutscenes when you stealthily kill somebody is awesome. Their heads just pop right off. You jab them and you can kick cats and dogs. All kinds of stuff. It's actually pretty good.
somebody get cut in the throat and you see like ten gallons of blood squirt out.
The bloodshed is the whole point of that game. The bloodshed is the point of that game as
to Resident Evil or anything else. It's just really really cool. It's like asking why anime
chicks have such big breasts. They just do. That is the point.
Why does Saga Frontier suck? Let's see here. Not only do you get 1 shitty quest, but no,
you get 12 shitty quests that you get to go on there almost exactly the same. Plus, the
graphics sucked ass, and the game was just boring as hell.
And the title's crappy.
The end. I ended up buying it, playing it for a week, and selling it back.
And for the record, graphics do not equal gameplay.
But the gameplay wasn't anything good either, so I was like, well, maybe the graphics...no, no, sorry.
I'm serious, if they had a role-playing game that was like just the regular text scrolling ones that were from way back in the day, I can enjoy those more if they had a good story.
No, what was freaking awesome is they're making this new side-scrolling game that's just like Contra, but you get to make your own levels.
Oh, that's cool.
It's got a level editor in it.
That's cool. Now, I've been hearing that Unlimited Saga's supposed to be pretty redeeming.
Yeah, see, well, it has about time.
Because it's technically in the series.
They've got like all sorts of neat limited box sets and blah blah blah.
Yes, we're going to come back after a quick break with the results for both list lists, because we never did those.
And the cage match, so it's going to be a whole results set when we come back from break.
But first, Chat Room would like to request no Saga Frontier bashing.
It sucks ass.
In fact, Square should denounce, you know, Soccer Patiers being part of their, you know, whole lineup.
You know what game that Square needs to denounce? Is, uh, freakin', um, uh, Legend of Mana, not, not...
No, not Secret of Mana, Legend of Mana. That game was shit.
Okay, I was thinking, I went ahead and got the import of that because I was like, oh, you know, it's Legend of Mana, what the hell?
You know, I was thinking it was, you know, more Seiken than Sezu. But that was ass.
I was about to think that you were about to say the Secret of Mana, and I would have bit-stopped you in a TomorrowCade.
No, dude, I have my copy, okay, with my character named after me, although I hate to really like the blonde girl, but...
Okay, so I don't have to bit-stop you.
And then I have Senka Densetsu, but I need to re-get the ROM for Senka Densetsu 3, the one that's fully translated down to the graphics.
Very nice. Or just, you know, borrow my friend's cartridge for Super Nintendo.
I bashed soccer frontier in my sleep that it was a horrible game and anyone who likes
it play it again yeah if soccer frontier happens to sneak into my dreams you know then suddenly
i wake up with the urge to vomit good i'm done with one club damn it there's more one
thing in this favor it had good music it had some good music it's like that rap city musical
the first village before we package that shit up and turn it back in. We did not even go
That game sucked, right slide. Um, Ephemeral Fantasia, that game sucked.
Is the game, it was a put out, it was a RPG put out by Konami, and apparently you can use your guitar for each controller with it?
That game is ass. Dan and I barely, we didn't even get past the first village before we packaged that shit up and turned it back in.
We did not even go as far to see if our controllers would work with the US version. We took that shit back.
More like effeminate fantasia.
I
When you're coming down, you'll be alive
You don't have to believe, you can call yourself
When it comes time to find things you wanted to do
So you don't start this city no fair
If you love me baby, you can call yourself
Before it won't give in
While you listen to the song
It's too much for me to ask
Do you write a song so hard on my side?
Lead up, talk to me
Do you feel like I'm gonna last
I'm in it all day
Do you wanna be fine?
If I look at you
I'll be right with you
Ready, ready, ready
Who's on the turntables tonight, my son?
Let's listen in on an Orange Lounge Radio staff meeting.
Do we want to be accepted by Hollywood?
No!
Do we care what people think of us?
Do we want people to kiss our ass?
Yeah!
Extreme Babati Radio
That's us, Orange Lounge Radio
Alright, we're back
Featuring the buzz, episode number 37
Episode number 37
Thank you.
Of Orange Lounge Radio.
We're back.
And we have results, results, results for you people.
And then we're going to whore a few things out.
We're going to give, we're going to open it up to the chat room to plug anything they
want.
Anything they want to plug.
You got 15 minutes left to show to do it.
What?
Don't be afraid of people plugging stuff in public.
Anything you guys want to plug, send it to me over a private message and we'll plug it.
Live on air.
Alright.
And we got a few plugs of our own we want to do.
So we're going to have plug mania in a minute.
In the meantime, let's announce, first, the winners of our listless segment.
Top three things that Konami needs to apologize for.
Number three.
Bag.
Yay!
Please apologize.
You can send those cards and letters care of all Bomani players.
Bag.
Number two.
Castlevania 64.
Indeed.
And you can write that to all of America for Castlevania 64.
Apologies.
The number one thing that Sami needs to apologize for is fucking Polteri.
By quite a bit of a margin.
She seems like she's being fucked.
That's why she keeps going off key and rhythm.
Alright.
Moving on, now let's announce the winner of the cage match.
The cage match had a lot of votes tonight, you guys.
I'm very happy and it was actually kind of close.
I was very surprised.
What a wonderful world wins the cage match this week.
I'm full of happy feelings right now.
So, enjoy.
Now, let's see.
We're going to plug stuff.
So, first thing we want to plug. There's tournaments we have to plug.
In two weeks, we will be broadcasting live from March Madness.
It's going to be a huge tournament.
DDR Freestyle Idol is a part of that.
PA 64 person bracket.
So even if you suck at PA, come because you're going to qualify.
With 64 people, that's awesome.
Not to mention, I think the first NorCal 2DX tournament, right?
Yes, the very first NorCal official 2DX tournament.
I think there might have been some impromptu ones, but this is the first official 2DX tournament.
That one's only on Saturday, by the way.
Yes, that's Saturday night, only Saturday night.
And Saturday and Sunday, both days, is the tournament.
We'll be broadcasting live both days, all day long.
So that's something else.
Join us in the channel and all that fun stuff.
Another tournament we're going to be at in May, and I'm sure I've already gotten private
messages asking me to plug this, so I'll get to those in a little bit.
But B3, going to be huge, Pier 39, two days, I believe it's May, and I'm going to get killed
if it's the wrong date, but I'm going off the top of my head, May 17th and 18th, yes?
I think.
Look at the calendar.
I'm going to look at the calendar, because I think I might be wrong.
I have this really bad feeling I'm wrong, but somebody, I'm sure somebody asked me to
plug it anyway.
I'm right, it is 17th and 18th, woohoo!
Okay, so we'll be broadcasting live from there, too.
And then, season three of Orange Lounge Radio
starts also in May, and that's gonna be a big deal,
because we have a new toy
that we're gonna be bringing with us.
We can't say anything about it,
because we don't know for sure we're gonna have it yet,
but we're trying very hard.
And we're gonna have a lot more wonderful interaction
with audio-wise movement,
hook the hell out of TVs hooked up to the sound system,
other things. We get to play porn on air and all that wonderful stuff.
It's going to be very interesting. Also, the other thing that's going to be different about
Season 3 is that we're going to have a much larger studio.
Oh, hell yeah. So that should be interesting too.
Hopefully we won't suffocate to that. Okay, so let's see what the chat room wanted
us to plug. Because they do this on late night talk shows. You know, they get to plug whatever
they want when the guests come on. So, is there anything in here anyone would like to
plug? It doesn't even have to be Monty related. Something you want to plug. That you need
to date, do you need any money? As always, of course, it's going to be www.willddr4food.net
slash leech from Loki. Can't forget that. Tomorrow, there will be an update. A couple
hundred files will be coming up online. It's going to be the official stuff. Right now,
we've got prepped, let's see, most of DDR Extreme, all of DDR First through Fifth Mix,
DDR Solo and I'm going to try to get Max and Max 2 done tonight as well as the other smaller ones like OHA and all those. I think I should be able to get those done tonight. We'll see.
So those will be coming out tomorrow.
Anybody else want to plug something in here?
I need SEX!
And if they want to fuck the shit out of you, where should they email?
9-1-6, go cheap.
Or just look for him on the corner of 27th and J.
1-900-FUCK-ASS
Alright, let's go through the shower and see what they want to plug.
Justin's Circuit would like us all to pay a visit to www.sifam.com
I would also like to plug Wil Wheaton.net, just because Wil Wheaton is freaking hilarious.
one l not to
will we done that is a hilarious site will we miss like the coolest guy
i'd like to plug uh... w w w dot rate my rack dot com
i'd like to
i'd like to plug matt damon
getting jokes jesus
set up it
all right uh... i'd like to go on
i'd like to
I'd like to plug, but I can't. Okay, thank you, sorry.
Uh... 23rd Magus says he would like to plug and chug
www.unglued.tk
or ungluedbamani.tk. I'm not sure if they're two different sites or the same
site, but visit them both.
unglued.tk and ungluedbamani.tk. Fear some more and fear him the most.
That's alright. And they're having a cake versus pie
argument in the chat room right now. Quick, quick everybody, cake or pie?
Pie. Cake. Cake. 3.14
Cake. I say pie. But you know what? Cheesecake
owns them both. I like cake though. I like cake better than pie.
Cheesecake owns them both, end of story.
Ice cream cake.
Alright. Cake pie. Yes, cake flavored pie.
For my birthday, I want an ice cream cake. I want a cold-stead one that's cake batter flavored with brownies in it.
I want an erotic cake for my birthday. No, just like in the end of that Simpsons episode.
A cake with boobies?
My dad, for his 50th birthday, had a booby cake. And it was a couple of big boobs that was a cake, and then it had a little bra on it.
And it had a skier, skiing down one of the boobs.
Oh, slopes.
Okay, enough of cake versus pie, we're done.
Alright.
AZHP wants us to plug NBOR3.
Very good opportunity.
I try to plug these occasionally, we all try to talk about our forums, but not enough people
are going there.
You need to visit our forums.
They're at calibomani.com slash NBOR3.
Or you know what, even quicker?
Just go to calibomani.com and then click on forums.
Awesome.
Or go to the Orange Lounge website and click on forums.
They go to the same place, visit the forums, post, they're the best damn forums anywhere.
They're good.
Except for the Gold Club Centerfolds forums, which are better.
Oh my gosh.
That's a strip club, by the way.
If they get so much more activity on the forums, I'm like, what are you doing posting on a
forum about a strip club?
How sad is that that people just constantly visit strip clubs, then they go post about
it on a forum.
I'll tell you what else is funny, the Gold Club Centerfolds forum, which is a strip bar
I would also like to plug Neopets.com. Go there, earn lots of Neopoints, and give them
to me.
Snub Dispenoid would like to say, Paranoid survivor MaxoniSteps has a max combo of 641
and has slides inside the final runs. How the hell can anyone pass that? Just thought
I would share slash ask.
This is not Ask Orange Lounge.
Yes, this is NASCAR. I'm sorry
Because slowly over time playing DVR you will slowly become Asian
Once you've achieved the ultimate Asian status, you will be able to pass that song but only then
Will you be able to pass that song and not before then the machine must choose you
Then you'll become the last starfighter
Japan Man wants me to plug a site that's like a two-year-old internet joke, so when you
find something funny that's new, let me know, because Goat Sei is like two years old, okay?
Dark Tetsuya says that look out for his DWI for love and the angel, it's in the making.
And will he be hosting that on Leech and Wookie?
Who knows?
I hope so.
Yeah, that's another thing about my site, pretty soon it's going to be really easy to
upload files, like, really, really, really easy. So, yeah.
Okay, morethanjake543 says, I need someone to do something that will make Rio shut down
for a day. That's his school. Oh, ratemyhuck.com. Uh-oh, I'm scared to know what a huck is.
I don't know what a huck is. Let's see what a huck is.
Is that like a pecker? I don't know. Let's find out. I hope so.
Is that a cog? It's a cog. Let's see, we're going to ratemyhuck. I wonder
I wonder if it's vomit.
Hux kind of sounds like vomit.
No, because I'm going to rate my huck.
Here it is.
It's a Norwegian thing.
If this is poop or something, I'm going to be pissed.
Oh, it's biking.
Okay.
Alright.
That I can do.
That I can deal with.
Rate my...
Do they have RateMyCock.com?
It's like a bicycle thing.
Okay.
That's fine.
RateMyHuck is acceptable.
Rob, see if they have RateMyCock.
ratemycock.com
Okay, let's see. We're going to enter.
There is a RaidMyCock.com.
Uh, yeah!
What do you guys think?
I still think that the penis is the funniest looking thing in the world.
Praise God for internet porn.
I would give that, oh, I'd say about a five on size.
Style?
No, okay, I'll give it a seven.
Okay, let's go to the next cock. Let's look at the next one.
Okay, we're going to look at one more cock, then we're done.
They have their name, and then they have the cock.
Oh, I want him.
Okay, you have to log in to vote, and I'm not going to log in.
I don't know if you want to rape people's cock.
This is great.
The greatest thing about the site, even if you're straight, this is funny.
I swear, if you're a straight guy, this is still funny because it has their name and
then their cock's name.
That is so photoshopped, okay?
God, I hope the neighbors aren't listening.
More plugging.
Sautome Ron Mo would like to plug www.starmen.net as well as my huge, huge penis.
How many Neopoints do you need, Jamie?
I'm actually about 30,000 away from my next bank account.
I'll take whatever I can get.
My Neopets name is DJ underscore Celica.
Yes, we got a lot of cool new listeners from Starman.net, so go visit them.
Especially if you like Earthbound, which you should because it was the greatest Super Nintendo game ever.
23rd Magus would like to plug Pi, American Pi style.
We don't need to know about your secret nighttime activities involving pies.
And Rice would like to... This is the greatest site. Okay, in all seriousness, this is the greatest site.
Rice is having us plug the greatest site. RYC3 would like us to plug RateMyKitten.com.
It is the cutest site. No, let's go. Let's go. Let's visit it. Let's visit it. Okay.
I should put pictures of Shermie on there.
Let's visit. It's pussy that's actually good!
I want to see more kitties!
I love doing this because all I...you just hear this be ahhh!
We're like one big girl.
Okay, what do we rate this kitten?
He has the cans up the kitten's ass.
Yeah, he has the cans up the kitten's ass.
Okay, here's another kitten.
Ahhhh!
Yes, I like doing this just for the sound effects, okay?
This is great radio.
radio. This Indian's home has dinner already for tonight. Okay, okay, one more just for
the sound effect. Here we go. Ready? One more just for the sound effect. That one looked
kind of mean, so it didn't get quite the reaction we were hoping for. Okay, let's try this.
Okay, it's getting old. Okay. Okay. Okay, go to this side. All right, Rob. Okay, okay,
This is my cat, who owns all cats.
This is Shermy sleeping in a pizza box.
Shermy is a big cat. You've got to realize that when this cat is standing up and walking around, it looks like a soccer ball.
But Shermy is cute.
Very cute, very cuddly, very nice, very sweet and all that. But oh my god, I have never seen a cat get so big.
It's because she doesn't do anything but lay around. I tried to chase her back and forth to make her hop over my legs, chasing the feather.
And then she sat down and was like, you can be the feather to me, bitch.
That's my baby. Isn't she cute?
And by the way, you'll also see a few neat things in the background, like a 32X and an activator.
Some of Jamie's toys.
And you're a keyboard mania controller.
Okay, uh, me and my friend were playing Vice City His Place. Then what happens? He starts firing at some cops when this black man just jumps on the bike.
I think he came from this hole.
What?
So, he found a man whore in Vice City, I guess. It's like some big deal.
Huh.
That's beautiful.
Wow.
More thanjake would like us to plug collegehumor.com and mycathateyou.com
Ooh, the other side of it. Let's see, let's have a look at it.
mycathateyou.com
How's the mean little kitty?
Oh no!
I've seen that picture over e-mail.
I know about that.
About the line.
Oh, these are all like, mean cats.
Oh, that's a cool one.
Okay, okay. This is an awesome site. It's, uh, hctp dot, alright, it's actually, um,
madox, m-a-d-d-o-x dot xmission dot com.
Uh, oops.
No WWE.
Okay, here we go.
The best page in the universe. Oh, is this the one where he rips on the little kid's
arms and stuff?
Yeah, but he, there's much more of that. Let's see here.
Oh, who would make a better President Bush or a box of Tic Tacs?
That's beautiful.
Wait, wait, look at this picture. This is the best.
Um...
Oh, here we go.
Wonderful.
All right, so I'll, uh...
I'm gonna post that to the chat room if they'd like to check out that little ball of joy.
Let's see what, uh, Sharkscroll wanted us to plug.
Oh, she says to tell Jamie that I will send her, Shermie, and horse pics.
Very cool.
Yes, go ahead and email that to me so I can have my tiger horsey.
Callie Bamani wants us to plug topromin.com.
It's a porn site.
Is it?
I wouldn't have guessed.
I like it.
I like porn.
Matt's saying, I like ramen.
Okay, it is a porn site.
Beautiful.
I would also like to plug cospa.co.jp for any cosplayers, it's a site that sells pre-made cosplay pieces, but also it's very good images on things that you can make for your own costumes.
And also tokyostreets.com for anyone who's into the whole fruits fashion, it has pictures of street fashion in Tokyo.
Okay, 23rd Magus would like a way to plug my BWC.
Big white cock?
I don't know.
Okay.
These are the last plugs, you guys, and we're going to end the show.
Get the final thoughts, end the show.
Brack2000 wants to plug emotioneric.com.
Yes, this site is very cool.
Thank you.
Thank you for plugging this.
This is a great site.
This is this guy, and all he does is he emotes things.
So let me show you.
Like here.
God damn, these fucking pop-up ads.
all
for love
mode icon for drunk
and then we get to like kill number three
finding dead body in the trunk
but
uh... freedom
so you motion eric dot com great uh... many as pending requests
he also takes requests like yoga, fire, and things like that.
Okay, uh, what is the request?
Home Star Runner!
Rise Princess, Home Star Runner.
Yes!
I'm sure everybody on the internet has seen that.
Alrighty, late late, ending late, yeah big deal.
So what, it's our show.
Oh, Cali Bamani says, I would never go to a site like that, Sean found it.
Sure.
Alright, that's it, we got all the plugs in, so
Thank you for helping to participate.
I want Loki to read on air the article Maddox wrote about vegetarianism for morals on the Maddox.xmission.com.
You up for it?
I've read all of his articles, so...
Where's the vegetarian one?
Let me find it.
That's the continuity one with Daredevil, the movie.
Let's see here.
Oh, this one's funny too, but I'm not going to read that one.
PETA, preventing suffering.
Wait, that's hate mail, I think.
That might be the one.
It's about the guiltless grill.
Make it quick, we've got to end the show.
Long fucking article.
First paragraph.
PETA stands for People Before the Ethical Treatment of Animals.
Let's ignore that for a moment.
That implies that there exists a universal set of ethics
instead of let's focus on the meat of this email.
that is primarily concerned with preventing and suffering of living animals.
Oh really?
As opposed to preventing and suffering of dead animals?
Good thing they clarified that because I was confused and couldn't infer that they were
saying animals that they didn't mean dead animals.
Glad we have cleared that up.
Let's move on.
Alright, that's enough.
Anyways, to basically summarize that, he's just telling that more animals get killed
in the harvesting of grain than by a sin.
So what he says is, for every one piece of, like, or every steak that they're not going to eat, he's going to eat three.
That's awful.
All right.
And I'm getting asked to play the second song that JB sent me, which I will do after the show is over.
So, let's get to those final thoughts.
Guess first. Zero?
Is he here?
Somewhere, he's hiding.
No, I ran away.
No, um, I guess my final thought is pretty much, um, yeah, have as many parties as you possibly can because they're really fun and you can get drunk and you can make an ass out of yourself.
I have to say in that motion, ass is good but then so is boobs.
Um, okay, I don't think you said ass is good and so are boobs.
I'm sorry, let me clarify. Ass is good, and so is booze. That's an alcohol.
Okay, glad we clarified that. My final thought? Be happy. That's all I got to say.
My final thought is black CDRs are really red.
Vegetarians suck. You should eat all the meat that's possible, otherwise cows go to waste. You care to counter that?
That sucks.
For those of you who don't know, I am a vegetarian.
I don't eat cows or pigs because I don't want a heart attack.
I say we just eat the vegetarians.
I say we kill you and waste your meat.
Cannibalism.
I could go into this, it's just too long.
And then we trap your soul and make you watch your body rot.
Let's see, salad or BEEF!
How's that?
Beef it is!
Sausage is always good for me.
Stop it with the gay references!
Did everybody get to do the final thought except me?
Well, I want to know if Loki would kill his own cow to get his beef.
Oh damn, that'd be fun!
It's all, oof, oof, oof, oof, oof!
In reference to that, Dennis Leary did have the funniest thing regarding being pro meat eating.
and that was, bring out a live cow, I'll carve off what I want and ride the rest home.
And if one of the meat eaters had a heart attack and fell over, we'd just throw him in the pit too. More meat for the meat eaters!
I wouldn't kill my cow, I would get a guy cow and make them have more cows, and then I would kill them and eat them.
Beautiful. My final thought for the day is, uh, Kuntai. Good night!
You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
Orange Lounge Radio is hosted by Dark Sakura, Skye, and Loki.
If you'd like to leave us a comment, send us an email at orangeloungeradioatyahoo.com.
And now, here's your fortune cookie message of the day.
Inform the commander that Lord Vader's shuttle has arrived.
Lord Vader, this is an unexpected pleasure. We're honored by your presence.
Yo, G, I'll be here to see why your homies ain't working their booties off.
I assure you, Lord Vader, my men are working as fast as they can.
We be seein' if they get this ride goin' with 60 foot 7 of black staring down him.
I tell you if this station will be operational, it's not.
Man, don't think of any of you cruisin' down here to check out this ride.
The Emperor's coming here?
Yeah, and he gonna put a cap in your white ass.
We shall double our efforts.
Damn straight! And remember, this be CNN.
Thank you very much for listening, and we'll see you next week.