[SPEAKER_13]: Do you want to hear the most annoying sound in the world?
[SPEAKER_03]: You're listening to Orange Lounge Radio, the Monty Talk, and then some.
[SPEAKER_03]: Orange Lounge may contain adult content.
[SPEAKER_03]: Orange Lounge may contain many four-letter words.
[SPEAKER_03]: Orange Lounge may contain a scene of nudity.
[SPEAKER_03]: Orange Lounge may contain hot monkey sex.
[SPEAKER_28]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_28]: Orange Lounge will not contain hot monkey sex.
[SPEAKER_37]: In this episode... Hey, are there any balls down there?
[SPEAKER_37]: That's the biggest bear you've ever seen, Jingleberry.
[SPEAKER_37]: What's your favorite scary movie?
[SPEAKER_05]: Showgirls.
[SPEAKER_05]: Absolute fright.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's yours?
[SPEAKER_05]: There are no stupid questions, just stupid people.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't torture yourself.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's my job.
[SPEAKER_37]: Now's the time our sprockets made me dogs!
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll get you, my pretty, and your little dog, too!
[SPEAKER_05]: I know Kung Fu.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry, but all questions must be submitted in writing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why did they have to take the word gang?
[SPEAKER_13]: No one expects a Spanish exposition!
[SPEAKER_13]: It's Kendo.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hey!
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, Sky, Loki, Orange Lounge Radio We are live and this is episode number 38 for March 23rd of 2003.
[SPEAKER_28]: Hey, shut up, no buzz this week.
[SPEAKER_28]: We hope.
[SPEAKER_28]: We hope it stays this way through the whole show.
[SPEAKER_28]: You're tuned into the Vimani Scene's most Oscar-nominated radio station of all things Vimani.
[SPEAKER_28]: My name is Rob Roberts, but you might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_28]: Joining me, as always, are my awesome, wonderful, happy, and Oscar-nominated co-hosts.
[SPEAKER_28]: In this corner, in her lovely Versace gowns, say hello to the happiest bunny on the farm, Miss Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_28]: You know her better as DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_15]: I still think it's Versace.
[SPEAKER_24]: In that corner wearing a lovely Calvin Klein garb is Loki.
[SPEAKER_30]: I didn't know Calvin Klein made these.
[SPEAKER_28]: And also say hello to the other folks assembled in here and the lovely Vera Wang.
[SPEAKER_28]: Say hello to Intern Zero.
[SPEAKER_15]: They said Wang.
[SPEAKER_29]: And the Oscar goes to me for coming up with Versnatchi.
[SPEAKER_24]: And also here in a... I'm wearing bum clothes.
[SPEAKER_24]: Who are you?
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, he's the guy who found the Oscars in the dumpster.
[SPEAKER_18]: He's the... No, he's the key grip.
[SPEAKER_28]: Fuck you, man.
[SPEAKER_27]: It's a radio.
[SPEAKER_28]: And then our best boy.
[SPEAKER_28]: Say hello to JB.
[SPEAKER_28]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_28]: It's okay to talk on the mic.
[SPEAKER_28]: Quit giving head to the propel and talk.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's not going to hurt you.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh my god, it's cute.
[SPEAKER_10]: He's turning purple.
[SPEAKER_33]: Whoa, he's getting really red.
[SPEAKER_28]: Wearing a lovely Jolly Rancher face is...
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay, we also have some other guests coming.
[SPEAKER_28]: They're just not here yet.
[SPEAKER_28]: A rice princess is somewhere in the house, but she must be... Oh, she went to get food.
[SPEAKER_28]: We have DDRholic coming.
[SPEAKER_28]: And then we also have Asian Innovations coming.
[SPEAKER_28]: Mike Ngo, you know him.
[SPEAKER_28]: And Dark Child.
[SPEAKER_28]: That'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_28]: If they get here.
[SPEAKER_28]: Hopefully they didn't get lost.
[SPEAKER_28]: You did draw them a good map, right?
[SPEAKER_18]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_18]: I gave written directions and then I drew a map that said which house it was.
[SPEAKER_18]: Because I didn't remember your house number.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_18]: Rob lives at blank, blank, blank, blankity, blank, blank.
[SPEAKER_28]: Hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm moving in a month, so it won't matter.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah, he probably don't.
[SPEAKER_28]: He thinks Pomani's weird enough as it is.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh my god, it's this guy's house.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh my god, oh my god.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, we'll be talking about tons of stuff a little bit more later, including announcing the March Madness 2DX qualifiers.
[SPEAKER_28]: We'll talk to Mike Ngo, we'll talk to everybody, but first, Daikin Kai, the long version.
[SPEAKER_28]: Enjoy, we'll be back.
[SPEAKER_37]: Music, Music,
[SPEAKER_37]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_37]: I'm just a boy, I got beat!
[SPEAKER_37]: I got beat!
[SPEAKER_37]: Thanks for watching!
Thank you for watching
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi everybody, this is DSDS.
[SPEAKER_06]: Make sure to visit SoCalKicks.com and you're listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: We finally accomplished ultimate evolution just now.
[SPEAKER_28]: Hello everybody, you are listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_28]: Live here for episode number 38.
[SPEAKER_28]: Whatever happened to SoCalKicks?
[SPEAKER_28]: I hardly ever see him in the chair anymore.
[SPEAKER_28]: Quit eating everybody.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_28]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_28]: No, my fur!
[SPEAKER_28]: It's kind of a crazy house tonight.
[SPEAKER_28]: No!
[SPEAKER_18]: No!
[SPEAKER_28]: Everybody's all hyper.
[SPEAKER_28]: Everybody's all hyper about the Oscars.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, because Spirited Away fucking won.
[SPEAKER_30]: That's all that matters.
[SPEAKER_18]: I have to make a new ad.
[SPEAKER_30]: What are they called again?
[SPEAKER_18]: They came up with the best name.
[SPEAKER_29]: Shingles.
[SPEAKER_30]: Yes, the Pringles.
[SPEAKER_18]: That tastes like shit.
[SPEAKER_18]: Everybody, go to this address.
[SPEAKER_18]: Rob, type it up.
[SPEAKER_18]: www.sakuramani.com slash scattles.
[SPEAKER_18]: No, I take that back.
[SPEAKER_18]: They're not there.
[SPEAKER_18]: Go back.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's not www anything.
[SPEAKER_18]: Members.aol.com slash darksakura slash scattles dot jpg.
[SPEAKER_18]: I think that's it.
[SPEAKER_18]: I might want to click it to see if it works.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's what I do when I'm bored, is I take products and then make, like, foul approximates of them.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's either .jpg or .gif.
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_18]: But that's what I do when I get bored.
[SPEAKER_18]: I find neat products.
[SPEAKER_18]: It is .jpg.
[SPEAKER_18]: No, not neat.
[SPEAKER_18]: I find products and then I make them, um, a little bit different.
[SPEAKER_28]: You should have made them all brown, though, instead of, like... What?
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm being summoned.
[SPEAKER_18]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_28]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_28]: Question from the chat room.
[SPEAKER_28]: Did the Disney version of Spirited Away win or did the original Japanese one?
[SPEAKER_28]: Well, it would be the Disney one.
[SPEAKER_28]: But that's because... Well, I don't really know why that is.
[SPEAKER_28]: I think that's just because to the Oscars it's the same movie.
[SPEAKER_28]: Just a different language track.
[SPEAKER_28]: But it's still the same visual.
[SPEAKER_28]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_28]: But yeah, the Disney one won.
[SPEAKER_28]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_28]: Wow, what a busy week.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm so exhausted.
[SPEAKER_18]: I was impressed.
[SPEAKER_18]: She pronounced his name right.
[SPEAKER_28]: She probably had a lot of training.
[SPEAKER_28]: Cameron Diaz probably had to be coached backstage.
[SPEAKER_28]: Can I just give somebody heads?
[SPEAKER_28]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_28]: This is going to be the second tournament I've done that's been around times of unemployment for me.
[SPEAKER_18]: Give me a job!
[SPEAKER_18]: That lion is demonic.
[SPEAKER_28]: The lion is demonic.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yes, we have March Madness coming up, which by the way means there will be no live show next Sunday because...
[SPEAKER_28]: will be live all day, Saturday and Sunday.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'll be all over the freaking place.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's gonna be like Shaft was, except I get to do it for two days.
[SPEAKER_28]: And Loki, once again, gets to head up taking the reins all by himself.
[SPEAKER_28]: Hey, what are you guys doing?
[SPEAKER_28]: I will be helping you 90% of the time, but I have to emcee the 2DX tournament.
[SPEAKER_28]: And then I'm going to be participating in one event, but I can't say what.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm doing everything else.
[SPEAKER_18]: You're doing everything else?
[SPEAKER_18]: Well, just on the admin side.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_18]: But you'll be by to say hello, right?
[SPEAKER_18]: Getting volunteers, offering them potato chips and not paying anybody.
[SPEAKER_28]: You'll say hi on the show, right?
[SPEAKER_18]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_18]: It'll be like this.
[SPEAKER_28]: What's going to be really cool about March Madness is that the machine's going to be set up outside, from what I understand.
[SPEAKER_28]: For those of you that are worried about glare, don't worry about it.
[SPEAKER_28]: The staff's already thought about it.
[SPEAKER_28]: They're going to set it up in this tent thing with a lot of tarp, and they're going to set it perpendicular to the sun.
[SPEAKER_28]: They have this all worked out, so don't worry.
[SPEAKER_28]: You won't be able to get any glare on that.
[SPEAKER_28]: So, but what's cool about that, this is the machines outside, we're going to be, for any of those that have ever been to Scandia before, we're going to be out in the gazebo.
[SPEAKER_28]: So, you can't miss us.
[SPEAKER_28]: This is what's cool about Scandia, letting us do that tournament there.
[SPEAKER_28]: They cancelled all the parties, so we could have the party room and the gazebo.
[SPEAKER_28]: And Orange Lounge gets the gazebo, so that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_28]: Children, screw your birthday, we're having a DDR tournament.
[SPEAKER_28]: Word of advice, if you're coming down to the tournament at Sacramento Scandia, and we hope you are, come early, because it's going to fill up fast.
[SPEAKER_28]: Like the parking lot I'm talking about, because there's a lot of people expected to show up next Saturday between the normal patrons and the DDR tournament.
[SPEAKER_28]: So come early to be sure that you can actually park nearby.
[SPEAKER_28]: What are you mewing about?
[SPEAKER_10]: I just wanted to see what you noticed.
[SPEAKER_28]: So how was your week?
[SPEAKER_28]: What'd you do this week, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_28]: Screwed cats?
[SPEAKER_28]: What?
[SPEAKER_18]: I didn't do shit.
[SPEAKER_33]: What's that, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_33]: Timmy's caught in a well?
[SPEAKER_24]: What's that, Timmy?
[SPEAKER_24]: Timmy?
[SPEAKER_24]: Fuck it, I fucked it up!
[SPEAKER_28]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_28]: Timmy's caught in your ass?
[SPEAKER_28]: What?
[SPEAKER_28]: Gotcha.
[SPEAKER_28]: Do anything fun this week, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_18]: Went to a party.
[SPEAKER_18]: Watched Battle Royale.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yes, last night was the big party at Zero's house.
[SPEAKER_18]: We watched Battle Royale.
[SPEAKER_18]: You know, I still miss the beginning.
[SPEAKER_18]: Every time I start to watch that movie, I either catch it in parts because I have to go to the bathroom and do the whole thing, or I miss the very beginning.
[SPEAKER_18]: And I miss the beginning again.
[SPEAKER_18]: Was that the special edition?
[SPEAKER_18]: Or just the normal?
[SPEAKER_18]: I need a special edition now because there's a bunch of scenes that they cut out.
[SPEAKER_28]: Was this the song from the credits?
[SPEAKER_28]: This song that you had very first on pre-show night?
[SPEAKER_28]: Because somebody recognized it.
[SPEAKER_28]: Somebody in the chat room recognized it when it first played.
[SPEAKER_18]: I downloaded it last night when I got home.
[SPEAKER_18]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_28]: I didn't even know what to expect when I saw that movie.
[SPEAKER_28]: Did you know about it?
[SPEAKER_28]: No, I didn't even know anything about it.
[SPEAKER_28]: I didn't even drink last night, so I was actually perfectly sober watching the movie, which at a party is actually a pretty rarity for me.
[SPEAKER_28]: But I'm just kind of sitting there going, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_28]: Everybody was arguing about what movie you want to watch.
[SPEAKER_28]: Some people want to watch Battle Royale.
[SPEAKER_28]: Some people want to watch, what was it called, The Swimmers?
[SPEAKER_28]: The Water Boys.
[SPEAKER_18]: If you want to know more about Battle Royale, now the site does have a good bit of spoilers, but it's a very in-depth site, one of the best I found.
[SPEAKER_18]: Go to BattleRoyaleOnline.com
[SPEAKER_18]: and it actually is R-O-Y-A-L-E You know what?
[SPEAKER_30]: I was curious because in the background of the training video how they had www.br.com I'm wondering if that's... I went to that site.
[SPEAKER_18]: It wasn't there.
[SPEAKER_30]: How about br.co.jp?
[SPEAKER_18]: I didn't try that.
[SPEAKER_18]: Try br.co.jp.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, br.co.jp.
[SPEAKER_18]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_18]: Because there was not a br.com.
[SPEAKER_18]: I looked.
[SPEAKER_30]: Uh, probably not.
[SPEAKER_18]: No.
[SPEAKER_18]: But, um...
[SPEAKER_18]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_18]: But try that site, BattleRoyaleOnline.com.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_28]: Explain the premise of Battle Royale, because we're talking about this movie.
[SPEAKER_28]: We haven't talked about what it's about, for those that don't know.
[SPEAKER_18]: Children do not respect their elders, and the world is thrown into chaos.
[SPEAKER_18]: So they enact this thing called the Battle Royale Act, where they take a randomly pulled class of students... And put them in Iraq.
[SPEAKER_18]: and put them on a deserted island and have them kill each other until there's one left and they have these little collars that make their necks explode in cool bloody ways
[SPEAKER_18]: That was cool, but I like that guy.
[SPEAKER_28]: It was a really violent movie.
[SPEAKER_28]: Like, if you like young children and violence... I like the guy that joined up for fun.
[SPEAKER_30]: That guy kicked ass.
[SPEAKER_30]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, I like the fact that... Sorry, Misako was the best one.
[SPEAKER_15]: I like the fact that they're in 8th grade.
[SPEAKER_15]: The slut was the coolest person.
[SPEAKER_30]: I nominate for best student on the island for the males is gonna go to the guy that joined up for fun, and then of course, you know, best female would be the slut, yeah.
[SPEAKER_28]: I was going to say something profound about the movie.
[SPEAKER_18]: She got six kills.
[SPEAKER_18]: That site that I just told you about, it has character profiles for like six of them.
[SPEAKER_18]: And it actually has the cool slut girl's profile, including her family history and everything.
[SPEAKER_18]: She was a prostitute.
[SPEAKER_18]: And she was pimping out other girls.
[SPEAKER_18]: And she got six kills in the movie.
[SPEAKER_28]: and actually this site is really cool because it has pictures of all of the scorecards so that's really cool and you know what's interesting about that movie what makes it a lot more fun if you imagine it being like 8th graders from your local Roseville Golf Land or your local arcade that pisses you off and then every time they run in front of that area between the pad and the machine that little necklace goes off and they explode hey I'd join up for fun to kill them
[SPEAKER_29]: Yeah, the best thing about that movie, it had the whole 90210 effect.
[SPEAKER_29]: You have eighth graders that are like 30.
[SPEAKER_18]: And you have your different types.
[SPEAKER_18]: You have the slut, you have the prep.
[SPEAKER_29]: Then you have the loner guy, and you have the nerds.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, the nerds were the best.
[SPEAKER_18]: The nerds were so cool.
[SPEAKER_29]: I want a pot lid to kill people with, because that would be so cool.
[SPEAKER_18]: The pot lid saved him.
[SPEAKER_29]: I know, that was the coolest part.
[SPEAKER_30]: I still think Gak did the best, he kicked ass.
[SPEAKER_30]: Oh yeah.
[SPEAKER_28]: You might want to talk about Battle Royale 2, because you're given the website for it in the chatroom right now by Jazz.
[SPEAKER_18]: Actually, if you can get the link out of my live journal and post it in there.
[SPEAKER_28]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_28]: Actually, Jazz just posted it in the chatroom for our convenience.
[SPEAKER_18]: Ah, thank you.
[SPEAKER_18]: Battle Royale 2 is set after, of course, Battle Royale, about three years afterwards, with the survivor.
[SPEAKER_18]: And actually the other, I don't want to go into detail.
[SPEAKER_18]: Right.
[SPEAKER_18]: There's another character who makes an important cameo, as far as I know.
[SPEAKER_18]: On that side, though, there's a cool thing.
[SPEAKER_18]: They have scenes of their rehearsal.
[SPEAKER_18]: I want to play with your pussy.
[SPEAKER_28]: Jamie, please stop playing with Irene's pussy on the show.
[SPEAKER_28]: Ooh, can I fist your pussy?
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_28]: Can you describe what the pussy is here, for those that are shocked and amazed right now?
[SPEAKER_14]: Dead cat.
[SPEAKER_14]: Where did you get that from?
[SPEAKER_14]: Hot gothic.
[SPEAKER_14]: A long time ago, like three years ago.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, man.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's so cute.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, and it's dead.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's got X's for eyes, and it's got a pink tongue.
[SPEAKER_14]: I have a panda for you at my house, by the way.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, thank you.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's got an opening where the pussy is.
[SPEAKER_14]: And it's pink inside.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, the interior is pink.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's really cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: Or whatever.
[SPEAKER_28]: That was a lovely image, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm sure our listeners are happy that we could share that with all of you.
[SPEAKER_18]: There's my cell phone.
[SPEAKER_18]: Here, somebody talk.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, I bet that's my... Oh, we're lost.
[SPEAKER_28]: So anyway, we need to fill a little more time here.
[SPEAKER_28]: Let's look at this profile, this one chick.
[SPEAKER_28]: I guess the chick that makes a cameo in the beginning of Battle Royale 1 has a full part in the second movie.
[SPEAKER_28]: That should be fun.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yes, they are.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, what the hell is this?
[SPEAKER_28]: There's some chick that looks like a Barbie doll that Chaz put in the chatroom.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah, it looks like Christina Aguilera.
[SPEAKER_28]: That's scary.
[SPEAKER_28]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, enough about Battle Royale.
[SPEAKER_28]: Somebody wants to take the mic.
[SPEAKER_28]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_30]: You should have Dragon Ash in the next one.
[SPEAKER_28]: So, how was your week, Loki?
[SPEAKER_28]: What'd you do?
[SPEAKER_30]: I worked on the website.
[SPEAKER_30]: Yes, I know, there's nothing on there new right now.
[SPEAKER_30]: But trust me, tomorrow you're going to be seeing differently.
[SPEAKER_30]: Yeah, I was busy downloading shit.
[SPEAKER_30]: I was actually trying to organize all my sim files because now I'm up to 2446.
[SPEAKER_30]: And I was just putting them in the official categories and CD tagging them and all that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_30]: So...
[SPEAKER_30]: That's what I've been working on.
[SPEAKER_30]: So there should be a huge update, and then I'll finally start doing more regular updates, but they'll be obviously much smaller than this.
[SPEAKER_30]: But what will be coming up hopefully tomorrow, if I am able to zip everything up tonight, would be all the official sets for DDR, everything from first through extreme.
[SPEAKER_30]: So everything that's done so far.
[SPEAKER_28]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_28]: God.
[SPEAKER_30]: and a lot of times people just either make heavy steps or they'll just make basic steps and really annoying shit like that so you have to go back and fix them so that's what I'm hoping to do also with releasing files on my site is it'll allow me to go in and check these files and be able to fix them because you know obviously put them on the internet I want to make sure that they're nice and fixed they have nice backgrounds you know with artists named in the banners and all that wonderful stuff so that's what I'll be working on and
[SPEAKER_30]: You know, just to forewarn everyone, because obviously I'm sure people will be noticing this, all the sim files, you know, the official sets, are not created by me.
[SPEAKER_30]: Yes, I know, shocker, I didn't have the time to create, thousands and thousands of sim files are already done, and already synced, so, you know, I'm just sticking them on my website in case some of these other websites go down, or it's just another place to find them, you know, bandwidth-wise or whatever.
[SPEAKER_28]: Hi, welcome back, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_30]: But there will be some official stuff that will be exclusive to my site, such as the solo non-stops.
[SPEAKER_30]: Those are going to be all done by me, and those are not anywhere to be found on the internet.
[SPEAKER_27]: Very cool, very cool.
[SPEAKER_30]: That's about it.
[SPEAKER_30]: But if you're looking for DDR Extreme stuff and pretty much anything else right now, two sites you can look at would be Abomani Style.
[SPEAKER_30]: They've got a lot of the stuff on there.
[SPEAKER_30]: Or DDR UK, they've just opened their download section again to everyone instead of just level 2 members or whatever like that.
[SPEAKER_30]: So you can go download everything.
[SPEAKER_30]: I swear by Lawrence on that site because he thinks files better than anyone.
[SPEAKER_30]: But I took his files and put the CD tags for Bomani, so I just like their CD tags better.
[SPEAKER_30]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_30]: This is picky, but.
[SPEAKER_30]: They're all up, or they will be all up tomorrow as soon as I upload them.
[SPEAKER_30]: And there's going to be a change with how you download them.
[SPEAKER_30]: It's going to be all through FTP now instead of just through the website.
[SPEAKER_30]: Because one, it'll allow me to update it faster.
[SPEAKER_30]: And two, the FTP's unregulated as far as bandwidth-wise and the website.
[SPEAKER_30]: Normally, you have unlimited bandwidth.
[SPEAKER_30]: They do watch if your site uses a lot of bandwidth, they're going to close you down.
[SPEAKER_30]: And unfortunately, my site is shared with Stepmania.com and a bunch of other ones.
[SPEAKER_30]: So I don't want those going down, so I'm going to take measures to prevent that.
[SPEAKER_27]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_27]: Question from the chat room.
[SPEAKER_27]: Brack2000 wants to know, are you going to post announcer files?
[SPEAKER_30]: No, actually, I could probably do that.
[SPEAKER_30]: I have those.
[SPEAKER_27]: Well, he wants them.
[SPEAKER_30]: Well, maybe.
[SPEAKER_30]: Maybe later this week.
[SPEAKER_28]: What does it feel to want?
[SPEAKER_30]: I made a tower.
[SPEAKER_28]: Another call?
[SPEAKER_28]: People, turn your phones off!
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_18]: I had my phone off, but Mike would not know where we were.
[SPEAKER_18]: Was Mike here?
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_18]: But he's not here.
[SPEAKER_28]: He got ice cream?
[SPEAKER_28]: Did he get me?
[SPEAKER_28]: Did he get me ice cream?
[SPEAKER_30]: Know what else I did this week?
[SPEAKER_18]: We need something sweet.
[SPEAKER_30]: I went and saw Dreamcatcher.
[SPEAKER_22]: Was that any good?
[SPEAKER_30]: Well, the final flight of Osiris was kick-ass.
[SPEAKER_30]: Dreamcatcher, well, Dreamcatcher was a lot of fart jokes, bad acting, and a giant worm alien that speaks with a British accent.
[SPEAKER_30]: I don't understand that at all.
[SPEAKER_28]: Good night, Angel.
[SPEAKER_30]: Mr. Grey, he speaks to the British.
[SPEAKER_30]: But it's hilarious, they've got one part in the movie, because obviously all the aliens look like these giant worm things.
[SPEAKER_30]: Well, they make themselves look like, you know, the traditional looking alien, the grey humanoid thing with the weird eyes.
[SPEAKER_30]: So, basically there's one scene in the movie where they're going to destroy the alien ship, and you see all these aliens going, No, don't hurt us, we don't... What was it like, though?
[SPEAKER_35]: We're not infected.
[SPEAKER_35]: Don't hurt us.
[SPEAKER_35]: We're not... Right.
[SPEAKER_30]: But yeah, Dreamcatcher, it was decent.
[SPEAKER_30]: I wouldn't go see it again.
[SPEAKER_30]: And, well, actually, it kind of sucked ass.
[SPEAKER_30]: But, next week, The Core comes out, and that is going to really suck ass, so don't go see that one.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, um, why don't we go to a quick break, I guess, unless, or is there any other sim news you want to talk about, Loki?
[SPEAKER_28]: Things going on in the sim world?
[SPEAKER_30]: Uh, well, just, that made me as, you know, obviously the CS, watch for the CSV updates for that.
[SPEAKER_30]: Last one they had was from the 6th, so it's a couple weeks old, but they're working on it.
[SPEAKER_30]: And Bomani sells, you know, if you're looking for, like, other sim file stuff, like, you know, for 2DX and that kind of thing, Bomani sells got some, uh, you know, Bomani,
[SPEAKER_30]: They're really working on their Bomani
[SPEAKER_30]: on their Bomani sim files.
[SPEAKER_30]: They've got like a lot of 2DX stuff on there and Beatmania 3 and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_30]: So check them out for everything else because they will have like one of the most complete sim file collections.
[SPEAKER_30]: But DDRUK will probably have the best synced DDR DWIs.
[SPEAKER_30]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_30]: Then of course there's my site which will have just a lot of shit.
[SPEAKER_30]: A whole bunch of stuff on there.
[SPEAKER_30]: So...
[SPEAKER_28]: All right, cool.
[SPEAKER_28]: We're going to go to a break, and we'll be back in a little bit.
[SPEAKER_28]: We're going to do this break, we'll do... I don't know, what song can we do?
[SPEAKER_28]: Let's do something... Wait, wait, wait!
[SPEAKER_10]: I know!
[SPEAKER_10]: What?
[SPEAKER_28]: Play my song.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, scary.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay, we'll play something that Loki wants us to play.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_30]: Here.
[SPEAKER_28]: Da-da-da-da-da.
[SPEAKER_30]: We're loading up a really cool remix I just found on Monty Sims a while ago.
[SPEAKER_32]: Kala kala kuta kuta kuta eh oh eh oh
[SPEAKER_32]: Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_10]: I am a taxi driver man I am a taxi driver man
[SPEAKER_07]: Hiho, Kermit the Fog here, informing you that today's broadcast of Orange Lounge Radio is brought to you by the letter B, the letter A, and the number 59.
[SPEAKER_10]: Can you tell me how to get, how to get to Sesame Street?
[SPEAKER_18]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_18]: That woman is scary.
[SPEAKER_18]: I saw her.
[SPEAKER_18]: Who's scary?
[SPEAKER_18]: The, um, the, uh, Ganguro.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, the chick we were just looking at from Battle Royale 2?
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_18]: No, show that picture.
[SPEAKER_18]: Go back.
[SPEAKER_18]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_18]: Show her.
[SPEAKER_18]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_18]: She is scary.
[SPEAKER_18]: She's gonna be in Battle Royale 2.
[SPEAKER_28]: She looks like Christina Aguilera.
[SPEAKER_18]: She's what's referred to as Ganguro.
[SPEAKER_18]: You know, the super tan, the uber blonde in the panda makeup.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ah.
[SPEAKER_18]: Which, from what I understand, are now a dying breed.
[SPEAKER_10]: So.
[SPEAKER_18]: I got that a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_18]: Paul.
[SPEAKER_18]: Let's.
[SPEAKER_18]: We got that to throw it, Rob.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sniff.
[SPEAKER_28]: Say hello, we got some new guests in the house.
[SPEAKER_28]: Say hello to Asian Innovation.
[SPEAKER_28]: Word up, full shizzle, my nizzle.
[SPEAKER_28]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_28]: Doing alright.
[SPEAKER_28]: Could you possibly be here to promote anything tonight?
[SPEAKER_28]: Is my microphone on?
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah, I think it is.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah, it is on.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_28]: Because if yours is off, then this one's off too, and that would be bad.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay, so I'll turn it off.
[SPEAKER_28]: Are you here to promote anything tonight, by chance?
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah, I'm here to promote Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_26]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_26]: Definitely.
[SPEAKER_26]: We're sponsored by Pringles Original, Potato Crisps, for you that speak Spanish, Papitas Cuyentes, in three flavors.
[SPEAKER_26]: Original, Sour Cumin Onion, and Cheezums.
[SPEAKER_26]: Not to confuse with Cheez-Its.
[SPEAKER_26]: Also, we are also sponsored by Kelby Shrimp Flavored Chips.
[SPEAKER_26]: Remember, they're always baked, not fried.
[SPEAKER_26]: They taste like Long John Silver.
[SPEAKER_26]: I don't like them.
[SPEAKER_26]: I don't know why we're sponsored by them, but we're sponsored by Propel, which is, yeah.
[SPEAKER_26]: We're also sponsored by Triple Black By Triple Black, smearing off ice, which I'm going to get about ten of those later And the guacamole chips!
[SPEAKER_26]: I don't even have to tell the brand because you know how good it is Alright, on to the real topics Next week there's going to be a tournament No!
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah, there isn't.
[SPEAKER_26]: It's off.
[SPEAKER_26]: It's cancelled.
[SPEAKER_18]: Sorry Haha, fooled you
[SPEAKER_26]: Not really, I'm serious.
[SPEAKER_26]: We're not having a tournament.
[SPEAKER_26]: Oh, wait.
[SPEAKER_26]: I was thinking about the Home Run Derby.
[SPEAKER_26]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_26]: Do that again.
[SPEAKER_26]: That's pretty kinky.
[SPEAKER_26]: Also, we have another special guest in the house.
[SPEAKER_26]: Many of you guys maybe have heard of him before.
[SPEAKER_26]: Give it up for...
[SPEAKER_20]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah, I'll remind you, he's been playing since DDR used to cost $18,000 a machine.
[SPEAKER_26]: It's been that long.
[SPEAKER_26]: But back on topic, yeah, it costs $18,000 a play.
[SPEAKER_28]: Are you here promoting anything tonight, DJ Chow?
[SPEAKER_20]: I'm promoting that right now I'm still, most of the way, single.
[SPEAKER_20]: So, yeah, I'm promoting myself.
[SPEAKER_20]: Most of the way?
[SPEAKER_20]: Who's got your other part?
[SPEAKER_20]: Got your back cover?
[SPEAKER_20]: Her name's Susie, but there's nothing official yet, so I don't know.
[SPEAKER_20]: I think I'm still single.
[SPEAKER_28]: So if you want to come on down to March Madness.
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_26]: Alright, there's a tournament coming up, March Madness.
[SPEAKER_26]: If any of you watch NCAA college basketball, you already know the format.
[SPEAKER_26]: If not, let me break it down for you.
[SPEAKER_26]: It's like the WWF, 64 Hell in a Cell match.
[SPEAKER_26]: No, not really.
[SPEAKER_26]: It's going to be 64 people, all in bracketed play.
[SPEAKER_26]: and basically you score off head to head against each other.
[SPEAKER_26]: You will be seeded like the NCAA tournament.
[SPEAKER_26]: So basically if you're from SoCal and NorCal or any other state, we're going to try to keep you guys separate from one another.
[SPEAKER_26]: We're basically going to take your abilities and we're going to rank you accordingly.
[SPEAKER_26]: and every match will be one song only.
[SPEAKER_26]: And the person with more perfects will advance to the next round.
[SPEAKER_26]: And the winner must win six grueling matches because I will make it especially tough for you.
[SPEAKER_26]: As a hint, I guess I'll... Okay, there's 64 matches.
[SPEAKER_26]: I will tell you one song in the tournament you guys should practice.
[SPEAKER_26]: Practice bag.
[SPEAKER_28]: Tee hee.
[SPEAKER_28]: No, I hate that song.
[SPEAKER_28]: All right.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm being told about freestyle.
[SPEAKER_28]: You want to talk about freestyle?
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_28]: The way freestyle's going to go down?
[SPEAKER_26]: I'm also taking freestyle to a new level.
[SPEAKER_26]: I want to get some reality DDR going.
[SPEAKER_26]: So we're basing it off American Idol with DDR Idol.
[SPEAKER_26]: I haven't released this yet, but I will tell you guys the judges now since we're only one week away.
[SPEAKER_26]: Ooh, okay, let's hear it.
[SPEAKER_26]: Alright, of course you guys all know Simon, Paula, and Randy.
[SPEAKER_26]: Our versions of Simon, Paula, and Randy.
[SPEAKER_26]: I'll start with... Randy.
[SPEAKER_26]: He is someone that has the GDR credentials, he's someone that has won tournaments, and he's someone that uses dog in every sentence.
[SPEAKER_28]: So, we can't go wrong, it's Mel B. Oh, yes, wait, wait, I think we might have a little clip of Mel B here somewhere.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, this is Mel B of our team.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah, there we go.
[SPEAKER_28]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_26]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_26]: Alright, on to Paula.
[SPEAKER_26]: Some of you might know her, some of you might not.
[SPEAKER_26]: She's a SoCal DDR player.
[SPEAKER_26]: I know Paula Abdul.
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_26]: She also goes by the handle...
[SPEAKER_26]: She also goes by the handle GoodAttackGirl Her name is Angela Is she sweet?
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah, she is Okay That's all that's important Yeah She'll try to keep Simon in check Alright, good Alright, many of you have been wondering Who is Simon gonna be?
[SPEAKER_28]: Many people have wanted to be Simon, including our own Loki kept begging.
[SPEAKER_28]: We got people in the chatroom begging.
[SPEAKER_28]: But it's already been sealed, right?
[SPEAKER_28]: The deal's been sealed a long time ago, right?
[SPEAKER_28]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_28]: You signed a deal with the devil.
[SPEAKER_26]: Basically, before the tournament even started, I secured my Simon.
[SPEAKER_26]: Because if I would have gotten this person a Simon, I think this tournament would have been on hold.
[SPEAKER_26]: This is someone that won't be afraid to tell you to your face that you suck shit.
[SPEAKER_26]: He'll tell you to your face that he'll never want to see you on the DDR platform ever again.
[SPEAKER_26]: This person will also tell you not to ever put a quarter in the machine.
[SPEAKER_26]: He'll tell you that you're ugly.
[SPEAKER_26]: He'll tell you that your routine was ugly.
[SPEAKER_26]: He'll tell you you can't dance.
[SPEAKER_26]: He'll tell you you're the worst dancer in America.
[SPEAKER_26]: He might even tell you he might be the worst DDR player in the world, or even the universe.
[SPEAKER_26]: But I don't think I'll tell you guys, because I want to keep the suspense for a week.
[SPEAKER_26]: Oh, come on.
[SPEAKER_26]: Just a hint?
[SPEAKER_26]: Okay, I think you guys should know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, yeah, yeah, tell us.
[SPEAKER_26]: He's none other than... Josh.
[SPEAKER_26]: Failure.
[SPEAKER_26]: Be afraid.
[SPEAKER_24]: Be very afraid.
[SPEAKER_24]: That will be fun.
[SPEAKER_18]: Hide your egos.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, so that should be interesting.
[SPEAKER_28]: Sounds like a good group of judges.
[SPEAKER_28]: Now, are you going to be announcing America or is that a wait until the next week?
[SPEAKER_26]: Um, so we don't give away everything.
[SPEAKER_26]: We're not going to have America announced.
[SPEAKER_26]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_26]: Sounds fair enough.
[SPEAKER_26]: And also, um, just to let you know, Ryan Seacrest, uh, we're going to have two co-hosts.
[SPEAKER_26]: So you got Dunkleman back.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_26]: We're going to have two co-hosts, so it's going to be fun.
[SPEAKER_22]: Definitely fun.
[SPEAKER_22]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_22]: You going to talk about who that is, or is that a surprise to you?
[SPEAKER_22]: I think it's better if you find out next week.
[SPEAKER_22]: Many surprises.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah, you have to come to figure it out.
[SPEAKER_28]: Or if you're too far away, like if you're on the East Coast and something can't make it out here, you have to tune in live because we'll be broadcasting it live and you'll find all that out because we'll tell you.
[SPEAKER_18]: I think all those people on the East Coast should just, you know, bite the bullet and get a plane ticket.
[SPEAKER_18]: Ride the Amtrak, use a Greyhound, hitchhike, sell yourself to be at this tournament.
[SPEAKER_30]: And don't worry, Sacramento doesn't really have any large skyscrapers, so you're still good.
[SPEAKER_18]: Folsom has a dam.
[SPEAKER_26]: What about nuclear power plants?
[SPEAKER_28]: They shut down Rancho Sego years ago, right?
[SPEAKER_20]: What about all the Air Force bases we have here?
[SPEAKER_20]: Shh!
[SPEAKER_28]: They all keep getting bought out and privatized.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, so, any other things about March Madness we gotta talk about?
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh my god, oh my god, we should bomb RBGL.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah, that's the only thing you have to worry about.
[SPEAKER_26]: I second that notion.
[SPEAKER_26]: But I will have to say, this is one of the tournaments that you actually want to participate in because last year was so much fun.
[SPEAKER_26]: I mean, going through the 64 people and 32 matches, who really gives a shit about the 7-10 matchup, right?
[SPEAKER_26]: So it ended up being one of the most exciting matches in the first round.
[SPEAKER_26]: Hyperbroken versus Liquid Blue.
[SPEAKER_26]: It's just a little blast from the past, but what happened was Hyperbroken was the number 10 seed, Liquid Blue was the 7th seed.
[SPEAKER_26]: And Liquid Blue was lucky enough to get his song, La Seorita.
[SPEAKER_26]: But Hyperbroken won by one great, and everyone in the building was chanting Upset.
[SPEAKER_26]: Upset.
[SPEAKER_26]: and who couldn't forget Chubbs taking out the number one, Enoan.
[SPEAKER_26]: You know, I think this year there's going to be much more upsets.
[SPEAKER_26]: The way it's structured, one win all the way throughout, so nothing is guaranteed.
[SPEAKER_26]: You can get your song and run the table.
[SPEAKER_26]: Anyways, you want to say anything, DarkShark?
[SPEAKER_26]: Nah.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm wondering if we're going to have our great white ninja.
[SPEAKER_26]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_26]: The Great White Ninja's in Wisconsin right now.
[SPEAKER_26]: It's kind of hard to get a ninja, you know, magically appear here.
[SPEAKER_28]: Well, I have been asked to let it be known to the Asian innovation that the Caucasian innovation, 23rd Magus, will do a max unlimited routine with DDR Idol.
[SPEAKER_26]: Be prepared to have your statements on videotape.
[SPEAKER_26]: Let it be known.
[SPEAKER_26]: Alright, by the way, we will be producing a DVD eventually with this tournament, so if you guys miss it, you will be able to relive all the moments again with commentary.
[SPEAKER_30]: I'm on DVD, sweet.
[SPEAKER_26]: Trust me, this will be just like Jackass.
[SPEAKER_20]: Hey, could my double trick paranoia routine be a special feature?
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah, baby, yeah.
[SPEAKER_26]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_26]: This is how Dick Vitale does it.
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah, baby, yeah!
[SPEAKER_18]: Maybe we should get the bats.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah, maybe Jamie and I will do a reprise of our middle two routine.
[SPEAKER_28]: That'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm actually half-tempted to auction off my orange pad on Sunday.
[SPEAKER_28]: Nice, nice.
[SPEAKER_18]: Auction the bat for charity or something.
[SPEAKER_18]: All five cents it's worth.
[SPEAKER_28]: Fried Twinkies
[SPEAKER_28]: One very cool thing that's going to be run on the side of March Madness is a 2DX tournament.
[SPEAKER_28]: I believe, am I not correct, this is NorCal's first big 2DX tournament, correct?
[SPEAKER_26]: I think so, yeah.
[SPEAKER_28]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_28]: So the very first 2DX tournament will be this weekend.
[SPEAKER_28]: And guess what?
[SPEAKER_28]: We're going to announce the qualifying songs here live, but we'll do that after the FUs.
[SPEAKER_28]: You want to do it right now?
[SPEAKER_28]: Right now?
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, let's talk about it.
[SPEAKER_28]: Now, what's funny about this, only like four people in the whole world know about the 2DX qualifiers right now.
[SPEAKER_28]: Mike doesn't even know.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's his dang tournament, the March Madness, but he doesn't know.
[SPEAKER_28]: But you're going to be competing in 2DX, right?
[SPEAKER_28]: Yes, I will.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, so it would be good to get some reactions from some contestants here live on air.
[SPEAKER_28]: So let's talk about what those qualifiers are going to be.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_28]: I've got to bring them up, so fill time.
[SPEAKER_28]: Tell us more about how the 2DX tournament will work, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_18]: You hit the keys, turn the slidey thing, and you make a song.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's how 2DX works.
[SPEAKER_18]: Really, the way it's going to work is qualifiers are going to have two songs that they have to play.
[SPEAKER_18]: Higher score moves on, basically.
[SPEAKER_18]: And the rest of it's going to go like that.
[SPEAKER_18]: However, for anyone who went to Shaft, the rest of the tournament is going to work very much like Shaft worked, where we have the categories with the songs.
[SPEAKER_18]: And the categories, by the way...
[SPEAKER_18]: In our minds, they're associated with the songs.
[SPEAKER_18]: They may not necessarily be that way in your mind.
[SPEAKER_18]: And it's going to be challenging.
[SPEAKER_18]: We can put it that way.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's going to be challenging.
[SPEAKER_18]: But it'll be a fun tournament, and I don't think anyone's going to walk away from that being really unsatisfied.
[SPEAKER_26]: Unless you start with the qualifiers with V and other.
[SPEAKER_18]: We're not going to go that hard.
[SPEAKER_18]: No.
[SPEAKER_18]: It might get harder though in the later rounds.
[SPEAKER_18]: Definitely would get harder in the later rounds.
[SPEAKER_10]: But we're not going to say anything about that.
[SPEAKER_18]: What about squeezing crotch?
[SPEAKER_20]: Dude, this ferret.
[SPEAKER_20]: These noises he's making.
[SPEAKER_20]: You have to squeeze his crotch to make these noises.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'd be making noises if someone squeezed my crotch.
[SPEAKER_18]: Last week on Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_18]: We don't do those anymore, you know?
[SPEAKER_28]: I got lazy, so I stopped doing those flashback clicks.
[SPEAKER_28]: And yes, we will be announcing qualifiers here in just a second.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm just killing some stuff up.
[SPEAKER_30]: I'll do them when we get in our new place.
[SPEAKER_30]: I'll make them evil.
[SPEAKER_26]: And we're sponsored by Pringles.
[SPEAKER_18]: God.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm sponsored by Propel and the letter Z. Yeah.
[SPEAKER_18]: I thought that was what they said about sex.
[SPEAKER_26]: No, once you pop it.
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah, you don't stop it.
[SPEAKER_30]: Oh, too bad these Pringles taste like shit.
[SPEAKER_26]: Actually, sex tastes like shit too, depending on what kind you do.
[SPEAKER_20]: Dude, I don't know who you're having sex with.
[SPEAKER_20]: It shouldn't taste like that.
[SPEAKER_26]: Well, it depends on how you... Wrong end.
[SPEAKER_30]: That was a cartoon too.
[SPEAKER_26]: We have an unpaid sponsor now, www.rotten.com
[SPEAKER_19]: www.styleproject.com That's S-T-I-L-E styleproject.com Alright, you guys ready to hear those qualifiers for 2DX?
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay, as you know, or may not know, the 2DX qualifiers are in pairs.
[SPEAKER_28]: So you have to play two songs, and you can't pick two songs on the list.
[SPEAKER_28]: Each song has a partner song that must be played with it.
[SPEAKER_28]: So here it is.
[SPEAKER_28]: The first pair of qualifiers is Deadline.
[SPEAKER_28]: Fucking shit!
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_28]: Followed by, oh I should say Deadline 7 Key, followed by the Safari, Light 7
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, it's the first pair, Deadline and Safari Light 7.
[SPEAKER_28]: The second pair that you can pick from is Airflow, 7Key.
[SPEAKER_28]: That song sucks.
[SPEAKER_28]: Sorry, I pulled these really quickly.
[SPEAKER_28]: And the partner song to that is Kochiwo Muteo from 6Style.
[SPEAKER_26]: Okay, I know I'm not going to be picking that pair.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just shoot me.
[SPEAKER_28]: Third pair that you can pick from.
[SPEAKER_28]: This is the third pair.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's Cheer Train.
[SPEAKER_28]: What the hell is Cheer Train?
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_28]: And that's partnered with Abyss.
[SPEAKER_28]: And the third pair is Indigo Vision And that's partnered with Spooky And the last pair is Alien World Well, that's an easy one, but it's partnered with Rizlem
[SPEAKER_28]: All these suck.
[SPEAKER_28]: So... So there they are.
[SPEAKER_28]: Those are the qualifying songs for the 2DX tournament.
[SPEAKER_28]: What the fuck is Cheer Train?
[SPEAKER_28]: You want to hear Cheer Train one more time?
[SPEAKER_28]: Wasn't that a side quest of Final Fantasy VIII?
[SPEAKER_28]: No, it's from VII Style.
[SPEAKER_28]: We'll play some of those during the breaks, so you can get refreshed with those songs.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yes, songs were kind of picked on purpose.
[SPEAKER_28]: Half songs people play and half people don't play.
[SPEAKER_28]: Let me run down those one more time.
[SPEAKER_28]: These are the pairs you can pick from to qualify with for the 2DX Tournament of March Madness.
[SPEAKER_28]: First pair, Deadline, 7Key, and Safari, Light 7.
[SPEAKER_28]: Second pair is Airflow, and pronounce that for me because I'm too white.
[SPEAKER_18]: Where?
[SPEAKER_28]: and the third set is Cheer Train and Abyss.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's both seven key.
[SPEAKER_28]: The fourth pair is Indigo Vision and Spooky, both seven key.
[SPEAKER_24]: Four key!
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, I love this tournament already!
[SPEAKER_28]: And the fifth pair is Alien World and Rizlem, seven key.
[SPEAKER_28]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_28]: Now you can start practicing and picking which pair you think is the best one.
[SPEAKER_26]: These choices suck.
[SPEAKER_26]: Literally, they suck.
[SPEAKER_26]: These songs suck.
[SPEAKER_26]: I already know what I'm doing.
[SPEAKER_26]: We're going by expert score, so I already know what I'm doing.
[SPEAKER_26]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_26]: I think I'm not entering this song.
[SPEAKER_18]: I can pass half of those songs.
[SPEAKER_18]: And the other half I can't.
[SPEAKER_18]: Which one's the one with your train?
[SPEAKER_18]: Abyss.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay, I failed Abyss with like a vengeance today.
[SPEAKER_18]: I got a 12 on it.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay, so...
[SPEAKER_28]: Hooray for that.
[SPEAKER_28]: As promised during this segment, we would get to the FUs of the week, so if we're done talking about March Madness now... You guys done?
[SPEAKER_28]: Is there anything else we need to say about March Madness?
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay, well let's do... Let's do the FUs of the week, and you know, since Asian Innovation and Dark Child have never been here for the FUs of the week, Jamie, you wanted to explain to them how it works.
[SPEAKER_18]: Busy opening my Propel, fuck you.
[SPEAKER_18]: Um, oh wait.
[SPEAKER_18]: Um...
[SPEAKER_18]: That is exactly it.
[SPEAKER_18]: Fuck yous of the week are where you talk about shit you're pissed off about.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_18]: Anything that you want to give a fuck you to, just tell them right now on the air.
[SPEAKER_18]: They may not be listening, but oh well.
[SPEAKER_18]: It feels better to get it out.
[SPEAKER_26]: I fucking hate the fucking gas prices fucking going on fucking right now.
[SPEAKER_26]: You gotta wait your turn.
[SPEAKER_26]: Fuck!
[SPEAKER_28]: So, with that being said, let's get started, shall we, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_08]: This is fucked up!
[SPEAKER_18]: My first fuck you of the week goes for being unemployed.
[SPEAKER_18]: But also being unemployed is a good thing because my life is much more enjoyable since I can go wake up at 2 in the afternoon and go to Scandia, play 2DX for three hours and then go back home and sleep.
[SPEAKER_18]: Um, fuck you to my car still not being tuned up, although they're doing everything they can.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm being patient about it.
[SPEAKER_18]: But, um...
[SPEAKER_18]: It's just been a while, okay?
[SPEAKER_18]: It's just been a while.
[SPEAKER_18]: Also goes for people who can't drive.
[SPEAKER_18]: And goes toward the particular exit from the Boston Market parking lot.
[SPEAKER_18]: And for the woman who looked like a troll.
[SPEAKER_18]: You remember her?
[SPEAKER_18]: The woman in the white car who I seriously thought... You've seen that movie Troll, right?
[SPEAKER_18]: She looked like Troll.
[SPEAKER_18]: Except she was not great.
[SPEAKER_18]: Um...
[SPEAKER_29]: She was going to live under a bridge.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, she was driving to a bridge.
[SPEAKER_18]: And then my other fuck you goes toward not being able to think of anything else to say fuck you to.
[SPEAKER_18]: I wasn't going to say it.
[SPEAKER_18]: Hire me.
[SPEAKER_18]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_30]: There's a big, huge, like, knot in the cord here.
[SPEAKER_30]: I mean, we're talking, like, massive knot here.
[SPEAKER_30]: That's a big, huge knot.
[SPEAKER_30]: FU to Rob for keeping his cords all knotted.
[SPEAKER_30]: Of course, I can't really say much about that because you should see it on my computer.
[SPEAKER_30]: It's like a giant, massive cord.
[SPEAKER_30]: Anyways, um, let's see.
[SPEAKER_30]: I know I had... Oh, yeah!
[SPEAKER_30]: F you to McDonald's for putting their freaking condiments and everything under the cheese.
[SPEAKER_30]: I don't like pickles on my fucking cheeseburgers if I ever ask for them to take them off because that takes extra time and they're slow as it is.
[SPEAKER_30]: So this dumb bitch puts the fucking pickles underneath the cheese where you cannot get at the pickles because they're under the cheese and melted over, you know.
[SPEAKER_30]: So it pissed me off because I was biting into the hamburger.
[SPEAKER_30]: First I looked at it and go, oh look, no pickles on this.
[SPEAKER_30]: and they didn't put any condiments.
[SPEAKER_30]: I bite into it, taste pickle, and then get pissed.
[SPEAKER_30]: So, you're so stupid, you can't even... You fucked up a burger!
[SPEAKER_30]: How easy is that?
[SPEAKER_30]: Fucking a burger?
[SPEAKER_30]: Put this shit together.
[SPEAKER_20]: You're fucking a burger?
[SPEAKER_30]: They're fucking a burger.
[SPEAKER_30]: They're fucking up a burger.
[SPEAKER_30]: Well, that explains a lot.
[SPEAKER_30]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_18]: You weren't complaining, I fixed it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, anyways.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um...
[SPEAKER_30]: I don't know that much.
[SPEAKER_26]: Fuck you to microphones that aren't low.
[SPEAKER_30]: F you to my stupid, your remix, DarkSakura, that's not coming along because it's just, I don't know, not good.
[SPEAKER_30]: F you to me for having a headache and I don't know where it's coming from.
[SPEAKER_30]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_30]: Damn, you know, it sucks because I was really angsty earlier this morning, but then after hearing that Miyazaki screwed way one, I just kind of forgot about everything.
[SPEAKER_30]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_30]: I don't give a fuck about watching an explosion that happened six hours ago, numerous times,
[SPEAKER_30]: all day long.
[SPEAKER_30]: Look, it's bombing.
[SPEAKER_30]: Look, there's bombing going on.
[SPEAKER_30]: No shit.
[SPEAKER_30]: What do you think they're doing over there?
[SPEAKER_30]: Having a rave?
[SPEAKER_30]: Having a party?
[SPEAKER_30]: Is everyone getting along?
[SPEAKER_30]: I don't care about your fucking bombing and seeing the little explosions.
[SPEAKER_30]: If I wanted to see explosions, I'd watch fireworks.
[SPEAKER_30]: You know...
[SPEAKER_30]: It's stupid, and I don't give a crap about half the stuff they have on there.
[SPEAKER_30]: Yahoo News now, there's like, the print is so small because there's so many stupid, you know, headlines on there.
[SPEAKER_30]: I can't read any of it.
[SPEAKER_30]: It's like, uh, soldiers something, something.
[SPEAKER_30]: It's annoying.
[SPEAKER_30]: I just really wish... If I wanted to watch 24-hour news, I'd tune into CNN.
[SPEAKER_30]: I don't want CNN on another station because I'm trying to watch, you know, some other show like American Idol or something like that.
[SPEAKER_30]: My girlfriend watches American Idol, I just watch it with her.
[SPEAKER_30]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_28]: Uh, my FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_28]: You know, I haven't even really thought about these.
[SPEAKER_28]: Um, FU to having nothing to really rant about.
[SPEAKER_28]: FU to still being single.
[SPEAKER_28]: FU to six months without sex.
[SPEAKER_28]: That sucks.
[SPEAKER_28]: FU to being tired.
[SPEAKER_28]: I got tired way too easy the other, uh, I got tired way too easy that last night.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm feeling old.
[SPEAKER_28]: I wasn't even drunk.
[SPEAKER_28]: There's no excuse for that.
[SPEAKER_28]: And, uh, FU to Anita.
[SPEAKER_28]: Wink, wink, nudge, nudge.
[SPEAKER_28]: Just like I did at Faces, baby.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay, I'm older than you, and if you feel older than me, then you suck.
[SPEAKER_28]: F that.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, moving on, let's go around the room.
[SPEAKER_28]: Uh, who wants to start?
[SPEAKER_28]: Start with Zero?
[SPEAKER_29]: My baby's mama.
[SPEAKER_29]: I'm not even gonna say anything.
[SPEAKER_29]: But about, like, watching fireworks, bombs are really, really big fireworks that blow up people's houses and buildings.
[SPEAKER_30]: Yeah, but I didn't see any bodies flying in the air, nothing happening, they're all... Like earlier today, they just had a picture of the night sky, they're all... They're all now... Hold on, hold on, hold on.
[SPEAKER_30]: Hear that?
[SPEAKER_30]: In the distance?
[SPEAKER_30]: There's bombing going on... FALL AWAY WHERE WE CAN'T SEE IT!
[SPEAKER_30]: BUT WE'RE STILL SHOWING THE GODDAMN CITY!
[SPEAKER_30]: WHO CARES?
[SPEAKER_30]: TURN IT OFF!
[SPEAKER_30]: DO SOME OTHER NEWS!
[SPEAKER_30]: I'M SURE THERE'S SOMETHING ELSE HAPPENING IN THE WORLD OTHER THAN THIS STUPID BOMBING!
[SPEAKER_30]: NO, EVERYTHING'S STOPPED!
[SPEAKER_30]: Just for the bombing.
[SPEAKER_29]: No, but I gotta, like, the only thing I really like about watching those is when they make you listen to all the gunfire and all the stuff.
[SPEAKER_29]: You know somebody's dying somewhere, or someone just got blown up, and that's the coolest part about the reward.
[SPEAKER_18]: Fox News showed the caravan, and then they showed camels and goats following the tanks.
[SPEAKER_29]: Yeah, after some stupid fucking guy says, yeah, we see camels out here, and they're very distressed.
[SPEAKER_29]: It's like, whatever.
[SPEAKER_29]: But anyways, back to my FUs.
[SPEAKER_29]: One, I have an F you to, well, kind of war related.
[SPEAKER_29]: There's a stupid guy in the UK and I know he's listening.
[SPEAKER_29]: Stop sending me fucking...
[SPEAKER_29]: Yeah, or IMs over MSN Messenger telling me to go on busy for 15 minutes to, to like, grieve the 15 UK soldiers who died.
[SPEAKER_29]: I'm not gonna go on 15, on a 15 minute busy every damn 15 fucking minutes.
[SPEAKER_29]: You know, you might be an absolute sort of stupid loser, and who the hell cares, get a life, and get off the internet and go do something.
[SPEAKER_29]: Um...
[SPEAKER_30]: Oh my god, say that again.
[SPEAKER_30]: Well, because Dreamcatcher told me that British people are aliens anyways.
[SPEAKER_30]: Giant worm aliens.
[SPEAKER_30]: They're shit weasels.
[SPEAKER_30]: They fly out of your ass.
[SPEAKER_25]: Like Sam Cassell.
[SPEAKER_30]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_29]: My other FU is to my computer.
[SPEAKER_29]: I just got a new webcam, and it'll install it, and then give me a fucking warning every damn time I try to open the stupid program.
[SPEAKER_18]: Give me your webcam, you can have mine.
[SPEAKER_29]: If it works, I mean, mine's just stupid.
[SPEAKER_29]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_29]: Okay, well, I might have to reinstall the thing.
[SPEAKER_29]: But anyways, um, another FU is to, like, the friggin', whatchacallit, like, not having money sucks, but I got money yesterday, though, so I'm okay with that.
[SPEAKER_29]: Um, an FU is to the stupid bastard who decided it'd be a good idea to take off the damn yard sale signs at my mom's yard sale, so I had to go and fucking put up all ten of them again, and if I ever see you again, because I know who you are, I swear to God I will kill you.
[SPEAKER_29]: Another F you is to these stupid shrimp chips because they're too addicting and they make me sick.
[SPEAKER_29]: What?
[SPEAKER_25]: Sponsored by Kelby.
[SPEAKER_29]: Um, that's all I really got right now.
[SPEAKER_29]: Oh yeah, stupid, um, fuck you to the stupid road to perdition, getting the best cinematography, uh, just winning for cinematography.
[SPEAKER_29]: It should have gone to, um, uh, what is it, Gangs of New York, because they actually did really well, and that's all I gotta say, so I'm done.
[SPEAKER_29]: One last thing, you are cool.
[SPEAKER_26]: Alright, first off, um, I wanna give some fuck you's out to everyone that is listening.
[SPEAKER_26]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_26]: Very, very much.
[SPEAKER_26]: Alright, the next fuck you goes out to the Tomahawk Missiles, the Cruise Missiles, and the Patriot Missiles.
[SPEAKER_26]: Each missile costs us about 1 and 2 million each.
[SPEAKER_26]: We're launching billions of missiles on the air atmosphere.
[SPEAKER_26]: You know, all that money that we've been spending on these fucking missiles could be going to the Somalians so we can be feeding the Somalians, giving them food, and building future terrorists.
[SPEAKER_26]: You know?
[SPEAKER_26]: So I think we're killing two birds with one stone right now, aren't we?
[SPEAKER_26]: Alright, yeah, yeah, my next fuck you goes out to Windows XP, today I was trying to, you guys shouldn't do this, I was trying to install a pirated copy of Windows XP, but I tried to get a Windows update and it wouldn't let me because it was pirated, what the fuck, why would I even, I got a corporate version for you if you want it.
[SPEAKER_26]: Alright, uh, fuck you to professional Windows XP.
[SPEAKER_26]: Amen to the corporate versions.
[SPEAKER_26]: Alright, fuck, okay, my next fuck you goes out to all these people on the freeways that speed, that don't know how to drive.
[SPEAKER_26]: Cause on my way to Sacramento today, I was stuck in traffic.
[SPEAKER_26]: No, not because traffic was slow.
[SPEAKER_26]: But some idiots decided to get into a car accident.
[SPEAKER_26]: Yes, they did decide to get into it because they were driving probably 150 miles an hour in a 70 zone.
[SPEAKER_26]: But it's alright because they're on stretchers now and they're feeling the pain.
[SPEAKER_26]: Hint, hint.
[SPEAKER_26]: Don't be stupid.
[SPEAKER_26]: Let me see, where does my next fuck you go to?
[SPEAKER_26]: I had it a second ago.
[SPEAKER_26]: Oh, come back to me.
[SPEAKER_26]: I'll pass it on until I get it back.
[SPEAKER_33]: I'm going to use this mic because it's a bit better.
[SPEAKER_20]: I got a lot of fuck you's.
[SPEAKER_20]: First off, fuck you to all your stupid, high horse, prissy little DDR players that make fun of all those people who are just beginning or you think are just beginning.
[SPEAKER_20]: I know who you motherfuckers are.
[SPEAKER_20]: You guys were laughing at me when I was playing.
[SPEAKER_20]: You have no idea who the hell I am.
[SPEAKER_20]: I'm coming after you fools.
[SPEAKER_20]: Next big fuck you.
[SPEAKER_20]: I'm going to get a lot of shit for this one.
[SPEAKER_20]: Fuck you, President Bush.
[SPEAKER_20]: Fuck you and this goddamn war.
[SPEAKER_20]: Spending $400 billion on this goddamn war.
[SPEAKER_20]: $161 billion would solve all the problems with our education system.
[SPEAKER_20]: Fuck you, Bush.
[SPEAKER_20]: Or free the Somalians.
[SPEAKER_20]: Another big fuck you involved in the war.
[SPEAKER_20]: Fuck you, American media and all your goddamn lies.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, we're the media.
[SPEAKER_20]: We're indie.
[SPEAKER_20]: Not American press.
[SPEAKER_20]: Indie press is cool.
[SPEAKER_20]: I ain't got nothing against them.
[SPEAKER_20]: Let's see, what other big fuck yous?
[SPEAKER_29]: Yeah, media needs to just stop telling us that they know shit, but then say, oh, but we don't know that for sure.
[SPEAKER_30]: Whatever happened to that shuttle crash that, I don't know, took place a while back and then all of a sudden, oh, hey, war!
[SPEAKER_20]: Whatever happened to, uh, what was that guy's name again?
[SPEAKER_20]: Um, what was it?
[SPEAKER_20]: Osama bin Laden.
[SPEAKER_20]: Where's he?
[SPEAKER_20]: But anyways, another big fuck you.
[SPEAKER_20]: Gas prices.
[SPEAKER_28]: What about stories about how ugly Rosie O'Donnell is?
[SPEAKER_28]: Why don't I see those anymore?
[SPEAKER_28]: Because the lesbians gave up on that one.
[SPEAKER_30]: And did Michael Jackson just stop molesting kids all of a sudden, you know?
[SPEAKER_30]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_26]: And we've tried so hard to get Rosie O'Donnell out of our minds, so yeah.
[SPEAKER_30]: You know what's funny about this whole thing?
[SPEAKER_30]: They're never going to catch Saddam.
[SPEAKER_30]: He's just going to slip through again.
[SPEAKER_30]: And we're going to have this all in like another ten years.
[SPEAKER_30]: All over again.
[SPEAKER_18]: I think that he exists in a virtual reality.
[SPEAKER_29]: Osama Bin Laden's hand is up Saddam's ass, that's where he is.
[SPEAKER_26]: Saddam's been dead for 20 years, haven't you guys known that?
[SPEAKER_26]: He's been using one of his doubles.
[SPEAKER_28]: But he has a live journal.
[SPEAKER_26]: So there's one post, because there's one computer that's actually connected to the internet.
[SPEAKER_26]: Good job!
[SPEAKER_20]: Okay, another fuck you.
[SPEAKER_20]: I don't remember your name.
[SPEAKER_20]: I don't remember what you look like.
[SPEAKER_20]: It was at Asian Innovation's birthday party.
[SPEAKER_20]: You showed up uninvited, but with Hyperbroken.
[SPEAKER_20]: No beef against Hyperbroken.
[SPEAKER_20]: Hyperbroken, you're cool, alright?
[SPEAKER_20]: But this motherfucker, tall ass, lanky white dude, he's about 6'3", you might know who he is.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh shit, it's Brad.
[SPEAKER_20]: I only know his call name, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_20]: But this motherfucker, alright, I send money out with Hyperbroken to pick up some drinks.
[SPEAKER_20]: That does not mean this motherfucker can then go and spend some of my goddamn money on his own personal drink.
[SPEAKER_20]: That's what tall, lanky-ass white boy did.
[SPEAKER_20]: If you know who he is, let me know.
[SPEAKER_20]: I want to find his ass.
[SPEAKER_20]: He still owes me two bucks.
[SPEAKER_20]: Motherfuck you.
[SPEAKER_20]: Fuck you to the people who are unemployed and can go to bed and stay asleep till 2 in the goddamn afternoon.
[SPEAKER_20]: I envy all you guys, so fuck you.
[SPEAKER_18]: But I want to have a job.
[SPEAKER_18]: Because I need money.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm not getting unemployment.
[SPEAKER_20]: Oh, that sucks.
[SPEAKER_18]: I could, but I'm not because my man makes enough to support us both, which is enough.
[SPEAKER_18]: But... Hey!
[SPEAKER_18]: Tell someone to hire me!
[SPEAKER_28]: All right.
[SPEAKER_28]: Chat room is demanding we get to their FUs, so here we go.
[SPEAKER_28]: Fuck you!
[SPEAKER_28]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_20]: Fuck the chat room FUs for breaking up my fuck you.
[SPEAKER_28]: What were you doing?
[SPEAKER_28]: Did you have anything else you wanted to add?
[SPEAKER_20]: Fuck you, the crazy-ass women giving us double signals.
[SPEAKER_20]: One minute they hot, one minute they cold.
[SPEAKER_20]: You don't know what the fuck is going on.
[SPEAKER_18]: That just means they're in menopause.
[SPEAKER_20]: At 22?
[SPEAKER_20]: Shit.
[SPEAKER_28]: I was thinking exactly.
[SPEAKER_26]: Okay, I got a fuck you to Sacramento because I cannot find a bank anywhere.
[SPEAKER_26]: When you need money, you cannot find a bank anywhere on the road.
[SPEAKER_26]: Who do you bank at?
[SPEAKER_28]: Wells Fargo.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, Jesus.
[SPEAKER_28]: Go to any store.
[SPEAKER_28]: There's a Safeway up the street.
[SPEAKER_28]: They're 24 hours.
[SPEAKER_28]: They have a Wells Fargo in them.
[SPEAKER_28]: And based on my last fuck you about women, I'm sorry Susie, if you're listening somehow, I didn't mean it Alright, let's get to the chat room DDR Angel says, F you to being halfway across the world when I want to be home and hanging out with Orange Lounge Radio I love you guys And F you to futons that make your back sore, or is that just from sleeping on the floor?
[SPEAKER_28]: Well, anywho, F you anyway
[SPEAKER_28]: 23rd Magus says, F you to popping into the chatroom right when Angel leaves.
[SPEAKER_28]: F you to not having a routine for Mountain Mikes.
[SPEAKER_28]: Or, Mountain Mikes.
[SPEAKER_28]: March Madness.
[SPEAKER_28]: I keep thinking MM means Mountain Mikes.
[SPEAKER_26]: Fuck you for saying Mountain Mikes.
[SPEAKER_28]: Eek.
[SPEAKER_28]: F you to having two essays due tomorrow and not having started.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh my god, what the fuck.
[SPEAKER_28]: DarkTartuya says, F you to being single still, someone date me dammit.
[SPEAKER_28]: I think that's it.
[SPEAKER_20]: Are you a male or a female?
[SPEAKER_20]: Male.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, nevermind.
[SPEAKER_28]: Arcadian42 says, fuck you to my body for being in bad shape this week.
[SPEAKER_28]: I started out with a sore throat that developed into a cold, then went away, then came back.
[SPEAKER_28]: Also...
[SPEAKER_28]: My left foot hurt at the beginning of the week and then stopped hurting and now my right foot hurts.
[SPEAKER_28]: It also kept me from getting anything accomplished this week since I didn't want to go out at all.
[SPEAKER_28]: Fuck you to tailgaters who can't see that you can't move up any farther in traffic.
[SPEAKER_28]: Fucking idiots.
[SPEAKER_20]: That reminds me of a fuck you.
[SPEAKER_20]: Fuck you goddamn pneumonia.
[SPEAKER_20]: Once you get rid of a cold, this motherfucker kicks in and it doesn't go away.
[SPEAKER_26]: Fuck you to bad Chinese immigration.
[SPEAKER_28]: F you to, or I'm sorry, Subdisciplinary says he's angsty this week.
[SPEAKER_28]: So a big fat fuck you goes out to all the people at Fry's for not having metal pads when I really wanted them and had the money to buy them.
[SPEAKER_28]: I call, they say they have them.
[SPEAKER_28]: I get there and they're like, oh, you mean the metal ones?
[SPEAKER_28]: We don't have those anymore.
[SPEAKER_28]: So fuck them for being fucking retarded cousin-humping cock gobblers.
[SPEAKER_28]: Also, fuck you to my current pads for sucking so much.
[SPEAKER_28]: I can't pass any onis on these fucking steaming piles of monkey doo that have arrows scrawled in them.
[SPEAKER_28]: Fuck those poo pads.
[SPEAKER_18]: Cock Gobbler.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's almost as cool as ass meat.
[SPEAKER_28]: No, you missed this.
[SPEAKER_28]: Fuck those poo pads.
[SPEAKER_28]: Also, fuck my new shoes for not being dusty and frippy and shit.
[SPEAKER_28]: I get like 47 greats on Matsuri Japan yesterday and that's too many.
[SPEAKER_28]: I miss my old DCs because they weren't flaming pieces of lemur shit.
[SPEAKER_28]: I can PA about as well as a mouse sphincter now.
[SPEAKER_28]: Wow, that's all.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh wait, fuck you to not being able to go to the Bomani party last night because I wanted to show off my edits in Step Mania Files.
[SPEAKER_29]: It's okay, I'm going to have more, so you have to promise to at least come to one of my upcoming ones.
[SPEAKER_28]: Ness151 says, can I F you DDR Coralville again for DDR extremage?
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay, sure.
[SPEAKER_28]: SkylineDC505 says, F you to Starbucks for being so damn expensive.
[SPEAKER_28]: Japan Man says, fuck all the hair cutters in my city for doing a lousy ass job every time I get a haircut.
[SPEAKER_28]: Fuck the mall for throwing you out for just carrying a skateboard.
[SPEAKER_28]: Fuck my dad for bitching about me doing stuff that I didn't do, plain and simple.
[SPEAKER_28]: No, screw my dad one, oops.
Oops!
[SPEAKER_28]: Fuck the poppin' music non-stop for making me get one good three times in a row.
[SPEAKER_28]: That guy was so stupid, he was in the middle of Madison on a bike.
[SPEAKER_18]: In the middle, crossing traffic.
[SPEAKER_29]: For no reason.
[SPEAKER_18]: What a moron.
[SPEAKER_18]: And that, and he looked like a troll too.
[SPEAKER_29]: You should have gotten another kid's nil.
[SPEAKER_29]: Maybe you would have felt better.
[SPEAKER_28]: Rice, RYC3, says F you to AOL and I'll leave it at that.
[SPEAKER_28]: F you to dumb people, F you to stupid kids at CGL.
[SPEAKER_26]: Alright, I have a fucky.
[SPEAKER_26]: Fucky for all these kids.
[SPEAKER_26]: There are, like, probably 12 to 15 that are thinking that AOL is the only way you can connect to the internet.
[SPEAKER_20]: Big fuck you to all you kids who post comments saying fuck you to other kids when you're a kid yourself.
[SPEAKER_30]: F you to frickin' AOL for ruining the whole theme to the Six Million Dollar Man.
[SPEAKER_30]: You suck.
[SPEAKER_30]: Their new commercial is the Six Million Dollar Man theme, and they fucked it up.
[SPEAKER_18]: See, I don't watch TV, so I don't know these things.
[SPEAKER_18]: I still have AOL, but that's just because I don't want to get rid of my DarkSakura and Killmilder.
[SPEAKER_26]: I have a sentimental attachment, I've had that name for like 9 years now Another fuck you to AOL for being so complicated now, you can't sign on without a fucking GPS system
[SPEAKER_28]: EOSFVB says, fuck you to war, if you can even call it that.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's more like an assault, seeing as how Iraq can't do shit.
[SPEAKER_28]: They've got like three anti-aircraft water balloons and a Nerf gun.
[SPEAKER_28]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_28]: Saddam gasses his own people.
[SPEAKER_28]: Those people suck dick, so fuck them too.
[SPEAKER_20]: Yeah, yeah, fuck that shit.
[SPEAKER_18]: One thing about that, BBC.com has actually a really good breakdown of...
[SPEAKER_18]: What the average quality of life is as far as what people make, how much things cost.
[SPEAKER_30]: They wear pink scarves, goddammit!
[SPEAKER_18]: I just kind of, I mean, I understand what they think the reasons are.
[SPEAKER_18]: My brother's actually in the Marines over in Kuwait right now.
[SPEAKER_20]: Are you going to trust the media that's ran by Tony Blair?
[SPEAKER_18]: Well, apart from that, though, I mean, you can go look anywhere and find the same stats.
[SPEAKER_18]: But I find it very funny that the average doctor makes $45 a month, whereas how much does the average doctor make a year per month?
[SPEAKER_18]: They maybe make $45 a half hour?
[SPEAKER_30]: You know, Iraq doesn't really exist.
[SPEAKER_30]: It's just a giant pool for all the money that Bush is spending right now to go to the Area 51 and Alien Projects things.
[SPEAKER_30]: Really, this whole war does not exist.
[SPEAKER_30]: It's a big, giant cover-up.
[SPEAKER_30]: You heard it here first!
[SPEAKER_30]: Yeah, I think he's trying to compensate for something.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's actually all taking place in the studio in New Mexico.
[SPEAKER_26]: Alright, I want to give a fuck you out to France, Montreal, and Quebec.
[SPEAKER_26]: First of all, yeah, it's not French fries anymore, it's American fries, and call everything Freedom Fries on American toast.
[SPEAKER_18]: They're from Belgium.
[SPEAKER_20]: Okay, about France real quick.
[SPEAKER_20]: How can we say fuck you, because they were going to just go against one of our security resolutions that we proposed.
[SPEAKER_20]: I mean, come on, the U.S.
[SPEAKER_20]: has vetoed over 24 U.S.
[SPEAKER_20]: resolutions that were going to reprimand Israel for what they've done to the Palestinians.
[SPEAKER_20]: And we get pissed off because of one veto.
[SPEAKER_15]: How about Calvin's Quet de Mer?
[SPEAKER_15]: Out of shit.
[SPEAKER_26]: Speaking of head of state, that's going to be a good movie.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm looking at a picture that Jazz posted in the chatroom.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's all greats on Happy Wedding, and thank you.
[SPEAKER_28]: And that'll get you a C, yeah.
[SPEAKER_28]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, anyway, let's finish up the FUs.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm not done yet.
[SPEAKER_28]: Manikinigo Jazz says, FU to having no money because now I can't go to March Madness.
[SPEAKER_28]: Cry, sniff.
[SPEAKER_28]: You need to get up here somehow.
[SPEAKER_28]: And I'm going to jump the bandwagon.
[SPEAKER_28]: FU to being single.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm white, what do you expect, babe?
[SPEAKER_28]: That's it, oh, I have to check the mailbag, but as far as I know, that's it, so Does DDRholic have something?
[SPEAKER_30]: Once again, continuing FU to the DDR Extreme Roulette System.
[SPEAKER_30]: God damn it!
[SPEAKER_30]: Fucking A!
[SPEAKER_30]: Every fucking time I do Roulette, I get one away from Legend of Max!
[SPEAKER_30]: And you taunt me with your goddamn shifting!
[SPEAKER_30]: It goes to Legend of Max, and it's like, Ha!
[SPEAKER_30]: You can't have that!
[SPEAKER_30]: You can have 2D Chaser Morning Mix instead!
[SPEAKER_30]: Asshole!
[SPEAKER_30]: So, FU to the freaking Roulette System.
[SPEAKER_20]: All right, I could go on and on with fuck yous for the whole entire night.
[SPEAKER_20]: If anyone wants to hear the rest of my fuck yous, you can catch me on AIM under darkchild999, that's C-H-Y-L-D-E-9-9-9, or on Yahoo on dchild999, or on ICQ at 110960221.
[SPEAKER_20]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_20]: or you can email me at darkchild999 at hotmail, dchild999 at yahoo, jwilson at wowdy.net, wilsonjason at acmsystems.com, and I could go on and on, but that's enough.
[SPEAKER_30]: I wonder if I should make a Bomani player singles page on my website.
[SPEAKER_26]: That would be funny.
[SPEAKER_26]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_26]: I want to give a fuck you out to Singular Wireless for only having reception when your phone is off.
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't know why what you said just gave me flashbacks to that thing posted on DDR Freak that J-Dog posted.
[SPEAKER_18]: The hi, please date me thing.
[SPEAKER_20]: Fuck you, J-Dog.
[SPEAKER_20]: Fuck you, Jason Coe.
[SPEAKER_28]: Can I elaborate on that as long as we're going to be controversial here?
[SPEAKER_20]: fuck you for being a whiny little bitch because some people made fun of your little slide, slide, slide AM3P routine made fun of it, had a good time and you had a little hissy fit about it oh poor baby
[SPEAKER_28]: Address those cards and letters to D. Okay, so I think we're finally done.
[SPEAKER_28]: Is everybody feeling a little less angsty now that we were able to get that off?
[SPEAKER_18]: I always feel angsty.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm female.
[SPEAKER_28]: You didn't have any FUs, did you, Holly?
[SPEAKER_28]: Do you have anything you want to say?
[SPEAKER_18]: She's playing with the ferret.
[SPEAKER_20]: One more.
[SPEAKER_20]: This one's a big one.
[SPEAKER_20]: Fuck you, U.S.
[SPEAKER_20]: Army, for still having me under obligation until August 23rd.
[SPEAKER_20]: I pray this war doesn't go bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_18]: We can put you on a boat in the cargo hold and send you to Taiwan.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, we're going to take a quick break and we'll be back.
[SPEAKER_28]: And when we come back from the break... What?
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, you want Cheer Train this break.
[SPEAKER_28]: Just for... Dancer.
[SPEAKER_28]: Anything else?
[SPEAKER_28]: Dancer and that's it?
[SPEAKER_28]: Dancer and Cheer Train?
[SPEAKER_18]: and, dude, play Paranoia Clean Mix.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, I'll see what I can dig up for you guys.
[SPEAKER_18]: No, play old stuff.
[SPEAKER_28]: Some old stuff after Dancer?
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, some old school stuff after Dancer and then we'll be back to talk about shit.
[SPEAKER_28]: You're listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
VOG Network VOG Network VOG Network
[SPEAKER_09]: Jojo, Miyato, Wakata, Toshiki, Jojo
Thanks for watching!
Thank you for watching
[SPEAKER_08]: Just one, just one, when I come down, I come down right to the sun Get right down, get right down the fence Round and round, spooks like ghosts in love Stick to the script, flick, back to the script, go down, yeah, yeah Nevertheless, I'm impressed with the best, get to the table I'm kicking the floor, don't you nobody know When I come around, I get down, yeah, yeah, down, down
DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
I'm the best, I'm the best, I'm the best I'm the best
[SPEAKER_28]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_28]: We put your thing down, flip it, and reverse it.
[SPEAKER_28]: Hi, you're listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_28]: We're back.
[SPEAKER_18]: We're talking about horse crack.
[SPEAKER_28]: More derby again.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_18]: And my horse is birdie.
[SPEAKER_28]: So there's all new Bomani CDs, or Bomani-related CDs coming out.
[SPEAKER_28]: I thought we could talk about a few of them.
[SPEAKER_28]: Loki, you might know more about this than I do, but I mean, the chatroom's kind of been talking about this guy on and off tonight, and I thought maybe we'd bring him up.
[SPEAKER_28]: The Kutimu guy?
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, he's got a CD coming out.
[SPEAKER_10]: A dog?
[SPEAKER_26]: You can sync up your VBMS to that Katimo V. And it works!
[SPEAKER_26]: It works.
[SPEAKER_18]: It was cool.
[SPEAKER_18]: The one that you were playing over last night had them doing Butterfly, but you could hear the background music.
[SPEAKER_18]: I think that's how they do it.
[SPEAKER_30]: He just did Felice 100 Seconds and some other one, I forget, with some other song.
[SPEAKER_18]: Rob, you should play that.
[SPEAKER_18]: I tried to find them all.
[SPEAKER_30]: Well... Here, change your encoding to Japanese.
[SPEAKER_30]: Here, I know.
[SPEAKER_30]: Let me find them stuff.
[SPEAKER_18]: Don't step on the shrimp chips.
[SPEAKER_18]: Um, I have it.
[SPEAKER_18]: I think Rob has it, because Rob, we have to play, um... Which one were you looking for?
[SPEAKER_28]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_28]: You guys took over.
[SPEAKER_18]: I didn't do anything.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm sitting here.
[SPEAKER_18]: We have dead airspace.
[SPEAKER_18]: Dead airspace.
[SPEAKER_18]: Here, Anita's going to talk.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, sing for us.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay, so we can't really find the Coutinho stuff right now.
[SPEAKER_28]: We'll look.
[SPEAKER_28]: Maybe we'll look and see if we can get it later.
[SPEAKER_16]: What's new at tonight's farmer's market?
[SPEAKER_16]: An auction.
[SPEAKER_28]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_28]: When did this turn into karaoke night?
[SPEAKER_28]: You want to serenade us with some DDR karaoke?
[SPEAKER_17]: Sing for us some DDR karaoke.
[SPEAKER_28]: You want some background music?
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't know if I know the words to anything.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, aye, aye, aye, I'm your little butterfly.
[SPEAKER_16]: Green, black, and blue, paint like flowers in the sky.
[SPEAKER_16]: Aye, aye, aye.
[SPEAKER_18]: And he just voiced the game.
[SPEAKER_18]: Let's wait for DWI to come out for that.
[SPEAKER_20]: The whole Barry White thing?
[SPEAKER_20]: It's called pneumonia, that's what it's called, not Barry White.
[SPEAKER_20]: Alright, I'll sing the words of one good song.
[SPEAKER_20]: Mommy, play this song, trip machine.
[SPEAKER_20]: Okay, that's the whole song.
[SPEAKER_20]: Asian Innovations turn.
[SPEAKER_20]: I remember we used to have some kind of really good butterfly rethink that we did for it.
[SPEAKER_20]: I don't think he remembers it though.
[SPEAKER_34]: Yeah, I can, I guess.
[SPEAKER_26]: I can't think of anything I want to sing about.
[SPEAKER_23]: I can see the stars, cause I'm in the sky, wherever you are, I'm gonna see you fly.
That was perfect.
[SPEAKER_16]: Okay, if you also think Japanese, what?
[SPEAKER_16]: We have ferret mix.
[SPEAKER_28]: They're suggesting in the chat room that we actually have a karaoke contest at Mountain Mike's.
[SPEAKER_16]: March Madness, David!
[SPEAKER_16]: March Madness.
[SPEAKER_16]: Kick that frecky fresh beat.
[SPEAKER_20]: Alright, am I playing this other Kutimu clip here that we wanted to hear?
[SPEAKER_20]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: Tirole, Tirole, Tirole, Tirole
[SPEAKER_04]: Beautiful.
[SPEAKER_20]: Dude, that shit rocks.
[SPEAKER_20]: That's the first time I heard that.
[SPEAKER_28]: So, now is it true this guy's got a CD coming out, or what's the deal with this?
[SPEAKER_30]: It's not really a CD.
[SPEAKER_30]: He just makes supposed CDs, but they're just a bunch of MP3s that he has.
[SPEAKER_30]: He's doing a non-stop of his songs, and he's doing some new ones.
[SPEAKER_30]: I forget what was on the list of stuff to be done.
[SPEAKER_30]: If you could pull up our forums again, we can check that, because I actually wrote it down on there.
[SPEAKER_30]: But, uh, let's see here.
[SPEAKER_30]: Um, oh shit, I can't remember offhand what he was doing.
[SPEAKER_30]: There's some good ones.
[SPEAKER_30]: I think a lot of stuff from Beat Mania, if I remember correctly.
[SPEAKER_30]: Um, ah shit.
[SPEAKER_30]: Let me see here.
[SPEAKER_30]: Uh...
[SPEAKER_30]: Let's see, he was going to be doing... Oh, here's some of the new tracks he's going to be doing.
[SPEAKER_30]: He's going to be doing another version of TTR.
[SPEAKER_30]: I guess that was... I have no idea.
[SPEAKER_30]: I think that's the Dance Dance Revolution song, the bonus song.
[SPEAKER_30]: Then he's going to be doing Y31, and he's also doing Butterfly as some of the other tracks coming out soon.
[SPEAKER_30]: So, yeah, that's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_30]: and his new CD, The Power of Mouth.
[SPEAKER_30]: Which also will be a pack of DWIs coming out soon.
[SPEAKER_30]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_18]: The Power of Mouth sounds like an erotic title.
[SPEAKER_28]: I know, it sounds like pretty... That should have been one of those rejected erotic songs.
[SPEAKER_28]: We talked about it a couple weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_28]: Speaking of CD releases, topic change.
[SPEAKER_28]: Dance Mania is putting out a whole shitload of albums this month.
That series still exists?
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah, believe it or not.
[SPEAKER_28]: Well, there's no... There's actually... No, the last one that came out was Dance Mania EX2.
[SPEAKER_28]: It was the last one that came out in the actual Dance Mania line.
[SPEAKER_28]: But a lot of these sister compilations... Well, let's think.
[SPEAKER_28]: Let's think.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay, there's been 10.
[SPEAKER_28]: There were 10 of them.
[SPEAKER_28]: No, there were 9 plus another 9, 18, were all the Xs and the ones without the X. And then...
[SPEAKER_28]: Right, okay, so there's 20, okay, right, yeah, there's 20, and then two more, 24, you're right.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay, so anyone, these are the new ones that are coming out very soon, or are already out in Japan, they're just not over here yet.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay, there's Base 11 Hyper Best, which is... Huh?
[SPEAKER_28]: I don't think there's any samples for this one, I... Where?
[SPEAKER_28]: Where's sample?
[SPEAKER_28]: No, it wasn't sample.
[SPEAKER_28]: Um...
[SPEAKER_28]: It has my baby mama on it, so you know this is more of like a best.
[SPEAKER_28]: There's Like A Virgin and Billie Jean.
[SPEAKER_28]: Best of Hardcore.
[SPEAKER_28]: Speed presents the Best of Hardcore.
[SPEAKER_18]: Now that has to be mine.
[SPEAKER_28]: It starts off with Triple J, Follow The Sun, and then goes into some other tracks, Let It Be, Time After Time, 99 Red Balloons, Heaven, Here Come The Noise.
[SPEAKER_28]: And then we have Trancemania 3.
[SPEAKER_28]: It has all sorts of interesting stuff.
[SPEAKER_28]: It has a group called the Porn Kings on it.
[SPEAKER_18]: Cool, I like them already.
[SPEAKER_28]: And then, of course, one more time we get Lasco is something.
[SPEAKER_28]: Jeez.
[SPEAKER_28]: Dance Dance Revolution Extreme, the official soundtrack, just came out on the 26th.
[SPEAKER_28]: March 26th?
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh yeah, how's it going?
[SPEAKER_18]: Gee, Rob.
[SPEAKER_18]: Get your chronology correct.
[SPEAKER_28]: You know, because I said that because I thought I had heard reports that it was released this week.
[SPEAKER_28]: I want!
[SPEAKER_18]: I want.
[SPEAKER_28]: And it has my fire again.
[SPEAKER_28]: It has my fire on it twice.
[SPEAKER_18]: Gimme.
[SPEAKER_28]: No, no, it was just once.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_18]: Gimme.
[SPEAKER_28]: You gotta go to Dance Media and get some.
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_18]: My birthday is next month.
[SPEAKER_18]: Someone buy that for me.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, and that comes out on the 29th.
[SPEAKER_18]: I want actually Best of Hardcore instead.
[SPEAKER_28]: And what's this?
[SPEAKER_28]: Disco Party 2.
[SPEAKER_28]: I guess it's a video.
[SPEAKER_18]: Super Disco Party.
[SPEAKER_28]: So is disco replacing Parapar or something?
[SPEAKER_28]: Is that why they got all these new videos and shit coming out?
[SPEAKER_18]: How to Disco, you shake your ass I need to download that
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm actually downloading Battle Royale, but I'm trying to find the special edition online.
[SPEAKER_18]: Because I need a special edition.
[SPEAKER_18]: I need, you know, extra scenes of death.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_18]: Someone needs to do a music video to Battle Royale.
[SPEAKER_18]: And then do, for the song, is Always Look on the Bright Side of Life.
[SPEAKER_30]: You know, not to like, you know, travel back in time here, but, um, I don't know, DWI contest?
[SPEAKER_30]: We just kind of, poof, forgot about?
Yes, speak on this.
[SPEAKER_30]: I ain't speaking shit on this.
[SPEAKER_30]: I got enough stuff to do with Rain and Website and doing God knows what other stuff.
[SPEAKER_20]: This DWI contest, does that involve alcohol?
[SPEAKER_18]: For Stepmania, we are having a contest where pick a TV song, not a remixed version, not a long version, just a TV theme song, and make steps for it.
[SPEAKER_30]: We have one for Mr. Rogers, and it's kind of stupid.
[SPEAKER_18]: I personally want to see one for Two Stupid Dogs.
[SPEAKER_18]: You've seen Two Super Dogs, right?
[SPEAKER_18]: That shit was cool.
[SPEAKER_18]: I want one for Two Super Dogs.
[SPEAKER_18]: And for Freakazoid.
[SPEAKER_29]: I made one for Funky Brewster.
[SPEAKER_29]: It's so slow.
[SPEAKER_18]: So do it in double speed.
[SPEAKER_30]: No, she's not.
[SPEAKER_29]: She got her reduction.
[SPEAKER_29]: She looked pretty hot in the Pumpkinhead movies, though.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay, first of all, I want to know what you think is more attractive, having really huge boobs and walking with a hunch, or having not as big boobs but still big and walking upright?
Big.
[SPEAKER_30]: This is where you think you're going to get me, but you're wrong.
[SPEAKER_30]: I didn't say big boobs at all.
[SPEAKER_30]: I said she got boobs.
[SPEAKER_30]: Firm breasts are what's good.
[SPEAKER_30]: Firm breasts are the greatest.
[SPEAKER_30]: I don't care if they have to be huge or what, but firm.
[SPEAKER_30]: Firm breasts are what is awesome, okay?
[SPEAKER_20]: If I'm allowed to touch them, it doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_16]: Loki, were you breastfed as a baby or not?
[SPEAKER_30]: Wasn't, like, practically everyone on the face of the earth, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_30]: No.
[SPEAKER_30]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_30]: We know how you... Yeah.
[SPEAKER_20]: Are you an 80s child?
[SPEAKER_18]: I was when my mom used to cloth diapers.
[SPEAKER_18]: I was a natural child.
[SPEAKER_16]: I was told I was breastfed, but I refused it.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm sorry, but... My sister, they tried to breastfeed her and she was allergic to natural milk.
[SPEAKER_18]: So it would make her sick.
[SPEAKER_18]: How does that suck?
[SPEAKER_29]: Like a baby.
[SPEAKER_29]: Like, um, basically when it comes to a girl, I don't want knee slappers, you know?
[SPEAKER_29]: I want them to sit where they're supposed to sit.
[SPEAKER_18]: What on your face?
[SPEAKER_20]: Alright, that seemed a bit too serious for me.
[SPEAKER_29]: What, what on your face?
[SPEAKER_29]: Alright, or anywhere else they need to sit.
[SPEAKER_20]: All right, since he was being us, no, size does matter a little bit.
[SPEAKER_20]: No knee slappers.
[SPEAKER_20]: They need to kind of have somewhat of a firmness.
[SPEAKER_20]: I mean, you don't want them going below the belly button, right?
[SPEAKER_29]: No, really, actually, size is the huge thing.
[SPEAKER_29]: I just don't want, like, when you're going to be 60, they're going to be hanging down to your knees.
[SPEAKER_30]: I don't want you looking like some freaking huge freak with these giant breasts that look like God knows what.
[SPEAKER_30]: And I also don't want you looking like a little boy, so... No, a little boy in J-Cups.
[SPEAKER_30]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_20]: And the Spice Channel presents the brand new Double O Size Bra
[SPEAKER_30]: But you know what's weird, though, is, like, okay, because I took a picture with these two chicks when we went to the Easy Rider Bike Show, and they're, like, some of the models, and they basically, for the pictures, they sit in your lap, which is really sweet, but their breasts were, like, up against my chest, and it just, like, felt weird, because it was, like, unnaturally firm.
[SPEAKER_30]: It was, like...
[SPEAKER_30]: Not rocks, but like, it's like, they're these like, um, balls I've seen where they're kind of like, you know, those inflatable beach ball type things.
[SPEAKER_30]: But they're like, they're a little bit firm, but it feels like an over-inflated beach ball.
[SPEAKER_20]: I think they need to have their sailing changed.
[SPEAKER_30]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_18]: Alright, what I think is incredibly stupid is there's these, um, and they're mostly novelty models, it's true.
[SPEAKER_18]: This was a lot back when I was still in high school, watching Geraldo or something, one of those talk shows.
[SPEAKER_18]: And they had these women on there who had had their chests enlarged to G-size and up.
[SPEAKER_18]: And seriously, each boob was like the size of a small country.
[SPEAKER_18]: It was like the size of a... They could have dropped those boobs on Iraq.
[SPEAKER_18]: Not quite as big as Quaid, I'm thinking more like... Like Nixon's sign.
[SPEAKER_18]: But they were huge.
[SPEAKER_18]: They're going to need back braces when they're 50.
[SPEAKER_08]: If they had their spine out of steel, then maybe that might work.
[SPEAKER_28]: Usually I would be surprised that y'all could talk about her breasts for so long, but then I remember what show I'm on.
[SPEAKER_18]: Don't you have a fascination with boobs?
[SPEAKER_28]: Boobs are interesting.
[SPEAKER_28]: I wouldn't want them for myself.
[SPEAKER_28]: But yeah, boobs are funny.
[SPEAKER_28]: Boobs are the punchline to a good joke.
[SPEAKER_28]: Knock, knock, who's there?
[SPEAKER_28]: Boobs!
[SPEAKER_20]: Sweet.
[SPEAKER_28]: On that note, why don't we get to this week's cage match?
[SPEAKER_28]: What do you guys think?
[SPEAKER_18]: I won last week.
[SPEAKER_20]: What's a cage match?
[SPEAKER_18]: We pick songs.
[SPEAKER_20]: I'm sorry, I'm a noob.
[SPEAKER_18]: Not me!
[SPEAKER_18]: Anyway, the cage match is where we each pick a song.
[SPEAKER_18]: And since we've been into it, one of us will have won last week, so our song remains over.
[SPEAKER_18]: So the other two people will bring in a new song.
[SPEAKER_18]: And chatroom votes on what they think is the best song, but we go around and rate it, sort of, you know, American Idol style.
[SPEAKER_18]: You know, usually with our generous person here.
[SPEAKER_18]: This, the...
[SPEAKER_18]: Bipolar Person here, and the Super Cynic.
[SPEAKER_18]: So, um, yeah, Cynic, you.
[SPEAKER_18]: Um, and then our chatroom gets to vote.
[SPEAKER_18]: We vote after all the songs are played.
[SPEAKER_18]: And I'm special because I won last week.
[SPEAKER_18]: But they hated my song from the week before, so we voted it off the island, and I picked a new one.
[SPEAKER_28]: So... Alright, so we're getting to this week?
[SPEAKER_30]: Alright, real quick.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_20]: Fuck you with obscure Survivor references.
[SPEAKER_20]: Ha ha ha ha ha ha.
[SPEAKER_30]: So, uh, like, um, yeah, I've got my track and everything, but I've got two.
[SPEAKER_30]: So do you guys want to hear a house track or a trance track?
[SPEAKER_28]: A house track or a trance?
[SPEAKER_28]: Do you want to let the chat room decide?
[SPEAKER_28]: Do you want to let us decide?
[SPEAKER_28]: Opera trance.
[SPEAKER_30]: We have, we have, we have either, like, sort of disco-y, but really hard house, um, track, or we've got opera trance.
[SPEAKER_10]: Mmm.
[SPEAKER_28]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_28]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_28]: Beatbox with What A Wonderful World
[SPEAKER_28]: All right, enjoy.
[SPEAKER_28]: This is Loki's pick.
[SPEAKER_28]: The title one more time?
[SPEAKER_30]: Spente La Style.
[SPEAKER_28]: Spente La Style.
[SPEAKER_28]: Or if you just want to vote for it, you can call it Opera Trance.
[SPEAKER_28]: But remember, you can't vote until we've played all three songs.
[SPEAKER_28]: So here's the Opera Trance song.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, that was Spente Le Stelle from Opera Trance.
[SPEAKER_28]: And by the way, that song is also on Dance Mania 20, did you know that?
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah, it is.
[SPEAKER_28]: Anyway, that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_28]: So, goodnight.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay, so here we go.
[SPEAKER_28]: What did you guys think of that?
[SPEAKER_28]: Go around the room.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's cool, and I liked it once it picked up.
[SPEAKER_18]: It gives an 8.
[SPEAKER_16]: I like it.
[SPEAKER_16]: I give it a 9.
[SPEAKER_16]: I like opera stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_30]: It reminds me of like techno mafia music, so I give it a 10.
[SPEAKER_20]: I second that techno mafia stuff.
[SPEAKER_20]: I give it 10 as well.
[SPEAKER_29]: I was severely disappointed so much I gave it a 10.
[SPEAKER_28]: It was okay, seven.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_28]: I have a little bit of backstory to my pick, because I know I'm going to get shit for this, but I don't care.
[SPEAKER_28]: Because everybody tells me I never can pick a song that wins, so I figure, fine, I'm going to go over the deep end this week.
[SPEAKER_28]: But I decided that, you know, everybody says, oh, you've got to pick something from SyFam.
[SPEAKER_28]: That's how you're going to win this.
[SPEAKER_28]: You pick something from SyFam.
[SPEAKER_28]: So...
[SPEAKER_28]: I asked JB, oh give me a song from Syafam that's sure to win it And he said, you know what Rob, this song's very you And I think you'll like it, so I'm going to put this in the cage match tonight And this is DJ Speedo featuring Wild Side And Wild Side is, as you know, the group that did Irresistible Mint from DDR Extreme And the song is called Asoreje But you might know it as a different name And I'm so going to die, but I don't care
[SPEAKER_28]: So, enjoy!
DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_28]: That song makes me want to go to RBGL and murder children.
[SPEAKER_28]: I give it a minus 58.
[SPEAKER_28]: I give it shit.
[SPEAKER_17]: Aw, that song was pretty poofy, pretty poofy.
[SPEAKER_17]: Hey, hey, haha, let's give it a two.
[SPEAKER_17]: Wait, we've got a little... Oh, okay, we've got a curling event.
[SPEAKER_17]: MoCap curling!
[SPEAKER_28]: Hello, Cage Match song.
[SPEAKER_17]: Jason has got a vacuum cleaner head thing, and we've got a little ball rolling, and Mike's rolling the ball, and Jason is vacuuming the floor ahead of the ball.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_17]: Back to Cage Match, Loki.
[SPEAKER_17]: Anyway, here's Loki.
[SPEAKER_30]: Okay, this song violated so many rules.
[SPEAKER_30]: Number one, being a ketchup song, it sucked ass.
[SPEAKER_30]: Number two, it was a speed mix, which really sucks ass.
[SPEAKER_30]: And number three, I'm mad at Syfan right now, so that also sucked ass.
[SPEAKER_30]: So I give the song an A for 100, but the curling gets a 10.
[SPEAKER_20]: Alright, um, I hate that song just because it sounds too much like Happy Hardcore to me, and I can't stand Little Candy Kids, so I'm gonna give it a 3, because it had a decent beat to it, so 3.
[SPEAKER_28]: Asian innovation.
[SPEAKER_26]: Seeing that I left the room because the song sucks so much...
[SPEAKER_26]: I'll give it a, out of a scale of 1 to 10, I'll give it a suck.
[SPEAKER_24]: And, uh, of course, my pick, um, I thought it was wonderful, a 10, alright.
[SPEAKER_24]: That balance is out to suck, doesn't it?
[SPEAKER_28]: And fuck all you who can't take a joke, alright.
[SPEAKER_29]: You sure are a damn liar.
[SPEAKER_29]: And...
[SPEAKER_28]: and Jamie gets a zero for hitting me in the nose with a ball.
[SPEAKER_29]: I gave it a ten.
[SPEAKER_28]: Now I have to get a new nose like Cher, Jesus.
[SPEAKER_29]: I gave that a ten.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_17]: Ron, I thought you'd be happy by getting me hit in the nose with a ball.
[SPEAKER_28]: Let's review what you can pick tonight, shall we?
[SPEAKER_28]: The first one that you can pick, and I have to I have to queue it up because I accidentally got rid of the CD.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, here's the first one you can vote for.
[SPEAKER_28]: Here's a clip.
[SPEAKER_28]: Beatbox with What a Wonderful World, last week's winner.
[SPEAKER_28]: And now the
[SPEAKER_28]: Second one you can vote for, this is Spente La Stelle, also known as Opera Trance.
[SPEAKER_28]: You can vote for that.
[SPEAKER_28]: Also you can vote for DJ Speedo featuring Wild Side with Asareje, also known as the Catch-Up Song.
[SPEAKER_28]: All right, you can vote for any one of those three.
[SPEAKER_28]: Just send your votes right now over private message in the chat room to Sky.
[SPEAKER_28]: If you vote for that, we will kill you.
[SPEAKER_28]: And then we'll tally up those votes and let you know who wins a little later in the show.
[SPEAKER_28]: And goddamn, I hope I win finally.
[SPEAKER_28]: I think there's a lot of people vote for me just because they feel sorry for me.
[SPEAKER_18]: Don't feel sorry for Rob.
[SPEAKER_28]: This is the week I want to win.
[SPEAKER_18]: Just keep in mind, if you vote for that song, you have to hear it for two weeks.
[SPEAKER_24]: That's right, because there's no show next week.
[SPEAKER_24]: So whatever wins tonight is two weeks.
[SPEAKER_18]: So choose wisely.
[SPEAKER_18]: Or we'll kill you.
[SPEAKER_28]: My ball.
[SPEAKER_18]: My ball.
[SPEAKER_20]: Well, your song sucked so horribly we had to entertain ourselves and everyone else who was suffering in this room.
[SPEAKER_20]: So we were curling.
[SPEAKER_20]: It's an Olympic sport.
[SPEAKER_26]: It doesn't get as much recognition as the other sports, but it's pretty hard because...
[SPEAKER_26]: I mean, you have to be really athletic to be a curler.
[SPEAKER_26]: Especially in the Olympics, because you have this broom, right?
[SPEAKER_26]: And you kind of need to know how to skate.
[SPEAKER_20]: And then you also... They have the ice shoes on, but it's still hard.
[SPEAKER_21]: And you have to, like, you know... You gotta keep ahead of whatever... You have to keep ahead of the mallet ball thingy, hockey puck thing they do.
[SPEAKER_26]: Right.
[SPEAKER_20]: Yeah, and pretty much it's like a big lead weight.
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah, for all you curling fans out there, you have to, you know, depending on how fast, you have to get this target at the end.
[SPEAKER_20]: I'm sweating my ass off and we just curled twice and it was only like 10 feet.
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah, and you know, you basically have to use the broom to reduce or increase the friction.
[SPEAKER_26]: It's kind of weird, you know.
[SPEAKER_26]: Simple point.
[SPEAKER_26]: But yeah, the brooms are, only if hockey was played with brooms.
[SPEAKER_26]: Man, the puck would go so much faster.
[SPEAKER_29]: Simple point, it's a Canadian sport.
[SPEAKER_20]: Just remember, look for me in Asian Innovation in the next Winter Olympics.
[SPEAKER_20]: We'll be trying to represent Sacramento.
[SPEAKER_21]: Team Sacramento, curling, 2008, in Beijing when they have no ice.
[SPEAKER_21]: Let's go.
[SPEAKER_28]: You know, you missed the show a couple weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_28]: We were talking about different mocap games that they can make.
[SPEAKER_28]: Mocap curling!
[SPEAKER_28]: Mocap curling.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_28]: That was brought up.
[SPEAKER_28]: We did a list list, which we'll hopefully get to a list list segment tonight.
[SPEAKER_28]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_28]: Although I'm thinking, you know, instead of list lists, you know what we haven't done in a long time?
[SPEAKER_28]: Let's do a Bomani match game tonight.
[SPEAKER_28]: What do you guys think?
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, you wanna do that?
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay, we'll do my money match game tonight.
[SPEAKER_20]: I'm a noob, you'll have to explain again.
[SPEAKER_28]: That's alright, I can explain it to you guys.
[SPEAKER_28]: I can do that.
[SPEAKER_20]: If I can find match game theme on my computer somewhere, I hope so.
[SPEAKER_20]: I could just come up with some porn themes off the top of my head.
[SPEAKER_28]: We'll end the show with Ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_28]: We'll do that later.
[SPEAKER_28]: So, but we'll get to that in a little bit.
[SPEAKER_27]: Because I have to have time to write up questions, so we have to take a break before we go to that.
[SPEAKER_27]: I think he's going to want a filler because he's typing stuff right now.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah, we need a filler.
[SPEAKER_20]: Alright, let's go more porn music.
[SPEAKER_20]: I'm too white for this.
[SPEAKER_30]: I'M GERMAN FOR GOD'S SAKE WE DON'T MAKE PEOPLE LAUGH THIS REMINDS ME EXCUSIVE REMIX, REMIX FREAKIN' MOVIE, MALMOO'S MOST WANTED SUCKS ASS THAT MOVIE SUCKS ASS WHAT IS THE MOST IMPLICATING STUPID PIECE THAT SUCKS ASS BUT NOT THE GOOD MOVIES LIKE BUBBA HOTEP FUCK YOU, FUCK YOU ASIAN BEATBOXERS THAT CAN'T DO IT RIGHT
[SPEAKER_28]: That was the beauty of silence, um, Fox Remix.
[SPEAKER_28]: They're having, they have a request for some impromptu tumu.
[SPEAKER_28]: You wanna do, want some?
[SPEAKER_28]: The, the, you know, talking.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ba, ba, ba, ba, ba, ba, ba, ba, ba, ba, ba, ba, ba, ba, ba, ba, ba.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, my dear good Lord.
[SPEAKER_28]: I think now would be a very good time to take a break.
[SPEAKER_28]: Hey, if you haven't sent in your votes already, there's not that many votes.
[SPEAKER_23]: There's not that many votes in right now for Cage Match.
[SPEAKER_28]: There's not that many votes in right now for Cage Match, which is, you know what happens when nobody votes?
[SPEAKER_28]: The underdog wins.
[SPEAKER_28]: All right.
[SPEAKER_18]: When no one votes, we gang up on Robin, then we win.
[SPEAKER_20]: Okay, if the underdog wins, I put zero votes, zero points for that opera trance, because it sucked ass, and I give ten to that crappy ass, sappy, hardcore wannabe shit.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, so we'll be back after this quick break, and we'll talk about some Babani Match Game and your cage match winner.
[SPEAKER_28]: We'll be back!
[SPEAKER_10]: Where were you to hold my hand?
[SPEAKER_10]: To the things that we have planned Yes, I need you by my side When things go crazy I just need to know you care
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_30]: Welcome to Orange Lunch Radio, where love is orange.
[SPEAKER_30]: Shaving monkeys is always permitted.
[SPEAKER_30]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_18]: But... But it's... You scare the monkey, you don't come in.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, no, I'll just bring Shermie.
[SPEAKER_31]: If Shermie doesn't like you, leave.
[SPEAKER_31]: A proceeding, as always, was brought to you by Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_28]: Hello again.
[SPEAKER_28]: We're back.
[SPEAKER_18]: The monkey sling poo.
[SPEAKER_28]: And I bet you'd love to know who won the cage match.
[SPEAKER_28]: Well, it was very close.
[SPEAKER_28]: And you know what's funny?
[SPEAKER_28]: We had a vote for Oprah Trance.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, I bet Oprah's glad to hear that.
[SPEAKER_18]: She needs to listen.
[SPEAKER_28]: But, I hate to say this, but it did win by one vote.
[SPEAKER_28]: It won by one stinking vote.
[SPEAKER_01]: Ha ha, ha ha.
[SPEAKER_28]: The chatroom conspired again.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oprah Trance won it.
[SPEAKER_28]: by one vote over the catch-up song.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm so mad.
[SPEAKER_28]: Damn you, people.
[SPEAKER_29]: See, they planned it out.
[SPEAKER_29]: They wanted you to make you think you were going to win and then slide in that last vote.
[SPEAKER_28]: I know.
[SPEAKER_28]: They need to make the Big Fat Pickle song.
[SPEAKER_28]: You're plotting against me, I cry.
[SPEAKER_18]: The Big Fat Pickle song.
[SPEAKER_18]: Someone make me a Big Fat Pickle song.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm a cucumber, I'm a cucumber, I'm a cucumber, I'm a cucumber, I'm a cucumber
[SPEAKER_30]: I have a suggestion because I've been noticing that this game is kind of flawed in a way.
[SPEAKER_30]: What we need to do is we need to get the answers from the contestants, but don't read them off and then get the answers from us first, then we get the contestants' answers.
[SPEAKER_30]: You know what I'm saying?
[SPEAKER_30]: Because then that way we're not influenced by their answers.
[SPEAKER_28]: What are you doing?
[SPEAKER_28]: Sorry, Darkchild's using the air duster on his head.
[SPEAKER_28]: Seven people match game, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_29]: We should do it like how we did it with Loaded Crescents and just show each other who brought our answers.
[SPEAKER_28]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay, we'll do that different this week and see how that works.
[SPEAKER_28]: We'll read the contestants' answers last.
[SPEAKER_28]: But, in order to get contestants, we have to have them answer a simple trivia question.
[SPEAKER_28]: What is the formula for a mole?
[SPEAKER_28]: I haven't been in school for a while.
[SPEAKER_29]: She said a bunch of stuff.
[SPEAKER_29]: How about this?
[SPEAKER_20]: What's 75 squared?
[SPEAKER_20]: What's 85 squared?
[SPEAKER_18]: The only thing that I learned when I was in school was how to avoid people and what a mole is.
[SPEAKER_18]: Which, by the way, is 6.02 times 10 to the negative 23rd power.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, how about this?
[SPEAKER_28]: We'll make it really easy.
[SPEAKER_28]: Well, Kogan's boot size was a 16 in 1985.
[SPEAKER_28]: No, I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_28]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay, whoever is the first two people to tell me what the fifth digit of pi is.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay, the first two people who tell me, and you've got to send it over a private message or it doesn't count.
[SPEAKER_28]: The fifth digit of pi.
[SPEAKER_28]: Because that was a big topic on DDR Freak earlier this week.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's I, right?
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay, here we go, let's see.
[SPEAKER_28]: I.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay, the fifth digit of pie is... I think the fifth digit of pie is pie.
[SPEAKER_20]: It's the letter E. P-I-E-E-E.
[SPEAKER_24]: Right?
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay, let's see.
[SPEAKER_24]: The fifth digit of me is my pinky.
[SPEAKER_28]: The fifth digit of pie.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, here we go, here we go.
[SPEAKER_28]: Let's see who got it.
[SPEAKER_28]: We got our winners.
[SPEAKER_28]: So we got three, one, four, one, five.
[SPEAKER_28]: So it's five.
[SPEAKER_28]: Jazz...
[SPEAKER_28]: Jazz said, well, he did say five, but he said four first.
[SPEAKER_28]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_28]: JB got it, so JB's in.
[SPEAKER_28]: He was next.
[SPEAKER_28]: And let's see.
[SPEAKER_28]: Well, it looks like we got 23rd Magus, so there you go.
[SPEAKER_20]: I thought you were counting from the end of Pi.
[SPEAKER_20]: No, sorry, I was not counting from the end of Pi.
[SPEAKER_28]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_20]: That's why I said it, dumbass.
[SPEAKER_28]: All right, here we go.
[SPEAKER_28]: We got our two contestants.
[SPEAKER_28]: We have JB and 23rd Magus.
[SPEAKER_28]: All right, here we go.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, the way the match name works, because you guys, not everybody's been here before.
[SPEAKER_28]: We're going to read questions, and they'll have a blank in them, and we have to fill in the blank.
[SPEAKER_28]: And if the contestants match what you say, then they get a point.
[SPEAKER_28]: And what does our fabulous winner tonight get?
[SPEAKER_28]: Now, they're both locals, so they can actually get a prize tonight.
[SPEAKER_18]: Nothing!
[SPEAKER_18]: Absolutely nothing!
[SPEAKER_18]: You get a free magazine at March Madness.
[SPEAKER_28]: Ooh, a magazine for the winner.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay, here we go.
[SPEAKER_18]: And a half-eaten bottle of Pringles.
[SPEAKER_29]: And a bright Twinkie.
[SPEAKER_28]: Let's introduce the celebrities.
[SPEAKER_28]: First off, celebrity number one, still wearing a lovely Versace gown.
[SPEAKER_28]: Say hello to DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yes, I know, I paid so much for this off my credit card You stole the gown I stole the gown Our second celebrity wearing absolutely nothing and loving it, it's DDRholic Hello everybody Don't look there, look at my eyes, thank you very much Alright, and our third celebrity I'm wearing a dead swan Don't call him a racist or a porn lover, it's Loki I'm wearing a dead swan
[SPEAKER_30]: I'm wearing a dead albatross.
[SPEAKER_28]: Our fourth celebrity is the official Orange Lounge intern, and you know what that means.
[SPEAKER_28]: Give it up for Zero.
[SPEAKER_29]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_29]: This is about to suck.
[SPEAKER_29]: And yes, I'm the damn intern, okay?
[SPEAKER_29]: I'm the fucking intern.
[SPEAKER_29]: God!
[SPEAKER_28]: Our fifth celebrity tonight.
[SPEAKER_28]: Basically came out of the middle of nowhere and somehow ended up here.
[SPEAKER_28]: And he's also wearing absolutely nothing.
[SPEAKER_20]: Say hello to DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_20]: I was taken hostage.
[SPEAKER_20]: Someone please save me now.
[SPEAKER_20]: These people are being mean to me.
[SPEAKER_20]: They're torturing me.
[SPEAKER_20]: They're making me listen to crappy trance.
[SPEAKER_28]: That's what we do.
[SPEAKER_28]: Welcome to Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_28]: Our last celebrity this evening.
[SPEAKER_28]: Say hello to the wonderful and also wearing a lovely Vera Wang gown.
[SPEAKER_28]: Say hello to Asian Innovation.
[SPEAKER_04]: I feel that sexy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah!
[SPEAKER_10]: I know you love me!
[SPEAKER_28]: And then of course me.
[SPEAKER_31]: And wearing saran wrap is Rob.
[SPEAKER_28]: Because I'm beautiful, dammit.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, let's get started.
[SPEAKER_28]: First question.
[SPEAKER_28]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_28]: Mr. Mike Ngo, also known as Asian Innovation.
[SPEAKER_28]: And what do you know, he's here.
[SPEAKER_28]: He was all ready to practice, or I'm sorry, he was all ready to participate in the 2DX tournament in Sacramento at March Madness.
[SPEAKER_28]: But when he heard that he didn't like any of the qualifier songs, he got so angry that he ran over to Scandia and decided to blank.
[SPEAKER_28]: Mike was all ready to participate in the 2DX tournament in Sacramento but when he heard that he didn't like any of the qualifier songs he got so angry that he ran over to Scandia and decided to blank I have one contestant locked in
[SPEAKER_28]: and we have both our contestants locked in.
[SPEAKER_28]: So is all the celebrities in?
[SPEAKER_28]: Yes?
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, Nina's still working.
[SPEAKER_28]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's for your own personal reference.
[SPEAKER_28]: You don't have to...
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, you ready?
[SPEAKER_11]: Dang, Anita, you don't have to write no novel.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_28]: Let's first, now we're doing it different this week, so we have the contestants locked in, let's see what the celebrities said.
[SPEAKER_28]: Jamie, Mike got so angry that he decided to go to Scandia and... Play Prop Cycle instead.
[SPEAKER_28]: Play Prop Cycle instead.
[SPEAKER_28]: Anita, Mike got so angry he decided to...
[SPEAKER_16]: Yodel at the top of his lungs.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yodel at the top of his lungs!
[SPEAKER_28]: Loki got so mad he decided to... start curling.
[SPEAKER_29]: Zero.
[SPEAKER_29]: He got so mad he mistakenly killed the Scandia kids instead of the RPGL kids.
[SPEAKER_29]: Dark child?
[SPEAKER_20]: Mike got so angry he decided to blow my mom.
[SPEAKER_28]: Mike!
[SPEAKER_28]: Mike got so angry he decided to... Kill DJ Syndrome and make a fake song list.
[SPEAKER_28]: Kill DJ Syndrome and make a fake song list.
[SPEAKER_28]: Beautiful.
[SPEAKER_28]: I said, Mike got so angry that he decided to go to Scandia and defecate on a child.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, let's see what the contestants said.
[SPEAKER_28]: JB said, roll on the ground.
[SPEAKER_28]: No, I'm sorry, that is not a match.
[SPEAKER_28]: 23 Magus said, hump the coin slot.
[SPEAKER_28]: He decided to run the Scandi and hump the coin slot.
[SPEAKER_20]: Wow, I actually had to get on the machine then.
[SPEAKER_20]: That's a good one.
[SPEAKER_20]: I like that one.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, can I change my answer to hump the coin slot?
[SPEAKER_28]: No, you cannot change your answer.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_28]: So, no points.
[SPEAKER_28]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's still a tie.
[SPEAKER_28]: Let's go to the next question.
[SPEAKER_28]: Question number two.
[SPEAKER_28]: Darkchild has been out of the Bomani scene a long time.
[SPEAKER_28]: He came back out of the darkness to see what was new in the scene, and he was surprised that the thing that had changed most in the scene was blank.
Wow, that sound of silence is like deep thought.
Okay, read it again.
[SPEAKER_28]: Darkchild has been out of the Bomani scene a long time.
[SPEAKER_28]: He came back out of the darkness to see what was new in the scene, and he was surprised that the thing that had changed most in the scene was blank.
[SPEAKER_28]: Be very, very quiet.
[SPEAKER_28]: People are thinking.
[SPEAKER_28]: Is there all the celebrities about walked in?
[SPEAKER_28]: A couple still writing.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm waiting on one contestant.
[SPEAKER_28]: Any day now.
[SPEAKER_28]: The thing that changed most in the scene was blank.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_28]: Come on, contestant.
[SPEAKER_28]: Hurry it up.
[SPEAKER_28]: Are all the celebrities done?
[SPEAKER_28]: Yes, all the celebrities done.
[SPEAKER_28]: We're waiting on a contestant.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, I think we got it.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_28]: Beautiful.
[SPEAKER_28]: Jamie, your answer.
[SPEAKER_18]: The only thing that had changed was the stench.
[SPEAKER_18]: No one bothered to shower after still trying to PA Paranoia.
[SPEAKER_18]: The stench.
[SPEAKER_28]: All right.
[SPEAKER_16]: Anita, the thing that had changed most in the scene was... Was all the DDR players were now wearing one white glove.
[SPEAKER_28]: All the DDR players were now wearing one white glove.
[SPEAKER_28]: Loki, the thing that had changed most in the scene was... I gotta follow that.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_30]: Um...
[SPEAKER_30]: I didn't really come up with anything funny, so all the DDR players are little kids that are really stupid and should die.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay, all the DDR players are little kids that are stupid and should die.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay, zero.
[SPEAKER_29]: I couldn't come up with anything, so I figured the thing that changed the most was the child molesting gangbangers.
[SPEAKER_28]: The child molesting gangbangers.
[SPEAKER_20]: Dark Child!
[SPEAKER_20]: I couldn't think of anything, so the number of white boys playing.
[SPEAKER_28]: The number of white boys playing, thank you, thank you.
[SPEAKER_34]: Alright, Butterfly is number two instead of number one on Player's Best now.
[SPEAKER_28]: That's a good answer.
[SPEAKER_28]: I put, the thing that changed most in the scene is that kids thought they could actually be cool by doing an online radio show.
[SPEAKER_28]: Anyway, let's see what the contestants said if we have any matches.
[SPEAKER_28]: 23rd Magus says the thing that changed most in the scene was mocap golf.
[SPEAKER_28]: JB says, the dirty little children at Roseville Golf Land had gotten a new soup called Cup of Child.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, going for an inside joke.
[SPEAKER_28]: Beautiful.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_28]: I don't know if that counts.
[SPEAKER_28]: What do you guys think?
[SPEAKER_28]: Who said the RVGL thing?
[SPEAKER_28]: Somebody said something about RVGL.
[SPEAKER_28]: Was that zero?
[SPEAKER_28]: No.
[SPEAKER_28]: Nobody.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_28]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_28]: I say zero.
[SPEAKER_28]: None.
[SPEAKER_28]: Zip, zip.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay, still tied.
[SPEAKER_28]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_28]: Next question.
[SPEAKER_28]: Jamie one day found herself on a deserted island with a shiny necklace on.
[SPEAKER_28]: She noticed that she was surrounded by children from Roseville Golf Land.
[SPEAKER_28]: The first thing she reached for was her blank.
[SPEAKER_28]: Jamie one day found herself on a deserted island with a shiny necklace on.
[SPEAKER_28]: She noticed that she was surrounded by children from Roseville Golf Land.
[SPEAKER_28]: The first thing she reached for was her blank.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, we have both our contestants in.
[SPEAKER_28]: How about the celebrities?
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay, working on it.
[SPEAKER_28]: How are you doing, Anita?
[SPEAKER_28]: About ready?
[SPEAKER_28]: Almost done.
[SPEAKER_28]: Anita doing another marathon answer.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_28]: woke up on a deserted island with a shiny necklace on.
[SPEAKER_28]: She noticed she was surrounded by children from Roseville Golf Land.
[SPEAKER_28]: The first thing she reached for was her blank.
[SPEAKER_28]: Ready?
[SPEAKER_28]: Jamie, what was the first thing Jamie reached for?
[SPEAKER_18]: Propel.
[SPEAKER_18]: RPGL children are easy targets.
[SPEAKER_16]: All right, Anita, the first thing she reached for was her... Was her coconut nunchakus to open up a can of whoop-ass.
[SPEAKER_28]: Her coconut nunchakus.
Loki.
[SPEAKER_28]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_30]: It should be obvious.
[SPEAKER_30]: Orange bat.
[SPEAKER_28]: Her orange bat!
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh!
[SPEAKER_28]: Good answer!
[SPEAKER_29]: Zero, the first thing she reached for was her... Well, with Jamie being surrounded by RVGL kids with their shiny new necklace on, I say, she reached for her necklace to take it off.
[SPEAKER_28]: Being surrounded by Rosal Goughland children, I'm... You know, I reached for my own.
[SPEAKER_18]: Dude, I just ripped theirs off.
[SPEAKER_20]: Dark Child.
[SPEAKER_20]: God, my mind is dirty.
[SPEAKER_20]: A jizz rag to wipe off that shiny necklace.
[SPEAKER_10]: I need to stay off the internet.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh my lord.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay, Asian Invasion.
[SPEAKER_24]: After that happened, the first thing she reached for was her... Immediately after that, she reached for her crack pipe.
[SPEAKER_28]: Jamie!
[SPEAKER_28]: You have a crack pipe?
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_28]: I said the first thing she reached for was her fan.
[SPEAKER_28]: Remember the movie?
[SPEAKER_28]: The guy with the fan?
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah, alright.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_28]: JB said the first thing she reached for... Let's check for a match.
[SPEAKER_28]: I said the fan was cool.
[SPEAKER_28]: We're going to check for a match.
[SPEAKER_28]: JB said the first thing she reached for was a fork.
[SPEAKER_28]: I almost said that.
[SPEAKER_18]: I almost said fork.
[SPEAKER_18]: But then again, RPGL children have herpes.
[SPEAKER_28]: 23rd Magus said the first thing she reached for was her boomstick.
[SPEAKER_33]: Good movie reference.
[SPEAKER_33]: Very good movie reference.
[SPEAKER_33]: Sam Raimi is God.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's still tied up.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's still tied up at nothing, nothing.
[SPEAKER_34]: Alright, let's go on to the next one.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_28]: Loki!
[SPEAKER_28]: Loki was really excited to be moving into a new apartment very soon.
[SPEAKER_28]: A couple days before the move, though, he started to worry.
[SPEAKER_28]: What am I going to do about packing my massive collection of blank?
[SPEAKER_28]: It doesn't have to be the obvious.
[SPEAKER_28]: Do whatever you want.
[SPEAKER_28]: You've got to want to match the contestants.
[SPEAKER_28]: Do say what the contestants would say.
[SPEAKER_28]: Loki was really excited to be moving into a new apartment very soon.
[SPEAKER_28]: A couple days before the move, though, he started to worry.
[SPEAKER_28]: What am I going to do about packing my massive collection of blank?
[SPEAKER_18]: I came up with an answer very quickly.
[SPEAKER_28]: We have one contestant locked in.
[SPEAKER_28]: I think that's both contestants.
[SPEAKER_28]: All right.
[SPEAKER_28]: Are all the celebrities ready?
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, I'm almost ready.
[SPEAKER_15]: Almost.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: How do you spell... Never mind.
[SPEAKER_15]: How do you spell V?
[SPEAKER_18]: V?
[SPEAKER_28]: All right, here we go, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_28]: Loki had to pack his massive collection of... Corpses.
[SPEAKER_28]: Corpses!
[SPEAKER_18]: Good idea.
[SPEAKER_28]: Anita said, what am I going to do about packing my massive collection of... Of Barbie dolls.
[SPEAKER_28]: Barbie dolls.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, so cute.
[SPEAKER_30]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_30]: Dead babies.
[SPEAKER_30]: Dead babies!
[SPEAKER_06]: Zero.
[SPEAKER_28]: I said shit.
[SPEAKER_28]: Massive collection of shit.
[SPEAKER_28]: How nice.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_28]: Dark Child.
[SPEAKER_20]: Real dolls.
[SPEAKER_28]: Real dolls.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh!
[SPEAKER_28]: You know the... The...
[SPEAKER_20]: For those who don't know, they're really high-end, non-blow-up girlfriends.
[SPEAKER_20]: I mean, fully articulate, they look realistic.
[SPEAKER_18]: On Real Sex, a guy's girlfriend... And they have men ones, too, with, like, big cocks.
[SPEAKER_20]: I don't care about the men ones.
[SPEAKER_18]: And they said that they were working on ones that actually came.
[SPEAKER_20]: RealDoll.com
[SPEAKER_20]: I'm sorry, not a match.
[SPEAKER_28]: I said, Loki, what is he going to do about packing his massive collection of cock rings?
[SPEAKER_28]: Cock rings, God.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, let's see what the contestants said.
[SPEAKER_28]: Let's see if we get a match.
[SPEAKER_28]: 23rd Magus says, What is Loki going to do about packing his massive collection of porn?
[SPEAKER_28]: JB says, What is he going to do about packing his massive collection of porn?
[SPEAKER_28]: Both contestants said porn.
[SPEAKER_28]: No match.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's funny that all the underage people think of porn.
[SPEAKER_28]: Shame on all of you perverts.
[SPEAKER_18]: We think of murder, right?
[SPEAKER_30]: I don't have a massive collection of porn.
[SPEAKER_30]: It's way outweighed by the massive collection of dead babies.
[SPEAKER_20]: Last question.
[SPEAKER_20]: This is your chance to shine.
[SPEAKER_20]: Just to be fair, I was going to say porn, but I thought someone else in the group would have already taken it.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, well, it's still tied up.
[SPEAKER_18]: Nothing, nothing.
[SPEAKER_18]: Here's your last question.
[SPEAKER_28]: Rob got made a lot of fun of for playing the catch-up song on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_28]: After the show was over, the room decided that his punishment should be blank.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, Rob got made a lot of fun of for playing the catch-up song on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay, we have both our contestants locked in.
[SPEAKER_28]: Is everybody else in the room?
[SPEAKER_28]: Anita?
I'm just writing my chapters.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay, here we go.
[SPEAKER_28]: Jamie, his punishment should be?
[SPEAKER_18]: To drink his weight in ketchup.
[SPEAKER_28]: To drink his weight in ketchup.
[SPEAKER_28]: That's a lot of ketchup.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, I didn't get quite as creative.
[SPEAKER_16]: Your punishment shall be to watch 24 hours of the Playboy channel.
[SPEAKER_28]: God, and softcore at that.
[SPEAKER_28]: Jesus.
[SPEAKER_28]: At least it was hardcore.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's somewhat exciting.
[SPEAKER_30]: You would fall asleep after about two minutes.
[SPEAKER_28]: I would seriously.
[SPEAKER_30]: I would fall asleep after about, like, a few minutes of that.
[SPEAKER_30]: It's awful.
[SPEAKER_28]: About five minutes for Loki?
[SPEAKER_30]: Uh, serious.
[SPEAKER_35]: It's just like, look at me.
[SPEAKER_35]: I'm rubbing my breasts.
[SPEAKER_30]: I mean, it's just like, who cares?
[SPEAKER_30]: It's so, why are you, like, sneaking into some person's house to rub your breasts?
[SPEAKER_30]: It makes no sense.
[SPEAKER_30]: Yeah, but it makes no sense when you're just standing there going, oh, look at me.
[SPEAKER_30]: I'm standing here in the wind, exotic location, rubbing my breasts for no reason.
[SPEAKER_30]: Just standing there.
[SPEAKER_30]: She's not having sex.
[SPEAKER_30]: She's not, like, you know, getting it on or anything.
[SPEAKER_30]: She's just standing there saying, look at me.
[SPEAKER_30]: I'm sexy looking.
[SPEAKER_20]: If you had the Playboy channel on my house, I'd end up turning it to CNN.
[SPEAKER_30]: Dude, let's put it this way, I get every single Playboy movie that comes out, and they all suck ass.
[SPEAKER_30]: They're all regurgitated clips from older Playboy movies, and it's just, it's awful, they try to think... Girl's gone boring.
[SPEAKER_30]: Okay, my answer was, punishment would be Rob would have to go straight.
[SPEAKER_29]: I almost said that.
[SPEAKER_29]: And by the way, they probably rub their breasts because it's cold on the beach, they gotta get warm.
[SPEAKER_30]: I don't understand how their nipples stick out all the time.
[SPEAKER_30]: How is that possible?
[SPEAKER_30]: Ice cubes, but... No, I don't want them.
[SPEAKER_29]: I said... It's called airbrushing.
[SPEAKER_29]: I said... I said at the end of the show, Rob would have to fuck... the ferret.
[SPEAKER_28]: How lovely.
[SPEAKER_28]: Dark Child.
[SPEAKER_20]: Rob's punishment should be... Jesus Christ, I am a child of the internet.
[SPEAKER_20]: Go down on everyone in the room and swallow.
[SPEAKER_28]: Ah!
[SPEAKER_28]: That is punishment, Jesus.
[SPEAKER_28]: That's punishment for everybody.
[SPEAKER_28]: You get to sell popcorn, there'll be plenty of salt.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's an innovation.
[SPEAKER_18]: Porn is the funniest thing ever.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's not exciting or anything.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's just funny.
[SPEAKER_22]: Easy and innovation.
[SPEAKER_28]: Rob's punishment should be the ketchup song.
[SPEAKER_28]: Good.
[SPEAKER_28]: Good answer.
[SPEAKER_28]: And my answer would be that Rob's punishment should be to have sex with lots of hot people.
[SPEAKER_28]: It sounds like a great punishment to me.
[SPEAKER_18]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_18]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_18]: Say that again.
[SPEAKER_30]: Who have leprosy?
[SPEAKER_18]: Rob, hand.
[SPEAKER_28]: Let's see if we actually got a match.
[SPEAKER_28]: JB said Rob's punishment should be to be spanked.
[SPEAKER_28]: That's a reward, babe.
[SPEAKER_28]: It depends who by.
[SPEAKER_28]: I mean, if we're talking like, you know, never mind.
[SPEAKER_28]: 23rd Magus said his punishment should be to be beaten with orange bats.
[SPEAKER_29]: Nobody said go straight.
[SPEAKER_29]: You guys could not have said go straight.
[SPEAKER_29]: That was the most obvious answer.
[SPEAKER_29]: Why do you think I'm kidding?
[SPEAKER_29]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_29]: You tell me.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's okay because boys are stupid anyway, except present company.
[SPEAKER_28]: on that note.
[SPEAKER_28]: So, we have our big finish.
[SPEAKER_28]: The big scores, here they are.
[SPEAKER_28]: Let's total it up.
[SPEAKER_28]: JB has a score of zero.
[SPEAKER_28]: And 23 Magus has a score of zero.
[SPEAKER_18]: You win nothing.
[SPEAKER_18]: Nothing at all.
[SPEAKER_18]: Good day, sir.
[SPEAKER_24]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_24]: You couldn't even get a magazine.
[SPEAKER_24]: That's pretty sad.
[SPEAKER_24]: So, this is what happens.
[SPEAKER_24]: As punishment,
[SPEAKER_24]: You two get all of the punishments that were mentioned earlier.
[SPEAKER_28]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_28]: Live at March Madness.
[SPEAKER_18]: They get to be spanked, anally raped, and then get hot people.
[SPEAKER_20]: And then go down on all of us.
[SPEAKER_20]: They're underage!
[SPEAKER_20]: Hey, but remember, one of your punishments was... Hey Rob, one of the punishments was getting to have sex with a bunch of hot people.
[SPEAKER_20]: That's true!
[SPEAKER_20]: I'd throw the game for that one.
[SPEAKER_28]: That's very true.
[SPEAKER_34]: Yeah, but I'll take the game back for the fair.
[SPEAKER_34]: No.
[SPEAKER_34]: That ain't happening.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_28]: So, um... They're demanding a tiebreaker, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_28]: We don't have much time.
[SPEAKER_28]: Because we have to take a quick break, and then we're going to come back and wrap up the show.
[SPEAKER_18]: Take a break.
[SPEAKER_18]: Take a small break, but we'll come back for our special.
[SPEAKER_28]: Small break, one song, and this is your chance to ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_28]: Or, tonight, you can ask...
[SPEAKER_27]: Who's fucking with the mic?
[SPEAKER_18]: or tonight... I have the mic.
[SPEAKER_18]: Or tonight, you get alienly raped by the ferret.
[SPEAKER_28]: No, tonight you can either ask Orange Lounge or you can ask Dark Child or you can ask Asian Innovation.
[SPEAKER_28]: Just send those to the chat room.
[SPEAKER_28]: And if you're not in our chat room, fucking get in there.
[SPEAKER_28]: Go to KaliBamani.com and then click on Orange Lounge and click on chat.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's super duper easy.
[SPEAKER_28]: Why aren't you here already?
[SPEAKER_28]: What do you guys think for a break song?
[SPEAKER_28]: Something from DDR, something from GDX.
[SPEAKER_18]: Something annoying.
[SPEAKER_28]: Something annoying?
[SPEAKER_18]: Play Orion.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, play Blue Moon Dollar.
[SPEAKER_28]: All right, so it'll be a quick break, and we'll be right back after Ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_28]: So send your questions to Sky in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_13]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: Easier to dance to than that freaking catch-up song.
[SPEAKER_03]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_28]: Ha ha.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oops.
[SPEAKER_28]: Nope, we're not doing Match Game anymore.
[SPEAKER_28]: I have to queue up the other music.
[SPEAKER_28]: So this is a little segment we do when we need some time filler.
[SPEAKER_28]: Because our chat room is very creative, so we allow them to ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_28]: So here we go.
[SPEAKER_28]: Show's ten minutes longer.
[SPEAKER_15]: Ask us questions.
[SPEAKER_15]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_28]: Ask Orange Lounge, or tonight you can ask Dark Child or Asian Innovation.
[SPEAKER_28]: 23rd Magus says, seriously though, if I beg and plead enough, will Orange Lounge sponsor me for March Madness?
[SPEAKER_28]: I'm already making my Orange Lounge shirt.
[SPEAKER_28]: If I endure all punishments mentioned, will I get sponsored?
[SPEAKER_18]: That would be amusing.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's a guy.
[SPEAKER_18]: Well, should we consider it?
[SPEAKER_28]: We'll consider it.
[SPEAKER_28]: We have to see.
[SPEAKER_28]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_18]: Keep in mind that one of us is unemployed.
[SPEAKER_20]: If you could out-drink me on Bacardi 151, I will sponsor you.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'll pay your win.
[SPEAKER_28]: Come to think of it, I think it would be worth it to see his freestyle.
[SPEAKER_30]: I'll do it.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah, one of us will do it.
[SPEAKER_28]: We'll figure it out.
[SPEAKER_28]: But you need to try and come up with the money yourself, because if we have to sponsor you, we're making you do something humiliating.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_28]: Justin S, your jazz, sorry, I just gave you a real name over the air, my bad.
[SPEAKER_28]: To everyone, can I have about $100 and a ride to March Madness?
[SPEAKER_18]: No.
[SPEAKER_28]: I'll bring Clock Tower 3 and bad horror movies.
[SPEAKER_18]: Um, I can't give you a ride, but you can, like, hang out.
[SPEAKER_28]: You know, um, you can certainly stay at the Orange Lounge World Headquarters, a.k.a.
[SPEAKER_28]: my house, if you can, uh, find a ride here.
[SPEAKER_28]: If you just post on DDR Freak, you might be able to find something.
[SPEAKER_28]: DarkTetsuya says, are we, me slash 23Maggots, still on for hosting Orange Lounge Radio next weekend?
[SPEAKER_28]: No, you fool!
[SPEAKER_28]: Me, DarkSakura, and Loki are the hosts of Orange Lounge Radio, but you guys can guest.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, you get to help.
[SPEAKER_28]: You can help.
[SPEAKER_28]: John Fields wants to know, how much of a hero would someone be if he or she created a DWI of a DDR non-stop megamix all custom steps?
Oh my god!
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm so excited!
[SPEAKER_18]: That would be long and I would fall over dead.
[SPEAKER_30]: No!
[SPEAKER_30]: Stop!
[SPEAKER_30]: Well, here's what people are doing, though.
[SPEAKER_30]: They're making steps for tracks off of the non-stop.
[SPEAKER_30]: Single tracks, okay, as long as the steps are good.
[SPEAKER_30]: Full non-stop, that's the stupidest idea ever.
[SPEAKER_30]: What do you think you are, DWI Insanity or something?
[SPEAKER_30]: I mean, it's not... I mean, they're the ones that make the 45-minute long ones.
[SPEAKER_30]: Stop it.
[SPEAKER_30]: Don't try to be... Come up with something original.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got mail!
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_28]: We have a question for Asian Innovation from DDR Mike.
[SPEAKER_28]: We have two questions.
[SPEAKER_28]: How much weight did you put on from yesterday's party?
[SPEAKER_24]: I only had two ribs.
[SPEAKER_24]: But, yeah.
[SPEAKER_24]: And then, how was that horrible, wonderful job at Jack in the Box?
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't know, I gave most of the food to you.
[SPEAKER_28]: Beautiful.
[SPEAKER_28]: And that's all the questions I've gotten so far for Ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_28]: So we'll give them a couple more minutes.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're not funny, Mike.
[SPEAKER_28]: Quit laughing.
[SPEAKER_28]: Does anybody have a question for someone else here in the room?
[SPEAKER_18]: Will someone hire me?
[SPEAKER_18]: Please.
[SPEAKER_20]: What are your job qualifications?
[SPEAKER_18]: Well, my resume is on Rob's computer.
[SPEAKER_20]: Is that resume in MPEG or QuickTime?
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay, Rob, you sat and watched Ally McFeel with me.
[SPEAKER_20]: Oh my god, you are gay.
[SPEAKER_18]: That was the funniest porn ever.
[SPEAKER_28]: Ally McFeel had fucking Ron Jeremy in it.
[SPEAKER_28]: It was awesome.
[SPEAKER_20]: Sweet.
[SPEAKER_20]: Ron Jeremy is a god.
[SPEAKER_28]: Have you seen Porn Star, The Legend of Ron Jeremy?
[SPEAKER_20]: No, I have not.
[SPEAKER_20]: It's a sweet movie.
[SPEAKER_28]: Rent it.
[SPEAKER_20]: Is it porn?
[SPEAKER_28]: It's not actually porn, but I mean, they have like little clips and things, but it's still kind of, it's NC-17, but not really like porn.
[SPEAKER_20]: What's this word, rent?
[SPEAKER_20]: I don't understand this word, rent.
[SPEAKER_20]: Rent.
[SPEAKER_20]: I have Kazaa.
[SPEAKER_20]: What's rent?
[SPEAKER_20]: Is that when I delete it after I watch it?
[SPEAKER_28]: Yes, yes.
[SPEAKER_28]: That's when you, you only have 24 hours after downloading this.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_28]: More questions.
[SPEAKER_18]: I have a question for the chat room.
[SPEAKER_18]: Anyone in there, find me Battle Royale Special Edition and buy it for me.
[SPEAKER_20]: I have a question for the chat room.
[SPEAKER_20]: Uh-huh?
[SPEAKER_20]: Do I know anyone in the chat room?
[SPEAKER_27]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_27]: Want to come look?
[SPEAKER_28]: The list?
[SPEAKER_27]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_28]: They might have changed their names.
[SPEAKER_28]: That's very true.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay, John Fields has a follow-up project.
[SPEAKER_28]: He says, let me plug, oh, this isn't the plug segment, this is the ask segment, but fine, I'll let you get away with it.
[SPEAKER_28]: Let me plug a project I'm working on then, http://www.squaredancedance.tk That's a little scary, let's look at the site real fast.
[SPEAKER_28]: Loki, what do you think of this?
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh, wait, I think I've heard of this.
[SPEAKER_30]: SquareDance is just those remixed Final Fantasy and Square songs.
[SPEAKER_30]: And I know there's a guy that's been releasing DWIs for them.
[SPEAKER_28]: I think I played one of those.
[SPEAKER_28]: I have a splitting headache and it hurts!
[SPEAKER_28]: Didn't I play one of those the other night?
[SPEAKER_28]: At your party?
[SPEAKER_28]: I think you have all these already.
[SPEAKER_23]: I think I played one of them.
[SPEAKER_28]: Yeah, I...
[SPEAKER_20]: I think Squaresoft Rocks.
[SPEAKER_20]: I'll go to that page a lot.
[SPEAKER_20]: But that's not Orange Line talking, that's just me.
[SPEAKER_28]: DDR Mike, by the way, says, Her, her, shut up, squinty-eyed Asian hoe.
[SPEAKER_34]: Why did he call you a hoe?
[SPEAKER_34]: I'll be over at your house tonight at 11.
[SPEAKER_28]: All right.
[SPEAKER_28]: You other hoe.
[SPEAKER_28]: DarkTetsuya wants to know, how come more females don't come in the chat room?
[SPEAKER_28]: Cry.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's because there's no one there who excites them enough.
[SPEAKER_28]: They're too busy cooking.
[SPEAKER_18]: Are there females coming in the chat room right now?
[SPEAKER_18]: First of all, they don't come in the chatroom because it'll make a big stinky mess.
[SPEAKER_27]: They don't come because you haven't found the G-spot.
[SPEAKER_20]: It's because I haven't been here yet.
[SPEAKER_18]: Because I can't come when you fuck me.
[SPEAKER_26]: Yeah, if a girl was coming, she wouldn't be in the chatroom.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_28]: Last one.
[SPEAKER_28]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_28]: Last question from Justin Circuit says, can you give me money?
[SPEAKER_18]: Depends on what you'll do for me.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'll give you a dollar.
[SPEAKER_28]: Can you give me stuff?
[SPEAKER_28]: Can you give me head?
[SPEAKER_28]: From Justin?
[SPEAKER_28]: I'll close my eyes.
[SPEAKER_29]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_29]: I'll give him money from Argentina.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay, so, on that note, that's the end of Ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_28]: Alright, one more, there's one more, there's one more.
[SPEAKER_28]: One more, this is the last question.
[SPEAKER_28]: This is a good one to end it on because it kind of relates to March Madness.
[SPEAKER_28]: Oh!
[SPEAKER_28]: Skyline DC505 wants to know, would doing bag five speed for the qualifier be noobish?
[SPEAKER_28]: Go ahead, I don't care.
[SPEAKER_25]: Just do it on one speed later on.
[SPEAKER_25]: Have fun.
[SPEAKER_28]: Okay, and now's that time of the show where we have to wrap it up.
[SPEAKER_28]: But first, we go around the room and get everyone's final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_18]: Rob, can we wrap it up in ribbon and bows?
[SPEAKER_20]: And confetti.
[SPEAKER_18]: And leather.
[SPEAKER_18]: And chains.
[SPEAKER_18]: And whips.
[SPEAKER_20]: Okay, now I'm getting into this.
[SPEAKER_18]: And, and, like, playing hot pokers.
[SPEAKER_16]: I don't have much to say, how about... Pikachu!
[SPEAKER_30]: All I gotta say is, uh, unfortunately there will not be an update to my site tonight or tomorrow because I have a headache and I'll probably be going to sleep.
[SPEAKER_30]: So maybe Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_30]: What?! !
[SPEAKER_30]: What the hell's your problem, man?
[SPEAKER_11]: You're a savior because you don't have one of those live doll things.
[SPEAKER_11]: Real dolls, whatever it is.
[SPEAKER_29]: Um, I accept this award on the behalf of myself because you all suck.
[SPEAKER_29]: And one last thing, you are cool.
[SPEAKER_18]: You're so cute.
[SPEAKER_18]: You're the coolest girl in the world.
[SPEAKER_20]: I declare war on Iraq because I'm a Texan.
[SPEAKER_20]: Bang, bang, bang.
[SPEAKER_20]: I'm a Texan.
[SPEAKER_20]: Bang, bang.
[SPEAKER_30]: April 15th, go buy your Miyazaki films.
[SPEAKER_30]: Castle in the Sky, Spirited Away, and Kiki's Delivery Service come out on DVD in English.
[SPEAKER_18]: And April 19th is my birthday, so give me stuff.
[SPEAKER_34]: Your final thought, Mike?
[SPEAKER_34]: Go to March Madness, please.
[SPEAKER_34]: I don't want to turn on, like, five people.
[SPEAKER_34]: All right.
[SPEAKER_34]: Thanks.
[SPEAKER_34]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_28]: My final thought is Zelda comes out tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_28]: Is anyone moist?
[SPEAKER_18]: Has anyone already played it?
[SPEAKER_28]: All right.
[SPEAKER_28]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_28]: End of show.
[SPEAKER_28]: Don't forget, no show next week because we're live all day long, Saturday and Sunday.
[SPEAKER_28]: Listen, for God's sake, or at least come to the tournament.
[SPEAKER_28]: Because if nobody listens, we'll never do it again.
[SPEAKER_28]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_28]: We're already planning on doing it at B3 as well, but not after that.
[SPEAKER_28]: All right.
[SPEAKER_28]: Thank you very much for listening.
[SPEAKER_28]: It's 44 Times Radio.
[SPEAKER_28]: We love you.
[SPEAKER_03]: The system is down.
[SPEAKER_03]: Go, go, Power Rangers!
[SPEAKER_36]: Hey, dude!
[SPEAKER_36]: Hey, you just changed!
[SPEAKER_36]: Yeah, I know, we always change characters every day.
[SPEAKER_36]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_36]: Hey, I'm a little kid and I'm gonna join the Power Rangers.
[SPEAKER_36]: How do you know about us?
[SPEAKER_36]: Because I watch the show every day.
[SPEAKER_36]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_36]: Hey, guys, look, it's those three teenagers that exactly match the Power Rangers personalities and their voices and every single thing about them.
[SPEAKER_36]: Let's go harass them.
[SPEAKER_36]: Okay, Bull, come on.
[SPEAKER_36]: Okay, cool.
[SPEAKER_36]: Hey, we know praying mantis.
[SPEAKER_36]: Hey, you're not supposed to kick around, Bull.
[SPEAKER_36]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_36]: Rangers, Rangers, what?
[SPEAKER_36]: Power Rangers, what do you know?
[SPEAKER_36]: Fire teenagers with attitude.
[SPEAKER_36]: What's wrong?
[SPEAKER_36]: What's going on?
[SPEAKER_36]: There's a bunch of disturbances going on.
[SPEAKER_36]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_36]: You better check it out.
[SPEAKER_36]: Oh, no, it's a monster that's terrorizing the city.
[SPEAKER_36]: What are you doing here?
[SPEAKER_36]: I'm the master of the world.
[SPEAKER_36]: I'm a giant pig.
[SPEAKER_36]: I eat stuff.
[SPEAKER_36]: Oh, no, we need to destroy him.
[SPEAKER_36]: Posing.
[SPEAKER_36]: Moving around.
[SPEAKER_36]: We are the Avengers, and we are going... Oh, yeah, well, uh, yeah, well, you weren't smart enough to call upon your Megazords now.
[SPEAKER_36]: Whoa, what the heck?
[SPEAKER_36]: Oh, no, we need to call upon the Megazord Megazord.
[SPEAKER_36]: Fusion.
[SPEAKER_36]: Thank you very much for listening and we'll see you next week.