[SPEAKER_05]: Do you want to hear the most annoying sound in the world?
[SPEAKER_25]: You're listening to Orange Lounge Radio, the Monty Talk, and then some.
[SPEAKER_25]: Orange Lounge may contain adult content.
[SPEAKER_25]: Orange Lounge may contain many four-letter words.
[SPEAKER_25]: Orange Lounge may contain a scene of nudity.
[SPEAKER_25]: Orange Lounge may contain hot monkey sex.
[SPEAKER_17]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_17]: Orange Lounge will not contain hot monkey sex.
[SPEAKER_30]: In this episode... Hey, is there any balls down there?
[SPEAKER_11]: That's the biggest bear you've ever seen, Jingleberry.
[SPEAKER_11]: What's your favorite scary movie?
[SPEAKER_31]: Showgirls.
[SPEAKER_31]: Absolutely frightening.
[SPEAKER_31]: What's yours?
[SPEAKER_31]: There are no stupid questions, just stupid people.
[SPEAKER_31]: Don't torture yourself.
[SPEAKER_31]: That's my job.
[SPEAKER_31]: Now's the time when Sprockets made me dogs!
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll get you, my pretty.
[SPEAKER_07]: And your little dog, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know Kung Fu.
[SPEAKER_31]: I'm sorry, but all questions must be submitted in writing.
[SPEAKER_31]: Why did they have to take the word gay?
[SPEAKER_07]: Nobody expects us to punish acquisitions.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's handover.
[SPEAKER_25]: DarkSakura Shut up!
[SPEAKER_07]: Where's my gun?
[SPEAKER_07]: This is my boom stick!
[SPEAKER_18]: Sky Come on girls, it's time to drop the bomb!
[SPEAKER_18]: Loki I can't for the life of me get the hooker to have sex with me.
[SPEAKER_12]: What kind of warping being would find that funny?
[SPEAKER_17]: Orange Lounge Radio We are live and this is episode number 36 for March 9th of 2003.
[SPEAKER_17]: We're live from La Casa de Jamie tonight!
[SPEAKER_24]: So with me... Fuck my mixer, it won't let me play Waves in the background.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, with me, of course, she needs no introduction.
[SPEAKER_17]: Say hello to DarkSakura, also known as Jamie.
[SPEAKER_24]: Welcome to my house.
[SPEAKER_17]: Welcome to hell.
[SPEAKER_24]: Get the fuck out my house, bitch!
[SPEAKER_17]: And joining us as usual, say hello to the Tech Master, Loki!
[SPEAKER_17]: Tech Master?
[SPEAKER_17]: I think I need to change the title.
[SPEAKER_24]: Like what?
[SPEAKER_17]: Welcome, everybody, say hello to the show's bitch, Loki!
[SPEAKER_24]: Hey, bitch!
[SPEAKER_18]: I thought that was someone else.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah, where's our intern?
[SPEAKER_17]: Everybody say hello to the asshole, Loki!
[SPEAKER_17]: That'll do.
[SPEAKER_17]: How are you today, asshole Loki?
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm fine.
[SPEAKER_17]: And joining us, of course, our intern, say hello to Zero.
[SPEAKER_21]: I am not Orange Launch's bitch.
[SPEAKER_17]: No, you just give head.
[SPEAKER_17]: No.
[SPEAKER_17]: Like interns do.
[SPEAKER_18]: Never mind.
[SPEAKER_18]: I was going to be mean, but never mind.
[SPEAKER_17]: Be mean!
[SPEAKER_17]: Come on, this is Orange Lounge, you can be mean.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, fine.
[SPEAKER_17]: Also joining us in studio, say hello to DarkTetsuya.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, hey.
[SPEAKER_17]: How are you doing?
[SPEAKER_17]: How are you, gentlemen?
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_17]: How's your week been?
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, just waiting on my FUs.
[SPEAKER_17]: Wait a minute, it's been about, well, I don't know, probably about 25 weeks since we've had you on the show, so how's the past, like, four months been?
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, well, long story.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_18]: Also with us...
[SPEAKER_18]: 25 weeks on the show.
[SPEAKER_18]: I think that's about, I don't know, six months?
[SPEAKER_17]: I can do math.
[SPEAKER_17]: This is what happens when you drop out of college.
[SPEAKER_17]: Stay in school.
[SPEAKER_17]: Be cool.
[SPEAKER_17]: All right.
[SPEAKER_17]: And also with us tonight, say hello to Sunya Bunya.
[SPEAKER_17]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_17]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm okay.
[SPEAKER_17]: Did I pronounce that okay?
[SPEAKER_17]: Soonja, Soonja Boonja.
[SPEAKER_17]: I wanted to make it rhyme with Boonya, so I said Soonja.
[SPEAKER_17]: And Bombay, I called him by his nickname tonight so he wouldn't cut me.
[SPEAKER_20]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_17]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_20]: I appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_20]: I'm doing okay.
[SPEAKER_20]: I'm a little tired from Scandia, but other than that, I'm pretty good.
[SPEAKER_20]: I see you're wearing your uniform.
[SPEAKER_20]: Yes, I just got off about two hours ago.
[SPEAKER_17]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_17]: Jamie said you got off.
[SPEAKER_17]: Also with us, say hello to Puppy.
[SPEAKER_17]: Woof.
[SPEAKER_17]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_17]: You just came from downstairs.
[SPEAKER_17]: You were playing Animal Crack.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_17]: Killing roaches.
[SPEAKER_17]: Because you haven't played in about a month.
[SPEAKER_19]: There's like tons of them.
[SPEAKER_19]: I know, but there's like tons of them.
[SPEAKER_19]: I killed 20 so far.
[SPEAKER_19]: The last time you played Animal Crossing was when Joe was on this show last, I think.
[SPEAKER_19]: No, it was like a month ago.
[SPEAKER_24]: Did you like what I did with your house?
[SPEAKER_24]: I gave you matching floor and wall and some furniture that went with that set.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's the Kadana set.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's like trading spaces.
[SPEAKER_19]: Anybody ever watch that shit?
[SPEAKER_19]: My mom watches that.
[SPEAKER_18]: They have the best of season one of that stupid show on DVD now.
[SPEAKER_18]: Sad.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm waiting for the Gay Weddings DVD.
[SPEAKER_17]: That shows the shit.
[SPEAKER_17]: What?
[SPEAKER_17]: We're giving a shout-out.
[SPEAKER_17]: Shout-out.
[SPEAKER_17]: Do shout-outs, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yo!
[SPEAKER_24]: All you people who want shout-outs, yo, I'm just not gonna name anybody.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yo.
[SPEAKER_17]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_17]: Hello to our chat room.
[SPEAKER_17]: If you want to join our chat room, go to orangelounge.skie.cx and click on chat.
[SPEAKER_17]: And then you should also post in our forums, because our forums have been kind of dead, and we need people to post in them.
[SPEAKER_24]: Not in the quote forum, my God.
[SPEAKER_17]: No, not the quote forum.
[SPEAKER_17]: Whoa, but everything else has been dead.
[SPEAKER_17]: So we need people to go there and post love letters, if you wouldn't mind.
[SPEAKER_17]: I need a lot of attention, and so does Jamie.
[SPEAKER_17]: Jamie likes attention, so go post your love and affection letters to Jamie.
[SPEAKER_17]: And then Loki, tell him what a dick he is.
[SPEAKER_14]: Jerk.
[SPEAKER_17]: Tell him you don't appreciate those racial slurs and homophobic comments, and what else has he said on this show, Nox?
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah, you porn monger, you.
[SPEAKER_24]: The hell?
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm like totally opposite from everyone perceiving me as, like some crazy racist guy out there.
[SPEAKER_18]: I should just like shave my head, join the Ku Klux Klan and shit, man.
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't know what the problem is.
[SPEAKER_17]: You were saying, Loki?
[SPEAKER_17]: All I have to say is you should have been there last night.
[SPEAKER_17]: We were playing this game, loaded questions.
[SPEAKER_17]: And Brad had to answer this question.
[SPEAKER_17]: What's the problem that you would fix in America?
[SPEAKER_17]: And he said, well, we should get rid of all the... I'll just leave the rest to your imagination.
[SPEAKER_17]: But he got a lot of stuff thrown at him.
[SPEAKER_17]: All right.
[SPEAKER_24]: I think that's when I was sort of passing out.
[SPEAKER_17]: Deprivation and alcohol.
[SPEAKER_17]: You had a lot to drink.
[SPEAKER_17]: We'll talk about drinking when we get back.
[SPEAKER_24]: I didn't have a lot to drink.
[SPEAKER_17]: I was just tired.
[SPEAKER_17]: That stuff's pretty strong.
[SPEAKER_24]: That stuff was weak.
[SPEAKER_21]: No, you want to know what's worse than writing it?
[SPEAKER_24]: You had, what, three shots and you were giggling on the floor rolling around?
[SPEAKER_24]: I threw, like, stuff at you and you didn't move.
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't have to be drunk to do that.
[SPEAKER_21]: You put peanut butter cups on your head, too.
[SPEAKER_24]: I put one in your ear.
[SPEAKER_21]: No, wait, wait, hold on.
[SPEAKER_21]: I got one thing to say.
[SPEAKER_21]: You want to know what's worse than writing what was read?
[SPEAKER_21]: Writing what was written was being the one who had to read it out loud and being afraid everyone's going to attack you instead of the person who wrote it.
[SPEAKER_17]: Because everyone knew who wrote it.
[SPEAKER_17]: And then somebody said, who tried to balance this bottle of Smirnoff Black on me while I was sleeping?
[SPEAKER_17]: Was that you?
[SPEAKER_17]: That wasn't fun.
[SPEAKER_17]: Can we go to break now?
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright, bye.
[SPEAKER_17]: We'll be back.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, I guess we're going to do one more, because I got these much better parody lyrics for Bumblebee than that shit I did a little bit ago, so we're going to do this one instead.
[SPEAKER_17]: This comes from DDR Angel and Stress, this is much better, so enjoy.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know I'm going to fuck this up, I apologize.
[SPEAKER_10]: Fuck you.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sweet little bumblebee Get the fuck away from me Sweet little bumblebee
[SPEAKER_11]: My foot kicks your ass when you walk in the room I go boom, boom, boom, you go zoom, zoom, zoom You're my format, dance pad, killable friend I wanna kick your ass until you're dead I'll shove my foot right up your ass To help you see it's true I don't like you, can't you see?
[SPEAKER_11]: Now get the fuck away from me
[SPEAKER_11]: Fuck you!
What?
[SPEAKER_23]: with Orange Lounge Radio with the Ping Pong Boys.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yay, we're back.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yay, we are back.
[SPEAKER_24]: Did you miss us?
[SPEAKER_17]: Bork, bork, bork.
[SPEAKER_24]: No, for that break we had Bumblebee's Sky's Wizard Mixer.
[SPEAKER_24]: Just for the fact that I wanted to annoy Rob with it.
[SPEAKER_17]: Thank you, by the way, Jamie, for embarrassing me because I had no idea she was going to be playing.
[SPEAKER_17]: And surprisingly enough, a lot of people in the chatroom have not heard that before And a lot of people want to get an mp3 of that I'm not sure I should be advertising this I find that thing quite embarrassing I don't know why you guys like it so much Who wants it?
[SPEAKER_17]: PM me No, I'll tell you I'll tell you what, even better Talk to Stressa I don't know if he's awake right now or active in chat I'm not sure I can't really see the chatroom from where I'm sitting Jamie's in the chat tonight
[SPEAKER_17]: RobEatingPussy
[SPEAKER_17]: Ew.
[SPEAKER_17]: Go ahead, Jeremy.
[SPEAKER_17]: If you want DWIs, go and ask Dressa.
[SPEAKER_17]: Is he in chat?
[SPEAKER_17]: He's not even in chat right now, is he?
[SPEAKER_17]: No.
[SPEAKER_17]: So I guess he's out.
[SPEAKER_17]: But when he's around, ask him about it.
[SPEAKER_17]: And I think some other folks might have it.
[SPEAKER_17]: DDR Angel, I know, has it, but she's on vacation right now.
[SPEAKER_17]: She's in Japan.
[SPEAKER_17]: Japan.
[SPEAKER_17]: We'll find a way for you folks to get it.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm sure Loki will put it up.
[SPEAKER_17]: Speaking of DWIs and Loki...
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm eating fucking pretzels right now, man.
[SPEAKER_17]: Ooh, his mouth is full.
[SPEAKER_17]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, how was your week, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_17]: We'll get back to that.
[SPEAKER_17]: How was... Is everybody going to eat?
[SPEAKER_17]: So I have to just sit here and just talk to myself.
[SPEAKER_17]: How are you, Zero?
[SPEAKER_17]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_24]: I have new horses.
[SPEAKER_17]: You have new horses?
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, let's talk about yesterday's trip.
[SPEAKER_17]: That was fun.
[SPEAKER_24]: To go play Derby Owner's Crack.
[SPEAKER_17]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_24]: Um...
[SPEAKER_17]: For those that don't know what Derby Owner's Crack is, it's a game where you race horsies, and it's a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's like Initial D, but horses.
[SPEAKER_17]: But you don't actually ride the horses like you drive the car.
[SPEAKER_17]: You just whip them.
[SPEAKER_17]: You have a big button for your whip, and you just beat your horse to get them to run faster.
[SPEAKER_17]: And you breed them.
[SPEAKER_17]: And then if you do well in the races, people give you things.
[SPEAKER_17]: I have a horse named Politary.
[SPEAKER_17]: and she gets chicks and pussies.
[SPEAKER_17]: Like, every time I win a race, a chick will come to the stable, or a cat.
[SPEAKER_17]: So, you know, Politary gets the chicks and gets the pussy.
[SPEAKER_17]: What can you say?
[SPEAKER_17]: Hi, we're doing a show, hi.
[SPEAKER_17]: Hello, what's up, what's going on?
[SPEAKER_17]: Hey, wait, Anita, Anita, Anita, come back.
[SPEAKER_17]: Anita, come say hi.
[SPEAKER_17]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_17]: Hi, everybody, how are you?
[SPEAKER_17]: We don't get women on this show very often, and poor Jamie's starting to... Well, I mean, Jamie, you were bitching about this the other day, that you're like, I'm the only woman on that whole show.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm all for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, it only takes like a few because women rule.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, is it going to be one of those nights?
[SPEAKER_24]: Every one of us is at least worth a thousand of you.
[SPEAKER_17]: Is this going to be one of those nights where it sounds like we're at some women's rights march and my vagina is a vortex from which all life explodes.
[SPEAKER_24]: Lastly got Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_24]: By the way, I did find a site for Derby Owners Club, so you can see what the machine looks like.
[SPEAKER_24]: Go to expertdoc.flex.com And you'll post that in the chat room, won't you?
[SPEAKER_17]: I just did already.
[SPEAKER_24]: That is Derby Owners Club.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's very casino-like.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's purposely looking like that.
[SPEAKER_24]: I made four new horses.
[SPEAKER_24]: One of them was called This is a Horse.
[SPEAKER_24]: The other one was called Happy Bunny, which won a bunch of races.
[SPEAKER_24]: and then Mel and Melody let me use two of their horses to breed a horse because I used one called Vanilla Ice that was all albino and then Saved by the Bell as in B-E-L-L-E That horse rules.
[SPEAKER_24]: The front part was black and the back was white.
[SPEAKER_24]: And I bred a tiger horse.
[SPEAKER_24]: Gold and white with tiger stripes and gold eyes and a tiger tail and everything.
[SPEAKER_17]: It looks like a tiger, but it's a horse.
[SPEAKER_17]: What's up with that?
[SPEAKER_24]: And I thought it was going to be a boy because I've been breeding nothing but boys lately.
[SPEAKER_24]: And this one was a girl, so I couldn't get the name I originally wanted.
[SPEAKER_17]: Last week on Orange Lounge, I've been breeding nothing but boys lately.
[SPEAKER_24]: So I named it Strong Badette.
[SPEAKER_17]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_24]: And my other horse's name is for people who's missed it.
[SPEAKER_24]: My very first horse was Slytherin Chaser.
[SPEAKER_17]: Because you're a Harry Potter whore.
[SPEAKER_24]: And then I had, I like cheese.
[SPEAKER_24]: And then Hot Man Sex, S-E-C-H-S.
[SPEAKER_17]: Because the machine will try to censor you.
[SPEAKER_24]: and then I had Fajitas and Jin Kazama because I'm a Tekken whore.
[SPEAKER_17]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_17]: I made two new horses yesterday.
[SPEAKER_17]: I made a horse dedicated to one of my favorite Animal Crossing characters, Elmer.
[SPEAKER_17]: So I made Elmer the horse.
[SPEAKER_17]: And then I made a horse called Sir Mix-a-Lot.
[SPEAKER_24]: My next horse I'm going to make is called Glue Factory.
[SPEAKER_17]: Glue Factory?
[SPEAKER_17]: Glue Factory.
[SPEAKER_17]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_24]: Rob is da funny.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm just reading.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm trying to catch up on chat room, so...
[SPEAKER_24]: Horsey sex is bad, I want to make a law about that.
[SPEAKER_24]: Horses have to have sex too!
[SPEAKER_24]: Have you ever seen a horse that has got any... That's the thing about Derby Owners Club.
[SPEAKER_17]: Derby Owners Club has this really explicit birthing scene to it.
[SPEAKER_17]: Like when you make a new horse for the first time... They go on a date.
[SPEAKER_17]: They go on a date.
[SPEAKER_17]: They send off the horses and they trot off.
[SPEAKER_17]: And then they go to a tree and it fades out so you don't have to see horsey sex.
[SPEAKER_17]: But then the next scene is them in a stable and then you see the male horse being all nurturing or whatever.
[SPEAKER_17]: The male horse isn't even there.
[SPEAKER_17]: The male horse is there, kind of looking.
[SPEAKER_17]: The male horse is just kind of looking.
[SPEAKER_24]: No, the mare is laying down.
[SPEAKER_17]: All I know is that you see the female horse, and all of a sudden it looks like she's going to take a giant crap.
[SPEAKER_17]: No, it doesn't.
[SPEAKER_17]: And then all of a sudden there's a little baby.
[SPEAKER_24]: No, that's not how it happens.
[SPEAKER_17]: I swear to God that's what I saw.
[SPEAKER_24]: No.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes, thank you for that.
[SPEAKER_24]: The mare is laying down, and the foal is laying beside her.
[SPEAKER_24]: And the foal gets up and goes, you know, it's like suddenly there's another horse, and then suddenly it's an adult.
[SPEAKER_24]: Happy Bunny is still childish.
[SPEAKER_18]: That horse sort of looks like Mr. Garrison.
[SPEAKER_24]: I would not want to be Mr. Hat and have a hand on my ass.
[SPEAKER_17]: The chat room is referencing a movie called Freddy Got Fingered, which I never bothered to watch.
[SPEAKER_17]: Because, you're going to have to explain this to me, because I never found Tom Green funny.
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't know if it's just me, but... He masturbates a horse in that.
[SPEAKER_18]: So look what I can do!
[SPEAKER_18]: Look what I can do!
[SPEAKER_17]: Brilliant comedy.
[SPEAKER_17]: Brilliant.
[SPEAKER_24]: But anyway, that site that I just linked in the chatroom, there are screen captures of a... See, look, there's the mayor and there's the freaking pony.
[SPEAKER_17]: I swear to God, I had one where the chick was squatting and then out comes baby.
[SPEAKER_24]: That is not what happened.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's a hidden... I got an Easter egg.
[SPEAKER_17]: Boy, was it ever an egg.
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay, chatroom, look at this.
[SPEAKER_24]: Does that look like the mayor is giving birth?
[SPEAKER_24]: No.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's a vicious lie.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's photoshopped.
[SPEAKER_24]: Although one thing that's in here that makes me a little bit wondering is there's a picture of the horse walking on a path.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's the one.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, there's the exercises you can do to the horse.
[SPEAKER_17]: There's one where you can rest it.
[SPEAKER_17]: The item all the way on the right is just like rest your horse and it goes on a trot through the forest and it's like your horse is relaxing.
[SPEAKER_17]: To which it gets attacked by a bear and dies.
[SPEAKER_24]: Hey!
[SPEAKER_17]: Now that would be cool.
[SPEAKER_17]: Is it true that there's a Derby Owners Club 2 coming out?
[SPEAKER_24]: Um, yeah, let me find the site again.
[SPEAKER_24]: Someone hold the microphone.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_17]: What?
[SPEAKER_17]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_18]: Anybody else in here ever played Derby Owners Crack?
[SPEAKER_18]: Nobody else has played?
[SPEAKER_18]: I have four horses.
[SPEAKER_18]: I've got... What are you guys doing?
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay, anyways.
[SPEAKER_18]: I got, um... I have a horse called Mr. Spanky.
[SPEAKER_18]: An ode to the stupid character from DDR PC.
[SPEAKER_18]: We've got one called Big Black Cock, which was an inside joke on the show, so I have that.
[SPEAKER_18]: And then I've got one called... I've got one called Cloud, and that was the one I stole from the little girl.
[SPEAKER_18]: And then...
[SPEAKER_18]: What was it?
[SPEAKER_17]: Loki is not lying.
[SPEAKER_17]: He did steal that card from a little girl.
[SPEAKER_18]: Shit, I have another one too.
[SPEAKER_18]: I can't remember what it was called.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's why all the kids run across the panels on you.
[SPEAKER_18]: They attack you for stealing cards.
[SPEAKER_18]: They're just stupid, those kids.
[SPEAKER_18]: But I'll go into it later.
[SPEAKER_18]: Trip them.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_17]: I want to talk about what pissed me off yesterday, though.
[SPEAKER_17]: This kind of goes into an FU of the week, but not really.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, because this is video game related.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, the Derby Owners Club, the way it works is you have one giant monitor, and there's eight little stations that you can sit at to play, so theoretically eight people can play the game at once.
[SPEAKER_17]: And if you visited the website that was given out in the chatroom, you saw a picture, so you know what I'm talking about.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, well, at Milpitas Golf Land on a Saturday, it's pretty busy, so there's a lot of people that kind of want to play, and it's kind of full.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, you know, so I'm sitting there kind of waiting.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm waiting for a game.
[SPEAKER_17]: And there's freaking people just sitting there at the stations not doing anything.
[SPEAKER_17]: And they're just like, they just have all their crap there.
[SPEAKER_17]: And like you can try and like wave at them, you know, go, hi, I want to play.
[SPEAKER_17]: And they just totally ignore you.
[SPEAKER_17]: They're totally oblivious to you.
[SPEAKER_24]: Some of the people there were actually waiting on particular races.
[SPEAKER_17]: And see, I think that, personally, I think that's bullshit.
[SPEAKER_17]: Like if you're going to do that, if you're going to...
[SPEAKER_17]: If you're going to do that where you're just going to sit on the game and wait for particular races, you need to do that on weeknight when no one's there.
[SPEAKER_17]: You need not do that in the middle of a Saturday.
[SPEAKER_17]: So, poo on you, you derby squatters.
[SPEAKER_13]: Guess that's happened to me with the initial D before.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's the difference between having two, where people are taking, where there's big lines of people, and then one with eight terminals, and people are just sitting there.
[SPEAKER_24]: There's a difference between initial D and Derby Owners Club.
[SPEAKER_17]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_17]: Initial D is not better.
[SPEAKER_17]: Initial D is smelly.
[SPEAKER_17]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_17]: Johnny's fighting.
[SPEAKER_17]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_20]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_24]: Who?
[SPEAKER_24]: You got admonished, Mr. Loki.
[SPEAKER_24]: Ninja Usagi Koi says, bad, stealing from kids.
[SPEAKER_24]: Who said that?
[SPEAKER_24]: Ninja Usagi Koi.
[SPEAKER_18]: Well, I didn't technically steal it.
[SPEAKER_18]: She was dumb and left it there, so I took it.
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay, taking advantage of other people's stupidity is okay.
[SPEAKER_24]: Should we actually try to have FUs of the week?
[SPEAKER_24]: Well, let's...
[SPEAKER_17]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay, Poppin' Music 8 is coming out, and they've estimated that it's going to have over 100 songs on it, plus a new mode that's called Live Mode, which has something to do with these live videos of them playing.
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't know what the fuck it is, because I don't play Poppin' Music.
[SPEAKER_18]: I played it once, and I didn't like it, so there.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, great.
[SPEAKER_17]: Where's 2DX7Style?
[SPEAKER_17]: Why do they keep cranking out the Poppin' Music?
[SPEAKER_18]: Hello, 2DX7Style has already been announced.
[SPEAKER_17]: When?
[SPEAKER_18]: When?
[SPEAKER_18]: I thought it was coming out in April.
[SPEAKER_15]: I think that's just a rumor.
[SPEAKER_18]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_15]: We're going to research this a little bit.
[SPEAKER_18]: You know, I should really pay attention to all this news since I read it all the time.
[SPEAKER_17]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_17]: Poppin' Music, it's okay.
[SPEAKER_17]: I mean, I like it.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's cool.
[SPEAKER_17]: But I think the reason a lot of people like it a lot, seriously, is because they don't have it many places.
[SPEAKER_17]: So, like, having played it is like a special club.
[SPEAKER_17]: Like, your leader, if you've played Poppin' Music or whatever...
[SPEAKER_17]: Poppin' Music's cool and all, and it has some good tunes, but it makes my freaking hands hurt.
[SPEAKER_18]: What about Aerobics Revolution, huh, huh?
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh, and Max 2 for the Japanese home version, Max 2.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, Matt the Ice Princess has a question, or I'm sorry, the Ice Queen.
[SPEAKER_17]: Hold on, you have to speak into the mic so they can all hear you.
[SPEAKER_22]: Alright, so why don't you go ahead and enlighten all of us idiots out here who don't know what the hell you're talking about when you talk about Poppin' Music.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'll let Loki do it.
[SPEAKER_18]: Pop music is like 2DX, but you have big buttons that are round, you know, kind of like the bishy-boshy buttons, big round buttons, and you just, yeah, like trouble.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yes, it's like nine pop-o-matic bubbles that you have to hit in tune to music.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's an excellent way of describing it.
[SPEAKER_17]: Thank you, Bombay.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's just, it's like, it's almost like if you were to take 2DX and turn it into like a Saturday morning cartoon, that's what it would be.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's just like all nice and stuff, but it's still kind of difficult like 2DX.
[SPEAKER_18]: Overplay
[SPEAKER_18]: POPPING MUSIC
[SPEAKER_18]: They've got some weird shit, weird modifiers on there and stuff, but it's pretty much like... But it's more like happy and rainbow-y and gay, because like the buttons are these big, right?
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, yeah, I knew that would make you cheer.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, it's got these big like red and yellow and blue and green buttons and they all flash.
[SPEAKER_17]: And little things that fall, it's falling pancakes.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's what they look like.
[SPEAKER_17]: They're big falling pancakes that have big eyes on them.
[SPEAKER_17]: They go, hi, meet me.
[SPEAKER_17]: And they hit the button when they hit the blind and they go, ooh, excellent.
[SPEAKER_17]: But like, sometimes you have to hit four buttons at once So you're playing the game like this with your elbows Well, that's good radio, no one can see that I know, okay You all did though Imagine doing the Tran Dance in the Stoic video That's kind of like what playing some poppin' music is Anyways And the only place I know of anywhere that has poppin' music I think they have a machine in Portland Yes, Bombay
[SPEAKER_20]: Yeah, I found one in Orange County, actually, at Camelot Golfland.
[SPEAKER_20]: Oh, I'll be damned.
[SPEAKER_17]: In Orange County.
[SPEAKER_20]: That's the one near Disneyland.
[SPEAKER_20]: Camelot, yeah, CMGO.
[SPEAKER_20]: It's pretty tight.
[SPEAKER_20]: I didn't get a chance to play.
[SPEAKER_20]: There's actually a lot of people playing, so.
[SPEAKER_17]: And then, of course, AI has one.
[SPEAKER_17]: They have Pop Music 9, which I did get to play when I was down there.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, yeah, when we went down there, they had that shitty M, whatever that is, stupid MLO.
[SPEAKER_17]: See, now that's one of Janie's favorites.
[SPEAKER_17]: That one sucked ass.
[SPEAKER_17]: If you like anime, it's going to have all the songs you like in it.
[SPEAKER_18]: Mambo Go Go was better than that.
[SPEAKER_17]: Leave me alone, I'm white.
[SPEAKER_18]: I can't pronounce shit tonight, leave me alone.
[SPEAKER_18]: But, uh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_18]: Um, let's see here.
[SPEAKER_18]: Other than that, it's just a lot of home versions coming out.
[SPEAKER_18]: Pretty much everyone's waiting for Max 2 to come out.
[SPEAKER_18]: We talked about that a little bit last week.
[SPEAKER_18]: And then there's Aerobics Revolution.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm so moist from excitement about Max 2.
[SPEAKER_17]: That no one gives a shit about.
[SPEAKER_17]: Have they figured out if there's going to be anything special in it yet?
[SPEAKER_17]: Have they announced any features or anything like that?
[SPEAKER_17]: They announced how many songs there's supposed to be.
[SPEAKER_17]: How many?
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't remember!
[SPEAKER_18]: It's like 60 or 70.
[SPEAKER_18]: You're fired.
[SPEAKER_18]: You don't do anything.
[SPEAKER_13]: Loki, you're supposed to remember these things.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, when I'm like busy running a couple sites and doing shit for my work and... Listen, my job on this show is to be cute, and I fulfill that, so... What's your job?
[SPEAKER_17]: Bring us news.
[SPEAKER_17]: Are you bringing us news?
[SPEAKER_17]: The fuck?
[SPEAKER_17]: That's messed up, man.
[SPEAKER_17]: You're bringing us like half the news.
[SPEAKER_17]: You're like MSNBC, Jesus.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh, oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_18]: No, on Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_18]: No.
[SPEAKER_18]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm trying to think.
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't really know much about that.
[SPEAKER_18]: I have, like, gossip news.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_18]: As reported on DDR Mania X in one of their random topic things, Monty Ruler, his backgrounds, he didn't make them.
[SPEAKER_18]: He stole them.
[SPEAKER_18]: Gossip!
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_17]: So who did?
[SPEAKER_17]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_14]: Who did?
[SPEAKER_17]: Who did?
[SPEAKER_17]: He just got them off some sites.
[SPEAKER_17]: It doesn't really matter.
[SPEAKER_17]: So like he downloaded the artwork and just added the text or what?
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_17]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_18]: I thought for whatever reason you had a grudge against him or something and you would have liked that news.
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't have a grudge against him.
[SPEAKER_18]: I do not have a grudge against him.
[SPEAKER_18]: The only thing I was saying was that his step-files are too hard.
[SPEAKER_18]: You cannot possibly play them on the feet.
[SPEAKER_18]: I mean, try playing Stoic on a pad.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's like... Hot Limit's not a ham.
[SPEAKER_18]: You're Hot Limit, whatever.
[SPEAKER_18]: No, I'm just talking... It's just... I don't know, his stuff's hard.
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't like it.
[SPEAKER_18]: Everyone calls it 4-key beat mania.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, I'd say it's pretty accurate.
[SPEAKER_18]: But, um, yeah.
[SPEAKER_17]: So wait, how do you get news like that?
[SPEAKER_17]: I mean, so a site actually ran a news story saying, guess what?
[SPEAKER_17]: Actually, it was a forum post, so.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, it was a forum post.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, I thought it was like, I thought it was like front page.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm like, that's pretty sad.
[SPEAKER_17]: You know it's a slow news day when the front page news is, uh-uh, bitch didn't do his own art.
[SPEAKER_18]: Who gives a shit anyways?
[SPEAKER_18]: It's like art isn't really a big... Well, yeah, it makes your file look nice, but it has nothing to do with the steps at all.
[SPEAKER_17]: And I think the only thing was is because... Maybe, okay, maybe because TourneyMix, they insisted that you make your own backgrounds, right?
[SPEAKER_17]: And didn't he... Wasn't he a judge for that?
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_18]: Well, he was a judge in the last one, but...
[SPEAKER_18]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, I invite him for an interview on this show to clear the air, if he or any of his cohorts are listening.
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't really know half the stories, because obviously I'm only reporting half the stories, since that's what you said.
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't even know, I just think he might have been claiming that he did all the artwork, instead of just saying, hey, I got this from here, I have the text, done.
[SPEAKER_18]: I mean, if he just came forward and said that, everything would be fine.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's all it is, but...
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, it was really fucking slow as far as nudes goes.
[SPEAKER_18]: There's nothing.
[SPEAKER_17]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_17]: I want him on the show.
[SPEAKER_17]: How can we make that happen?
[SPEAKER_17]: I want to get him on the show and have him explain what happened.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's never going to happen, so isn't that your job?
[SPEAKER_18]: Getting guests on the show?
[SPEAKER_17]: I'll see what I can do.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's never going to fucking happen.
[SPEAKER_18]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_18]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_18]: So what's coming up?
[SPEAKER_18]: What's 4.15? 4.15?
[SPEAKER_24]: According to BuyRight, Beatmania 2DX7 style is coming out on April 15th of 2003.
[SPEAKER_24]: But BuyRight is a shitty-ass place to order games from anyway.
[SPEAKER_24]: Because they cheated me with my Tekken 4 and they suck and need to die.
[SPEAKER_24]: Bitter, are we?
[SPEAKER_17]: Bitter, party of one, your table's ready, bitter.
[SPEAKER_24]: Don't bite my ass.
[SPEAKER_24]: But, um...
[SPEAKER_24]: But I mean, I don't know if anyone can find any... If anyone can look on Konami's Japanese site and find me proof that they have something up for Beatmania TDX7 style to be out and on home, or from any reliable place, send me a PM in the chatroom, please.
[SPEAKER_24]: DarkSakura, SSF.
[SPEAKER_17]: Speaking of chatroom, what's going on in there?
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm talking about NCSX.
[SPEAKER_24]: I was just looking at NCSX and I didn't see any pre-order stuff.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm going to actually check NCSX right now.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, so what else is going on?
[SPEAKER_17]: MSNB Loki?
[SPEAKER_18]: Damn right!
[SPEAKER_18]: Now, you know, you'd be surprised, like, all the stuff that I do during the week, because basically my job, for those who don't know, I'm answering phones and talking to people, and I have my, you know, I have my Internet Explorer open all the time, you know, browsing webpages, because we're on T1, and I download about 500 megs worth of files every week, and, you know, so that's what I do all day.
[SPEAKER_18]: So I read about eight forums at the same time, all day long, and, um,
[SPEAKER_18]: You'd think that I would know more what's going on, but really, to be honest, for the last three months, there has been nothing going on in the news.
[SPEAKER_18]: Our shows have been just kind of like, okay, just find some new shit to talk about.
[SPEAKER_18]: Nothing there.
[SPEAKER_18]: So...
[SPEAKER_18]: It really isn't that much going on right now, other than waiting for the home version of Max to come, which is probably going to have the same rehashed shit from DDR Max USA, which, you know, some of those songs.
[SPEAKER_18]: But at least we'll be able to make edits for it and stuff, and maybe a few new songs for Extreme 2 and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_18]: And then, obviously, probably later on this year we'll have some news about DDR Extreme 2 and its development and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_18]: and then, you know, that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_18]: But right now, there's not too much.
[SPEAKER_18]: New Guitar Freaks, obviously, is being, I think, playtested right now.
[SPEAKER_18]: I want it to be available somewhere else besides, like, where you know it'll go to RPGL.
[SPEAKER_18]: Let's talk about MoCap Golf, because we just got it at Sandia, and that game looks really fun.
[SPEAKER_17]: Before we get on the mocap golf tangent, I just wanted to say, I'm looking at BimaniX.com, and they have 2DX 7th style coming out in August for the PS2.
[SPEAKER_17]: So take that in your will.
[SPEAKER_17]: However, they said that Beat Me is 7th mix, plus the finals coming out on PS2 in March, but I haven't heard anything about that yet, seeing as, hmm, it's March.
[SPEAKER_17]: Uh, yeah, it's kind of surprising.
[SPEAKER_18]: If my memory serves me right, I think it was the 24th or 25th.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, I thought I heard that was going to be late March.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, like last week.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, gee, Konami of Japan's doing a great job promoting it.
[SPEAKER_18]: Well, they do a great job with everything, like, you know.
[SPEAKER_13]: Now, wasn't it supposed to come out, oh, I don't know, Christmas Eve last year?
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, if I remember right, what they said about Christmas Eve was that that was just supposed to be 7th Mix for the PS1.
[SPEAKER_17]: And now they're doing 7th Mix plus the final PS2, whatever.
[SPEAKER_17]: Eh, who cares?
[SPEAKER_19]: Could you get on the boat, CapGolf, now?
[SPEAKER_18]: And, like, an open letter to, like, frickin', um, Konami.
[SPEAKER_18]: Why are you ignoring Dead End?
[SPEAKER_18]: I mean, that song back in third mix is a pretty cool song.
[SPEAKER_18]: You haven't remixed it at all.
[SPEAKER_18]: You've, like, remixed the hell out of Trip Machine and Paranoia and all those brilliant tunes and shit.
[SPEAKER_24]: I wanna see Dead End in 2DX.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_18]: That would be kinda cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, MoCapGolf.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay, MoCapGolf, yes.
[SPEAKER_19]: Greatest motion capture game ever.
[SPEAKER_21]: It is so cool.
[SPEAKER_21]: It is damn cool, don't say that.
[SPEAKER_21]: It freaking rules.
[SPEAKER_21]: Dude, what other game can you hit a golf ball off the top of a building onto another one?
[SPEAKER_19]: Give him a microphone so I can bitch at him.
[SPEAKER_20]: The only reason I'm mad is because over at Scandio, we're supposed to have Soul Calibur already, but instead I went into work today and saw a golf game.
[SPEAKER_20]: Now, that made me kind of mad.
[SPEAKER_20]: I think a lot of other people... Soul Calibur 2's been out for a while now.
[SPEAKER_20]: I know, but I'm waiting for it.
[SPEAKER_20]: Like, Keith said he has this really, really awesome system for it, and I'm really excited about it.
[SPEAKER_20]: But he just needs the software.
[SPEAKER_20]: Okay, yes.
[SPEAKER_20]: Broaden your horizons.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's all I need to say.
[SPEAKER_19]: Golf, man.
[SPEAKER_19]: Golf.
[SPEAKER_18]: I like Soul Calibur, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_18]: I tend to want to play other things now.
[SPEAKER_18]: You know what game... It's not golf's better, it's just good.
[SPEAKER_24]: They need Tsuguri, the sword game.
[SPEAKER_24]: It was called in America Blade of Honor or something.
[SPEAKER_24]: And you can play it in like different sword styles and everything too.
[SPEAKER_24]: That would be cool.
[SPEAKER_24]: And like you can cut people in half.
[SPEAKER_24]: And I played it in Vegas.
[SPEAKER_24]: Vegas?
[SPEAKER_24]: Because they actually had the Tsuguri one.
[SPEAKER_24]: It was at New York.
[SPEAKER_18]: I am going there.
[SPEAKER_24]: I paid four bucks actually to play that game and have a replay.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's Vegas.
[SPEAKER_24]: No one can hear what you're saying, by the way.
[SPEAKER_20]: I played it in Orange County and it was only eight nickels.
[SPEAKER_24]: Well, there, but I was in Vegas and everything costs more in Vegas.
[SPEAKER_24]: That was the only place I had ever seen it.
[SPEAKER_24]: Um, but that game kicks mocap, you know, takes mocap golf, bends it over and says, hey, here's a sword, guess where it is?
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, but usually golf clubs are longer than swords.
[SPEAKER_24]: Swords hurt more.
[SPEAKER_19]: They're sharper.
[SPEAKER_19]: Have you ever been hit with a golf ball before?
[SPEAKER_24]: Have you ever been anally raped by a sword?
[SPEAKER_19]: Have you?
[SPEAKER_24]: I read a lot.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's all you could come up with?
[SPEAKER_21]: Have you?
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes, that's all I could come up with right now.
[SPEAKER_21]: This is like another Dave over here.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm like open all night.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, he's like CCL Dave.
[SPEAKER_18]: Lightning Dave.
[SPEAKER_18]: I will just be on the attack all night.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_18]: Because you play mocap golf.
[SPEAKER_18]: And you can play on the beach.
[SPEAKER_24]: And for the record, by the way, I have been hit with a golf ball in the neck.
[SPEAKER_24]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_19]: We're at, oh, I mean, no, not, no, where is it, where is it, someone actually hit it?
[SPEAKER_24]: Someone hit a golf ball.
[SPEAKER_19]: No, she threw it at herself.
[SPEAKER_24]: Into my neck.
[SPEAKER_24]: At themselves?
[SPEAKER_18]: In the throat.
[SPEAKER_18]: You're kind of an idiot, aren't you?
[SPEAKER_23]: They're gonna throw the ball at my throat!
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh!
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh, man!
[SPEAKER_23]: It sounds so like you, Loki.
[SPEAKER_24]: Rob's drinking nuclear waste.
[SPEAKER_17]: This green drink that I'm drinking is Hawaiian Punch Green Blast, or what's it called?
[SPEAKER_17]: Hawaiian Punch Green Shit Flavor.
[SPEAKER_24]: I think they only had it in SoCal, and now they have it at the Ralph's by my house.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yes, it's very nice.
[SPEAKER_24]: I blame Melody for getting me hooked to that.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm going to share my accomplishment with everyone on the radio here.
[SPEAKER_17]: I am nine days without soda.
[SPEAKER_17]: I haven't had a soda in nine days.
[SPEAKER_24]: We're starting a 12-step program, Soda Drinkers Anonymous.
[SPEAKER_17]: I should crack open a Pepsi, fuck off So yeah, now this is a big deal for me Because I usually have a Mountain Dew in the morning just to wake up And then like, you know, I drink like three vanilla Cokes when I get home So it's a pretty big deal, so Of course, Hawaiian Punch really isn't that much better for you than soda But eh, you know, it's a special day You know what, it's a special day, so eat shit
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, so should we take a break for a minute?
[SPEAKER_17]: Should we take a break for a minute?
[SPEAKER_17]: You want to do the FUs when we come back?
[SPEAKER_17]: Prepare yourself for the FUs that are coming up when we get back.
[SPEAKER_17]: If you would like to submit an FU, remember, tonight we're at Jamie's, so don't send them to me.
[SPEAKER_17]: You'll see my name in the chatroom says I'm out, out and about.
[SPEAKER_17]: So you want to send them to Jamie.
[SPEAKER_17]: Her nickname is DarkSakuraSSF.
[SPEAKER_17]: So send your FUs of the week to Jamie.
[SPEAKER_17]: And we'll try to keep it short this week, we promise.
[SPEAKER_17]: Everybody in the room is going to keep them short tonight, yes?
[SPEAKER_17]: FUs will be short tonight, yes?
[SPEAKER_17]: No?
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright, so short FUs tonight.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, so we'll be back in a little bit.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, we'll stretch a little more.
[SPEAKER_17]: Let me plug the website.
[SPEAKER_17]: Let me plug the chat room.
[SPEAKER_17]: If you want to be able to submit those FUs, you've got to get to our chat room, and the chat room's at our website.
[SPEAKER_17]: Just orange line, skie.cx, and then click on chat.
[SPEAKER_17]: That URL's a little hard to remember.
[SPEAKER_17]: I've got a much easier one for you to remember.
[SPEAKER_17]: Just go to calibamani.com, C-A-L-I-B-A-M-A-N-I dot com, and we're an affiliate of calibamani.com, so they've got a link right there on the front page to the radio station.
[SPEAKER_18]: You should do a TK, like register a TK, you know, one of those.
[SPEAKER_17]: No.
[SPEAKER_18]: Fine!
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, but they cost money.
[SPEAKER_17]: Actually, yeah, when I get a little more money, I'm going to purchase a .org on behalf of the stations, or .com or .org, so we'll be at Orange Lounge Radio or Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_18]: How about .tv?
[SPEAKER_18]: Because all the good websites have .tv.
[SPEAKER_17]: And then we could say, as seen on TV, even though, you know, we've never been on TV.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, I was on TV for Understation Live, and Jamie's name was in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_18]: My friend Sean wants us to take our recordings of the show and actually broadcast them on public access radio.
[SPEAKER_17]: Can you say shit and fuck on public access radio?
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_19]: Sure you can, they just might censor, I don't know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_19]: If they censored this show, there'd be like three episodes worth of time.
[SPEAKER_24]: Shit, fuck, damn, cock, pussy.
[SPEAKER_24]: Cut!
[SPEAKER_17]: That's my favorite.
[SPEAKER_17]: Little known fact, I actually was a public access celebrity.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, we're going to break.
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright, we're going to break.
[SPEAKER_24]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_24]: We're playing our fuck you songs, so stay tuned.
Rock'n'roll!
Junkie!
JoJo!
[SPEAKER_09]: Miyato, Konoha, Tosuke, Jojo
Yeah, Dr. Bob!
[SPEAKER_01]: Solid Snake, Solid Snake, Solid Snake Can you hear what I'm saying?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, this damn sicko man's in a wheelchair bag I'm gonna kick your ass, beat him, kill him, oh Don't, what am I gonna do?
[SPEAKER_01]: Don't, don't, what am I gonna do?
[SPEAKER_01]: Don't, what am I gonna do?
[SPEAKER_01]: Don't, don't Have you ever seen a cool game like this?
[SPEAKER_30]: Niko Meow, Niko Meow, Niko Meow, Meow, Meow, Meow Oh, ass!
[SPEAKER_30]: This randomness could only be brought to you by Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm eating a taquito.
[SPEAKER_24]: We are eating taquitos.
[SPEAKER_24]: Taquito!
[SPEAKER_24]: I love taquitos.
[SPEAKER_15]: The official food of Orange Lounge?
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_17]: Thank you, Ice Queen, for getting the taquitos.
[SPEAKER_17]: They're delicious.
[SPEAKER_18]: I hate them good.
[SPEAKER_18]: Why?
[SPEAKER_18]: Because I don't like Mexican food.
[SPEAKER_17]: Because it makes you poop?
[SPEAKER_18]: No, I just don't like Mexican food.
[SPEAKER_18]: Their food sucks ass!
[SPEAKER_18]: That's what I have against them.
[SPEAKER_17]: Loki, you forgot the water, too.
[SPEAKER_18]: But I'm pleasantly surprised that, what was it, Chevys, they have hot wings and they were damn good.
[SPEAKER_18]: That was the only thing I ate last night at Chevys.
[SPEAKER_24]: Chevys has damn good fajitas because they have that cornmeal stuff.
[SPEAKER_24]: And me, I'm allergic to corn, but I will eat that cornmeal stuff like all day.
[SPEAKER_24]: I had them give me an extra thing of it and I did nothing but eat that cornmeal one day.
[SPEAKER_17]: Amanda, one of the official lesbians of Orange Launch Radio who was here a couple weeks ago, we were at Chevy's the other day and she kept threatening to tell them it was my birthday.
[SPEAKER_17]: And that got me to thinking, you know, how would the restaurants know?
[SPEAKER_17]: Like, you know, if you go in there every time you eat and tell them it's your birthday, they'd never know, huh?
[SPEAKER_17]: And you can get, like, free ice cream.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, okay, as long as you didn't go to the same Chevy's every week, okay, then they'd probably catch on.
[SPEAKER_19]: But, you know, if you go a different... Then again, they'd probably, like, keep track of it.
[SPEAKER_19]: They'd, like, take pictures of you, like...
[SPEAKER_17]: They don't take pictures.
[SPEAKER_17]: Have you ever seen them snap a camera as they're singing happy birthday?
[SPEAKER_17]: No, they put the sombrero on your head, sing their verse, they leave.
[SPEAKER_17]: If you don't tip them, then they'll know who you are.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's a thing we should do.
[SPEAKER_21]: Just, like, send you out to as many places and see how many places you get a birthday at a day.
[SPEAKER_21]: For, like, a week and just see what you can do.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay, okay, we can do it.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, well, you can pull that off.
[SPEAKER_17]: You're the intern, though.
[SPEAKER_17]: You have to do the embarrassing stuff.
[SPEAKER_17]: We'll tell them it's your birthday.
[SPEAKER_18]: I have to do the embarrassing stuff?
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh, thank you.
[SPEAKER_18]: See, I love my birthday.
[SPEAKER_18]: And then we'll give me the ice cream.
[SPEAKER_18]: My birthday kicks ass because I get to be cheerful and everyone's, like, so sad.
[SPEAKER_18]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_18]: That was the best gift anyone could give me was the death of thousands and thousands of people on my birthday.
[SPEAKER_17]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_17]: Unpolitically correct statement took less than an hour this time into the show.
[SPEAKER_17]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_24]: I think we should get to the fuck you's of the week, right?
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, good idea.
[SPEAKER_19]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_24]: Um, but we don't have, we can't play music in the background because my mixer sucks and I need a new sound card.
[SPEAKER_24]: Anyone wants to get me a new sound card?
[SPEAKER_24]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_24]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_24]: First fuck you of the week goes to my sound card.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm sorry, Cacuaint.
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_18]: This is fucked up.
[SPEAKER_24]: Um... Also, it goes toward having no money right now because I'm paying for my car.
[SPEAKER_24]: Um... Also... It goes toward, um... Not being able to go buy myself, like, more socks because I have this unnatural sock collection.
[SPEAKER_24]: Look at my socks.
[SPEAKER_24]: They're cool.
[SPEAKER_24]: My socks look like a big pink and black barcode.
[SPEAKER_24]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_24]: Um...
[SPEAKER_21]: I said you are $2.37.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_24]: I actually only have $11 I make right now.
[SPEAKER_24]: Um, fuck you to bandwidth.
[SPEAKER_24]: And I really am not angsty about much of anything else.
[SPEAKER_24]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_24]: Fuck you to work tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't want to go.
[SPEAKER_24]: Next.
[SPEAKER_17]: Let's see, my FUs of the week are FU to those people that squat on Derby Owners Club, that sucks FU to gas prices, oh my god Even the cheap shit's two bucks a gallon, F that What else do I want to say FU to?
[SPEAKER_17]: And, I don't know, FU to the fact that I haven't gotten laid in six months, that sucks
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright, Loki's turn.
[SPEAKER_17]: Cause we're all keeping him quick tonight, yeah, yeah?
[SPEAKER_18]: Um, let's see, well, F you to the stupid little kids, just everywhere.
[SPEAKER_18]: Kill them while they're young.
[SPEAKER_18]: Um, if it was a stupid slow-ass van that was in front of me on my way here, um, I understand that you like going 25 miles an hour in a 35, and the fact that all the people in your van are disabled, probably blind or deaf or something, um, you know, seriously, if I had any sort of, you know, rocker-propelled explosive, that van would be gone.
[SPEAKER_18]: And, you know, I almost, I was almost tempted to push them into traffic, because I figure, you know, who's gonna miss them?
[SPEAKER_18]: No one's gonna miss them, so...
[SPEAKER_18]: F you to that.
[SPEAKER_18]: And F you to my site for being stupid because FTP went link right and that sucked because all the files are down for like all day.
[SPEAKER_18]: But I fixed that and that was cool.
[SPEAKER_18]: And F you to me for having so much work because I'm like busy all the time and I can't enjoy anything.
[SPEAKER_18]: Just work, work, work, work, work.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh, F you the gas prices because they suck.
[SPEAKER_18]: I just know because all the gas station tenants are just jealous that we're bombing their country.
[SPEAKER_18]: So, that's it.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right, I only got a few FUs.
[SPEAKER_21]: One is to those people who get on the bus in the wheelchairs but manage to get up and walk when they get off the bus.
[SPEAKER_21]: I always wondered, like, to some of these people who just look absolutely normal, if you push them out to traffic, I bet you anything they would get up and run.
[SPEAKER_21]: They would leave the wheelchair at the middle of the road and get up and fucking run.
[SPEAKER_21]: Another one is to my lack of concentration.
[SPEAKER_21]: Today I almost full combo cancelled off Falling in Love on Light 7 on 2DX and I missed the last fucking note and so I almost killed the machine as I jumped up in circles.
[SPEAKER_21]: What?
[SPEAKER_21]: No, I have a mic.
[SPEAKER_13]: Fuck you to the assholes that were getting in my way while I was trying to pass Daikin Kai Light yesterday at Country Club Lanes.
[SPEAKER_18]: You couldn't pass it anyway.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, I know, but still.
[SPEAKER_13]: They're getting in my way, getting on the machine and giving me shit.
[SPEAKER_13]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_18]: And one of these days on the show, I'm just going to be myself and be nice.
[SPEAKER_18]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_18]: Because I'm, like, a really nice person.
[SPEAKER_18]: I mean, I'm a really nice person.
[SPEAKER_18]: I just have, like, weird strangers.
[SPEAKER_18]: Really?
[SPEAKER_18]: I am!
[SPEAKER_18]: I am nice!
[SPEAKER_18]: You guys have all made me out to be, like, this crazy racist guy.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm not that person.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's what you get for hanging out with Rob.
[SPEAKER_18]: I love everybody.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_18]: Except that... Forget the porn addicts.
[SPEAKER_18]: I love everybody except the disabled and stupid people.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_18]: That would fall under stupid people.
[SPEAKER_18]: Actually, disabled people are cool if they're smart.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's just the stupid people I hate.
[SPEAKER_18]: I hate stupid people all about.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, I hate humanity.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh, well, I guess, you know, I can't win.
[SPEAKER_13]: Fuck the shit I've been having and fuck being single.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_20]: If you had Scandia still for nobody ever giving me my watch back still, it's been a week and I still don't have my watch back.
[SPEAKER_20]: That's all.
[SPEAKER_22]: Fuck you to cunt.
[SPEAKER_22]: Fuck you to stupid people.
[SPEAKER_22]: Fuck you to pussy everywhere.
[SPEAKER_22]: And that's about it right now.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, and fuck you to big ass on the fucking sliding glass window.
[SPEAKER_15]: Check, one, two.
[SPEAKER_15]: Are we still up?
[SPEAKER_15]: Check our level.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, we're going.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: Give your F you one more time, Matt, because they're so great.
[SPEAKER_22]: I said, fuck you to pussy and fuck you to cunt and just pussy everywhere.
[SPEAKER_22]: Just fuck you.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, yeah, I am stupid, people, but that kind of falls in the same category.
[SPEAKER_32]: You've spickled.
[SPEAKER_32]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, you're too nice.
[SPEAKER_17]: We don't like nice.
[SPEAKER_18]: No, I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_18]: and fuck you, the Oprah, because who are you trying to fool reading British lit?
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, like you're reading British lit.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm talking loudly.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think somebody's shooting a machine gun out front.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, we have firecrackers outside or something.
[SPEAKER_17]: Jamie's going to run away.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm going to see if I hear a yell.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm going to see if she yells something.
[SPEAKER_15]: Wait, hold on, hold on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Somebody was knocking on the door.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_32]: They're leaving?
[SPEAKER_02]: Sunja and Johnny are leaving?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, okay, Johnny's not leaving.
[SPEAKER_21]: I gotta say, fuck book clubs.
[SPEAKER_21]: You can say fuck book clubs.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm in a book club.
[SPEAKER_21]: Fuck book clubs.
[SPEAKER_21]: They're stupid.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not Oprah's book club, but it's like Oprah's book club.
[SPEAKER_24]: We need to take a moment so we can let some very special people say hi.
[SPEAKER_24]: She eats books and craps cash.
[SPEAKER_32]: Hi, this is Rick.
[SPEAKER_32]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_32]: And fuck you to Rick for never being around anymore.
[SPEAKER_32]: My life's been good.
[SPEAKER_32]: My week's been good.
[SPEAKER_17]: So your life's good, so you can't say hi to us anymore?
[SPEAKER_32]: I don't know, I've been poking around Scandia lately after work, but I get off work at 1.30, so... Oh, poopy.
[SPEAKER_17]: So nobody gets to see me over there by myself.
[SPEAKER_17]: You're just a mystery now.
[SPEAKER_17]: I am?
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, I mean, you know, because we don't see you.
[SPEAKER_32]: You know what, I've really gone down in skill, too.
[SPEAKER_32]: I mean, I was doing just a standard little one, and then all of a sudden my legs stopped working.
[SPEAKER_17]: Me too, and I've gotten fat, see?
[SPEAKER_17]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_17]: You're expecting to.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_17]: So what do you want to say to all the listeners, the worldwide listeners of Orange Lounge Radio?
[SPEAKER_32]: Play lots of DDR and try to lose your belly.
[SPEAKER_32]: For God's sake, you're embarrassing yourself.
[SPEAKER_32]: That's all.
[SPEAKER_18]: We want to talk about embarrassing yourselves.
[SPEAKER_18]: We saw this guy today.
[SPEAKER_18]: Holy crap.
[SPEAKER_18]: Did he suck ass at freestyle?
[SPEAKER_18]: Man, he was just, like, getting up on their doubles.
[SPEAKER_18]: He had no sense of, you know, coordination, balance, rhythm, or anything.
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't even know why he was... I don't even know how he was able to do doubles to begin with.
[SPEAKER_24]: Robin, I don't know anything about that.
[SPEAKER_18]: He was just up there, like, doing his thing, like, holding the bar, and he tried jumping... Okay, first he started off his first song playing light, little, with no free zeros, and he jumped up over the bar, totally off cue, and totally missed the first step, nearly, like, broke his ankle.
[SPEAKER_18]: It was hilarious.
[SPEAKER_18]: Bye!
[SPEAKER_02]: Bye!
[SPEAKER_17]: Did you ever get to do your FUs, Nita?
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't really have an FU.
[SPEAKER_17]: Why are all the women nice today except Jamie?
[SPEAKER_17]: Jamie's always mean, though.
[SPEAKER_17]: We expect that of her.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, my week's been going okay, so I guess I don't really have enough you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have you always just made furniture?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Furniture made by what we assume to be communists.
[SPEAKER_21]: Dude, it took like four hours to put a fucking desk together.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, this desk, first of all, weighed like 200 pounds.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just to carry it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it was a desk, a wooden desk, a computer desk.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nothing worked right, nothing fit together the way it was supposed to.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, and what about the drawer thing you're making now?
[SPEAKER_21]: The drawers don't even fit right.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm putting together a four-dresser drawer that's got another six million pieces.
[SPEAKER_02]: It sucks.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's communist.
[SPEAKER_02]: So fuck you to furniture that you have to put together.
[SPEAKER_18]: How do you like my desk?
[SPEAKER_18]: It has all these extra pieces.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have to put each individual screw together.
[SPEAKER_02]: A lot of screwing going on.
[SPEAKER_21]: If anybody doesn't know what that's from, watch the Clerks cartoon.
[SPEAKER_21]: It is the best VIG ever.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anybody else have any fuck yous?
[SPEAKER_19]: Give me microphone.
[SPEAKER_19]: Time for puppy to bitch.
[SPEAKER_19]: Hey, wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_19]: Like a bitch is a dog?
[SPEAKER_17]: Get it?
[SPEAKER_17]: That's funny.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_19]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_18]: Damn, why you gotta be such a bitch?
[SPEAKER_19]: Shit.
[SPEAKER_19]: Let me catch you.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_19]: What the... Who the hell... Okay.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay, look out.
[SPEAKER_19]: Jamie needs to get through.
[SPEAKER_19]: Do your abs, Bobby.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_19]: Uh, first of all...
[SPEAKER_19]: Fuck, uh, I'd like to give a fuck you to my toilet in my bathroom, because the toilet seat broke a couple days ago, and now I cannot sit on it.
[SPEAKER_17]: Given the term, I'm gonna cut your ass up in a whole new meeting.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yes, indeed.
[SPEAKER_19]: And then, uh, let's see, um, fuck the smell of weed, because it stinks, and it doesn't come out of carpeting very well.
[SPEAKER_19]: I think you should use an umlaut.
[SPEAKER_19]: I could do that, yes, but I was too lazy to try and figure out what key that is.
[SPEAKER_24]: Now we get to the chatroom Zephius.
[SPEAKER_24]: Has everyone gone?
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay, first one comes from Japanman.
[SPEAKER_24]: Fuck you little kids who get on when he plays Cool 7.
[SPEAKER_24]: And fuck you people who don't like my baby mama.
[SPEAKER_24]: Agreed.
[SPEAKER_17]: Now who that is?
[SPEAKER_17]: My baby mama.
[SPEAKER_24]: We should play that during the next break.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yes, but you need to play it.
[SPEAKER_17]: Sorry, I'm killing JB.
[SPEAKER_24]: The next one is from JB, or Justin Circuit in the name.
[SPEAKER_24]: Jenny's bitch.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah, Jenny's bitch.
[SPEAKER_24]: FU to ATTBI Comcast to cancel the account due to a server glitch and couldn't get on for three days when it did work.
[SPEAKER_24]: The emails didn't work.
[SPEAKER_24]: And hasn't gotten two of his secondary accounts and called the customer service 18 times and been on the line with them for five hours total.
[SPEAKER_24]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_24]: There's a solution to that.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's called Better Business Bureau.
[SPEAKER_24]: You should write them.
[SPEAKER_24]: That doesn't do shit.
[SPEAKER_18]: I haven't...
[SPEAKER_18]: I have an FU for my computer FU to Microsoft because their Windows XP thinks it wants to try to connect to the internet all the time even though I click the option that says do not connect to the internet and instead it's like oh I want to connect to the internet JB by the way talk to me later and I'll let you know how you can get them in legal trouble with the federal government Go frivolous lawsuits and tell them to suck your dick
[SPEAKER_24]: John Field says F you assholes in his dorm that let the air out of his two rear tires and forced him to call AAA.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yes, that sucks.
[SPEAKER_17]: Fuck AAA for having such high insurance rates.
[SPEAKER_17]: What the fuck is that?
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah, but AAA, I don't have AAA and my friend's AAA let me unlock my car door when I let my keys in.
[SPEAKER_14]: That is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_24]: But AAA can still blow me.
[SPEAKER_24]: We need to get through these.
[SPEAKER_24]: Next is Ninja Usagi Koi.
[SPEAKER_24]: I want to send an FU to our mom for not letting us put the DDR machines outside for a tournament.
[SPEAKER_24]: And now all the people are going to die from heatstroke.
[SPEAKER_24]: And yeah, an FU to her dad.
[SPEAKER_24]: And for not letting her hang out with Yogi.
[SPEAKER_24]: Dad.
[SPEAKER_24]: Love ya.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_19]: I know that situation about not moving machines outside for a tournament.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_24]: DBGL.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_24]: Moohymer, first of all, hello to DarkTetia.
[SPEAKER_24]: Hi, Moohymer.
[SPEAKER_24]: And so now, fuck this dumbass lifeguard instructor bitch who looks and acts exactly like Phoebe from Friends.
[SPEAKER_17]: Smelly cat!
[SPEAKER_24]: She told us she had to go potty three times.
[SPEAKER_17]: Was it number one or number two?
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, she should have gone to the pool.
[SPEAKER_24]: Maybe I'll be swimming in pee.
[SPEAKER_24]: Fuck that feeling when you have 800 different food items in your house and you can't find the one unknown thing you're craving.
[SPEAKER_24]: And... Aww.
[SPEAKER_24]: And fuck gay people for not living near him and making him feel lonely.
[SPEAKER_14]: You need to come to Frisco.
[SPEAKER_24]: Next is Ness151.
[SPEAKER_24]: Fuck DDR Coralville.
[SPEAKER_24]: Because it's DDR crippled right now.
[SPEAKER_24]: Next is Sautome Ranma.
[SPEAKER_24]: Fuck you to dead air.
[SPEAKER_24]: We don't have dead air.
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't know what you're talking about.
[SPEAKER_17]: It might be rebuffers or something.
[SPEAKER_24]: But it's not us, because as far as I can see, we're still broadcasting just fine.
[SPEAKER_24]: One problem with my microphone is that everyone here is going to have to do that.
[SPEAKER_24]: Talk into the microphone and talk loudly.
[SPEAKER_24]: Project.
[SPEAKER_24]: Because... Oh, shut up.
[SPEAKER_24]: La la la la.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, anyway.
[SPEAKER_24]: Um, yeah, and anyway, um, PsyQ of the Week goes to Hormones, enough said.
[SPEAKER_24]: PsyQ of the Week goes to a DDR Extreme OST for apparently not being released.
[SPEAKER_17]: They're not going to release it?
[SPEAKER_24]: It's not going to be out for a while.
[SPEAKER_24]: Um, however, talk to me later.
[SPEAKER_24]: Um, SkylineDC505.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, we might be able to hook you up anyway.
[SPEAKER_24]: F you to the California High School exit exam for making me come to school while three-fourths of the whole school got to sleep in.
[SPEAKER_24]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_24]: For the Alabama ones, they just gave it to us while we were in class.
[SPEAKER_17]: There's an X exam now in high school?
[SPEAKER_24]: And, like, I got a hundred on it.
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't remember that.
[SPEAKER_24]: Holy shit!
[SPEAKER_24]: Snub dyspnoid.
[SPEAKER_24]: Long F you.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_24]: First off... First off... Hey, let me read!
[SPEAKER_24]: Shut up!
[SPEAKER_24]: First off, fuck driver's training school and the poop shoot.
[SPEAKER_24]: I would honestly rather have a duck shit down my throat than to sit through that boring ass shit.
[SPEAKER_24]: Everyone in the class.
[SPEAKER_15]: This one was off.
[SPEAKER_24]: We had a mic off.
[SPEAKER_24]: Everybody, don't touch the on-off switch on the microphone.
[SPEAKER_24]: Guys, we're sorry.
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_24]: And actually, then, we probably didn't get DCB's post.
[SPEAKER_24]: DCB, send me yours again.
[SPEAKER_17]: What was the last thing you guys heard?
[SPEAKER_17]: We didn't know what the chatroom, the last thing they heard.
[SPEAKER_24]: I was reading the thank you, so I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_24]: Bitch, you did miss the whole big thing about 24.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, that's okay if you missed the whole thing about 24.
[SPEAKER_17]: That was nothing.
[SPEAKER_24]: Because we don't give a shit.
[SPEAKER_24]: Sorry, Rob.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay, then.
[SPEAKER_24]: That's a while.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_24]: DCB, send me yours again.
[SPEAKER_17]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_17]: It just came in at the land there.
[SPEAKER_24]: Fuck you to Photoshop7 for taking 7 minutes to load.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm sorry, Photoshop7 for taking 7 minutes to load.
[SPEAKER_24]: Fuck his dad for buying lots of food and not letting him eat it.
[SPEAKER_24]: And fuck you to the green card manager for telling him to get off the horse ride at MGL.
[SPEAKER_24]: Brad, LankyStyle.
[SPEAKER_24]: This fuck you goes to Racist.
[SPEAKER_24]: I hate you all equally.
[SPEAKER_24]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_24]: Next is Jazz.
[SPEAKER_24]: Fuck school.
[SPEAKER_24]: Die, die, die.
[SPEAKER_24]: And I laugh at all the exit exam people.
[SPEAKER_24]: They just started that this year, so I missed it by a year, so I laugh.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ha, ha, ha, ha.
[SPEAKER_19]: I thought they started the exit exams, like, last year, because I heard about it, that they were giving it out in my school, but I didn't have to take it.
[SPEAKER_24]: By the way, it died at duck shit down the throat.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_24]: If you want to send me that again, but you did say fuckity, fuck, fuck, fuck, and fuck him up the nose hole.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, we missed that whole thing with Snub Disanoids, FU?
[SPEAKER_17]: We've been down that long?
[SPEAKER_17]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, that sucks.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm sorry, guys.
[SPEAKER_17]: Send that again, because I nom- What you also missed is I nominated that as one of the top three FUs ever.
[SPEAKER_17]: That was beautiful.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, as long as they heard Fuck Em Up the Nosehole, that was the best.
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_24]: Um, Muhymer, Dead Air.
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay, that ends our Fuck You's of the Week.
[SPEAKER_24]: So to our Fuck You's of the Week, we say, fuck you.
[SPEAKER_17]: Beautiful.
[SPEAKER_17]: Break time?
[SPEAKER_17]: When we come back from break, believe it or not, when we come back from break, I have big Bomani news.
[SPEAKER_17]: It might be rumors, but I went and looked up news.
[SPEAKER_17]: So, we're going to talk about Bomani.
[SPEAKER_17]: We're going to talk about Bomani when we come back.
[SPEAKER_17]: Believe it or not, on this show, we're going to talk about Bomani.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yes, break time.
[SPEAKER_17]: Come on forward dots.
[SPEAKER_00]: Everybody to the limit, who's that?
[SPEAKER_00]: It's to the limit, everybody come on, Fahogwa guys.
[SPEAKER_00]: Come on, Fahogwa guys.
[SPEAKER_00]: I see you jocking me, trying to play like you know me.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm like, come on, Fahogwa guys.
[SPEAKER_00]: I said, come on, Fahogwa guys.
[SPEAKER_00]: Everybody to the limit, the G is to the limit, everybody come on, Fahogwa guys.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know who it is, but it probably is Fuhogwa Guys.
[SPEAKER_00]: I asked my friend Joe, I asked my friend Jake, they said it was Fuhogwa Guys.
[SPEAKER_00]: I said, come on, Fuhogwa Guys, I said, come on, Fuhogwa Guys.
[SPEAKER_00]: Who's it to the limit?
[SPEAKER_00]: Say me, I'm to the limit, everybody come on, Fuhogwa Guys.
[SPEAKER_00]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_26]: Please listen to Orange Lounge Radio, because real radio makes Captain Jack cry.
[SPEAKER_17]: Hi, we're back.
[SPEAKER_24]: You're listening to Orange Lounge Radio, and... By popular request, actually, we do need to give a mention of this.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, what's this?
[SPEAKER_24]: We're going to do... The F2 that everyone missed from Subdisfinoid.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, that was so horrible.
[SPEAKER_17]: Too bad about that.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, let's hear it again.
[SPEAKER_24]: First off, fuck driver's training in the poop chute.
[SPEAKER_24]: I would honestly rather have a duck shit down my throat than to have to sit through that boring-ass shit.
[SPEAKER_24]: Everyone in the class is a total bitch, even the teacher.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's not like if you have a penis and testicles, I hate you.
[SPEAKER_24]: I will smash your testicles because they're sensitive.
[SPEAKER_24]: Bad men... Or men bad, I should say.
[SPEAKER_24]: Respect women because we spit you out our baby holes.
[SPEAKER_24]: Indeed.
[SPEAKER_24]: Fuck driver's training only, fuck it so exclusively so that all of my horrible negative energy can be used to destroy driver's training forever.
[SPEAKER_24]: That fucking school can suck my ass.
[SPEAKER_24]: I haven't slept more than four hours each night this past week and I won't get enough sleep this week.
[SPEAKER_24]: Fuck that bullshit, fuck it up the nose hole.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yes, the nose hole.
[SPEAKER_24]: But you missed the fuckity fuck fuck fuck.
[SPEAKER_24]: That was the best.
[SPEAKER_17]: Fuck fuckity fuck fuck.
[SPEAKER_17]: Fuck you, you fucking fuck.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_17]: Shit.
[SPEAKER_17]: So, we wanted to do...
[SPEAKER_17]: We wanted to do another song really fast, but it's something that Loki has to introduce.
[SPEAKER_17]: And why is that, Mr. Loki?
[SPEAKER_18]: It's another remix I did.
[SPEAKER_18]: You know, it's not as good as my last one.
[SPEAKER_18]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
Are we coming?
Into the dark, black forest.
[SPEAKER_24]: That was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_24]: I was really impressed with that.
[SPEAKER_17]: That was pretty neat.
[SPEAKER_17]: It was very subtle.
[SPEAKER_17]: The modem stream probably doesn't do that justice because a lot of it's very subtle.
[SPEAKER_17]: But...
[SPEAKER_18]: But, as, okay, well we probably should go into SimCon news since this is SimCon news.
[SPEAKER_18]: Um, okay, obviously SimCon news, the big news, well for me at least, is Leech from Loki 2.0 has finally, finally, two month delay launched.
[SPEAKER_18]: Um.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's got, right now, the initial update had the 2DX DWI project files for 2DX 2nd style through 5th style.
[SPEAKER_18]: And so there's about, I'd say about 50-some files up there at the moment.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm uploading more probably later this week as I get to work on them.
[SPEAKER_18]: I went ahead and... Oh man, that looks ugly on that.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay, anyways.
[SPEAKER_18]: So...
[SPEAKER_18]: I went ahead and, as promised, exclusive to Orange Launch Radio, if you're a wonderful listener of the show, you get access to a special page every week.
[SPEAKER_18]: Now, I was kind of bad and didn't really hide the page well enough this time, but next time the files will be more hidden.
[SPEAKER_18]: But anyways...
[SPEAKER_18]: This page, exclusive to you guys, is going to be the release of my two remixes, The Legend of Trance and the Dark Black Forest Midnight Angel mix.
[SPEAKER_18]: And so, to access this page, what you want to do is go to my site, which is www.willddrforfood.net slash leechfromloki.com
[SPEAKER_18]: and then what you want to do once you get to that and you want to type in also the special HTML page which is going to be hotmonkeysex.html and that will bring you up to the wonderful page with my two links for my MP3s.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's a secret page and what are the special MP3s that they can download this week?
[SPEAKER_18]: The Legend of Trance which is a remix of The Legend of Max which is just fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's my favorite remix so far.
[SPEAKER_18]: and that's Legend of Trance, Loki vs. ZZ featuring Sundecade.
[SPEAKER_18]: Then we have the Dark Black Forest, Midnight Angel mix, Steve Reiner vs. Loki featuring Sonaris.
[SPEAKER_17]: So those are exclusive remixes to Orange Lounge listeners and we just posted the link in the chat room if you didn't get it and so go leech away and you can listen to those.
[SPEAKER_17]: But don't listen to them now, wait until after the show because we need our listeners.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, so we'll have...
[SPEAKER_18]: Well, as far as DWIs going, you know, for Legend of Trance, as mentioned on the page, I'm thinking about that one for Tourney Mix 4, so that'll be that one, but Dark Black Forest, Midnight Angel Mix is up for grabs, so.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's just a steady 140 BPM.
[SPEAKER_17]: In other words, you're basically saying, you can't, or basically you're telling the listeners, don't do a DWI for Legend of Trance, because you claim it for Tourney Mix 4.
[SPEAKER_17]: You peed on it and made it your territory.
[SPEAKER_10]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright, well, speaking of your mixes, how about something that was your choice?
[SPEAKER_24]: How about the, uh, Cage Matches?
[SPEAKER_24]: You wanna do that?
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_24]: Let's do Cage Match.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright, um, I don't have Holic, I have Holic, but it won't play a background because of my stupid sound card.
[SPEAKER_24]: Fuck my sound card!
[SPEAKER_03]: You sound like Hee-Haw.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not like, Ah, Mamie Pearl, this is Hee-Haw!
[SPEAKER_24]: But no, we're going to go ahead and play, basically the way that our cage match works is that each of us picks a song, and one of us will have won the previous week, so that's the song that should be in rotation right now, but really isn't right now.
[SPEAKER_17]: It isn't right now, but we'll figure it out.
[SPEAKER_17]: We'll put them both in or something, the last week's winner, unless it wins again, which it may.
[SPEAKER_17]: It may win again, but I don't think it will.
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't like it.
[SPEAKER_24]: I think it stunk.
[SPEAKER_24]: Don't let us influence you, or better yet, just let me influence you.
[SPEAKER_17]: So we're just going to play a clip of last week's winner, right?
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah, I'll play a decent-sized clip of it, because I actually have Life Out 3.
[SPEAKER_24]: This is, what was that track again?
[SPEAKER_17]: Sasha with Expander.
[SPEAKER_18]: Sasha with Expander.
[SPEAKER_17]: This is last week's winner.
[SPEAKER_24]: That was a little bit of an expander.
[SPEAKER_24]: Anyway, this is Rob's pick of the week.
[SPEAKER_24]: You want to tell us about it?
[SPEAKER_24]: Actually, we should rate that song.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's cool.
[SPEAKER_24]: I give it a 7.
[SPEAKER_17]: No, we don't do last week's.
[SPEAKER_17]: We don't do last week's.
[SPEAKER_17]: Usually.
[SPEAKER_17]: Because we already ranked it last week.
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_17]: And we said it shouldn't win, and it did, because our chatroom hates us.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, my song, and I had to kind of come up with this at the last minute.
[SPEAKER_17]: This really isn't what I would have usually picked, but I completely forgot that, like, hi, we're moving the show tonight, so I actually have to burn a CD off my song.
[SPEAKER_17]: But luckily I have a CD in my car, and this is actually a pretty good song.
[SPEAKER_17]: And I got turned on to this song a couple years ago because I...
[SPEAKER_17]: Tell me a fable, a fable Tell me a fable
[SPEAKER_08]: Tell me a fake, tell me the fake one A fake, tell me the fake one Talk to me, tenderly, so reality and fantasy Will meld together, only in one thing
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura.com
Thanks for watching!
Tell me a fable.
A fable.
A fable that will never end.
And now, I dream.
Dream.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_24]: That was Robert Miles of Fable.
[SPEAKER_17]: The big plop at the end is the best.
[SPEAKER_24]: As far as my opinion of that song, he's done better.
[SPEAKER_24]: So it gets a six.
[SPEAKER_18]: Microphones are going every which way.
[SPEAKER_18]: The song is alright.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, like, he could have done better.
[SPEAKER_18]: But, um, Ever After really sucked ass.
[SPEAKER_18]: So, uh, that's gonna affect my decision.
[SPEAKER_18]: Um, I'm gonna have to give it a 6.
[SPEAKER_17]: That song rocks and you don't, 10.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, wow, that's a real biased opinion there.
[SPEAKER_18]: Um, I have a really bad experience with that movie.
[SPEAKER_18]: And, honestly... Care to explain?
[SPEAKER_21]: Go there with the chick who cheats on you and gets pregnant.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's all I gotta say.
[SPEAKER_21]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's about the song, not the movie.
[SPEAKER_21]: I know, that's why I just said, people tell me to explain.
[SPEAKER_18]: No, honestly, I really didn't like that song, so I'll give it like a four.
[SPEAKER_18]: And that's being really, really, really nice.
[SPEAKER_19]: For those people that are listening, Rob's just giving raspberries to Zero right now.
[SPEAKER_19]: Many times.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know, I think it's nice.
[SPEAKER_19]: Honestly, that song would put me to sleep if I weren't in here talking to other people right now.
[SPEAKER_19]: Three.
[SPEAKER_13]: Six.
[SPEAKER_13]: I could probably see it in, like, Keyboard Mania or something.
[SPEAKER_22]: Okay, I like that song, okay?
[SPEAKER_22]: So, I have a new FU to all of you bitches in here.
[SPEAKER_22]: I give that song a ten, because that's, like, my kind of song.
[SPEAKER_22]: I liked it.
Damn right!
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd have to give it like a 9.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a pretty good song, I like it, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like any trance just about, so I mean, soft, hard, anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, I'll say that again, I'd give that song a 9.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not perfect, but it's pretty damn good.
[SPEAKER_20]: Alright, well, I'd have to give it a 7, because I heard a DJ Epic version that's about, like, that's twice as good as that.
[SPEAKER_20]: So, I'll give it a 7.
[SPEAKER_17]: So, the average score is, and remember, I'm not very good at math, 9.
[SPEAKER_24]: So... Okay.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's my turn now.
[SPEAKER_24]: Um, I don't know who did this, because I downloaded it by accident one day, but this is Link's theme, Heave Dance Remix.
[SPEAKER_24]: Here you go.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay, I know it's not the best and I didn't put it in there with an intention of winning, but when I first downloaded it, it made me really bouncy and hyper, so I give it a seven.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'll go ahead.
[SPEAKER_17]: Like, when I'm listening to that, I bounce up and down a lot, and then I want to take a really big shit.
[SPEAKER_17]: So, I give it eight rolls of toilet paper.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay, um, let's see here.
[SPEAKER_18]: Uh, let's see here, it violated so many rules.
[SPEAKER_18]: What's a speed mix?
[SPEAKER_18]: And speed mixes all suck ass.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_18]: Two, if... What the hell, they make it with mod trackers, some shit like that?
[SPEAKER_18]: Sounds like it's eight years old.
[SPEAKER_18]: Fucking, the song had no... Oh, it had big bass.
[SPEAKER_18]: People like big bass, I'll put big bass in there.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay, drum beats, drum beats sound good.
[SPEAKER_18]: Let's throw those in there, too.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh, and let's get a MIDI of Link's theme.
[SPEAKER_18]: We'll put that there.
[SPEAKER_18]: Look, I made a remix!
[SPEAKER_18]: Woohoo!
[SPEAKER_18]: Look at me go!
[SPEAKER_17]: I got a big bass, wanna come over?
[SPEAKER_18]: So, um, yeah, I'm gonna have to give that, like, a two, and, uh, and Robert Miles' song, well, is better now.
[SPEAKER_18]: Having, having, having, you know, it's like, it's like if you have the ugly chick and you stand next to her and it makes you look better, that's what this song was.
[SPEAKER_18]: This song was the ugly chick.
[SPEAKER_19]: And the rest of the group moans and groans with that comment.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, come on, is, was it really that bad?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_13]: Uh, eight.
[SPEAKER_19]: I... Oh, come on, Loki could do better than that.
[SPEAKER_19]: Anyways, uh... Yeah.
[SPEAKER_19]: I like it.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's short!
[SPEAKER_19]: It's short.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's the good thing about this song.
[SPEAKER_19]: It doesn't drag out.
[SPEAKER_19]: I give it an 8.5.
[SPEAKER_22]: Okay, so I like the fact that it was bouncy.
[SPEAKER_22]: It was bouncy.
[SPEAKER_22]: So there's a couple of points there.
[SPEAKER_22]: And it had Link's theme, which... A couple of other points, but other than that, it sucked ass.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm giving it a 2.
[SPEAKER_22]: Real, real, real quick.
[SPEAKER_22]: If it's going that fast, how the fuck are you going to dance to that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Woo, it's fast, I mean, I mean.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, it's a little fast, a little too bouncy, a little too happy, happy.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think I like it that much.
[SPEAKER_02]: I give it like a seven or a six, but I give Loki's commentary a ten.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love that.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, I just want to say really fast, though, Loki, you don't dance to it, you have sex to it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just don't want to tell Dan that Rob did humping motions in his chair.
[SPEAKER_21]: You know, I say, if the FUs were still going, I would say fuck you to all who gave it lower than at least a 7.
[SPEAKER_21]: Cause, if you don't have any, like, $8,000... Well, the fuck yous are over.
[SPEAKER_21]: Fuck you, buddy.
[SPEAKER_18]: Fuck you, too!
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_18]: Here's an idea, okay?
[SPEAKER_18]: Here's an idea.
[SPEAKER_18]: I've heard better Final Fantasy remixes, okay?
[SPEAKER_18]: Better Final Fantasy remixes, they need to just do a decent remix of it, then we'll give it a decent score.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright, well let's just go ahead and get voting out of the way.
[SPEAKER_24]: We're going to play a little bitty clip to the songs one more time.
Name them all.
[SPEAKER_24]: We're going to name them all, and here's like a little bit of it.
[SPEAKER_24]: This one is Sasha with Expander.
Okay, that's enough.
[SPEAKER_24]: Next one is Robert Miles with Fable.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay, that's enough of that.
[SPEAKER_24]: And then Link's theme.
[SPEAKER_24]: Vote!
[SPEAKER_24]: Vote now!
[SPEAKER_24]: In the meantime, we're going to hand the microphone to Loki to go angst on us again while I pull up the next sub break.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, I'm going to do Bimani News because we promised it like an hour ago and we never did it.
[SPEAKER_17]: So you've all been sitting there getting moist, your panties have been getting moist in anticipation of this hot, hot... I can't believe puppy just said that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Say that again.
[SPEAKER_17]: Things dried up by now.
[SPEAKER_24]: Now they're crusty.
[SPEAKER_17]: God, things I did not need to know
[SPEAKER_17]: I am stealing this news.
[SPEAKER_17]: I will quote my source because a lot of people don't.
[SPEAKER_17]: I was just surfing around the net during one of the weeks and I found this news.
[SPEAKER_17]: It was posted on the LiveJournal community for Bomani.
[SPEAKER_17]: So it's just username Bomani on the LiveJournal community.
[SPEAKER_17]: LiveJournal.com slash tilde Bomani.
[SPEAKER_17]: And by the way, I'll take this opportunity to plug that Orange Lounge also has a LiveJournal community.
[SPEAKER_17]: So if you go to LiveJournal.com slash tilde Orange Lounge, there's our community.
[SPEAKER_17]: So if you use LiveJournal, add us to your friends list because we like it when people add us to their friends list.
[SPEAKER_18]: I had a live journal once, then I never posted, and they got rid of it for me.
[SPEAKER_17]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm not a racist, bastard.
[SPEAKER_17]: This was, I'm going to credit, and actually I think this person's on the Orange Lounge community, which makes them that much cooler.
[SPEAKER_17]: This was posted by Hata, H-A-T-A, maybe that's Hata or something.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, Hata.
[SPEAKER_17]: It looks like Hata to me.
[SPEAKER_24]: She's also in our community, too.
[SPEAKER_17]: 2DX Night Style Location Test
[SPEAKER_17]: So, again, I don't know how reliable this news source is, take it with a grain of salt, but this is just all in fun, right?
[SPEAKER_17]: So, finally, Konami will launch the location test for Bomani 2DX 9th Style on May 5th.
[SPEAKER_17]: We have rumors saying that this is going to be the last installment.
[SPEAKER_17]: But it has not been confirmed yet.
[SPEAKER_17]: On the official site, they announced a few songs that will be brought back.
[SPEAKER_17]: However, that is not all.
[SPEAKER_17]: We all know that Beatmania has closed its history last year with the release of Beatmania the Final.
[SPEAKER_17]: It was not over yet.
[SPEAKER_17]: They are also bringing back some songs that was on Beatmania.
[SPEAKER_17]: The songs include LED Hellscaper, Tack with Release Your Mind, Pink Pong with Pink Dream, The Bald Head, Ska Go Go, DJ Naguro with Miriam featuring Believe Again.
[SPEAKER_17]: Just to name a few, I'm pretty sure that some of those songs would be remixed by our favorite artists.
[SPEAKER_17]: Due to massive resurrection of classic Beatmania songs, it is possible that they may have to take out many 2DX songs as well.
[SPEAKER_17]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_17]: Of course, we will have new songs.
[SPEAKER_17]: We will have new songs brought to us by DJ Taka, Tak, Ram, and many other familiar names.
[SPEAKER_17]: Some songs that would definitely catch our heart include Taka with Natural Principle, Aya with Death Wind, Tak with Irrational, Yamato with X-49,
[SPEAKER_17]: and Akira Yamaoka with Electric Wave.
[SPEAKER_24]: First of all, I went to Tac's site and Irrational's not on there.
[SPEAKER_17]: Ah, so maybe... No, it's Tac.
[SPEAKER_17]: It says Tac here.
[SPEAKER_17]: Tac with Irrational.
[SPEAKER_24]: I also scoured several of my downloading places and I haven't found that anywhere.
[SPEAKER_17]: So, might be a little bit of bullshit, but there you go.
[SPEAKER_17]: So, what do you guys think about 2DX9's style possibly being the last?
[SPEAKER_24]: Fuck you, Konami.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't think they would do that.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm sorry, but that series makes way too much money.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_19]: Even with as rare as some machines are in here in the US, it could make a lot more money here if Konami in Japan paid attention, but I'm sure as popular as it is in Japan, they wouldn't cut it off now.
[SPEAKER_18]: Just don't let 2DX get in the hands of Konami of America.
[SPEAKER_18]: Holy crap.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh god, that's a scary thought!
[SPEAKER_24]: Unless they're going to give us 9-key 2DX or something, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_24]: That'd be weird.
[SPEAKER_19]: But then it'd be Poppin' DX!
[SPEAKER_18]: Resurrect, freaking, what was it, Kraken DJ.
[SPEAKER_17]: Kraken DJ's the shit, I like that game a lot.
[SPEAKER_17]: Anybody else want to say anything about Night Style, Night Style being the last things they want to see on Night Style?
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't know, more Taka.
[SPEAKER_17]: If this were the last 2DX...
[SPEAKER_17]: Say if they do a Beatmania 4, a fourth series or whatever, what do you think they should do in it?
[SPEAKER_18]: I was actually talking about this earlier today with Zero.
[SPEAKER_18]: I was saying that they should add, much like Beatmania 3 had the foot pedal effector thing, which didn't do shit, Crossfader.
[SPEAKER_18]: Like we were talking about, what was it we were talking about?
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh, Healing Vision Angelic, where that one part where it's just all din-din-din-din.
[SPEAKER_18]: Have that be like a Crossfader part on there.
[SPEAKER_18]: Something like that.
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_18]: A little bit more elaborate.
[SPEAKER_19]: I was thinking also, you know, like in Keyboard Mania, how you have the wheel?
[SPEAKER_19]: Something like that.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_17]: Here's my suggestion.
[SPEAKER_17]: This is the same thing they need to do to DDR.
[SPEAKER_17]: Like when they bring DDR to a new series, if they're going to do a DDR 2DX or whatever.
[SPEAKER_17]: They need to do a... Well, Freeze Notes is one thing, because Easy to DJ has that, but it's kind of overrated.
[SPEAKER_24]: Beatmania, the final, does have the full rotational... They do have that.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_17]: They haven't done that in 2DX yet.
[SPEAKER_17]: I would suggest some kind of more elaborate battle mode.
[SPEAKER_17]: Like, imagine if they had the thing in Disney's Rave to 2DX.
[SPEAKER_10]: That would be cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes, exactly.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, they have all these characters.
[SPEAKER_24]: That they don't use anymore because they're the total background.
[SPEAKER_17]: I think the new versions of DDR and 2DX need to have more competitive modes, because DDR's always been a co-op game till now.
[SPEAKER_24]: They need freakin' Dance Battle again.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, if it were... That was the second mix.
[SPEAKER_17]: Exactly, if it had more, if it elaborated a little more on competition, like, I think it would be a kick-ass game.
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, actually, what I would like to see again is an actual, another Link version.
[SPEAKER_19]: I think that would be a really good idea.
[SPEAKER_19]: So you think maybe it's coincidence they're ending DDR and 2DX at the same time?
[SPEAKER_17]: To bring them back?
[SPEAKER_17]: It's this big, substream resurrection?
[SPEAKER_17]: Maybe, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_17]: Maybe, maybe not.
[SPEAKER_18]: You know what I'd like to see?
[SPEAKER_18]: I'd like to see Beat Mania's song selections on DDR.
[SPEAKER_18]: Just get rid of all that shit that they're ripping from like Dance Mania, like all these speed mixes.
[SPEAKER_17]: Anything from Wild Side, I say the Dance Mania stuff is the best stuff in DDR.
[SPEAKER_17]: It always is.
[SPEAKER_17]: A little, sometimes not.
[SPEAKER_19]: As in the Queen songs that they horribly rape and destroy.
[SPEAKER_17]: The most freestyling songs.
[SPEAKER_17]: Always the most freestyling songs out of anything in DDR.
[SPEAKER_18]: So you're saying that you would rather take Scenarius Speedy Mix versus The Sound of Goodbye or Never Look Back.
[SPEAKER_16]: But Sound of Goodbye and Never Look Back are licensed songs as well.
[SPEAKER_17]: Fly Away.
[SPEAKER_17]: Those are all licensed songs you're naming.
[SPEAKER_17]: They're not Konami originals.
[SPEAKER_17]: They're all licensed songs.
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright, fine.
[SPEAKER_18]: General Relativity, 19 November.
[SPEAKER_18]: How about Wow Wow 70s?
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm not saying to get rid of those, but don't get rid of the Dance Meeting stuff because that's some of the best stuff.
[SPEAKER_18]: What am I talking about?
[SPEAKER_18]: Anyway, say just fuck up the steps in the first place.
[SPEAKER_13]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, most of the Dance We Need stuff is fine, but I got one word for you.
[SPEAKER_13]: Joga.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_17]: I got one word for you.
[SPEAKER_17]: I got one word for you, bitch.
[SPEAKER_17]: Politary.
[SPEAKER_24]: No, Joga, also known as Ban For More's Lounge.
[SPEAKER_24]: Because they do nothing but the same damn song every time.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh god, Loki just said he wants to make a remix.
[SPEAKER_24]: Please do a Joker remix.
[SPEAKER_17]: Please, please, please.
[SPEAKER_24]: Rob, by the way, I've warned you, that's the trap chair.
[SPEAKER_24]: Don't fall.
[SPEAKER_19]: Rob almost fell out of it again.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's like the second time in five minutes.
[SPEAKER_18]: You know, one thing I like about Extreme is how you're seeing more music that you wouldn't expect to see on DDR at all.
[SPEAKER_18]: I would hope to see that, like, even if they did have, like, a next version or whatever, or didn't, I would just hope that they would, like, keep going with the evolution of music that they're finally doing in Extreme.
[SPEAKER_21]: Like, how they have, like, rock beat music and they actually have real stuff instead of all that same annoying crap that they had from the past.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, like, uh, We Are The Champions, because that song's just played so much.
[SPEAKER_18]: I mean, I can't tell you how many times I tell people, stop playing We Are The Champions, keep hearing that song over and over.
[SPEAKER_17]: They took Queen and made it gay.
[SPEAKER_17]: And for the record, I play that song.
[SPEAKER_19]: And for the record, Queen was gay.
[SPEAKER_19]: I know that, dammit!
[SPEAKER_17]: But the music wasn't until that.
[SPEAKER_24]: I think we just made JB have a cry because it's SyFam.
[SPEAKER_17]: Ice Queen, by the way, just got a zing with that.
[SPEAKER_18]: Even still, you know, there's better stuff that's come from SyFam.
[SPEAKER_18]: Look at freaking DDR USA.
[SPEAKER_18]: I mean, those songs were awesome.
[SPEAKER_18]: You know, Take It To The Morning Light, you know.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah!
[SPEAKER_18]: Seriously, we are the champions!
[SPEAKER_03]: Ooh, na-na-na-na-na, yeah!
[SPEAKER_18]: DarkBlackForest, I mean, that was awesome.
[SPEAKER_19]: Ooh, and Sandstorm!
[SPEAKER_19]: We can rave!
[SPEAKER_24]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_24]: I think we're going to probably have to take a break.
[SPEAKER_17]: I have one more story that needs to be read.
[SPEAKER_17]: Needs to be read.
[SPEAKER_17]: Because actually some people were alluding to this.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm sorry, what were we saying?
[SPEAKER_24]: We have to also tally the votes.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, we have to tally the votes.
[SPEAKER_17]: We'll do that during the break.
[SPEAKER_17]: But I have to read this news.
[SPEAKER_17]: And now, again, as with the last story, as with the last story, take this as a rumor.
[SPEAKER_17]: Take this as a rumor.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_17]: It's just a rumor until we know more about it.
[SPEAKER_17]: Konami of Japan told that they are thinking about introducing Beatmania 2DX to the USA.
[SPEAKER_17]: After gaining so much popularity by their release of DDR USA Mix, they said they are considering the release of the 2DX series as well.
[SPEAKER_17]: The Konami of Japan says DDR USA was a big success.
[SPEAKER_17]: The number of players is still increasing and we also get several emails asking if we are going to release the American version of 2DX.
[SPEAKER_17]: Konami of America is excited about this as well.
[SPEAKER_17]: One of the spokesmen said the DJ scene is probably more popular in America than Japan.
[SPEAKER_17]: I am sure that the game will catch the heart of both real DJs Not yet, Loki And the people who want to be one So, want to be a DJ?
[SPEAKER_17]: Just start playing 2DX That's exactly what they're saying here
[SPEAKER_17]: The music is great for audience, too, and I don't see why this can't be a success.
[SPEAKER_17]: It is rumored that the new machine will be revealed at E3 2003.
[SPEAKER_17]: Depending on the schedule, it might be postponed to 2004.
[SPEAKER_17]: I wanna go!
[SPEAKER_17]: Nope, nope, not done yet.
[SPEAKER_17]: Unlike DDR, instead of the home controller, the entire machine will be brought in and it will be on free play.
[SPEAKER_17]: They are also thinking about bringing guest players from Japan to show us how the game is played.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's where I start to think the story is bullshit.
[SPEAKER_17]: I think the story is bullshit right there.
[SPEAKER_17]: I want to see DJ Lee too.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, you know, that would be cool and all, but they don't need to do that.
[SPEAKER_17]: There's very good players here locally that they could get.
[SPEAKER_17]: I mean, when I say locally, I mean California.
[SPEAKER_18]: They don't acknowledge any of those people.
[SPEAKER_18]: I mean, hello, look at DropTheBombSystemSMF.
[SPEAKER_18]: Six foot!
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh my god, not six feet!
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm talking about bringing in the players and stuff.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's what they did last year, D2.
[SPEAKER_17]: They had all US players.
[SPEAKER_17]: I know Mel was down there.
[SPEAKER_19]: It would make sense that they would use local players if they know that there's a local scene.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, anyway, let me finish and Loki can give the rest of his comments.
[SPEAKER_17]: One more exciting news about this is that they will have some songs that's only featured on the USA version of 2DX only.
[SPEAKER_17]: However, it may not satisfy some expert players.
[SPEAKER_17]: This is going to be the first release of 2DX in America.
[SPEAKER_17]: It may be aimed at beginner players so they can get into the game easily.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's possible that the new features included like the beginner mode in DDR USA, possibly similar to the drill mode that's featured in 2DX 5th, 6th homestyle version.
[SPEAKER_17]: This might be a good chance for people who live outside of California to try this game out.
[SPEAKER_17]: All right.
[SPEAKER_24]: Have at it, Loki.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm actually going to take those to a source and see if I can find any legitimacy, but I doubt that it is.
[SPEAKER_17]: We'll find out, but just take it with a grain of salt.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's a new story going around.
[SPEAKER_17]: We're going to report it.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_18]: The only...
[SPEAKER_18]: The only way this is going to work is if they actually do a good job on this and pick good music for this.
[SPEAKER_18]: However, looking at Konami of America's past track record, it's not looking good, folks.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's not looking good at all.
[SPEAKER_18]: I think they're going to take 2DX and go, you know what?
[SPEAKER_18]: I think these players haven't played the Japanese songs, so let's take a bunch of stuff from first style, and then we're going to take a shit on it, and then we're going to add some new songs too.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm going to disagree.
[SPEAKER_17]: Because if they don't try to do this, we're going to do it on a learning curve.
[SPEAKER_17]: We're going to start easy with DDR USA, and then we're going to go to Canomics, and then we're going to go to Max USA.
[SPEAKER_17]: Which Max USA, if that had been the first one, we would never have people bitching.
[SPEAKER_17]: People would have been happy with that, and you know what?
[SPEAKER_17]: People wouldn't bitch about how Konami messes it up.
[SPEAKER_17]: You know what, Konami?
[SPEAKER_17]: What you need to do, even though you want to milk the sales, if you want to keep the fans happy, put it all encompassing into one game.
[SPEAKER_17]: Something that the beginners can pick up.
[SPEAKER_17]: Have your beginner mode, but have those and others that will murder us too.
[SPEAKER_17]: The expert stuff and good songs.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, not just Light Seven.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm talking like the beginner one, two, where every song is one star.
[SPEAKER_17]: The Japanese ones have that.
[SPEAKER_17]: No one complains.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's pretty nice.
[SPEAKER_17]: It helps you learn how to play.
[SPEAKER_17]: Do that.
[SPEAKER_17]: Don't just, don't give us a game that's only the one, two, and three stars or people are going to bitch.
[SPEAKER_17]: That would be ugly.
[SPEAKER_24]: If you want to learn how to play, Light 7, leave it there.
[SPEAKER_24]: Keep your Light 7, keep your 7 key.
[SPEAKER_24]: That way you have room for people to get better.
[SPEAKER_18]: Let's just put it this way.
[SPEAKER_18]: You put Vincent DeMora's Eternity on there, I don't care what the fuck you do with it, you can put big gay-ass...
[SPEAKER_03]: Hello, this is DJ Spanky, saying everybody should play 2DX USA.
[SPEAKER_03]: I endorse this fully.
[SPEAKER_03]: It has such wonderful songs in it, like Justify My Love by Madonna.
[SPEAKER_24]: So Mr. Spanky, does the nice booming subwoofer make you feel special?
[SPEAKER_03]: This is what I would suggest you do when 2DX comes to the USA.
[SPEAKER_03]: Get your subwoofer and mount it really high so it comes up to the bar.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then when you play, straddle the subwoofer.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's much funner.
[SPEAKER_03]: It'll make your balls bounce.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay, that was a little too much information.
[SPEAKER_19]: And the room falls silent.
[SPEAKER_24]: I think that we should go to break while we tally the votes for Cage Match, which actually I've already done.
[SPEAKER_24]: But we'll go to break, we'll play a few songs, especially one by request, and then we'll announce the winner for the Cage Match, which I tabulated while Noah was looking.
[SPEAKER_24]: Anyway, yeah, here you go.
[SPEAKER_12]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_12]: If I can't get a D, round down to a D
Thanks for watching!
and
Thank you for watching!
Lyrics, Lyrics, Lyrics, Lyrics
[SPEAKER_30]: Hi, this is Mel B of RTF, and for an extra $1.99 a minute, my girlfriend Mel B can join us on all the fun together.
[SPEAKER_29]: But hey, if you're a broke ass like I am, why don't you come to one place that costs absolutely nothing to go to, and still the fun is just as great.
[SPEAKER_29]: It's Orange Lounge Radio, Sunday nights.
[SPEAKER_29]: Kick it with me, and you just might realize the best things in life are free.
[SPEAKER_24]: That's one of some of my regular guests.
[SPEAKER_17]: Miss Starmelby, who we saw yesterday at Derby Owner's Crack.
[SPEAKER_17]: That was a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_17]: He's good people.
[SPEAKER_24]: Well, anyway, we're going to go ahead and make the announcement then of... Oh, shit, I actually deleted all their songs.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'll have to find it again.
[SPEAKER_24]: Well, we're not even going to play it.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah, anyway, the winner is, by a pretty big vote, is the Zelda mix.
[SPEAKER_17]: Goodie, goodie.
[SPEAKER_17]: Not a damn person voted for Fable.
[SPEAKER_17]: You people made me cry.
[SPEAKER_24]: You people made me laugh.
[SPEAKER_10]: I laughed with Jamie.
[SPEAKER_17]: God, I thought my cackling was bad.
[SPEAKER_17]: I thought Ice Queen's cackling was bad.
[SPEAKER_17]: Jesus.
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright, so what we got to do now though, we're going to set up for a list list.
[SPEAKER_17]: We're going to do a list list tonight, right?
[SPEAKER_17]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_17]: And what is the list list topic?
[SPEAKER_24]: Tonight's list list topic is...
[SPEAKER_24]: What mocap game do we want to see?
[SPEAKER_17]: You've had mocap boxing, mocap golf, and now what should the next mocap game be?
[SPEAKER_17]: What would we want to see here in the studio?
[SPEAKER_17]: That's tonight's list list.
[SPEAKER_17]: So can we cue up a quick song to give us time to think?
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm going to do a few songs.
[SPEAKER_17]: Just do like, maybe like, we hate to play so many songs in a row, but we just need the time to think here.
[SPEAKER_17]: So we're going to do like maybe one or two quick songs, and then we'll be back.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, we're going to do just a couple quick songs.
[SPEAKER_18]: Play the Legend of Trance.
[SPEAKER_18]: You want to do Legend of Trance?
[SPEAKER_18]: I got an overwhelming response.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, so we're going to do Legend of Trance and we'll come back and do mocap.
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright, we're loading it up.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, so if you haven't downloaded it yet, the secret website so you can get to this is willddrforfood.net slash leechfromloki, and that's the secret page where you can download these songs.
[SPEAKER_18]: Well, the show never contained hot monkey sex, so now... Now it does.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_18]: So.
[SPEAKER_17]: Enjoy.
[SPEAKER_17]: So we're going to play Legend of Trance?
[SPEAKER_17]: Yes?
[SPEAKER_17]: If we can get it?
[SPEAKER_17]: Do-do-do-do-do!
[SPEAKER_17]: So, it's with an L. Unfortunately, not everybody in the studio is going to be able to help with listless tonight, but we'll let them break any ties we have, which we usually do to people who... What?
[SPEAKER_17]: It's not working.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_17]: What do you mean?
[SPEAKER_17]: We're having technical difficulties, so we're trying again.
[SPEAKER_17]: What do you mean it's not reading the CD?
[SPEAKER_17]: In the meantime... That's the CD.
[SPEAKER_17]: What else were we talking about during the break?
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_17]: We're looking for that.
[SPEAKER_17]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, yay, we got it.
[SPEAKER_17]: So we're going to play Legend of Trance and prepare our list list and we'll be right back.
[SPEAKER_17]: You are listening to Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, we are back and we're ready.
[SPEAKER_17]: We're going to do the list list.
[SPEAKER_17]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_17]: So, the way this list works, in case you're a new listener to the show, what we're going to do, we're all going to name our top three.
[SPEAKER_17]: We have six people in studio participating, the three hosts, Intern Zero, Puppy, and DarkTest Studio are all participating tonight.
[SPEAKER_17]: Top three mo-cap games.
[SPEAKER_24]: By the way, for the record, mo-cap stands for motion capture.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yes, very good.
[SPEAKER_17]: And you may have seen games like mo-cap, boxing, golf.
[SPEAKER_24]: And another one, Tsuguri, which is the sword game.
[SPEAKER_17]: Very good.
[SPEAKER_17]: Also, if you've never, if you've policed 9-1-1's kind of a mocap game, you can kind of count Parapara, whatever, you know, if you've never seen an actual mocap game, those are kind of rough estimates of what it is.
[SPEAKER_17]: It basically uses a sensor for your movement.
[SPEAKER_17]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_17]: So, and then once we all name our top three, then we're going to do the elimination round, which is always fun.
[SPEAKER_17]: Each of us gets to take one off the list of somebody else's picks, or your own, if you so choose.
[SPEAKER_17]: I just kind of verped a little.
[SPEAKER_17]: That was good.
[SPEAKER_17]: And then the chat room has the ultimate vote.
[SPEAKER_17]: They're going to vote on their top three.
[SPEAKER_17]: And Ice Queen and DDRholic, they're not doing lists, but they'll help us break ties.
[SPEAKER_17]: And Bombay's in the back there too, but he's digging through things.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, you look like you were hunched over looking at something.
[SPEAKER_17]: Are you going to hurl?
[SPEAKER_17]: Do you need a barf bag?
[SPEAKER_17]: Are you okay?
[SPEAKER_17]: Do you need a donkey bag?
[SPEAKER_17]: All right, here we go.
[SPEAKER_24]: My first choice for a mocap game is mocap horse racing.
[SPEAKER_17]: MoCap Horse Racing, yay!
[SPEAKER_24]: Where you're suspended on a giant saddle and have to spank.
[SPEAKER_17]: I almost had one like that on my list.
[SPEAKER_24]: Almost like that horse humping game that Namco put out, but not.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, Final Furlong?
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_17]: That would be fun.
[SPEAKER_17]: MoCap Horse Racing.
[SPEAKER_17]: Would it be complete with initial delight cards?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, cool.
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_17]: Who's next?
[SPEAKER_14]: Next...
[SPEAKER_18]: Um, my first choice is mocap drug dealing.
[SPEAKER_18]: Mocap drug dealing, how would that work?
[SPEAKER_17]: Is that like Police 911 in reverse?
[SPEAKER_21]: Pretty much.
[SPEAKER_21]: Like, you have a certain time period to get your product out on the street as much as possible.
[SPEAKER_21]: What exactly is being mocapped?
[SPEAKER_21]: You run from cops.
[SPEAKER_21]: You actually gotta hand it to people and stuff.
[SPEAKER_17]: Are you on a treadmill when you do the running part?
[SPEAKER_17]: How fast can you whip out a ten?
[SPEAKER_17]: How fast can you take the money and do the drop and run?
[SPEAKER_17]: Catch the dime bags.
[SPEAKER_18]: Well, I'm just gonna kind of expand on one of them that I had.
[SPEAKER_18]: I originally had put down mo-cap dancing, but instead I'm gonna put down mo-cap
[SPEAKER_18]: Rayvar.
[SPEAKER_18]: No, that's just Parapara, I thought.
[SPEAKER_18]: No, see, Parapara is more organized.
[SPEAKER_18]: MoCap Rayvar is more of like, you're kind of just, yeah, more flailing involved.
[SPEAKER_18]: You got special bonus rounds where you get to massage people on E. Yeah, like the first thing, right, when you put in your money, it drops out an E pill.
[SPEAKER_18]: You have to take it and wait five minutes.
[SPEAKER_18]: Exactly.
He'll have little glow sticks on strings.
[SPEAKER_17]: He'll have little glow sticks on strings.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's beautiful.
[SPEAKER_17]: All right.
[SPEAKER_17]: I think the lights flicker, too.
[SPEAKER_17]: MoCap Rayvar.
[SPEAKER_17]: Moving on to Dark Tetsuya.
[SPEAKER_17]: MoCap Murder Simulator.
[SPEAKER_17]: MoCap Murder.
[SPEAKER_17]: So would it just be just like stabbing people or shooting them?
[SPEAKER_17]: I guess, yeah.
[SPEAKER_17]: What kind of people would you be murdering?
[SPEAKER_13]: Terrorists.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, terrorists.
[SPEAKER_13]: What an American answer.
[SPEAKER_14]: Go down.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_14]: Puppy.
[SPEAKER_19]: Mocap binge drinking.
[SPEAKER_17]: Mocap?
[SPEAKER_17]: That's kind of like last night.
[SPEAKER_17]: Mocap binge drinking.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't think anyone was binging.
[SPEAKER_17]: That was great, yeah.
[SPEAKER_17]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, mocap binge.
[SPEAKER_17]: How would that work?
[SPEAKER_17]: Would you have to, like, would it have, like, a floating keg?
[SPEAKER_19]: You'd probably have to, like, run... Okay, kind of along those same lines.
[SPEAKER_17]: My number three choice, I said, is mocap Girls Gone Wild.
[SPEAKER_17]: or what it does is it motion caps the girls lifting their shirts and showing their hooters to the mocap.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, I can see it now.
[SPEAKER_21]: A bunch of little 8-year-old kids lighting up around this machine and seeing this chick just lifting up her shirt.
[SPEAKER_17]: And mocap girls gone wild would have internet ranking, of course.
[SPEAKER_17]: Co-sponsored by AreYouHotOrNot.com
[SPEAKER_17]: Seriously, they've got a site.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's called RateMyBoobs.com.
[SPEAKER_17]: And of course, if Girls Gone Wild does well, we get the sequel, Guys Gone Crazy.
[SPEAKER_19]: You have to have, you have to have, the versions would have to be like the Snoop Dogg, the doggy style one, and then the door room fantasies.
[SPEAKER_19]: No, we want penis.
[SPEAKER_24]: I want to see the cock.
[SPEAKER_17]: Whip it out.
[SPEAKER_17]: How fast can you whip it out?
[SPEAKER_24]: I want initial pee.
[SPEAKER_17]: What's the chatroom say about all this crap?
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_24]: I haven't been paying attention.
[SPEAKER_24]: Fucking pump it up.
[SPEAKER_24]: No mocap, Mardi Gras.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, um, so now We just, we are just now checking the chatroom by the way, so we didn't steal any answers, so So now for a, I say we go to mine Alright, your number two My number two, MoCap Kama Sutra MoCap Kama Sutra, oh Once again, eight year old children What would be the last level of MoCap Kama Sutra?
[SPEAKER_24]: One where you have to, you know, dislocate your hip and your shoulders to get into the position And then hop around like a drunk monkey
[SPEAKER_21]: As I said before, eight-year-old children.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's just problems right now.
[SPEAKER_18]: Next one, I changed.
[SPEAKER_18]: It'll be MoCap DC Sniper.
[SPEAKER_17]: MoCap DC Sniper.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, that's bad.
[SPEAKER_17]: How is this... No, see this whole thing, though?
[SPEAKER_24]: This has, like... No, you'd have, like, the From the Trunk level.
[SPEAKER_24]: And then you'd have, like, the building level, and you'd have to, like, run up the stairs to get the building.
[SPEAKER_17]: Bombay was in the back.
[SPEAKER_17]: He was saying, for those that didn't hear it, the downtown bike puncher mocap game.
[SPEAKER_17]: Because, I don't know if you guys have heard, but here in Sacramento we have this guy who's famous for riding around on a bike in the middle of the night and punching women in the face.
[SPEAKER_17]: Which sounds funny, but it's a horrible crime, I mean, but... Just, it's weird.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's the only way you can describe it.
[SPEAKER_17]: What kind of guy just goes around and punches people in the... Anyway...
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't think it's a guy, I think I'm doing it.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_21]: You know, like, DC Sniper, you would, like, actually have to get in different positions, like the prone position and hiding in bushes and stuff.
[SPEAKER_21]: And then you'd have to, like, trek your way across the country to try to get away.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, so, moving on, Loki.
[SPEAKER_18]: Alright, I've been changing mine, like, as I'm thinking here, sitting here.
[SPEAKER_18]: I was gonna stop with, uh, mocap surgery, but no.
[SPEAKER_18]: We're not doing mocap surgery.
[SPEAKER_18]: Um...
[SPEAKER_18]: Instead, it's going to be mo-cap vandalism.
[SPEAKER_18]: I mean, this could include, like, freaking mailbox baseball, you know, classic, spray painting.
[SPEAKER_18]: Dude!
[SPEAKER_18]: Wait.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay, we're going to limit it now.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's going to be mo-cap graffiti.
[SPEAKER_18]: Mo-cap graffiti.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, like you've got to, like, you know, tag shit.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's got skill and, you know, it's cool.
[SPEAKER_17]: Wonderful.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: Wait, Joe's next.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think, for this one, I'm pretty sure that Kat and I, Joe, would probably in it.
[SPEAKER_13]: MoCap line dancing.
[SPEAKER_17]: MoCap line dancing.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh my lord, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wanna do the electric slide!
[SPEAKER_17]: That would be beautiful.
[SPEAKER_17]: Complete with a ten gallon hat.
[SPEAKER_17]: And boots!
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_17]: Recycle your para para boots with your line dancing.
[SPEAKER_17]: My number two, mocap donkey punch.
[SPEAKER_17]: Um, what exactly would you be doing in that game?
[SPEAKER_17]: Anita, could you explain this?
[SPEAKER_17]: How does the donkey punch work?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, how come you think I know so much about it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because you brought it up last night.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, everybody knows what donkey punching is.
[SPEAKER_17]: No, we don't.
[SPEAKER_17]: Could you please explain it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, if you are doing a person in the...
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, yes, let Loki do it.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay, freakin' donkey punching is when you're, like, taking a chick from behind, and then you just, you take your fist and you smack it in the back of her head.
[SPEAKER_02]: As hard as you can.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that she clenches?
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_22]: So you're fucking somebody else, and then you start slapping him in the back of the head.
[SPEAKER_02]: It can also be applied to men.
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_17]: Right.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_17]: MoCap Donkey Punch, great.
[SPEAKER_24]: My number two... Um, we have a comment, yay, more about Loki's sex life.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_17]: Uh, my number two is, uh, MoCap Snow Art, where, uh, it records your movements of, like, like stage one is writing your name in the snow.
[SPEAKER_17]: and then like, you know, mocap, you know, like just peeing things in the snow.
[SPEAKER_17]: Be beautiful.
[SPEAKER_17]: Only guys can play that.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, you know like Mario Party 4?
[SPEAKER_24]: The game for every woman who wishes she had a penis.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, now you can.
[SPEAKER_17]: Now you can.
[SPEAKER_17]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_17]: I know women that do the same damn thing.
[SPEAKER_17]: They pee in the snow.
[SPEAKER_17]: They kind of run.
[SPEAKER_17]: They write their name by writing.
[SPEAKER_24]: I've heard stories.
[SPEAKER_24]: They write their name really big by running.
[SPEAKER_24]: For the people who are not here watching, Rob just turned purple.
[SPEAKER_24]: My turn.
[SPEAKER_24]: And actually, mine is not a funny one.
[SPEAKER_24]: Mine is actually a legitimate thing that I wish that they would make.
[SPEAKER_17]: We can't have that.
[SPEAKER_24]: Mocaptron.
[SPEAKER_24]: By the way, Tron 2.0 needs to hurry up and come out.
[SPEAKER_17]: Mocap Zanadu We were back?
[SPEAKER_17]: Hello I hope they got the Mocap Did they get Mocap Tron?
[SPEAKER_17]: I hope so We'll see Alright, keep going
[SPEAKER_21]: Um, one I got is for the most worthless sport in the world, and it would be mocap curling.
[SPEAKER_21]: So I just see someone, like, shuffling a disc, and then you have, you can have, like, a friend play.
[SPEAKER_21]: You're both running in front with these little brooms, trying to scrape out imaginary ice.
[SPEAKER_18]: Mocap curling.
[SPEAKER_18]: Greatest Olympic sport ever.
[SPEAKER_18]: Because you can, like, thank the Canadians for the greatest sport in history.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_18]: Imagine it now.
[SPEAKER_18]: The game about the thing that most people despise.
[SPEAKER_18]: The worst form of life on the face of the earth.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_18]: MoCap Panamime.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh, that's great.
[SPEAKER_17]: MoCap Mime.
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_17]: If you kicked a mime in the nuts, would you scream?
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright, DarkTetsuya says for his number one.
[SPEAKER_13]: Three words.
[SPEAKER_13]: MoCap Mud Wrestling.
[SPEAKER_17]: MoCap Mud Wrestling.
[SPEAKER_17]: Beautiful.
[SPEAKER_13]: Wonder where that came from.
[SPEAKER_17]: Would the sequel be MoCap Cream Corn Wrestling?
[SPEAKER_19]: KY Wrestling.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh!
[SPEAKER_19]: No, there's a scene for that in that movie Old School.
[SPEAKER_19]: Anyway... It's...
[SPEAKER_19]: I realized that my number one choice sucks.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm trying to think of a new one, so Rob can go ahead of me.
[SPEAKER_19]: Number one sucks?
[SPEAKER_19]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, just read it anyway.
[SPEAKER_19]: No.
[SPEAKER_17]: But curling's legitimate!
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_17]: You want to give us some help?
[SPEAKER_17]: Maybe read some things from the chatroom that the chatroom has suggested?
[SPEAKER_19]: Shades?
[SPEAKER_24]: Two words.
[SPEAKER_24]: Mocap shades.
[SPEAKER_24]: And now I shall put on my shades MoCap Rob's voice MoCap Volleyball MoCap Shell Military in Nigeria What?
[SPEAKER_24]: MoCap Quidditch, yes!
[SPEAKER_19]: MoCap Quidditch Well, there already is There was that motion sensing Tekken 3 thing before Um, no Yeah Keep going MoCap Friday the 13th
[SPEAKER_10]: MoCap, HotMonkeySex MoCap, Christian Fiction MoCap, Hitler Oh god Mike, take this one I have it for MoCap Finish You can't really motion capture that How about that one?
[SPEAKER_19]: I want mocap shopping.
[SPEAKER_19]: You know what, actually, I'll go with that one that Loki recommends here.
[SPEAKER_19]: Mocap pole dancing.
[SPEAKER_17]: Mocap pole dancing.
[SPEAKER_17]: Beautiful.
[SPEAKER_17]: Be your own.
[SPEAKER_17]: Be the strip.
[SPEAKER_17]: I like that mocap shopping, though.
[SPEAKER_17]: That could be, like, they could have snow art on one side and shopping on the other.
[SPEAKER_17]: Something for the guys and the girls.
[SPEAKER_17]: Mocap supermarket sweep.
[SPEAKER_10]: You want to change your answer?
[SPEAKER_10]: I want to change my answer.
[SPEAKER_17]: Puppy Changes from Pole Dancing to Supermarket Sweep.
[SPEAKER_17]: That show is cool beyond belief.
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright, my number one answer, and I can't believe this hasn't already been named, but I think it's the obvious.
[SPEAKER_17]: MoCap Spanking.
[SPEAKER_19]: I thought there was that one game where you actually had to slap... You actually shove your finger up your ass.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, not your ass, but the guy's ass.
[SPEAKER_17]: Whatever, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_17]: I say, well, you know what?
[SPEAKER_17]: It isn't a mo-cap game, and they need mo-cap spanking.
[SPEAKER_24]: I think we should start voting shit off the list.
[SPEAKER_17]: Do you want to read what we have so far?
[SPEAKER_24]: So far we have MoCap Horse Racing, MoCap Drug Dealing, MoCap Brave R, spelled R4V4R, MoCap Murder, MoCap Binge Drinking, MoCap Girls Gone Wild, MoCap Kama Sutra, MoCap DC Sniper, MoCap Graffiti, MoCap Line Dancing, MoCap Donkey Punch, MoCap Snow Art, MoCap Tron, MoCap Curling, MoCap Mime, MoCap Mud Wrestling, MoCap Supermarket Suite, and MoCap Spanking.
[SPEAKER_24]: I take out
[SPEAKER_17]: I would have to take off the, um...
[SPEAKER_18]: MoCap Mud Wrestling, because how could you really motion capture that, though?
[SPEAKER_18]: Unless there's two players, you know?
[SPEAKER_17]: Ice Queen's offering to demonstrate.
[SPEAKER_13]: I have had a cry.
[SPEAKER_13]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_17]: All right, Dark Tetsuya.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, no, I'm sorry, Loki's next.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm sorry, Loki.
[SPEAKER_17]: Whatever, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_17]: Dark Tetsuya's going instead.
[SPEAKER_17]: Binge drinking.
[SPEAKER_17]: MoCap binge, I agree.
[SPEAKER_17]: I was going to take that off.
[SPEAKER_17]: Just because you can't really get liquor from the machine, so it kind of sucks.
[SPEAKER_19]: We should have done mocap praying.
[SPEAKER_19]: Mocap for God.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh well.
[SPEAKER_19]: No, it's actually going to be... We're taking off... Drug dealing, because...
[SPEAKER_18]: It's... It's just like... It's... No, it's... It's kinda... You need something simpler than that.
[SPEAKER_18]: Like, mocap, uh... Yeah, or something.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_14]: Puppy.
[SPEAKER_19]: Mocap.
[SPEAKER_19]: Uh... Uh... What?
[SPEAKER_19]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm trying to decide here.
[SPEAKER_19]: Uh... You gonna fucking cap somebody?
[SPEAKER_19]: Bust a cap in your ass!
[SPEAKER_19]: We're almost done, don't worry.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_19]: I will get rid of mocap mine, because it'd be all black and white.
[SPEAKER_19]: And it'd suck.
[SPEAKER_17]: Aw, alright.
[SPEAKER_17]: It should've been mocap charades.
[SPEAKER_17]: This is hard, because I like all of these.
[SPEAKER_17]: Um... I'm gonna have to take off with a little bit of... I have to take off mocap line dancing.
[SPEAKER_17]: Aw.
[SPEAKER_17]: Just because that's kind of what Parapara is.
[SPEAKER_17]: Parapara is kind of line dancing, so they already have it, as far as I can see.
[SPEAKER_17]: Otherwise, they're... Anyway, they're...
[SPEAKER_17]: We're having a little bit of dead air right now.
[SPEAKER_17]: So what are we going to do?
[SPEAKER_17]: Are we going to read the list?
[SPEAKER_24]: We'll read the list.
[SPEAKER_24]: The first one is MoCap Horse Racing, MoCap Ravar, MoCap Murder, Girls Gone Wild, Kama Sutra, DC Sniper, Graffiti, Snow Art, Tron, Curling, Supermarket Sweep, and Spanking.
[SPEAKER_03]: and Spanking.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ooh, Spanking.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, sorry.
[SPEAKER_18]: Nobody else took it off.
[SPEAKER_18]: MoCap UPS delivery driver.
[SPEAKER_18]: Just like frickin' Ace Ventura, the opening scene there.
[SPEAKER_18]: Sounds a little broken.
[SPEAKER_17]: You know what else?
[SPEAKER_17]: It's just, you know MoCap UPS driver, you just walk up to the door and then like hot women jump on you and try to fuck you.
[SPEAKER_17]: Because like everybody, like a bunch of women I know get really horny over the UPS driver for whatever reason.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the fact that he comes and he goes.
[SPEAKER_02]: He comes to the place, he brings a package, and he leaves.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what it is.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's the track.
[SPEAKER_13]: People love the track.
[SPEAKER_24]: Anyway, we're accepting your votes right now.
[SPEAKER_24]: We're going to go to break while you send in your votes.
[SPEAKER_24]: And we'll have a response when we come back.
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay.
and many more.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes you do, yes you do, you do my faction
[SPEAKER_10]: I said, try me, take a chance on my passion We'll be together all the time I said, try me, take a chance on emotions From now and ever, into my heart I said, try me, take a chance on my passion We'll be together till the morning light Don't stand so, don't stand so, don't stand so close to me
Don't you know, don't you know, I've been waiting for you Don't you know, baby, you just showed up right on time Can't you see, can't you see, I've been waiting for you Can't you see, baby, you just showed up right on time Don't you know, don't you know, I've been waiting for you Don't you know, baby, you just showed up right on time
[SPEAKER_24]: Listen to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_28]: Because Bongo demands it.
[SPEAKER_24]: We're back.
[SPEAKER_24]: And we have a winner.
[SPEAKER_24]: A few of them.
[SPEAKER_24]: Number three for Best MoCap Game is MoCap Snow Art.
[SPEAKER_24]: Hooray for P. Number two winner is MoCap Rayvar.
Whee!
[SPEAKER_24]: And the number one is MoCap Kama Sutra.
[SPEAKER_24]: Because, dammit, we like the nookie.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright, another fabulous list list comes to a close.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_17]: What happened?
[SPEAKER_24]: I meant to save it and I closed it.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh well.
[SPEAKER_17]: Life goes on.
[SPEAKER_24]: Somebody in the chat room posted on Yusuf Osaka Forest.
[SPEAKER_24]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_24]: The end.
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_17]: So, now we're going to do, we're going to Ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_17]: We're going to close out this with a couple quick questions for Ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah, let's do Ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, so.
[SPEAKER_17]: We've got ten minutes.
[SPEAKER_17]: Send your question over PM.
[SPEAKER_17]: Send your question over private message to DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_17]: Remember, we have a ton of guests in studio tonight.
[SPEAKER_24]: By the way, by the way, bad grammar.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's not should of, it's should have.
[SPEAKER_24]: And you're guilty of that, too.
[SPEAKER_16]: So what?
[SPEAKER_24]: You still knew what I was saying.
[SPEAKER_24]: I went off on that on one of my fuckies of the week.
[SPEAKER_24]: Well, let's see if we have our first question.
[SPEAKER_17]: Here's a big ball of Kleenex just for you, dear.
[SPEAKER_24]: First question comes from ManekiNekoJass.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, yay!
[SPEAKER_24]: Are you gay?
[SPEAKER_24]: If you scream, you call, you gay.
[SPEAKER_17]: So wait, are we going to go around and find out who's gay?
[SPEAKER_17]: Is he directing that one person?
[SPEAKER_24]: This is a Margaret Cho quote.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, it's just a Margaret Cho quote?
[SPEAKER_17]: Are you gay?
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, well then, if it's not a real question, forget it.
[SPEAKER_24]: I have a response to that.
[SPEAKER_24]: I actually have a response to that.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, wait, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_17]: Mommy think everybody little bit gay.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm a lesbian trapped in a man's body.
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't know, I like boobs sometimes.
[SPEAKER_24]: I like boobs sometimes.
[SPEAKER_18]: How many times have we heard that one before?
[SPEAKER_17]: Were you going to play a response to that?
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, I am.
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright, then let's hear it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I inherited my father's eyes and my mother's...
[SPEAKER_02]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'll eat pussy.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just not my first choice.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'll eat pussy if they run out of what I really want.
[SPEAKER_17]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_17]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_24]: Next question comes from JB.
[SPEAKER_24]: When will my SciFam CD get here?
[SPEAKER_17]: It will get here on next Thursday.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, let's see if Rob's right.
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay, our next one comes from Japan Man.
[SPEAKER_24]: Anyone looking for a good time?
[SPEAKER_17]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_24]: Not from you.
[SPEAKER_24]: That's why we're here.
[SPEAKER_17]: Do you have a phone number we can call?
[SPEAKER_24]: Hey, baby.
[SPEAKER_17]: By the way, just between you and me, that's what I'm aiming for for Season 3, is the debut of the phones.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_17]: When Loki and I move, because then we'll be able to dedicate a home line, because, you know, who cares if Orange Lounge people are calling during the middle of the day?
[SPEAKER_24]: The next question comes from 23rd Magnus, actually for DarkTessia.
[SPEAKER_24]: I never asked you, if you had to collide Japanese girls in a bucket of chocolate, what would you do?
[SPEAKER_13]: Our next question comes from Chubbs.
[SPEAKER_13]: Will you be hosting Orange Dome's radio during March Madness and can I be a guest?
[SPEAKER_17]: Yes and yes.
[SPEAKER_24]: When's your next drunk show?
[SPEAKER_24]: When we have a three-day weekend.
[SPEAKER_17]: Probably the Saturday night.
[SPEAKER_24]: I got it.
[SPEAKER_24]: Sunday night after March Madness.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, that's right, because you and me have Monday off.
[SPEAKER_17]: We should do a fuck-up drunk.
[SPEAKER_17]: You and me.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, the thing is, okay, this is the interesting thing.
[SPEAKER_17]: In two weeks, Orange Lounge will be preempted by the live running.
[SPEAKER_17]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_17]: If you want to get in on this, listen to our live tournament coverage.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's going to go all day long, and it's just for you guys who are far away, because we figure most people from California are going to be here at the tournament.
[SPEAKER_17]: You'll get to hear everybody.
[SPEAKER_24]: And our next drunk show is probably going to be right after that, because we're going to be like, fuck this, and get drunk.
[SPEAKER_17]: We will probably do a live fuck-off show immediately following the March Madness coverage.
[SPEAKER_24]: Well, our next question comes from SkylineDC505.
[SPEAKER_24]: It says, will I pass my drive test this Thursday?
[SPEAKER_17]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_17]: You will pass it with an 80 like I did.
[SPEAKER_24]: AOSFE, what type of questions can I ask people to make them think I'm interested?
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm sorry, what was it?
[SPEAKER_24]: What type of questions can I ask people to make them think I'm interested?
[SPEAKER_24]: What color panties are you wearing?
[SPEAKER_17]: I like peanut butter, what the fuck?
[SPEAKER_17]: There you go, that's a great question.
[SPEAKER_17]: More than Jake.
[SPEAKER_17]: I like peanut butter, do you want to fuck?
[SPEAKER_24]: More than Jake asks, why won't anybody pick up the phone?
[SPEAKER_24]: Because we're not there.
[SPEAKER_17]: Send an email.
[SPEAKER_17]: Welcome to the new millennium.
[SPEAKER_17]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_24]: 23rd Magus.
[SPEAKER_24]: Have any of you actually called 867-5309?
[SPEAKER_24]: No, I never have.
[SPEAKER_17]: Everybody in their lives.
[SPEAKER_17]: But I have called.
[SPEAKER_17]: Hey, for those of you local in Sacramento in the 916 area code, I have called 332-2222.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's all I'm going to say.
[SPEAKER_18]: Well, I'll have you know that actually because of that song right there, that's why in every single movie all the phone numbers are 555.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_18]: Because 555, no one can have a number with that on it because those are dedicated straight for like the movies and stuff because people like that call that number and then some guy just got, I mean, totally pissed off at that, you know?
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, I mean, really, don't you guys watch Pop-Up Video?
[SPEAKER_21]: They said it like 80 times now.
[SPEAKER_17]: Actually, I believe if any of you saw the movie Punch Drunk Love, there's a scene where Adam Sandler's calling a porn sex line or something and they use a real number.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, what they did is that Hollywood bought that 800 number and then put an advertisement for the movie on it.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_24]: Um, JBS, can I talk on the air during March Madness?
[SPEAKER_24]: I will hypnotize you all with sci-fi and talk mohahaha.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yes, any- Okay, this is the interesting thing.
[SPEAKER_17]: If March Madness gets set up like we hope it does, we're not gonna be, like, tucked away in the corner, like, way in the back where you won't be able to see us.
[SPEAKER_17]: We are hoping that we're going to have, if the tourney is outdoors, like we're thinking it's going to be, provided it's not raining, we're hoping that the gazebo is going to be Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_17]: And if any of you have been to Scandia and see the gazebo out back, it's huge.
[SPEAKER_17]: You won't miss us.
[SPEAKER_17]: So come on by.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's going to be open door all day.
[SPEAKER_17]: So nobody else needs to ask that.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yes, you can be on the show.
[SPEAKER_17]: Just come on by and say hi.
[SPEAKER_24]: Will you guys be here in the summer for CBN too?
[SPEAKER_24]: So can I be a guest that's from Rice?
[SPEAKER_17]: Uh, give me some dates, as long as it's, I can afford it, I don't see why not, yeah, I've, I've not heard anything about CBM2.
[SPEAKER_19]: Cause there, we already know there's gonna be B3, uh, May 17th and 18th, and definitely gonna be there, so, you should be there too!
[SPEAKER_17]: May is a little before summer though.
[SPEAKER_17]: I imagine CyberBeat, they wouldn't want to do that more than twice a year, if even that.
[SPEAKER_17]: So I would think that January, probably July would be the earliest they'd want to do that.
[SPEAKER_17]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_17]: Give us dates, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_24]: And another one from Jas, what are each of our favorite extreme songs first?
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't really play extreme that much, because I would normally name anything that Tack does.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm actually going to go with Guacamole Del Taco.
[SPEAKER_18]: Contrary to what a lot of people see me play, I actually seem to like B-11 a lot more than I put on.
[SPEAKER_18]: I always play A on doubles only because the steps are fun.
[SPEAKER_18]: And people like watching you run around the pad really fast.
[SPEAKER_18]: They're like, ooh, arrows going up the screen.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, so.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay, so who wants to make a comment?
[SPEAKER_18]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_18]: I will.
[SPEAKER_13]: V, definitely.
[SPEAKER_13]: V or Butterfly.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hey, that's on Extreme.
[SPEAKER_13]: Right on.
[SPEAKER_20]: Le Copa De La Vida.
[SPEAKER_20]: Amen.
[SPEAKER_33]: Okay, don't laugh.
[SPEAKER_33]: All right.
[SPEAKER_33]: Jeanne, Jeanne, Doubles Heavy.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it's cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's fly.
[SPEAKER_19]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm stuck between Mobile Logan, Golden Decouple.
[SPEAKER_19]: Ice Queen?
[SPEAKER_19]: Favorite extreme song?
[SPEAKER_22]: Rhythm of Police on Devil's Heavy.
[SPEAKER_17]: You big stud.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm going to call me fag, but I do, I do, I do.
[SPEAKER_17]: I love that song.
[SPEAKER_24]: Fag.
[SPEAKER_24]: He said so.
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay, and Rob, can he sit at your house with your mic?
[SPEAKER_17]: I think so, yeah.
[SPEAKER_17]: I still haven't run that by Brian for sure, but I have told him there is a tournament and people will probably be here.
[SPEAKER_17]: I just, yeah, I'm pretty sure.
[SPEAKER_17]: Let's just say yes.
[SPEAKER_17]: If there's a change to that, I'll let you know.
[SPEAKER_17]: He's pretty cool with stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_24]: JB wants to know if I can legally become his cousin.
[SPEAKER_24]: We could try.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm adopting you anyway, so... Interesting.
[SPEAKER_17]: How would that work?
[SPEAKER_24]: Your aunt would have to adopt me.
[SPEAKER_17]: What about, could your aunt adopt him?
[SPEAKER_17]: Do you have an aunt?
[SPEAKER_17]: I have a bunch of aunts, but... You don't want them to adopt JB?
[SPEAKER_24]: You'd rather be adopted by JB's... I'm scared of my family, so...
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, so you'll try.
[SPEAKER_17]: Maybe you can go on the people's court and make that happen.
[SPEAKER_24]: Let's go on people's court and have them legally make us cousins.
[SPEAKER_17]: This is the plaintiff.
[SPEAKER_24]: And then, can I kill ATT, Comcast?
[SPEAKER_24]: Well, ATT can go, but Comcast is actually doing good service for me.
[SPEAKER_24]: You can come over here and use my cable.
[SPEAKER_24]: Can I put a big sign on the gazebo that says Orange Lounge Temple of Butt?
[SPEAKER_24]: No.
[SPEAKER_17]: No, because it's Scandia Family Fun Center.
[SPEAKER_24]: If we shake hands at March Madness, does that make one of us outface?
[SPEAKER_24]: And that's the DT.
[SPEAKER_24]: Um, no.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, sure.
[SPEAKER_24]: Ask us more questions.
[SPEAKER_24]: We have one more minute.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wasting time, wasting time, wasting time.
[SPEAKER_16]: Does anybody in the room have a question for anyone else that they want to ask live on air?
[SPEAKER_24]: I didn't mean to say that, but yeah, I was answering a question.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah, that's why I said the evil.
[SPEAKER_24]: Hey, we have a question from Japan Man.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_24]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_24]: That's what it says, hey.
[SPEAKER_17]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_24]: Yo.
[SPEAKER_24]: More than Jake, how many questions can you ask in a minute?
[SPEAKER_17]: Start asking, let's see.
[SPEAKER_17]: At least 60.
[SPEAKER_17]: Why?
[SPEAKER_24]: Why?
[SPEAKER_03]: Why?
Why?
[SPEAKER_24]: Why?
[SPEAKER_24]: Does 1, 2, 3, 4, Max 300's owner suck?
[SPEAKER_14]: Really?
[SPEAKER_14]: Bad.
[SPEAKER_14]: Awful.
[SPEAKER_14]: Piece of shit.
[SPEAKER_24]: It was created in the temple of butt.
[SPEAKER_14]: Worse than T-word.
[SPEAKER_24]: Hi, guys!
[SPEAKER_24]: Hi!
[SPEAKER_24]: And JB, what's your favorite SyFam song?
[SPEAKER_24]: That track 16 one.
[SPEAKER_17]: Ah, You Leave Me Alone.
[SPEAKER_24]: The Jennifer song, it's too late to say goodbye or something.
[SPEAKER_17]: You Leave Me Alone, Venus.
[SPEAKER_17]: Easy.
[SPEAKER_17]: Anybody else want to say favorite SyFam song?
[SPEAKER_13]: Rob, you should probably know this one.
[SPEAKER_13]: Love the Angel.
[SPEAKER_09]: Boom, boom, boom.
[SPEAKER_18]: That Irresistible Man or whatever, that one that's on the Darkstream.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm actually going to play the one that I really like after the credits, so stay tuned for a bit.
[SPEAKER_24]: Um, you know what, that does it.
[SPEAKER_16]: Let's get into the last question, we'll cut it off.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, if it's Jennifer Rice and Scythe, then never mind.
[SPEAKER_24]: Then I don't know, Irresistible Monk.
[SPEAKER_24]: Are you in joy?
[SPEAKER_24]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_24]: Are we in joy?
Yes!
[SPEAKER_16]: Final thoughts, time.
[SPEAKER_24]: Um, final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm still going to play that song anyway.
[SPEAKER_21]: Um, don't fall down and hurt yourself.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't have any.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm sorry, I don't have any.
[SPEAKER_13]: How about you?
[SPEAKER_13]: I have to go home and work on my website and my anime ezine that I have to do for my work.
[SPEAKER_19]: Full of peanut butter cups are harder to throw than just wrappers.
[SPEAKER_20]: I have to go to work tomorrow and I really don't want to.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know nothing.
[SPEAKER_22]: If you ever go to Chico, beware the sheep, they're all sluts.
[SPEAKER_17]: Will someone fuck me if I just lie there?
[SPEAKER_24]: No comment.
[SPEAKER_22]: Do you really want somebody to answer that, Rob?
[SPEAKER_22]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_24]: And on that note, bye everybody!
[SPEAKER_24]: Bye guys!
[SPEAKER_25]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_25]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_25]: Orange Lounge Radio is hosted by DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_25]: If you'd like to leave us a comment, send us an email at orangeloungeradio at yahoo.com And now, here's your fortune cookie message of the day.
[SPEAKER_28]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_28]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_25]: Thank you very much for listening, and we'll see you next week.