[SPEAKER_07]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and released to our podcast stream twice weekly To listen to the first half of this episode visit www.orangeloungeradio.com for links to websites with listings of past episodes Now the conclusion of this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_09]: And welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio, live on this Sunday evening, July the 1st of 2007.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you haven't heard Part A of our program yet, go back to wherever you got this episode, whether it be iTunes or Dig or wherever you got this, and look for Part A, because Orange Lounge Radio tapes in two parts every week.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's the little announce in the beginning of the show told you.
[SPEAKER_09]: So why am I repeating myself?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: So let's get back to the gaming news.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's an interesting little blog post I've seen pop up on Engadget showing someone that's modded a Wii Remote with a Zapper Gun from the Nintendo Entertainment System.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now what they've done with this, and you might be wondering why the hell would they do this, is they've actually kind of repositioned the IR sensor that's in the front of the Wii Remote to the front of the Zapper Gun.
[SPEAKER_08]: And of course the trigger on the Zapper Gun is now the B button for the Wii Remote.
[SPEAKER_08]: Duck Hunt on Virtual Console already?
[SPEAKER_09]: So we can really get some use out of this.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think Dokkan's going to be a little harder because a lot of those gun games now, it's not going to be a straight port over.
[SPEAKER_08]: They've got to rebuild the whole thing for the Wii Remote.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, I guess that's kind of true, huh?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, can't, I mean, because basically these games run off of emulators anyway, so can't the Wii Remote kind of emulate a light gun in the same way that some Nintendo emulators let you use your mouse?
[SPEAKER_08]: I suppose, but, you know, obviously the people that make the emulators aren't exactly the people that work for Nintendo either.
[SPEAKER_09]: I would like me some Battle Clash.
[SPEAKER_08]: and some SuperScope 6 stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: The Doctor in chat says, I want some awesome 3D duck hunt.
[SPEAKER_09]: That could be kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: Shadow Charlie says, but isn't there supposed to be a Zapper adapter coming soon?
[SPEAKER_08]: There is something that's officially going to come out at some point pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would imagine that, you know, because they were showing stuff at E3 last year that looked like a shotgun kind of attachment.
[SPEAKER_08]: Obviously, that was, you know, more of a prototype.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, we might see something in E3.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_08]: That's when they drop bombs like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, this is going to be coming out soon.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_08]: Just like Castlevania.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: But certainly this is like a really high, you know, very highly anticipated A-list title, so to speak.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: So that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: But not the first time that Konami has gone to the Internet to find musicians.
[SPEAKER_09]: Of course, if you follow the DDR series, the Ultramix and Universe series have previously had a competition to put indie artists in the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Other thing that people might be looking for, I mean, granted the classic controller is pretty good for fighting games, but, you know, when you're looking for something just a little bit better and a little bit more like the arcade, well, you might be turning to a company like Hori, and they're actually going to be releasing a fighting stick for the Wii, which I imagine would be kind of hooking up to the Wii Remote, very similar to, like, the classic controller.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, I mean, this is everything that you could possibly want in an arcade stick, and
[SPEAKER_08]: It looks awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Perfect for Street Fighter 2 Turbo or, of course, Guilty Gear XX Accent Core.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was going to say all those original Wii fighting games that the Wii doesn't have right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, they'll have Guilty Gear soon.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, virtual console stuff, and this will also be good for arcade games and stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: Not a lot of people really pick up these arcade sticks.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's the people that really are into their hardcore.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fucking hardcore.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, games like that, so...
[SPEAKER_09]: Can I use it backwards compatible with GameCube, like for Soul Calibur action?
[SPEAKER_08]: Probably not, because this is going to be hooking up via the expansion port on the Wii Remote, so since you can't use the Wii Remote or Classic Controller on GameCube games, you're out of luck.
[SPEAKER_08]: And you probably wouldn't be able to anyways, because there's really only one directional button...
[SPEAKER_08]: Directional Joystick on there and eight buttons, so you wouldn't have all the analog sticks and stuff that the GameCube would have.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh well.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry, I was just responding to some comments in chat there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Somebody who just joined, who hasn't changed their nickname yet, says, why can't the PSP get Contra 4?
[SPEAKER_09]: Why didn't Contra 4 go to the PSP?
[SPEAKER_09]: And Ranma responded, because the PSP sucks ass.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I was like, play FF1.
[SPEAKER_08]: It doesn't suck ass, but I think that this game would work pretty good on the DS.
[SPEAKER_08]: After all, the first three Contra games were on the Nintendo system, so only fitting that Contra 4 come to the DS.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_09]: Radio Esther Nolan's show, and actually said here, "...I thought it was absolutely appalling that a word like this should be used to describe someone who has not achieved very well."
[SPEAKER_09]: The three-year-old, by the way, to put this in perspective, her three-year-old suffered from cerebral palsy and was also severely brain damaged.
[SPEAKER_09]: So she was kind of... That's not funny!
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm just thinking of what the word was.
[SPEAKER_09]: Not the situation.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's really sad.
[SPEAKER_09]: And the lady was very shocked because she performed poorly in this one stage and the game called her, quote, it rated her efforts in a manner derogatory to the disabled.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I'm thinking the word is retarded?
[SPEAKER_09]: I guess, which, you know, is a word.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll admit, we do it here on the program.
[SPEAKER_09]: A lot of, you know, we throw that word around sometimes and not really think about what it really means.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, you know, you have to understand that we, I mean, the word retard means to slow or, you know, to, I guess, I don't know, basically slow, you know, retarding something.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, retard your anger, you know.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was in anger management.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to tell the Loki next time the subject of Apple comes up.
[SPEAKER_09]: Retard your anger.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, but seriously, that's how you... In music, you use that term.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's how you use the word.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's unfortunate.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just like, you know, what is it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Fag.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, people... It isn't, you know, to describe a cigarette and stuff, but it's, you know, slang in the UK, but over here, you know, we use it as, you know, what I get called.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, exactly.
[SPEAKER_10]: Fag your anger, Rob.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: I think mine was by Ubisoft, so shame on them.
[SPEAKER_08]: What do you think, Rice Princess?
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you have an opinion on this?
[SPEAKER_09]: Because you haven't really been talking the rest of the show otherwise, so I'm trying to encourage you to participate.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I'm totally looking at my life journal.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: It really depends on what the word actually is.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just think that they should have included that in the article.
[SPEAKER_10]: Otherwise, it could be something like, you know, I don't know, farty butt or something, you know, being the actual word.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've never heard of farty butt.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're so dumb.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've never heard of farty butt be used for a derogatory term that is disabled.
[SPEAKER_10]: I personally think it's the word Cali from Battlestar Galactica.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dark Knight says it's the French Ubisoft
[SPEAKER_09]: GirlBakura says, something with the word spastic.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe like a spaz, or I don't know, maybe could be the word there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_09]: Azurame says, I think she is right.
[SPEAKER_09]: I work in the mental field, and they could get in some serious trouble if told to the right people.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ranma also says, whatever happens, sticks and stones may break my bones, but names will never hurt me.
[SPEAKER_09]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sigh.
[SPEAKER_09]: and ACHP says the word was spastic.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is spastic really that bad?
[SPEAKER_09]: Have I just been ignorant all these years?
[SPEAKER_09]: Ignant?
[SPEAKER_10]: Why are you so ignorant?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Spastic I don't think is a bad term.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's stupid.
[SPEAKER_09]: She's spastic.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fucking spaz.
[SPEAKER_09]: This frustration leaves me with no other choice but to bring on one of our very favorite segments because I'm just left confused and unsure with what else to do at this point.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's the F-U's of the week time.
[SPEAKER_09]: And just before we get started, AZHP says that spastic is a bad word in the UK but not in America.
[SPEAKER_09]: Kind of like how fag...
[SPEAKER_09]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_08]: It was nice to see that they've repaved the freeway.
[SPEAKER_08]: The only problem is they forgot to paint lines on the freeway.
[SPEAKER_08]: So there's this four-lane highway that all of a sudden becomes one lane because there's no lines on it!
[SPEAKER_08]: Makes it a little unsafe.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just a little, you know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Especially when cars are like, well, I don't know where the lane ends, so... That's kind of bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: Kind of something you should have, I don't know...
[SPEAKER_08]: Done before you finish your project here.
[SPEAKER_08]: At least put something that indicates where the lane ends and begins.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, fuck them, because I know someone's going to get injured and hopefully sue for a lot of money.
[SPEAKER_09]: My F.U.
[SPEAKER_09]: of the week goes to the fact that I just put in my notice I'm going to move on August 1st today, and I have no place to live lined up just yet, so I'll be hitting Craigslist all next week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or it might be OLR, Live From Your House, a contest from the listeners, because I'll be homeless.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_10]: Pretty fat.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Rice for toast.
[SPEAKER_10]: F you to the weather because it's way too fucking hot.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I don't have an air conditioner in my car.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because I'm Poe.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I can't afford a luxury car.
[SPEAKER_10]: And that's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm sorry too.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyhow, what are you giggling at over there, Loki?
[SPEAKER_08]: Shadows liar.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fag your anger, Loki.
[SPEAKER_09]: If anybody hasn't left a review on iTunes... Oh, damn it, they're going to block that word.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're not going to be able to put fag in a review on iTunes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Damn, because I was going to say... Oh, that's retarded.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's horrible.
[SPEAKER_09]: I apologize if you were offended by that and the fact that I laughed at it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, whatever, that's your automatic gut reaction.
[SPEAKER_09]: You don't have to apologize for who you are, Rob.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I really want to see a review on iTunes that says, these guys need to learn how to fag their anger.
[SPEAKER_09]: That'd be brilliant.
[SPEAKER_09]: Can someone make that happen?
[SPEAKER_09]: Get around the word censor somehow.
[SPEAKER_09]: Put P-H-A-G or something.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll give you the link in iTunes if you want to go leave a review there for our chatters, because I'm sure there's someone in there that hasn't done it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Good idea.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, there you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: And Sickester, Insanist, in the chat says, F-H-A-G, Fag Your Anger.
[SPEAKER_09]: I really want someone in the chat to leave that as an iTunes review.
[SPEAKER_09]: These guys need to learn how to fag their anger.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, good times.
[SPEAKER_08]: So anyways...
[SPEAKER_08]: So, guess what?
[SPEAKER_08]: There's this brand new, well, it's not brand new, but a racing series coming back to consoles exclusively to the Wii.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's called Cruisin', and it's going to be exclusively coming to the Wii with licensed cars and whatnot, body kits, upgrades, turbos, all that fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, Cruisin', coming to the Wii.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, to be honest, I never was a huge fan of the Cruisin' series.
[SPEAKER_08]: I always thought them to be kind of cheesy and stupid.
[SPEAKER_08]: I seem to remember DarkSakura as a big fan, though, so she'll probably be excited about this.
[SPEAKER_08]: I played the games.
[SPEAKER_08]: They were pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did anyone remember Rush?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Rush 2049, San Francisco Rush?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I meant the last Rush game that they released that was basically... I don't remember if it was Rush.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it was just San Francisco Rush, but they redid it.
[SPEAKER_08]: for the PSP and stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: It wasn't very good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you think this game might be a disaster as well?
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it might be.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just what we needed in this next gen of gaming or new gen of gaming, whatever you want to call it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Another fucking racing game.
[SPEAKER_08]: That sucks.
[SPEAKER_09]: Even if it is a memorable one from the years past.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: which was a TurboGrafx game there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Bloody Wolf?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, it's like a war-ish game there on the TurboGrafx-16.
[SPEAKER_09]: So you get cutesy cutesy Kirby and Bloody Wolf.
[SPEAKER_09]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: Kirby's Bloody Wolf.
[SPEAKER_09]: What came out in America?
[SPEAKER_09]: I totally missed it.
[SPEAKER_09]: We got the F-Zero, didn't we?
[SPEAKER_08]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I haven't downloaded anything from Virtual Console since Zelda 2.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wasn't that just two weeks ago?
[SPEAKER_08]: It wasn't that long ago.
[SPEAKER_08]: It seems like a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_08]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, some other stuff you're going to be able to download soon.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I don't know why this is a news story, because I always thought this was still on there in the first place.
[SPEAKER_08]: But also a reminder, if you haven't downloaded the internet channel yet, you're now going to have to pay for it.
[SPEAKER_08]: So screw you guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not that it's any good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not that we don't have an OLOB site, because I never made one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because you're lazy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I'm lazy.
[SPEAKER_08]: But anyways, there's going to be a brand new service coming to have original downloadable tiles called WiiWare.
[SPEAKER_08]: And if I remember correctly, that's already online with, I think, the internet channel and also the Wii Vote channel.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's called WiiWare.
[SPEAKER_08]: And hypothetically, there's Dr. Mario Wii, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, hypothetically.
[SPEAKER_09]: 2 plus 2 equals 4.
[SPEAKER_08]: This, I'm not sure if it's going to be a brand new channel, but currently online right now, they do have a section for WiiWare.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's been there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Forever, but they just want you to remember that there is going to be a WiiWare service that's going to be kind of like Xbox Live Arcade or the PlayStation 3 PSN Network.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Going to be seeing some original titles, which will be cool, and I guess we'll have to wait until E3 to find out what exactly is coming there first.
[SPEAKER_08]: Obviously, we're thinking Dr. Mario Wii.
[SPEAKER_09]: I haven't checked the Everybody Votes channel in weeks.
[SPEAKER_09]: Did they ever use the question I submitted to them?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Last one I saw was thank you or hello.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, the question I submitted was which is funnier, clowns or rape?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know if they use that, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm thinking they probably didn't because I probably would have heard something about it.
[SPEAKER_09]: It probably would have made the gaming blog news.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also making the gaming blog news this week is the launch of Three Speech because everybody and their fucking mom has to have a podcast.
[SPEAKER_09]: And so Sony started one.
[SPEAKER_09]: They have the Three Speech podcast.
[SPEAKER_09]: And what did they do in their first podcast?
[SPEAKER_09]: It might not have been the first episode, but definitely they're still early on in their podcasting life.
[SPEAKER_09]: They've taken a shot at Major Nelson.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's interesting, though, is that upon reviews of the new Three Speech podcast, Three Speech doesn't really let you know that they work for Sony, where Major Nelson kind of makes it no secret he does work for Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_09]: But the interesting thing about Major Nelson, he'll say nice things about the Wii once in a while, and even PlayStation 3 if they deserve it.
[SPEAKER_09]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: and, sorry, I laughed because I'm reading chat here.
[SPEAKER_09]: WonderDogHerald suggests everybody votes question, which do you prefer, cock or vag?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I'm sure that'll get through.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're dinner meats.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyhow.
What the hell?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, they're dinner meats.
[SPEAKER_10]: Great way to cover that up there.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: Forget the other story.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just a story about Sony making fun of Major Nelson.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, who cares?
[SPEAKER_09]: Boo-hoo.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm seriously reading this going, who cares?
[SPEAKER_02]: Boo-hoo.
[SPEAKER_09]: They refer to Major Nelson as the unnamed blogger.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh my god!
[SPEAKER_08]: No!
[SPEAKER_08]: Why do they say he's unnamed?
[SPEAKER_08]: He clearly has a name!
[SPEAKER_08]: Major Nelson!
[SPEAKER_08]: That is just pure falsity.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's right, I made up a word, falsity.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't really care.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've listened to Major Nelson once, not that I have anything against the guy, I just don't have time to listen to him.
[SPEAKER_09]: And the three-speech podcast I'll probably never listen to, so you know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: Listen to this podcast, it's all you need.
[SPEAKER_08]: Major spoiler alert here, but I hear that the next three-speech podcast calls Leo Laporte spastic.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then the next one, they tell Reggie if he's made of faggot's anger.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, this is kind of interesting, actually.
[SPEAKER_08]: We've been seeing a lot of these weird third-party adapters and stuff come out for the 360.
[SPEAKER_08]: This one, though, is being created by XMN, and that's a mod company.
[SPEAKER_08]: And they're actually creating an HDMI cable for the regular non-elite
[SPEAKER_08]: and no word yet on how exactly it's going to work but apparently it's going to allow you to use HDMI cables obviously for 1080p on systems that may not be black and supporting a HDMI out on it so the speculation I believe is that it's going to be something that has to do with the VGA cable maybe converting the signal over to work on HDMI I don't know
[SPEAKER_08]: But it should be interesting to see.
[SPEAKER_08]: So if you want to keep an eye on that, check out xcm.cc.
[SPEAKER_08]: And they have all the information on that.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now, why would I want to get an HDMI cable?
[SPEAKER_09]: Is it really that big a difference?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think it's a big difference.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's really, you know, if you want that kind of cable for your console.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think they're maybe worried that later on when...
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: Also on the Xbox 360, something you can see in this lovely new HDMI would be some of the new achievements in the NCAA Football 08.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now, there's an achievement list, and what's kind of interesting about it is that there's actually some product placement in the achievement list.
[SPEAKER_09]: They even use, for the little icons for the achievement, like Pontiac and Old Spice.
[SPEAKER_09]: There are actual official logos there.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm trying to look at what some of these are actually called, some of these achievements.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can get the list for yourself at Xbox360Achievements.org.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_09]: There it is, yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Old Spice Red Zone Perfection.
[SPEAKER_09]: Complete a Play Now or Dynasty Mode game with Red Zone efficiency rating of 100%.
[SPEAKER_09]: You get 15 gamer points for that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Pontiac Fourth Quarter Comeback, with a little Pontiac logo.
[SPEAKER_09]: Win a Play Now or Dynasty Mode game when down by 14 to start the fourth quarter.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, I don't understand, but yet still with all these corporate sponsorships, and now they're going to throw their logos into my achievements list, these games are still $60!
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks for watching.
[SPEAKER_08]: See you next time.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: And Solid Goomba in chat says, remember the Fight Night achievements?
[SPEAKER_09]: Like there was like a Burger King match and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: But the interesting thing about that, I mean, yeah, it hasn't happened in a while though.
[SPEAKER_09]: And the interesting thing about this is that these achievements like actually have the company's logos in them.
[SPEAKER_09]: And remember that these things will show up on like your gamer thing in the Xbox and when you look on the internet and all that crap.
[SPEAKER_09]: So it's just kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's going to filthy up your profile with corporate logos.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, not a problem for me because I hate sports games, but...
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to tell you this much.
[SPEAKER_08]: But you love achievements.
[SPEAKER_08]: I do like achievements, but I'm not going to buy a product because I see a fucking logo for it.
[SPEAKER_08]: If it were that easy, then, you know, these people would be making billions upon billions of dollars just for having their logo out there.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just you don't automatically go.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, they obviously pay for this because it works.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, it's like product recognition.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe somebody sees the little Old Spice logo and goes, oh, yeah, I need to pick up, you know, some deodorant.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll get, you know, get that.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then that's like in their mind.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_08]: I knew you would like this news.
[SPEAKER_08]: I love the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can pick up a cow with your tractor beam and then hug it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I notice there's a theme here.
[SPEAKER_09]: You like these games where you get to play as aliens and do things to humans.
[SPEAKER_09]: Not necessarily.
[SPEAKER_09]: I like Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_09]: I like sandbox games.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, well, another very popular series that a lot of people like is Geometry Wars Galaxies.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I'm sorry, Geometry Wars, but people are looking forward to Geometry War Galaxies because they like the old school one.
[SPEAKER_09]: And GameSpot put up a video this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was a demo of the upcoming Wii title, Geometry Wars Galaxies.
[SPEAKER_09]: But what kind of caused some people to turn around and go, huh?
[SPEAKER_09]: Is that during the demo, the developer actually pauses the game and the word achievements comes up.
[SPEAKER_09]: So the question comes up, is this game actually secretly being developed for Xbox 360 as well?
[SPEAKER_09]: Or are there achievements coming to the Wii?
[SPEAKER_09]: Or is it because the game is early in development and it's a port and they just haven't gotten rid of that yet?
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, there's a million different theories, but it certainly has made some people go, huh?
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it's just probably, you know, not necessarily... It doesn't have to have the achievement system from 360 in order to have achievements.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, look at Resistance.
[SPEAKER_08]: Resistance has achievements in it, but it's just for the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not anything... Like internal achievements.
[SPEAKER_08]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just for unlocking bonus content and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not necessarily... EA has that even on the 360, like the Burnout games.
[SPEAKER_08]: You get those stupid trophies for, like, everything you do.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_09]: You hit the gas pedal.
[SPEAKER_09]: You get a trophy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_08]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_08]: Another interesting thing, though, coming from Geometry Wars Galaxies is they're going to have download play in there as well.
[SPEAKER_08]: So if you own the DS version of the game, you can actually transfer over and download play a full version of Geometry Wars Retro Evolved onto other stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also, if you have the Wii version, you can transfer over a full version of Geometry Wars Retro Evolved onto the DS.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it's going to have cross-platform play that way.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's Connie.
[SPEAKER_08]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: The Animal Crossing Island is the thing I always think of.
[SPEAKER_09]: Remember in Animal Crossing you could go to the island on the Game Boy?
[SPEAKER_08]: It was awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now another thing that's super awesome, and it's because it's Grand Theft Auto 4, the brand new trailer came out.
[SPEAKER_08]: It looks pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: They didn't show a whole lot in there, but definitely...
[SPEAKER_08]: The graphics looked a little bit scaled down from what they were before.
[SPEAKER_08]: Obviously, though, they're probably tweaking it to make sure that the frame rate is good.
[SPEAKER_08]: But they did show some gunfights and, of course, car chases and all that fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just more of a tease right now, and I'm sure there's going to be a new trailer coming out about once a month or so.
[SPEAKER_08]: Especially with E3 right around the corner, you know there's going to be something that they're going to be teasing at least.
[SPEAKER_08]: Only a few months away now.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, so are you still very excited about this?
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, was there any kind of revelations that the trailer had for you, or is it just more like mouth-wetting?
[SPEAKER_08]: It was just mouth-wetting.
[SPEAKER_08]: They did show the main character, Nico, actually holding on to the back of a truck, kind of being held on to that, and then also hanging from a helicopter, which looked pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: It looks awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think once we see this game in action...
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just going to be phenomenal.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I have the collector's edition on order, because I have to have all that crap that comes with it.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, we're going to get into another segment here, and we're going to go from something very, very new to a classic segment on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a game we like to play, especially during slow news weeks such as this one, called Beat the Host.
[SPEAKER_09]: And tonight on Beat the Host, we're going to be looking for a contestant to call us on our Skype line.
[SPEAKER_09]: Go ahead and call now if you'd like to play.
[SPEAKER_09]: However, for tonight's Beat the Host, you should know retro knowledge is really going to help tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: So 1-877-GAME-OLR if you'd like to play, or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: So go ahead and give us a call right now, and we will take the first person to call in on our Skype line.
[SPEAKER_09]: And the way it's going to work, we're going to change up the rules again a little bit tonight, but it is going to have to do with identifying game music or game noise, and I will let you know a little more about that when we get into the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, we're starting to get some calls on the line.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's go to a call.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, it's Ranma.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_09]: Finally, a normal sounding call.
[SPEAKER_09]: We have our contestant.
[SPEAKER_09]: Stop calling everybody.
[SPEAKER_09]: You guys can call later when we open up the Skype line for calls.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ranma, you ready to play some Beat the Host?
Yeah!
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, tonight, you get to challenge Loki.
[SPEAKER_09]: He's the only one, because I already know the questions, and well, Irene, you would just whoop her ass, I mean, no matter what the game is.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wait, what is the topic?
[SPEAKER_09]: The topic is Atari 2600 games.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh yeah, pick that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, so Matt, in part A, you may remember, seemed to be, he flaunted his Atari 2600 knowledge.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just like playing Atari 2600, it doesn't mean I've played everything.
[SPEAKER_09]: I like combat.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is going to be tough tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because it's so tough, we're going to change up the rules of Beat the Host a little bit tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because you know every time we play Beat the Host, we change the rules.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, Ranma?
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, so what we're going to do, I'm going to need you to speak nice and loud, or I might not hear you over the game music, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, hold on, let me, I'm going to leave the chat room.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, yes, you need to leave the chat room.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's good.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's very ethical of you.
[SPEAKER_09]: I appreciate that.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now, what's going to happen is that we're going to play some music from Atari 2600 games.
[SPEAKER_09]: I actually recorded myself playing some Atari 2600 games earlier today, and you're going to hear some music from them.
[SPEAKER_09]: The first one of you guys to shout out the correct answer gets a point.
[SPEAKER_09]: Game number one
[SPEAKER_09]: It's based on a vector arcade game, but the Atari 2600 couldn't support vector graphics.
[SPEAKER_09]: No.
[SPEAKER_09]: Since there was no separate hyperspace button, you used this by pulling the joystick down.
[SPEAKER_09]: Galaxin?
[SPEAKER_10]: Can I answer?
[SPEAKER_09]: No.
[SPEAKER_09]: When you shoot a rock, it splits into two smaller rocks.
[SPEAKER_09]: Asteroids.
[SPEAKER_06]: Asteroids.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ah, Loki got it first.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki gets a point.
[SPEAKER_09]: Good job, Loki.
[SPEAKER_09]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: One point for Loki.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was Asteroids.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just didn't remember the er, er, er, er part.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, here we go.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's go to, you ready for number two, Rama?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you can get it like three seconds sooner next time, you'll be good.
[SPEAKER_06]: No problem.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, here's song, or game number two.
[SPEAKER_09]: Combat.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, Loki got it without even a hint.
[SPEAKER_09]: I knew he'd get it when he said he'd played all those Combat back in the day.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're not looking at my computer screen, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: I can't see anything on your computer screen.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was Combat.
[SPEAKER_09]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was the default packing game for the Atari 2600, by the way.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_09]: You ready for number three, Ranma?
[SPEAKER_09]: You can do it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're losing 2-0.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's see what we can do.
[SPEAKER_09]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tempest.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's a version of this on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_08]: Centipede.
[SPEAKER_08]: Millipede.
[SPEAKER_09]: Pressing the button flapped your wings.
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: Joust.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, you got it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was joust.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nice job.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: 3-0, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're killing me here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry, dude.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's all right.
[SPEAKER_09]: I still love you, man.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now, this one is a tricky one.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to tell you straight up.
[SPEAKER_09]: This one is fucking hard, all right?
[SPEAKER_09]: So here we go.
[SPEAKER_09]: If either of you get this, I will be very impressed.
Boom.
[SPEAKER_02]: Boom.
[SPEAKER_09]: Evil Otto was a character that would chase you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Robotron?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_09]: Some people know this game from the big happy face bouncing creature that would stalk you.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's Evil Otto.
[SPEAKER_09]: Frenzy.
[SPEAKER_09]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Damn.
[SPEAKER_09]: You shot robots in a maze.
[SPEAKER_06]: Robotron 23?
[SPEAKER_09]: No.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ten seconds.
[SPEAKER_09]: Evil Otto, Big Happy Face, Bouncing Creature, Robots in a Maze.
[SPEAKER_06]: Galaxian?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Berserk.
[SPEAKER_09]: Berserk is the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Berserk.
[SPEAKER_06]: I actually had the board game to that.
[SPEAKER_09]: You what?
[SPEAKER_06]: I actually had the board game to that, like,
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, very long time ago.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ah, good job.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, and, oh well, it happens.
[SPEAKER_09]: Brain fart.
[SPEAKER_09]: Frenzies just like that game, too.
[SPEAKER_09]: Good job in the chat room, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: Some folks there got bizarre.
[SPEAKER_09]: Some folks were saying it was Sword Quest, which was a really good guess, but unfortunately not right.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, this next one's a toughie, too, and I'll also be impressed if either of you get this.
[SPEAKER_09]: In this game, you are out to rescue Lady P. Lady P is being held by a jungle tribe.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_09]: You start this game swinging from rope to rope, then you fight crocodiles, then you dodge falling rocks.
[SPEAKER_10]: Can I please answer?
[SPEAKER_09]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_08]: This wasn't Kongo Bongo.
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ranma, you still with us?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I know what the game is, I just can't remember the title.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not Donkey Kong Jr., is it?
[SPEAKER_09]: Ten seconds, no.
[SPEAKER_09]: Lady P, Jungle Tribe, Swinging Ropes, Fighting Crocodiles, Dodging Falling Rocks.
[SPEAKER_09]: You do all that in Jungle Hunt.
[SPEAKER_09]: Jungle Hunt.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, still 3-0 in Loki's favor.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can still win it, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, I got an easier one for you this time.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, you ready?
[SPEAKER_09]: Ready.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_09]: Pac-Man.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, my God, that was fast.
[SPEAKER_09]: He knew it right from the starting tone there.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was Pac-Man.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's play a little more of that, because I barely got to hear any of it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Remember little ghost chasing noises?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, there it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: Based on a very popular arcade game, but it was considered a disappointment, the home version.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have a poster for this at my work.
[SPEAKER_09]: You eat a wafer for bonus points in Pac-Man.
[SPEAKER_09]: Look at that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Damn.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's four left, so Ranma, you can still tie it up.
[SPEAKER_09]: Working on it.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's alright Ranma.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_09]: I barely remember these when I was playing through them today.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, now this one is fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: This one's a tricky one, but I love this game.
Burger time.
No.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, Ranma gets one!
[SPEAKER_09]: It was Popeye.
[SPEAKER_09]: It sounded familiar.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Of course, you can kind of hear a little theme being used in the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: There was a movie out around the same time.
[SPEAKER_09]: And remember, this was a really cool game at the time because the stages were so unique.
[SPEAKER_09]: And in that first stage that you were hearing, Olive Oil was actually throwing hearts down that you had to catch before they sank in the water.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ranma is on the board!
[SPEAKER_09]: Good job, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_09]: Pitfall 2 Pitfall 2
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, poor Ranma.
[SPEAKER_09]: It is Pitfall 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was one of the first games to feature a full soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_09]: The sequel to another popular Atari game and the main character was Pitfall, Harry.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ranma, so close.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: Just because Loki pisses me off sometimes, I'm going to give that to you anyway.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're going to give it to you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sweet.
All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, so there we go.
[SPEAKER_09]: So what do we have?
[SPEAKER_09]: Four for Loki, two for Ranma.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, here we go.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's go to another one.
[SPEAKER_09]: This one is also very hard.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_09]: This game was also based on a popular movie series.
[SPEAKER_09]: Star Trek?
[SPEAKER_09]: No.
[SPEAKER_09]: Star Wars?
[SPEAKER_09]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_01]: E.T.?
[SPEAKER_09]: You can walk into a phone booth to change from one character to another.
[SPEAKER_09]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Superman?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, Ranma got it.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was Superman.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ah...
[SPEAKER_09]: Remember the Superman game?
[SPEAKER_09]: It was great.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was so weird because, like, you could fly up and you would fly into another screen.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, you moved up, down, left, and right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, it was weird.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was very weird.
[SPEAKER_09]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ranma's got three now.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, because you gave him one.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I did.
[SPEAKER_09]: I totally gave him one.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's see if we can tie it up, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is the last one.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: And this is a doozy.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is a hell of a game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Miss Pac-Man.
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_09]: This game was made by Mystique Entertainment.
[SPEAKER_08]: Adventure?
[SPEAKER_09]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a highly controversial game that shows up on lots of gag Atari 2600 lists.
[SPEAKER_09]: Custer's Revenge.
[SPEAKER_09]: Good job, Loki.
[SPEAKER_09]: It is Custer's Revenge.
[SPEAKER_09]: And of course, the object of the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Your naked ass has to fuck an Indian girl lots and lots and that's why the game is very controversial.
[SPEAKER_10]: You were just playing that earlier.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, that's when I was recording the clips.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh my god, that was so funny.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's why you couldn't play because you walked in here when I was setting it up.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, well the final score Ranma, you got three points a very good showing and unfortunately Loki beat you with five so unfortunately you got beat by the host tonight but you made a damn good effort on a very tough topic.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks, man.
[SPEAKER_06]: I appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_09]: No problemo.
[SPEAKER_09]: Take any shout-outs or plugs you want to give as long as we have you on the air as a consolation prize.
[SPEAKER_06]: Visit my website, www.djranmas.net.
[SPEAKER_09]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_09]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_06]: Got it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now, the audio looked a little low to me on the board here, but it seems like the chat room was able to play along just fine, so I'm hoping the audio was just fine there as far as...
[SPEAKER_09]: Live radio, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_09]: Take it or leave it.
[SPEAKER_09]: HURRICAN
[SPEAKER_09]: and you can download Hurricane from the site hurrican-game.de because it's German.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a 40 megabyte game.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's Windows compatible and if you remember gaming on the Commodore 64, you're probably going to love this.
[SPEAKER_09]: So check it out, Hurricane.
[SPEAKER_08]: Another game that's getting a sequel and it's long due, I think, and this is, I guess, a rumor for right now, but Parasite Eve is...
[SPEAKER_08]: Slated on possibly coming out to the PlayStation 3 and 360.
[SPEAKER_08]: And no word exactly on any details on that, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess people were thinking, because they originally announced Parasite Eve 3 as a mobile game, but they're thinking this is going to be something else.
[SPEAKER_08]: It says also, I guess Quarterman from EGM is saying that they're going to be, Hideo Kojima is going to be...
[SPEAKER_08]: I was?
[SPEAKER_08]: I was.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe I'm smoking crack.
[SPEAKER_10]: I thought it was a good game.
[SPEAKER_10]: I never actually beat it, but I played through a good part of it.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was me in most Final Fantasy games.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like the combat system in that.
[SPEAKER_08]: The combat system in the first Parasite Eve reminds me much of what they're doing in Final Fantasy XII right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: How that system, you know, kind of, you have a big dome or whatever that you can attack in and stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: It reminds me very much of that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, before we get to the Skype line, I got one more story for you guys.
[SPEAKER_09]: And since it is July 1st, also known as Canada Day, I thought those of you Canadians would appreciate this.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can get a red PlayStation 3, and it's a special kind of Canada event.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can only get this in Canada.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's actually a contest that's being held, and the contest is being run through July 15th at playstation.ca.
[SPEAKER_09]: and you can actually win yourself a red PlayStation 3 or a limited edition Canada PlayStation 3 t-shirt there.
[SPEAKER_09]: It doesn't have the maple leaf on it, but it has a 3 in place of the maple leaf.
[SPEAKER_09]: Otherwise, it kind of looks like the Canadian flag.
[SPEAKER_09]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: Only three of those red PlayStation 3s, by the way, will be made.
[SPEAKER_09]: So that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, technically four, since there's already been a red PlayStation 3 out there custom made.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, that's different, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is kind of officially endorsed, so to speak, by Sony, so...
[SPEAKER_09]: I know you have some Canadian listeners there, so you might want to go enter that contest and brag to all your friends, eh?
[SPEAKER_08]: This is completely random, but I feel that we should talk about this real quick.
[SPEAKER_08]: We went over the fries the other day, because I had my motherboard.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's a fan that went out.
[SPEAKER_08]: My computer is kind of on the fritz.
[SPEAKER_08]: But we saw, or Nelly picked up this USB stripper.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's on a stripping pole that you can buy.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've seen that before, because we were thinking about getting it for her for her birthday before we realized we were all freaking poor.
[SPEAKER_09]: I thought that was funny.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was great.
[SPEAKER_09]: Did you guys actually see it in motion or what?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, but we almost bought it.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then, like, common sense kicked in and we said, no, we probably don't need a $30 USB stripper.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because she wanted to take it to work and, you know, her work wouldn't really, you know, think too highly of that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, well we're going to open up the Skype line if you'd like to give us a call 1-877-GAME-OLR or you can call us on the actual program Skype.
[SPEAKER_09]: Orange Lounge Radio is our username.
[SPEAKER_09]: We always like to hear from our listeners and get your guys' two cents on what's going on in the gaming scene and the gaming community.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you have any feedback to tonight's articles or what have you or you just want to tell Rice Princess to say hi to you and actually talk on the program tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: All of that you can do by calling our program.
[SPEAKER_09]: So while we wait for some calls, because there's a little bit of a lag, do you have any last minute stories?
[SPEAKER_09]: No.
[SPEAKER_09]: No?
[SPEAKER_09]: No last minute stories tonight?
[SPEAKER_08]: Not at the moment.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh my gosh, it really is a slow gaming week.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was looking for stuff, but I haven't seen anything.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well... Should I pick up Project Silphid?
[SPEAKER_09]: I haven't... I saw it scroll by your screen there, and I'm curious about that game, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: It looks okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want to get this t-shirt.
[SPEAKER_08]: It looks like one of those Target t-shirts, like the don't bother me ones, and it says good, and it has, you know, the male, female, like almost looks like a restroom-like logo or something, and that's good, and then better has a guy with two girls, and then best shows a guy playing a video game.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're finally getting calls, thank God.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_09]: Hello, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, damn it.
[SPEAKER_10]: It didn't work.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hola, bienvenidos a Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you always wanted to test your Skype line, you can do that by calling Echo123.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is the username on Skype if you'd always like to test your connection in advance, which we highly recommend.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey, it's DJ Tyrant.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, what's up DJ Tyrant?
[SPEAKER_09]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey, I'm doing pretty good.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm at Anime Expo 2007 right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now you actually got into Anime Expo 2007 on behalf of Orange Launch Radio, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, then you better have a good report for us.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's going on at Anime Expo?
[SPEAKER_01]: Lots of anime, fandom type stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's actually a lot of gaming stuff also.
[SPEAKER_01]: What did I check out today?
[SPEAKER_01]: I checked out the Naruto fighting game for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_01]: Those are a little sloppy for that, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wait, what was sloppy?
[SPEAKER_09]: The controls are sloppy?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, that sucks.
[SPEAKER_01]: But there's Guilty Gear, the new one, XX, forget the subtitle for that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Accent Core.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki says it's Accent Core.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, that sounds right.
[SPEAKER_01]: I didn't get to play it, but it looked pretty solid.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, they are.
[SPEAKER_09]: Apparently Square has a bunch of stuff for Eleven.
[SPEAKER_09]: I didn't get to swing by their booth because I don't play Eleven, but...
[SPEAKER_01]: I saw a lot of people with stuff from Final Fantasy XI Yeah, there's
[SPEAKER_01]: Tons.
[SPEAKER_01]: As the resident's wow addict, I found about three really, really good costumes.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I'll post some pictures up when I get home, but they're, like, really well done.
[SPEAKER_01]: They look exactly like they look in game, which I found really impressive.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now, Ranma would like to point out, for those of us here, that Anime Expo is not an anime con.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a trade show.
[SPEAKER_09]: And apparently there's a very distinct difference.
[SPEAKER_09]: I guess because I don't follow the con scene enough, it kind of feels the same to me.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, what about, you said there was some gaming stuff there.
[SPEAKER_09]: What about tournaments?
[SPEAKER_09]: Has there been any big tournaments?
[SPEAKER_09]: I know these cons usually have a game room.
[SPEAKER_09]: What kinds of stuff have been around in the game rooms?
[SPEAKER_01]: There's a pretty big console room with Guitar Hero and
[SPEAKER_01]: The typical fighting type games.
[SPEAKER_01]: There was a Pokemon tournament last night and there's been various fighting game tournaments for Guilty Gear and Naruto.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's a Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_01]: tournament tomorrow that I will be playing in and losing in the first round in.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's definitely a lot of stuff for gamers to do at the show.
[SPEAKER_09]: Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_09]: Tournament Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_09]: Tournament
[SPEAKER_09]: So how long is the con running?
[SPEAKER_09]: How long is the con?
[SPEAKER_09]: It ends tomorrow?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, well make sure you go get your hands on Guilty Gear for us so you can give some impressions of it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Definitely will.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ranma would like to clarify, Anime Expo is a trade show because their board of directors are people from the anime industry and they use Anime Expo to promote new titles more than any other con.
[SPEAKER_09]: Think of Anime Expo as the anime equivalent of E3.
[SPEAKER_09]: and Insanus adds to that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also, Anime Expo sucks.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, that's an opinion.
[SPEAKER_09]: But you sound like you're having a lot of fun at the con, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Right, Jimmy?
[SPEAKER_01]: He just wants to kick you because he can't come to it.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, well, Jimmy, anything else you want to add about the convention?
[SPEAKER_01]: If you can come next year, we can come hang out.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'll buy drinks.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, hey, if there's drinks there, I'm there.
[SPEAKER_09]: But, you know, I will be in SoCal for E for All, so we'll see you then.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right, have a nice night, guys.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right, later, buddy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks for the call.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_09]: Our roving reporter, Jimmy, also known as DJ Tyrant.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, let's go to the phones.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's GS68.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hello, GS68.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's on your mind, my friend?
[SPEAKER_03]: First of all, that was me calling before Matt because my mic wasn't set up right.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll forgive you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Could you hear us yelling at you in Spanish and everything?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's got to be embarrassing.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, well, now you're on.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_03]: First of all, I have...
[SPEAKER_03]: I was eating cup noodles when Rice Princess was saying fag or anger so I had to spit that out.
[SPEAKER_09]: What else do you want to talk about tonight, GS68?
[SPEAKER_03]: On the Guitar Hero message board, I've been talking about the hyperspeed code lately and how some people think it's a cheat.
[SPEAKER_03]: What are your thoughts on it?
[SPEAKER_09]: I do not know of the hyperspeed code.
[SPEAKER_09]: Give me a little background on this.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's this about?
[SPEAKER_03]: On the Guitar Hero 2 title screen, you press orange, blue, orange, yellow, orange, blue, orange, yellow, and then it says cheat activated hyperspeed.
[SPEAKER_09]: And what exactly does that do to the game?
[SPEAKER_09]: Does it make the songs run faster or something?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, it makes the notes scroll faster.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's kind of like times two speed in DDR or high speed in Beatmania.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I don't know if that's cheating or not.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, I guess maybe the developers intended it to be a cheat if that's what they're labeling it as in the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like in Beatmania, I never considered that a cheat.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, God, that's what you have to use to play some of those songs.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know any other way.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe it is cheating even in Beatmania.
[SPEAKER_09]: And for whatever reason, the community doesn't really look at it that way.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I think they just never looked at it that way because it's always been considered a modifier.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because, like, people whose music game experience is one of the Guitar Hero, like, have never heard of it being a mod, so when they saw that it was a cheat, they automatically thought it was a cheat because it has cheat activated.
[SPEAKER_03]: What are your thoughts on it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I think it's legit.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, if you think it helps you, just use it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it's still the same notes, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's not going to help you beat Jordan on Expert, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Probably, probably not.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, what's the big freaking deal?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, if you close your eyes and play the song, I mean, does Hyper Speed really make a difference?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, if you close your eyes and play the song, is that how you have to beat Jordan on Expert?
[SPEAKER_09]: Probably, huh?
[SPEAKER_09]: If you've actually gone to the great extents to memorize Guitar Hero 2 songs, instead of using the speed modifier, I would recommend you go outside.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm just messing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hypothetically speaking.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, people memorize the DDR songs, so why not the Guitar Hero songs?
[SPEAKER_09]: It happens.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, well, any other thoughts, GS68?
[SPEAKER_09]: No.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's pretty much it
[SPEAKER_05]: Nothing much.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thought y'all would talk about Soul Calibur for a little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wanted to touch up on something I discussed last week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sure, Soul Calibur 4 online, good stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_05]: There's supposed to be like a sad story game, Soul Calibur Legends.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, that was the game that's being created for the Nintendo Wii if I remember right, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's not side-scrolling though, it's just kind of a hack and slash.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wasn't that how Mortal Kombat, what was that, Shaolin Monks or whatever was kind of like that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was thinking more of Tekken Force I would say it looks more like the Immortal Combat Channel amongst games Because I know Tekken Force is more like Final Fight or something like that Here's the only thing I care about, is Ivy in it, yes or no?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes Sold!
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it would be a multiple problem round 6 for you, I think, if I'm not mistaken Alright, well what else have you heard on the game?
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, just early development details and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_05]: They had a picture on it on Kotaku.com and it just looked like a test shot because all it saw was basically Siegfried swinging his sword around a bunch of mummies.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I like the concept and all, so.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is it the type of game you think you're going to buy?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't own a Wii, so.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, you don't own a Wii.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is that because you don't want one or because you can't find one?
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, both.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, I actually decided that I was gonna go get, um, 360.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ah, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: But that won't be until November, so that would offset itself.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, you never know, you might luck out, maybe the game will come out cross-platform.
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh, yeah, give it time and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, another game I had on mind, but I think I just totally lost track.
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh, Guitar Hero 80s.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, I actually saw the, um, song list and everything.
[SPEAKER_05]: And there are actually some decent songs in that list.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know why some of y'all didn't like some of the songs.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, what's your problem, Rice Princess?
[SPEAKER_09]: Why didn't you like Guitar Hero's 80s editions?
[SPEAKER_09]: What's your big issue?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, if I knew any of the songs, I might like it better.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: You're a baby.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do you remember Friendship Bracelets and Garbage Pail Kids?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, do you remember Slap Bracelets?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, I do.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, those were pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: And Hypercolor shirts.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, anyway.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, then I don't know what her problem is.
[SPEAKER_09]: She was just listening to the wrong kind of music in the 80s.
[SPEAKER_10]: The wrong kind of music?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I don't.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have to admit, I'm not that excited about the track list either, Dark Knight.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's some songs that made me go, woohoo!
[SPEAKER_09]: But a lot of it kind of makes me go, hmm.
[SPEAKER_09]: Not really a memorable song.
[SPEAKER_09]: But what to you makes a song list great?
[SPEAKER_09]: Convince us we're wrong.
[SPEAKER_05]: Give me Stairway.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, Turning Japanese might be one.
[SPEAKER_05]: But if I had the power to add a song, give me Stairway to Heaven.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know exactly.
[SPEAKER_09]: No Stairway denied.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dark Knight, we gotta let you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: Any last thoughts real quick?
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, you need to start playing PSU again because, well, that's right, you have 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: You probably already got it.
[SPEAKER_05]: But they recently gave out Sonic statues.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, God, I haven't touched the game in forever, but I think my membership's still active and I'm paying for it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just haven't gone into the game in forever, so...
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, everybody got Sonic statue now.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: Pull me away from World of Warcraft, seriously.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I feel like, I know I'm going to get so much hate mail like, Rob, play a real game, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I can't explain how addicting this game is and it's the social end of it completely because the fact that a lot of my friends play it.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's not even really the game itself that I'm in love with.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm in love with Ventrilo.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's my problem.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not going to go into detail about the Ventrilo thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I think it's just right now the game
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's kind of winding down now because the expansion is coming.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, hopefully the expansion will give it a badly needed kick in the pants because I would like to get back into some PSU.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: But anyway, quick plug for my show because I do a show on Disney Genius Radio, Dark Knight Ninja Dojo on Thursday nights.
[SPEAKER_05]: Welcome to join if you like.
[SPEAKER_05]: Basically going to be talking about this week, the iPhones.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ooh, iPhone.
[SPEAKER_09]: I saw one this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're very pretty.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I will try to tune in and I think I'm supposed to be on the show this week or very soon, yes?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Scott will be there, hopefully.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, I just have to double check my personal calendar, but I should be there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks for calling.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bye, folks.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dark Knight here on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_09]: and everybody's got their own show these days.
[SPEAKER_09]: I swear to God.
[SPEAKER_09]: Swear to God.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, it's all good though.
[SPEAKER_09]: I like Dark Knight.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, you're on.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to punch that guy in the face.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know who you are.
[SPEAKER_09]: Punch him in the neck.
[SPEAKER_09]: You told me you fixed it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now that's another edit.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ah, forget it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm not going to edit that out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Podcast listeners, you guys can deal with it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Way to be lazy.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was DMN, by the way.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you want to hate somebody for blowing your ears out, that was Insanest
[SPEAKER_09]: DMM, whatever the hell your name is right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: Love you!
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, you're on Orange Tons Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_09]: Mushy Mushy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Mushy Mushy?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it's relevant.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, like you're saying hello.
[SPEAKER_09]: I hear myself.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sometimes there is a bit of an echo.
[SPEAKER_09]: Identify yourself, please.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, uh, Nintendo Maniac 64.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nintendo Maniac 64.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's on your mind, my friend?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, dealing with the
[SPEAKER_04]: What was it?
[SPEAKER_04]: You got a letter... Is this your first Japanese listener on the show?
[SPEAKER_04]: A letter in the book?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I think Peker Uno is also in Japan from my following him on Twitter, because I actually have a Twitter account, and some of the listeners have me added on there as Sky on Twitter, and I picked up that he's in Japan.
[SPEAKER_09]: So... Is he really Japanese, though?
[SPEAKER_09]: I haven't the foggiest idea, but I'm sure I'm going to get a Twitter about it now.
[SPEAKER_09]: So...
[SPEAKER_09]: We don't even know if our guy's message is Japanese.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, I've looked at the statistics.
[SPEAKER_09]: We do have some Japanese listeners.
[SPEAKER_09]: We have listeners all over the world, just not all of them are vocal.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I understand, it takes a lot of effort to write an email, so no expectations.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I don't think this guy's the first one, but he's the first email I can recall getting from Japan, but we have had emails from other parts of Asia.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Other than that, oh yeah, you know how I was talking about earlier with the
[SPEAKER_04]: Outro
[SPEAKER_09]: So I don't know, well, I don't know, because culturally over here, that's not really a bad word.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I suppose, you know, if the game had called me a fag, I may not have liked that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wait, you know who we could ask?
[SPEAKER_10]: Wait, no, wait.
[SPEAKER_10]: Where is it a bad word?
[SPEAKER_10]: In England?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: We could ask Sasha.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't think he's listening.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't see him in chat tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: He's not listening.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, he listens to your show.
[SPEAKER_10]: He's sleeping.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, he does.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's kind of late over there in Britain right now, so we don't have a lot of time.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, but I'll ask him.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: You do that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Call him a spastic and see what happens.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_10]: He might make me number two on his MySpace.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_09]: I love how Rice Princess' biggest concern in the world is that OMG, I might get demoted in the top 8 on Myspace.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_09]: Get a life, woman.
[SPEAKER_09]: I can't.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's never going to happen.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, Orange Lounge Radio has a Myspace, so I can't complain too much.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, Nintendo Maniac, anything else on your mind?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I finally, finally got TimeSplitters 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've been trying to find it forever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Finally got it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that brick-smashing glass level, I got gold in it, and like
[SPEAKER_08]: It gets harder as you pass through some of the levels in there.
[SPEAKER_08]: What exactly do you do in this level, Loki?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, there's, like, they have different levels, like, breaking stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Usually it'll be with a brick or something, and you have to smash windows.
[SPEAKER_08]: And, um, you have to throw a brick through it, and it's pretty hard.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have to go through and... I think it's a little shorter, actually, if I think of it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Either way.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, we're going to go ahead and let you go, buddy, but thanks so much for giving us a call and enjoy TimeSplitters, okay?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Later.
[SPEAKER_09]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, that's going to do it tonight for the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry to those calls we didn't get to.
[SPEAKER_09]: We did have a lot of calls coming through, but we have a lot.
[SPEAKER_09]: We've been on the air quite a while now.
[SPEAKER_09]: We've got to wrap things up.
[SPEAKER_09]: So let's go around now.
[SPEAKER_09]: Since there's no last-minute stories, we're going to go around and get everybody's... No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's not the case.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, you found something.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, of course.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was taking the time to pull up the stories.
[SPEAKER_08]: Go for it.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the rumor is, apparently, Beautiful Katamari is going to be skipping the PlayStation 3 and going straight to the Wii.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it's supposed to be coming out next year on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_08]: Although, to be honest, though, I would say it's coming out in both fiscal year 2008.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's just my guess, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: Didn't you get in trouble for that once before?
[SPEAKER_08]: Uh, no.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, I'm guessing...
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know, but if I were to guess, I would say it's coming fiscal year 2008.
[SPEAKER_09]: I honestly don't give a fuck anymore.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't give a fuck.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let the game come out wherever it's going to come out, and maybe I'll buy it if it's not just a copy of the first game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyways, so some other stuff that's going to be interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: This was kind of a surprise to me, although this is one of the only films of his I'm going to go see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Postal is being called...
[SPEAKER_08]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_08]: My microphone went out there for a second.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I turned the audio in the studio down.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyways, Postal is being called one of the best films, and apparently it got standing ovations at Cannes, which is very surprising, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Everybody at the Cannes Film Festival is on ecstasy, apparently.
[SPEAKER_08]: It says, anyways, it says,
[SPEAKER_08]: Uwe Boll calls it his final statement.
[SPEAKER_08]: He says, you can't make a more radical movie.
[SPEAKER_08]: There is no way you can ignore Postal.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's one of the funniest and most important films of the last decade.
[SPEAKER_08]: It is one of the best films of all time.
[SPEAKER_08]: Of course, this is Uwe Boll talking about himself.
[SPEAKER_09]: Were they giving it a standing ovation because they got to leave?
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it looks cheesy.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know it's going to be offensive.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkTetsuya says, or was Uebol just dreaming the whole thing?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, he might have been.
[SPEAKER_08]: Some other interesting stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: A game that's been announced to be coming to the Wii is called The Blob, which apparently is going to be kind of similar.
[SPEAKER_08]: There was actually a contest that was involved, a student project.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's kind of a cross between Katamari and, I guess, I don't know, you paint buildings with this giant blob of paint.
[SPEAKER_08]: and roll it around and stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it looks kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_08]: Will the game also feature a boy?
[SPEAKER_08]: Uh, no.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it can be a boy in his blob.
[SPEAKER_08]: Get it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I got it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, and then real quick, um, some of the virtual console games coming out here in the next few weeks.
[SPEAKER_08]: At least it's TurboGrafx-16 stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: This ought to make Christopher happy.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, um, let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's got to be Devil's Crush.
[SPEAKER_08]: Devil's Crush.
[SPEAKER_08]: I knew it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Uh, Air Zonk, Drop Off, and Silent...
[SPEAKER_08]: Debuggers.
[SPEAKER_08]: Where the fuck is Splatterhouse?
[SPEAKER_08]: Splatterhouse came out, I thought already.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, shit.
[SPEAKER_08]: I need to go back and get it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's been out for a while.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, Splatterhouse kind of sucked.
[SPEAKER_08]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe I skipped over it.
[SPEAKER_08]: We had this conversation before.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did we?
[SPEAKER_02]: Never mind.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then, of course, if you are pre-ordering your Eternal Sonata at GameStop, you will be receiving one of these wonderful faceplates.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, my God, those things are gorgeous.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wait, what?
[SPEAKER_10]: I want to see, I want to see, I want to see.
[SPEAKER_08]: They are gorgeous.
[SPEAKER_08]: Receive one of five custom faceplates for Eternal Sonata for your 360.
[SPEAKER_08]: I never pre-order games.
[SPEAKER_09]: This might make me do it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do you get to pick which one, though?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I guess you don't know yet, huh?
[SPEAKER_09]: Those are beautiful.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_09]: So now we can go around and get everybody's final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_09]: And we'll start with Rice Princess, who's been oh so quiet tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: But thank you for being here and for your moral support, nonetheless.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, you're welcome.
[SPEAKER_09]: And what's your final thought?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't have anything.
[SPEAKER_10]: Fag your anger.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki, what's your final thought?
[SPEAKER_09]: My final thought is I get a kitty this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: My final thought is now I'm craving In-N-Out Burger after watching Rice Princess stuff one down her face.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I really want an In-N-Out Burger now.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you very much for making me crave that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Totally welcome.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because they're not healthy.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's why I got it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you guys for supporting and tuning into Independent Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: As always, we really appreciate the support.
[SPEAKER_09]: And hey, if you like Orange Ons Radio, tell two of your friends.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because if you tell two friends, then slowly but surely, we take over the entire world.
[SPEAKER_09]: And viva la independent podcasting.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you guys very much.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll see you next week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Jamie should be back and a whole lot more gaming news for you as we ramp up for E3 next weekend here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: See you then.
[SPEAKER_00]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_00]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_00]: For more information on our live and podcast programs, visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com See you next week.