[SPEAKER_00]: Tonight, July 1st, 2007, Soul Calibur IV goes online, the world of Civilization comes to consoles, and are achievements about to get product placements?
[SPEAKER_03]: Hello everybody out there on the internet and welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: We are that podcast dedicated to video games, gaming culture, and the gamer lifestyle.
[SPEAKER_03]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_03]: You might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not joining us tonight, sadly, DarkSakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_03]: She has the night off.
[SPEAKER_03]: As many of you long-time listeners of the show may know, she's been very active in taking up massage therapy.
[SPEAKER_03]: She has a little bit of a conflict with her schooling tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the show must go on.
[SPEAKER_03]: And joining me as always, say hello to Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_03]: How you doing, Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm doing okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just scoffed down a sandwich.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, you had like a large Quiznos.
[SPEAKER_03]: It wasn't like a regular size.
[SPEAKER_02]: Was it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it was a regular size.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was a balancing act with the sandwich, and also it is spicy, so it's like, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Spicy sandwich.
[SPEAKER_02]: Regular size Black Angus steak sandwich.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, there you have it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yum, yum.
[SPEAKER_03]: But not that we endorse any particular commercial products here on this program.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_03]: Good, thanks.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you want to tell Rice Princess how you're doing, head on over to our chat room, chat.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: We do tape live here on Sunday nights at orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Rice Princess will just be helping us get a third perspective tonight.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_03]: But also the chat room is there as always to give us a million more perspectives.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, you're right.
[SPEAKER_03]: As if we actually had a million people in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_01]: That would be the best thing ever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, not in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_03]: Four or five different opinions in the chat.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Over and over.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, anyhow, let's start off tonight's show with a little bit of How Is Your Gaming Week, where we talk about what we've been playing this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, I guess you're going to start us off tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, this week I've been playing some interesting things.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some have actually, you know, people have been questioning why I'm playing them, like the Transformers game, for one.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was playing that on 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's okay, it's kind of like, I like the game like, um, I like Driver 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a poorly put together game, and it has some blatant flaws in it, but it's, it's okay, it's just I play it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like what, the same type of graphical stuff?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, let me put it, put some examples in place here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, when I first started the game, immediately there was a big pileup of cars in the street because they couldn't figure out how to turn the corner correctly.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, that was kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: The other thing is, if you throw anything at anything in the game, you know, pretty much like, you can throw a road cone at a building.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, what happens is, when you hit something with said road cone, shrapnel comes off the building.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, that shrapnel hits another building, and then more shrapnel comes off that building, and sometimes it goes back to the original building.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, you can literally destroy an entire block by just throwing a road cone at something.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so that's kind of fascinating at the same time.
[SPEAKER_03]: First comment of the night, DarkTetsuya in our chatroom says, Loki, testers not doing their job?
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course not.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was definitely a rushed game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is it that testers aren't doing their job, or is it that testing gets their corners cut because the game has a strict deadline of trying to be out in time for the movie?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's probably corners cut.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what I figured.
[SPEAKER_02]: But other stuff that's kind of crappy in the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, the very first boss that I fought in the Autobots campaign killed himself.
[SPEAKER_02]: Suicide man.
[SPEAKER_02]: We were fighting in this, like, I don't even know what it's supposed to be, like a power plant or something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they have all these explosive, like, I guess, I don't know, propane tanks or something all around.
[SPEAKER_02]: And unfortunately, you set off one, the whole place goes up.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: A lot of our chatters are big fans of Transformers, looking forward to the movie, and I understand you actually got to see a little sneak peek of the movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, I got to see the movie last Wednesday.
[SPEAKER_02]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: How was it?
[SPEAKER_02]: They're dying to know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why?
[SPEAKER_02]: What was awesome about it?
[SPEAKER_02]: It was awesome because the action in the movie is just non-stop throughout the thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's very similar to Independence Day, how it jumps back and forth between different character story arcs and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you've got that, plus, you know, in the beginning of the movie, when, like, Scorponok comes out and stuff, fucking spears a guy through the chest and pulls him into the ground.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right there, I was like, fuck yeah, this is gonna be awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, you know, any spoilers?
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, there is a couple spoilers I was gonna mention.
[SPEAKER_02]: These are kind of cameos towards the end of the movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember that rumor going around that there was gonna be an Xbox 360 robot in the movie?
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_02]: There is, briefly, a cameo, because, um, the AllSpark, whatever, causes things to come alive.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: and so one of the things that happens to get set off by this is a 360, so you see this guy carrying it out of, I don't know if it was a GameStop or something, but, you know, it busts out the side, just for, you know, half a second, then there's a Mountain Dew Machine robot, which is funny, shooting cans at people, so...
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a brief little cameos there, but it was an excellent movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Highly recommend it if you like action movies.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you're looking for a deep storyline or something like that, you're not going to find it here, but it was good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, unfortunately we're radio and not television, so you can't really see everything that goes on here in studio, but Rice Princess is making her patented Laura Roslin face.
[SPEAKER_03]: and the Laura Roslyn face is, if you've ever watched Battlestar Galactica, you know, what's the actress's name?
[SPEAKER_03]: Mary McDonald, is that it?
[SPEAKER_01]: I think that's what it is, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, like, you know, the actress, she has this, whenever something negative happens, she has this very distinct look where she kind of scrunches up her nose and her mouth and, like, Irene or Rice Princess has that look down pat.
[SPEAKER_03]: So when she's displeased with something, it's the Laura Roslyn look.
[SPEAKER_03]: So why are you giving this review the Laura Roslyn look?
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, the Xbox...
[SPEAKER_01]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_01]: Come on, Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_02]: They don't even show the 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: All they show is the white premium box and an arm punch out the side.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, and that's it, and the guy drops it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's there for literally one to two seconds.
[SPEAKER_01]: I would drop it, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: I caught it, you know, real briefly, but a lot of people probably won't even notice it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It does not detract from the film whatsoever.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not like, let's call Xbox 360 robot.
[SPEAKER_02]: He will defeat everybody.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's not anything like that at all, so...
[SPEAKER_03]: He will charge you 800 Microsoft points for every projectile that he throws.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a good movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: I liked it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I cannot wait to see it again.
[SPEAKER_03]: I keep forgetting that Rice Princess is really anti-Xbox and Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_03]: Remind me again real quick.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm not super anti-Xbox and Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm not.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't even know much about Microsoft to really hate them.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just
[SPEAKER_01]: Don't prefer them.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're very underwhelming to me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Didn't you tell me it has to do really with the games that they offer, though?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what I'm saying.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm very underwhelmed because they don't have anything to offer to me.
[SPEAKER_01]: Nothing appeals to me on that system.
[SPEAKER_03]: You need to see the Eternal Sonata demo, though, if you haven't yet, because that seems like a Japanese RPG.
[SPEAKER_01]: I have actually seen it, and it does look really pretty, and I would totally play it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe Blue Dragon in the future?
[SPEAKER_03]: She made the Rosalind face like a second.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're getting so good at that.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've been practicing for a long time.
[SPEAKER_01]: But, yeah, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Blue Dragon might be cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_01]: But definitely the other one looked really good.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyhow, let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ross Steel UT seems to agree with you in chat room.
[SPEAKER_03]: Xbox 360 is all first-person shooter.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not all first-person shooter.
[SPEAKER_03]: He also says, listen to Loki blindly defend a shitty unrelated marketing ploy.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is a blatant, but the whole movie has blatant, you know, product placement everywhere.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, come on, a fucking Mountain Dew robot, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Enough movie chat, game chat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry to interrupt your gaming week, but anyways.
[SPEAKER_03]: What else?
[SPEAKER_02]: So, other than that, actually, when Nellie, I bought Nellie the Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix for the Wii, which I might add that has the worst cameras ever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ever in a game is so awful.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know, she likes it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's, you know, Harry Potter.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think she actually finished it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I forgot that was out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you really like cast spells with the Wiimote and everything?
[SPEAKER_02]: Heck yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just the whole game, I mean, it sounds fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: You get to cast spells and stuff, but the whole game is doing tasks for people.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like running around this stupid place and doing, you know, meaningless tasks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, I've lost my stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: People have hidden it somewhere in Hogwarts.
[SPEAKER_02]: Go find it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, thank you for giving me no hints whatsoever, and Hogwarts isn't exactly small, so, you know, it takes a lot of time, and there's also a lot of things where if you forget what you're supposed to be doing, you go back and ask them, they won't give you any hints to what you're supposed to do or something like that, and a lot of the puzzles are hard to figure out what they want you to do.
[SPEAKER_01]: What a bunch of fuckers.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_02]: The combat in the game, using the wand and stuff, is pretty stupid, because Nellie didn't really have a grasp on any sort of strategy, so she's just swinging the wand around, or the remote, I guess, around like crazy, and it won every battle.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, you know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's cool if you love Harry Potter, you'll definitely like the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I would recommend, though, probably don't get it on the Wii, maybe get it on the 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: or the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: So the Wiimote waving for your spells is not all that.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not all that.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just, I think, I'm not sure if the second, if in the normal, like the 360 and the PlayStation 3, if you use the other analog stick as, you know, maybe a camera look or something, but I know in the Wii version, it was hard to even face in the right direction for, you know, certain things.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, you'd be facing at what you want to cast a spell at, pull out your wand and you'd turn around.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just like, you know, it's like, come on.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, what the hell?
[SPEAKER_02]: But it looks cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: The other games I've been playing on the PSP, actually Wipeout Pulse, which is not out over here in the US yet, but it's okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just like Wipeout.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've played a lot of Wipeout Pure before, and it's very similar to that.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks actually almost like a PlayStation 2 game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pretty awesome, so that's going to be coming out in September.
[SPEAKER_02]: The other game I've been playing is Final Fantasy, the remake on the PSP, and that's actually really awesome looking.
[SPEAKER_03]: You showed that to me, and I played it for about 15 seconds, and I'm so fucking sold on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: The game is freaking gorgeous.
[SPEAKER_03]: The screenshots don't do it justice.
[SPEAKER_03]: The game looks so beautiful.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's amazing.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's just amazing.
[SPEAKER_01]: We're actually going to get married, me and the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: You and Final Fantasy are going to get married?
[SPEAKER_01]: We totally are.
[SPEAKER_01]: We've already discussed this.
[SPEAKER_02]: The last game I was playing was a game called Zainide Revolution, I think.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's a sequel to an Xbox shooter game, like one of the shoot-em-ups that came out probably very late in the Xbox lifecycle.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's kind of different.
[SPEAKER_02]: This one now is a 3D shooter.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're kind of going towards the screen, I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: And...
[SPEAKER_02]: It's still, you know, got the shoot-em-up aspect stuff in the game, but it's, you know, after seeing, you know, games that are free, like No Gravity and stuff, I'm sorry that, you know, the background of the whole game is just a full motion video and you can see artifacts and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just not very good when, you know, a free game like No Gravity does everything in real time and it looks amazing for no money.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, I, you know, I'd probably hold off on buying that, but...
[SPEAKER_02]: It's pretty cool, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: Definitely get Final Fantasy and Final Fantasy II when those come out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Awesome games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll go next.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, Rice Princess, why don't you tell us about your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, my quite substantial gaming week that consists of
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: Why are you on this show?
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't really know.
[SPEAKER_01]: To cuss a lot.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: But we're going to be creating a twink guild.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's a twink guild?
[SPEAKER_03]: I know we've had this discussion on a previous show.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not going to go to the porno-related side of this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just tell us straight up.
[SPEAKER_03]: What is this guild all about?
[SPEAKER_01]: The guild's all about PvP.
[SPEAKER_01]: We're going to be doing Morsangulch and Narathi Basin.
[SPEAKER_01]: And we're going to stay at level 29 because it's like, you know, so we can do AB and it's like the first one we can do it at.
[SPEAKER_01]: and Twinks.
[SPEAKER_01]: Everyone knows what Twinks are.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're just the really like super awesome like characters that have all the best gear and all the best enchants and all that stuff and
[SPEAKER_01]: BattleStarGalactica
[SPEAKER_03]: It's Lee Adama.
[SPEAKER_01]: Lee Adama?
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, you nerd!
[SPEAKER_01]: Lee Adama's mine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_01]: You shut up.
[SPEAKER_01]: Mine's going to be Tyrell because he's hot and sexy and nobody likes him except for me.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I'm like, whatever, I'll take his name.
[SPEAKER_01]: Who else do we have in our PvP guild?
[SPEAKER_03]: A lot.
[SPEAKER_03]: Really?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm pretty sure there's a Roslyn.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know if there is a Roslyn.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, one of our guilds said they wanted to be a real bitch, so we said do Admiral Kane.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, oh my god, isn't that the best thing ever?
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_01]: She's my hero.
[SPEAKER_01]: So that's pretty much it on my end of the gaming week.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ross Steel, UTSM Advice, Rice Princess, you might have time to game if you didn't upset over that useless time sink.
[SPEAKER_03]: In other words, stop playing WoW and get out of the games.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, man.
[SPEAKER_01]: That was hilarious.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because you're never going to get away from WoW, huh?
[SPEAKER_03]: Not really, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: She's giving you a Rosalind face.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: My gaming week actually, sadly, was pretty similar.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't play a whole lot outside of WoW, but I have a good reason because I was out of town for three days.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was in L.A.
[SPEAKER_03]: and kind of – I had to do this thing for work where we were kind of – we stayed all together for this team-building thing away from the society, so I couldn't even get out to an arcade or a bar or anything, so –
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: I've been playing Survivor, like the TV show, I've been playing Survivor on LiveJournal Imagine like, you know, because a lot of people play Dungeons & Dragons online So there's Survivor on LiveJournal, so I'm playing that And I wasn't the first voted out, thank God So, there you go So, I was very happy about that
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, you know, I was kind of having, I was dishing out PSP Uncertainty because, like, there wasn't really, again, it was kind of like the Xbox.
[SPEAKER_01]: There was nothing that was really appealing to me except for Luminous, you know, but now I'm seeing all these games and I'm totally going to invest in one.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yep, thought I'd interject that.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, well, let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now that we've gone through our gaming weeks, perhaps we should get into some housekeeping tonight and tell you guys about what's going on with us.
[SPEAKER_03]: We are going to be making an appearance at SAC for Sacramento Anime.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're going to be going to that convention, which is, I believe, two weeks off.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think we're going to be making an appearance on Saturday the 14th.
[SPEAKER_03]: and for those of you that are in the Sacramento area it's at that hotel that's across Martin Fair Mall all the details we will have next week we're still trying to work that out with the folks and I need to make sure even all of us are available or else it's only going to be some of us however
[SPEAKER_03]: We will not be taping one of our live usual shows at this convention as we did for Fanime.
[SPEAKER_03]: We will be recording a special bonus show that only folks on the LiveJournal, the MySpace, our communities will be able to direct download.
[SPEAKER_03]: It will not go into the RSS feed.
[SPEAKER_03]: So if you are interested in keeping tabs on all that type of special stuff that we put out that's extra, check out our LiveJournal community, which is Orange Lounge on LiveJournal, or you can check out our MySpace.
[SPEAKER_03]: Our username is Orange Lounge Media.
[SPEAKER_03]: Orange Lounge Radio on MySpace.
[SPEAKER_03]: You'd think I'd just learned English this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: What the hell is going on?
[SPEAKER_03]: You did.
[SPEAKER_01]: You did.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jeez.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you know, because last week was the five-year anniversary and all.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now this week, we're just set up for disappointment.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's like, who gives a fuck anniversary?
[SPEAKER_03]: How did we top last week?
[SPEAKER_03]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who gives a fuck anymore?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm surprised we're here.
[SPEAKER_01]: When you're at the top, you've got to have to bring it down a notch and gradually go down a bit so that you can bring it back up.
[SPEAKER_03]: For 250, because 250 is a landmark number, so you have to bring it up again for that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Totally right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: Happy Canada Day!
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: We're getting a cat.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not buying an Apple product, ever.
[SPEAKER_02]: An iPhone?
[SPEAKER_02]: I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: One of our friends got an iPhone.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're pretty sexy.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was bringing sexy back.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just knowing Apple, there'll be something even better next year, so I'm going to hold off, and hopefully I'll have money because I'm moving soon.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, also, the countdown is beginning for the last shows in this studio.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're going to be moving to a new room because I'm moving to a new place, and hopefully a bigger studio.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hope so.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, you already named it?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, we didn't name it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a foster cat right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's in a foster home, so we are going to be picking it up on Friday of this next week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jake Simmons says, name it Kitty Bobo, and RawSteelUT says, name it Tingle.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't name it Tingle.
[SPEAKER_02]: It responds to Stella.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see about nicknames.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, I wanted to mention this real quickly.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're going to be hearing this a lot, especially those of you guys that listen to a variety of podcasts.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're really going to get sick of hearing this after this month is over, so we're really only going to say this once, but it is that time of year.
[SPEAKER_03]: The podcast awards are open and nominations have started as of today.
[SPEAKER_03]: And of course, we would be tickled pink if we could get nominated again this year for
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: All we really want to see is the independent podcasts prevail in this.
[SPEAKER_03]: And last year, even though we weren't nominated, we were very happy to see that five independent podcasts were nominated.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's why we want to keep it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because you know what, guys?
[SPEAKER_03]: Those podcasts that are owned by the corporates and the big game companies and the big gaming magazines, they don't need the exposure.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have...
[SPEAKER_03]: Lots of ad dollars that go into their print, their TV.
[SPEAKER_03]: They don't need the exposure.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the independent folks, a podcast award can really help them out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because when we won it in 05, it really did help us out.
[SPEAKER_03]: So please, you know, make sure an independent wins it, guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: If it can't be us, we definitely would like to see another independent win it.
[SPEAKER_03]: So there you have it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Podcast awards.
[SPEAKER_03]: The nominations are open, I think, through the 15th.
[SPEAKER_03]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'm hoping that people will suggest independent podcasts from other categories in our thread on the forums to maybe nominate, because I don't know a lot outside of gaming.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, I know a couple sci-fi and a couple, but not a lot.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'm hoping that we can kind of share and help promote the indie podcasts.
[SPEAKER_01]: That would be cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyhow, let's move on and get into tonight's gaming news.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, not a huge surprise, especially with E3 around the corner.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're getting a lot of announcements of what's going to be coming out at E3, what you can expect to be reading about, because obviously most of you probably aren't going, including us.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck you, people.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways, so one of those, which isn't a big surprise, and I'm surprised we haven't seen more of it yet, Killzone 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sony's invite for, I believe, their press conference and whatnot was, of course, Killzone-themed, and they're probably going to be featuring the game playable or in some sort of trailer.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm guessing playable.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's got to be coming out pretty soon at the event, so...
[SPEAKER_02]: and DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it'll all be on the internet within five seconds anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, you know, we've seen enough of how the gaming industry works on the inside that what's really going to happen is that the game companies will sell the rights to one of those big box gaming companies.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the big box gaming companies will actually post it the day before E3, meaning that all the independent press who actually manages to get into E3 has to run their stories 48 hours late.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the way it's really going to work.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: We're just going to stay at home and steal other people's articles this year because, hey, it's the American way.
[SPEAKER_02]: All I know is when these press conferences will be going on, I will not be doing much work at my desk because that's usually the case.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm usually just hitting refresh, refresh, refresh, refresh, refresh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, news!
[SPEAKER_02]: Read it!
[SPEAKER_03]: Can you watch them live, like last year, or is it because it's not as big a, you know, it's low-key, you can't watch that stuff live?
[SPEAKER_02]: I can, but at the work, you know, a lot of the internet's blocked, so a lot of the, you know, unless they're streaming it straight off their site and not off something else, you know, most likely I can't watch it live.
[SPEAKER_02]: But who cares, you know, if I can read about it, that's all I really care about.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think I've told you this.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll have to tell you a little more, give you details offhand.
[SPEAKER_03]: But one of our other folks that works for Orange Lounge Radio on one of the other weeknight shows actually had some touch with a game company this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that game company said they'd invite us to E3.
[SPEAKER_03]: But now it's, like, too late.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like E3's only ten days away.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm like, great.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now we got a possible invite, and now it's too freaking late.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know, that sucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: But oh well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe next year.
[SPEAKER_03]: Too bad it's on a weekend.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'd drive my ass down there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: Big deal.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean... I sadly can't go to PAX because of a wedding, but I hope somebody from the Orange House Radio staff is able to go up there.
[SPEAKER_03]: E for All I'm definitely going to, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm trying to make it to E for All.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if I'll end up making it out there, but I would like to go, because it'd be nice to see that stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Will Rice Princess be going to any of these big gaming conventions?
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to go to BlizzCon.
[SPEAKER_01]: BlizzCon?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: I can't, though, because all the tickets sold out within, what, fucking four days or something like that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Why does that not surprise me?
[SPEAKER_01]: I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think about four hours.
[SPEAKER_01]: Four hours?
[SPEAKER_01]: Really?
[SPEAKER_02]: It was pretty quick.
[SPEAKER_01]: Days, hours, doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm really sad about that, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'll go next year.
[SPEAKER_03]: GS68 says the SF Bay Area needs a gaming convention, darn it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Damn it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_03]: I agree, except there is a whole Game Developers Conference, which is kind of a big deal.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, if you remember, though, they did try to do something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did they?
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember there was that one convention that was in San Francisco?
[SPEAKER_02]: It was a weekend, and I don't remember what exactly it was.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was, I want to say, it wasn't like sponsored.
[SPEAKER_02]: It might have been sponsored by GameSpot.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was like a GameSpot Expo or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tech TV used to be there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Didn't Zip Davis own GameSpot one time?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, that's one up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hello, no, I'm crazy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ring Game Pro or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was a GameSpot Expo, I want to say, that was in San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was really small.
[SPEAKER_02]: They only had maybe 15 publishers out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: But from what I remember reading, there wasn't that much response to it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was pretty crappy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Besides, we're being totally selfish because obviously the SF Bay Area is pretty much in our backyard.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's about two hours away, so it's totally drivable.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I'm sure everybody's like, I wish they'd have a gaming convention in my part of town.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the good news is, you know, usually there's at least something small-ish in any type of town.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, even if it's like an anime slash game convention, which you see a lot of those everywhere.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would rather, you know, go to Gamers Days over, you know, the...
[SPEAKER_02]: Giant E3s any day.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, at least you get more one-on-one time with games.
[SPEAKER_02]: I kind of agree.
[SPEAKER_02]: I liked the first Konami Gamers Day that we went to.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was pretty low-key, and we got to play pretty much everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: The last one, though, not so much because of too much press, and the place was kind of smaller, and it seemed like, you know, well, we got to get the shot for our TV show, you know, get out of the way type shit, and everyone's kind of there to do jobs instead of report stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, anyhow, obviously one big announcement that came out of... Oh, actually, I want to read a chat comment here.
[SPEAKER_03]: GS191 is correcting me here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, actually, CNET is actually owned by Ziff Davis, so GameSpot by proxy is.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't realize that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh!
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, I keep reading chat and I see new stuff pop up.
[SPEAKER_03]: There was a big convention this weekend that might be a little bit near and dear to our hearts, and the folks have been listening to us from the beginning.
[SPEAKER_03]: Beaumonti Fest was this weekend on the East Coast, which is, of course, this big Beaumonti and Beatmania and DDR convention that's on the East Coast that they have at a bowling alley, hence the term Beaumonti, which is cute.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they actually get, usually, some folks that are actually in the games to come out there and perform, so that's cute.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wish I was at the East Coast a couple weeks later than I was.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe I could have gone.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyhow, big conventions.
[SPEAKER_03]: Last year, one of the big things we saw at E3 was Final Fantasy XIII.
[SPEAKER_03]: And of course, everybody wants to know, when?
[SPEAKER_03]: When will we get this game?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, Square Enix has actually said that they will be doing no games for the PlayStation 3 until after April 1st of 2008.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why then?
[SPEAKER_03]: because that's the new fiscal year.
[SPEAKER_03]: There will be no games from Square Enix for the PlayStation 3 this fiscal year.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not a big surprise as far as Final Fantasy XIII is regarded.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think most of us here in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_03]: were thinking we'd be lucky to see it at the end of 2008 with all the translation and stuff that has to go on.
[SPEAKER_03]: But there it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, that's really sad, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, when you think about it, because, you know, Sony really needs some strong titles to come out in order to be able to push this PlayStation 3, you know, to the level that the 360 and the Wii are right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: And people were kind of hoping for Final Fantasy XIII or Metal Gear Solid 4, and both of those now are, you know, after March of next year.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, oh, missed another Christmas.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's not good.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, that's going to really put them behind.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think they're going to be able to catch up.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, they're going to need...
[SPEAKER_02]: It's gonna have to be one of those, you know, fucking one in a million shots that's gonna...
[SPEAKER_02]: So what's Sony going to push this Christmas?
[SPEAKER_02]: LittleBigPlanet, Home?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, Home, LittleBigPlanet, I get their first party stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Killzone's not going to be out this year.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's no way.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yes, that's true.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, you're probably looking at second quarter of next year, but I would say this year probably Heavenly Sword, I mean, because that's pretty much God of War on the PlayStation 3 anyways.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lair is going to be good, and probably some unannounced stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ratchet & Clank, the new Ratchet & Clank, it looks awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, same people did Resistance, and that game was sweet, so...
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be hard for them.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ranma says, we'll see Final Fantasy XIII before Duke Nukem Forever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Very true.
[SPEAKER_03]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't wait for the day when Duke Nukem Forever is actually going to come out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Frisbee calls it Final Fantasy Sporever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Get it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because spore.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just been delayed a year or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: These are all games that people cannot freaking wait for.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, Spore that we've seen playable in some form, and you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just a very large game, and they have to make sure that it's going to be everything that they want it to be before they release it.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's just like Fable 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just like Fable 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fable 2 is probably going to be delayed forever because they want to make sure that it's perfect.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd rather them be perfect than, you know,
[SPEAKER_02]: Have another Transformers game come out, or Spider-Man 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: One thing that's definitely not been perfect is the brand new firmwares for the PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not one firmware so far released has been able to be not hacked, and such is the case with 3.5.
[SPEAKER_02]: In fact, last week they found a new kind of workaround called the Illuminati version,
[SPEAKER_02]: and basically uses the old Luminous to run homebrew code.
[SPEAKER_02]: And of course, immediately after that came out, there is now a 3.5 downgrader.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you can downgrade your PSPs to be able to run either 1.5, so you can run homebrew that way, or to be able to run custom firmers, which, you know, custom firmers are the way to go, I think.
[SPEAKER_02]: Other interesting things, though, because of the Illuminati exploit,
[SPEAKER_02]: The Luminous sales have skyrocketed about 14,000%.
[SPEAKER_02]: So a lot of people are picking up Luminous, which, you know, it's a great game anyways, but...
[SPEAKER_02]: It might be a little hard to find it if you don't have it already.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, most people were ignoring Luminous 1 because Luminous 2 was out now, and I doubt Q Entertainment's making a lot of those.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who published that one, actually?
[SPEAKER_03]: Was it Q?
[SPEAKER_03]: Or was it Sony actually published it?
[SPEAKER_03]: It was Q, but I think Ubisoft published it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ah, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: But Ubisoft has been making a lot of copies of that probably because of Luminous 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think it's available anymore.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think so either, but people are trying to scrounge them up now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also on Sony platforms, much anticipated, Guitar Hero rocks the 80s And they've done a brilliant job over at Activision of keeping this game in the press every week Before it's released, because they'll give you a few more songs this week A few more songs, a few more songs Well finally we know the whole dang song list Because we've got some more songs this week, and that's it We've got the whole song list Caught in a Mosh by Anthrax is in the game I'm only going to read the songs I care about
[SPEAKER_03]: Police Truck by the Dead Kennedys We Got the Beat by the Go-Go's and I love this one.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think I'm turning Japanese by the Vapors.
[SPEAKER_03]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's going to be a great guitar song.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why are you making Rosalind face, Rice Princess?
[SPEAKER_01]: Because the song list sucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: You don't like the song list?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't like it at all.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's some other stuff though that was already announced.
[SPEAKER_03]: I read the whole song list.
[SPEAKER_03]: You read the whole thing?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_03]: They could have done a little better.
[SPEAKER_03]: What were you hoping for?
[SPEAKER_01]: For like better 80s music that wasn't all just like hair bands and just like
[SPEAKER_01]: Pauly Abdul
[SPEAKER_03]: Ranma says Guitar Hero needs Weird Al.
[SPEAKER_03]: Frisbee says Elite Beat Agents was going to have Weird Al.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, that was also a song list that turned out to be fake.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know if that was ever actually going to be in the band, I think, or in the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think somebody just kind of pulled that out of their butt.
[SPEAKER_03]: Money for Nothing would be fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_03]: That'd be cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Drew Nami says give us Bohemian Rhapsody.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that was 70s, though, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it'd be too long.
[SPEAKER_02]: 79 or 78.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, there you have it, Guitar Hero 80s Edition.
[SPEAKER_03]: Those of you guys that do like the hair bands, I'm sure you're very excited about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways, since E3 is right around the corner, not too surprising, we're starting to get leaked lists from E3.
[SPEAKER_02]: This, of course, should be interest to everybody.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Konami E3 list was leaked out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Looks like coming from a tip to Xbox Live Radio or XBL Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who is another affiliate on allgames.com, just like us.
[SPEAKER_02]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some stuff, of course, not too surprising.
[SPEAKER_02]: DDR Supernova 2 for PlayStation 2, Universe 2 for the 360, Karaoke Revolution American Idol 2 for the PlayStation 2, a game called DDR Disney Challenge for the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see here what else we got.
[SPEAKER_02]: DDR Disney Challenge?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I thought I read a report somewhere else.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was following that said something Disney Channel.
[SPEAKER_02]: It probably is Disney Channel or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: Disney Challenge sounds kind of weird unless it's like all hard stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's this weird game called Girl's Secret Diary for the DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: Record your secrets and dreams in your journal.
[SPEAKER_01]: I can't wait.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is that a game that will finally tear you away from WoW?
[SPEAKER_03]: Girl's Secret Diary?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah!
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know why, but that game starts to sound like Ping Pals to me and I get very worried because Ping Pals is shittacious.
[SPEAKER_02]: It should have Girl's Secret Diary RPG or something.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think you're just bitter because it's Girl's Secret Diary and that means you can't use it, Rob.
[SPEAKER_01]: And you're like, oh fine, it just sounds like Ping Pals anyway.
[SPEAKER_01]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_01]: You shut up.
[SPEAKER_01]: Shut your face up.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, I'm totally not going to get that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know, I'm sure we'll find out more.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's being Avery's, like, what, just over a week away.
[SPEAKER_02]: Come on, folks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it's around the corner that the PlayStation 2 is going to kind of have their year or two of being the budget system, you know, because it's so cheap and most of the games are probably going to fall to $19.99, $29.99.
[SPEAKER_03]: So like a Disney game on PlayStation 2 kind of makes a lot of sense to me because, you know, who's going to have the PlayStation 2 now is the young kids that, you know, mommy and daddy are buying systems for.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a perfect title for a $29.99 price point.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, well, even though we might be seeing DDR on the PlayStation 2 soon, the PlayStation 3 is going to be getting another long-time series coming to it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wipeout Pulse is going to be coming out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sony Computer Entertainment of Europe has been showing this off for the past few weeks over there in London.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, Wipeout Pulse is going to be a high-def version of Wipeout, and it's going to be released in 2008, but hopefully we're going to get to see some hints at the game at E3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whoopity-doo!
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, okay, it's high def.
[SPEAKER_02]: The whole thing was pretty much cel-shaded anyways.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's not like that, you know, upping the textures are going to make it any better or anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: But hey, cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I'm sure they'll use the six axis and all that fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: As long as we get some great raving soundtracks like all the other games, that'll be great.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, Pulse's soundtrack is actually pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now some other interesting stuff coming from the Sony camp.
[SPEAKER_02]: This one though in India, and unfortunately we're not going to see an advertising campaign like this over here, but oh my god, I wish it was.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently they have a new advertising campaign that is a little bit chauvinistic, I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let me just really quickly read the entire ad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sherry is such a bitch.
[SPEAKER_02]: Last night I saw her with this weird guy whom I think she's seen.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, she created such a scene.
[SPEAKER_02]: When she broke up with Josie, bloody attention seeker, it's not been a week and she's already sleeping around.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think Nicole is two-timing Ron again.
[SPEAKER_02]: And in the very bottom it says, PlayStation 2, because your girlfriend bores you shitless.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ha ha ha!
[SPEAKER_02]: That's funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why don't they do that here?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's really funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: People would be pissed off and get offended and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are you offended as a woman?
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm offended it's not being advertised here because that's like one of the best advertisements ever because it's so true.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't give a shit While his girlfriend's like So that was kind of funny
[SPEAKER_03]: Ross Steel, UT in chat says, and then we wonder why women don't play video games.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, that's the only reason why, because gaming companies make offensive advertisements.
[SPEAKER_03]: Most women I know would see the offensive advertisement and then go, well, if they're going to be like that, then I'm going to play lots of video games.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll show them.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't have to be boring.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, it could be like, you know... Then they'll realize how terrible they are at video games and then they'll stop.
[SPEAKER_02]: PlayStation 2, if your boyfriend can't satisfy you, Rez will.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh man, that's so true.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a great ad campaign as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't wait to see the ad campaigns for Soul Calibur 4.
[SPEAKER_03]: Especially, you know, being that Ivy's... Now with more jubblies!
[SPEAKER_03]: Ivy's slut-tacious boobs are being shown off in the trailer there.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's massive side boob in those pictures.
[SPEAKER_03]: There is massive side boob in those pictures.
[SPEAKER_03]: And a massive bombshell drop this week in regards to Soul Calibur 4.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, the game is coming out next year on the PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: and, you know, Tekken is online now.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, hello, Namco, is Soul Calibur 4 going to be online?
[SPEAKER_03]: And the answer is yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that quote comes from Namco.
[SPEAKER_03]: It says, quote, With the current environment, we really couldn't make Soul Calibur 4 without online play.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's from the director, Katsutoshi Sasaki, who makes Soul Calibur 4.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's exciting, because I know a lot of folks like to play their online games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hopefully there is not some crappy lag.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would be bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because crappy lag always ruins those online fighting games.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I actually remember reading some other unrelated story this week that talked about a lag-free system for fighting games that have been developed that's supposed to eliminate practically all the lag that you see in fighting games.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know how well it works, but maybe Soul Calibur 4 will be able to implement some of this technology.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's a myth.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kind of like those cars that run on air or something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: The magical cars that zero emissions and fuel would be plentiful.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's all a myth.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways...
[SPEAKER_02]: What's interesting, though, this announcement just came out recently.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently, the Bourne conspiracy is going to be coming to Xbox 360 and PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, it is based on the Jason Bourne character from the book series, and not necessarily from the movie series, even though the Bourne... Oh, so Matt Damon?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, Matt Damon.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, um...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: We're getting some feedback on the last story because sometimes there's a little bit of lag here between chat and what we're taping live.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, chat.orangehauntsradio.com Toshin is in chat and says, this is not a myth, the whole lag-free fighting thing we're talking about.
[SPEAKER_03]: He says, my friend made it.
[SPEAKER_03]: FYI, ggpo.net.
[SPEAKER_03]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess we'll see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see how well it's implemented.
[SPEAKER_03]: I haven't seen any videos of it in action yet or gotten to use it myself, but the prospects of it sound very exciting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't get me wrong.
[SPEAKER_03]: Moving on to another title that's having another version coming out.
[SPEAKER_03]: TimeSplitters 4 is coming out on the Xbox 360 and the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: TimeSplitters kind of seems to... It's not a game you hear about a lot, but a lot of folks that have played this game seem to really enjoy it.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're a TimeSplitters fan, aren't you, Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: I love TimeSplitters.
[SPEAKER_02]: I cannot wait for this.
[SPEAKER_02]: TimeSplitters is probably hands down one of the best first-person shooter games out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Especially TimeSplitters 2, which is...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: The forum post that originally tipped people off to this also says about the article, there's no actual news on the features other than Steve Ellis says, quote, they're gearing up to insert monkeys and guns into all the wrong places.
[SPEAKER_03]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that game had lots of monkeys.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll make Loki very happy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some other interesting stuff, you know, a lot of people have been, of course, overclocking their PSPs with...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: The first game that's going to be doing this, though, is God of War Chains of Olympus, and it's going to be running at the full speed on there, because obviously the game's going to be quite graphically intensive.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting to see that they're actually finally kind of saying, fuck battery life, we're just going to use the full speed of this system.
[SPEAKER_03]: So why is it that folks don't want to use the full speed of the system normally?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't understand the way that works.
[SPEAKER_02]: Originally, it's because it cut down on battery life, and so they couldn't advertise that the battery lasts X amount of time.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, originally, they could run it at the full speed.
[SPEAKER_02]: In fact, you can overclock yours to run at 333 megahertz instead of 222.
[SPEAKER_02]: In fact, that's what we do for playing Grand Theft Auto, so it's smoother, less load time.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just their choice, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: They don't want to do it.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, our chat room, of course, we're a little bit behind, apparently, because they're still reacting to the last story.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they're talking about the racing cats.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Actdeft says, we don't want monkeys.
[SPEAKER_03]: We want laser cats.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because remember, we talked about laser cats, the game, and how somebody badly needs to make that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Go ahead.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was going to say, and then the chat room says that they actually want rap cats.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kill me now.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, they're going to either have a way to dump games to the memory stick, or you're going to have a new download service where you're going to be able to download games to run straight off the memory stick.
[SPEAKER_02]: Even though they kind of do that with demos right now, but it is an official ISO loader, which apparently is going to be included in the next homebrew firmware that's going to be made.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mmm, the plot thickens.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, anyhow, let's open up the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_03]: Even though DarkSakura isn't here this week, we're going to sneak behind her back and open up the email bag because we can't wait.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're like kids on Christmas Eve.
[SPEAKER_03]: We can't wait to open up our presents.
[SPEAKER_03]: And when you guys send us emails every week at mailbag at orangeontradio.com, they are like little presents.
[SPEAKER_03]: So let's open up the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, not a whole lot of emails this week, I think because a lot of folks actually got to call into the show last week and kind of say their piece.
[SPEAKER_03]: However, we do have some emails.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to start with this.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is from DarkMutz.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey guys and gal, I have been listening to you for about six months and I found your podcast to be the only one that is consistent and always entertaining.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have to thank Loki because without his clever insight about what makes a game fun, I never would have found Earth Defense Force 2017.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have been addicted since I acquired it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Congrats on five years and keep it coming.
[SPEAKER_03]: The three of you keep me going through my work day without having to light anyone on fire.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks again, DarkMuds.
[SPEAKER_03]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Isn't that a weird feeling when somebody says, like... You know, because video games aren't cheap.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, like, somebody says, like, based on your word, I spent $50 of my hard-earned money for my day job that drives me insane to buy this game.
[SPEAKER_03]: At least it's only a $40 game, so that doesn't, you know... But still!
[SPEAKER_02]: But still.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: So what makes a game fun for you, Loki?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just... It's gotta be fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, you know, we're at the Fence Force.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's one of those games I'm still playing.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's because...
[SPEAKER_02]: TimeSplitters 2 TimeSplitters 3
[SPEAKER_02]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, D3's awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've been playing, was it, Work Time Fun right now, and that game is so stupid and awful, but I can't stop playing it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jvmon says, Loki is the king of OLR, and Rob is his puppet.
[SPEAKER_03]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: RossDLUT, who I've been quoting a lot tonight, I guess I like the cynics tonight, because RossDLUT's kind of our in-house cynic, says, Loki, very fucking insightful.
[SPEAKER_03]: What makes a game fun?
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, the game's fun?
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: I like blowing stuff up.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like writing boobs in places I shouldn't be able to and naming things.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, everybody finds something different to be fun, usually, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: It doesn't matter what I find fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's whatever you find fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you don't want to trust my judgment with buying a game, you can always go rent it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, and that's a lot cheaper, and I'm sure a lot of the mom and pop shops out there would really appreciate that from you.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkTetsuya says, Tonight's OLR has been brought to you by D3 and by GameTap.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, I...
[SPEAKER_03]: I neglected to say I played GameTap during my gaming week because I just needed to leave it out for once, alright?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I knew there was going to be that fucking comment at some point.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not on D3 payroll, that's for sure, but at least they have the balls to bring over games that might not necessarily work over here, like Earth Defense Force, and they have that one that's coming out at one point.
[SPEAKER_02]: on the 360 where you're like some chick in lingerie with a cowboy hat fighting zombies with a samurai sword.
[SPEAKER_02]: That might not necessarily do well over here, but at least they're going to give it a shot.
[SPEAKER_02]: What the fuck are you talking about?
[SPEAKER_02]: That sounds awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's the name of the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't remember what it's called.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's got some long Japanese name and I'm not even going to attempt to remember what it was.
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh, let's see, um, Actdeft says, uh, Pac-Man Championship Edition is fun, yet Loki doesn't see that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, because everybody, I think Pac-Man Championship Edition is a hell of a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's way more fast-paced than the old one, which I think is awesome, and, you know, the Ray-Ban music and everything, but Loki, I'm just not a fan of Pac-Man that much.
[SPEAKER_03]: But see, I love the retro, like, really, really retro classics and updates and that stuff, you know, like the old school arcade games.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just like I'm playing Zelda 2 now for some reason, and I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_02]: Zelda 2?
[SPEAKER_01]: Because it's a good game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like a great game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's great.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think I need to buy that on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: You totally do.
[SPEAKER_03]: What else was I going to say?
[SPEAKER_03]: Any other fun factor games that people are overlooking right now?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think about Katamari Damacy.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, what sold that game?
[SPEAKER_03]: The fun factor and the fact that it was a low price.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the game itself was, you know, it wasn't exactly graphically the most impressive.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was just like, you know, you would ask people, what draws you to Katamari Damacy?
[SPEAKER_03]: And people just go, it's fucking fun to roll over shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then, of course, you have your cynics.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's one everybody should say, that game sucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know they're welcome to that opinion.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would recommend it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, and this would be pretty hard to find nowadays, but if you can, find it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I don't recommend buying it, but if you can rent it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Driver 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, I know, it's such a horrible game.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's really a game that you need to play because you're just like, oh my god, I can't believe it's really this bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's entertaining in that aspect.
[SPEAKER_02]: My sister is borrowing my PlayStation 2 and we have that game dumped on the hard drive so she can play it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I swear to god, she plays this thing more than anything else.
[SPEAKER_02]: on that damn system.
[SPEAKER_02]: They will sit there for hours recording instant replays and watching the AI get all fucked up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Driver 3 is the showgirls of gaming.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's so bad, it's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just, you know, there's a lot of games out there that are really hard to, a lot of people overlook that are fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: You just really have to play a lot of the stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Saints Row is another one that I love.
[SPEAKER_01]: New email.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh man, Saints Row, the musical.
[SPEAKER_01]: That was so funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: Only three emails tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here's the second one.
[SPEAKER_03]: And this is from The Doctor.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: urge her to leave her friend code in our forums because we actually have a forum post for Pokemon friend codes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Moving on back to the doctor's email.
[SPEAKER_03]: Second is for Sky.
[SPEAKER_03]: I heart you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: And could you say, excuse me, DarkSakura, again, please, please, please.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll see what I can do.
[SPEAKER_03]: Third is for Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: Really, they can be as hard as you want to make them, I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was, oh my god, and I don't remember the guy.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's this one Japanese guy that had a website with edits on there, and they were the fucking shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't remember who the guy is now because I haven't been playing edits for a long time, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you look for some DDR edit websites, this guy is just amazing.
[SPEAKER_02]: And he had a bunch of ASCII artists on his site, so.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, I wish I could be more helpful there, but some great stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: They had one for, it was called Swingman, that was on... I remember that.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was on the jazz, and it was an awesome edit.
[SPEAKER_02]: It had just this real flow to it that was really cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: One last question from the doctor.
[SPEAKER_03]: When did Squaresoft become Square Enix, and why?
[SPEAKER_03]: Or as we call them here on the show, Squeenix.
[SPEAKER_03]: When did Square Enix become... Why?
[SPEAKER_03]: It was, what, about three years ago?
[SPEAKER_03]: Two or three years ago.
[SPEAKER_03]: They bought Enix, which made a bunch of games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dragon Quest is probably their most popular series of games, which you may know as Dragon Warrior.
[SPEAKER_03]: Years ago, it was called.
[SPEAKER_03]: And what else did they make?
[SPEAKER_03]: I know on Super Nintendo, they were very popular for Brain Lord and Illusion of Gaia and those games.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then later on, I also know for music game fans, they were the folks that made Bust a Move.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did they do the Tobol series?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, excuse me, Dark Sakura!
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm so gonna get beat up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Love you, Jamie, wherever you are.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyhow, one more email.
[SPEAKER_03]: And this one wasn't signed, so I don't really know who to say who this is from.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't even know if I want to read the name.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ikuma is in the header, so we'll just say it's from them.
[SPEAKER_03]: It says, Hi there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've been listening for one and a half year, and just want to take this opportunity to wish you guys happy 5th.
[SPEAKER_03]: I am a developer in Japan, and yes, Rob had once mentioned our game in the new release section.
[SPEAKER_03]: We all just love it when Rob reads in Japanese.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then there's a cute little face there.
[SPEAKER_03]: And who says no love from developer?
[SPEAKER_03]: Ha ha ha.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hope you guy would be part of my Friday for another five years to come.
[SPEAKER_03]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, unfortunately, this person didn't say who they are, what developer they're talking about, or any of that stuff, just that I have horribly butchered the name of one of their games on the program in the past.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's love, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you so much for the email.
[SPEAKER_03]: Gee, tell us who you are, because we'd love to have more developers on the show, especially ones that are, you know, crazy enough to listen to this.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'd also love to be invited to Tokyo Game Show.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkTitsuya asks, was it the developer of Dust Cap Extreme 2 Collector's Edition?
[SPEAKER_03]: Probably one of your, like, hamster love games or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: God, I hope so.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_03]: Please tell me you guys develop one of those, like, hamster games.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's another one of those hamster games coming out over here.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a couple hamster games coming out over here.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think Hamster Life 2 is coming out over here now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Those Ubisoft games.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was the last email.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to close up the old mailbag.
[SPEAKER_03]: How it comes to the Wii, because I would totally buy that game.
[SPEAKER_03]: God, that made me so happy when I read that email.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was like, oh, good.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're not getting all pissed off that I'm butchering their...
[SPEAKER_03]: Their releases.
[SPEAKER_02]: Funny American.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Back to the gaming news.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you want to email us, mailbag at orangelauncher.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you're from an American, Canadian, Antarctican developer, who cares?
[SPEAKER_03]: Email us and tell us you're listening because we love to hear that folks in the industry are listening.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dude, totally need to meet up at the arcade in Antarctica to play some DDR.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shut up and get to the next story.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways, Civilizations coming to consoles and...
[SPEAKER_02]: Handheld soon, being brought over by 2K Games and developed by FireAxis Games, Civilization Revolution.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's going to include 16 civilizations to master and lead to victory.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, of course, famous historical leaders, yada, yada, yada.
[SPEAKER_02]: Online multiplayer as well is going to be in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not a huge Civilization fan, but it sounds interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: and Stab Myself with the blunt end gauge.
[SPEAKER_03]: But these are what, spin-off games?
[SPEAKER_03]: Or are these direct ports?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think this is a spin-off series.
[SPEAKER_03]: When I read it, it sounded like a spin-off series, which can go who knows any which way.
[SPEAKER_03]: That could, you know, God, then that makes me worry, is this going to turn out like the Mortal Kombat anthology stories?
[SPEAKER_03]: Remember like the Sub-Zero game?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think it's anything like that, but I hope not.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, it's probably going to be maybe a little bit more scaled down for consoles.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It sounds okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, do you really need to scale down for consoles?
[SPEAKER_03]: I just could not see the full game itself on an Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the biggest reason why is that there's no mouse, and those thumbsticks don't cut it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, some games were meant to be played with a mouse, and that's all there is to it.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I don't understand why they just don't have keyboard and mouse support, since it has fucking USB ports.
[SPEAKER_02]: In fact, all of the quote-unquote next-gen, you know,
[SPEAKER_02]: platforms have USB ports that can put a keyboard and mouse on there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Except for maybe the Wii, that'd be kind of stupid because you have the Wii remote, but, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Still, though, if you really want to, and if they really would decide to support it, they could put a keyboard and mouse on there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, well, another very popular PC gaming series is Guild Wars, and IGN had an interview this week on their PC side about Guild Wars 2 and the Eye of the North expansion for Guild Wars.
[SPEAKER_03]: You played Guild Wars for a little bit, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: I totally did.
[SPEAKER_03]: And what'd you think?
[SPEAKER_01]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, maybe there's something in the Eye of the North for you, because Eye of the North, I was kind of reading through the interview here, and if you want to read the full thing, head over to pc.ign.com and you can read the full thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: What I didn't know, because I didn't know a lot about these games before I was reading the interview, and Eye of the North is actually the first Guild Wars expansion that requires one of the other expansions to play.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the reason for that is that all of the content they've put into this, they put 18 new dungeons, and they're all for, like, endgame characters.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, whereas with any of the other expansions, you can buy them by themselves and create a character from the ground up.
[SPEAKER_03]: But for this one, they didn't waste any time making a level 1 through 20 story.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's all like hardcore endgame content, which I think is kind of interesting about that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Totally.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then it kind of went to talking about how they're actually developing the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did they actually split into two different development teams?
[SPEAKER_03]: And yes, there's a development team for Guild Wars 2 right now, but then the Eyes of the North people will come over when Guild Wars 2 is done.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they admit that most of the resources are being focused on the Guild Wars expansion, but then they're going to all shift over to Guild Wars 2 once the expansion is done.
[SPEAKER_03]: So this definitely sounds like it's going to be the last Guild Wars expansion.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they actually say that they do kind of tend to monitor the trends in the PvP, like, metagames that people come up with.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then they kind of, like, figure out, use those ideas for, like, live events and holiday events.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they claim them for themselves.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're like, that was my idea!
[SPEAKER_02]: Wait a minute!
[SPEAKER_03]: No, they just sound like they're really tied down to the community, which I think is great.
[SPEAKER_03]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some exciting news for Guild Wars fans.
[SPEAKER_03]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways, so we've got some interesting stuff, I guess, making its way out to the U.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not a whole lot, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: This week's kind of dead, as most of July usually is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pretty much this week, though, the only things you've got are Ninja Gaiden Sigma for PlayStation 3 and Vampire Reign on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: PC games, there's a bunch of weird stuff coming out, including, let's see, well, actually, Marvel treating card games coming out on PC.
[SPEAKER_02]: Title Legends 2 is coming out on PC.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ride, Carnival Tycoon.
[SPEAKER_02]: I swear to God, every fucking week there's a goddamn tycoon game coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: DS, Platinum Sudoku, and Vegas Casino High Five.
[SPEAKER_02]: Making its way out.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that is it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, let's head on over to the Japanese release dates and check out what's going on in Japan.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is Chicken Shoot coming out this week?
[SPEAKER_03]: Chicken Shoot came out last week, though.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh my god, did it really?
[SPEAKER_01]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh my god, Chicken Shoot's great.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, because it was on the list over here, but as a US release, so...
[SPEAKER_03]: Boku no Natsusiasa Boku no Natsuyasumi
[SPEAKER_03]: Boku no Natsu Yasumi 3 is coming out.
[SPEAKER_03]: See, the more I practice, the better I get.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a bug-catching game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why don't we get anything like that over here?
[SPEAKER_03]: Doesn't that look cute?
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe that's what Africa is going to actually be all about.
[SPEAKER_03]: Africa.
[SPEAKER_03]: Poaching animals?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, you poach animals.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would be fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm assuming that because I see the little guy on the cover of the game is holding a little bug net and a little thing that you keep bugs in.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see if there's anything else coming out on some of the other platforms that you might be looking forward to.
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's really crazy kid with bug net murders family.
[SPEAKER_03]: PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some stuff really just moving into the best hits like Winning Post 7, Ape Escape 3, and Ratchet & Clank 4th is all moving into the best.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not a lot of new stuff coming out otherwise, but some price reductions there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Cururin Donuts, Okashi Recipe
[SPEAKER_03]: I have no idea what that is, but it's got a happy donut on the cover and it's an action game.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it kind of makes it look like it might be a racing game involving donuts.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have no fucking idea.
[SPEAKER_01]: Happy donut action game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, but who wouldn't want to buy a happy donut action game?
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'd buy a happy donut action game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Poochie Poochie Virus.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sounds fascinating and is also coming out on the DS.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's also another action game.
[SPEAKER_03]: with a cast of very chibi-looking characters there, also coming to Japan.
[SPEAKER_03]: Quickly looking to see if there's anything on the PSP this week in Japan.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just some games going into the best hits, including Rengoku 2, The Stairway to Heaven.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or Hell, depending on how you look at it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, going over to the European release dates.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, sadly not here this week, but on July 6th,
[SPEAKER_03]: Those of you over in Europe can look forward to The King of Fighters Maximum Impact 2 and The King of Fighters 11 on the PlayStation 2 as well as the Metal Slug Anthology coming out on the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's really it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a very slow week for those of you guys in Europe.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, that does it for release dates.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, um...
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, it may be a little too soon, but the VTech report covering what happened with the shootings at Virginia Tech, apparently there's no mention of the video game issue, despite the fact that everybody was saying, hey, video games made him kill people, da-da-da-da-da.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: But apparently the PAC, though, they've denounced the report saying that it's a cover-up
[SPEAKER_02]: and they're claiming, you know, that really it was video games to blame and it's this giant cover-up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, shut up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shut the hell up, people.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why do people want to blame video games for everything?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just, you know, people want to focus on whatever their agenda is and if they really have, you know,
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Chat room, chat.orangehauntradio.com, live on Sunday nights.
[SPEAKER_03]: Solid Goomba says, didn't they search his room and not even find a single console?
[SPEAKER_03]: I seem to remember that to be the case.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly, just because he participates in a goddamn extracurricular activity, which includes playing a computer game, oh my god, oh my god, you know, that doesn't mean that he's trained on that computer game to be a killer.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm sorry, but there is no way on the face of the earth to train on a PC game to become a killer.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think for some sad whatever reason, people have the need to blame something.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, and obviously what happened at Virginia Tech was just absolutely tremendously horrible, and a lot of us had that reaction of, how could something like this happen?
[SPEAKER_03]: How fucked up is this world that some kid would do this to their peers?
[SPEAKER_03]: And so I think out of that desperation, people look for something to blame, and video games, unfortunately, are an easy target.
[SPEAKER_03]: because, you know, they allow you to pretend that you are someone else and unfortunately not everybody can see that line.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't even know why this was an issue when they didn't even have any sort of evidence in the beginning that, you know, video games were even involved in any way.
[SPEAKER_02]: But immediately they're saying, oh, it must be this.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's Doom, it's Marilyn Manson, it's MTV, it's all this that did this.
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just take responsibility, people.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was, uh...
[SPEAKER_03]: A crazy, crazy, crazy person that probably, I don't know, I don't even want to speculate because I'll say something that will be foot and mouth syndrome.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, you know, it was a very unfortunate thing, period.
[SPEAKER_02]: I blame World War II.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what I blame.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's all those, you know, World War II documentaries out there that show the kamikazes.
[SPEAKER_02]: I blame the Atari 2600, don't you?
[SPEAKER_02]: I do.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, they have the man bomber after all in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: So I don't know if it's going to actually support ROMs or if you're going to buy games a la iTunes or what the deal is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because it's really easy to get free Atari games online at this point.
[SPEAKER_02]: I swear to God, the entire collection of Atari games, everything ever made, is six megs.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you could easily fit that on a USB card.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's very tiny.
[SPEAKER_03]: But what I would like to see that used for is maybe some homebrew.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because, you know, even the Atari 2600 still has some homebrew love.
[SPEAKER_03]: A lot of homebrew love for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you never know what might happen.
[SPEAKER_03]: So.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know if I would necessarily buy this though, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: It depends.
[SPEAKER_03]: If it was like 20 bucks or something, it might be worth it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Games were so simple back then, and sometimes that's kind of like, you know, like I was saying last week, I found myself playing Pitfall for God knows what reason for quite a chunk of time on last Saturday.
[SPEAKER_02]: Can you imagine, if you will, if they were to bring combat to Xbox Live Arcade?
[SPEAKER_02]: and have like leaderboards for that shit, that'd be fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Weren't they going to bring some old Atari classics?
[SPEAKER_03]: Like I seem to remember Warlords was coming to Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's an old school Atari game.
[SPEAKER_03]: And of course we have Centipede and Millipede.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want combat with no graphical upgrades whatsoever.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just want the whole thing to be done like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: What if they did the classic graphics slash upgrade graphics?
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess if they really want to do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I'd be fine with just the classic graphics because I think that'd be funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: And just have like a leaderboard thing where you know...
[SPEAKER_03]: So I did not realize you were such an Atari 2600 fan.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I used to play the Atari 2600 all the time.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm a huge Combat fan.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, keep that in mind for later on.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're going to see what happens later on.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to tease something coming up in Part B. That's all I have to say.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways, so...
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently, the ESRB is cracking down on violent game trailers now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nothing really new, but of course, especially after the whole fiasco with Manhunt 2, they're kind of, I guess, taking notice on some of the trailers that have been released out there, including Gears of War, which was available online since January, is now, of course, coming down.
[SPEAKER_02]: And apparently, Darkness and Dark Sector videos have been
[SPEAKER_02]: immediately, I guess, pulled because, I guess, they were too bloody or whatever and, I guess, were an adult-only thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, they should have such a thing as a Red Band trailer for games, I think, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's kind of stupid, though, since, you know, before they were rating them with, you know, oh, because they're interactive and stuff, we've got to rate them a little harsher, which is dumb anyways, but you're watching a video of gameplay.
[SPEAKER_02]: You don't have any sort of interaction with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think, you know,
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_03]: where the preview is for restricted audiences only.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's because they'll have a gunshot in it or a real quick bloodshot or maybe some boobie.
[SPEAKER_03]: It might be an ad for a sexy movie and you see a lady wearing a dress that's see-through or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: You see Red Band trailers once in a while.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's kind of ridiculous that they're policing game trailers because that's not even... It's not the actual game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of a video.
[SPEAKER_02]: They'd be like,
[SPEAKER_02]: I know that they do that with movie trailers, you know, that they rate that this trailer isn't good for all audiences and stuff, but I think it's kind of ridiculous to do that with games.
[SPEAKER_03]: I could have sworn I heard some point that yellow bands were coming for the PG-13 and up audiences only.
[SPEAKER_03]: I couldn't, I can't remember, maybe it was R, no, yeah, it was PG-13 audiences only were going to have yellow band trailers, but I don't know if that ever, I might just be pulling that out of my butt, but I seem to remember reading that somewhere.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, obviously this next topic is rated G. This is definitely for everybody.
[SPEAKER_03]: This cat!
[SPEAKER_03]: Wait, hold on!
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura is not here this week, so we can't do a website of the week.
[SPEAKER_03]: But if she could, and she was here this week, I'm pretty sure this would have been a top contender for her website of the week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, yes, Loki, you can do your outburst now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, this cat right here made me get a cat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Really?
[SPEAKER_03]: Why is that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because it's super cute, and I want a gaming cat.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, well, yes, this is the Famico blog, and you can visit this blog if you'd like to at lovefami.blog90.fc2.com, and this is just a cat that poses with it.
[SPEAKER_03]: They make poses of it playing the DS and the 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did you ever see the other?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's so cute.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, see?
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, look at that one up.
[SPEAKER_02]: One more.
[SPEAKER_02]: One more up.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was that one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Keep going down.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, keep going.
[SPEAKER_03]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is so cute.
[SPEAKER_03]: Go, go, go.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's a picture right there.
[SPEAKER_03]: That is a very cute cat.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I believe the cat's name is Famicom, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's Fami, or Fami, named after the Famicom.
[SPEAKER_03]: Very cute.
[SPEAKER_03]: Named after famine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Are you wanting to... You're so messed up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Are you wanting to get a kitty someday, Rice Princess?
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just wanted you to contribute something to this show.
[SPEAKER_02]: I am going to attempt to get the cat that we're getting to sit there in a pose that'll look like it's playing DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think it's going to work, but we're going to try it.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what you need to do is get the cat to pose reading porn.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would be funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: Get a picture of that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't have any porn.
[SPEAKER_02]: At least not in magazine form.
[SPEAKER_02]: How can you not have porn?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll get my laptop and put porn on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will buy you a freaking Playboy or something and you can pose the cat with porn.
[SPEAKER_02]: and have it drinking alcohol.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, you should be Stella the Porno Cat.
[SPEAKER_03]: You should get a little pimp hat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, boy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and is podcasted to the world twice a week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Stay tuned to our podcast feed for the conclusion of this week's Orange Lounge Radio.