[SPEAKER_03]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and released to our podcast stream twice weekly To listen to the first half of this episode visit www.orangeloungeradio.com for links to websites with listings of past episodes Now the conclusion of this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_05]: Welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio here live on this Sunday evening, July the 15th of 2007.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going through the E3 wrap-up, of course.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, I know you guys have probably been reading about it on the various blogs, but maybe there's some things that we caught that maybe slipped off your radars, off the cracks.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, of course, we didn't get to go to E3 this year, so we're just kind of like a lot of you guys on the outside looking in.
[SPEAKER_05]: And so we're kind of collecting our thoughts.
[SPEAKER_05]: What do the people who weren't there think about it?
[SPEAKER_05]: What do the gaming fans who didn't get to go to E3 this year really think about it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because, hey, it's our money.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're spending it.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: It's supposed to be 33% lighter, 19% slimmer, has a longer battery life, and is also going to be having a video out on it as well, which is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll be retailing for $169.99, so the same price as the normal PSP now, and we'll eventually replace those as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: And we'll be loaded with the 3.6 firmware, so...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Star Wars Battlefront Renegade Squadron
[SPEAKER_05]: Video Out does sound pretty cool, and I know a lot of people kind of wrote it off, like, whoop-dee-doo, Video Out, you know, who cares?
[SPEAKER_05]: But, you know, it does make those UMDs at least a little more usable, that you can have them on your TV, but also, just getting to play, you know, some of these games, like the Final Fantasy remake and stuff, like, on my big TV!
[SPEAKER_06]: And if you think about it, if you're looking at, you know, possibly just using this as, like, even, you know, portable and standalone video player at home,
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I'm kind of excited about the Video Out, but the problem is I already own a PSP, so I don't really want to buy a whole new one just for Video Out.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have to admit, I'm a little bit disappointed this wasn't on the first, but I guess this is how they get you to buy another one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's the thing, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: Video Out uses the serial port that's on the bottom of the PSP.
[SPEAKER_06]: Supposedly, this one's redesigned.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not sure if that's actually the case, but they're saying it's redesigned.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's possible with this new firmware update 3.6 that maybe with the current ones you can do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Please let that be the case.
[SPEAKER_06]: It wouldn't be too surprising if they don't mention that until later on, much like certain other stories we'll get into later where they don't mention certain aspects of things.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_05]: So do you think you'll pick up a PSP redesign?
[SPEAKER_06]: I think I will just because I have two of them right now and I want to sell one of them or at least get rid of it because I have no use for it right now and that would be a good excuse to buy one of those because it wouldn't really cost me much the other thing though about it though this is kind of a trend you'll see at the Sony press conference something that they've been denying and denying yet people are saying it's going to be happening we've heard rumors and lo and behold it's true kind of a trend that's going along with it
[SPEAKER_05]: We shall see as we continue throughout the press conference stories here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, there is something that I... I have to say that I actually expected this.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, with all of the rumors going around about exclusive game this and exclusive game that, I honestly, this is what I expected, is that Metal Gear Solid 4 is going to be exclusive to the PS3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Reaffirmed.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not buying it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not buying it, and this is why.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, it may be a PSA exclusive when it comes out.
[SPEAKER_06]: I do not doubt that it's going to come to the 360 eventually, because it would be dumb for them to ignore the entire Xbox 360 user base.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's not because they're playing sides or anything, it's just about money.
[SPEAKER_06]: and they want to sell as many copies of this as possible.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wouldn't be surprised if we see a release on the Xbox 360 maybe later on.
[SPEAKER_08]: I will be surprised.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think it's going to happen.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it's going to stay on PS3.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it really all depends on sales.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, I'm not, I can totally see how it could happen where like, kind of like how the first Metal Gear, no, one of the Metal Gears ended up coming out for GameCube later on.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, like, I think it was the first Metal Gear was redone.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: and you know I could see something like that happening and this seems to happen a lot with the Metal Gear series where it shows up on the Sony platform first and then kind of mutates into a special edition thing that comes out on Xbox or whatever later on but like a year later I could see something like that happening if the sales aren't strong enough on its own so it's really going to depend but I mean that a year is such a long wait that you know it's it's not going to have a huge impact as far as the fanboys are concerned I don't know
[SPEAKER_05]: I think what you can count on, you can count on them not announcing another platform until well after the game is out.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that is something that will be a given.
[SPEAKER_06]: Unless, for whatever reason, that Sony has a really shitty fourth quarter, and they don't sell that many units or whatever, and...
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm thinking, Konami kind of does this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Konami's not only done this with the Metal Gear series, but Silent Hill as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember Silent Hill 2 was out on the PlayStation 2 first, then the WrestleStreams came out on Xbox, you know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Little things like that happen.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hitstunt says,
[SPEAKER_05]: until the PlayStation 3 version comes out, just like the standard six-month delay like Metal Gear Solid 2 and Virtua Fighter 5.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_06]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's good for them that they do have this, because at least this is something, hey, maybe this will sell a few systems for them.
[SPEAKER_06]: They need all they can take.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, well, we'll see where that leads.
[SPEAKER_05]: But nevertheless, the Xbox 360 folks who were convinced it was coming to their platform...
[SPEAKER_05]: Get a little bit of a setback.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I suppose hope is never lost, but hope has been diminished quite a bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, speaking of exclusives, another exclusive that was announced for the PlayStation 3 is Unreal Tournament 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, it was only affirmed as a timed exclusive for the PlayStation 3, but that does mean if you're a Sony fan and you got your PlayStation,
[SPEAKER_05]: You're going to get it first on the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, as far as the time thing, I could care less.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think this is the much cooler part about it, is that you're going to be able to use mods on the PlayStation 3 and the PC version.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, the PC version will come out a little later, but that's kind of cool for the modding community, of which a game like Unreal gets a lot of this stuff, is that the mods you make for PC you're going to be able to use on PS3 as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they're saying everything from weapon mods to total conversions for it are going to be available.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that's tons of extra content for it, which is awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now we need Duke Nukem 3D with mods and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: That'd be cool too.
[SPEAKER_05]: We shall see.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's pretty interesting about the whole Unreal Tournament 3 thing is as of May, it was actually going to be exclusive to the 360.
[SPEAKER_06]: So kind of flip-flopped there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Amazing what money can do.
[SPEAKER_06]: Something very interesting, probably a little bit surprising, would be that NCSoft has actually pledged support for the PlayStation 3 platform and are going to be releasing exclusive PlayStation 3 online games.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, not sure if they're actually going to be bringing their current titles over, like Lineage, Guild Wars, City of Heroes, and stuff like that, but they will be making at least some of their current IPs and new IPs available for the platform.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm still waiting on those online games that they were talking about at E3 the year before.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you think that maybe some of those are being now ported to PlayStation 3?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't see why they weren't all that big graphic monsters.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe if they did all of them at once.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I think their whole intention was having a big service available to people just to come in and play.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that's what I want to see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you think we might see Guild Wars 2 on the PlayStation 3?
[SPEAKER_08]: I hope not.
[SPEAKER_08]: Shit.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hate MMOs on consoles.
[SPEAKER_06]: MMOs should stick to freaking PCs unless they are specifically made for a console I disagree on Guild Wars because I believe since the whole format of Guild Wars is you buy the game and you go online for free that really works for a console because then you don't have to pay those monthly fees and stuff and then maybe a little bit more casual and later on when they offer their expansions or whatever you can download those as a microtransaction or whatever
[SPEAKER_06]: That would actually work very well for consoles.
[SPEAKER_06]: Whereas an MMO like Final Fantasy XI or something, not as good as normal.
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting points.
[SPEAKER_05]: We shall see what ends up happening.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, as far as other stuff, for people who wanted the 60GB PS3, get it while you can because we're not going to be getting any more.
[SPEAKER_08]: So yeah, let's cut the price and then get rid of them.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Despite what they say, it was unavailable to buy after about December.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's just, you know, they give you the impression that, you know, oh, well, you really want that 20 gig one, but, you know, you can't find it and you really, really want the system, so you're going to spend the extra $100 on it because you get this free game now and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, I don't know, I'm not surprised.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, you know what sucks for our friends in Europe is that they're not getting a price cut.
[SPEAKER_08]: Instead, what they're getting is a bundle with...
[SPEAKER_08]: Some first party titles and another six axis controller for 115 pounds.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which in my mind just reaffirms why Sony's doing this.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not so much about, you know, oh, we're going to give the U.S.
[SPEAKER_05]: a price cut.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's about, oh, we need to stop losing so much money on the systems.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we're going to give the U.S.
[SPEAKER_05]: the system we've been putting out in Europe that costs us less to make.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, they'll be getting a choice to pick from Resistance, Fall of Man, Motorstorm, Genji, Days of the Blade, Formula 1, Championship Edition, Ridge Racer 7, two of those plus the two 6-axis controllers.
[SPEAKER_08]: And they'll be available.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's actually due on sale on the 18th of July for the UK and starting in Europe on the 1st of August.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, if you want to get a PlayStation 3 and emulation is of a concern to you, maybe you don't have a PlayStation 2 or a PlayStation 1, this would probably be the time to get it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, honestly, if there's one positive thing you could say about this is that it does give you the chance to snatch up that system while you still can.
[SPEAKER_05]: Be sure to read the labels carefully.
[SPEAKER_05]: The new systems will show you.
[SPEAKER_05]: It has a little warning about the emulation on the new box that says not all games are actually playable.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, it wouldn't be fair to...
[SPEAKER_05]: mention this and then not mention, well, you know, the Xbox 360 uses software emulation as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: So to rag Sony for cutting back on the emulation may be a little bit unfair.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: But however, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: You do still feel like this sense of loss with this whole little switch going on.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the fact that they're, you know, maybe I don't want to dig out my PlayStation 2 when I'm going to go through all this to hook up my PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: and what's very interesting about Echo Chrome is that the graphics are very simplistic.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're black and white MC Escher style drawings and what's kind of cool, I watched a video of this game in motion, is that the way you rotate the screen around will affect the way the painting looks, thusly affecting the little runner that runs around the painting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now there's little holes
[SPEAKER_05]: and little launch pads and little gaps that as you rotate the screen become filled because of your perspective.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a very interesting type of thing for a puzzle game.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's certainly not going to push the envelope as far as next-gen graphics are concerned, but the graphics are crisp according to folks that have seen it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Plus, it's supposed to make web browsing a little bit easier and be able to load some of the larger pages out there and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Other things they were showing off, Gran Turismo 5.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to be coming out, of course, next year at some point.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they're going to be releasing a Gran Turismo 5 prologue to the PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's going to be kind of just like Gran Turismo HD.
[SPEAKER_06]: A little bit of a demo taste of it, as you will.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also, they were showing home and some of the improvements done to that.
[SPEAKER_06]: They've redesigned the whole kind of lobby system for it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It looks almost like an outdoor mall.
[SPEAKER_06]: And also, you'll be able to jump into multiplayer games with people as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's pretty much, I think, the big stuff they were kind of showing off on their network.
[SPEAKER_06]: My only gripe with them, remember last week how we were talking about, oh yeah, they're going to be bringing demos and videos to the PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to be just like the Xbox Live thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're going to be bringing it home and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, they didn't.
[SPEAKER_06]: They brought videos.
[SPEAKER_06]: Great, because I can watch those all over the internet and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not a single demo.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bobby Blackwolf has asked why you're not mentioning Chewbacca.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, Chewbacca announced the PSP redesign thing with Darth Vader.
[SPEAKER_06]: Great.
[SPEAKER_06]: At least that guy's still getting work.
[SPEAKER_05]: Same thing we've done before for all of the other three conferences.
[SPEAKER_05]: Chatroom, I ask for your opinion as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: What did you think of the Sony press conference?
[SPEAKER_05]: Rate it on a scale.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tell me what you thought.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who wants to go first?
[SPEAKER_05]: You all right, DarkSakura, with that resounding yawn?
[SPEAKER_05]: Is that your summary?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Short and sweet, Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think their whole theme of promises, promises, and not following through has kind of shown through again this year.
[SPEAKER_06]: The price cut, they made it look like a price cut, but it's actually not a price cut, which is fucked up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not to mention some other stuff we'll get into a little bit later on that's also fucked up, especially if you buy a system now.
[SPEAKER_06]: and just this whole oh look at all these games that are coming out and not mentioning oh by the way they're not coming out until next year.
[SPEAKER_06]: I do have to give them props on Killzone 2 though.
[SPEAKER_06]: That looks fucking amazing.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that is about the only thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you for satisfying a chat comment before I read it.
[SPEAKER_05]: TigerClaw was just complaining we forgot to mention the new Killzone 2 trailer.
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't forget to mention it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't mention it on purpose.
[SPEAKER_06]: It looks really good and it's actually it's a game I want to buy now because it looks kind of like Resistance a bit.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know Resistance with a little bit of Gears of War thrown in there.
[SPEAKER_06]: And
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: It impressed me a lot more than Halo 3 did.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, you know, props to them for that.
[SPEAKER_06]: But the problem is, it's not coming out this year.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, once again, you're showing me shit that, you know, I'm not going to buy your PlayStation 3 for these games that are coming out next year.
[SPEAKER_06]: At least I wouldn't be buying it if I didn't have one right now this holiday season, which is really where it's going to count for you guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll be buying it when it comes out, you know, actually in the summer of next year or whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it doesn't do them any good for this holiday.
[SPEAKER_06]: Once again, if they don't come out with something amazing, they're going to lose out on another holiday.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's really going to hurt them.
[SPEAKER_08]: The only thing I really care about coming out of there is, of course, Silent Hill 5, and I really want Metal Gear Solid 4.
[SPEAKER_05]: As far as my thoughts on Sony's press conference, I said before last week that Nintendo had the most to lose going into E3, and Sony had the most to gain.
[SPEAKER_08]: Getting a new Civ game?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, it's also coming on Xbox 360, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: I downloaded the trailer, and I'm pretty excited about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: But that's different.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think Sony did a way better job than they did last year.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think they certainly changed the tone of their press conference and had it a little well-oiled and got the kinks a little better worked out this year.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I still walked away from it being more excited about the PSP than the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I don't know if that's a good sign.
[SPEAKER_05]: and this whole bait and switch leaves a real bad taste in my mouth.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's the problem, last year, remember last year, it was all, oh, Gran Turismo 5, it's going to be like Gran Turismo HD and stuff, but better and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: No Gran Turismo 5 this year.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then this, you know, the E3, ooh, Gran Turismo 5, it's so awesome and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, and it does look really good, but Project Gotham 4 also looks really good, and if this game is going to take, you know, until Summer 08 to come out...
[SPEAKER_06]: They're going to have Project Gotham Racing 5, which is going to look even more amazing.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's just, it's all this promising of really good games that are coming out way later.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the problem.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not like Microsoft where it's like, here's these great games, they're coming out this fall.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, get excited for them because they're right around the corner.
[SPEAKER_06]: Whereas, this stuff's coming way later on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I kind of feel the same way.
[SPEAKER_05]: It sounds like I'll have a lot more to get excited about with the PlayStation 3 at next year's E3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or hopefully Final Fantasy XIII is there.
[SPEAKER_05]: But is it going to be too late?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or remember, they're showing LittleBigPlanet, that's next year.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're talking about Home, which I hope that's this year.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it's, yeah, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, it's just disappointing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Part of me on a scale of 1 to 10 wants to give Sony a question mark.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Their press conference looks like the town of Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's too much haze around everything for me.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I will reward them for their PSP redesign even though they're taking the old ones away or whatever is supposed to be happening.
[SPEAKER_05]: I give that
[SPEAKER_05]: Good points, but the PlayStation 3, although some games look cool, I'm not completely blown away.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I give them credit.
[SPEAKER_05]: I give them the most improved player award.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would give their conference a 6.
[SPEAKER_06]: Explain this to me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why should I get a PS3 with a larger hard drive when there's nothing to download for it?
[SPEAKER_06]: There's trailers for movies.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's trailers for games.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's literally less than 10 demos online.
[SPEAKER_06]: and there's a handful of, you know, PlayStation download titles.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, am I buying this larger hard drive system for, you know, so I can dump some of my game's stuff to the hard drive so it can cache the system and make it run faster since the Blu-ray drive's too slow?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it's... They haven't really shown me why we need to buy a system with a larger hard drive in the first place.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're really pushing... Trust me, hard drive space is not what's holding people back from buying your system.
[SPEAKER_05]: BlackWolf says, going to chat room, all three companies pretty much surrendered the press conferences.
[SPEAKER_05]: Floridine says, Sony fails 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkTetsuya says, I liked everything I saw except the new Ratchet and Clank, which should just be released on PlayStation 2 if it's not already.
[SPEAKER_05]: SSJ100Matt says, Sony, they showed everyone what they wanted.
[SPEAKER_05]: Games, Killzone 2, Unreal 3, etc.
[SPEAKER_05]: They showed that the PlayStation 3 has real future.
[SPEAKER_05]: Solid B plus, A minus.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: I will give them credit for this.
[SPEAKER_05]: And maybe, actually, maybe I'll bump up my score to a 7 for this sole reason.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Eye of Judgment was nowhere to be seen.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I will bump up Sony's score to 7 for scrapping that piece of shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: They showed it on the show floor, so that was there.
[SPEAKER_06]: But we're grading the conference.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'll give them the bonus point.
[SPEAKER_06]: I will give them the same as I gave Nintendo a 6.
[SPEAKER_06]: And just because it's promises.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I think there's going to be...
[SPEAKER_06]: Where the disappointments were with the whole... Blackwell says Eye of Judgment was not on the floor.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I saw a video of it, so I know that it was there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe behind a door that Bobby didn't look behind.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, it was there.
[SPEAKER_06]: They were showing it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's going to be a whole line of disappointments with Sony.
[SPEAKER_06]: As we go through the fourth quarter, it's just going to be disappointment after disappointment.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think...
[SPEAKER_05]: The PlayStation 3 is really set to go the same way as the PSP.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not going to get really, really cool until like three years later.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or two or three years later.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: BlackWolf says it might have been in their invite-only hotel suite.
[SPEAKER_05]: He wanted to ask about the copying of cards just for you, about going to Kinko's and making your own cards.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's their reasoning behind it.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're saying...
[SPEAKER_06]: They basically didn't give a reason.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's no copy protection on the cards, but their thing was it would be like playing Magic the Gathering with someone with photocopied cards.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like you'd really play someone with photocopied cards.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was their reasoning behind it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So in other words, yes, you can copy the cards or download images off the internet instead of buying booster packs and whatnot and copying the card stock and it'll work just fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: TheRobD asks, The PSP is really, really cool?
[SPEAKER_05]: I might buy a PSP for the emulation.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, maybe less of the really, really.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, you know, the PSP...
[SPEAKER_05]: is never been solely a gaming system.
[SPEAKER_05]: I do respect the system for everything else it can do, like being kind of a little mini media kit.
[SPEAKER_05]: But yeah, there's some pretty cool stuff that have come out for it in the past year.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think they can't be ignored.
[SPEAKER_06]: But did you notice, though, that they're kind of making the PSP out now to be almost like more of an iPod or a Zune or something?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because now it has a video out thing on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're going to be able to charge it using the USB cable on there as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: So if you're on the go, you can charge it and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: and then of course memory stick prices are coming down quite a bit so I don't know it's interesting and the problem is though their PR department is so horrible so horrible and they really their upper management needs to shut the hell up it's not helping them and I know Ken Kutaragi's gone now because he was making dumb statements before but my god Kazurai is not any better it
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not any better with him.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, well, there you have it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Our thoughts on the Sony press conference.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's go now to some more listener feedback via the email bag, because we love to get emails.
[SPEAKER_05]: And if you weren't in our chat room tonight and you want to give your two cents to the press conferences or anything you saw at E3...
[SPEAKER_05]: Send us an email, mailbag at orangelauntradio.com, because DarkSakura opens up the mailbag every week and reads a few of her favorite pieces of email here with us.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_08]: He, he, he, Captain Crayola.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jump in the mailbag and pull something out for us, will you?
[SPEAKER_08]: First email.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, OLR crew.
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess this is where I should say I'm a long-time listener but a first-time emailer.
[SPEAKER_08]: I first heard about your show from Bobby Blackwolf.
[SPEAKER_08]: He's an old friend of mine from the days when we were moderators on the forums for a TV channel, but are left unmentioned.
[SPEAKER_08]: And have been listening to the podcast on and off for about a year.
[SPEAKER_08]: I always find the show enjoyable, and you've become one of my mainstays for relatively unbiased or biased in a way that matches my own opinions at Gaming News.
[SPEAKER_08]: Recently, I listened to the podcast of your five-year plus-one episode, and I have a bone to pick with Loki and Rob regarding the Harvest Moon series.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki is on record as enjoying sandbox games.
[SPEAKER_08]: and the Harvest Moon series fits this description to a tee.
[SPEAKER_08]: The games have something for everyone.
[SPEAKER_08]: Real-time strategy fans can strategize to get the most crops each season.
[SPEAKER_08]: Those who enjoy dating sims can, in most of the games, date the NPCs, culminating in creating a family.
[SPEAKER_08]: Action fans can have fun catching fish, chopping down trees and planting endless fields of grass.
[SPEAKER_08]: RPG fans can engage in as many tedious and pointless quests as have ever been found in one game.
[SPEAKER_08]: There are no expectations and certainly no requirements for the manner in which one plays the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's not to love?
[SPEAKER_08]: Not liking the series because farming isn't for you makes more sense than disliking them because all the games are the same.
[SPEAKER_08]: After all, doesn't Halo do the same thing?
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, my husband and I love the show and are looking forward to listening for years to come.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks for brightening up our week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yours, TheBlackMonster.
[SPEAKER_08]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_08]: This email was written on a G4 Titanium Power Book.
[SPEAKER_06]: Grats.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, you start.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll address this.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, Microsoft isn't releasing eight copies of the game a year.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, seriously, there are so many Harvest Moon games that they're saying that are different, but aren't really different.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, there's the Harvest Moon Boys and Girls, which I'm going to take a wild guess and say it's probably just like the Harvest Moon Boys and Girls on the GameCube and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's the whole, was it Innocent Life of Futuristic Harvest Moon or something like that, which was just...
[SPEAKER_06]: Like a futuristic setting, still farming.
[SPEAKER_06]: And still all the same stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Great.
[SPEAKER_06]: If that's for you, awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not a sandbox game.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is not Grand Theft Auto farming.
[SPEAKER_05]: See, this is the problem.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is that this game doesn't involve guns and violence.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's where your problem is.
[SPEAKER_06]: The problem is, is it doesn't change.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not innovating any.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it's farming.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, great.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, are there different crops this time?
[SPEAKER_06]: Ooh, goody.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it's not like, you know, you have a crop or something and you have to...
[SPEAKER_06]: Fight Off, the man who's trying to steal your property to build a mall or something on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think what's going on here is that sandbox is kind of being seen as a very general term where Loki likes a very specific type of sandbox game like the 3D jump, shoot, find, destroy, rape type of sandbox game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, the sandbox games are basically games you can go in there and do whatever you want and tackle it however you want.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is a farming... This is a sim game.
[SPEAKER_06]: You start off with crops...
[SPEAKER_06]: You tend to the crops and stuff, and it's a farming sim with RPG elements.
[SPEAKER_05]: From my perspective, I've tried Harvest Moon.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, I played the one on the GameCube, and I just...
[SPEAKER_05]: I just couldn't get into it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know what it was.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think for me there was like just kind of like too much going on at once.
[SPEAKER_05]: It didn't have that kind of simplicity that Animal Crossing had.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, you know, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess maybe I need to give the series another look because if I like Animal Crossing, I should like something like Harvest Moon.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I just wasn't feeling it.
[SPEAKER_05]: There was just, there was nothing to keep me coming back.
[SPEAKER_06]: What they need to do is instead of releasing, like,
[SPEAKER_06]: 4 or 5 titles a year of Harvest Moon.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just release one good title of Harvest Moon each year and do it that way.
[SPEAKER_06]: Put some more effort into the game instead of just rehashing the same thing and giving it a new coat of paint.
[SPEAKER_05]: Devil's Advocate, I have to.
[SPEAKER_05]: I may not agree with what I'm about to say, but Devil's Advocate, I have to.
[SPEAKER_05]: Doesn't DDR do the same damn thing?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, it does.
[SPEAKER_06]: It does the same damn thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's another reason why that series is starting to go downhill.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's because that's all they do is just give it a new fresh coat of paint, change the colors of the menu or something, and then just add some new songs.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And expect you to buy it.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_06]: Take it or leave it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Can we talk about something other than Harvest Moon now?
[SPEAKER_06]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_08]: This next email though is super cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dear OLR crew, this is Ranma the Blind from Indonesia.
[SPEAKER_08]: I finally wrote my second email to you and I hope I could share some video game related contents that might interest you all and all of your listeners.
[SPEAKER_08]: First of all, I would like to announce that I finally bought a Wii.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's because I've got nostalgia for old Nintendo systems, so I wish I could play some of the old classic games via virtual console.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or perhaps I could hear my friends play the games as my eye condition makes me impossible to play all the games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: Right now, I'm still trying some other Wii titles, and I hope I can discover more games for blinds to play.
[SPEAKER_08]: I wish that Nintendo could make research about this, and perhaps create accessible contents for the blind to purchase.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you guys, do you have any comments about this?
[SPEAKER_08]: And I'll pause here if you guys have any comments.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I appreciate hearing back because it's always interesting to hear from this kind of perspective that doesn't often get enough recognition at large in gaming blogs and things.
[SPEAKER_08]: There were sound games on the Saturn back in the day.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why can't Nintendo do that?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm actually going to turn around and ask another question.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm really curious because I bet this email was sent in before Nintendo's press conference this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm really curious what this emailer thinks about some of these other new innovations like Wii Fit and some of these other directions that Nintendo's going that has a little more to do with movement, if that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, email us back.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, I'm going to have to ask him to email us back because of the next part.
[SPEAKER_08]: But did you have a comment?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I was just going to say that, you know, unfortunately, you know, blind gamers are such a small...
[SPEAKER_06]: percentage of their demographic that I don't think you're going to ever see anything that's really dedicated to it, unless you get some independent company out there that's really gearing towards, you know, that.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's no reason for them to make sound-based games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Unless they could do something pretty innovative, because there was some stuff on the Game Boy Advance that was just sound, part of that bit generation series, but it's just unfortunately, you know, blind handicap and stuff, it is such a small market, you know,
[SPEAKER_05]: What about something that would make the existing games more accessible to the audience?
[SPEAKER_06]: Great, if they can do something like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I sort of think about how Windows has the Zoom feature and those other types of accessibility options.
[SPEAKER_05]: Could a game console adapt something similar?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's possible, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mortal Kombat Armageddon would probably be a lot easier to play and waggle the thing around.
[SPEAKER_06]: Broad caliber!
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, anyhow, sorry, let the email finish.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, the next part is, another thing I would like to share is a Final Fantasy concert held in my country.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, this is the second one as the concert was also held last year, but it was still enjoyable, especially in Indonesia where video game music is rare to find, and game music concert is like a distant dream.
[SPEAKER_08]: You did say you uploaded pictures and videos from the concert.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want your permission before I make that public to chat, so...
[SPEAKER_08]: or if you would like to go into our forum at OrangeDodgeRadio.com and make a thread about it, then we would appreciate you sharing it with everybody that way.
[SPEAKER_08]: I wish in the future another video game music concert will again be held here, perhaps by Video Game Music Live or Play, a video game symphony.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think that's all for now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Take care and have a good show.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for the email.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, this one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey guys, how's it going?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's me, Nim.
[SPEAKER_08]: I haven't been listening lately because of the fact that my iPod was stolen.
[SPEAKER_08]: I usually listen to the downloadable version, but more than likely I'll be tuning in more often and jumping in chat.
[SPEAKER_08]: Lately I've been playing a lot of Bimani, Beatmania, Dance Dance Revolution, Parapara, and I just heard Poppin' for the first time last week.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm pretty sure you've answered this question before, but knowing that you used to be nothing but a show about Bimani, which out of the line are your favorites?
[SPEAKER_05]: Out of the entire Bomani series?
[SPEAKER_05]: Is that what the question?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm assuming.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, that's a tough question.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to say 2DX, but the series has gotten really stale.
[SPEAKER_05]: God, the same goes for DDR.
[SPEAKER_05]: The problem is most of the Konami Bomani series has gotten a little bit stale.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's not been a lot of innovation within the games.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would say, I guess, back in the day, it was definitely Beatmania, 2DX.
[SPEAKER_05]: Keyboard Mania?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh yeah, oh fuck, I loved Keyboard Mania.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, Keyboard Mania is my answer.
[SPEAKER_08]: I loved Drum Mania a whole lot, and my drum pads were, unfortunately they're just not as strong as how I like to play, because I'm used to the arcade, but I still like to get out and shake my booty on Parapara, that's always fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like Dance Maniacs.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I didn't like Dance Maniacs.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: I love Dance Maniacs.
[SPEAKER_08]: I love Marathon Road.
[SPEAKER_06]: I, you know, personally, I would love to see another Bomani game that was using the Parapara control system, but with non-Parapara music.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, just like another, like, dancing game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hell, they can do another dancing game like that and have, like, you know, the, almost like the Wii Fit board on the bottom or something, have, like, pressure sensors or something to do something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: That'd be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, any more emails?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, let's hear them.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's move forward.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey all, just wanted to chime in as another developer that listens to your show each week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Technically, I'm an associate producer, which, if you enjoy abbreviations, turns into ass prod.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love people that can be self-deprecating in their humor.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, um...
[SPEAKER_08]: You can tell by my email address where I work now.
[SPEAKER_08]: And before this, I ran my own indie studio and developed a little strategy game for PC called Land of Legends.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I'm not going to say where.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not going to say either, because I read the email beforehand, so I know where this person is from from the email address.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I will say...
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to say that it's a company that I know takes a lot of crap from the hardcore community sometimes, but I think they really do some awesome things for the non-hardcore audience.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think they've done a lot, especially in the past year, and a lot of stuff that I really enjoy.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I'm not just saying that because you emailed.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, I just wanted to say thanks for the show and let you guys know that you have
[SPEAKER_08]: Yet another developer listening.
[SPEAKER_08]: Feel free to write if you have any questions or issues I can help with.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm just going to use the nickname HeroAntagonist.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, it's funny, I heard back from the developer that emailed us previously and he was willing to do an Ask a Developer type segment.
[SPEAKER_05]: So maybe we can get this guy in on it too and have some type of roundtable thing on a later show.
[SPEAKER_05]: That might be kind of fun, especially during the next few months.
[SPEAKER_05]: It might be a little bit slow before we get into the fall rush of game news.
[SPEAKER_05]: It might be kind of fun to do an Ask a Developer roundtable.
[SPEAKER_05]: So please write us back if you'd be willing to participate.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can contact me directly or send back the email bag, whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because we're going to try definitely doing something like that in the future.
[SPEAKER_08]: This one's short.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, OLR.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know I'm kind of late with this one, but happy belated birthday, OLR.
[SPEAKER_08]: You guys are awesome and keep it up.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ron.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you, Ron.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you bring us a present?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: You said, Ron, I think of Potter Puppet House.
[SPEAKER_05]: Stop.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's Snape.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's bother him.
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: This last one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just want to say I love the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: And what do you think about young gamers on online games that they really shouldn't play?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm 14, so I really shouldn't be talking.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just wanted your opinion.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sincerely, Christian.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who says you shouldn't talk if you're 14?
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, age...
[SPEAKER_08]: Age is a number.
[SPEAKER_05]: Age is a number.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maturity is everything.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I think if you can play a game maturely, and that doesn't mean you have to play adult or act adult.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can have fun but still be mature.
[SPEAKER_05]: And by that, I mean you don't go on to Xbox Live and yell, you know, N, N, N, F, F, F, and all those words that people scream on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you can have fun and have that self-deprecating humor and laugh and have a good time, then, you know,
[SPEAKER_05]: I do have a suggestion.
[SPEAKER_05]: Use periods when you type.
[SPEAKER_05]: I had perfect grammar when I was fourteen.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's dig up some of your high school papers and check.
[SPEAKER_08]: Honestly?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I really don't care that much.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can say, because I can prove it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can back it up.
[SPEAKER_08]: But no, seriously, it's just a matter of how you... If you're typing on an MMO and you have something to say, think... Something my granddaddy used to always say, I will quote a bit of wisdom, put brain in gear before mouth in motion.
[SPEAKER_08]: In this case...
[SPEAKER_08]: Put brain in gear before typing, I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kevin DDR in chat would like to point out, I am a 14-year-old playing online games.
[SPEAKER_05]: See?
[SPEAKER_05]: So you're not alone.
[SPEAKER_08]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just a matter of, you know, just thinking before you do something.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was playing online games at 14.
[SPEAKER_05]: Only when I was 14, the online games we had to play were Legend of the Red Dragon, Trade Wars, The Pit...
[SPEAKER_05]: and so on and so on.
[SPEAKER_05]: And if you catch my references, you're a winner.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is that it?
[SPEAKER_08]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you'd like to send us an email, mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: And by the way, I give everybody a hard time for their grammar, so don't worry about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mine's really not all that great.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, it's really better than Rob's on AIM, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: I will say that.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, shut up.
[SPEAKER_05]: We will get on to...
[SPEAKER_05]: Some other news coming out of E3 that didn't necessarily have to do with the press conferences.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, I want to spend a little time talking about music games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because, you know, that's how we started.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's our roots.
[SPEAKER_05]: We need to talk about some of the music games that were going on at E3 and some of the events that happened this week outside of E3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's start with a game that was coming out from EA.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's called Boogie.
[SPEAKER_05]: EA announced the soundtrack to the game called Boogie.
[SPEAKER_05]: It comes with a karaoke microphone and it's actually on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they were trying to put together basically a lot of generations of hits.
[SPEAKER_05]: And in this game you're supposed to be able to dance, sing, and make music videos using the Wii controls.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that should be interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some of the songs that will be in this game.
[SPEAKER_05]: ABC by the Jackson 5.
[SPEAKER_05]: Brick House by the Commodores.
[SPEAKER_05]: Canned Heat by Jamiroquai.
[SPEAKER_05]: Love Roller Coaster by the Red Hot Chili Peppers.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's Get It Started by the Black Eyed Peas.
[SPEAKER_05]: Love Shack by the B-52s.
[SPEAKER_05]: Milkshake by Khalees.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's so rad.
[SPEAKER_05]: One Way, that's the song we gotta get Loki to play.
[SPEAKER_05]: One Way or Another by Blondie, Groove is in the Heart by D. Light, Girls Just Wanna Have Fun, Cindy Lauper, Get the Party Started by Pink, Fergalicious by Fergie, there's another Loki song, YMCA by The Village People, Can't Touch This by MC Hammer, SOS by Rihanna, Oops I Did It Again, Britney Spears, that's a pretty fun list that brings across all generations there, so.
[SPEAKER_05]: Black Sabbath Paranoid
[SPEAKER_06]: Blue Oyster Cult, Don't Fear the Reaper, The Ramones, Rockaway Beach, Rush with Tom Sawyer, Bon Jovi with Wanted Dead or Alive, Nirvana in Bloom, Stone Temple Pilots, Vaseline, Weezer, Say It Ain't So,
[SPEAKER_06]: Foo Fighters, Learn to Fly, Metallica, Enter Sandman, The Hives, Main Offender, The Strokes, Reptilia, and Queens of the Stone Age go with Flow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now I heard in this game you'll be able to use the microphone as claps or a tambourine.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I demand this mix have Stevie Nicks somewhere in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fleetwood Mac, whatever you have to do to do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you cannot have a game where you play the tambourine and not represent Miss Stevie Nicks because...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: That has the possibility of being a pretty awesome game.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's one reason I'm sad I didn't go to E3.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would have liked to play that.
[SPEAKER_05]: They also promise new content every week.
[SPEAKER_06]: For how long?
[SPEAKER_06]: If it takes off, I'd say probably for a year.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's something that could just keep going, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think that's great.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's going to be very interesting to see what that does.
[SPEAKER_08]: Quite ambitious.
[SPEAKER_05]: Harmonix gets it, you guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: They get it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rock Band teams with MTV.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to take off.
[SPEAKER_06]: and it's kind of interesting to see what's going to happen to Guitar Hero this year because they've almost got to beat their own game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I realize there's a guitar and drum element in this game that makes this, but I hope somehow poppy songs can, you know, because I love poppy songs as well as rock, so I hope somehow they can be integrated into this game one way or another.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's just a weird side of me that would like to be able to sing, you know, just the weird songs you wouldn't expect in this game, you know?
[SPEAKER_06]: And I want Rock Band 2 or whatever to have different instruments.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rock Band 2, Electric Boogaloo.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hopefully Rock Band 2 gives us a little more, you know, so we can sing different songs.
[SPEAKER_08]: It would be damn hard to do a keyboard style thing, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: Please give me keyboard.
[SPEAKER_04]: Please give me keyboard.
[SPEAKER_08]: The format that they have set up for that, I doubt very seriously that would be possible unless it's like seven keys.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's USB.
[SPEAKER_06]: How hard could it be?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm talking about screen format.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, especially when you've got the voice track, guitar, all this other business going on on the screen, and your animation going on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Doing keyboard mode is not going to be... I'm trying to think of the way that they have the Guitar Hero style play going in.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're not going to be able to do keyboard that way.
[SPEAKER_08]: They could do it with Keyboard Mania because you had a full screen.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, Destroyer of Dreams, everybody.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm just being realistic, Rob.
[SPEAKER_08]: I understand, but... Rob, there is no Easter Bunny!
[SPEAKER_08]: I hate you.
[SPEAKER_08]: There was no bunny hanging out at Easter.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can we please move on?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, please.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, it's my turn, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_08]: I have good news.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, it would be good news if it was still 1991, wouldn't it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, please read the story now.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know what's coming.
[SPEAKER_08]: Slash, our curly-haired, top-hat-wearing hero of Guns N' Roses, currently a Velvet Revolver, is a boss in Guitar Hero 3.
[SPEAKER_08]: Buckethead is cooler!
[SPEAKER_05]: I absolutely agree this news would have been ten times cooler in 1991.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's still kind of cool, you have to admit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Having Slash in the game, that is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because, you know, those of us that remember Slash from our high school days are a little bit more grown up now and can spend the money on things like Guitar Hero 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: And there is a certain cool factor to having Slash in the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, Guitar Hero 3 knows they're going to really have it in for them with this whole rock band thing coming out, but...
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it could be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Again, it all boils down to song list for me.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's almost like this year's lineup, EA has it in for Activision.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, they've got Skate coming out with Tony Hawk's Proving Ground coming out later, Rock Band, and I don't know, I guess with licensed games, you know, The Simpsons and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Activision has a lot to lose if they don't innovate.
[SPEAKER_08]: Innovate or Die GK128 says Fuck Slash
[SPEAKER_05]: Guitar Hero needs a college rock edition featuring Frank Black from the Pixies and Jay Maskis from Dinosaur Jr.
[SPEAKER_08]: I love you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Officially.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what we need?
[SPEAKER_08]: We need like late 70s, early 80s rock like Enid Tho and some Joy Division for me.
[SPEAKER_08]: That'd be great.
[SPEAKER_08]: And some Bauhaus.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, speaking of music games and going over to Konami, kind of talking about what they're up to, Supernova 2 was tested this week, and some of the news has been a little bit lost in the shuffle of all the E3 news, but if you head over to a site like BomaniStyle.com that dedicates themselves to all the music game news, you can get some of the latest wrap-ups from the fans out there playing the location test.
[SPEAKER_05]: A whole list of the extra songs that are in the game has shown up.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's some interesting covers in it, including Come Clean, which if I remember right was like a Hilary Duff song, I think.
[SPEAKER_05]: Faint, Me Against the Music
[SPEAKER_05]: It's very interesting that Konami sticks with all these covers, not the real things.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, anyway, some other reports that come in from the updates.
[SPEAKER_05]: Marvelous ratings in Supernova 2 don't seem to award more points than perfects, and for some reason seemed easier to obtain than usual.
[SPEAKER_05]: Strings of perfect ratings will by no means hamper a great song rating.
[SPEAKER_05]: Konami finally has spelled Marvelous the right way with one L, and it's a solid silver color.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: If a player is able to receive all perfects or better, the AAA rating on the results screen will feature the text, Full Perfect Combo.
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some other news there.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's an extra stage that has a background video with Black Roses, people, and other things that are going on.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess the song is called Unreal.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's an introduction video to DDR has returned.
[SPEAKER_05]: It hasn't been one of those in a little while.
[SPEAKER_05]: They say since 4th Mix there.
[SPEAKER_05]: But they say some of the songs feel a little off sync.
[SPEAKER_05]: People were complaining that some of the older songs from DDR Extreme and DDR Supernova didn't feel quite right.
[SPEAKER_05]: It wasn't off-sync by much, but they were bitching it was off-sync.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it should also be noted they were also bitching that the pads being used on the location test machine were not perfect, which might be a good point to reiterate that maybe it's time for Konami to come out with some new pads that are a little better with the technology that's a little newer.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not to mention, I mean, but if you guys remember the original Supernova beta test, same issues, you know, that stuff was off-sync.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just...
[SPEAKER_05]: BlackWolf says only in DDR is perfect, not good enough.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: So for DDR fans who are looking to get back into arcades, also the rumor is EMUs is coming with Supernova 2, which you might remember from the Japanese Pomona games.
[SPEAKER_05]: It never really came over here, but the rumor is the test machine had the EMUs set up on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see where that goes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Could make up for lack of memory cards.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hopefully.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyways, so I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is, I guess, cool that there's new content coming out for Guitar Hero 2 for the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the new pack actually is going to have a few more songs in there.
[SPEAKER_06]: But at the same time, you know, it's got... I want to be sedated, smoke on the water, and you've got another thing coming.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's still going to be 500 Microsoft points, or $6.25.
[SPEAKER_06]: And guess what?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because, you know, people that did download it before the first pack
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, of course.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: I was going to have something petty to complain about, but I just realized something.
[SPEAKER_06]: DDR hasn't had another download pack since the launch of the fucking, you know, Universe game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Where the fuck are the downloads?
[SPEAKER_06]: Shit, Universe 2 is right around the corner.
[SPEAKER_06]: Where the hell is my goddamn downloads for Universe 1?
[SPEAKER_06]: Or did you just forget to do that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Kind of like the karaoke revolution append discs.
[SPEAKER_05]: Want to know my theory?
[SPEAKER_05]: They ain't coming because the song packs were all already on the disc and that's all they made.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's my theory.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fuck them for that.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_05]: My FU of the week goes to the fact that I have to move in two weeks and I still don't have a place to live.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a little bit frustrating.
[SPEAKER_05]: But hopefully I will be better very soon and I'll have a place because that would be nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because otherwise I'm going to cry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's move on to some other news.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now we're going to get into some news that, you know, some other things picked up around this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not necessarily at E3, but some of them are, some of them aren't.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, there is some other stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Disney has actually purchased War Inspector, their Junction Point Studios.
[SPEAKER_08]: So now we'll be getting some new games, and Disney is going to have some stuff coming to the new consoles.
[SPEAKER_08]: War Inspector brought us the Deus Ex, Thief, Deadly Shadows, System Shock.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um...
[SPEAKER_08]: I really don't know how to feel about this.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's a quote on here saying, Warren Spector's unique talents as leading creative forces in the world of video games, his knowledge and passion for Disney, his legacy of storytelling and character development adds a unique creative dimension to our portfolio.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it's from the executive VP of Disney Interactive.
[SPEAKER_08]: So maybe we'll get some good.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, Disney's been up to a lot of wheeling and dealing lately.
[SPEAKER_05]: They, at E3, announced a new online service that will be on all of their DS titles.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's called D-Gamer, and it's going to be first in the Chronicles of Narnia game that's coming out for the DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: And basically what D-Gamer's going to do is it's going to turn your Nintendo DS into Xbox Live of sorts.
[SPEAKER_05]: There will be avatars, you can chat with other people, and you can look at the achievements that your friends have unlocked.
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting that it took a third party to do this.
[SPEAKER_05]: So the system is more than capable of handling this type of technology, it's just that Nintendo doesn't want to do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: And interesting that somebody has decided to step up and do it, if not just for their own games.
[SPEAKER_05]: But let's face it, there's a certain audience that gets a lot of these Disney games that come out, you know, the Hannah Montana games and the That's So Ravens game.
[SPEAKER_05]: that will benefit from this, whereas the rest of us hardcore gamers that are too cool to go out and buy a Chronicles of Narnia video game are going to be sitting here going, gosh, I wish I had something like that when I was playing, you know, the games I'm playing, like Pokemon, even though that's not much cooler.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because Rob really likes Hannah Montana.
[SPEAKER_06]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Another disappointment.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well...
[SPEAKER_06]: Still rumors that the 6-axis controller is gonna be rumbling soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: In fact, it's been confirmed by a few different places, one of which is supposedly a Sony employee.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently, I guess...
[SPEAKER_06]: Sony employee confirmed directly to Kotaku that the 6-axis will be rumbling soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course, shortly afterwards, Immersion comes out saying, hey, we're making a TouchSense rumble controller for the PlayStation 3 in September.
[SPEAKER_06]: So if a third-party company is making it for the PlayStation 3 in September, because why the hell would you add rumble to your controllers if, I don't know, there wasn't rumble coming, because that would be kind of stupid.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, that's very interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: But Sony is still denying it, saying, hey, yeah, it's not coming, you know, this is all rumor, blah, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_06]: But then again, last week, they were also saying, hey, we have no plans on cutting the PlayStation 3 price.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or, you know, hey, the 60 gig system is going to be $4.99 and we're going to be still producing them, you know, that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let me put it this way.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rumble isn't so last gen after all.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to take a wild guess and say it's probably coming this fall.
[SPEAKER_06]: And so when you buy your PlayStation 3 systems, guess what?
[SPEAKER_06]: You get to buy new controllers.
[SPEAKER_06]: Much like the PlayStation 1, if you remember.
[SPEAKER_05]: Devil's Advocate, could the rumble in these controllers be for the backwards compatible games?
[SPEAKER_06]: It would be weird to see them.
[SPEAKER_06]: It could possibly, I guess, for that.
[SPEAKER_06]: But right now, as far as I'm aware, I don't think the rumble stuff is in there.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess it's possible.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it'd be kind of weird to buy a controller just for the backwards compatible games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, because that would imply that somebody bought a PlayStation 3 would totally skip the PlayStation 2, and I can't think that that's a very large audience.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I can't imagine that programming or whatever would be built into the emulation either.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_06]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: It'd be an interesting theory, but I think it's coming.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, well we shall see what Sony does in the upcoming months.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sony's gonna eat crayon pie is what they're gonna do.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, except this.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is redemption, I think.
[SPEAKER_08]: They did a poem that hinted to a coming of something.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, I'm just gonna say it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Silent Hill 5 has been announced for the Xbox 360 and PlayStation 3, which I'll probably get it on PS3.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm happy.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, how would your inner fangirl feel if I told you that Silent Hill 5 is not being developed by Team Silent, but in fact is being developed by the team that brought you Mark Echo's Getting Up?
[SPEAKER_05]: and the first Buffy the Vampire Slayer game on the Xbox.
[SPEAKER_08]: The first Buffy game was really good.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: So your inner fangirl may give this a chance?
[SPEAKER_08]: As long as my man does music.
[SPEAKER_05]: Akira Yamaoka
[SPEAKER_05]: and then, of course, Silent Hill Arcade, which I had my fangasm over in Part A. Seriously, if you haven't seen the videos, it's so... I don't want to spoil what happens, but, like, the battle with Pyramid Head ends in, like, the raddest way.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, fangasm all over.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, yes, I am a fanboy for Pyramid Head and Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_05]: I will admit it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, I'm also a fanboy for Price Drops, and I was kind of hoping, like many of you, that Microsoft would announce one this week at E3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: There was an interview from 1UP with Shane Kim and they were talking to him.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's of course the corporate VP at Microsoft Game Studios.
[SPEAKER_05]: They were asking him about the whole, you know, what does Xbox 360 need to win and where's the price drop?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, Shane Kim doesn't completely count out a price drop.
[SPEAKER_05]: In fact, he says, stay tuned.
[SPEAKER_05]: We didn't announce anything here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Didn't feel the need to.
[SPEAKER_05]: July is a very odd time to announce a price reduction.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not even sure Sony announced a price reduction anyway, because, you know, the whole bait and switch thing going on.
[SPEAKER_05]: So they said we didn't feel the need to do it at E3.
[SPEAKER_05]: So they're not cutting it out of the picture.
[SPEAKER_05]: It might just not be coming for a little while, kind of like was speculated earlier in the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: So very interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course, I should say there's a huge rumor going around about the August 1st price drop.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: That seems a little soon.
[SPEAKER_05]: If they were going to do it then, they might as well have announced it at PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Blackwolf has an interesting thought.
[SPEAKER_05]: He says they might announce it at Penny Arcade Expo.
[SPEAKER_06]: They might announce it... Take it directly to the fans.
[SPEAKER_06]: They'll love it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Announce it at PAX or now there's X07, you know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I heard they canceled it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, well... No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe I'm thinking... I'm thinking they're...
[SPEAKER_05]: Event over in Europe.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is that it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it's Exo 7.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think that's happening this year.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, what about Tokyo Game Show then?
[SPEAKER_05]: That could be.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: You never know.
[SPEAKER_06]: They have plenty of time to do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Especially waiting until closer to Halo and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think they're in trouble.
[SPEAKER_06]: Another thing I was going to mention real quick though, there was also Capcom was saying that they speculate that
[SPEAKER_06]: The PlayStation 3 will drop price again.
[SPEAKER_06]: And there's also speculation that I know Europe was supposed to be getting the 120 gig PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: And can you imagine if they do the same thing here?
[SPEAKER_06]: And so it's going to be every few months or so you're going to get price drop, clearance, new system come out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_06]: So GamePro, on top of their game apparently, did a little article of seven games that mysteriously were missing from E3.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: which is full of inaccuracies.
[SPEAKER_06]: So let's just go down the list, shall we?
[SPEAKER_06]: Grand Theft Auto 4.
[SPEAKER_06]: God, where was Grand Theft Auto 4 other than the PlayStation press conference, the Xbox press conference, the Take-Two press conference where they did a walkthrough demo of the thing?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it wasn't there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Spore.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, Spore was there.
[SPEAKER_06]: They showed off a few more things on it and had a little press demo for it.
[SPEAKER_06]: God of War 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, that wasn't there.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll give them that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see what other stuff they're talking about here.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm surprised there was no God of War 3, but I guess they always have Heavenly Sword.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's probably so far off in development.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, true.
[SPEAKER_05]: So was Halo 3 when they first started cock-teasing us with it?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: A new Rainbow Six game?
[SPEAKER_06]: They're saying the successor to Rainbow Six Vegas?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, the last game just came out, what, a few weeks ago?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think they need to be teasing the new one yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Especially if it goes the way of Splinter Cell Conviction.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was another thing out of the Microsoft conference.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's exclusive to Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_06]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, Prince of Persia 4.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't really think we need a new Prince of Persia game since we have, like, kind of, uh, Assassin's Creed kind of fills that void there for a little bit.
[SPEAKER_08]: We haven't needed a Prince of Persia game since, you know, what, 1994?
[SPEAKER_08]: At all, ever.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: The new ones are okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Peter Jackson's Halo.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because they didn't have enough Halo content with the gift cards and the 360 and everything else.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Final Fantasy XIII.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, they announced it wasn't going to be there anyways.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: How about some other stuff?
[SPEAKER_06]: How about, was it that new Rygar game that was supposed to be out there?
[SPEAKER_06]: Why didn't they show that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because, I mean, that was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Where the fuck is Animal Crossing Wii?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, actually, Rygar was Tecmo, and I don't believe Tecmo was there.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, that's probably why that wasn't there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Where the fuck is Animal Crossing on the Wii?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's still being worked on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Work faster!
[SPEAKER_06]: Done by the guy apparently who did the Mii Channel.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_06]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: How much do you want to bet there's no Mii support in the game whatsoever?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, the irony.
[SPEAKER_05]: Blackwolf would like to point out there were no console games for Squeenix.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was all DS and PSP.
[SPEAKER_05]: So nothing on the console.
[SPEAKER_05]: Where the hell's that Final Fantasy game on the Wii then?
[SPEAKER_05]: Wasn't there a Crystal Chronicles game coming out at launch?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_05]: What happened?
[SPEAKER_05]: Where's the Dragon Quest slashy slash game?
[SPEAKER_08]: Who cares about Crystal Chronicles?
[SPEAKER_05]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: This year, the time waster was waiting in traffic to get to your next appointment or get to more games.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right, because last year we were in Santa Monica because of the whole, you know, all games arena thing that was going on.
[SPEAKER_05]: And driving to E3 was a bitch every day.
[SPEAKER_05]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, and I mean, the traffic around was really horrible.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, two miles from all the hotels and the show floor.
[SPEAKER_02]: and there were no press rooms at the Barker Hangar.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you couldn't get on the internet.
[SPEAKER_02]: You couldn't report anything from there.
[SPEAKER_02]: You had to go back to the Fairmont Hotel which was probably the farthest hotel away because that's where the press room was.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if you were on a deadline like for the working press like newspapers and other internet sites had deadlines, they had to spend a lot of time going back and forth, back and forth just so they could do their work.
[SPEAKER_02]: So
[SPEAKER_02]: The ESA knows that the physical location was really the only downside.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think if they consolidated it more and still only invited about 3,000 or 4,000 people, it'd still be a great show.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, couldn't they just rent one small part of the LA Convention Center?
[SPEAKER_05]: I have a hard time believing LA Convention Center is the only place in the area.
[SPEAKER_05]: Couldn't they find another convention center in an LA suburb to do it in?
[SPEAKER_05]: Or move it to Vegas, like I've heard suggested?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, Lawrence Young was telling me Long Beach Convention Center, maybe.
[SPEAKER_02]: All I know is that you're going to have to bring us as your crew next year, Bobby.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: That loophole will probably be very closed next year.
[SPEAKER_05]: We shall see what happens.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe they can open it up a little more in Vegas.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_05]: Really quickly, what were your thoughts?
[SPEAKER_05]: You got to walk the show floor.
[SPEAKER_05]: What impressed the hell out of you?
[SPEAKER_05]: What disappointed the hell out of you?
[SPEAKER_02]: What impressed me was Burnout Paradise.
[SPEAKER_02]: In fact, on my show, Plug Plug, since it's not your five-year anniversary, I'm going to plug my show.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Everyone has a podcast.
[SPEAKER_05]: You might as well say it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I interviewed the producer for Burnout Paradise.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're really doing some really interesting things with the online multiplayer, and they have added enough to the game itself that it's going to be a great game for communities to play.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be a great game to play online.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm really hyped for Burnout Paradise.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was already hyped for Burnout before you said that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now I'm even more hyped.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, they're doing seamless online multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's no lobby.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's an open world, and people just drop in on the open world, and then the host says...
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, you want a race?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, boom, and he starts the race.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like Test Drive Unlimited.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's talk a little bit about Rock Band because I did get to play it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I played it four times on the drums just to make sure that all my rants about the drum peripheral were founded or unfounded or whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: I still don't like the placement of the pads.
[SPEAKER_02]: Everything else is fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: and it does feel like you're playing a drum set except for the fact that your arms are in the wrong place.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, the thing is, I was the only one there who had a problem with the drum set because the harmonics people and the MTV people, which were extremely nice to me, they were very receptive to me, they're like, oh, you're a drummer.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, you like that drum peripheral, huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it's awesome, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_02]: And I go, not really.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: Good for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: I talked to the marketing manager at EA.
[SPEAKER_02]: I talked to a guy who works for MTV.
[SPEAKER_02]: I talked to one of the Harmonix developers, and I said, you know, the pads are great.
[SPEAKER_02]: The hardware is great.
[SPEAKER_02]: The UI is fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: The placement sucks of the pads.
[SPEAKER_06]: I heard that they were adjustable, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it's not just that.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the fact that the note chart has the hi-hat on the second drum from the left, and usually you have to cross your arms for that.
[SPEAKER_02]: My biggest issue was the far right drum, which they used as the symbol a lot of times.
[SPEAKER_02]: All the drums could change at any time.
[SPEAKER_02]: They weren't really married to one thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: But having to pull back on your arm instead of go forward, which is the natural motion of your arm, that took a while to get used to, and so I would overshoot the pad all the time.
[SPEAKER_02]: And also, they have the Xbox guide button right in the center, and I hit it like three times bringing up the guide while playing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh-oh, you pulled a Peter Moore.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: and so finally one of the harmonics chicks was like, I'll sing Tom Sawyer, come on, let's go.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it was fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: I will still get it because I'm a whore for that stuff, but I still don't like the placement and I'm going to be very vocal about the placement of the pads.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let me ask you real quick, I don't want to take up too much time, but since you were there, I do want to pick your brain on some of these things.
[SPEAKER_05]: How did it compare to last year's E3, and how did it seem to be received by the audience as a whole?
[SPEAKER_05]: Were people enjoying the fact that it was more of an exclusive event, or did people miss the glitz and glamour and the booth babes of yonder past?
[SPEAKER_02]: Everybody I spoke to that attended E3 loved the new E3.
[SPEAKER_02]: The people who didn't like E3, some of them had good reasons.
[SPEAKER_02]: The more indie games scene, they didn't like it because they were shut out.
[SPEAKER_02]: and they kind of used the lack of the booth babe, the lack of the glitz as part of it, but really it was about they couldn't be a part of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: They were not invited to even exhibit.
[SPEAKER_02]: The ESA wouldn't even let them there.
[SPEAKER_02]: But everybody that was there loved the fact that you could have a conversation with people on the show floor.
[SPEAKER_02]: You could walk up to anything and play it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Square Enix might not have liked it because every time I walked by their set of kiosks, nobody was playing the games.
[SPEAKER_02]: But
[SPEAKER_02]: Other than that, everybody loved it except for the physical distance between things.
[SPEAKER_02]: I missed a few appointments because I couldn't get there in time.
[SPEAKER_02]: I did not get to see Fallout 3 because I was 20 minutes late because of traffic.
[SPEAKER_05]: Question from Rob D in chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ask Bobby if he thinks that E3 can stay alive this way.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it did its job.
[SPEAKER_02]: It did.
[SPEAKER_02]: It did its job admirably.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whether the ESA will actually continue doing it in this way, that I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if they made enough money doing it this way or not.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyone else have a question for Bobby who got to go there and actually be at E3?
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess it was kind of bad that I didn't accept my invite.
[SPEAKER_02]: You could have had a cameraman and a sound guy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Damn it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki's making pouty face at Jamie right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wish we were a TV show.
[SPEAKER_08]: However, I did get to sleep a lot, so that was good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not really, I had to work.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, and the day you all were at E3, I was on jury duty, so I had one of the website's mobile version on refresh on my cell phone to follow the press conferences.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was sad and pathetic.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was my E3.
[SPEAKER_06]: I did that at work.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: They'd only say that because it didn't have the glitz, it didn't have the glamour, and really, to be honest, like the press conferences, everybody surrendered.
[SPEAKER_02]: Usually E3 is about who had the best press conference, and all of them said, we don't want the best press conference this year.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're not going for that, and so that might be where a part of that came from.
[SPEAKER_02]: But no, I mean, in terms of seeing things, getting things done, getting contacts, networking, all that stuff, this E3 was the best out of the 11 that I went to.
[SPEAKER_02]: and I even said that on the Xbox Live Marketplace video that I'm apparently all over.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was going to say, a perfect example of that would have been the Konami press conference where it's like, yeah, two DDRs, Silent Hill 5, go get your press kit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, what's up with that, Bobby?
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, now since there's less people at E3, you have a bigger chance of being a media whore, and Bobby, you really got some media whoring done this year.
[SPEAKER_05]: I understand you're on a banner ad for, what, game trailers?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: You show up in Xbox, what video in Xbox Live Marketplace are you on?
[SPEAKER_02]: the on10.net E3 show floor wrap up video because I was with the TV channel that should be renamed Name Nameless and I was with All Games even before then I've known Laura Foy for many many years so when she saw me in the empty square on Wednesday she came over and asked me a few questions and apparently I get more air time than a frag doll on this thing but I was on that MTV Latin America made me sign a waiver because they filmed me playing Tom Sawyer on the drums huh
[SPEAKER_02]: and then Hudson, their video crew, the same ones that made the Bomberman video that's on YouTube that says Act Zero sucked ass and we know it.
[SPEAKER_02]: They came around and did something and it was really stupid.
[SPEAKER_02]: If they used my thing, the question was, it was this chick and she goes, okay, here's the question, games or girls?
[SPEAKER_02]: And I look at her because it's the most absurd question I've ever heard in my life
[SPEAKER_02]: Act Zero, I'll Take Girls, For Sure
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I think my response was games have pause buttons.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, care to rebuttal?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I have something that involves a button.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or even better, you just go, what, you're offering?
[SPEAKER_08]: Heart, Bobby.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, well, Bobby, thanks so much for the call and for the perspective from someone who was actually there.
[SPEAKER_05]: And congrats on, I'm sure, what was going to end up being a lot of exposure for you and your show and all that good stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: So congratulations.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Until next time, my friend.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, later.
[SPEAKER_05]: See ya.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very good call.
[SPEAKER_05]: We always like hearing from Bobby.
[SPEAKER_05]: More calls, please.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who is this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello, Orange Lounge Radio land.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is a guy who's disappeared for far too long.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ah, is this VXJasonXV?
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Howdy, how are you?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm, uh...
[SPEAKER_04]: I listen to the whole thing while I was working way too many damn hours at work
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh, belated happy birthday to Orange Lounge Radio, belated happy birthday to you, Rob, and belated happy birthday to myself, because I am a whore for that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you, where's my present?
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, I don't know, where's mine?
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, real reason, Ace Combat 6, holy cow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ah, here's the game we didn't talk about yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: The, uh, yeah, no kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: The, um...
[SPEAKER_04]: Last Monday I do believe it is I got a new monitor for my birthday and I have a nice little consolidation thing going on because it's my computer monitor for two different computers as well as my Xbox 360 screen and it does high definition.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm finally running my 360 in 720p and a lot of things are looking a hell of a lot better than standard components.
[SPEAKER_04]: and I finally managed to get a hold of the demo from the E3 category and I played it and holy cow that game looks beautiful I don't know if it's satellite imagery high resolution satellite imagery or low level aircraft imagery of the landscapes but oh man they're doing a beautiful job with that that game was so fun just to look at and it played so well still I've loved that series ever since Air Combat on the Playstation
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't like simulations like Flight Simulator.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love arcade-style games, and Air Combat and Ace Combat have always been that, and they are doing a good job continuing the series.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not as free.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of teetering towards the more realistic flying, but still arcade dogfighting.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't have anything else to say.
[SPEAKER_04]: I am buying that game the day it comes out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, shame on you guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I watched a couple of the trailers, uh,
[SPEAKER_04]: Skate looks pretty boring, but I think that goes back to the whole simulation versus arcade thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: The project, Prove Yourself, crap, Tony Hawk game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tony Hawk's Proving Ground.
[SPEAKER_04]: Proving Ground, thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mixing all those words up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Proving Ground seems to be going right down the same path, again, expanding on a few more elements, and it looks like it's a very true-to-form continuation of the series.
[SPEAKER_04]: What else did I look at?
[SPEAKER_04]: Beautiful Katamari told me absolutely nothing new, but I don't know yet whether I'm going to like it if it's the same thing all over again or not.
[SPEAKER_04]: The music was kind of... I don't know how to describe it, but the music is kind of making me teeter on the side that I might not be caring for that game too much.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bomberman Live... Oh man, I haven't played a Bomberman game in forever.
[SPEAKER_04]: The trailers and all of the media that Microsoft posted was really fun to look at and hopefully the rest of the year and into the first half of the next year when all this stuff is going to really all be coming out is going to not be too much of a drain on my banking account.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jason, I know you've been a music game fan for a long time obviously because you've been with OLR for a long time and Actdeft brings up a very interesting question in chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wonder if Jason will talk about Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_05]: What do you think about Rock Band?
[SPEAKER_04]: I...
[SPEAKER_04]: We went over this over a little bit in the forums, so all you people who aren't a part, go read.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's always great to do that in between shows.
[SPEAKER_04]: The aesthetics of cramming everything in for multiple person play seems to be really, really off.
[SPEAKER_04]: The lyrics are probably going to be the most underused portion of that game, and for good reason.
[SPEAKER_04]: Less people sing than sit there and play a guitar or a drum or anything else.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't really know too much about the drum.
[SPEAKER_04]: Four versus five is kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: Guitar Hero goes five while Guitar Freaks is three.
[SPEAKER_04]: The drum peripheral is going to be four while Drum Mania was five.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've never liked console Drum Mania.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll play it because I like Drum Mania in general, but I've played the arcade version of MGL.
[SPEAKER_04]: The console version wasn't very faithful.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't like cramming my arms that close together.
[SPEAKER_04]: What Bobby was saying was just kind of driving that point home again.
[SPEAKER_04]: bass I don't know I don't think I've got enough hands on with it on guitar here too but the vocals are going to be the lowest point other than that I'm still recognizing a couple of the songs which makes me happy enough that I'll actually have something to play and it looks like it's going to be fun you know for a game that's changing companies it looks like it's still going down a very good path for the general makeup and play of the game and fun is really what it's all about right?
[SPEAKER_04]: hell yeah good music good game all right
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, Jason, we've got to let you go to get probably about one more call in here, but thanks so much for the call.
[SPEAKER_05]: We appreciate it, okay?
Yep.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_04]: See you, guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, we always appreciate Jason when he gives us a call.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll do about one more call.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know we've got a lot of people trying to get through tonight, but we also want to wrap up pretty soon here, so let's do at least one more call.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, you are on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's GS68.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, GS68.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_01]: Um...
[SPEAKER_01]: Basically, I read about Ghost Squad coming out for the Wii, and that just reminded me about the arcade version.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry, you heard about what coming out for the Wii?
[SPEAKER_01]: Ghost Squad for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: And one thing that's always bugged me about the arcade version is that, like, I went to the Philippines, and most of the Ghost Squad machines there have card slots, but, like, here in California, like, none of the machines have card slots, so I
[SPEAKER_01]: I can only, like, go up to level 4 on the missions and only get... And I don't get a whole lot of stuff as much as on the card slots and machines.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, like... I'm sorry, you cut out a little bit there, so I'm sorry, what was the question out of that?
[SPEAKER_01]: Uh, like, yeah, like... One thing that's bugged me about that game, the arcade game, is that... Like, in the US, the...
[SPEAKER_01]: Like, almost none of the machines in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_01]: have car slots, but if I go to any other country with that game, like, the machines usually have car slots.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like, I went to the Philippines earlier this year, and most of their machines there had car slots, which is nice, because, like, I get to have, like, more levels and features and stuff, and I just don't wonder why they don't, like, for games like that and the
[SPEAKER_01]: Why... Like, why don't...
[SPEAKER_05]: I think if you're talking about as far as the arcade scene goes and why is it that they have the cards in some places and not in others, I think it just has to do with the arcade scene in general here.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think there's enough of a scene to support that type of technology here.
[SPEAKER_05]: And obviously Konami and DDR is one thing that comes to my mind like that and everything they're doing with EMUs overseas and things.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's just that Japanese has more of an arcade culture now
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I look at Asian arcades and they have a lot of cool stuff like... There are pachinko places in the US, by the way.
[SPEAKER_05]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, hey, anything you want to share about your thoughts with E3?
[SPEAKER_05]: Was there anything that really got you excited at E3?
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't really catch.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wasn't really caught up with E3.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't read much about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, hopefully you learned stuff here tonight by listening to the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hope we could educate some folks.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, hey, thanks so much for the call, GS60.
[SPEAKER_05]: We really appreciate it, okay?
[SPEAKER_01]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_05]: You too.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that's going to about do it because we're running almost an hour 40 for this segment so we really need to switch back over and wrap things up so I'm sorry to those calls we didn't get to tonight but we'll also take more calls next week I'm sure we always do so we're going to go around now and ask if there's any last minute stories here in studio any last minute stories I have a couple actually go for it this is more European news coming to Xbox Live Arcade there was Bomberman and Yaya Kung Fu on the 18th it'll be out July
[SPEAKER_08]: Also, the fifth Harry Potter game demo is on Xbox Live Arcade in the UK.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just for the record, it is out here as well.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, but it's actually supposed to take up 2.55% of the 20 gig hard drive.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the Lost Planet PC is getting Mega Man.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_08]: A Mega Man patch for Lost Planet PC.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, if that's it, then Loki, anything you want to share?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, there's some interesting stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: IGN just did their Week in Review podcast, I guess, and one of the things that they mentioned is Rock Band coming to the Wii in 2008.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that's interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Another interesting thing caught in, I guess, a trailer for Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_06]: Brawl is, I guess, Bulbin from...
[SPEAKER_06]: The Zelda series is going to be either a assist trophy character or a playable character.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry?
[SPEAKER_06]: Bulbin.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like one of those... I don't know if they're elves or what.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some sort of enemy from the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anywho, other interesting things...
[SPEAKER_06]: Simple Series, one of my favorite things to talk about.
[SPEAKER_06]: D3's lineup there.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're releasing their first two volumes on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: Volume 1 looks like a kart racing game, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the other one looks like a frog jumping game.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hopefully those make their way out over here at some point.
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course, one thing we can't forget.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know my wife might be looking forward to this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nitro Bike was announced for the Wii by Ubisoft, and it's being developed by Leftfield Productions, the creators of the classic Excitebike 64.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's kind of like, I guess, Excite Truck, but with bikes.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, Excitebike.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some other interesting things.
[SPEAKER_06]: One game we've talked about here before, 2 Mickey Fighters.
[SPEAKER_06]: and DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_06]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: As we get into, because, you know, now E3 was in July and not May, so there's a little less time before the fall rush.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'll be looking forward to sharing that all with you.
[SPEAKER_05]: And speaking of the fall, you know, we hit our 250th episode this fall, if you can believe that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Lots of fun stuff in store, but we're not going to do anything special for it because, you know, we did the 200th show last year and the 5th year anniversary of this show.
[SPEAKER_05]: We don't want to celebrate ourselves too much, but it certainly is a milestone that's interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Every day is a celebration.
[SPEAKER_08]: Every day is a new celebration of life.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, Loki, I noticed Loki's watching the Silent Hill Arcade videos on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_05]: It looks nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: Doesn't it look hot?
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you see the pyramid head thing?
[SPEAKER_06]: Uh...
[SPEAKER_05]: Watch the beginning of Part B. It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I'm watching the beginning of Part 2 right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, it's in there then.
[SPEAKER_05]: You'll see it.
[SPEAKER_05]: See?
[SPEAKER_05]: Pyramid Head goes, Slice.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're gonna die.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then he goes, Slice.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then right when it's about to hit the guy's head, it switches back to the day.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or whatever you want to call it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I thought you said you weren't spoiling it for our listeners.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, I did.
[SPEAKER_08]: Robbie Meany, bud.
[SPEAKER_05]: You need to watch it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't spoil anything.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's on IGN.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll watch it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It would be cool, though, if they brought it to the Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it looks like these gun games are going to be taken off.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dan and I had an idea a while back.
Point blank Wii.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, you remember the Biohazard Gun Survivor, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: And we got it over here as Resident Evil Gun Survivor and they took out the gun support.
[SPEAKER_08]: You had to play it with a controller.
[SPEAKER_08]: We were thinking back in the day how would the Dreamcast...
[SPEAKER_08]: You remember the Dreamcast gun had a controller on it, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_08]: Couldn't they do something like that with the Wii?
[SPEAKER_08]: Use the controller on it to do your motion, move back and forth, and then shoot with the gun?
[SPEAKER_08]: They could easily do those games.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, it's kind of the way they did it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Resident Evil 2 Arcade, you used your actual gun as your direction.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: that was kind of cool too and then you got to shoot people dead here's one other game that came out of E3 I didn't hear any other news on but there's a new Trauma Center game that's going to come out for the Wii and this one actually supports widescreen and looks pretty and has new characters I'm very excited about a new Trauma Center game for the Wii because Trauma Center is awesome alright, what are you laughing about?
[SPEAKER_06]: they should have a game they should have like a game for Silent Hill Konami, hear me out on this I think you've got a hit with this
[SPEAKER_06]: You know how these sim games and stuff like, you know, pets and dogs and cats and stuff's all really popular?
[SPEAKER_06]: They should have a Pyramid Head game where you just, you know, you take care of Pyramid Head or you are Pyramid Head and you feed him corpses.
[SPEAKER_06]: You feed him corpses and you can, you know, feed him, let him rape stuff, you know, and you can slice people with the blade.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sometimes I think we take our Pyramid Head love a little bit too far on this program.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if it's just me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, let's go around and get everybody's final thought.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, go ahead and start us off tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: My final thought is there's going to be more announcements coming out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not everything gets announced at E3.
[SPEAKER_06]: God's sake, most people nowadays have their own gamer days and shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: My final thought is I twisted my ankle earlier and it kind of hurts.
[SPEAKER_05]: Owie.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know I need to.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_08]: Reject false conventions.
[SPEAKER_05]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_00]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production For more information on our live and podcast programs visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com See you next week!