[SPEAKER_00]: Tonight, July 8th, 2007, the PlayStation 3 might be getting a price cut in the name of E3, notable games may not even show up at E3, and lots of tunes are dying over a new advertisement in World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello everybody out there on the internet and welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: We are that radio program dedicated to video games, video gaming, gamer culture, and the gamer lifestyle.
[SPEAKER_02]: My name is Rob Roberts and joining me as always, say hello to DarkSakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: What, huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: How are you doing?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm here, aren't I?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, you finally saw Transformers today?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, verdict?
[SPEAKER_03]: I have a major female boner for Ironhide now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob Williams, let's go!
[SPEAKER_02]: Also joining us, I will not be going on a date with Techmaster Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because your wife might disapprove of that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_02]: Probably not.
[SPEAKER_02]: She might like it, actually.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_02]: How's your week been?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's been good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, you saw Transformers last week and told us all about it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Have you seen anything new this week?
[SPEAKER_01]: No.
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, I meant to see Transformers again this week, but I got lazy.
[SPEAKER_01]: We got out of work early on the 3rd, and I was like, you know, I could go see Transformers again.
[SPEAKER_01]: But then I got out to my car and it was like hot and I was like, I just want to go home and sit in the air conditioning.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's been very hot here in Sacramento where our show is based.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like 106, 107 this week has been crazy.
[SPEAKER_02]: At least we don't have humidity.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, you'd think we were a movie podcast or something, but we're actually not.
[SPEAKER_02]: We talk about video games, so we're going to start off tonight's program as we always do, talking about How Was Your Gaming Week.
[SPEAKER_02]: But first, I want to introduce our chat room.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's over at chat.orangelongeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: We do tape live Sunday nights at 6 o'clock, and interesting things always happen if you're listening live, such as if you listen tonight, we had to do two takes of our intro because I made a big boo-boo.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if you want to hear the whole show, you've got to listen live Sunday nights at 6 o'clock Pacific Standard Time at OrangeLondonRadio.com on our live 365 feed.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you can always participate in our chat room, chat.OrangeLondonRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll also be opening up our Skype line later on.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's also a telephone number, an 877 number you can call in to.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we'll get those calls a little later on in the program.
[SPEAKER_02]: But first, DarkSakura is going to tell us all about her gaming week.
[SPEAKER_03]: I had one.
[SPEAKER_03]: I did try to play some World of Warcraft and then I got tired of updating all that crap.
[SPEAKER_03]: So all I did was play a little bit of Pokemans.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was really it.
[SPEAKER_02]: How's Pokemans been going?
[SPEAKER_02]: We had an email actually last week asking how you were doing on your Pokemans.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm hardly doing.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what I answered.
[SPEAKER_03]: I played a crap ton of pinball.
[SPEAKER_03]: We got too many machines.
[SPEAKER_03]: We finally got rid of Retardo Johnny Mnemonic.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we got rid of Guns N' Roses.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have a Simpsons pinball party now, which is really freaking cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: and we have World Cup Soccer, which was my favorite machine ever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, my first time playing it, I cracked a billion points, which just goes to show that my mad skills at that game have only diminished very slightly.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because you didn't break two billion.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've almost gotten there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was really, really good at that machine.
[SPEAKER_03]: I also played the Spider-Man pinball today.
[SPEAKER_03]: The new one is really, really good.
[SPEAKER_03]: and I kept hitting Sandman over and over and over again.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is what you get for being a bad, bad guy in a movie.
[SPEAKER_03]: The end.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_01]: And less dramatic, please.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was good.
[SPEAKER_01]: We finally hooked up.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, we have a temporary setup for the 360 LAN systems at my work now.
[SPEAKER_01]: So we tried a few test games of Saints Row and it's fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: I can't wait.
[SPEAKER_01]: The only problem is right now we have
[SPEAKER_01]: Some of the systems have the patch for the multiplayer in it so that there's no lag, and some of them don't, so we ran into a few issues with that.
[SPEAKER_01]: But one thing that's awesome in the game is the pimp slap power-up that you can get.
[SPEAKER_01]: Basically, you run around with a pimp hat on, you can backhand people and fling them across the entire stage, which is awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: Um, the only problem is the game only has three multiplayer maps, which kind of sucks, and, you know, I've been kind of spoiled with Infinite Sprint and, um, Grand Theft Auto, so.
[SPEAKER_01]: It'll hold us over until, uh, Grand Theft Auto 4.
[SPEAKER_01]: Um, been playing lots of Final Fantasy on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know why, but I've been playing it, and it's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_01]: Just finished, um, was actually...
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_01]: First you have to fight Starscream, and then you eventually have to fight Blackout, then you have to fight them both together.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, the little drones that they throw down in the middle were actually harder than Starscream and Blackout, which is stupid.
[SPEAKER_01]: But, I don't know, the whole game is very glitchy, and I highly recommend not playing it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I will play it through to get some more achievement points, but I'm going to quickly sell this.
[SPEAKER_01]: But you did give this game a favorable review last week, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: It was okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: Some of the missions are alright.
[SPEAKER_01]: I haven't played too many of the Decepticon missions.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm still playing through the Autobots because I want to play the worst part of the game first and then play stuff where you have to blow up things.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I actually watched my friend play the first mission of...
[SPEAKER_01]: The Decepticons, and it didn't look that much more fun, actually.
[SPEAKER_01]: It looked like it sucked, so I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's just a really bad game, I guess, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_02]: TigerClaw, a big, big Transformers nerd, has some advice for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, Loki, to beat the drones, you have to throw things at them first.
[SPEAKER_01]: I understand that, and that's what I was doing, because there's, obviously, each drone has the same damn, you know, pattern to them, and I was throwing stuff, and it wasn't doing anything.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, it was dumb.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: now this happens though sometimes we do change our opinions on video games and not something that's really talked about a whole lot you know like sometimes this happens with movies you may watch a movie like one time and you didn't like it but then like the second time you watch it you see something you didn't see before like sometimes that happens with games too can you think of other games that you've ever like changed your mind on after playing them either favorably or unfavorably um hmm I can't think of anything offhand maybe like Guitar Hero you know it was cool in the beginning and it kind of sucks now
[SPEAKER_01]: But then again, I'm just not really in... Music games for me right now, I just can't dedicate enough time to them.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: But, um... I would say World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_01]: I didn't get into it the first time I played it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Maybe Final Fantasy XI?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, maybe.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because after a while, you know, it started just... After two years for me.
[SPEAKER_01]: After you finally, you know, you get done with the low-level partying stuff, and then you realize, oh, yeah, this kind of sucks now.
[SPEAKER_01]: But, um... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's just...
[SPEAKER_01]: It's just something you don't... Activision is pulling an Ubisoft, is what they're doing.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're really letting me down with a lot of their games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or we talked about this last week briefly, Nintendogs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, I think it was the last week or two weeks ago, we talked about how we all loved Nintendogs when we first played it, and then we actually played the full, full game and was like, wow, this got old quick.
[SPEAKER_01]: And really, I can't blame Activision, I guess, too much for these games, because they're not developing them, but... Stop publishing crappy games.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, seriously, I...
[SPEAKER_01]: I was discussing something with you guys off-air earlier, and it's like, stop publishing crappy games.
[SPEAKER_01]: Dumb ideas.
[SPEAKER_02]: What else was I going to say?
[SPEAKER_02]: I was just thinking that you don't really see that a lot in the review game industry, where people kind of change their minds over time.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not really addressed a lot, but it can happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, anything else for your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_02]: My gaming week wasn't anything too spectacular because I was still playing some World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've been working on the Battlestar Galactica themed PvP guild because we aren't just nerds playing World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have to take it one step further and incorporate Battlestar Galactica into our guild.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's like double nerd.
[SPEAKER_02]: and so I've been playing a lot of World of Warcraft but also the new game I checked out this week I did check out Missile Command on Xbox Live Arcade because I do love the old old 2600 version and the old arcade version to some extent as well and you know the Atari ports are coming out pretty good you know they're cheap they're five bucks and you know the enhanced graphics are actually really good it doesn't feel like kind of like the same type of graphics they actually when they enhanced the graphics they enhanced it for widescreen mode as well so it kind of changes the element of Missile Command and
[SPEAKER_02]: The only thing I don't really like is that I want to be able to control the game with a mouse.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't like using the stick to control the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Missile Command was the type of game that was meant for a frickin' trackball or a mouse, which is essentially an inverted trackball, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's why I cannot play that game with a thumbstick.
[SPEAKER_02]: I need some type of mouse or trackball control to really play Missile Command.
[SPEAKER_02]: But as far as the presentation, graphics, sound, gameplay, it's Missile Command.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it's cheap, so it's fine.
[SPEAKER_01]: Rayman's Raving Rabbids
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I know!
[SPEAKER_02]: Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't like Silent Hill the first time I played it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And now I love it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's totally just one of those things where I saw something I didn't see before the first time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Driver 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Made peer pressure, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hate the game.
[SPEAKER_01]: I still hate the game, but it's fun to play.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, Burnout?
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought it was kind of stupid at first.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then when I saw how big explosions could be, I was like, I like explosions and wrecks.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I really like them in my video games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Especially when that's the whole point.
[SPEAKER_01]: I had just the opposite.
[SPEAKER_01]: I liked it when it first came out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, actually, I think the one that really stood out for me was Burnout Takedown.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then Revenge is kind of eh, it's okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then, you know, the newer ones are just kind of eh.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course, our chat room wants to chime in with their suggestions.
[SPEAKER_02]: JV Mon says, Katamari gets old really fast, like within minutes.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, the PSP one.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's a perfect example.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: SSJ100 Matt is commenting on Missile Command.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who needs a port when you got the real thing?
[SPEAKER_02]: I finally fixed my Atari 400.
[SPEAKER_02]: for the enhanced mode.
[SPEAKER_02]: For the enhanced mode is totally high def graphics and Ravar music and all that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's only $5, which if you think about how many quarters you popped into Missile Command back in the day, $5 is not too bad of a deal.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it just depends.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some people aren't into the old retro classics.
[SPEAKER_02]: I am, so it's worth it to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: But if you're not into the retro upgrades, then there's probably a lot on Xbox Live you don't like.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I also wanted to say I played Luminous
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, there's some pretty decent stuff in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh, a couple recycles from the old Luminous games, which isn't much of a surprise, but some new stuff as well, so.
[SPEAKER_01]: I did play a dance game this week, I forgot.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, what's that?
[SPEAKER_01]: Uh, I briefly played Neon FM, which, uh... Wow.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, on the PC or something?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, I got leaked in there.
[SPEAKER_01]: Uh, but, uh, well, it never got made, let me put it that way.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: It would have been pretty cool if they had the dance pads for it and stuff, it's just, you know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Uh, I guess, well, God, you want to keep interrupting my gaming week?
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't think of...
[SPEAKER_02]: Luminous, Missile Command, World of Warcraft GameTab
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe a little bit, but I'm not allowed to discuss it because I get called a whore and a sellout when I do.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Be a whore and a sellout.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's up to you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then I did play a little bit of GameTap this week as well, yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: And what did you play on GameTap?
[SPEAKER_02]: Old Atari 2600 games.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's one of my things.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've been going back through leaderboards trying to get high scores on stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: I play BurgerTime, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rob likes to score.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remind.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, sorry.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was going to say, remind me I need to loan you Salmon Mac Season 1.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you don't need to.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have it on GameTap.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just haven't played it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Then play it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I need to.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, anyway, so that's that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's go to some housekeeping, and then we'll get into gaming news.
[SPEAKER_02]: Housekeeping tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: SacAnime, we mentioned last week we'll be going to SacAnime.
[SPEAKER_02]: We only hit a little kink, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: We don't know if we're actually doing a panel at SacAnime, because communication has not been so great.
[SPEAKER_02]: But that's okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Things happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was very last minute.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know at least DarkSakura is going to SacAnime, and I'm going as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we'll be around.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if you're going to be there, say hi.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, I don't know if you're going or not.
[SPEAKER_02]: When is it?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's next weekend at the Doubletree.
[SPEAKER_02]: Next weekend.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_02]: As opposed to Quadruple Tree.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, I got an idea.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's name it Tree.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, Double Tree.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was holding up for Quadruple Tree.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow, that's really it.
[SPEAKER_02]: We just want to mention that we'll be appearing there one way or another, even if we're just walking the floor like the rest of you.
[SPEAKER_02]: and, again, we're always looking for anime conventions in California in the West Coast area that we can get to to come say hi because we love doing live panels and that's like, you know, we like doing our show live.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if you noticed, but we've recorded live.
[SPEAKER_02]: We always have the chat room and it's a whole other thing to have the studio audience.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't you love when everybody's staring right at you, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_02]: Isn't that the best way to record a show?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm used to it all the time.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's get into some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who wants to start us off tonight?
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess I could.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: If I got to.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, yes, you got it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, there is an expected price cut coming for the PlayStation 3, supposed to reduce by $100.
[SPEAKER_03]: There was an ad put out by Circuit City saying that it was going to be dropping.
[SPEAKER_03]: Right now it's $600, but I don't know, $500 might make it actually sell better, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's supposed to be in conjunction with E3.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's going to be this year's E3 speech.
[SPEAKER_02]: $499 U.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: dollars.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the rest of us are like, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Does that mean the other model is dropping to $399?
[SPEAKER_02]: What other model?
[SPEAKER_03]: They're not producing it anymore, are they?
[SPEAKER_02]: I got a collector's item, yo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Those bastards.
[SPEAKER_02]: Collector's item.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't even think of that because when I heard about the $100 price drop, I was like, oh, well, then the other one will be $399.
[SPEAKER_02]: That will be easily affordable.
[SPEAKER_02]: I forgot they got rid of that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sneaky bastards.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was all excited about this price drop too.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I guess everyone's doing it now.
[SPEAKER_01]: In fact, I think a few people, I remember seeing some scans of Target receipts where people are buying them for $4.99 already, so it's everywhere.
[SPEAKER_01]: But it's a secret!
[SPEAKER_01]: You're not supposed to know about this yet!
[SPEAKER_01]: Shh!
[SPEAKER_02]: God.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have to admit, though, I'm still not sold.
[SPEAKER_02]: $500 is still a lot for me.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're talking to a guy who's moving in a few weeks and has all those expenses, so I can't be thinking about video game expenses right now?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll just go over and play Jamie's.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know, people.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's collecting dust at my house anyway.
[SPEAKER_01]: And everyone's like, oh, well, that makes it more affordable.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm going to buy that instead of a 360.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, don't you think they're going to drop the price of the 360, too, to compete with this?
[SPEAKER_01]: Obviously.
[SPEAKER_01]: Otherwise, actually, they might leave it the same because...
[SPEAKER_01]: They feel it's competitive pricing still and stuff like that, but I'd hope that they drop the price to $360.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lots and lots of feedback in chatroom on this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ross Steel UT says, Price drop after less than a year, that's a problem.
[SPEAKER_02]: SSJ100Matt says, They can drop the price as much as they want, but people will still bitch.
[SPEAKER_02]: People bitched when the Wii was $50 more.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Ross Steel UT responds to that, True, if people had their way, they'd be free.
[SPEAKER_02]: and Sephiroth 1215 agrees we paid that $50 on the Wii for the crappy Wii Sports.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I don't know, see...
[SPEAKER_02]: As hardcore gamers, we look at Wii Sports and we go, eh, you know, the novelty wears off after a little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: But seriously, I know people that are not gamers that still all they talk about Wii Tennis.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like I was having dinner with some friends the other night who are not like the gamer crowd.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they were like, let's have a Wii party.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's get together and play Wii Tennis.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob, you have a Wii, don't you?
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's all get together and play.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so like it's still like a lot of fun for a lot of people.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just maybe not the hardcore audience who kind of, you know, got over it after a few months.
[SPEAKER_02]: JV Mon suggests $499 PlayStation 3 is better competition for the Elite 360
[SPEAKER_02]: Jorardimo says if PlayStation 3 dropped the price, I might buy one, even though there are still no games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hold out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hold out is all I can say.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, think about it.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're going to sucker you into buying it before the Holly season, and guess what's going to fucking come out later on?
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, look at that!
[SPEAKER_01]: It's the 6-axis controller with Rumble now!
[SPEAKER_01]: And now we're including them with the new systems.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oops, you already bought one, now you have to buy another controller too.
[SPEAKER_01]: Just fucking wait.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's no games really that are super huge coming out between now and Christmas anyways.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, wait until the fall.
[SPEAKER_01]: You can wait a few more months and just pick up the good games when they come out then.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I have a question for you guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: I already said I'm not a PlayStation 3 owner at this time, and this doesn't really change my opinion, but my question for you guys is, you guys have bought PlayStation 3s.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, you bought the old 499 model, which was the 20 gig.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jamie, you guys bought the deluxe one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you guys feel shafted by this?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: You don't feel like you got ripped off, even though they're dropping the... Because maybe you've had, what, nine months of good gameplay before that, or...
[SPEAKER_03]: Right.
[SPEAKER_03]: I got my PlayStation 3 first day, so I don't care.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wouldn't call it... I got my good out of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't really even care about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I got $100 off of it anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because we used our Discover card and got money back.
[SPEAKER_01]: I wouldn't call it good gameplay, but no, seriously, that's kind of one of my reasons why I'm telling people that they should hold off.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, I have my PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_01]: I have... I bought maybe like five games for it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I sold back most of those because...
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_01]: But that's the problem, though.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's only like a couple games, whereas the 360, I'm planning on buying a lot more than just a couple games.
[SPEAKER_01]: So that's a problem, because even if they do get you to buy the system, you're going to be waiting a while for some good games, especially if you're holding out for your Final Fantasy XIII or Metal Gear Solid 4.
[SPEAKER_01]: You plan on waiting about another, I don't know, almost nine months now until those games come out, if not longer.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, well, with this price cut on the PlayStation 3, I mean, there's a lot of possible factors for why this price cut is happening now.
[SPEAKER_02]: But could one of them be the pressure from the third-party companies?
[SPEAKER_02]: It also came out this week, just before the news of the price cut, that Sega made an interesting comment about the pricing of the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: One of the executives at Sega, Masano Medea, actually had this quote, quote,
[SPEAKER_02]: Name, brand, price, and software are what count.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is what he told Reuters in an interview.
[SPEAKER_02]: Quote, since it's getting difficult to make software availability a differentiating factor, superior marketing and pricing strategy will be the key for Sony.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_01]: I want to see them here because, you know, promises aren't getting us anywhere.
[SPEAKER_01]: Obviously, they promise all this shit, you know, that's supposed to be out at launch, never came out at launch.
[SPEAKER_01]: All these delays, all these third-party games getting delayed for the PlayStation 3 or just not coming out at all.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then, you know, at the same time, they need to have a strong Christmas or else they're doomed.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, because...
[SPEAKER_01]: Already, you know, the 360s had, you know, a couple strong Christmases already.
[SPEAKER_01]: And this is going to be the third strong one.
[SPEAKER_01]: They've got a really good lineup, especially with Halo 3, Grand Theft Auto 4, and God knows what other stuff's coming out around that time.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then the Wii, obviously, the Wii's going to take off like crazy at Christmas because you still can't find them.
[SPEAKER_01]: They really need to, because they're losing, you know, they're dropping behind a lot now.
[SPEAKER_01]: And if they don't, you know, pick it up,
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be hard.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, Matt, though, we are sitting just days away from E3 2007, and Sony pulled a pretty big trump card out of their hand at Game Developers Conference and really changed a lot of people's minds with Home and LittleBigPlanet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are they sitting on something else right now?
[SPEAKER_01]: I hope they are.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I really do, because I would like to see them be successful.
[SPEAKER_03]: A box of Crayolas.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't have much faith in Sony.
[SPEAKER_02]: Crash Bandicoot paint.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's that new Spyro game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was watching the ads for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry if all they have to release is Spyro as far as their games go, then...
[SPEAKER_02]: Macman makes an interesting quote, E3 will change everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it'll suck.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because we're not there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: Isn't all that same pressure still there this year?
[SPEAKER_02]: Has anything changed?
[SPEAKER_02]: People are still going to be making a lot of judgments based off of the cards that people lay on the table at E3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whether they're there or not, we're all on the internet now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you hear what Scott over at All Games is doing?
[SPEAKER_02]: They're going in there with a live camera that's going to sit on Scott's head so you can be at E3 with them.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just fucking nuts.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, if they think the pressure is gone from E3 because they locked it down like Fort Knox, you're mistaken.
[SPEAKER_01]: I understand why they... Critics are watching you.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, I understand why they did this, but E3 needs to succeed this year because this is kind of a whole new experiment for them to see, kind of changing things up and supposedly they're going to get more business done, but...
[SPEAKER_01]: Really, when you think about it, what kind of business can you get done at E3?
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, other than, you know, a lot of the press stuff where they're covering all these games and everything.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, is there really... I mean, granted us, I mean, we were only like three people at E3, maybe four or five or whatever.
[SPEAKER_01]: But, you know, obviously we can't see all of E3.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's impossible to cover everything in great detail.
[SPEAKER_01]: But, you know, these larger press outlets and stuff, it's a lot easier for them.
[SPEAKER_01]: But really, do you think there's stuff that they're just...
[SPEAKER_01]: Missing from E3?
[SPEAKER_02]: A lot of them just say what the game companies want them to say because they just copy-paste press releases anyway.
[SPEAKER_01]: So are we going to expect them to do any better work at these places?
[SPEAKER_01]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's still enough of the independent press getting in.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not as much as there should be.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not saying that bitterly, I promise.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I am.
[SPEAKER_02]: There is enough of the independent press getting in that are not going to be corporate whores.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, I'm extremely bitter.
[SPEAKER_01]: I found out with someone from our works going.
[SPEAKER_01]: Bastard.
[SPEAKER_01]: He's feeling it out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow, I had to say this in chat because now everybody's making plays on the E3 will change everything because now they're coming up with their own taglines.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kyle Snyder says, Dust Cap 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: This time it's not Dust Cap 1.
[SPEAKER_02]: Long running Orange Lingerie joke there.
[SPEAKER_02]: JV Mon says, Emodium AD will change everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have no idea what that's even supposed to mean, so forget it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm just excited.
[SPEAKER_01]: I can't wait to see the press releases and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: And also watching the conferences.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyways, another rumor that's supposedly coming out of the Sony press conference or speculation at least is that the 6-axis controller is getting rumble as well as touch sensitivity.
[SPEAKER_01]: It'll be interesting to see if they do that.
[SPEAKER_01]: They didn't really say what exactly it's going to be doing, but apparently that through...
[SPEAKER_01]: I guess different sections of the controller you'll be able to have touch sensitivity very similar to I guess like the DS touchscreen.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then the Rumble as well, there's been even some confirmation on that coming because apparently in a developer's behind the scenes video for Haze, they were showing...
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm telling you, Sony's got more cards they're going to show at E3.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh yeah, Eye of Judgment.
[SPEAKER_01]: Fuck the Eye of Judgment.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm telling you, PlayStation Eye, just a fucking eye toy again.
[SPEAKER_01]: Don't be suckered into it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm not suckered into it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, we're all going to end up being suckers if we've got a PlayStation 3 down the line because it looks like Sony is going to be working with the Nielsen research folks to see what we're playing, to see what they can advertise in.
[SPEAKER_03]: Isn't that special?
[SPEAKER_03]: So yeah, we're going to get more ads in our games thanks to this crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hooray, and we're still going to pay $60 for them.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's bullshit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Big stinking piles of horse hockey.
[SPEAKER_01]: Especially when they have tons of ads in games like Transformers.
[SPEAKER_01]: Come on!
[SPEAKER_03]: Does that mean... The whole movie was an Xbox ad, at least at the end.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because, like, you know, on TV, where the Neil's Rays are, if I want a show to get cancelled, I don't watch it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So how do I get a game to get cancelled?
[SPEAKER_02]: Just not buy it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't play it.
[SPEAKER_02]: How do they rate it?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't... I think it's to see who's playing what the most.
[SPEAKER_03]: so that they know what type of games to advertise in.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, doesn't Microsoft kind of already do that?
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I don't know if Sony does this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Microsoft kind of knows what you're playing all the time because you hit that little button to see your friends list.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can see what they're all playing.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Major Nelson posts every week, hey, these are the top ten games on live.
[SPEAKER_02]: So they kind of know what people are playing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I guess only out of those boxes that are connected to live, but that's still a pretty good representation.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow, one other thing that you could be playing on the PlayStation 3, and who knows how many ads are going to be in this game, Gran Turismo 5.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gran Turismo 5 will probably not see release until late 2008.
[SPEAKER_02]: This was something that director Kaonori Yamauchi said to Car and Driver magazine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because spring of 2008 is the earliest possible release window for the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sony is trying to get them to push the date further.
[SPEAKER_02]: But they want the game to be absolutely perfect.
[SPEAKER_02]: He did say, though, that there would be no crash damage physics.
[SPEAKER_02]: The perfect damage system will actually be changing the physics of the game and modeling of each panel of each car separately.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I have no idea, but they're taking out crash damage physics.
[SPEAKER_01]: But they did it in Forza.
[SPEAKER_01]: Why can't they do it in Gran Turismo 5?
[SPEAKER_01]: No idea.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of a weird, weird thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's not a big deal.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, Project Gotham I don't think does damage physics either.
[SPEAKER_01]: At least not that I'm aware of.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess not every racing game does.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, and it's, I mean, Gran Turismo's not Burnout, so, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I guess maybe that's why I kind of get a weird face, because when I think about playing racing games, I like racing games like Burnout, where the point is to crash into shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so I go, no crashing physics?
[SPEAKER_02]: What the hell kind of racing game is this?
[SPEAKER_02]: But then I go, yeah, that's right, I've never really been a fan of Gran Turismo, because I like my racers fake.
[SPEAKER_01]: Not real.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_01]: And once again, if you're hoping to see some cool shit, especially Final Fantasy XIII at E3, well, you better forget it, because it's not going to be at E3 at all.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, boo-hoo.
[SPEAKER_01]: Not surprising, though, because I know Square Enix this year, they've been doing a lot of Nintendo stuff, like DS and PSP titles.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think there's actually some Wii titles in there as well.
[SPEAKER_01]: Why did they decide not to bring Final Fantasy XIII?
[SPEAKER_01]: It's probably not done yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Duh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, obviously, how long did it take?
[SPEAKER_02]: 12 to come out?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, they had a freaking trailer.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why does Square do that?
[SPEAKER_02]: I remember my very first E3, they showed Final Fantasy XII, and then it wasn't even there the next year.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, but here's the thing, though.
[SPEAKER_01]: They show you a trailer, but then, you know, we'll use Sony, and I think Microsoft used this phrasing, mainly Sony, though.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's a target render.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is what we hope the game to look like.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, okay, thank you very much for getting my hopes up.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's not exactly what the game's going to look like, but it's a target, you know.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's one to strive to.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I'm sure the game's still going to look phenomenal and exceed a lot of folks' expectations.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, let's face it, Square's always pushed the envelope in that department, you know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, don't get me wrong.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's going to be awesome, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm more excited seeing what was it, Last Remnant.
[SPEAKER_01]: That looks pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I think that's going to be there in trailer form.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, take it away.
[SPEAKER_03]: Unfortunately, in the real world, it doesn't quite work that way, does it?
[SPEAKER_02]: So your F.U.
[SPEAKER_02]: is to patience, in a way.
[SPEAKER_03]: And money.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Patience and money.
[SPEAKER_02]: Patience and money.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, my F.U.
[SPEAKER_01]: goes to Stella the Kitty because she... Oh, I want to meet your new kitty!
[SPEAKER_01]: She's very persistent on chewing the power cord to the fan and the light in our house.
[SPEAKER_01]: And she doesn't realize that there's a lot of electricity going through that.
[SPEAKER_01]: And fortunately, she does...
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, you know, I didn't name the cat.
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, the woman that was fostering the cat, I guess Stella's full name, she calls her Stella Dora, so I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm totally going to caturday caption pictures of your cat.
[SPEAKER_01]: We've got plenty more.
[SPEAKER_02]: I brought my camera, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: You should tell your wife that there's a video game reference in your cat's name.
[SPEAKER_02]: She'll love that.
[SPEAKER_02]: You want to watch her go crazy?
[SPEAKER_01]: Get the Jingle Cats video I want to see Stella vs. Shermie
[SPEAKER_03]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: No force on earth can move the shirt.
[SPEAKER_02]: Can I do my FUs now?
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, my FU of the week goes to my new driver's license picture.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's horrible!
[SPEAKER_03]: Rob, your face does not look that fat.
[SPEAKER_02]: My face looks like a Christmas light.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's red and fat.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's horrible.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just had to get a new license picture taken.
[SPEAKER_02]: My birthday just passed and it's that year of my license.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had to go in and take a new picture.
[SPEAKER_02]: I look fat and red.
[SPEAKER_02]: You do not!
[SPEAKER_02]: It's horrible.
[SPEAKER_02]: I look like I have a bowl full of jelly.
[SPEAKER_02]: You do not!
[SPEAKER_02]: F you to the DMV!
[SPEAKER_02]: Why do you do this to people?
[SPEAKER_02]: This is why we have rampant anorexia and bulimia in our societies, because of the DMV.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's all.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_02]: And no, chatroom, you may not have a scan.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's personal information.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not scanning my driver's license and putting it on the internet.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's one of the dumbest things you could do.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, let's get back into the gaming news before I get more frustrated, because then I'm going to take out my wallet and look at my picture again.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to get more angrier.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, Rob, I'm sorry I'm about to piss you off again.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, don't we normally love Nintendo?
[SPEAKER_02]: I love Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nintendo, we love you so much, but why do you have to hurt us by not having a playable Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_03]: at E3?
[SPEAKER_03]: Fuckers.
[SPEAKER_02]: So Nintendo's not going to be showing Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_02]: at E3?
[SPEAKER_02]: What's their excuse?
[SPEAKER_03]: Wasn't it in Kojima's blog that he played an almost complete version?
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, in April?
[SPEAKER_03]: So why not?
[SPEAKER_03]: Why are you fucking with us, Nintendo?
[SPEAKER_03]: Give us a playable Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_03]: or I'll head up to Washington, beat you in the head with an orange bat, fly to Japan, and run over your headquarters with a tank!
[SPEAKER_03]: Give me!
[SPEAKER_03]: I need my pit, and I need my snake.
[SPEAKER_03]: The end.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got a snake, man.
[SPEAKER_03]: I got a snake, man!
[SPEAKER_03]: One time I fed my snake some beer.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Going to chat room.
[SPEAKER_02]: RawSteelUT says, Like we don't know how Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_02]: is going to play...
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_02]: My God.
[SPEAKER_01]: They do a damn update on the website every day.
[SPEAKER_01]: And every blog on the face of the earth covers the damn website.
[SPEAKER_01]: Just go to the website and check it out each day.
[SPEAKER_01]: We don't need to hear or see it updated every day.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't give a crap about the final moves and the control scheme and all that shit.
[SPEAKER_01]: Just wait for the game to come out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Be surprised.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, as if I wish I had good news for you, but the journey continues here with Nintendo and what they are and aren't going to be showing at E3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, this has nothing to do with what's at E3.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is just the way it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Michael Kelba, who is actually the head of Retro Studios, who is designing, of course, Metroid Prime 3 Corruption, in an interview recently with GamePro, he has confirmed that there will be no online multiplayer games.
[SPEAKER_02]: and Metroid Prime 3 Corruption.
[SPEAKER_02]: Those of us that were hoping and thinking and speculating and convinced that Nintendo is finally going to get into online gaming, they're finally going to open up to the world of online gaming and Metroid Prime 3 is going to be the game that will do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: We just got fucking shot down this week.
[SPEAKER_01]: Way to brace next gen.
[SPEAKER_01]: Or this gen.
[SPEAKER_01]: Last gen.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Online.
[SPEAKER_01]: God damn it.
[SPEAKER_01]: This makes me angry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why won't you embrace online gaming, Nintendo?
[SPEAKER_02]: What, did Phantasy Star Online Episodes 1 and 2 burn you that badly?
[SPEAKER_02]: What is your big problem with online gaming?
[SPEAKER_02]: Why do you have to spray us with these friend codes crap?
[SPEAKER_02]: Why won't you put your series that we love online?
[SPEAKER_02]: Why do you give us something crappy like the new Pokemon game that's your only online game and it's mediocre online stuff anyway?
[SPEAKER_02]: Why will you not wake up to the next generation of gaming?
[SPEAKER_02]: and I copy everything that Jamie said before about the deck.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyways, more positive news.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wait a minute, hold on.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to chat for a minute.
[SPEAKER_02]: HitStun says even fucking Virtua Fighter 5 is going to be online now.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know in a shittacious series like Virtua Fighter goes online and Metroid is still single player only.
[SPEAKER_02]: Something is fucked in this world.
[SPEAKER_02]: RossDLUT says, no Metroid Prime 3 online?
[SPEAKER_02]: Good!
[SPEAKER_02]: Nintendo Online sucks anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it could have been better.
[SPEAKER_02]: JVmon says, Pokemon Online is slow as hell.
[SPEAKER_02]: The DS games are fine!
[SPEAKER_02]: Nintendo can do it!
[SPEAKER_02]: They're just not doing it for some reason.
[SPEAKER_02]: RossDLUT says, people who play Nintendo systems don't want online.
[SPEAKER_02]: Those who want to play online have 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: I beg to differ.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you give them online, they will embrace online.
[SPEAKER_02]: Moms and grandmas like to play Bejeweled Online and that, like, you know, those fucking pop-it games on Pogo and shit and all those other games, like Poker Online.
[SPEAKER_02]: They'll play that.
[SPEAKER_02]: They'll play the Wii Online, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't give me that just because it's not a hardcore gaming audience or whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: This just makes me angry because I've been waiting so long for Nintendo to go online.
[SPEAKER_01]: What was last year's E3?
[SPEAKER_01]: We're embracing online.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, the system is going to be, you know, what was that, Nintendo is going to be providing new content daily.
[SPEAKER_01]: And every day you're going to be able to go to your Nintendo Wii system and see new content.
[SPEAKER_01]: Whether it be game downloads or all this shit.
[SPEAKER_01]: Or how about... What else were they promising that was going to be really cool?
[SPEAKER_01]: The Wii Connect 24.
[SPEAKER_01]: Providing updates automatically.
[SPEAKER_01]: Notice!
[SPEAKER_01]: All these promises and nothing following through.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I will let this slide, Nintendo, because you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: In all honesty, Metroid will never be as good 3D as it was in 2D.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can argue with me all you want on that one, but I just feel very strongly that Super Metroid was the all-time greatest Metroid game.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there will never be a Metroid game as good as Super Metroid.
[SPEAKER_02]: Unless... What?
[SPEAKER_03]: They do a new one...
[SPEAKER_03]: in the vein of Super Metroid on the DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, kinda.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, on the Advance, there was Zero Mission or whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not the same on a tiny screen.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the problem.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the DS is... The first time I played Super Metroid and Crayed, you know, multi-story boss on the TV, that was the shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Brinstar music.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can't duplicate that on a DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: Rubber, rubber, rubber.
[SPEAKER_03]: What are you doing on Thursday?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know what.
[SPEAKER_03]: We are playing Super Metroid.
[SPEAKER_03]: You are coming to my house and we are playing Super Metroid on my 50 inch widescreen.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll try to make that happen if we're not house hunting because I am in the middle of that right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: But anyway, what was I ranting about Metroid?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, Nintendo, prove me wrong then about this whole online thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let that be your cards on the table at E3.
[SPEAKER_02]: I will let this Metroid Prime 3 corruption thing slide if you tell me that Smash Brothers is going to be online.
[SPEAKER_02]: I will throw myself in front of Jamie's tank to stop her evil doings and then I will make love to all of you.
[SPEAKER_01]: Fuck that.
[SPEAKER_01]: I want to see it actually be online.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't want it being promised online, just like they promise new fucking content each day on goddamn, you know, WeConnect24.
[SPEAKER_01]: What's the point of having my damn system connected to the internet 24 hours a day if you're not going to do anything with it?
[SPEAKER_01]: Fuck, I even got to boot up my system before my messages will download onto it.
[SPEAKER_01]: What the hell is this WeConnect24 shit?
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyways, so hold on real quick.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Real quick comments from chat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mike W0440 says Metroid Prime was one of the greatest games of all time in some people's opinion.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: And some people are entitled to be wrong.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: Prime was a great game, but Super Metroid was better, that's all.
[SPEAKER_02]: GS191 says, Nintendo has labeled a big disappointment.
[SPEAKER_02]: If they add something, people want more.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nintendo is placed on a very high pedestal and is judged as such.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, that's true.
[SPEAKER_02]: As mad as I am, Nintendo has the most to lose going into this E3, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Sony has the most to gain, Nintendo has the most to lose.
[SPEAKER_01]: The problem is, Nintendo, they mark themselves as being innovative people.
[SPEAKER_01]: And they are in certain aspects, but in other aspects they're making really stupid mistakes.
[SPEAKER_01]: Not a lot of storage on their system.
[SPEAKER_01]: Not allowing third party or outside storage.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, granted they do have the SD memory cards, but other than transferring your game saves off of it and maybe playing some MP3s in Excite Truck, it's not being used.
[SPEAKER_01]: Or, I don't know, the whole online thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's all these promises, and you get your hopes up, and they don't fucking deliver.
[SPEAKER_01]: I want delivery, dammit!
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyways, please read a story that will not make me want to play the FU music again.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright, so, Nintendo in Japan.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're, of course, Club Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_01]: Including, they have a lot of exclusive games that get released on there, and they get to buy them off.
[SPEAKER_01]: with, I guess, points that you earn from buying different Nintendo games and stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: Such wonderful games include the Game & Watch Collection for the DS, Tingle's Balloon Fight, and now... Rad!
[SPEAKER_01]: No.
[SPEAKER_01]: And now, Explanation Warriors.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's a bizarre DS game that uses the microphone for gameplay.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, it's kind of like, I guess, a Sentai hero type thing, like Mighty Morphin Power Rangers.
[SPEAKER_01]: Punch!
[SPEAKER_01]: Kick!
[SPEAKER_02]: Kick!
[SPEAKER_02]: Kick, goddammit, I said kick!
[SPEAKER_02]: No!
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I said kick!
[SPEAKER_01]: Brew!
[SPEAKER_01]: Brew.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, my voice was already leaving before tonight's show, by the way.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tonight's show is just making it worse.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just kind of wanted to get that out there because I can feel myself losing my voice.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was already going away last night.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is great.
[SPEAKER_02]: This show is very healthy for me.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think I just shaved five years off of my life with tonight's bout of anger.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jenga!
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay people.
[SPEAKER_01]: Step away from the credit card.
[SPEAKER_01]: Here's why.
[SPEAKER_01]: Why the fuck would you buy a game that's probably not going to play very well?
[SPEAKER_01]: Granted, okay, yeah, it's the Wii.
[SPEAKER_01]: You can, you know, use the Wii Remote too.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, but yeah, honestly, the Wii is not that sensitive.
[SPEAKER_01]: Jenga doesn't cost, I would imagine, it's probably less than $10.
[SPEAKER_01]: And you're going to buy a game for at least $20.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's the low end.
[SPEAKER_02]: I bet this Wii version would not have Truth or Dare Jenga on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there is a Truth or Dare Jenga game available.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: So... I don't understand why people do this shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because people are too lazy to put the block sculpture together.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because it is a little bit painstaking.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, you have to put three this way, then three this way, and three... Oh my god, and you can just, like, I don't know, stack it in the plastic thing that comes with it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, that's so difficult!
[SPEAKER_01]: So difficult!
[SPEAKER_01]: That is a lot of effort for some people.
[SPEAKER_01]: What can you imagine, though, taking it out, you know, with the Wii Remote and stuff like that, and all of a sudden, your IR gets fucked up because something, you know, shiny's in the room, and it knocks the whole thing over, and you're like, fucking A, why the hell did I pay money for this damn game?
[SPEAKER_01]: I was doing it perfect, and it fucked it up.
[SPEAKER_02]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe this version of Jenga will actually be online.
[SPEAKER_02]: You could play online.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, wait.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Never mind.
[SPEAKER_02]: It can't be online, because that's not possible.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I agree.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have no idea why this game exists.
[SPEAKER_02]: But we can talk about some games that will exist pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jamie, are you excited about Jenga?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I want... I miss my actual Jenga.
[SPEAKER_02]: We should play Truth or Dare Jenga on OLR one night during a slow news week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because the little blocks that you pull out have little questions on them that you have to answer, or little dares you have to do.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's dumb stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like a Mormon Truth or Dare game.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're not going to do anything that dirty.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway...
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's talk about some upcoming release dates over in Japan and some things you can get your hands on pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's talk about the Xbox 360 on July 12th.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tom Clancy's Ghost Recon Advanced Warfighter 2 makes its way to the Japanese audience thanks to Ubisoft.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: Going over to some other platforms on the Nintendo Wii, Dragon Quest Swords finally shows up on July 12th from Squeenix on the Nintendo Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gundam Musou
[SPEAKER_02]: Also coming out on the PlayStation 2, a lot of the Grand Theft Auto games are going into the best hits, so they're getting big price reductions over there in Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, Disgaea, Hour of Darkness 2 is also getting a price cut.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not a whole lot of new games coming out over there in Japan, although if you're a music game fan, you probably already have Poppin' Music 14 Fever pre-ordered.
[SPEAKER_02]: Poppin' Music 14, of course, the
[SPEAKER_02]: EZUMO ZERO Adventure Game
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's yet another title that has a very nice looking anime chick on the front.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sure that's like every other game of that type.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm totally labeling this based on the box art alone.
[SPEAKER_02]: On the Nintendo DS, Death Note.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a Death Note game coming out in Konami.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, I need this.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you'll like that one.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Monster Farm DS also coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: One of my favorite titles, I have no idea what this is supposed to mean, but it's Kirarin Revolution Mezase Idol Queen.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a strategy game from Konami, but it looks like a pop idol kind of contest.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the chick's wearing a cowboy hat and winking at you on the box art cover, so I have no idea what the hell that game's supposed to be.
[SPEAKER_02]: Over on the PSP, coming out on July 12th over in Japan...
[SPEAKER_02]: You have Tekken Dark Resurrection getting a price cut, and that's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: No new games.
[SPEAKER_02]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Japanese releases.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was going to mention something real quick.
[SPEAKER_01]: The DDR Hottest Party page finally made it up on the Japanese site for Konami.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I thought there were some interesting... They had quotes from all the music directors and stuff from other Bomani games in Japan.
[SPEAKER_01]: And they have some really interesting quotes like, This game is killing it.
[SPEAKER_01]: The Dance Dance Revolution Extreme director...
[SPEAKER_01]: Um, Inubuzu, which I thought was funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what happens when I don't play DDR for like six months and I try to play like a ten foot song on the arcade.
[SPEAKER_02]: I go, this game is killing me.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually passed a nine footer the other day.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow, can I shake your hand?
[SPEAKER_03]: After a year of not playing.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, that's good, but did you want to die afterwards?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, I did, freaking Kakame.
[SPEAKER_02]: This game is killing it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyhow, more release dates, please, Loki.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, if you're looking for console games this week, keep looking.
[SPEAKER_01]: The only thing that you are going to find, though, is Project Silphid for the 360.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's going to be making its way out this week.
[SPEAKER_01]: Didn't that already come out?
[SPEAKER_01]: No.
[SPEAKER_01]: It is coming out this week, though.
[SPEAKER_01]: and that's about it for console games now for handhelds though we've got a few things Smash Court Tennis 3 is coming out to the PSP as well as Riviera The Promised Land is also making its way out to the PSP see for the DS just Vegas Casino High 5 that's making its way out and then on the PC not a whole lot of good stuff but yet again it doesn't
[SPEAKER_01]: Cease to Amaze Me, another tycoon game, Ride Carnival Tycoon, coming out.
[SPEAKER_01]: I swear to God, there's a new one every fucking week.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can probably play that piece of shit online, but I still can't take my Wii online.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow, how about some European release dates for the listeners?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, we have a few interesting things.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, on the 13th is Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix on Game Boy Advance.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mario Party 8 for Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tom Clancy's Ghost Recon Advanced Warfighter 2, also on the 13th for PC.
[SPEAKER_03]: On the 20th, we have The Darkness and Transformers The Game on DS.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, the DS release.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then on the 21st, the one thing everybody's been looking forward to on the PC.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is so exciting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Brian Lara's International Cricket.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hooray!
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm so excited.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because everybody loves cricket.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: And to that statement, I hear a chorus of crickets in the background.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh god, I'm fired.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wasn't that that little doll that you'd put the tape in her back and she'd read you a story?
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: It was called Cricket.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was Teddy Ruxpin.
[SPEAKER_03]: Have you been reading Penny Arcade lately?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're doing like... I don't read.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're doing like hardcore Teddy Ruxpin, the action hero.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now that's cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: There should be like a fighting game with our childhood favorites, like Teddy Ruxpin versus a Cabbage Patch doll.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: You probably never played this game, but it's a... I don't know if it's a tabletop RPG, but it is an RPG.
[SPEAKER_01]: Um...
[SPEAKER_01]: It's called Fuzzy Heroes, and you use stuffed animals.
[SPEAKER_01]: I swear to God, you use stuffed animals as characters in the game.
[SPEAKER_01]: And based on what the stuffed animal has attributes and stuff, you have different attack abilities.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it's a tactical, I guess, I don't know what you'd call it, tabletop RPG, but it's basically like a tabletop RPG.
[SPEAKER_01]: And you move them around and stuff, and you attack with different abilities.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, for example, I had...
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: It's an interesting idea.
[SPEAKER_03]: We could do that with Lugen.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my God, Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's what Miklatov... Best radio ever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sometimes I wish this were a TV show, but here is the present that Miklatov, Rice Princess, and Extafural went together and got me.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a panda bear wearing stripper boots and a tutu.
[SPEAKER_02]: A pink tutu.
[SPEAKER_02]: A pink tutu carrying a little wand with a... Jonas just joined us, by the way, and he's making this face like OMG.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jonas, can you please describe this... Her name is Sassy Pants, by the way.
[SPEAKER_02]: Can you please describe Sassy Pants to the listeners?
[SPEAKER_02]: And welcome to the show.
[SPEAKER_01]: How could I even explain?
[SPEAKER_04]: What the hell is this?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a panda bear wearing a pink tutu and stripper boots.
[SPEAKER_02]: So what I'm curious, how would Sassy Pants fare in Fuzzy Heroes?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I think she would dominate because she can cast magic.
[SPEAKER_02]: True.
[SPEAKER_02]: She has stripper boots, so you know she can kick.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I want to play Fuzzy Heroes with Sassy Pants.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm not sure because I unfortunately don't have the rulebook in front of me.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is someone else's thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: But okay, it's a game.
[SPEAKER_01]: If you go to fuzzyheroes.com, I think you can still buy the book.
[SPEAKER_01]: But anyways, it's created by InnerCity Games Designs.
[SPEAKER_01]: And let me see if I can read a brief description of what the game is.
[SPEAKER_01]: InnerCity Games Designs is probably best known for our Fuzzy Heroes line of miniature gaming products.
[SPEAKER_01]: Products that use stuffed toys and action figures as miniature combatants in 3D strategic simulations.
[SPEAKER_01]: These games are designed to be introductory for those who are new to the miniatures hobby, but we both...
[SPEAKER_01]: but with both enough depth and humor to engage the veteran miniatures gamer as well.
[SPEAKER_01]: We still make Fuzzy Heroes and in fact are gearing up for another set of both games and comics for this.
[SPEAKER_01]: I guess they have comics for this too.
[SPEAKER_01]: We also make several independent toy related games including Very Large Creature, Stuffed Toys vs. Miniatures, and
[SPEAKER_01]: Sports Fuzz, 3D football using toys, beer bottles, and whatever happens to be lying around.
[SPEAKER_02]: By the way, Sassy Pants' tiara fell off, so I found that in the living room, but there's also that, which must add some magical powers to it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know, but I swear you can probably find this in a comic shop, any place that has the miniatures, tabletop strategy games and stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: We're spending far too much time on this topic.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, it's funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd never heard of this.
[SPEAKER_01]: It would be fun for, like,
[SPEAKER_02]: That'd be a fun thing to record.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, for YouTube or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: OLR Plays Fuzzy Heroes.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wanted to say, though, about the Harry Potter game that's coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: It came out here, obviously, already, and I actually got to see it this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: I forgot to say it during my game week because I didn't play it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I watched somebody else play it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looked boring.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looked like all the other Harry Potter games.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, because I was really excited.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's because they're not very great.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was excited about getting to cast magic with the Wiimote.
[SPEAKER_02]: The funniest thing, though, is when my friend Eddie, who was playing it, picked up the table...
[SPEAKER_02]: and was slamming it into people.
[SPEAKER_02]: They would go, oh, oh, that hurts.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, that hurts.
[SPEAKER_01]: The game's really funny.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's like you go to Hogwarts and then you run errands for people.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's like Hogwarts errand boy.
[SPEAKER_03]: The game is really what... No, it's like Animal Crossing at Hogwarts.
[SPEAKER_01]: Except Animal Crossing is more fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can, instead of shaking trees, you get beaten up by the Whomping Willow.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just wanted to say that real quickly, because I watched the Harry Potter game, and it wasn't all that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, Australia.
[SPEAKER_02]: We haven't talked a lot about what's going on in Australia, but if you are a Wii owner in Australia, you have some good news for you this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: You got a ton of virtual console games this week, which is very interesting, and that's why we're kind of wanting to report it on the show, is that Nintendo can certainly...
[SPEAKER_02]: Just push out like a shitload of games all at once.
[SPEAKER_02]: Listen to this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Australians got like all of this in one week here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bonk's Adventure, Bomberman 93, Superstar Soldier, Victory Run, Alien Crush, Military Madness, R-Type, Dungeon Explorer, Soldier Blade, Motor Rotor, and Vigilante.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if you're a TurboGrafx fan in Australia, you had a very good week this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, Rob, while we're at it.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: There were actually new releases for...
[SPEAKER_03]: and actually now I'm trying to find them again.
[SPEAKER_03]: There were new releases for a virtual console in the UK as well and I unfortunately just lost my link to it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_02]: 2 in the US.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, and over there?
[SPEAKER_03]: I do believe that was one of them.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just had it and I feel really crappy about it because I just looked all this up last night.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think Paper Mario is supposed to be coming over here pretty soon too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have they said what's coming out over here on Monday?
[SPEAKER_01]: Nothing yet?
[SPEAKER_01]: I saw Paper Mario 4 I think is one of the other regions.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, the virtual console for UK, actually, Sonic the Hedgehog 2 just came out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Golden Axe 2, Echo Tides of Time, Dragon Spirit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Those are the games that just came out.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think we got most of those over here already, I think.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, for once, Europe didn't beat us to the punch on virtual console, because they have been lately.
[SPEAKER_03]: They did get some really good games, because I love Echo Tides of Time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sadly, though, I think this is the Mega Drive version and not the...
[SPEAKER_03]: Mega CD one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, good point.
[SPEAKER_02]: James Patrick in chat says, Australia never saw the release of the TurboGrafx at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if you're a TurboGrafx fan living in Australia, you might be the only one.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're a rarity.
[SPEAKER_03]: Either that or you were a major hardcore importer.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, you're a hardcore importer.
[SPEAKER_01]: Another game that's coming out here later in the fall, Resident Evil Umbrella Chronicles, is going to be supporting co-op gameplay as well.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, what good gun game
[SPEAKER_01]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_01]: They did an online game, I thought, with Resident Evil where if you got bit, you became a zombie and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I think they should do Marvel Zombies the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Where you're a superhero zombie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or a George Romero zombie type game or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, I guess that's what Dead Rising was.
[SPEAKER_02]: But like one where you actually get to be the zombie.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be kind of fun, like an online game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I guess, but that was Resident Evil on PS2, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_03]: I want Marvel Zombies the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: But make it good this time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Make it memorable.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, hey, I have something that's memorable.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_03]: People were crackheads like me back in the day.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ragnarok Online is going to be on Japanese DS in 2008.
[SPEAKER_03]: The game is also going to be released with Sakana no Aselbo, which is a fishing game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, there's actually going to be an Ikebana game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ikebana is flower arranging, by the way.
[SPEAKER_03]: But Ragnarok Online is going to be in real time using the Nintendo Wi-Fi And it's supposed to be, I guess, tailored to the DS But it's only going to be out in Japan right now Which means I'm going to be importing it and sitting around with my dictionary Either that or I will just probably remember where all the shit is anyway Because I played Ragnarok Online for, what, five, six years?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, there's really only one phrase that you need to know in Japanese, and that's, we ban you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but actually, theRobD makes an interesting point.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why are they calling it Ragnarok Online when it's not online?
[SPEAKER_03]: It is online.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to be on Wi-Fi.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_01]: Touche.
[SPEAKER_02]: So much for that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, speaking of quirky games coming over from overseas, Majesco is going to be making a local version of Furufuru Park.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was a game that came out in Japan in April, and get this,
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: By the way, the game also has original type of games.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a karate game, a safe-cracking game, so it's not just retro classics.
[SPEAKER_02]: But minigame fun, because who doesn't love their minigames on the Wii?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what I live for on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, something very interesting that's going to be coming to arcades pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_01]: Capcom is actually doing an original 2D fighting game.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's going to be the first one that they've done in three years.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it's coming soon.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's a new teaser page on Capcom Japan's site.
[SPEAKER_01]: No word exactly on what it is, although it looks very promising, seeing as some of the shots we've seen so far of the Street Fighter 2 HD for the Xbox Live Arcade and PlayStation Network and stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: Looks awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: Do you really think they'd put out Street Fighter 4?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, not for another five years.
[SPEAKER_03]: If Street Fighter 3 was any indication.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think we need another Marvel vs. Capcom.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what we need?
[SPEAKER_03]: We need a Cyberbot sequel.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because Cyberbot is Capcom's number one fighting game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting choice.
[SPEAKER_03]: To quote Puzzle Fighter, anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see, you could have... It's the game that gave us Devilot and Super 8.
[SPEAKER_02]: Capcom and SNK vs. Marvel and... I don't know, your mom.
[SPEAKER_02]: Arcades vs. Comics.
[SPEAKER_01]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_01]: It'll be like... Arcade fighting games vs. comic characters.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: We just need a new Cyberbot.
[SPEAKER_03]: We need a new Cyberbot.
[SPEAKER_03]: and another Red Earth.
[SPEAKER_02]: How about another Darkstalkers game?
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's all about a dude who played with his blood.
[SPEAKER_02]: That'd be cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Going to chatroomchat.orangelandre.com Rob D says, New Capcom 2D fighter?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm in.
[SPEAKER_02]: No questions asked.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shadow Charlie says, But fucking yeah, another Cyberbots.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hell yeah!
[SPEAKER_01]: What they need to do is they need to get, like, you know how they have the Triforce thing for, you know, the F-Zero stuff, whereas Sega and, you know, Namco and Nintendo, they need to do something like that for fighting games.
[SPEAKER_01]: You need to get SNK, Capcom, and, I don't know, maybe Sega, I guess.
[SPEAKER_01]: And do, like, some sort of all-encompassing thing that has a lot of characters from all these different games.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, you think all those brilliant minds put together could, like, I don't know, save arcades?
[SPEAKER_01]: No.
[SPEAKER_01]: Blood Orgy
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want a new Rival Schools.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ah.
[SPEAKER_03]: I played the crap out of the first one, out of the Evolution one.
[SPEAKER_03]: I paid 90 bucks for the Evolution one.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, no, there was a rumor about the Apollo Justice game or whatever.
[SPEAKER_01]: That was a subtitle and people are thinking it's either a new Phoenix Wright game or a new Rival Schools game, so...
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what, DJ Dark Knight makes this joke in chat, the super ultimate extreme fighting combat tournament, and that makes me think, oh my god, why doesn't Capcom and Midway just get together, give the fans what they want, Street Fighter vs. Mortal Kombat, come on, that would be hot.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be hot!
[SPEAKER_03]: It wouldn't work.
[SPEAKER_03]: They would have to use the really shitball Street Fighter of the game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Mortal Kombat.
[SPEAKER_01]: They could take the Mortal Kombat characters and make them all cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: With the EX.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or with the more recent ones that are all 3D, they could use the Street Fighter EX.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: But they would never do that because it would be awesome and make sense.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ross Steel UT says Street Fighter vs. Mortal Kombat wouldn't work.
[SPEAKER_02]: The games are too different.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know though, but they made, I mean, they made Capcom fight comic book characters and that somehow worked.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean... And, you know, Marvel vs. or Capcom vs. SNK, you know, and... It could, I mean, I understand because there's a lot of weaponry that goes into Mortal Kombat and it's a much darker game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, it's a total fanboy thing I'm going off on here with, but come on, in
[SPEAKER_02]: Indulge me for just like five seconds.
[SPEAKER_02]: It might be a fun game.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you don't mind me going to a previous topic, by the way, the Ragnarok Online DS is not actually online.
[SPEAKER_03]: They just have multiplayer elements over Wi-Fi.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to refrain from making the obvious joke here about Nintendo because I'm irritating some folks in chat, although they can kiss my big fat butt.
[SPEAKER_03]: They should just do it on Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: But instead of your little Ragnarok characters, you have your Miis.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, that might be cute.
[SPEAKER_03]: You have, like, Ragnami.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ragnami.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're weird.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, enough of this whole fighting game talk.
[SPEAKER_02]: Somebody please bring up another topic.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, anyone who's a fan of Valkyrie Profile will be happy that Valkyrie Profile 2 has a date.
[SPEAKER_03]: It will be out on the 7th of September!
[SPEAKER_03]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_03]: So, um, the, uh, this one is, uh, you know, got a different story.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's going to be the youngest of three Valkyrie is, uh, booted out of heaven and has to go do shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would suck to get booted out of heaven, actually.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is one of those series I've wanted to play but haven't gotten a chance to check out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, seeing as how if you're Valkyrie, you have to fight all the time and then pick people to die.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I think being booted out of heaven might not be so bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: The only other game with a Valkyrie I can think of is Gauntlet because I always used to play Blue Valkyrie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or Macross.
[SPEAKER_02]: Blue Valkyrie.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, but that's a different kind of Valkyrie.
[SPEAKER_03]: Duh.
[SPEAKER_01]: I like that Valkyrie a lot better.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dude, I wouldn't mind having the one where you use your brain like in Macross+.
[SPEAKER_03]: The YF21.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, a lot of folks in chat, going back to the fighting game topic for a moment, now they're getting all Killer Instinct on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're like, who owns Killer Instinct now?
[SPEAKER_02]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_02]: Killer Instinct sucked.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually have both of them.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have the one on Nintendo 64.
[SPEAKER_02]: I forgot they had it on 64.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, they did KI2 Gold.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I remember, this was before I moved out here, I had Dan play the game over and over and over again just to rip me Orchid's music.
[SPEAKER_02]: SSJ100Matt says, Rare says they have no intention of doing a new Killer Instinct.
[SPEAKER_03]: DIAF Rare.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, I did play a Rare game at the party.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pinbot.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rare published Pinbot for the Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_01]: But thank God, though, they're going to be doing that Banjo-Kazooie sequel.
[SPEAKER_01]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_01]: Cannot wait.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's going to be so awesome and totally won't suck.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, look, let's change the topic completely here.
[SPEAKER_02]: One last topic for this Part A, then we're going to go into a break and come back for Part B. Talking about the Simpsons game, you know, the Simpsons have a game coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's no coincidence there's a movie, and pretty soon there'll be a game.
[SPEAKER_02]: And this game is like a spoof of every other video game, yes?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, the ultimate spoof waits for you at the very end of the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: The very last boss, the final boss in the Simpsons game is...
[SPEAKER_02]: Matt Groening, the creator of The Simpsons, is who you will face at the very end of the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ooh, spoiler!
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, sorry, OMG spoiler, but, you know, come on.
[SPEAKER_02]: You don't play a Simpsons game for the plot.
[SPEAKER_02]: You play it because it's funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: The game looks sexy, too, by the way.
[SPEAKER_02]: And this is like EA's first Simpsons game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, props to EA.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, sometimes we dog on that company a little bit on this show, but props to them if they pull this off.
[SPEAKER_01]: Definitely not anything like Superman Returns, the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Simpsons game, by the way, will be out this fall, so it's going to miss the movie, but probably make it in time for the DVD release, yes?
[SPEAKER_01]: That would be my guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: TheRobD says, you totally spoiled the Simpsons game I wasn't going to play.
[SPEAKER_02]: How could you?
[SPEAKER_02]: SSJ100Matt says, still waiting on Simpsons arcade game on 360. 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: You never know, the movie's around the corner.
[SPEAKER_02]: It could happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: But again, it's going to be like that whole, you know, Konami and Ubisoft had to kind of team up to get us Ninja Turtles, so what, Konami and EA are going to have to team up to get us Simpsons, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Could happen, though.
[SPEAKER_01]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_01]: It very well could be like Doom, where it's like, Doom, there it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: We didn't tell you about it, so there it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's exactly what Peter Moore said at the press conference, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like, Doom, there it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, we need a break.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, that's how I feel too.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to take a quick break and we'll be back with a little more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, and part B tonight, listless.
[SPEAKER_02]: E3 is just around the corner, so we need to do an honorary E3 listless.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you haven't heard listless before, definitely stay tuned for part B. And we'll be back with more of Orange Lounge Radio right after this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and is podcasted to the world twice a week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Stay tuned to our podcast feed for the conclusion of this week's Orange Lounge Radio.