[SPEAKER_00]: Tonight, July 15th, 2007, an E3 wrap-up.
[SPEAKER_00]: Microsoft gets Disney movies, Nintendo wants you to get fit, and Sony gives the PSP a makeover.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello everybody out there and welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: We are that podcast dedicated to video games, video gaming, gaming culture, and the gamer lifestyle.
[SPEAKER_02]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_02]: You might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_02]: Joining me as always, say hello to DarkSakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yo.
[SPEAKER_02]: How you doing, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh, a little, uh.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm conventioning to this morning.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll talk a little more about that in just a moment, but let me introduce as well Techmaster Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_02]: How are you doing, Techmaster Loki?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm doing fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Swell.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are you all conventioned out as well?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, that's too bad or good?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if that's good news.
[SPEAKER_01]: I didn't really go to the convention at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, we'll talk about the convention in just a little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have, unfortunately, no real special guests in the studio tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, Xfer's over there playing WoW, but that means he's probably too busy to actually comment on tonight's programs.
[SPEAKER_02]: But other folks might come in and out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob sounds different from the podcast.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, well, it could be the fact that it's a different bit rate when we stream live than it is on the podcast.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's a little cleaner.
[SPEAKER_02]: Our live stream actually uses MP3 Pro encoding.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, the podcast, our audio archive uses MP3 Pro as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Unfortunately, the iPods don't recognize MP3 Pro, which is how most people listen to us.
[SPEAKER_02]: But if you listen to the shows on WinApp, it actually sounds a little cleaner if you have the MP3 Pro plug-in installed.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just a little tip for those of you guys that listen live at home.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow, let's start off tonight's program talking about how is your gaming week.
[SPEAKER_02]: And unfortunately, none of us were able to go to E3 this year, so we didn't get to do that, but we'll be talking a lot about that and giving our opinions on things as, you know, outsiders looking in, as well as really relying on your comments as well to kind of let us know what you thought of this year's E3.
[SPEAKER_02]: But what kind of games did you play this week since you weren't at E3?
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I tried to play some Power, Power, Paradise, got as far as getting everything set up and then left the room.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which we'll be getting into that later.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then I played a little bit of pinball.
[SPEAKER_04]: Played some Burning Crusade.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, actually, I got as far as setting it up and then realizing I had to patch.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then saying, screw this noise and not playing.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I finally got my first badge in Pokemans.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: While I was on the recumbent bike at the gym.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Recumbent Bike for people who are not gym savvy or vocabulary savvy means you sit back on your ass and pedal in front of you.
[SPEAKER_02]: What was that bike, Loki?
[SPEAKER_02]: You would know this better.
[SPEAKER_02]: In that one episode of South Park, Mr. Garrison invented the bike.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was the It, I think.
[SPEAKER_01]: The It?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, remember?
[SPEAKER_01]: Because it was a parody of...
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Bob, get me one.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: Please.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't have money.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Getting you presents requires money that I don't have.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, Loki, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_01]: I meant to play all the E3 demos that were available on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just never got around to it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I got around to downloading them, just not playing them.
[SPEAKER_01]: So that wasn't really helpful.
[SPEAKER_01]: I did
[SPEAKER_01]: I played more Saints Row multiplayer because we're still testing out the LAN stuff and it works great now that I actually updated all the systems to have the multiplayer patch on it so now it works awesome and it's pretty fun actually the other thing we tried was the other thing I played more Earth Defense Force 2017 because yes we're still not done with the game and it's getting pretty hard now because now we have to play on Inferno um
[SPEAKER_01]: So we finished a few things on that.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then I'm playing more Final Fantasy on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_01]: More Grand Theft Auto Vice City stories on PSP.
[SPEAKER_01]: I do have stuff to play this week.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just got a preview copy of Shin Megami Tensei Persona 3.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I'm going to be playing that.
[SPEAKER_01]: That'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then... A lot of folks liked the last game that came out in that series.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, so it should be pretty good.
[SPEAKER_01]: Um...
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, that's pretty much it for right now.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm looking, hopefully this week, Paper Mario is going to be making its way out on our virtual console because it's everywhere else.
[SPEAKER_01]: But, you know, I want to play that now.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because Super Paper Mario is pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I hear it's not really much different than the original Paper Mario.
[SPEAKER_02]: But do you have information to back that up that is definitely coming out here Monday?
[SPEAKER_02]: Or are you just speculating?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just guessing.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_02]: So.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: But I found in Blue Dragon, before you enter the room to start fighting monsters, you really have to just read these wall of words that talk about the game and how the battle system works.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that doesn't really do it for me.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like it when you fight a fight, and then somebody comes in helping explain it to you as you're fighting.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, maybe I'm just... It might be just because it's the demo.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm hoping, I'm really hoping.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I would never want to base my judgment of an entire game off a demo, but it was very hard for me to get into for that reason.
[SPEAKER_02]: I felt like I wasn't really understanding everything that was going on.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it does seem to have a pretty cool combat system.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's somewhat a real-time system, but you can have your attack stronger if you wait longer.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'm looking forward to seeing the finished product.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm such a fan of the Japanese RPGs, especially I'm interested in the products that Mistwalker's putting out.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm at least going to rent the darn game if I don't buy it.
[SPEAKER_02]: That and Eternal Sonata and the other stuff that's coming.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hear it's three this long.
[SPEAKER_02]: Blue Dragon, really?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought it was only two.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought it was three.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, well, well.
[SPEAKER_02]: So there's that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And as well, I downloaded Sonic on Arcade, which was a little silly because I have Sonic on the Wii as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I just kind of wanted to try it out to sort of see, okay, what's the differences between the emulating on the Wii and the emulating on the Xbox 360?
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'll tell you, the Xbox 360 one is actually a little bit better because it's not just a straight-up port.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, playing the Wii one does feel like you've whipped out your Genesis and hooked it up and you're playing the real deal.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the Xbox 360 one, you can kind of not only have that,
[SPEAKER_02]: Just a straight up emulation, but you can do the screen resizing.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can do the smoothing graphics, which, although it's an option, I don't think it looks that good.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have the online leaderboards.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, there's a lot of little extra things that are kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: And to my mind, it's a better value for $5 on the Xbox 360 than the $8 it is on the Wii, because of the fact that it was a Genesis title.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have to say if you didn't buy Sonic on the Wii and you're a fan of the series you should definitely check out Sonic on the 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: Golden Axe I checked out as well but the problem is that Golden Axe is one of those things that was much cooler when we were kids.
[SPEAKER_02]: For me anyway, the original Golden Axe was much cooler when we were kids, and yes, I know it's got a great ending and everything, and the game was so much fun to play, co-op, but I just don't see the magic there in this day and age playing it on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: The game's very repetitive to me, and I think it's just one of those things that was much cooler, watching the magic and everything when I was younger.
[SPEAKER_01]: Other than that, I was going to say, no, I'm really disappointed they haven't brought to live arcade yet is the Gauntlet Legends series.
[SPEAKER_01]: That would have been cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've tried Gauntlet.
[SPEAKER_01]: Not a big fan of the original Gauntlet.
[SPEAKER_01]: But Gauntlet Legends, you just go play that at the arcade all the time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gauntlet Legends was pretty rad.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had the port on the N64 they made of that, and I had a lot of fun with that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because that was a good party game as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Going to the chat room and looking at comments there, Peeker Uno says, Sonic is actually a lot harder than I remembered it to be.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I kind of am finding the same thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm finding this game is a lot harder than I remember it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I used to be better at video games when I was a kid than I am now in my old age.
[SPEAKER_02]: Looking to see what other comments there are.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_04]: Gauntlet 64
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll give you this.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think going back and playing a game like Gauntlet is much more fun with four people.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, yeah, that's what I mean.
[SPEAKER_04]: When you have everybody there playing all the old school stuff, that's fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I don't have a lot of friends, so I don't get to play the old school.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, we didn't play Super Metroid on Thursday.
[SPEAKER_02]: We didn't.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you had to play Super Metroid with me this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, it's funny you mention that because I did play.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had jury duty this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Suck.
[SPEAKER_02]: Poor Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, they called me back 13 months after I was there before.
[SPEAKER_02]: Long-time listeners of OLR may remember I was on like a two-week case last year.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I went back this year and thank God I didn't get called.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I had to sit around all day long waiting to see if they'd call me.
[SPEAKER_02]: I played Metroid Zero Mission like all day, which, you know, is the next best thing to Super Metroid.
[SPEAKER_02]: on the Game Boy Advance, or in my case, the DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: But all I could play was the one Advance game I had in the slot because I lost the stylus to my DS fat, which my DS Lite was uncharged.
[SPEAKER_01]: Fuck that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Use your finger.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's what I'd be doing.
[SPEAKER_01]: Screw it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Finger works just as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Metro Zero Mission is pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't want to play Puzzle Buster.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know originally you're thinking, hey, oh, crap, it's going to get the screen all messed up and stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, fuck it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_01]: You can just rub it on your shirt.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's all good.
[SPEAKER_01]: SSJ100 Matt says wow back to jury duty yeah unfortunately Pauly Shore wasn't there though or you know what those pencils that they make you fill out the forms or pens or whatever the fuck that they have use one of those just fucking turn that shit around or I don't know pen cap or something get creative
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, so that's pretty much all the games I really played this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: So some new stuff, thanks to the marketplace, and some old stuff, thanks to my lack of a stylist for the DS.
[SPEAKER_01]: I played one more game this week, and it's kind of, we'll get into later on with some other discussion, but I played Motorstorm again, and apparently there's a code out there now that unlocks everything, so I did that, thinking, hey, you know, it's been a while since I played this, I got frustrated with how hard the game was, you know, certain races, your bike, or whatever, the physics were really bugging me.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't like Motorstorm anymore.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think it's actually really boring.
[SPEAKER_01]: And, you know, before it was pretty good, but now it's just kind of dumb.
[SPEAKER_02]: I seem to recall this is the second week in a row you've changed your mind on a game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Have you gotten finicky in your older age?
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know, but, you know, I know later on we'll probably be talking... Well, last week we talked about the 88 system or whatever that they were releasing for the PlayStation 3 with Motorstorm bundled in.
[SPEAKER_01]: I would rather it be Resistance, I think.
[SPEAKER_01]: Just Motorstorm, it's a cool game.
[SPEAKER_01]: When the demo was out and stuff, everyone was like, oh, I gotta get the game.
[SPEAKER_01]: But then you play it, and it's just the layout's not very good, and the races are kind of, eh, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: The Breakfast is provided by the staff and the shuttles going from hotel to hotel and everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're kind of trying to look at, okay, so how does everybody else feel that wasn't there at E3?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because we're the ones that are really going to be buying all this stuff that they were selling.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is going to be kind of weird, but overall, in general, the layout and the way that they did E3 this year, I actually like it more than I did the original E3.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Listen to his show, Bobby Blackwell's show, and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: So here's what he said on his show this week, is that apparently he was talking to somebody, and the reason why they had to keep E3 in LA this year was because of contracts.
[SPEAKER_02]: They had already signed a contract with the city to have this convention, and it's all basically based on the number of hotel nights they guarantee that the city's going to get from it.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, it's kind of about, you know, the...
[SPEAKER_02]: Kickback on the revenue, thank you, for the city that they're going to get from this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, the thing is, this is why they're going to have E4ALL, is because they moved E3 to Santa Monica, which is still in L.A.
[SPEAKER_02]: County, and made it a smaller event.
[SPEAKER_02]: But E4ALL was supposed to pick up consumers now and bring in revenue from that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So they were still going to meet their numbers that they originally signed off to.
[SPEAKER_02]: But according to Bobby in his show this week,
[SPEAKER_02]: E3 is, or E for All, I should say, is not living up to expectations as far as the pre-sales are concerned.
[SPEAKER_02]: And not a lot of companies are really interested in going at this point.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nintendo's really the only one that's on board.
[SPEAKER_02]: Microsoft, don't give a shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: So there is a strong chance that they may opt to take the fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: and just cancel E4ALL.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a very strong chance that E4ALL is just going to get axed in favor of just paying a fine and saying, cut our losses.
[SPEAKER_02]: But that would mean E3, if it continues next year, which may not happen, ESA may just back out of the show biz altogether.
[SPEAKER_02]: If the ESA backs out of this, then...
[SPEAKER_02]: either the ESA is going to back out or E3 is going to move to another city and of course we've heard rumors that Vegas is a possibility San Francisco San Francisco is freaking expensive I don't care, Sacramento damn cheap yeah that's true, San Francisco is probably just as expensive as LA and worse traffic Sacramento, it's dirt cheap come on you can come out here and burn to death
[SPEAKER_02]: Good luck.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know it's like 106 degrees this whole week.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is really a minor summer in comparison.
[SPEAKER_01]: But Sacramento, then I can go.
[SPEAKER_04]: San Jose.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a good idea, San Jose.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'd go to Vegas.
[SPEAKER_01]: You guys afraid of planes?
[SPEAKER_01]: San Jose or Santa Clara would be pretty good, too.
[SPEAKER_01]: Middle Silicon Valley.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, I hope E4ALL didn't get canceled.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was kind of looking forward to going, but then again, if there's not going to be much support, maybe I shouldn't be so excited.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It'll be interesting to see what happens over the next few days and what the fallout is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Floridine says, what about PAX?
[SPEAKER_02]: Penny Arcade Expo, of course, you know, a lot of folks see PAX as kind of one of those expos that's stepping up to kind of fill in the void left by the old E3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bandit in chat.orangealtradio.com says, fuck E3, I can't wait for X0708.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, I just wanted to share that little tidbit rumor thing with you guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: Other housekeeping tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: One thing is that I think that I'm going to adopt Dark Tetsuya's nickname for Kaz Harai.
[SPEAKER_04]: and Captain Crayola.
[SPEAKER_02]: and we're going to be putting that on our live journal and MySpace and I guess Facebook communities.
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically any Orange Lounge Radio community will post the link to the MP3 but because of the fact that we also talk about E3 and that and even though it's a little more
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know how to phrase it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be a little more lax than even what you're going to hear tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because of kind of the duplicate news there, we're not going to post the same show to the feed.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it was kind of our initial reactions to a lot of the E3 news.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there were some funny jokes that came out of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if you're a fan of OLR, definitely check out the bonus show this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: and I think that's about all I wanted to say for housekeeping.
[SPEAKER_02]: So let's kick it off.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's start.
[SPEAKER_02]: First press conference at E3 this week was Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_02]: So let's start with some Microsoft news.
[SPEAKER_01]: So Microsoft, they had a lot of bombs to drop, of course, and this isn't
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_01]: We're not telling you yet, but soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the answer is $30 more than what it should cost because of the Halo propaganda that will be splattered all over this thing, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Am I right?
[SPEAKER_01]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_01]: But, I mean, this only joins, you know, what?
[SPEAKER_01]: There are two custom controllers that they have right now with Todd McFarlane art and, you know, collectible figurines.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, a wireless headset and...
[SPEAKER_01]: Also, their points cards, I believe, their three-month cards are now Halo-themed.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's just, it's overload is what it is.
[SPEAKER_01]: But hey, people will buy it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Halo 3 saturation.
[SPEAKER_02]: GS191 in chat says, that's one ugly Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: I agree, it was ugly.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, I don't think it was that ugly.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's not that bad.
[SPEAKER_01]: But here's the thing, though.
[SPEAKER_01]: If you're really looking to buy an Elite or something because of the HDMI, but you don't really want to spend the $479, this might be a cheaper alternative for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Donate the money to OLR.
[SPEAKER_01]: We'll make good use out of the money.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe it can send us to Vegas for next year's E3, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, here's the thing, I would just wait and see, because later on they're going to be dropping the price of the 360 anyways, and I want to bet that maybe they're going to add HDMI to all of the Xbox 360s at some point, because I believe the Elite is only a limited time thing anyways.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, well, for the record, I actually have a Halo 2 Xbox 360 or a Halo, I'm sorry, a Halo Xbox minus the 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they're pretty.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're green and you can see through them.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're green and see through.
[SPEAKER_04]: When our first Xbox died, that's what we got.
[SPEAKER_02]: Compared to, like, the first Xbox was ugly.
[SPEAKER_02]: So the Halo one was kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: But this gray one doesn't do it for me, I have to say.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not gray, it's green.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gray-green.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks like the color of
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's translucent.
[SPEAKER_04]: It looks like violence.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: And violence sells.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not buying this 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't need HDMI that badly.
[SPEAKER_04]: I already have an Elite anyway, so I don't care.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if I want my HDMI, I'll just play my PS3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, though, speaking of HD, this is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Disney is actually going to have their movies available in high definition through the download service.
[SPEAKER_04]: X-Box Live Marketplace
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought that was kind of interesting, too, for that exact same reason, is that Disney's been kind of Blu-ray oriented, but now here they go with the Xbox service, where Xbox has kind of been with HD DVD, but I guess it's really apples to oranges.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can't really compare the two.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, but I think Disney's both, actually.
[SPEAKER_01]: They do both Blu-ray and HD DVD.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, they're exclusive to Blu-ray.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's a few that do both.
[SPEAKER_04]: However...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't see why it's win-win for them.
[SPEAKER_02]: And when you hear Disney put their movies on Xbox 360, my mind automatically goes to the animated classics.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I go, ooh, I can go download The Little Mermaid on my 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's not quite like that, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, there are some of the stuff on there.
[SPEAKER_01]: Tarzan, The Hunchback of Notre Dame, Treasure Planet.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was a crap movie anyway.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, this is just their initial offering.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tarzan was okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: When they put Tron on there, though, let me know.
[SPEAKER_02]: But having Rosie O'Donnell as a gorilla was pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: If they did Tron HD, ha!
[SPEAKER_02]: Heck, ooh, maybe they will in time because we know we're getting the games on Xbox Live Marketplace, so maybe, maybe.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, but I just want to say it's a lot of Disney subsidiaries as well, like Miramax and Touchtone are putting their movies out, too.
[SPEAKER_01]: Clerks, please.
[SPEAKER_01]: Clerks animated series, please.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, what you will be able to download soon on Xbox Live Arcade are a lot of new Xbox Live Arcade games.
[SPEAKER_02]: They showed this little trailer at E3 that showed a whole lot of new Xbox Live Arcade games, including the stuff that you can now download right away, Sonic the Hedgehog and Golden Axe, but here's some new stuff that's coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Next week is Bomberman Live, they've already announced that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Undertow, Hexic 2, which is, am I, is that the, that was the sequel to Hexen, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: That's the sequel to Hexic.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, Hexen was the sequel to Heretic.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ah, crap, never mind, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hexen, you could turn people into chickens.
[SPEAKER_02]: Damn it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was great.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because when I first saw that, I was like, oh, because I thought it was like the sequel to the Doom game, but I'm just stupid.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, then we have War World, Sensible World of Soccer, Every Extent Extra Extreme.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gion, Wing Commander Arena, Feeding Frenzy 2, Track and Field, Spyglass Board Games, Space Giraffe, Puzzle Fighter 2, HD Turbo Remix, etc, etc, blah, blah, blah Marathon, Poker Smash, Switch Ball, Tetris Splash, Puzzle Quest Switch Ball is supposed to be just like Marvel Madness, apparently And that doesn't mention the Battlestar Galactica game either, which, per Kotaku, sucks
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's kind of sad, if the Battlestar Galactica game sucks, because I was really looking forward to that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Wing Commander game sucks too, from what I hear, so stop making space combat arena games.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sadness.
[SPEAKER_01]: What they should be making is more space RPGs, like Mass Effect, which is coming in November, and is supposed to be the, you know, I guess the cat's meow, or whatever you would say.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's gonna be fucking awesome, is basically it.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it should be, you know, it's Bioware.
[SPEAKER_01]: Um...
[SPEAKER_01]: Also coming in September will be Project Gotham Racing 4, which in itself is also pretty impressive.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know, Project Gotham Racing 3 was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know if I'll get 4, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't control the cars in that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I suck at those type of games.
[SPEAKER_02]: I keep crashing into walls.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know how to drive.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I get all woman when I play those games.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't drive.
[SPEAKER_04]: Die.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Mass Effect.
[SPEAKER_02]: I looked at the trailer for Mass Effect.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think I got a semi.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was a real hot trailer.
[SPEAKER_02]: That game looks awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: When you saw Mass Effect, didn't you... For like a half a second, I thought, you know, Phantasy Star Online could have been this good if they had actually tried.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is like what Phantasy Star Online should have been.
[SPEAKER_01]: But instead, Phantasy Star Online gave us... Na, na, na, na, na, na, na.
[SPEAKER_02]: Na, na.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry, please listen to the theme of Phantasy Star Online if you don't get my joke.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or Phantasy Star Universe, whatever the hell it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: But no, Mass Effect looks great.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks like V, or some type of epic miniseries movie that's coming soon to the SyFy Network, but in HD.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's going to be pretty epic, too.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is only the first of the trilogy, I believe, for it.
[SPEAKER_01]: So it will be a pretty long story, and hell, just make a movie out of it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, it looks like a movie already, so.
[SPEAKER_02]: I heard that the conversation style in it's really cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, you use the thumbsticks to talk live.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, you basically have to choose an option while the other person's kind of talking or whatever, and then that can have an effect on the conversation.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that sounds kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_01]: I say they take the Mass Effect engine and give us another space quest.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess anything is possible.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who knows what might happen?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, there's actually a good thing that's going to happen for our friends overseas.
[SPEAKER_04]: In Europe, the Xbox 360 Elite will be out on the 24th of August, which actually was released, the information was released at E3, of course.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's not a price listed.
[SPEAKER_04]: The speculation is that it will be close to what it cost over here in the U.S.,
[SPEAKER_02]: So congratulations to Europe, even though you have to wait for things a little later.
[SPEAKER_02]: At least you're finally getting your Xbox 360 Elite.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you want it.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you want it, yeah, if you care.
[SPEAKER_01]: And if you can find it, because I know the ones over here are practically sold out everywhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: Make friends with people who work at video game shops.
[SPEAKER_01]: I guess producing that larger hard drive is a real challenge out there.
[SPEAKER_01]: Slapping that laptop drive into a little case.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wee.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, one thing you might play on your new Xbox 360 Elite is Seen It.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course, this was a big announcement that Microsoft made at their press conference this year, is that they're going to be putting out a casual game called Seen It.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, you might have heard of Seen It before.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a really popular DVD board game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, I don't know if they have this outside of the U.S., if they have this in other countries.
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically, it's a board game, and you play it with a DVD.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've played this before.
[SPEAKER_02]: You watch, like, little...
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, you know, didn't...
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I guess Uno was another attempt, but what have we really had since Uno?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like pure casual, maybe the solitaire game, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: But nothing's really caught on like Uno has.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, maybe Hold'em.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess I'll give you that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I think if you really want to reach the casual gaming audience, make your system a lot cheaper, and then they will come because of the price cuts, because it'll look more attractive, but
[SPEAKER_02]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a new controller, by the way, that will come with CNET, and it's a controller so simple that even your grandma can use it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's one giant button and four little buttons to use for the answers.
[SPEAKER_02]: And apparently the game is going to come with four of these controllers, which is kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: The funny thing, too, is it's ripped off of the controller from the Buzz game series, which looks almost identical to that one.
[SPEAKER_01]: Viva Piñata Party Animals
[SPEAKER_01]: And that's due out in November.
[SPEAKER_01]: Also, they announced some other stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: Some more games will be joining the Games for Windows lineup.
[SPEAKER_01]: Gears of War and Viva Pinata.
[SPEAKER_01]: Gears of War is actually supposed to have some additional content for it as well, which I imagine would be probably downloadable here on the Xbox 360, probably around the same time.
[SPEAKER_01]: And...
[SPEAKER_01]: Call of Duty 4, they announced that they're going to be doing an exclusive online beta with Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_01]: No details on what's going to be involved with that since they haven't launched these signups yet.
[SPEAKER_01]: But hopefully we'll know more about that soon since the game does come out in November.
[SPEAKER_01]: The other thing, which kind of joining the whole multiple colored accessories trend here,
[SPEAKER_01]: Pink and Blue Controllers in October
[SPEAKER_01]: And then if you didn't have a chance to go to E3, there are some pretty cool stuff on Xbox Live Marketplace for you.
[SPEAKER_01]: Some new demos including Blue Dragon, Ace Combat 6, NCAA Football 08, Stuntman Ignition, The Bigs, and Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix.
[SPEAKER_02]: So let's go around and talk about Microsoft's press conference and sort of your guys' reaction to it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'll pose this question to chat as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll read some of your comments.
[SPEAKER_02]: Were you happy with Microsoft's conference?
[SPEAKER_02]: Was there more you were looking for?
[SPEAKER_02]: And if you could, like, I don't know, I'll throw this totally arbitrary thing out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you could rate the press conference on a scale of 1 to 10, what would you give it?
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'm going to say this right off the bat, and I think this goes for all of us.
[SPEAKER_02]: Where was the anticipated price cut?
[SPEAKER_02]: It was indisposed.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: They hinted that they will be making an announcement closer to the fall.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I think we might have more on that later in the show, so we'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, Loki, did you like it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you not like the conference?
[SPEAKER_02]: What would you say?
[SPEAKER_01]: I would say that they set an example of what their conferences should be like.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's basically, they said, here, all the games we're going to show you are going to be coming out this year.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's how you fucking do it.
[SPEAKER_01]: You say, here's our lineup for this fall.
[SPEAKER_01]: Get excited, it's going to be out in a few months.
[SPEAKER_01]: As opposed to certain other companies that said, here's what's coming out.
[SPEAKER_01]: I forgot to mention that most of that's going to be next year, late next year, if not later.
[SPEAKER_01]: Stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_01]: I thought that they really hit the nail on the head with that stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's not really much more I could want from it.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was a little bit disappointing that certain games were announced also coming to their platform, but they're going to have a really solid lineup
[SPEAKER_01]: There are really certain other publishers and hardware makers are going to have a hard time catching up if something magical doesn't happen in the fourth quarter.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I would say probably give them an 8 or 9.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, care to give your two cents on what happened?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, given that you two covered most of my same thought on it, really...
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, I'm still in, I actually, I think that they are going to do the, I think actually I agree that it was smart for them not to announce a price drop, that if they put something like that more out public around Christmas, or, you know, right after Thanksgiving, you know, for the Christmas rush, then that will, I think, be more of a reason for consumers to go out and get one then.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't think there's a need that they... They don't need to really announce a price cut right now anyways because they're going into a really strong fourth quarter.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it's not like that their system's not number one selling right now in the United States.
[SPEAKER_01]: They don't really need any extra momentum right now.
[SPEAKER_01]: They need to see what the fourth quarter's like and then right at the prime moment, boom!
[SPEAKER_01]: And then just hit the Christmas rush right there.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I think that's what they're going to end up doing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, well, I guess my thoughts on it... I...
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I kind of would like to know what's going to be the big thing that I should be excited about after Halo 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was kind of hoping there might be a little hint of what's to come in 2008.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I guess I understand the strategy of putting all the cards on the table.
[SPEAKER_01]: What?
[SPEAKER_01]: They did.
[SPEAKER_01]: They were talking about Halo Wars.
[SPEAKER_01]: They were talking about Lost Odyssey, Mass Effect.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mass Effect is this year.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know, but it's after Halo 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, Grand Theft Auto 4, Beautiful Katamari.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, there's a big lineup that's not just Halo 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I figured they'd show that.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was all stuff that was previously announced, and the stuff that they, this is the first time we're announcing, Viva Piñata Party, and I was like, I don't fucking care.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, the CNET thing is a good effort, I suppose, but it's not enough to make you go, wow, you're really gonna win with that.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was like, ooh, it's neat, because, you know, I'm in the movie industry, so, you know, oh, that's kinda neat, that'd be kinda fun to play at work.
[SPEAKER_01]: I wasn't thinking, ooh, I gotta go get me one of those.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would maybe rate the conference like a
[SPEAKER_02]: 6.5, I don't know, it's better than Middle of the Road, but not by much, like, there was nothing that made me go, like, hooray, you know, or, like, maybe give me a gamer fangasm, it was mostly, okay, I figured that was coming, I figured that was coming, I figured that was coming, so, that's just me personally, let's go to chat, let's see what some chat folks thought there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lots of you guys here in chat commenting on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: DJ Tyrant says, Microsoft's conference should have addressed the rings of death issue much, much more.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, what do they need to... Why would they bring attention to that?
[SPEAKER_01]: Why would they even need to address that?
[SPEAKER_01]: They've already addressed that.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm just reading someone else's thoughts.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, I'm answering to that.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're expanding.
[SPEAKER_01]: Listen, I'm expanding on this, okay?
[SPEAKER_01]: And I'm tired of people complaining about it, and no, I'm not a fucking Microsoft fanboy.
[SPEAKER_01]: But here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're dealing with the problem.
[SPEAKER_01]: Your consoles now have a three-year warranty on them from the announcement date.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're going to fix any of them for free, and they've already fixed the problem in new consoles being manufactured right now.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, what part of it are they not doing anything about?
[SPEAKER_01]: That's what I want to know.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's no reason to even mention that stuff, because, okay, and actually Peter Moore did announce, okay, yeah, we made a mistake, but we're taking care of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, enough said.
[SPEAKER_02]: SSJ100Matt says, Microsoft Prince Conference was basically the status quo, not that many surprises, B in my mind.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think the status quo would be a C. No, that's all right.
[SPEAKER_02]: In the gaming industry, we always inflate scores a little bit, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: DDRDollarBill says, I wish achievement points meant something.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, you know, whatever happened to the whole... You win a no prize.
[SPEAKER_02]: But what happened to the whole thing?
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, remember they had the Old Spice Inflate Your Gamer Score Challenge, and, you know, you could win, like, actual... Like, whatever happened to that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, it just kind of...
[SPEAKER_02]: I agree, they need a little boost there.
[SPEAKER_02]: That could have been something that they could have talked about that might have gotten me a little more excited, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: TheRobD says, I gotta agree with Loki on Microsoft's press conference.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is a good example of how they should do a press conference.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just wish they would have announced some worthwhile stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: DJ Dark Knight says, Call of Duty 4 totally won me over.
[SPEAKER_02]: And ShadowNextGen disagrees with RobD and says, I thought Microsoft announced a great lineup.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a wrap-up on Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, before we get into some of the other companies, I want to ask real quick, because we didn't really cover it in the Gaming Week, but we did talk about how we were at SAC Anime, and I wanted to ask DarkSakura kind of how the rest of the convention went, and if you met any listeners of the program, or what kind of stuff was there game-wise, or what you did.
[SPEAKER_04]: I walked in with my Dolphy this morning and got attacked by Dolphy people.
[SPEAKER_04]: So hi, everybody that I met at the convention who was into Dolphys.
[SPEAKER_04]: and my poor doll got petted quite a bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that was really it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then I bought a Dalek.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exterminate.
[SPEAKER_04]: I spent most of the time in the dealer's room.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I'd have to say that I didn't watch any anime.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't really meet anybody except for Warrior Bob.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Andrew was there.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I bought a Dalek.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I bought a Heartless.
[SPEAKER_04]: Plushie.
[SPEAKER_02]: because this is not what conventions are about, buying crap just because you want it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I bought a Starman keychain for Mario and a boo and a coin box and a fire flower.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not a bad-sized convention for this town, considering we just had a big one in the Bay Area.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was actually better than the Japan Town Anime Fair, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: The only good thing about the Japan Town Anime Fair is that they had better cosplay.
[SPEAKER_04]: There was good cosplay, don't get me wrong.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sack anime is going to grow.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's gonna be bigger.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're gonna have a real, real big convention.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everybody was great.
[SPEAKER_04]: The staff was fantastic.
[SPEAKER_04]: Honestly, I was very ill-prepared for it, given that I've just come off Fanime.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, I think that, you know, with... Yeah, I almost cosplayed the Doctor.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shadow Next Gen.
[SPEAKER_01]: I wish I had thought about the free donuts and orange juice earlier, so we could have promoted that and maybe got a few more people in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, we had a bad time.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's my only complaint, is that we had a bad time for the panel.
[SPEAKER_04]: And these guys are suckers.
[SPEAKER_04]: They'll fill in that one time slot no one wants.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was good, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Next year, primetime.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow, you guys are turning into divas.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, we want to seriously say thanks for having us.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love A1 Comics now, even though they're local, because I got my Dalek for a lot less expensive than eBay had it.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's probably the same one I saw in their store that I called to tell you about.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, how funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Before we get into Nintendo's conference, let's talk release dates real quick, because we like to cover what's going to be coming out in the gaming world with our release dates.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jamie, why don't you start us off?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, for our friends in the UK, we have a few things coming out within this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: On the 18th, we have Bomberman Live for Xbox 360, and the 20th, we have The Darkness, Transformers the Game, and Two Worlds for Xbox 360 and PC.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Momotaro Densetsu 16 Train Conductor
[SPEAKER_02]: One of those simulation games.
[SPEAKER_02]: That looks cute.
[SPEAKER_02]: Coming out on the PlayStation 2, Shonen Oyoji Tsubasa Yoima Ten Ikare is coming out on July 19, 2007.
[SPEAKER_02]: Looks like a little adventure game, probably based off yet another anime.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know this series, Ultraman Fighting Evolution 3 is coming out on the PlayStation 2, also on July 19, although I believe that is simply a price reduction, not just a brand new game.
[SPEAKER_02]: But hey, it's Ultraman.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had to mention it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cinnamon Ball, Kurukuru Sweets Paradise I had a Batsumaru pillow once
[SPEAKER_02]: I love Batsumaru.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's my favorite.
[SPEAKER_04]: I gave it to my friend in Texas.
[SPEAKER_02]: And since we just talked about an anime convention, of course we have to mention that there is yet another Naruto game coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Saikyo Ninja Daishu 5 is coming out on the DS July 19th as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Another Naruto game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bet you can't wait.
[SPEAKER_02]: All of you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can wait and keep waiting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now this is one you don't have to be a fan of Japanese games to know this game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bomberman, Touch Bomberman Land, Star Bomber, No Miracle World, coming out from Hudson July 19th on the DS in Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's all I will be mentioning this week for release dates.
[SPEAKER_02]: So let's go to the U.S.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: The U.S., you're going to be getting ready for some football because...
[SPEAKER_01]: NCAA Football 08 is going to be coming out this week on PlayStation 2, Xbox, PlayStation 3, and the 360.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then of course, if you're not a fan of college football, then maybe you want to check out the new All-Pro Football 2K8, which is coming out on both Xbox 360 and PlayStation 3 this week.
[SPEAKER_01]: If you're not a fan of football at all, maybe you're a fan of some other sports games, including Hot Shots Tennis on PlayStation 2 and Rugby 08 on PlayStation 2, both coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_01]: Or, let's see, on the PSP, Smash Court Tennis 3 is making its way out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Tales of the World Radiant Mythology on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then just a small little game called Parappa the Rapper on the PSP is finally making its way out, which will be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then, of course, on the Wii, you have absolutely nothing.
[SPEAKER_01]: Surprise.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then on the DS, absolutely nothing as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I was wrong.
[SPEAKER_02]: In the US, this isn't a slow game week because you named a lot of big sports titles there, especially with Madden.
[SPEAKER_02]: NCAA Football 08 Escape from Bug Island
[SPEAKER_01]: and Mario Strikers Charge
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: By the way, speaking of Naruto, bringing up the game during the Japanese release dates reminded me, did anybody catch that Xbox 360 tried to, like, at Microsoft's conference, they tried to make a big deal out of how they had, like, this exclusive Naruto game coming to the 360?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, well, goody.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was on damn near everything else.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which was met with a resounding meh.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, this one hasn't been on every other system.
[SPEAKER_01]: However, it's not the only Naruto game coming out this year.
[SPEAKER_01]: In fact, there's another one on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's one already that's come out, one more that's coming out on PlayStation 2, another one on the PSP, and I think a few more on the DS.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, if you don't have the Xbox 360, man, how are you going to play some Naruto games?
[SPEAKER_01]: That's what I want to know.
[SPEAKER_01]: TheRobD in chat says, the Naruto game on 360 is exclusive and it looks damn good.
[SPEAKER_02]: It does.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's not a fighting game, I think.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, well, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_02]: We can give it a chance.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're just teasing a little bit on the Naruto stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, let's check out Nintendo's press conference.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll go over and get some stories from Nintendo's press conference.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um...
[SPEAKER_04]: Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_04]: Brawl
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm a good girl.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's worth the wait if it's going to be good, like really good.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it does look like it's going to be really good.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know they've showed a stage.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think this was in the last week or two.
[SPEAKER_02]: They showed a stage from Animal Crossing, an Animal Crossing-inspired stage.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that looked awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: But did you hear about if you play it at 8 p.m.
[SPEAKER_01]: on Saturday?
[SPEAKER_01]: Because the stages will change depending on the time of day that you play.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, no, I know it's coming.
[SPEAKER_01]: You play at 8 p.m.
[SPEAKER_01]: on Saturday, you get, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: KK comes out and sings.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is great.
[SPEAKER_04]: He should be a selectable character, but only at 8 o'clock.
[SPEAKER_01]: Did you see the other thing?
[SPEAKER_02]: These are those types of little details that are going to make Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_02]: Brawl like...
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought he was playable.
[SPEAKER_02]: The impression I got was like, you know how in the last Brawl game you had the Pokeballs, and it was all the Pokemon that would come help?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, now it's Assist, and various characters will come out and help you, like the Nintendog will paw at the screen, and Dr. Right makes the skyscrapers that go boom!
[SPEAKER_02]: But nevertheless, it's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, but it's, what a random little tidbit, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, SSJ100Magichat confirms he's not playable.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, I thought that he would have been a weird character.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was surprised, that, you know, that was another thing I was surprised we didn't hear anymore of like, hey, Mega Man's gonna be in the game, or hey, you know, Sonic's gonna be in the game, although I'm pretty much guaranteed right now Sonic's gonna be in the game since, uh, they're making a Mario and Sonic game, so obviously they're gonna, that's what a lot of fans think, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do something.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nintendo also announced at the conference that there is going to be a Wii Mario Kart, to no one's real big surprise.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, we kind of speculated that of course there would be a new Mario Kart game coming to the Wii, but there were some surprises, and one of them was that it will be online...
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you, Nintendo, for hearing our prayers.
[SPEAKER_02]: For that game, at least.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, at least for that game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe if, you know, they could have done it for some other stuff, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: But that's okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: At least they're starting to move in the right direction.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, Mario Kart was one of the first online games on the DS, so I suppose tradition can continue.
[SPEAKER_02]: But then they're also going to be bringing out a Wii wheel, which will be a peripheral that you can use with Mario Kart on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, of course, obviously... Oh, Wii!
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a little Wii wheel that you plug your Wii mode into, and you can actually turn it like it's a regular steering wheel.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wii!
[SPEAKER_02]: And Loki, I know you mentioned on Saturday at the convention, they already have this type of peripheral out there, and... This has been out since launch.
[SPEAKER_01]: They've got two really shitty-ass Ubisoft games called Monster 4x4 World Circuit and GT.
[SPEAKER_01]: And let me tell you, it comes with a crappy wheel just like this.
[SPEAKER_01]: Basically, you snap the controller in.
[SPEAKER_01]: It serves no purpose other than, oh, I can't imagine that the remote's a wheel, so I need an actual wheel in front of me to turn it.
[SPEAKER_01]: So then you play the game with that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, granted, okay, I'll give them this.
[SPEAKER_01]: It is free, but it's a gimmick to sell the game, just like it was a gimmick to sell those two other games.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I'm going to tell you this much.
[SPEAKER_01]: I will not play it with the damn wheel, and thank God they're going to have multiple control options, because I fucking hate games with the Wii that require you to have the Wii remote sideways to steer it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I like Excite Truck, where you have it, you know, flat, and then you steer it that way.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Blaze in our chat asks, does Excite Truck come with a wheel?
[SPEAKER_02]: It actually does not.
[SPEAKER_01]: It does not.
[SPEAKER_02]: But some people use the other wheel adapter for it.
[SPEAKER_01]: You can't.
[SPEAKER_01]: You can't use the other wheel adapter for it.
[SPEAKER_01]: It won't work because the actual controller needs to be held parallel to the ground and then you steer it that way.
[SPEAKER_01]: Whereas the Ubisoft games, you have to hold the controller perpendicular to the ground and
[SPEAKER_01]: and then turn it that way.
[SPEAKER_01]: So it's a completely different axis that you would turn it on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, Actdeft says the Ubisoft wheel is crappy.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Wii wheel looks like it's better designed.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, I mean, it is a Nintendo first-party product.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, great.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's a better designed piece of crap to get the Sigma controller in.
[SPEAKER_01]: Here's the thing I have a problem with.
[SPEAKER_01]: And we'll get into some more of this stuff with our next story.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm having a problem with them releasing stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: I thought, okay, the whole point of having the expansion port in the bottom of the Wii Remote is that we would be getting new peripherals that will plug into the bottom, other than the nunchuck.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_01]: Which I will go into this next story here with the Zapper.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wait, real quick, before we get to the Zapper, can I say one other thing about Mario Kart?
[SPEAKER_02]: You couldn't see a whole lot of the actual game itself, but I did notice in the brief little bits that they showed of Mario Kart on the Wii...
[SPEAKER_02]: There's only one person in the car.
[SPEAKER_02]: So thank God this isn't a sequel to Double Dash.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I will give Nintendo another few points there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now you can move on.
[SPEAKER_01]: The other thing they announced was the Wii Zapper.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, I remember looking at this at E3 originally, you know, last year when they had a prototype.
[SPEAKER_01]: And that prototype looked pretty awesome because it was actually something that the Wii controller would plug into, you know, and it's a whole new peripheral.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: Knock it off!
[SPEAKER_01]: Seriously!
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, this thing looks like crap.
[SPEAKER_01]: The only thing that's going to be a selling point for is it's $19.99 and it will come with a pack-in game.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, great, you get a game for $20 and this piece of crap with it.
[SPEAKER_01]: But, seriously, they need just... Instead of releasing something that the remote, you know...
[SPEAKER_01]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_01]: Just, you know, they kind of looked at these other companies out there and said, oh, look, they're making gimmicky crap and people are buying it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's make some gimmicky crap.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, we don't want to be left out of that gravy train.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry, it's just gravy train.
[SPEAKER_01]: But isn't this, don't you think this is one of those things that you should really try?
[SPEAKER_01]: No.
[SPEAKER_01]: I can tell you right now, okay, if I want, I like the other one because the trigger is in the back, it was like a shotgun, you know, it would be comfortable.
[SPEAKER_01]: It had a little analog stick above the top there, kind of like the new GunCon, and that would be comfortable to hold.
[SPEAKER_01]: This thing looks like crap.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's just probably because, I don't know about you guys, but right now I know nunchucks are hard to come by.
[SPEAKER_01]: Why I don't know that they can make them fast enough is beyond me, but...
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, obviously making any additional peripherals that have actual working parts in there would be too much for them.
[SPEAKER_01]: Instead, molding plastic is a lot easier.
[SPEAKER_01]: If you want to pay $20 for a piece of molded plastic, go right ahead.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I guarantee you, playing these games without the zapper will be fucking easier and a lot better than playing it with the zapper.
[SPEAKER_01]: And you will be sorry that you bought this product.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know this isn't in our show role tonight, so I can say that there's YouTubage on the internet of the new Silent Hill arcade game because it's being location tested in Europe or something right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: So some bootlegs of the game hit the internet and...
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: I might have sex with everybody at Nintendo because that would be phenomenal.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's just, it's crap.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, there's other third-party, you know, peripherals out there.
[SPEAKER_01]: If you want the B like a gun, I've seen one that the remote plugs into it, and it looks like a pistol.
[SPEAKER_01]: It has a pistol grip on it, and you just pull the trigger, and it's like pulling the B button.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, now, BlackWolf says you don't use the front trigger at all, and he was at E3.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, the front trigger in the front, okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: Why would you not use the trigger in the front?
[SPEAKER_01]: What the hell is there a trigger there for, then, if you don't use it for the game?
[SPEAKER_01]: It's for pushing the goddamn B button.
[SPEAKER_02]: I still say bring me Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks like crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bring me Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shoot him up to the Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: I will buy the Zapper.
[SPEAKER_02]: I will hump the Zapper.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I will be raped by Pyramid Head and it will be good.
[SPEAKER_01]: I put out this challenge for you.
[SPEAKER_01]: When this shit comes out and when these two fucking games, Resident Evil, Umbrella Chronicles, and Ghost Squad come out, I would like to see a side-by-side challenge with someone with the Zapper and without the Zapper and see who gets a better fucking score.
[SPEAKER_01]: I bet you anything...
[SPEAKER_01]: Money!
[SPEAKER_01]: I will bet fucking $50 that the goddamn person without the zapper will wipe the floor with someone with the zapper.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's why.
[SPEAKER_01]: This thing is a piece of awkward shit, is what it is.
$50!
[SPEAKER_01]: I have $50 on this.
[SPEAKER_01]: I will like to see this challenge.
[SPEAKER_01]: We will perform this challenge in studio.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, Rob, you up to it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sure, I don't have $50.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I'm not...
[SPEAKER_04]: Taking the bet, I'll just play the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_02]: How about this?
[SPEAKER_02]: Since I don't have $50, how about this?
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll make the bet.
[SPEAKER_02]: The bet will be a date.
[SPEAKER_02]: If the gun is indeed better, then I will take your wife out on a date and take her off your hands for a night so you can do nothing but play video games.
[SPEAKER_02]: but if the gun is better then you will take me out on a date deal that's it deal alright then the whole chat has heard it so if the Wii remote is better and the games are better without the zapper peripheral then I will take Loki's wife out on a date and she won't be able to nag at Loki for a whole night but if the gun is indeed better Loki will take me out on a date and you better put out
[SPEAKER_04]: We have this on record.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm telling you, this thing looks like crap.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's no way it's going to make it better.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's no way at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: WeDoInChat says, Rob offers himself again.
[SPEAKER_02]: What a skank.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: My significant other might have problems with this, but that's all right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: BlackWolf says, I really don't want to interject facts into a Loki rant because it's too funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: Weedo also says, Loki needs a hug and Rob needs to stop being so skanky.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Frisbee says it's a 9.4 on the Loki scale.
[SPEAKER_02]: And SSJ100Matt says, Loki's rant level was at 9 out of 10.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, there we go.
[SPEAKER_02]: So the date bet over the zapper is on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let your wife know she was just completely used as an object in the program.
[SPEAKER_02]: $50 for one night with your wife.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, indecent Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, anyway, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_02]: New story, please.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, in other releases in regards to Nintendo, for anyone who cared, Super Mario Galaxy will be out on November 12th.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: Mario Sunshine Mario 64 Mario 64
[SPEAKER_02]: If they could ROM hack GameCube games like they can the old school 8-bit Nintendo games, I'm sure there would be a Super Mario Water Sports.
[SPEAKER_02]: They would just redo the sprites so he whips it out and uses it as a gun.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's freaky.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was back on the Game Boy with the Link's Adventure.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow, I'm looking forward to Mario Galaxy as well, but I don't want to make a complete opinion until I'm able to play it, but certainly the screenshots and videos look enticing.
[SPEAKER_02]: This was Nintendo's big thing, for lack of a better term.
[SPEAKER_02]: This was their big thing at the press conference.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have to admit, nobody called this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nobody knew this was coming.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wii Fit.
[SPEAKER_02]: was the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be a game that comes with what's called the balance board.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you can think of it as kind of brain training for your body, which I'm sure the idea came from.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's probably borrowed from the brain training series.
[SPEAKER_02]: But using the balance board, you can do push-ups, steps aerobics, this goalie defense type thing, and dancing.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I guess it's taking the old school 8-bit game dance aerobics into a whole new... Remember with the power pad?
[SPEAKER_02]: Take it into a whole new generation.
[SPEAKER_02]: And this was met with a resounding meh from the gaming community.
[SPEAKER_02]: But there's something about this that I think is going to make the Wii catch fire even more.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because soccer moms are going to continue to want to buy this for their kids.
[SPEAKER_02]: Honestly.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's fucking smart.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think it looks cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, this is something I actually kind of want to buy.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because I need an excuse to work out, apparently.
[SPEAKER_01]: But here's the other thing, too, that a lot of people aren't looking at.
[SPEAKER_01]: See, this is how they need to do their peripherals.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is something new.
[SPEAKER_01]: Something innovative.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_01]: This...
[SPEAKER_01]: You can imagine incorporating it into a snowboarding game or a skateboarding game or something like that.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's actually a kind of neat peripheral if they use it in that sense.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like, say, the next SSX game that comes out, you can use this with a remote as some added immersion into the game.
[SPEAKER_01]: But this plastic add-on shit is stupid.
[SPEAKER_01]: But this will be cool, though, I think.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Honestly, it's a really freaking smart move, and I hate to come off sounding like a Nintendo fanboy.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, this is nothing that, you know, obviously I'm still very disappointed there was no real news about, like, online gaming or whatever, but honestly, in the direction the Wii has always said they were going to go, and that they've been going in, this is a logical next step that's going to make these things be popular all over again this Christmas.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's going to be a smart move for them.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's not coming out this year, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, it's not?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I thought it was this Christmas.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, next year.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, damn them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Really?
[SPEAKER_02]: That long?
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it looked like the game was pretty well into progress, and they're really going to make us wait that long?
[SPEAKER_01]: It's not coming out until 2008, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, I will say, though, however, that the announcement of Wii Fit did give us this year's Giant Enemy Crab Award.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, that would be the biggest flub ever.
[SPEAKER_02]: D.K.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bongo Blast is coming out in October
[SPEAKER_01]: This is the bongo racing game that's coming out.
[SPEAKER_01]: I guess, I think actually you can use the bongos if you've got them.
[SPEAKER_01]: Otherwise, you can just use the Wii Remote and nunchuck and stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it's going to be a racing game, which looks like crap.
[SPEAKER_01]: The other one is a brand new channel called the Check Me Out Channel.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it's kind of a combination of a me community as well as a hot or not thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: You basically can search for different me's.
[SPEAKER_01]: I use this example on Saturday.
[SPEAKER_01]: If you're looking for a Chuck Norris me, you can browse through all the people's Chuck Norris me's and check out the one that you think most looks like Chuck Norris.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then you can vote that one high or download it and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_01]: So that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, that's pretty much, I think, all the big stuff that they were announcing this year.
[SPEAKER_01]: A lot of it...
[SPEAKER_01]: A lot of it was just kind of like, yeah, we've heard your cry for online gaming and stuff, and we're doing what we want still.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bobby Blackwolf had a really funny comment in chat that I think really sums things up here.
[SPEAKER_02]: It says, Nintendo's press conference summarized by Bobby Blackwolf.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is how we've printed money in the past.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's a bone we're throwing to hardcore gamers, and here's how we will print money in the future.
[SPEAKER_02]: I...
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of a true statement in my mind.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, let's do the same thing we did for Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's go around what you liked, what you didn't like, rate it.
[SPEAKER_02]: You want to start us off, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_04]: For Nintendo?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that Wii Fit's redeemed the whole thing, so it gets a nine.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you are really excited about Wii Fit that much?
[SPEAKER_04]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: I actually think that they lost some
[SPEAKER_01]: I kind of thought they were a little bit better than that.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was nice to see that they did announce some street dates for some games coming out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Good, because, you know, there's some definite spaces in between some of these better games.
[SPEAKER_01]: And, I don't know, the Wii Fit thing is great, you know, because they're looking for that whole health fitness angle, but I was really disappointed there's not a lot of talk of online.
[SPEAKER_01]: They really seem to skimp that whole part of, was it Super Smash, or
[SPEAKER_01]: Not Super Smash Bros., but Metroid Prime.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know it's not supposed to be online, I guess, so... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then I would rate it probably... Probably a 6, actually.
[SPEAKER_01]: It just wasn't... This was one of those things, I was watching the live feeds of them, I actually turned it off because I got bored.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'm a little bit torn because I want to give Nintendo props for sticking to their guns and kind of continuing down this path that they promised they were going to do next year in regards to the new generation of gaming versus the next generation of gaming.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I give them props there, but I am still left with disappointment over the lack of some type of centralized online system.
[SPEAKER_02]: It talks about more details on WiiWare, anything that could compete with the behemoth of Xbox Live as far as online goes.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I still felt like there was a lot
[SPEAKER_02]: to be desired.
[SPEAKER_02]: But then again, you know, that is for the hardcore gamer.
[SPEAKER_02]: But they're going to win a million points with Soccer Moms, and, you know, they're going to continue to do very well in the next year.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I personally give them a 6, but looking from it, like, if I wasn't so selfish, I would probably give them more of an 8.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, that's that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's look at chat and see what the chat says.
[SPEAKER_02]: SSJ100Matt says, I'm giving it a C-D+.
[SPEAKER_02]: They showed their true colors this year that they are careless about hardcore gamers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actdeft says, Rob D, I think Microsoft was worse.
[SPEAKER_02]: They didn't show anything new.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that was to Rob D's comments that says, I give Nintendo 6 out of 10.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was worse than the other two.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're going in a different direction, but they announced Mario Kart.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob D also says, Nintendo's press conference was extremely disappointing to me because I think they're showing me that they might be leaving me behind a little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Zappy asks, was that fitness game for Xbox any good?
[SPEAKER_02]: If you're talking about your self-fitness, no, it wasn't.
[SPEAKER_02]: Weedoo says Wii needs a soccer kicking game to win over the soccer moms.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you know, they have the goalie thing in Wii Fit, so who knows.
[SPEAKER_02]: GS191 says, I'll make a bold statement.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nintendo did nothing, I mean nothing, to convince me to buy a Wii between now and Christmas.
[SPEAKER_02]: BlackWolf asks, do you have a source for Wii Fit not coming out in 2007, Loki?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because they did not confirm or deny that on the show floor.
[SPEAKER_01]: I thought it was not on their list.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was on their release list, I believe, for 2008.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because it was supposed to be... God, I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know it said not this year, though.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know that for a fact.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, two more comments then we'll move on.
[SPEAKER_02]: DJ Tyrant says, I give them an 8 out of 10.
[SPEAKER_02]: They showed why they're in a great position right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: They've got solid titles and a great lineup ahead of them with their regular titles, Mario, Metroid, etc.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Gerardimo says, Just my opinion on Nintendo's online situation.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are there really that many games worth playing online right now?
[SPEAKER_02]: Seriously, Mario Party or Big Brain Academy online?
[SPEAKER_02]: That wouldn't be much fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I disagree.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think Mario Party would actually be a lot of fun online.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think multiplayer is the only way to go and sometimes your house just can't accommodate all those people.
[SPEAKER_02]: But that's my opinion, and that's yours.
[SPEAKER_02]: So chat.orangeontradio.com if you ever want to join us in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, of course, we do tape live on Sunday nights at orangeontradio.com on our live 365 feed, which did not shut down on July 15th, contrary to the rumor about the whole Internet.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, thankfully, there was a little reprieve by Congress, which has given people time more to negotiate the rates.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course, we encourage you to visit savenetradio.org and learn more about the situation impacting Internet radio that continues to.
[SPEAKER_04]: for now let's move on to some other stories that don't have really to do with press conferences per se but some other things going around around the gaming industry well this is actually pretty cool we mentioned earlier but Paper Mario is going to the European Virtual Console and I think that's pretty cool because it was a really you know cool game I didn't get to play a whole bunch of it but it was you know classic Nintendo 64 stuff it's kind of hard to think of Nintendo 64 stuff as being classic though because you know I remember when it was new but um
[SPEAKER_04]: It is, though, 1,000 points to download.
[SPEAKER_04]: So right now, though, on the European Virtual Console, then the total of Nintendo 64 games, they have now Paper Mario, Super Mario 64, Mario Kart 64, The Legend of Zelda Ocarina of Time, Lylat Wars, and F-Zero X. Also coming out on Virtual Console is Airzonk, which was a TurboGrafx-16 game, which was sort of okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's a 600-point game.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: GamePolitics.com
[SPEAKER_02]: And of course, we remember we talked previously about the brain training-ish game, or it was actually Mind Quiz was the real game, that had the controversy behind it because it used the word spastic in it, which here in the U.S., not really a big deal of a word.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not a very controversial word, but in the U.K.
[SPEAKER_02]: carries a lot more meaning and oomph about the mentally handicapped.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's tragic.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting that it kind of continues another recall over that word.
[SPEAKER_02]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, another thing that's tragic is the fact that the government and government groups feel that they need to step in to protect kids from M-rated games.
[SPEAKER_01]: So the National Institute on Media and Family is building an army of undercover agents or shoppers for their 11th annual video game report card.
[SPEAKER_01]: And, um,
[SPEAKER_01]: They're going to be finding actual miners to go in and attempt to buy M-rated games to see if the actual retailers will prevent them from buying them.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think it's good that they're trying to enforce that stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: I still think, though, that parents should be more responsible.
[SPEAKER_01]: Stop giving your kids money if you don't want them buying crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well...
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's move on to another segment we like to do every week here on the program.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's called the Website of the Week, and it's brought to you by DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: She likes to surf the Internet up and down and all over every week and find a website to share with you all out there on the Internet.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, where should the kids be pointing their web browsers to this week?
[SPEAKER_04]: The Website of the Week is one that will definitely make an impact, I think, on the world at large.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is awfulplasticsurgery.com It's a site taking very famous people and showing just how bad their plastic surgery is.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm really not joking.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's awfulplasticsurgery.com Is it not for the squeamish?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I have a feeling a site like this may make you kind of go, No, it's not that bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just, you know, pictures you can find anywhere on the internet.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, thank you, DarkSakura, for that lovely website of the week.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's also, I think, one that's called goodplasticsurgery.com, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: That shows, you know, plastic surgery's done right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, an example on here is, like, I find this one funny, Brooke Hogan's boob implants.
[SPEAKER_04]: And who was it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Victoria Beckham, her boobs that just look wrong.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: it's funny, I think it's hilarious
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, also something I think that is kind of funny and looks like maybe plastic surgery gone wrong is this very interesting peripheral that was announced at E3 2007.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the Wii Party Station.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the Wii Party Station.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nyko is, you know, they make a lot of these types of interesting peripherals.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, look at this.
[SPEAKER_02]: They've made this party station.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a coffee table centerpiece for the Wii games.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's basically got four stations that can hold your Wii remote there.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's a little party station for all your Wii crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's kind of smart.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can have a Wii tennis party, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, and the price for it?
$24.99.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that's not bad just as a storage unit.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, yeah, it's kind of actually not a bad price.
[SPEAKER_02]: I look at it and go, WTF?
[SPEAKER_04]: If they had a coffee table, it'd be great.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, there's a lot of people that are into having the Wii sports parties, and, you know, especially for, again, the casual gamers and the soccer mom parties of the world.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, you know, I keep using them, but you know what I mean.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, people that aren't really...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: I like having the freezer tray.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a really good idea.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sure, go ahead and buy this.
[SPEAKER_01]: You're just encouraging them to make more crap like this.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's going to come out later.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's not that bad, Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's better than those little plastic golf clubs that you put your remote into.
[SPEAKER_01]: Is it?
[SPEAKER_01]: Really, is it?
[SPEAKER_01]: If the little golf club held chips and dip in it, would it be better?
[SPEAKER_04]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everything is better with chips and dip.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to take a quick break because as GS68 says in the chatroom, Loki's hit his limit break.
[SPEAKER_02]: So he needs to calm down a little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: He needs to go fag his anger, which by the way, somebody left an iTunes review.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: MGS68 makes a good point here chips equal oily equals oily remote which equals more remotes being thrown into TVs so keep the paper towels nearby shut up alright we're going to take a quick break we'll be right back after this with more of Orange Lounge Radio Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and is podcast to the world twice a week stay tuned to our podcast feed for the conclusion of this week's Orange Lounge Radio