[SPEAKER_05]: Tonight, January 1st, 2012, DLC is finally coming to the 3DS, Valve says Half-Life 3 rumors are just trolling, and a fan remake of a computer game classic has been released.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hello my friends out there on the internet and welcome back to another week of the show where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_09]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: It is episode number 440 for this January 1st, 2012.
[SPEAKER_09]: Really easy day to remember.
[SPEAKER_09]: My name is Rob Roberts and I'll be joining you over the next few hours to talk video games with my co-host, first off, the one, the only, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or DarkSakura, whatever you want to call her.
[SPEAKER_09]: How are you doing?
[SPEAKER_06]: When people get my name right.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: He had a family engagement, I mean it is technically a holiday, New Year's Day, and so sometimes there's family stuff, especially with the new baby he's got.
[SPEAKER_09]: So they've got a family thing going on, so he's not here tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: That baby is not as new as that baby once was.
[SPEAKER_06]: He better have the baby thing down.
[SPEAKER_09]: That baby's getting older just like you.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you.
[SPEAKER_09]: But joining us tonight, as he tends to do when we need another host, please welcome to the studio, Alan.
[SPEAKER_09]: How you doing, Alan?
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_09]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_02]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_09]: The week before that, though, was our last show, and that was the last show from Studio DarkSakura, or the fifth studio in OLR's history.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: But tonight we are in a new studio.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's Studio 6, and it's from Alan and I's place.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_09]: So... Rob.
[SPEAKER_09]: What?
[SPEAKER_09]: Watch your grammar.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mine and Alan.
[SPEAKER_06]: It should be Alan and my house.
[SPEAKER_09]: How about Shut and Up?
[SPEAKER_06]: How about Bite My Butt?
[SPEAKER_09]: 3rd, no, 2nd studio we were in, which was when Loki and I lived together.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was a while ago, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: We actually did the show kind of in the dining room and in the living room.
[SPEAKER_09]: There was antics that always happen.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's kind of a similar setup to what we have going on right now in this Studio 6.
[SPEAKER_09]: So we're hoping at some point we can return the live streaming of games and stuff during the show over one of them stream and video websites.
[SPEAKER_09]: We used to use JustinTV.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've done stuff on Ustream.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know which way we'd go.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll figure that out when we actually have video.
[SPEAKER_06]: I now have experience doing custom graphics for Justin, for not for Justin TV, for Ustream, so.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, hey.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_09]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: I did them for you, for Umlaut.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Say hello to the chatters, chatroom.orangeloungeradio, or excuse me, chat.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm a little rusty after a week off.
[SPEAKER_09]: Chat.orangeloungeradio.com is where you can join us if you want to talk live with us here on this New Year's Day.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it looks like we have a Bobby Blackwolf Did he just join?
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi Bobby How come Bobby could show up for our show but he couldn't be bothered to do his own show tonight?
[SPEAKER_09]: That's because he likes our show better As I said to the all games chatters, Bobby didn't want to work, he just wanted to bang on the drum all day That's a joke because he does drumming stuff for the Atlanta Falcons So my mother is calling me on my cell phone right now, like doesn't she know I have a radio show on Sunday nights?
[SPEAKER_09]: Doesn't she know?
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe she's listening.
[SPEAKER_09]: Rob, what do you mean you moved the show to your house?
[SPEAKER_09]: Rob, did that cost money?
[SPEAKER_09]: Rob?
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_09]: We are live, of course, Sunday nights, every Sunday night, even when it's New Year's Day.
[SPEAKER_09]: And All Games Radio is the kind and gracious network that allows us to steal their bandwidth no matter what studio we're in.
[SPEAKER_09]: www.allgames.com, 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern, typically after the Bobby Blackwolf show when he's, you know, not off drumming.
[SPEAKER_09]: Tonight, after the show, R9 cast.
[SPEAKER_09]: They had a jumbo episode because they are usually on it for Pacific.
[SPEAKER_09]: And they went long.
[SPEAKER_09]: They had an extended edition.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: I think I might have caught a couple.
[SPEAKER_09]: But the flea market is basically... I don't know how to describe it for those that have never been.
[SPEAKER_09]: I imagine everybody's been to one at some point in their town, but then some people might not live in places big enough that have them.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: But they're basically like gigantic garage sales.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is that an accurate description, Alan?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, yeah, I guess you could say that.
[SPEAKER_02]: A lot of the wares are new and handmade, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not all recycled junk, but... I like to think of it as a giant thrift store.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: That works.
[SPEAKER_09]: So...
[SPEAKER_02]: Huge farmer's market.
[SPEAKER_02]: Probably the biggest farmer's market I've ever seen.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: The one here we have locally in the Sacramento area is just gigantic.
[SPEAKER_09]: So one of the things that's fun to go shopping for is produce.
[SPEAKER_09]: And we bought blood oranges.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: But the other thing that's fun to go shopping for is video games.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because there's a lot of people that will bring out their old shit.
[SPEAKER_09]: And even I saw arcade machines for sale in some of the little side... They have a side auction.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's weird.
[SPEAKER_09]: So in the side auction, they had...
[SPEAKER_06]: It's technically a different one.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's Auction Town.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's not part of Deny-Os where we went.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, we saw Burger Time for $950, like a legit arcade cabinet.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the cabinet was in good shape.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was pretty good for its age.
[SPEAKER_09]: Considering that game is from, what, 82?
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe somewhere around there, 82, 83.
[SPEAKER_09]: Considering that game is as old as it is, that machine was in beautiful condition.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was $950, and I was like,
[SPEAKER_06]: Alan!
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you see what was on the other side of the machine next to it?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, what was that?
[SPEAKER_06]: A berserk in just as good condition.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like that's the old one with the little bouncing ball, like the little happy face.
[SPEAKER_09]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_09]: But we did buy video games.
[SPEAKER_09]: At least I know I bought video games.
[SPEAKER_09]: I bought SingStar Queen, which I've talked about on the show before that I wanted it, but I wasn't going to get it until it went on sale.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I guess I forgot to get it amongst all the other video games that came out last year because it was a crazy year.
[SPEAKER_09]: and I bought Seeing Star Queen for $8 at the flea market.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was awesome and it was sealed.
[SPEAKER_09]: It might have been resealed.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sometimes the stuff at the flea market, they've used the little machine to reseal it, but it worked fine.
[SPEAKER_09]: I played it the other day.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then I bought, get this,
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_09]: it didn't play exactly like the board game like it kind of put this logic puzzle twist on it where it would tell you like the lead pipe was in the conservatory and you have to kind of like tie it all together so if if Miss Peacock was in the conservatory then she must have had the lead pipe you know that whole thing so um yeah good times so it's cool to play retro games and a favorite of mine was Clue on the Super Nintendo for no particular reason it wasn't really that great of a game but it's
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: I did and we ate them all last night.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_09]: That tortilla lady took you to the cleaners.
[SPEAKER_06]: I bought two for three.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's not bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: Two bags and there were six in each.
[SPEAKER_06]: I did what she suggested.
[SPEAKER_06]: I got pumpkin tortillas which were amazing because pumpkin everything is awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know it wouldn't be OLR if we didn't have a food tangent.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: I think you're projecting a little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just a little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, the thing is that I had a lot of amazing Super Nintendo games with the box and instruction booklet and they were all in perfect shape because I treat my stuff very well.
[SPEAKER_02]: They've all been sold on eBay years and years ago for a lot of money and I was kind of reminded actually of the price of how some of those games go for at the flea market.
[SPEAKER_02]: Was it the Super Nest Lufia?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was like 80 bucks you wanted for that cart.
[SPEAKER_02]: So yeah, there's still some rare stuff out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I used to have them but I got rid of them.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know you guys are welcome to borrow.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you have the wild hair to play anything, you're welcome to borrow anything I've got.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think most stuff on the Super Nintendo, I don't know, it's really like I'll get an urge to just play it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm usually trying to play the new stuff to keep on top of stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's very rare that I'm like, oh, I want to go play Clue on the Super Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_09]: But when it's right in front of me, I go, I remember how cool this game was.
[SPEAKER_09]: I need to just pick this up and take it home because it's half off.
[SPEAKER_09]: I paid...
[SPEAKER_09]: How many did you get through?
[SPEAKER_09]: Not even one.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're toward the end of what we just got.
[SPEAKER_06]: When we last played, everyone got their upgrades.
[SPEAKER_09]: You got through Final Fantasy 1-2.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's Final Fantasy Half.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, something about just starting off with 6.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sitting down and going through 6.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like 4 don't get me wrong but 6 is one that we'll just take turns with because I know that game like the back of my freaking hand I've played through that game so many million times or Chrono Trigger because then it's just a matter of New Game Plus
[SPEAKER_09]: Super Nintendos Never Die
[SPEAKER_09]: Those things are pretty durable.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I thought this was interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: Kaijudo kind of followed it up a little later with, the sad thing is 20 years from now, I doubt many people will say they have a PlayStation 3 or Xbox 360 that still works.
[SPEAKER_09]: How true.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, the old systems were quite durable, weren't they?
[SPEAKER_02]: And they were all just hard plastic with a little green circuit board in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, not many moving parts.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think Dan said that they had dropped a Super Nintendo down two flights of stairs and it still worked when he was a kid.
[SPEAKER_09]: Those things are rocks.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, they were.
[SPEAKER_09]: But yet, an Xbox 360, you're lucky to get one that never red rings.
[SPEAKER_06]: You knock it over once onto the carpet and it's dead.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_09]: They sure don't build them like they used to, but of course, a lot of that could be, to be fair.
[SPEAKER_09]: We did make a conversion somewhere along the way from cartridges to CDs, therefore DVDs, therefore Blu-rays.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was a pretty major shift in format.
[SPEAKER_06]: well you can even see just in model releases they go from being super sturdy like I have a first model PS3 and it's still in perfect condition it still plays everything wonderfully well but then you get the newer ones the slims and they're just they feel like nothing they've got no durability they're missing options and they cost you know when they were coming out they were costing as much as the old models did
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, awesome, because I do have Keyboard Mania.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's in the trunk.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was going to say, if you wanted to hold on to it and do doubles, you're welcome to.
[SPEAKER_09]: So now I'll have to get out my PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway, so yeah, flea market shopping, that's one of the things, fun things we did.
[SPEAKER_02]: And also I saw in chat, Actdeft says a friend shops on flea market swap meets and resells the stuff he finds on eBay for a living.
[SPEAKER_02]: I believe DarkSakura was actually talking to one of her friends there that she used to buy a lot of stuff from who said that he doesn't haggle.
[SPEAKER_02]: Trader Dan.
[SPEAKER_02]: He doesn't haggle really because he knows that if they haggle with him, they're just trying to remarket it on eBay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's exactly what he said.
[SPEAKER_06]: And he's actually said he stopped dealing on eBay and he's doing like on eTrader or something, some website.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I caught that end of the conversation.
[SPEAKER_09]: He seemed very irritated with eBay and Amazon.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm not sure what happened there.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, Amazon... He used to just completely resell everything, all the good stuff on eBay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, and didn't Amazon kick everyone in California out because of the whole tax thing?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think they did.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I don't think he did Amazon.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think he was strictly eBay and Yahoo.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_09]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: I like this comparison.
[SPEAKER_09]: Very interesting comparison.
[SPEAKER_09]: Then we'll move on with How Was Your Gaming Week here in the chat room from SepWin.
[SPEAKER_09]: CEPWin in the chat at chat.orange.com says, It's like buildings.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do you think the biggest NFL stadiums will be around 100 years from now, let alone 2000 as the Roman Coliseum?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, here's an example.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sure I've made no thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm from Mobile, Alabama.
[SPEAKER_06]: We have a building that was recently restored that was built in like 1850 something.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, maybe after the city was like 150 years old.
[SPEAKER_06]: And...
[SPEAKER_06]: It's still in, even when it was run down, it was still in sturdy condition and lived through years of hurricanes.
[SPEAKER_06]: A hundred years worth of hurricanes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Where we had, you know, some of the newer buildings had been flooded down and were corroded and everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: So just even as an example, in a couple hundred years, you know, construction, we're leaning towards cheaper things that they don't last, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, a lot of stuff is built for the environment, too.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, here in California, you don't have brick buildings because of earthquakes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: But in Alabama, almost everything is made out of brick and concrete.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, it's just interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: And buildings are cheaper there, ironically.
[SPEAKER_06]: True, true.
[SPEAKER_06]: Even though they'll last through probably more hard weather than California sees.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, construction.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alan, you didn't end up buying anything at the flea market, but did anything catch your eye?
[SPEAKER_09]: Like if you had the money burning a hole in your pocket?
[SPEAKER_02]: Trader Dan had a lot of big promotional standy things.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like he had that big Samus Super Metroid thing that was like six or seven feet tall from Super Metroid.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know I wanted that from the new studio.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's probably not for sale because he has it mounted way up high on the wall.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know, he'd sell almost anything if you offer him the right amount, so.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, no, because we've bought some stuff that was just on the collection wall before.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: But that was back when he had the store in Rio Linda.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, you know, we put some pictures in the new studio up at orangelawnradio.com.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's a little picture bar towards the top of the screen, and you can kind of see some pictures that we take.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know what the website says, you can send in your own pictures, but due to some abuse things we had happen a couple months ago, we had to pull that.
[SPEAKER_09]: So it's only the hosts, really, that are adding stuff to that, and we just added a bunch of pictures from the studio.
[SPEAKER_09]: So there's...
[SPEAKER_09]: You can see the scrolls and things like that, so it's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but it was funny looking at the flea market at the big collections of the Game Gear and the Atari Lynx and both the console and the cartridge.
[SPEAKER_02]: How did anyone ever try to market that as portable?
[SPEAKER_02]: Either system.
[SPEAKER_02]: They were both huge.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, look at an old school Game Boy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you remember the commercial with the guy sitting on the toilet playing the Lynx?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: and I had a Game Gear and I remember it went through four AA batteries probably every 72 hours and it's like worse battery life than a 3DS it weighs four pounds like how is that ever but yeah it was neat seeing all of that really old hardware well go look at an old school Game Boy like those things are fucking bricks but I remember you would have the case for it and I would put it in a backpack and take it to school and it was portable you know back then I just had an inspiration Rob what you know how the people built the house out of Legos
[SPEAKER_09]: I want to build a house out of Game Boys.
[SPEAKER_09]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_09]: That might be tricky.
[SPEAKER_09]: An entire house?
[SPEAKER_09]: You might be able to get a doggy house.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you know, maybe like a little office or a storage room or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I think that, or even just do a wall, a wall of Game Boy's.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like a modern art piece?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, instead of, you know.
[SPEAKER_09]: The 8-bit gaming exhibit that they do?
[SPEAKER_06]: But, you know, instead of tile, you know, with the plaster, tile and plaster, do plaster in Game Boy's.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_09]: Lots of World of Warcrafts.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, not a lot because my computer was off for close to a week.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then we just got our cable back.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, you had no interwebs for like four days.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, so I had to come over here on Christmas Day.
[SPEAKER_09]: I remember that.
[SPEAKER_06]: To get my damn Merrymaker achievement.
[SPEAKER_06]: Open presents under the tree in Ironforge.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, I remember that because then we went out for... Nothing's open on Christmas, but we were able to find that Pha was open on Christmas.
[SPEAKER_06]: So as a proper Jew, I had Asian food on Christmas Day, even if it wasn't Chinese.
[SPEAKER_09]: I remember putting a tweet or something.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was like, two gays and a Jew walk into a pho bar on Christmas.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was delicious.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it was very good.
[SPEAKER_06]: Delicious.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I played, well, once everything got hooked up, I played a little bit of Fractal, which I really like that game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, you talked about that last week on the show, or two weeks.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Very pretty.
[SPEAKER_06]: And we played rock band, of course, like we do every party that we have The quintessential party game Yes, and Bradley came over
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, Arcadian 42.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: We need to get him over here in the new studio.
[SPEAKER_06]: And he brought cymbals.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then he proceeded to impress the cousins with his prowess in pro drum mode.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, he does the pro drumming.
[SPEAKER_09]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: And we had... Well, when I left the house, Dan was watching a playthrough of Gradius on the...
[SPEAKER_06]: Game Boy, like the old school Gradius on the Game Boy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I saw little Moai heads.
[SPEAKER_06]: We did, I think we did have a little bit of Proteus going on in the house.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that was fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: But mostly it was just putting up games.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I've probably touched a couple thousand games this weekend.
[SPEAKER_06]: Literally touched them.
[SPEAKER_06]: But as for playing them, that's a different story.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then there's also the flea market games that you touched.
[SPEAKER_09]: You put your paws on a lot of those too, digging through things.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I really did try to... It's sad going to Trader Dan's, though, because the stuff that he had out, the stuff I would have wanted, was the stuff I already have.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I'm like, well, see, that's why I was asking who had a Master System, because we have spare games.
[SPEAKER_06]: We do literally have spare Master System games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which, by the way, any of our listeners, if you have a master system, send me a photo of your master system.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the first person that sends me a picture of their own personal master system will get a game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Where can I email that?
[SPEAKER_09]: Because you don't have an OLR email anymore.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mailbag at OrangeLunchRadio.com Show email.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mail the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it has to be your master system.
[SPEAKER_09]: Don't Google the picture Maybe they need to put You need to tell them to put a little post-it note that says OLR So we know they didn't like Google it OLR, has to have a post-it note And keep in mind, I'm a designer I can tell if you photoshopped it Yeah, or something If you don't have post-it notes for fuck's sake Just scribble it on a notepad or something And maybe I'll be kind enough And if you've got a power base converter I'll accept that as well Alright Anyhow Inadvertent contest here on the show Alan, why don't you go next
[SPEAKER_02]: It's been several months since I've been on OLRs.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've actually completed a lot of games.
[SPEAKER_02]: I remember Dragon Age Origins that came out in 2009.
[SPEAKER_02]: A couple months ago I fired that up and I just couldn't let it go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Between that and the expansion Awakenings, I completed both of those.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think I've logged nearly 100 hours on my Archer Ranger Rogue that I rolled.
[SPEAKER_09]: I never realized you finished Awakenings.
[SPEAKER_09]: I saw that you moved on to Dragon Age 2 at one point, and I was like, oh, maybe he just finally got ADD, and he was like, I gotta go play the sequel.
[SPEAKER_09]: I didn't realize you finished Awakenings.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pretty much with any RPG now, I use a FAQ or a walkthrough to play it, just because I'm old and lazy, and I don't want to miss things the first way through.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's something secret.
[SPEAKER_02]: So yeah, I used FAQs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dragon Age Oranges was about 70 hours, and Awakenings was about 24 hours before I beat it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So yeah, I played a little Dragon Age 2, which got derailed by Skyrim, because Steam had Skyrim for $40 for 24 hours during its holiday sale.
[SPEAKER_09]: Which, for the game that a lot are calling Game of the Year, that just came out a couple months ago, is a steal.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, so $40 for Skyrim, which is what I'm actively playing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just a PSA to live listeners, the Encore sale is going on today, and that is $40 again.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, so they brought Skyrim back for $40.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, but that'll be it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: I really don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll have to ask.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm curious if the folks... Do we have any chatters?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to have to go home now and check my Steam.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't do it during the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Unless there's Steam for Linux now.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm curious.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, did the folks in chat...
[SPEAKER_09]: No?
[SPEAKER_09]: Do we have any?
[SPEAKER_09]: I see Ake Ripper in chat.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ake Ripper, can you use Steam?
[SPEAKER_02]: Sweden?
[SPEAKER_02]: Close enough.
[SPEAKER_02]: You might be able to log into the Steam website and buy something on the website on your account and then it'll download to the client.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just wait till you get home.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have till 10 a.m.
[SPEAKER_02]: tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, so I'm kind of juggling Dragon Age 2 and Skyrim right now and those are both pretty meaty meals of a game so I don't know how long I'm gonna be able to juggle those two.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got a DSi XL for Christmas for my lovely, kind, generous boyfriend in studio.
[SPEAKER_02]: And because of my DSi XL, I've been playing WarioWare Touched.
[SPEAKER_09]: Can we back up a minute?
[SPEAKER_09]: Because this certainly caught me off guard.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because I asked you, I said, what do you want for Christmas?
[SPEAKER_09]: And you said you wanted a DSi XL.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm like, you want that?
[SPEAKER_09]: Even though it costs as much as a 3DS?
[SPEAKER_09]: So just for the listeners that might be asking the same question, why an XL?
[SPEAKER_09]: Why now?
[SPEAKER_09]: You got to answer.
[SPEAKER_02]: well you have a 3DS and I can play yours when you're at work honest answer that and I have a thing I almost have a thing against Nintendo but the first generation of their little hardware portables I thought the DS original the DS fat was ugly and it looked cheap and the DS light was like oh okay this looks like a good device that's when I finally got on board with the DS was with the light
[SPEAKER_02]: I just think with the weird analog stick on the right side attachment that came out for the 3DS I want the second generation and when I play Mario Kart 7 on your 3DS I can only do two races before my right hand is completely cramped because I have big giant spindly spidery man hands and it hurts to play so I have my giant DS XL and I've got a ton of DS games RPGs that I haven't played so
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: When you explained it to me, it made a lot of sense.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was like, all right.
[SPEAKER_09]: And plus, now that I've really got my paws on one of those.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a really nice device.
[SPEAKER_09]: It is a nice device.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's kind of a bummer it was so late in the life and now a lot of folks have moved on because, you know, it's a pretty rock solid DS.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just want to take a step back for just a minute and chatters have clarified Actdeft from Mexico, Steam sales work worldwide.
[SPEAKER_09]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: So aside from MarioWare Touched on the XL, I also did my sort of annual playthrough of Half-Life and Half-Life 2 episodes 1 and 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: I beat those from start to finish.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's kind of like your version of DarkSakura's Christmas Nights, I notice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Once or twice a year, I just get Half-Life fever and I got to play through it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just need to do Half-Life 2, like the proper Half-Life 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: I haven't done that yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: and some chatters in chat might be thinking about a story that happened in Gaming News this week and yes, we'll be talking about that later.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wow, Bastion's five bucks.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's a good game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Very good game.
[SPEAKER_09]: A lot of a game of the year list.
[SPEAKER_09]: Speaking of game of the year list, I do want to get this out at some point.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know it's 2012, but since we didn't have a show last week and the way timing worked out, we need to have a proper end of the year recap.
[SPEAKER_09]: So we will be talking about our games of the year.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, myself, and Alan have picked our top three games of the year.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll get Loki's next week, guys.
[SPEAKER_09]: Don't worry when he's back.
[SPEAKER_09]: But we want to hear your guys' game of the year picks too.
[SPEAKER_09]: So we have some posts on Facebook and Google+.
[SPEAKER_09]: So if you haven't chimed in yet, go do that because we're going to do that in part B. And some of our picks might surprise you.
[SPEAKER_09]: so I know that there are probably what three games that everybody's picking well we'll see maybe our lists are the same three maybe not but I want to emphasize there's no right or wrong answers and I gotta say just looking at Facebook and Google Plus I'm really impressed at the diversity of choices I really truly don't think that just because every media outlet says game A, B, or C is the game of the year means everybody else is on board like I don't think any two people have picked the same game very interesting so anyway
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry about that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Where were we?
[SPEAKER_09]: Your gaming week, Alan.
[SPEAKER_02]: I really think that that's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: As far as this week, I've scrambled around on the Steam contest for the holiday sale where you unlock Steve achievements to earn coupons.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, I have two coupons for 50% off any Valve game, good through, I think, the 1st of March.
[SPEAKER_02]: If an OLR listener wants to add me on Steam, I'll trade them that coupon.
[SPEAKER_09]: We actually have an OLR group on Steam that they could find you on.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I played Psychonauts for about an hour and a half to be able to use my mind power that Pyromania to burn two squirrels because there was an achievement for cooking two critters.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I played some games like Super Meat Boy has one yesterday that I need to go through.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's all.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know you're doing that too.
[SPEAKER_09]: So if you want to find us on Steam or any of that stuff, it's awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: On OrangeLaunchRadio.com, in the upper right-hand corner is this little box that says Extended Play, and you'll see all the logos for all the community social networking websites, and you'll see the Steam logo on there, and you can join the OLR clan, and you can say hi to Alan or Salacious Pop, and he'll give you treats, it sounds like.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_09]: He may not have enough for everybody.
[SPEAKER_09]: My gaming week.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've played a lot of hodgepodge kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like I mentioned before, I bought Seeing Star Queen, Clue.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's probably two games primarily I've been playing, kind of focusing on the past couple weeks.
[SPEAKER_09]: First one I'll mention is on the 3DS, a port of one of my favorite games that I played for the first time last year, even though the game is actually a couple years old itself.
[SPEAKER_09]: VVVVVV came out for the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's on the 3DS shop, I mean literally, like just last week.
[SPEAKER_09]: And, you know, it's a very faithful port of the version that's on the PC.
[SPEAKER_09]: You don't have the level editor, although they're saying that that may be coming in the future.
[SPEAKER_09]: But you do have some, like, best of user-created levels, which is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: and, of course, the game's in 3D a little bit.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, it's not complicated 3D.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's kind of like the NES classics.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like three different layers of 3D you kind of see things on.
[SPEAKER_09]: But the game itself, VVVVV, is a great game, an excellent game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Some folks may find it to be a little bit short, but I think it's well worth it for the $8.
[SPEAKER_09]: Kick-ass soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's kind of very similar to Super Metroid.
[SPEAKER_09]: Very easy gimmick, the whole gravity flipping thing, but it works so well.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, it's a great game.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_09]: And of course, as somebody who loved Commodore 64 and really grew up on Commodore 64, I love that the game has a lot of, you know, kind of tips of the hat to the Commodore 64 days, including the loading screen.
[SPEAKER_09]: So...
[SPEAKER_09]: I think the 3DS version is a worthy port.
[SPEAKER_09]: I realize some people may have a hard time justifying, well, I just bought VVVV as part of the Humble Indie Bundle that was just out because it was one of the games from the third that came back and I paid five bucks for like 15 games that included VVVV.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why would I go pay $7 in the 3DS shop now?
[SPEAKER_09]: That's a damn good question.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe it's not worth it in that regard.
[SPEAKER_09]: But for me, I love the idea of having a portable version.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, sometimes you just want games to be able to have wherever you are.
[SPEAKER_09]: Airport, you know, commuting or whatever it is that you're doing, you know, out and about, it's sometimes nice to have some games to go.
[SPEAKER_09]: And VVVVV is a worthy addition to the 3DS lineup.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, let's see.
[SPEAKER_09]: Otherwise, the other game that I spent a huge chunk of time playing is Star Wars The Old Republic, the new MMO that's out from BioWare and EA.
[SPEAKER_09]: I did pick this up the 21st, the day after it was out.
[SPEAKER_09]: and I've spent a good part of the past couple weeks playing it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have like four characters in the level 10-ish range.
[SPEAKER_09]: Two of them Imperial and two of them Empire.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I've gotten a good feel especially for the introduction parts of the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: God, where do I even begin with this?
[SPEAKER_09]: A lot of people are comparing it to WoW.
[SPEAKER_09]: and I gotta say this comment first I'm really amazed with how pressed some of the Star Wars players are when it comes to WoW because the general chat half the time is nothing but talk about oh this game is so much better than WoW and oh this game just kicks WoW's ass and oh WoW is a kiddie game and they're just bringing pandas because it's a kiddie game I used to play WoW but it sucks now and it's like wow you guys hate WoW so much you can't stop talking about it
[SPEAKER_09]: But that's not really a slam on Star Wars.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's just a slam on the chat community.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was comparing it to Star Trek Online.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, here's my point.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let both games just be.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because does Star Wars have a lot of inspiration from WoW?
[SPEAKER_09]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_09]: One of the classes I was playing, I was laughing because I'm like, this plays just like a warrior.
[SPEAKER_09]: It even has a talent called Sunder and you build up rage.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm like, this is just like a WoW warrior.
[SPEAKER_09]: But at the same time,
[SPEAKER_09]: The questing in Star Wars, the Old Republic, is so immersive.
[SPEAKER_09]: The voice acting really adds a neat element to it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Of course, the whole Bioware touch of the conversation trees.
[SPEAKER_09]: The fact that you can have your character be light side or dark side, even within...
[SPEAKER_09]: The Empire or Imperial like you can be a bad Jedi or you can be a good Sith it's really funky how that works but I like that and the group conversation is really interesting too I've been playing the game a lot with Shane and like we will both kind of go out and quest together and he likes to have his person be good and I like to have mine be bad so it's kind of funny watching that struggle and you get to see kind of different outcomes and all that so it's neat
[SPEAKER_09]: I wanted to finish my thought really quick though on the whole pressed Star Wars people and WoW.
[SPEAKER_09]: WoW obviously got its inspiration from other games too, and that's important to say.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think Star Wars is just this company's evolution of the MMO genre.
[SPEAKER_09]: And the question is, does it work?
[SPEAKER_09]: And my answer is, in most places, yes, but in a few places, no.
[SPEAKER_09]: and I think any MMO is going to have this problem when it first comes out and that's kind of about finding the balance and I think that's where the game has its trickiest part right now is balance and a lot of that has to do with the economy.
[SPEAKER_09]: The economy is really clouded, uncertain right now and it's really hard to make money and they just nerfed one of the big professions for that and so a lot of that needs some fine tuning but
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, the game's only been out two weeks.
[SPEAKER_09]: For an MMO, that's hardly anything.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sure a lot of that will be fixed in time.
[SPEAKER_09]: But the other thing I've got to knock Star Wars for, because this is something I keep saying every time I'm playing the game, damn, I wish they would fix this.
[SPEAKER_09]: One of the reasons I love WoW is the community and the UIs that they've built.
[SPEAKER_09]: And Star Wars desperately needs to open it up and let users make their own UIs and interfaces and add-ons, especially for things like the auction house, especially for things like targeting.
[SPEAKER_09]: and things of that sort.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because if you have two people and their companions out, healing is kind of a pain in the butt.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I'd like to see some UI changes for that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Some of the ways things are set up are a little weird and I just think the community could improve on that a little bit.
[SPEAKER_09]: but it's I mean especially compared to I played Rift when it first came out I played Warhammer when it first came out I played you know I've played a lot of the Ion I played Ion when it first came out I played a lot of the other ones and this is really the first one where I was like wow this really is something different this is a neat experience this you know I like the story which is weird because I'm not even that big on the Star Wars movies like you know I
[SPEAKER_09]: I appreciate them.
[SPEAKER_09]: I understand why there's fandom for the old movies from the 70s at least, not the new ones.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I get why Star Wars is popular, but I found myself really getting kind of sucked into the story, and it's really interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I really liked getting to kind of play this character that could be light or dark or neutral or what have you.
[SPEAKER_09]: So the biggest strengths are in the fact that
[SPEAKER_09]: Every single player game element is great.
[SPEAKER_09]: And you could go from 0 to 50 single player, no problem.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it really helps when MMOs have the mythology pre-built to then bring in... Because Lord of the Rings Online, obviously, Lord of the Rings is...
[SPEAKER_02]: Star Wars Galaxies wasn't necessarily a bad game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was a game that made bad decisions.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, yeah, because they switched it up to make it more accessible in all the diehard people.
[SPEAKER_09]: Right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Don't alienate your primary fan base.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's where WoW is at.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because for some people, Cataclysm was the equivalent of the NXE.
[SPEAKER_02]: and you know so anyway or new user what did they call it new user experience whatever it was called anyway but because Bioware doesn't as of yet have a good MMO pedigree they do have a great game pedigree I mean it's Bioware so I didn't really have any doubt in my mind that The Old Republic was going to be bad as just a campaign experience but a lot of people are wondering when once you get to level 50 are there I mean are there raids like what do you do once you're at max level
[SPEAKER_09]: Apparently there are operations, I think they're called, which are the equivalent of raids, I believe.
[SPEAKER_09]: And there's PvP.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can do PvP at level 10 and all that.
[SPEAKER_09]: But that's a good question.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm not really sure.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sitting here as somebody who's been playing the game for two weeks, and I'm not really sure.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because with Rift, Rift was a completely new property.
[SPEAKER_02]: They had to do all that world building about the conflict, and there's this race and this race and blah, blah, blah, and why these big portals are opening up in the sky.
[SPEAKER_02]: all the time which is a different problem altogether and it was just hard to really invest myself in the world that I was playing in whereas with Star Wars and WoW you have the mythology going back years and years that players already that's what brings people to those games I think
[SPEAKER_09]: So to kind of try and wrap up, because I know I'm rambling here a bit, but to kind of wrap up my thoughts on Star Wars The Old Republic, I think it's a good game, and if you're into MMOs, you'll probably want to pounce on this pretty quick, because a lot of people have been.
[SPEAKER_09]: But if you're not sure, I say wait, because I think the game's only going to get better with a little more maturity and age.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I think in six months to a year when they really have a lot of players in endgame and they have a lot of this ironed out, I think the game's going to be very neat.
[SPEAKER_09]: is it a WoW killer?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know I don't really like that term because I don't think like there's similar games out there all the time you know Burnout didn't kill Need for Speed and you know Call of Duty and Battlefield can compete you know it's just different and I it's expensive if you want to play both games that's the only bummer but
[SPEAKER_09]: The games can coexist.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't think one necessarily has to cannibalize the other.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think there's going to always be people that want to play WoW and there's going to be people that don't want to play WoW that want to play Star Wars.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's going to be people like me that kind of want to play a little bit of both.
[SPEAKER_09]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alan, I do want to quickly ask you, though, because you play a lot of MMOs.
[SPEAKER_09]: You've come on the other show, Horde House, a lot to talk about WoW.
[SPEAKER_09]: You play a lot of WoW.
[SPEAKER_09]: You raid in WoW.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're an endgame raider.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're one of the tops of the server.
[SPEAKER_09]: But you don't seem to have that same interest in Star Wars.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is that because of your investment in WoW?
[SPEAKER_09]: Is it a money thing?
[SPEAKER_09]: Is it just being a hater?
[SPEAKER_09]: What is it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I've dedicated myself to raiding with people 12 hours a week, which is a lot.
[SPEAKER_02]: and I am comfortable with that arrangement for right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Once I get a job, I will probably have to quit doing that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's a financial thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've already staked my claim with my rating guild in WoW.
[SPEAKER_02]: And yeah, I don't want to pay $15 a month twice for that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm also on the year-long Diablo III Death Pact.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I've pretty much said, yes, wow, regardless of how bad you get or how lame your patches are, I'm going to be sticking with you for a year, and I'm committed to that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't really need Wandering Eyes for MMOs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Though I will say, though, the reason why I...
[SPEAKER_02]: The reason why I decided to start playing Dragon Age Origins until I beat it was the fact that aside from raiding, I am kind of burned out on WoW, so that's helping my console gaming more.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've actually been more into WoW than I have been into WoW, which is really weird.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know if that's just because I've had a lot of time off work, so I've had more time to play things, or the fact that I am loving Arcane Mage right now in Warcraft, but...
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, like, I've really had to, like, I'll play WoW for a couple hours, then I play Star Wars for a couple hours, then I go back to playing WoW for a couple... You know, that's been a lot of my vacation when I'm not doing other more productive things, you know?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: A lot of chatter's talking about Guild Wars 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: Kaijudo, I think, kicked it off.
[SPEAKER_09]: I cannot wait for Guild Wars 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's gonna be my main MMO.
[SPEAKER_09]: And yeah, I gotta say...
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm really interested in Guild Wars 2 as well.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm hoping the payment model is the same as Guild Wars 1 where it's buy the game and never pay money again.
[SPEAKER_09]: Would be great.
[SPEAKER_09]: Not have to pay a monthly fee or whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I'm looking forward to Guild Wars 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: That'll be another MMO I'm going to have to somehow juggle.
[SPEAKER_09]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_09]: I kind of think in the long run, I may keep... It's hard to say.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've been off work this whole time, so I've been able to juggle two MMOs.
[SPEAKER_09]: But when I go back to work, I'm probably going to have to pick one or the other.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I've agreed to play WoW for a year.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm on the same thing where I've already signed the death pact.
[SPEAKER_09]: I want to be, but I'm not.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I think even if I had to choose between the two, I would choose WoW at this point.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because I think Star Wars will get better with age.
[SPEAKER_09]: Think about it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I didn't start playing WoW until Burning Crusade expansion came out.
[SPEAKER_06]: I started WoW with vanilla.
[SPEAKER_06]: and hated it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And hated it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then I played Burning Crusade and hated it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then I didn't even bother with any of the other stuff because I still hated it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then Cataclysm came out and I was like, I kind of like this.
[SPEAKER_09]: So just me saying I don't want to maybe play Star Wars right now a bad thing?
[SPEAKER_09]: Not necessarily.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, God, look at my WoW addiction and that just took a couple years to grow.
[SPEAKER_09]: So...
[SPEAKER_09]: I think Star Wars will still be here in a year or two unlike some of these other MMOs that have come out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is anyone still playing Age of Conan?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not on the show roll because I think it would have been for last week but we didn't do a Christmas show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Didn't SWTOR or The Old Republic hit a million paid subscribers the fastest out of even faster than WoW?
[SPEAKER_02]: Wasn't that a story?
[SPEAKER_02]: We're not covering it tonight, but they put out a press release saying that they have a million.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think they've sold like 1.5 million copies of the game globally.
[SPEAKER_09]: So that wouldn't surprise me at all.
[SPEAKER_09]: They have that many.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, there's still one or two more weeks before people start getting rebills.
[SPEAKER_02]: So the rebills is when they're going to be able to say that they have subscribers.
[SPEAKER_09]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: There is stuff going on besides MMOs in the world.
[SPEAKER_09]: Quickly, some housekeeping and then we'll get into some news.
[SPEAKER_09]: I already mentioned the game of the year we're going to talk about in part B. So stay tuned.
[SPEAKER_09]: Get your picks in at our Facebook or at our Google Plus page.
[SPEAKER_09]: And if you don't have us added on either of those pages...
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe you should take care of that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also, I want to plug some other things going on elsewhere.
[SPEAKER_09]: One of them that I really, really need to plug and make sure you guys know about is something called The Big Battle.
[SPEAKER_09]: And this is something that Derek from Dead Pixel Live, which is another show on the All Games Network, is kind of spearheading.
[SPEAKER_09]: But it's a lot of community shows kind of all pitching in to try and make this thing a success and get more people at the table wanting to kick each other's ass.
[SPEAKER_09]: In a good way, though, because it's all about fighting games.
[SPEAKER_09]: The big battle this time is, I think, the big beatdown.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's all fighting games.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's Mortal Kombat, it's Street Fighter, Arcade Edition, it's Street Fighter 3, it's Ultimate Mortal Kombat 3.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's all these fighting games.
[SPEAKER_09]: And we're trying to get as many people in to participate in the tournament to find out which show has the best fighting game fans.
[SPEAKER_09]: So far, I'm the only one signed up from OLR, so I'm hoping some of you will head on over to TheBigBattle.net and change that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sign up over there on the beatdown board for one of the games.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now, the only kind of deal-breaker for some people is that it's all Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_09]: So some of you have these on PS3.
[SPEAKER_09]: See, I have Mortal Kombat and Super Street Fighter IV on PS3, so I couldn't sign up for those games, but...
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, you can.
[SPEAKER_09]: What do you mean?
[SPEAKER_06]: You can come to my house.
[SPEAKER_09]: I guess I could, huh?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, you can.
[SPEAKER_09]: Would that mean you're going to sign up too?
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe I will.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, there you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: And keep in mind, this is Gimpy Hand Lady.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know?
[SPEAKER_09]: You have an arcade stick that you could use, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: We have several arcade sticks.
[SPEAKER_06]: That won't be a problem.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, so maybe, maybe we'll work something out.
[SPEAKER_09]: But anyway, it's all on Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_09]: So Super Street Fighter 4 Arcade Edition, Mortal Kombat, Street Fighter 3, Third Strike Online, Ultimate Mortal Kombat 3.
[SPEAKER_09]: Go sign up on the beatdown board at thebigbattle.net and say you're going to represent the OL Army or Team OLR.
[SPEAKER_09]: They'll know what you're talking about.
[SPEAKER_09]: Go sign up and...
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll kick your ass soon if you're playing Ultimate Mortal Kombat 3 Because that's the one of the games that I do own on the Xbox 360 Which I find funny because you can't buy that game anymore Yet that's the game that has the most signups right now I think people just love the classics What else can you say?
[SPEAKER_09]: So, go sign up Alright, other thing I gotta plug here The Geek-Life Awards You know, we've talked about this website before And part of it is because, you know, Dark Sakura is like, writes for it You still write for it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, I do.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just with the last semester, I slacked off on my writing.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know how busy I was.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, the editors over there, which I don't believe was DarkSakura, because I think there's got to be rules against that, but the editors over there did nominate us as one of the best podcasts of the years in the second annual Geek Life Awards!
[SPEAKER_09]: Woohoo!
[SPEAKER_09]: But the funny thing is, another podcast that was nominated was Horde House, my show about Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_09]: Right now in the poll, Horde House is beating Orange Lounge Radio for best podcast of the year.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sure Extrovert had nothing to do at all with that.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: God, what are you going to do if you lose to Extifer?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess talk about his bleached asshole.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Good answer.
[SPEAKER_09]: Speaking of Horde House, I should mention we haven't done a show for like two weeks over there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that a correlation?
[SPEAKER_06]: Bleach your asshole win an award?
[SPEAKER_09]: Do you want to find out?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway, I should say Horde House hasn't had a show for like two weeks and probably won't be back till next week.
[SPEAKER_09]: And that's just a timing thing on X for a Nice Part.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like I'm going to be gone for four days next week.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, yep.
[SPEAKER_09]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_09]: Busy, busy.
[SPEAKER_09]: But hey, it's the holidays so we can kind of get away with it.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, let's talk about gaming news.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's get back into what is going on in the gaming industry this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Not a lot come to find out, but there are some things going on we do want to bring to the table and talk about with you guys in our chat room at chat.orangelaunchradio.com.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alan, start us off tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: So Nintendo, they've been razzed on so hard, especially by the gentleman that I am subbing for tonight, as far as their inability to embrace stuff that other consoles are doing, particularly online play.
[SPEAKER_02]: But they are jumping on one bandwagon finally, and that is paid DLC.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is it true that the Wii didn't, you couldn't patch games on the Wii, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: There were no... You cannot patch games on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_09]: And the proof of this would be what's going on with Skyward Sword.
[SPEAKER_09]: They actually had to release this whole channel, and it's there in the Wii shop.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you go look, one of the games I forgot to mention I played this week, I found I had extra points in my Wii balance, or Wii account, so I went and bought Blaster Master for the NES on Virtual Console.
[SPEAKER_09]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_09]: But as I was looking for the shop, I saw the Fix Your Game File channel for Skyward Sword, and I was like, that has to be embarrassing.
[SPEAKER_09]: But yeah, they can't just patch Skyward Sword to do it.
[SPEAKER_09]: They have to have a Fix My Game channel.
[SPEAKER_02]: So even with their most up until the 3DS, the supplemental content, whether it be
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, absolutely.
[SPEAKER_02]: and it's going to cost several hundred yen.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of vague right now when it comes out.
[SPEAKER_02]: But yeah, you can expect with the online store that 3DS has where you can buy the old Game Boy Advance and the little...
[SPEAKER_02]: DSWare games now when you buy a actual retail cart product you can eventually log in maybe either through the game or through your 3DS and buy bonus campaigns for it which is just money money money I mean look at Microsoft and Sony and all the millions they've made with pay to unlock launch day DLC that's on the disc I should say this though the Wii does have the Wii does have kinda download content
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: All of it was third-party companies that were doing it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because, you know, Final Fantasy, Square Enix, Rock Band is, you know, Harmonix.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I don't think any of it is coming from Nintendo themselves.
[SPEAKER_09]: So that's what makes us notable.
[SPEAKER_09]: Both that, A, it's the 3DS, which, you know, we haven't seen DLC on the 3DS yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: We've seen, you know, Buy the Game, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: I just pimped BBB.
[SPEAKER_09]: But we haven't seen DLC.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's Nintendo themselves now.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's a big deal.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I stand corrected.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it did have the facilities for DLC, but this one for a handheld definitely is interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the Wii U, they've also confirmed that it's going to have paid DLC, but there's still a lot more we need to find out about the Wii U than just that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Some comments from our chatroom at chat.orange.com Yuki says, and here I was respecting Nintendo for not doing DLC till now.
[SPEAKER_09]: Tiger Claws theorizing, who knows, maybe a new Zelda quest via DLC.
[SPEAKER_09]: Kaijudo just says, yeah, the DLC sounds lame.
[SPEAKER_09]: So maybe this begs the question, is this good news or is this bad news?
[SPEAKER_09]: Dragon Age Awakening Dragon Age Awakening
[SPEAKER_06]: Fable
[SPEAKER_02]: Awakenings is closer to the model that PC games used in the 80s and 90s in that it was a proper expansion that was a good 20 or 30 hours of game which is about how long I spent on it with Dragon Age Origins before I played Awakenings I did go onto the Bioware store and buy some of their DLC and those were only like 2 or 3 hours long for 5 bucks but it was well done so they're not all terrible
[SPEAKER_09]: Dark Tetsuya says my brother was commenting to me about Nintendo not doing DLC said Nintendo should have made new tracks for Mario Kart and yeah I'm kind of like I would like to see Mario Kart 7 get more tracks download content you know as long as they don't go down that path that you know we talked about Ridge Racer on the Vita a couple weeks ago on the show like sounds like they're doing a horrible thing but like every Mario Kart game ever has had 32 tracks except I think
[SPEAKER_09]: The Game Boy One you could unlock all of the tracks from the original in, which was a hell of a deal.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_09]: But most Mario, you buy a Mario Kart game, you know you're going to get eight cups, four of them retro, four of them new, four, you know, it's like the same formula every time.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I think it would be pretty rad if some more of the retro levels came back as DLC.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, I would support that as long as it was reasonably priced.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, there's got to be a limit to it.
[SPEAKER_09]: But...
[SPEAKER_09]: It would be interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I think there's a lot of ways that Nintendo could do this very wrong too.
[SPEAKER_09]: And of course, pay to unlock content is the wrong way to do it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Stuff that doesn't enhance stuff that's required for the core gaming experience would be bad.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, going down the same path, I got a story here about what's happening at the Wii U. The Wii U, obviously, not going to be out for a while, but some rumors out there that Nintendo is going to be doing a full-blown app store for the system.
[SPEAKER_09]: So think like, you know, what iTunes has going on.
[SPEAKER_09]: Right now, you know, they've got the eShop, they've got little stores that
[SPEAKER_09]: but the Wii U supposedly is going to go one step further there's going to be a wide variety of apps it will be stuff that will operate on the Wii U itself like TV things like you see on Xbox 360 Major League Baseball but some things that will run independently on the controller because the tablet obviously is its own little screen or what have you
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: So my thought is, well, are you really downloading apps to your controller then?
[SPEAKER_09]: Or are you downloading apps that just play on your controller, but you can't really take them portable?
[SPEAKER_09]: Unless something drastic has changed with the specs of the system, maybe they are giving that thing a little processor.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I would think they're not because they want to keep the costs down.
[SPEAKER_09]: But...
[SPEAKER_09]: it would be interesting if that's happening but they are talking about you know check your email browse the web do Facebook and maybe some little games too on that little device I could see where you know you have the controller in your bedroom and it's streaming from the device in the living room and you can kind of like surf the web from bed and all that but I don't know most people have iPhones iPads Kindles you know other devices for that yeah so I don't know if the Wii U is necessary but I don't know what do you guys think
[SPEAKER_06]: I can see the advantage, especially if you just want one thing to give you all the convenience.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, maybe that's a good thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Honestly, it makes me think of that... What's that laptop that my husband wants?
[SPEAKER_06]: The Transformer.
[SPEAKER_06]: Where you pull off the top and it's a tablet.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it might be something to that extent.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, like, say that you're...
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's just a very domestic example, but say that your Wii is your way of surfing the web, and you're looking for a cake recipe.
[SPEAKER_06]: Put the cake recipe on your little tablet, take it to the kitchen, go make your cake.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, I'm just using that as an example.
[SPEAKER_09]: That would work.
[SPEAKER_09]: I could see that in the little Nintendo promo they do.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Family Oriented Domestic Level
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know why the chatters are doing this, but they're putting app in the names of all these Nintendo franchises like App Zero, the App of Zelda, App Icarus, App of Time, Excite App.
[SPEAKER_09]: One of the ones that was suggested by Giovedeo was App Crossing, and that made me think, oh God, there's where DLC could go really wrong, is Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, man.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, it could be really good, but I could just see the easy cash-in on Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what, though?
[SPEAKER_06]: For Wii U, imagine Animal Crossing with Wii U. You can go to the island again.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, what do you have for us news-wise?
[SPEAKER_06]: I have a little something.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, it's a cease and desist.
[SPEAKER_06]: My apologies.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's later story.
[SPEAKER_09]: You will cease and desist that story right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, I will.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's the UK prices.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, actually, the European Union prices for the Vita and the memory cards and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: So here's some of the game prices.
[SPEAKER_06]: Uncharted Golden Abyss will be 49.99 or 44.99.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bond Nation Racer will be 39.99 or 34.99, respectively.
[SPEAKER_06]: Everybody's Golf, the same.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wipeout, 2048, the same.
[SPEAKER_06]: Unit 13, also the same.
[SPEAKER_06]: Little Deviants will be 29.99 and 24.99.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then Reality Fighters is the same price as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: So as far as the different bits that go with it, the 4 gig memory card will be $19.99, $17.99 pound.
[SPEAKER_06]: 8 gig will be $34.99 or $31.99.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the 16 gig will be $49.99 and $44.99.
[SPEAKER_06]: Lots of other stuff too, like the charger is $49.99 slash $44.99.
[SPEAKER_06]: All these different...
[SPEAKER_06]: Man, England, why do you have to stick with the pounds?
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, probably kind of a decent thing that they did given where the euro started going.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, I'm actually trying to get the price of the system on here.
[SPEAKER_09]: While that's loading, why don't I just jump in here real quick?
[SPEAKER_09]: In case you are wondering, you hadn't heard the US, American currencies.
[SPEAKER_09]: I did pull up Amazon real quick to just kind of...
[SPEAKER_09]: Most of what DarkSakura said, if you just replace Euro with dollars, it's pretty much the same thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: The Wi-Fi system itself, $249.99 in dollars.
[SPEAKER_09]: The first edition bundle is going to be $349.99.
[SPEAKER_09]: The games right now are all over the map.
[SPEAKER_09]: It just really depends on what the game is.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like Uncharted, $49.99.
[SPEAKER_09]: LittleBigPlanet, $39.99.
[SPEAKER_09]: But like Hot Shots Golf...
[SPEAKER_09]: Golf?
[SPEAKER_09]: What is golf?
[SPEAKER_09]: Hotshots Golf?
[SPEAKER_06]: I know what GORF is.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a cool game.
[SPEAKER_09]: GORF is a cool game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hotshots GORF.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'd buy that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hotshots Golf, though, is $29.99, as is Wipeout 2048.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I'm assuming maybe those games are a little... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's hard to tell.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, Touch My Katamari is also $29.99.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is that indicative of the quality?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I hope not.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, we do have the list of the U.S.
[SPEAKER_06]: release titles, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: It actually says the full list from the U.S.
[SPEAKER_06]: PlayStation blog.
[SPEAKER_06]: On launch day, there will be Escape Plan, Hot Shots Golf World Invitational, Hustle Kings, Little Deviants, My Nation Racers, Road Trip, Super Stardust Delta, Uncharted Golden Abyss, Wipeout 2048, and as far as third-party stuff goes, just to look this over and point out the stuff that isn't absolute crap, as far as I know,
[SPEAKER_06]: BlazeBlue, ContinuumShift, Extend This is just a great name, Army Corps of Hell Luminous, Electronic Symphony Is that launch day or launch window?
[SPEAKER_06]: It says launch day What else is on here?
[SPEAKER_06]: Plants vs. Zombies Rayman Origins
[SPEAKER_06]: Touch of Space, Mutant Blobs, Touch My Katamari, Ultimate Marvel vs. Capcom 3, and as far as launch, Windows, Disgaea 3, Ridge Racer, Silent Hill Book of Memories.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, we're seeing some stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think Ninja Gaiden, is that Sigma?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's actually the Sigma symbol.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know my Greek.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, so, yeah, Vita, I know I'm going to probably have to pick one up, now especially that I know Luminous is out Do you want to touch my Katamari?
[SPEAKER_09]: I will totally touch your Katamari, I'll only touch yours if you touch mine Okay Alan, I know you're probably not going to buy a Vita the day they come out because, you know, you'll play mine when I'm at work, but what do you think about You're going to touch his Katamari when he's at work Yeah, probably Are you excited about the release at all or are you just like, eh, whatever, another system
[SPEAKER_09]: I've heard Vita has had some mixed stuff going on in Japan, that there's been a lot of bumps in the road.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't really have the energy to stand or to be really fanatical about a system, but it took about two or three years, but the PSP, I thought, was a really good system, a really good handheld.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I really think that the PSP is underrated dare I say it because the DS which was phenomenal sort of steamrolled it which is a reality but I'm looking forward to the PSP Vita because I thought the PSP itself was damn good but I just financially and with the time I have towards games I can't really get all that excited about a launch day purchase like I would have been 10 years ago
[SPEAKER_09]: So maybe for next Christmas though.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Once things get ironed out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, no, next Christmas I'll want a 3DS because if I'm doing things two years late, then I'll want... Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Good to know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I can start planning ahead.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, let's move on with some more news, Alan.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: He was basically answering speculation about a possible Metal Gear Solid remake because they are doing the HD remake for the PS3 of I believe it's Metal Gear Solid 2 and Snake Eater.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Metal Gear Solid, the original, isn't a part of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So people are like, well, obviously that was the most famous of the three because it was groundbreaking.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was probably one of the best looking games during the entire PS1 life cycle.
[SPEAKER_02]: Does that mean that they're going to be releasing one separately?
[SPEAKER_02]: And Kojima has just said, you know, that ultimately it's Konami's decision.
[SPEAKER_02]: If they want to do a remake of it, that's fine, but he won't really, like, he doesn't care enough.
[SPEAKER_02]: He thinks the game is perfect, or is good at it as is.
[SPEAKER_02]: He didn't think any corners were cut that he would want to go back and rewrite parts.
[SPEAKER_02]: He thought that the story was complete enough.
[SPEAKER_02]: The first time it was told.
[SPEAKER_02]: So they're welcome to do it, but Kojima's not really saying that he's psyched up about wanting to remake it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do you think it's worth it for them to put the time and effort into remaking the first game?
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, I kind of get why they're doing that, because I think they're probably taking the easy way out with the 2 and 3 remakes, you know, just quickly up-rezzing.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like with the God of War, which I know was Sony and not Konami, but it's just, they were already nice enough graphics that they could just upscale the textures.
[SPEAKER_09]: Right, which is probably what's happening with Silent Hill, too.
[SPEAKER_09]: But this, you know, going back and doing the first one would be, you know, they're not going to be able to do that as easy.
[SPEAKER_02]: didn't they kind of remake one already for the GameCube with Twin Snakes yes that was the script and the voice acting was changed a bit but it was still ultimately that game the story was retold
[SPEAKER_06]: And it was really great.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, I thought it was probably... Of course, we have just about every Metal Gear thing that comes out, so it was really great.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, so with Metal Gear Solid Twin Snakes for the GameCube, that's kind of like if they did an HD remake of Resident Evil when we have the Resident Evil remake on the GameCube.
[SPEAKER_02]: Again, totally different franchise, but it's the same thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, we've already kind of had that, so, you know...
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's be real, if they remade Metal Gear Solid HD as a separate release, people would buy it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if Konami wants money, they should do it, but Kojima is just, you know...
[SPEAKER_09]: He's not... But a lot of people would rather they just put that effort into making a Metal Gear Solid 5.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Which, story-wise... Which obviously you would want Kajima on board for that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because it'd be a new story.
[SPEAKER_09]: So... Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, moving on.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was brought up earlier in the show that Steam is having a crazy sale right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: I wanted to just take some time to kind of talk about a lot of the crap that's on sale.
[SPEAKER_07]: I did get Bastion.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm still looking at him.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: What's also interesting is the competition that they're doing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, it's a competition.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's the right thing to call it?
[SPEAKER_09]: The achievements for loot, basically.
[SPEAKER_09]: They have these set achievements and with them you can win little coupons for games.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like I got a 75% off Left 4 Dead 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: Basically like have the sale anytime you want type of thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: or you can get little pieces of coal and the little pieces of coal can either be contest entries into winning every game Steam has ever put out ever is the grand prize like you would never be able to play all that or I think you runner up prizes are like all the games on your wish list and like every Valve game ever made and you know things like that
[SPEAKER_09]: What's interesting, I was reading about this and something I wanted to bring up.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just read about this today.
[SPEAKER_09]: I guess Steam ran out of the third party prizes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like if you get seven pieces of coal, you're only going to be able to get Valve stuff with that now.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's nothing third party you can get with that now.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was a game, I'm blanking on what it was, that was released on Steam, I think it happened a year or two ago, where they ran out of the license, like the codes, like the CD key code.
[SPEAKER_02]: You get one of those digitally.
[SPEAKER_02]: They didn't have, like they ran out, so they couldn't sell the game anymore because they didn't have the manufacturer's
[SPEAKER_09]: so it's probably the same thing here they gave away the little free or the agreement was they would take the loss up to X many copies but a lot of people are upset because there's been those accounts out there that have kind of been abusing this we had a story a couple weeks ago about people were creating accounts just to trade the games and get the coupons kind of setting up all these sock accounts and Valve had to do this so a lot of people are kind of upset with the way this played out
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know, you've been trying to save up coal.
[SPEAKER_09]: Were you going to cash it in?
[SPEAKER_09]: Now maybe not?
[SPEAKER_02]: I need two or three more, and I have no idea what is even available.
[SPEAKER_02]: And now it sounds like, thanks to this story, there's even less available for me to look at, so I'm even less motivated.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is there anything Valve you don't own?
[SPEAKER_09]: Counter-Strike?
[SPEAKER_02]: Counter-Strike and just stuff that I don't care about because it's multiplayer or whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: One thing, though, about this whole sale and these achievements is that it really shows how Valve works with the developers of these indie games, because especially with Toki Tori, whenever Valve has one of these sales on Steam, there will be several games that will get updates where the developers have designed Christmas content specifically for
[SPEAKER_02]: Steam, which is unprecedented.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Toki Tori had, it was basically the first world, but it was all re-skinned with snow and Christmas trees.
[SPEAKER_02]: So the developers went in and added that for this sale.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Super Meat Boy, same thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's now a Christmas world for this sale that you can go in and play.
[SPEAKER_09]: The one for Beat Hazard was mean.
[SPEAKER_09]: You have to play 10 minutes of Christmas music without dying or without losing.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I did it twice and lost at 9 minutes 30 seconds.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was so pissed.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, so even the developers of Beat Hazard were like, all right, there's a Christmas sale.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to add Christmas music.
[SPEAKER_02]: Your Steam client will update the game automatically for this sale.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't really think of any other example of when that's happened.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, outside of Steam, yeah, but I was going to say the Portal 2 release.
[SPEAKER_09]: Remember they had the whole...
[SPEAKER_09]: Unlock Portal 2 early thing on Steam and they had special achievements and like Audiosurf.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like I remember one day I went to go play Audiosurf and suddenly Portal 2 music just showed up.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like I tried to play a song and it was like GLaDOS is taking over and suddenly it was a Portal 2 song that was really awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I like when they kind of do stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: But, you know, I like this comment from Derek H in chat, especially if the thing they are out of is digital and therefore not real.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's frustrating, knowing that, oh, you just ran out of something that's on the internet.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, it needs a license, but yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, um...
[SPEAKER_06]: Licenses themselves are more for inventory and marketing purposes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, my thought was that they just have an agreement with the developers.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, hey, we're not going to give away unlimited amounts of 75% off your game.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's going to be limited to $100,000 or something like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think for the sake of those third-party developers, many of them indie, I get it.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I cut them some slack.
[SPEAKER_06]: Whatever they sell, they have to report back to the manufacturer because they have those agreements.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry, I love Derek Hage's follow-up comment.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like running out of birthday wishes.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was going to wish you a happy birthday, but I used up my last one three days ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: When I woke up this morning, I had like five or six fucks to give, but now it's three o'clock and I don't give a fuck anymore.
[SPEAKER_02]: You missed.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're too late.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you caught me a noon, I would have gave a fuck, but now I don't.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actdeft in chat says, clarifies the abusing of this.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sky, many people cheated and had multiple accounts on Steam to trade coals and stuff with themselves.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why do you need all these fake accounts?
[SPEAKER_09]: Get a significant other.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alan and I traded stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: If I have any coal, you guys can have it.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's nothing left to get with it.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is why I don't even do this shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, seriously.
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't sign up for any of it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'd do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because you know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: I have other stuff to do.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, when I'm the winner of every Steam game ever...
[SPEAKER_09]: You can't play it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, some of the achievements are have a wish list.
[SPEAKER_02]: Make sure that your wish list has at least 10 things in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was worth a lump of coal.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if you created 20 accounts and you added 10 games to your wish list, you could then pipe all of those other 19 other coals to your... So some of them weren't necessarily game achievements.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was just Steam interaction.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, then I'm sure I have a coal.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm too good for coal.
[SPEAKER_06]: What are you talking about?
[SPEAKER_09]: You want diamonds.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess what Sky's trying to say is that if you're forever alone.jpg the sale isn't for you then apparently because you need a partner to help you do this.
[SPEAKER_02]: No forever alone on Steam.
[SPEAKER_09]: Some folks are talking about Skyrim and I just wanted to say because this made me think about you've been playing Skyrim.
[SPEAKER_07]: Challenge accepted.
[SPEAKER_09]: Kaijudo in chat says, I want Skyrim on PC for the mods.
[SPEAKER_09]: The mods are going to be sick.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've been playing on PlayStation 3 and I've been watching Alan play it on PC and I'm like, now I kind of want it on PC because you had an inventory mod or something that...
[SPEAKER_02]: I downloaded a mod from Skyrim Nexus that basically makes managing your bag.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can sort by weight so I can see what all the heavy shit is that's weighing me down so I can get rid of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can sort by weight.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can sort by... Yeah, so it's an awesome add-on to make bag management in Skyrim awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you can do that on PS3.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actdeft in chat says, Sky, you really have no idea.
[SPEAKER_09]: There are people with over 100 multiple accounts.
[SPEAKER_09]: Good thing they got banned.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, yeah, good thing they got banned.
[SPEAKER_09]: At least Valve banned them.
[SPEAKER_09]: Some companies may not have even caught it.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, you know, at least they got banned.
[SPEAKER_09]: But yeah, I agree.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, I don't think Valve is the type of company, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: Again, I just kind of look at their track record.
[SPEAKER_09]: Steam overall has been a great thing for the community.
[SPEAKER_09]: It really has.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: and I think in the long run they'll kind of look back at this and go okay next time we need to if we're going to give somebody coal for getting their wish list done we need to make it so that they can't trade that to somebody else who's already unlocked it for the same reason like they'll go back to the drawing board and I think they'll fix it for next time or they'll do something different you know
[SPEAKER_09]: They'll learn from it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think they will.
[SPEAKER_09]: But it does suck that it had its issues this time.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's move on with more news.
[SPEAKER_09]: Gosh, we're having a long show.
[SPEAKER_06]: How about the story that I was going to read?
[SPEAKER_09]: How about it?
[SPEAKER_09]: I guess I can lift that cease and desist order.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, actually, it was Activision that put out the cease and desist on a dude who hacked Skylanders!
[SPEAKER_06]: Spyro Adventures!
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, this guy named Brandon Wilson had hacked the game to where he basically figured out the conversation between the piece and the game so that he could basically mount any piece he wanted to in the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: and so uh so so he figured out how that little little uh um toy and portal magic portal were talking to each other yeah and he got he put it up on the internet which of course that's what they send out the cease and desist right and um he wrote out um a note that said you know what uh
[SPEAKER_06]: The accusations were inaccurate.
[SPEAKER_06]: He wasn't really sharing them with other people.
[SPEAKER_06]: He had them on a zip file for his own use.
[SPEAKER_06]: He wasn't circumventing the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: He was basically just using stuff that was available, not using the hardware on an iOS device.
[SPEAKER_06]: He didn't really trick anything.
[SPEAKER_06]: He just figured it out.
[SPEAKER_06]: He just found it out.
[SPEAKER_06]: He didn't actually use it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, are you able to rip off Activision by doing this?
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, you can't just suddenly magically... You can't buy the figure.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can just make the... If you use another system to make it think you have the figure.
[SPEAKER_09]: But doesn't... Isn't there still like a code for the DLC?
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, you can't just magically download something that isn't there, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, would you be able to exploit and steal money from Activision by doing this?
[SPEAKER_09]: Or is it just you figured out how magnets work?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, you figure out how magnets work.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I mean, isn't there inevitably going to be somebody that wants to know how the magician does the trick?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I'm double checking something on here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Basically, I just found out how they connect.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I'm trying to find where exactly he listed that.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm asking Chatters because I have not played Skylanders yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: So Chatters, do you have to have a code to get the DLC?
[SPEAKER_06]: He uses RFID.
[SPEAKER_06]: He was just playing to figure out how it worked.
[SPEAKER_06]: And he put up the way it worked.
[SPEAKER_06]: And so I guess maybe it's Activision is afraid that someone's going to use that to steal.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_09]: You mean if the game is successful, people are going to try to rip it off?
[SPEAKER_09]: If it's successful.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: I understand it's been doing alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I think that's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think he just got bored, figured it out, and saved the information for himself.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then Activision's like, oh my god, people are going to use it and steal from us.
[SPEAKER_06]: All these five-year-olds with their toys.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkTetsuya in chat says, this talk of Skylanders makes me want a new version of Barcode Battler.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wish you could see how I just rolled my eyes.
[SPEAKER_09]: I remember those.
[SPEAKER_02]: Since I'm subbing for Loki tonight, should I be throwing shit and screaming about Skylanders?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because we're talking about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Go for it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Go ahead.
[SPEAKER_07]: But don't throw anything because all the stuff near you is heavy.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I was going to say, but this is, I wouldn't throw stuff in Dark Sakura's house either, but like everything that I would hit with is all stuff that we own.
[SPEAKER_02]: So Skylanders makes me very angry there.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's my Loki.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was a pretty crappy impression.
[SPEAKER_09]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_09]: Folks in chat aren't really able to answer the question about Skylanders, but I do see Derek H. says, well, of course there's a delay.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's like a minute delay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Derek H. in chat says, so corporations are now trying to make it illegal to learn.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_09]: They've probably emulated it already or they have their competing version for their own franchise that's going to come out at the end of next year.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think the thing is, though, that if this somehow allows people to download free DLC, then that's going to be an issue.
[SPEAKER_09]: But at the same time, if they didn't think that far ahead, then I don't want to say they deserve it, but they were asking for it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hacker's going to hack, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, boo-hoo, go cry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Crimea River, Build a Bridge, and Get Over It.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I'm pretty sure those figures have to come with a code that you have to input to actually get the DLC.
[SPEAKER_09]: Otherwise, the figure just tells the portal, this is the one I want to use, or maybe we take it to friends' houses, whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, if it works on just, you know, talking to... Because I think that that would make sense to not exactly have a code for it, but to have it just, you put the figure down and it connects.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that they might have been confident that no one would be able to figure it out.
[SPEAKER_09]: But then again... That was a dumb assumption.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was a stupid, stupid assumption.
[SPEAKER_06]: But how many other video game companies have done the same thing is what I'm saying.
[SPEAKER_09]: Again, I don't want to say they deserved it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Our security is foolproof.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't want to say they deserved it in that case, but that wasn't a smart decision.
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it's been going around.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a common thing amongst developers.
[SPEAKER_06]: No one's going to figure this out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's just be all confident and kiss our own asses.
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: So.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's travel around the world and check out some release dates, some games that are coming to a store near you.
[SPEAKER_09]: I kind of don't think there's a lot this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wonder what that could be.
[SPEAKER_09]: Could it be that the holiday period's now over?
[SPEAKER_09]: But we'll see if there's anything after all.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alan, you're filling in for Loki tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: What about the US releases?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, according to the source that we use, it looks like there's one solitary, sad little game coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to pick up next week, I believe on the 10th, as some of the 2012 Q1 releases are coming out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Especially towards the 31st.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think you have a couple big ones on the 31st.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Between now and the next episode of OLR, we have Anarchy Reigns for the 360, and that is it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't even know what the game is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I couldn't tell you a thing about it.
[SPEAKER_09]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to Japan to look at... Well, I'm not going there physically, but I'm going to look at their releases of things that are coming out, and I gotta tell you, I don't see a damn thing coming out in Japan.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm looking quickly to see if even the 3DS... Well, don't they have any Week 2 Vita stuff, or did it just have its...
[SPEAKER_09]: 3DS is outselling it already in week 2
[SPEAKER_02]: Someone in chat was saying that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it was Ranma.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was like LOL at Vita.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe this was the 3DS's strategy the whole time.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sure, right.
[SPEAKER_09]: But whatever it is, it'll be interesting to see if the numbers are the same here.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't want to be all fanboy and root for one or the other.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm interested in both, but it's certainly not a good sign.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you look at the technology of what the Vita has feature-wise and what it's trying to do versus the 3DS, which is just, hey, it's a polarized 3D screen that you don't need glasses for, I think the Vita is trying to accomplish more with the technology that's in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But hey, sometimes that just goes to show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bleeding Edge Technology, and, you know, the perks aren't necessarily what move the system.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, no releases in Japan this week, so how about Europe?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, to quote a line from one of my favorite movies, Spaceballs, we ain't found shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_09]: A very slow release.
[SPEAKER_09]: One game coming out in the entire world.
[SPEAKER_06]: A game that I personally don't give a crap about is coming out on the 10th.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_06]: That Gotham City Impostors...
[SPEAKER_09]: What is your hatred for Gotham City Imposters?
[SPEAKER_06]: It looked silly, silly cute.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's kind of part of my problem.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like, it's a bunch of wannabes.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: If I'm going to play a wannabe, I'll just play DC Universe Online.
[SPEAKER_09]: I can't follow that.
[SPEAKER_09]: DC Universe was definitely not wow.
[SPEAKER_09]: DC Universe felt more like Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles the arcade game than it did wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hate the controller so much.
[SPEAKER_09]: And if you're not into that, then of course you're not going to be into DC Universe.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I hate the camera.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I thought PvP was a lot of fun in DC Universe.
[SPEAKER_09]: I gotta say.
[SPEAKER_09]: But you're not a player versus player kind of person.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I'm not.
[SPEAKER_09]: I will dabble in it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll experiment with PvP.
[SPEAKER_06]: And to expand on my previous statement, and if I want to play a superhero game, I'll go back and play City of Heroes.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's fair.
[SPEAKER_06]: And if I want to play a game by that company, I'll just play Star Trek Online.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which I'm going to once it's free.
[SPEAKER_09]: Isn't that later this month?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've been reading on the Road to F2P blog that every time they do an expansion or something it's Road to whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: So now they've got number 25 of the Road to F2P expansion.
[SPEAKER_06]: Blog going on, so I'm pretty excited.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, of course, you've ruffled the feathers of our chatroom, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't give a shit.
[SPEAKER_09]: Brad from PogCulture says, Oh, no, she didn't.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_09]: Tigerclaw says, Gotham City Imposters looks amusing.
[SPEAKER_09]: It looks like a bunch of people in bad cosplay costumes shooting at each other.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, yes, yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: And if I want bad cosplay, I'll go to Fonamay.
[SPEAKER_06]: where there's occasionally some good cosplay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Derek H has drawn a line in the sand and says City of Heroes is a lot crappier than DC Universe Online.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it has better control.
[SPEAKER_09]: And better camera.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alan, you were a City of Heroes stand for quite some time.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just played it for like 20 minutes just yesterday.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's free to play now.
[SPEAKER_02]: City of Heroes has a very strong RP community and it's still kicking.
[SPEAKER_02]: So yeah, City of Heroes is...
[SPEAKER_09]: But if you're not into RP, like, I don't know, when I listen to Dead Pixel Live and what I know of Derek H, he doesn't strike me as somebody that's really into RP.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, he might.
[SPEAKER_09]: It might be like a, you know, the secret lives of, you know, dot, dot, dot.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I just don't get that.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's why he plays games.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, my favorite thing to do, though, was in City of Heroes, make costumes, which is actually the same thing that the only thing I like doing in DC Universe.
[SPEAKER_09]: So why aren't you playing Barbie, the game?
[SPEAKER_06]: You should see how I play Sims.
[SPEAKER_06]: I spend all my Sim game building the damn house and deciding what they're gonna look like.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's what you fucking do in the Sims is you build a house.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I don't do any of the get married and have babies shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: If I do anything, it's go sit in the park and play guitar and get a lot of money and then go home.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hack computer, go home.
[SPEAKER_09]: You are living out your fantasies of being a bum.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's what you're doing in The Sims.
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can do that in real life.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm unemployed.
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Funemployed, funemployed.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, the fandom community for those games is still going strong, and a group called... You forgot Quest for Glory.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, Quest for Glory came later.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, judging you so hard right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love that series, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Infamous-Adventures.com just released their HD fan community remake of Space Quest II.
[SPEAKER_02]: VOHAL's Revenge, the original, came out in 1987.
[SPEAKER_02]: Space Quest only had two games that were the really blocky 16-color EGA graphics.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why are you smirking?
[SPEAKER_02]: What do you want to say?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I'm looking at chat.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm not smirking at you.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm looking at chat.
[SPEAKER_09]: I promise.
[SPEAKER_02]: and then Space Quest 3, the Pirates of Pestilon had a graphical update or like it just it looked even though it was still text-based but yeah Space Quest 2 is probably the probably the best one of the whole franchise to be honest or at least before they went to point and click it took them five years to get this out there but yeah it looks like on the 30th of December just two days ago
[SPEAKER_02]: It's final.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can play Space Quest 2 with updated graphics due to the fans that go through and revamp this stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: I would really suggest if you are interested in this at all, you grab it now.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's free, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: You should probably grab it now because as soon as everybody gets back to work on Monday and the lawyers are back at work, there'll be a cease and desist letter.
[SPEAKER_09]: Any predictions?
[SPEAKER_09]: Tomorrow?
[SPEAKER_09]: Tuesday?
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's get cease and desisted?
[SPEAKER_02]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think by...
[SPEAKER_09]: I think Monday 5 o'clock.
[SPEAKER_02]: See, there's a different community that remade King's Quest 3 and I think 4, Perils of Rosella, which I think when I sat in for DarkSakura was my pick for classic game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Those are still up there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Those didn't get C&D'd.
[SPEAKER_02]: Really?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, what about the whole Silver Lining thing?
[SPEAKER_02]: That was a new property, I think is why.
[SPEAKER_09]: Telltale Games is getting a new property.
[SPEAKER_09]: Right, and at the time, we didn't know that King's Quest had been handed off and there's going to be a new one coming out from Telltale, and Silver Lining went through this whole ugly thing where it was like, yes, you can do the game as a fan game.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, you can't do it at all.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, yes, you can do it, but it can't say King's Quest on it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, finally it fucking came out, but...
[SPEAKER_09]: I kind of look at what happened to the silver lining and I'm like, this is not going to last.
[SPEAKER_02]: There are fan remakes of some of the original King's Quest games that I know are still out there that have been out for a year more.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, King's Quest is Roberta and Ken Williams and Space Quest is the two guys from Andromeda, Mark and Scott.
[SPEAKER_09]: And Roberta don't give a fuck anymore.
[SPEAKER_09]: She has said fuck off to the game industry.
[SPEAKER_02]: She lives in a cabin in the Yosemite.
[SPEAKER_09]: She has accomplished the American dream of living in a fort and get off her property.
[SPEAKER_09]: Bless her heart.
[SPEAKER_09]: But...
[SPEAKER_09]: The fact that she did Kingsway.
[SPEAKER_09]: Somebody else owns it now.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's a prize.
[SPEAKER_09]: Probably why she bought a fort.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I'm not lying.
[SPEAKER_09]: I believe that she does live in an outwood type of thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but Space Quest 2 definitely improved on the first one.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's hard as hell.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's text-based.
[SPEAKER_02]: Save often, because you will die.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's possible, like with some of the other Sierra games, to save your game past a point where you didn't pick up the item that you need.
[SPEAKER_09]: to beat the puzzle and you literally have to start over.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I just want to be clear when I joke about the whole cease and desist thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't want to see this thing get ceased and desisted.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think this is a great, you know, imitation is the finest form of flattery.
[SPEAKER_09]: And obviously people have very big spaces in their hearts for these types of games of yesteryear.
[SPEAKER_09]: I will probably fucking download this and play it because I used to love these games.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was more of a King's Quest person than a Space Quest, but nonetheless, I'll still play it and check it out.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I also, unfortunately, am all too familiar with the business side of things and how these things tend to get shut down, so we'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, just this last year, Streets of Rage got the Super Hela fan remake, and that was 1, 2, and 3, plus a bunch of extra fan-added crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was up for a week before Sega was like, uh-uh, nope.
[SPEAKER_09]: Take the hint, game companies.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, I realize Telltale's like kind of trying to crank those out and that's kind of their niche now.
[SPEAKER_09]: But, you know, they can't do everything.
[SPEAKER_09]: So maybe people want to see a new game.
[SPEAKER_02]: They can try.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Vivendi Activision that I think has the Sierra properties.
[SPEAKER_09]: I will say I am stupid excited for a new King's Quest game from Telltale.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think it's going to rock.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I just, you know, please don't let me down with this Telltale.
[SPEAKER_09]: Please, please don't let me down with it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have high hopes for that.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's a series that has been gone from the gaming community far too long.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's King's Quest.
[SPEAKER_09]: These other games too.
[SPEAKER_02]: King's Quest VIII, Mask of Eternity was a horrible nightmare and never really happened.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would have moved into a fort too if I had put that game out.
[SPEAKER_02]: That wasn't her.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought it was.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, Mask of Eternity was developed by... She had nothing to do with King's Quest?
[SPEAKER_09]: I thought she still kind of oversaw it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Her name was just on it because she invented Graham.
[SPEAKER_02]: The plot of it was about some knight arriving in Daventry and becoming king after King Graham.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the whole style of it, because it was like ISO view 3D where you like... It was like an action game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was awful is what it was.
[SPEAKER_02]: So yeah, no, that wasn't Roberta Williams.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: I thought for some reason she had something to do with it, but maybe it's just because she invented King's Quest and all.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyhow, moving on.
[SPEAKER_09]: Some stuff that is coming to Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks to all these different ratings boards around the world, we know some of the games that will be coming to Xbox Live Arcade within the next year.
[SPEAKER_09]: And there's some interesting things that are on here.
[SPEAKER_09]: Uh, AMY, Babel Rising, Bang Bang Racing, Deep Black Episode 1 and 2, Defenders of Ardania, Dungeon Fighter Live, Happy Action Theater, Haunt, I Am Alive, uh, Nexuiz, Quarrel, Rayman 3, Hoodlum Havoc, Retro City Rampage, that's that Grand Theft Auto-y type game, uh, Saints Row Money Shot, a spin-off game that apparently-
[SPEAKER_09]: From what I was reading about this game, it's some type of little mini game where you play the bullet and you try to go through as many things as possible as the bullet.
[SPEAKER_09]: It sounds very over the top and very Saints Row.
[SPEAKER_09]: Scary Girl, Shank 2, The Simpsons Arcade Game that had been leaked earlier, Sign Mora, Sonic the Hedgehog 4, Episode 2, Spelunky, Tetris Party Challenge, Warp, World Gone Sour, and Reketeer.
[SPEAKER_09]: That is like a compilation of everything over the past few months that has been leaked and
[SPEAKER_09]: from ratings boards and other websites.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's what the roster will look like for 2012.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's a good six months of releases right there, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_09]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, well, we've been talking a lot about classic games and indie games and so forth.
[SPEAKER_09]: We need to take a step back in time.
[SPEAKER_09]: to a simpler time when there was no DLC or patches for games.
[SPEAKER_09]: If the game was broke, it was just broke.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura's picked a broken game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is a little broken sometimes.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura's picked a mighty fine game as a classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_09]: And as I understand tonight, kind of a nod to, you know, I don't usually pick these kind of games, but dot, dot, dot, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, actually, it was one that I found myself enjoying quite a bit when it came out.
[SPEAKER_06]: So...
[SPEAKER_06]: This is going to be surprising to a lot of people, even though I've brought it up before.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the game is WWF WrestleMania 2000 for Nintendo 64.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I said it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I picked it.
[SPEAKER_06]: With its bad guitar synthesizer sound.
[SPEAKER_06]: Basically, it came out in 1999.
[SPEAKER_06]: It actually came out in 2000 in Japan for Nintendo 64.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was based off of their annual pay-per-view event.
[SPEAKER_06]: And honestly, this was when I was watching WWF regularly.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, during their whole attitude thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was the NWO and... This was in China.
[SPEAKER_06]: China, yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh man, that one was a mess.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was a big China fan at the time.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, back when everyone was laughing because Stephanie McMahon got boob implants, like, and you could totally tell the difference between one episode and the next.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, you know, all the best divas coming out at the time, you still had Fabulous Moolah and what was her name?
[SPEAKER_06]: Mae... Mae, what's her name?
[SPEAKER_06]: Her buddy.
[SPEAKER_06]: They were both fantastic wrestlers in their day.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're asking the wrong people wrestling trivia.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, Mae Young.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mae Young.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who would threaten to show her puppies.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was the best era of wrestling ever.
[SPEAKER_06]: You had Test back in the day and you had the Hardy Boys and...
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't remember his name either.
[SPEAKER_06]: Kidman.
[SPEAKER_06]: I remember his last name.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was like the time that I would totally be into wrestling.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Dan and I were both watching it and we loved it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So when this game came out and everyone's like, this is the best wrestling game ever.
[SPEAKER_06]: You gotta get it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Guess who got it?
[SPEAKER_06]: That was us.
[SPEAKER_06]: So...
[SPEAKER_06]: When it came out, it actually had this amazing story mode.
[SPEAKER_06]: You had Royal Rumble, you had King of the Ring, you had the pay-per-views.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the story modes were like watching the TV episodes, all the steroidal man drama you could handle.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because honestly, I think that wrestling is soap operas for straight dudes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Some of the chatters are chiming in.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're a little bit delayed here.
[SPEAKER_09]: Mae Young, Ivory, Tori, not Tori Wilson, Lita, Billy Kidman, Attitude Era, Reality Era.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you also had a lot of stuff going on with Steve Austin, so there was that going on too.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have never played this game, but I'm loving in the background.
[SPEAKER_09]: I see some of the signs.
[SPEAKER_09]: One of the signs says, China, suck it.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was hugely into WWF at the time, like all 80s kids were.
[SPEAKER_02]: But there was a part where I think half of it was that I kind of grew out of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I remember it was Roddy Piper versus Hulk Hogan.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was the big...
[SPEAKER_02]: that was the big war of good and evil was Roddy Piper and Hulk Hogan and then a lot of the major characters left and it was Stone Cold Steve Austin that brought it back from the doldrums because they had an icon again that they could you know he was awesome but by then I think I had outgrown it I remember playing some of the PS1 wrestling games that were good though
[SPEAKER_06]: www.DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_06]: who because what happens I think is that they save the same engine and use it for like whatever the fire pro wrestling and the various ones over there but it had all the signature moves and you could do custom stage entrance when you did the creative character so you could actually design everything that happened when they come out into the ring you could choose their starting music and it would actually have loops of some of the
[SPEAKER_06]: Dan and I made this guy.
[SPEAKER_06]: D-Generation X D-Generation X
[SPEAKER_06]: and it was just so super fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was a really fun game but like some of the characters in it you had the Road Warriors and Hulk Hogan and Taka Michinoku who was a legend in Japan.
[SPEAKER_06]: He did not get enough nods over here.
[SPEAKER_06]: You could actually create some of the WCW characters because I believe it was THQ, but they had the same... They had done the other games too.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you could actually recreate Goldberg, Kevin Nash, Scott Hall.
[SPEAKER_06]: You could even make Macho Man.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe...
[SPEAKER_06]: There were... If you had two... If you were doing a tag team match and you actually picked people who were on the same team, it would, you know, have them be introduced under their team name instead of just their individual names.
[SPEAKER_06]: You had...
[SPEAKER_06]: All kinds of stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think you could also do Hell in a Cell and you could do... I don't think you could do... I don't remember if the Ladders, Tables, and Chairs matches were in it at the time.
[SPEAKER_06]: But those were pretty fun too.
[SPEAKER_06]: The commercials, I remember they were funny too because you had The Rock doing Christmas themed ads.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, Kane was in it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the Underfaker.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, the Underbiker.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, the Undertaker.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's still around, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, he's still doing it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know why, because that man's had knee surgery and back surgery and everything else surgery.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what was the best about this?
[SPEAKER_06]: It had mankind in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_02]: I remember him.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mick Foley.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Mr. Socko.
[SPEAKER_06]: He would put a dirty sock on his hand with a mouth drawn on it and shove it in people's mouths.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, even I remember that.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: That man's insane.
[SPEAKER_09]: I had to learn wrestling because one night... I know this was the doing of Travis and Jessica over at Under Station Live because we used to all do Rocky Horror in Sacramento together.
[SPEAKER_09]: We did a wrestling night one night.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know who suggested that was, but I somehow think Jessica was a part of it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_09]: I seem to remember she was heavily involved in that but I had to learn wrestling because I had to play one of the characters because we did we played wrestling people in Rocky Horror
[SPEAKER_06]: That was the invention of the metal bull bra, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, it was.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was supposed to be Steve McMahon, the owner guy, as Riff Raff.
[SPEAKER_09]: Vince.
[SPEAKER_07]: Vince McMahon.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was Vince McMahon.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: At least I didn't say Ed McMahon.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was Vince McMahon as Riff Raff.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because I had the sister or daughter or something that was Magenta.
[SPEAKER_06]: Stephanie McMahon.
[SPEAKER_09]: With the boobs.
[SPEAKER_09]: And we were Riff Raff and Magenta in the movie.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you're into Rocky Horror, it was really funny.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, seriously, one of the most fun fucking shows we ever did because we actually had our own TLC match.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was tables, ladders, and cookie sheets.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ow.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just hit my head on your counter.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sitting in front of the bar and we had a fucking table and a ladder and a cookie sheet.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, I miss the Deadly Boys, because they would actually set... They used to be in ECW, which was like the really hardcore wrestling association, and they would just set tables on fire and throw each other through it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway, anyway.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry, back to games.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anything else you want to say about this game?
[SPEAKER_06]: You could get special copies that had a special hologram card with it that had different pictures of in-game action like an intro to a finish.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, but I mean, it was just an awesome game and it had everything at the time that you would expect to see on TV.
[SPEAKER_06]: And yeah, the music was kind of crap.
[SPEAKER_06]: But who cares?
[SPEAKER_06]: It was fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: And like I said, Dan and I would spend hours making a character.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then watch him play.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just watch him play.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like we had that one dude who was in purple and lime green who beat everybody.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I think he had like Shawn Michaels hair.
[SPEAKER_06]: So he had a mullet.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anything else to say about Rasslin'?
[SPEAKER_06]: I missed when wrestling was good.
[SPEAKER_09]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: Some of the chatters would say it's still good.
[SPEAKER_09]: There it is, your classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alan?
[SPEAKER_02]: I was going to say you don't like John Cena.
[SPEAKER_02]: The John Cena era.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like John Cena.
[SPEAKER_06]: I do like John Cena.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have to say I like him because he doesn't look over-rewarded.
[SPEAKER_06]: And he's actually good.
[SPEAKER_09]: I liked The Rock because he wasn't acting then.
[SPEAKER_09]: Quick, name a good movie with The Rock in it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I can't do it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Doom.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was actually going to say The Mummy 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because he was in it for five seconds and he was CG'd.
[SPEAKER_06]: I did like Scorpion King for the rest of it.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're done.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's Classic Game of the Week.
[SPEAKER_06]: That man looks good in tight pants.
[SPEAKER_09]: WWF.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, because it was the WWF back then.
[SPEAKER_09]: WrestleMania 2000 on the Nintendo 64.
[SPEAKER_07]: Screw those pandas.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, we're going to take a break.
[SPEAKER_09]: When we come back, we have plenty more of Orange Lounge Radio to come, including the all-important, the moment you've been waiting for all night, I'm sure, Game of the Year 2011 discussion.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know what DarkSakura's going to pick.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know what Alan's going to pick.
[SPEAKER_09]: They don't know what I'm going to pick.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alan thinks he knows, but maybe I changed my mind.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm worried at least one or two of ours will be the same.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's okay because, you know, there is no right or wrong answer.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also, your picks for Game of the Week.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're going to come up with the OLR Game of the Year for 2011 all when we come back.
[SPEAKER_09]: You might be surprised.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or you might not be.
[SPEAKER_09]: So we'll be back with plenty more of Orange Lounge Radio right after this.
[SPEAKER_09]: Stay tuned.
[SPEAKER_09]: Welcome back, everybody, to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: We are live on this 1st of January.
[SPEAKER_09]: Happy New Year 2012 with the 440th episode of our show from the new studio setup.
[SPEAKER_09]: Although, if everything's been done right, you shouldn't really be able to tell at all that it's a new setup.
[SPEAKER_09]: Rob Roberts, of course, here with you with DarkSakura and Alan tonight filling in for Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: It occurred to me.
[SPEAKER_06]: I realize why we have less background noise and extra reverberation.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Carpet.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, that's a big part of it is that you don't have the sound bouncing everywhere.
[SPEAKER_09]: The way it's partitioned is differently too.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just setups are going to be weird.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyhow, Loki, of course, will be back next week I don't want anyone thinking funny business is going on But it is technically a holiday And he, like many other people, has to go back to work tomorrow So I think there's a dinner thingy going on tonight that he's at So he'll be back next week to talk Game of the Year with us But the three of us that are here tonight will get into our Game of the Year picks here shortly But first, we've got to talk about some rapid-fire news So, Alan, since you're filling in for Loki tonight, why don't you start us off?
[SPEAKER_09]: By the way, it was a slow news week, so there's kind of some less stories than we usually have, just so you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: There is an MMO coming out in China, I believe, called The Age of Wulin.
[SPEAKER_02]: And a certain gentleman who wants to play this game very much went to an auction being held by the developers, Snail Games, and basically he bought an online item for his character.
[SPEAKER_02]: Once this game comes out, he's going to have some epic god-tier sword.
[SPEAKER_02]: for his character that he spent US dollar equivalent $16,000 for.
[SPEAKER_02]: For a weapon for his toon in a game that no one knows if it's even a good game or not.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, looking at the screenshot, and I think this is the official Age of Woolen trailer, it's on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks pretty.
[SPEAKER_02]: So Vish, I mean, obviously it's not some back alley studio that is making an ugly game.
[SPEAKER_02]: But yeah, $16,000 for an epic item.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also at this auction, they sold a sheath, meaning not a weapon.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the thing that you put your weapon in for your character for the Hook of Departure for $1,600.
[SPEAKER_02]: And another sheath for the Lordly Spear.
[SPEAKER_02]: for $2,500.
[SPEAKER_09]: Does he get his name in the game or any special thing for spending this much money?
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've heard of people spending a lot of money on an eBay auction because they can win a role in the game or the money goes to charity or something, but this doesn't appear to be the case, does it?
[SPEAKER_02]: It sounds like... I would hope that this item would be bound to his account so whatever character he rolls can use it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe he'll be able to kick everyone's ass in PvP.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't really know enough about the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: to know what this is going to do for him.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it looks like he received a commemorative plaque with his name engraved on it by Snail Games saying, you know, thou own this sword and you're awesome because you gave us 16 grand for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's a one-of-a-kind item.
[SPEAKER_02]: So the graphic, I guess, of visually the texture of how the sword looks and its name and its stats, he's the only one in the whole system that's going to have it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So his EP will be even bigger.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: When I would do stuff like that for my private servers on Ragnarok Online, I would pay $5.
[SPEAKER_02]: when I was into City of Heroes I would buy their costume packs which was about three to six bucks for like mutant because you know when City of Heroes like DarkSakura was saying there are millions of combinations of costumes for your character some of them were DLC so I've spent money I've race changed I've race changed my Bane and WoW I'm just not going to spend what you could buy a automobile for
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_09]: I hope Star Wars does legitimately, you know, even though I say two games can coexist, I do hope the two games can kind of tug and pull from each other a little bit.
[SPEAKER_09]: It'll help us all in the long run.
[SPEAKER_06]: And for the record, all the cryptic points, I did a lot of that in Star Trek Online.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that's why I have a defiant retrofit.
[SPEAKER_02]: and it looks like this game in China is entering open beta this spring I should sign up for it and it looks like we are getting it here in the US but it still needs to be put through open beta in China so I don't think there's really a due date on when we're going to get it here soon
[SPEAKER_06]: I played Ragnarok Online in Korean.
[SPEAKER_09]: So did I. I remember that.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was like, Jamie, what do I do here?
[SPEAKER_09]: Jamie, what do I do here?
[SPEAKER_06]: You played with me on the American one.
[SPEAKER_06]: On the American beta.
[SPEAKER_09]: I remember a translation patch for the Korean.
[SPEAKER_06]: There was a translation patch because some of the NPCs were still in Korean.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Then alright, I played that one.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I played the Korean one before that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whatever, it wasn't that great.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: And this article does make a brief mention of the wank over Elder Scrolls IV Oblivion, which of course was the game that came out before Skyrim, which is making a lot of game of the year lists right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because Oblivion had DLC where you could make pretty armor for your horse that literally did nothing.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was just...
[SPEAKER_09]: you know metal for your horse I kind of think the gaming community just needs to let that go like I understand that that is the quintessential like thing that people will point out for DLC but also at the same time Bethesda has come out the industry has learned from that mistake though that we will not do that again that was you know you know what nobody was fucking doing it then and we did it and we learned you know so okay kind of a break yeah anyhow what else you have for us
[SPEAKER_02]: What do I have for you?
[SPEAKER_02]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pirated games via torrents or Usenet or whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Torrent Freak, which is a big torrent, sort of underground torrent news site.
[SPEAKER_02]: If a torrent site gets raided, like the Pirate Bay, if they ever get raided, Torrent Freak is usually the site that reports on it, you know, like journalistically.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have compiled lists of the top pirated games via piracy.
[SPEAKER_02]: by digital torrent download.
[SPEAKER_02]: For PC, we've got Crysis 2, Call of Duty Modern Warfare 3, no surprise there, would have been probably number one if it came out earlier in the year.
[SPEAKER_02]: Top Wii game downloads, Galaxy 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mario Sports Mix, surprisingly, and Xenoblade Chronicles, which is... What the hell is... Oh, Super Mario Galaxy 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, sorry, Super Mario Galaxy 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mario Sports Mix.
[SPEAKER_02]: And number three is interesting, Xenoblade Chronicles, which you would think would be a no-one-curr game, but it's an issue of... It was translated in English for the Europe market, and according to this, the tally, 950,000 confirmed downloads via the various torrents that you could get this game on.
[SPEAKER_02]: and that's a thing where if Nintendo didn't have their head up their ass and put that out here then maybe that number... But they are going to put it out here, Alan.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, too little too late.
[SPEAKER_02]: Everyone here who wanted it either bought it and paid the 90 bucks to import it for their modded Wii from London or wherever their UK retailer is or they pirated it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And of course Modern Warfare 3...
[SPEAKER_02]: Access isn't a problem there because it's, you know, America is the biggest market for that game and it's just people don't want to pay 60 bucks for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So sometimes it's just an issue of people being cheap.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: But yeah, and then top 360 pirated downloads via BitTorrent, Gears of War 3, no surprise there.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then of course, number two, Call of Duty Modern Warfare 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: So all the, mostly the big multiplayer games.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_09]: We've talked about it here on this show before.
[SPEAKER_09]: Obviously, we don't support it either here at Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it seems like the number of people that are supporting it are dropping.
[SPEAKER_09]: Obviously, I don't think I need to touch on it here.
[SPEAKER_09]: It doesn't really directly relate to video games.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I'm sure you've all heard about what GoDaddy's been going through with this whole thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: And obviously, they had quite a number of embarrassing PR stumbles where I think you were hearing the Benny Hill theme playing in the background with every press release.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, the good news is that Nintendo, Sony, and EA have all as well dropped SOPA support.
[SPEAKER_09]: An update to the government's list of SOPA supporters show that the names are now no longer on there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Of course, there is no word as to why.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is it because they saw the tech community backlash to what happened to GoDaddy, or maybe that whole debacle made them rethink the position, or maybe they just realized finally it was not a good idea?
[SPEAKER_09]: For whatever the reason, it's a relief to see these gaming companies are finally dropping out and taking their names off the list.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hooray!
[SPEAKER_09]: Some more rumors are floating around about Epic Mickey 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now, you might remember there was an earlier rumor based on a survey that had been out there, some type of focus group thing that had people choosing the box art.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, the rumors are circulating again this week because I guess there was an online newsletter that Disney put out that just flat out said,
[SPEAKER_09]: Epic Mickey 2 is coming out on PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, and Wii in fall of 2012.
[SPEAKER_09]: You might remember the original Epic Mickey game was a Wii exclusive, but maybe because of that or what, it didn't sell maybe as much as it could have.
[SPEAKER_09]: And so it's kind of interesting in a way that it is getting a sequel after all.
[SPEAKER_09]: Supposedly the sequel, Epic Mickey 2, will also have co-op play, including two-player split-screen, which is something we don't see in games all the time anymore.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, in other news, there's a fun little game that I just purchased today called Bastion.
[SPEAKER_06]: And apparently other people have decided to buy it as well because it exceeded $500,000.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's an indie game.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, I mean, it's really catching on, don't you think?
[SPEAKER_06]: At any rate, that's with Steam and Xbox Live Arcade sales.
[SPEAKER_06]: And my apologies, I didn't mean dollars.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's 500,000 copies sold.
[SPEAKER_06]: My apologies.
[SPEAKER_06]: So yeah, good game.
[SPEAKER_06]: And a lot of people think so.
[SPEAKER_09]: To be honest, with some of the deals on Steam and so forth, I'm surprised it's not higher.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a quality game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, it's, you know, the story is also like from what, a couple days ago?
[SPEAKER_06]: So maybe, who knows, who knows.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it just exceeded that, so.
[SPEAKER_06]: And also, a really, really hard NES game has been translated into English.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's called Takeshi's Challenge.
[SPEAKER_06]: And to quote the article here, the game was made by the devil.
[SPEAKER_06]: one of the Ram modders King Mike has translated it into English so you can play it is it like Beat Takeshi the guy that was in Battle Royale I want to think so actually I'm pretty sure that it is but I can find out I am though very sure that it is from Beat Takeshi very cool
[SPEAKER_09]: and he has the show that's been ripped off here as Wipeout, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: Takeshi's Castle and they had the dubs that were on here in the States.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wasn't that a thing?
[SPEAKER_09]: Isn't that still on?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it was Takeshi's Castle and it was the ultimate challenge, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, Takeshi no Chosenjo And it is Beat Takeshi Takeshi Kitano Nice
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, well, before we get into some more news, the time has come for you to lip sync.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, just kidding.
[SPEAKER_09]: For us to talk about the Game of the Year of 2011.
[SPEAKER_09]: And we're going to go around the table and see what we here at OLR thought was the Game of the Year.
[SPEAKER_09]: We want to start with the community.
[SPEAKER_09]: Obviously, it's a show where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_09]: And earlier this week on Facebook and Google+, in our communities there, we asked you guys, what do you think is the Game of the Year?
[SPEAKER_09]: and I wanted to make sure this is important you guys understand there's no right or wrong answer the whole point of the show here is that it's where every gamer has a voice and everybody's into something different people can only afford sometimes to buy the games that were from last year or you know not everybody is necessarily into RPGs or shooters or racers
[SPEAKER_09]: So I think this is important to really just kind of open it up to actual gamers that are enthusiastic enough to be listening to a podcast and fan their page, yet may not necessarily find the same critical darlings to be as successful.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or maybe they did.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, sometimes what the critics pick really is the cream of the crop.
[SPEAKER_09]: So let's see.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's start with the community first and see what some of you guys out there said.
[SPEAKER_09]: was the absolute bestest game to come out in 2011.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or I'm sorry, that you played in 2011.
[SPEAKER_09]: It may have been a game that actually came out previously.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because, you know, God, there'll probably be some games I don't get to play until 2012 because 2011 was so crowded with so many good releases.
[SPEAKER_09]: Can I also start off by saying
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't remember looking back at last year going, this was the best year ever for games.
[SPEAKER_09]: But this year was really, really, really good.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, here's some of what you guys picked.
[SPEAKER_09]: Over on Facebook, Zether said, number three, Mario Kart 7, the best one.
[SPEAKER_09]: Number two, Saints Row the Third, wacky, insane, better than Grand Theft Auto 4 in every way.
[SPEAKER_09]: And his number one game of the year is Portal 2, an excellent follow-up with a very good single-player campaign and solid co-op.
[SPEAKER_09]: John Keegan said I shouldn't say the full last name sorry John K said over on Facebook best 2011 game Arkham City based on the variety of missions and improvement on an already awesome original otherwise I played older games in 2011 of which Assassin's Creed 2 and Uncharted 2 topped the charts based on awesome story and solid gameplay Derek W said
[SPEAKER_09]: said Resident Evil 4 HD.
[SPEAKER_09]: Kind of a remake of an older game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Great injection to a boring year of military shooters.
[SPEAKER_09]: Looks beautiful.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fallout New Vegas download content.
[SPEAKER_09]: The most rewarding and content-heavy DLC seen yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: And number one, Skyrim.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fus Ro Dah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Tom S said Skyrim Skyward Sword and Saints Row 3 didn't really give reasons but those are the top three Mike B said Gears of War 3 very well done kind of like a masterpiece of sci-fi shooters let me think about the other two time's up
[SPEAKER_09]: Johnny R says, number three, Alice Madness Returns, beautifully haunting sequel to one of my most beloved games as a child.
[SPEAKER_09]: Number two, Catherine, excellent puzzle game with a rad story to go with it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Number one, Mortal Kombat, great fighting game that stepped it up with an amazing story mode.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, Mike B did come up and say Saints Row 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, two, not three.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just discovered it in 2011.
[SPEAKER_09]: Kashuniko, or sorry, Kashuiko Janai, I think it's DJ Janai.
[SPEAKER_06]: Katsuhiko.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, says number three, Super Mario Land 3D.
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't watch a lot of El Hazard, did I?
[SPEAKER_09]: A great blend of traditional Mario and new Mario styles.
[SPEAKER_09]: If only Sonic could achieve this feat.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, snap.
[SPEAKER_09]: Number two, Portal 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: Funny story, great puzzles, awesome acting.
[SPEAKER_09]: Number one, Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_09]: The ultimate never-ending sandbox of building ADD insanity.
[SPEAKER_09]: OMG.
[SPEAKER_09]: Joe R said, number three, DDRX3 versus DDR Second Mix.
[SPEAKER_09]: Still some love for the Bomani games.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, it was either this or DDR2, and I noticed they still couldn't get the interface quite right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Number two, La Mulana on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_09]: No surprise there.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think I'm more surprised that it's not number one.
[SPEAKER_09]: He says, take what made Cade's story so great, but throw in some extra block and switch puzzles.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also recently announced that a PC port will come to Steam.
[SPEAKER_09]: Number one, The Legend of Zelda Skyward Sword.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm digging up this one a lot more than Twilight Princess.
[SPEAKER_09]: Great game, expecting to sink at least 30 hours in before I'm done.
[SPEAKER_09]: Bradley B said, number three, Chime Super Deluxe.
[SPEAKER_09]: Adds four good to great songs to the roster and adds perfect quads and changing layouts to further add to the gameplay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Number two, Portal 1, or excuse me, Portal 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oops.
[SPEAKER_09]: Number two is Portal 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: All around fun and adds so many more hilarious quotable quotes to the Portal universe.
[SPEAKER_09]: Number one, Bastion.
[SPEAKER_09]: The narration makes what would be a pretty good action game a great one.
[SPEAKER_09]: The narration adds a story that is full and vibrant and memorable.
[SPEAKER_09]: Miguel I says, Portal 2, best sequel ever.
[SPEAKER_09]: Forza 4, best driving game to date.
[SPEAKER_09]: A great combination of arcade and simulation type racing.
[SPEAKER_09]: And Sequence, DDR and RPG combined into a really fun and addicting game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Jim H says, Infamous 2 improves on everything from the first game and the user generated content was a great addition.
[SPEAKER_09]: Number two, LittleBigPlanet 2 improves
[SPEAKER_09]: Any other year, the sequel to one of my all-time favorite games that improves on the original would be my number one.
[SPEAKER_09]: And number one was Portal 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: He picked all twos for his top list.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sticking with the theme, it's an improvement on the original, has some of the best storytelling and voice acting in gaming history.
[SPEAKER_09]: Add in the great gameplay, and it makes it the game of the year.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let me quickly run over to Google+, because we had a few responses over there as well.
[SPEAKER_09]: I wanted to read for you guys and we had from DeadPixelLive commented F1 2011 Forza 4 and Pinball FX 2 F1 2011 because it did what a sports sequel is supposed to do leave the good stuff in and add more good stuff
[SPEAKER_09]: Forza 4 because the rival mode made driving and competing fun, and Pinball FX 2 because at the end of the year I realized I had played it more than all my other games.
[SPEAKER_09]: Good reason.
[SPEAKER_09]: We have another response here.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's written in Russian, so I'm not sure how to say this, so I apologize.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, do you read Russian?
[SPEAKER_09]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, so just pipe it through Google Translate.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, unfortunately, name I can't read.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ignorant American.
[SPEAKER_09]: Says, number one, Deus Ex, Human Revolution for a great cyberpunk story and enjoyable gameplay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Too bad Extro is not here.
[SPEAKER_09]: Extro can read Russian.
[SPEAKER_09]: Little known fact about Extro.
[SPEAKER_07]: I remember when he was learning.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I remember that, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks to Nelly.
[SPEAKER_09]: Number two, Bastion.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, because Loki's wife is Russian.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I remembered all of the cards all over your apartment, and I almost learned to read Russian, too.
[SPEAKER_09]: You'd think I'd know more after living there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyhow, number two, Bastion for very polished representation, great music, and awesome narration.
[SPEAKER_09]: And number three, The Witcher 2, Assassins of Kings for old school hardcore RPG brought up to the next level on every aspect.
[SPEAKER_09]: Lastly, Wendy S says, number three, Battlefield 3, favorite shooter, love the way they did multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_09]: Number two, NHL 12...
[SPEAKER_09]: Favorite sports game?
[SPEAKER_09]: Realistic simulation of hockey but not inaccessible.
[SPEAKER_09]: And number one, Portal 2 drew me in like nothing else could.
[SPEAKER_09]: So those are some of the responses from Facebook and Google+.
[SPEAKER_09]: Very diverse.
[SPEAKER_09]: Did you guys catch that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, but I put a game on my list that they didn't.
[SPEAKER_09]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: So we're about to get to that here in a minute.
[SPEAKER_09]: I wanted to quickly see if I could bring this up.
[SPEAKER_09]: I forgot to put it in the link or in the show role because over on NeoGAF, there's a thread where they're actually tracking what the media, all the different gaming outlets are naming as the game of the year.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I kind of wanted to give you an idea.
[SPEAKER_09]: What they were saying, kind of what the rest of the internet is saying, or what the critics are saying and so forth Let's see, I'll have to try and dig for this a little bit here Any games that the chatters mentioned that you were like, oh I forgot about that game
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, no.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because they all like Angry Birds, apparently.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't think anybody said Angry Birds, actually.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_09]: I found it.
[SPEAKER_09]: So this is from NeoGaf.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you to the folks over there that tallied this all together.
[SPEAKER_09]: Poster was Cheesemeister.
[SPEAKER_09]: Has tallied up what the media.
[SPEAKER_09]: 72 different outlets has picked Skyrim.
[SPEAKER_09]: And that's the number one.
[SPEAKER_09]: 22 outlets have picked Portal 2, 17 have picked Batman Arkham City, 7 for Zelda Skyward Sword, 7 for Uncharted 3 Drake's Deception, no listener put Uncharted 3, very interesting, 4 said Gears of War 3, 2 said Bastion, 2 said Catherine, 2 said Dark Souls
[SPEAKER_09]: Two said Deus Ex Human Resolution Two said L.A.
[SPEAKER_09]: Noire Again, surprised I didn't hear that from any of the chatters either Two said Star Wars The Old Republic Two said Super Brothers Sword and Sorcery EP and a handful of other games got a mention as well So
[SPEAKER_09]: Who cares about what the media thinks?
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's talk about what we think.
[SPEAKER_09]: Skyrim Why did you pick Skyrim?
[SPEAKER_02]: it tries to do something that a lot of game developers are afraid to do Bethesda rather the makers of Skyrim ever since the original two Elder Scrolls games which most people haven't played Arena and I'm blanking on what the second one was
[SPEAKER_02]: they're sandbox games before Grand Theft Auto which is where that genre and that term sandbox game came from so you can literally do anything if you want to make a plate wearing warrior who casts
[SPEAKER_02]: you can go exploring for hours ignore the main plot completely and still have stuff to do Bethesda with Morrowind and Oblivion and now Skyrim that's always been their thing to make this really immersive almost impossible to complete game and Skyrim is the best attempt at it yet where even I know people in real life that have played Morrowind and Oblivion and it was such a burden all this openness
[SPEAKER_02]: they hated it and Skyrim there's something about it where they get better each time in streamlining that combination of keeping your attention plus holy shit this is a whole huge world to dink around in visually it is gorgeous it's one of the most beautiful games I've ever played especially on my PC which is now four years old and yeah it's for a for you know kind of a
[SPEAKER_02]: I get really into exploration and min-maxing stats and doing crafting and Skyrim has all of that.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a great game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now, is it just me, or for a game as vast as Skyrim, we really need a new fucking mem besides this arrow to the knee shit?
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't get that until I finally was in a town, and I heard some dude, I used to be an adventurer like you, but then I took an arrow to the knee, and I was like, oh, thank you, it's something that some dude says to you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now I finally get that man.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: yeah it was from the game but it's like with a game so fucking huge like seriously there has to be something else the 50,000 cheese wheels off the mountain was funnier than an arrow to the knee I'm sorry there's a great picture of the the um the aural of Whiterun the first king that you meet where someone had stacked hundreds of like carrots apples cabbages all over him and they took a picture and he's got his chin on his fist like a thinking man on his throne being all kingly and he's just surrounded by like cabbages it's awesome
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, what is your number three pick for Game of the Year?
[SPEAKER_06]: Batman Arkham City.
[SPEAKER_09]: Batman Arkham City.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why did you pick Batman Arkham City?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because, and I honestly didn't play it, but I watched Dan play it most of the time.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I just sit back and it's like watching a movie.
Really?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's what happens when you're married or in a committed relationship.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sometimes you let the other person do the driving.
[SPEAKER_09]: I get it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, well, we've done that for tons of games between the two of us.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, you know, I just sit back and I totally dig the character designs.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love that they got Penguin right.
[SPEAKER_06]: That he's this British gangster kind of guy, you know.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Catwoman was absolute hotness.
[SPEAKER_06]: Except it is physically impossible to leap around like you do in four-inch heels, just saying.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mark Hamill's last performance as Joker.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, officially.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but then they went and teased Arkham World and you're like... He said on Twitter that he would come back specifically for a Killing Joke animated special.
[SPEAKER_09]: But yeah, it's interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: Throw enough money at him, he'll do it.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_09]: Get him better seats at the VGAs next year.
[SPEAKER_06]: but that was just like a fantastic performance and I really liked their Harley too especially you find the little Easter egg and oops spoilers oops you find a positive pregnancy test in their little love nest and then in one of the endings she's singing to her baby so it's just lots of neat little things thrown about in there and the whole business with Hush that was pretty cool because that was actually the last Batman thing I ever read was Heart of Hush
[SPEAKER_06]: I was not a big DC person but that was a really good storyline.
[SPEAKER_06]: So yeah, it was really cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: It had lots of nods to just all kinds of different characters and it was really neat.
[SPEAKER_06]: And also, as a designer, love the design in the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's beautiful.
[SPEAKER_09]: for me I just have to start off by saying this has been extraordinarily hard this year there have been so many not just good but fucking phenomenal games this year that I have like I told Alan like three days ago what my list was going to be and I've changed it since then I've changed it several times since then and even now in my head I'm like
[SPEAKER_09]: Do I really want to say this as number three?
[SPEAKER_09]: Or do I want to put this game in there because this game was so fucking good?
[SPEAKER_09]: But I'm going to just commit to what I'm going to say here.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I really think, you know, I kind of look back at fun and what game did I really enjoy.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think my number three game of the year is...
[SPEAKER_09]: Super Mario 3D Land on the 3DS because you know and I said this on the show when I first reviewed it I really think it is the greatest Mario game they have done since the Super Nintendo one I think it's just the 3D works it makes you understand why a 3DS you know can can work it's one of those games where you keep peeling back the layers and even though it seems like god this game is easy as cake it's
[SPEAKER_09]: in the beginning.
[SPEAKER_09]: It just gets crazier and crazier as you move on.
[SPEAKER_09]: It has a lot of the retro stuff that, you know, we love retro games here at OLR that we love.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's such a worthy reason to own a 3DS, and I think that Mario 3D Land is my number three pick for Game of the Year.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it might very well be the only 3DS game right now where the 3D is more than just, oh, that looks neat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's in 3D.
[SPEAKER_02]: When you play Super Mario 3D Land, the 3D is an integral part of the gameplay and the experience.
[SPEAKER_02]: And turning that little notch down on the side...
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, it damages the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I love that you can invert the 3D, too.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, it's hard to explain unless you do it, but it's very easy.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have it pop out or be recessed inwards, but it's still 3D.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I gotta remind you guys, I think, still to this day, that Mario 64 was quite a bit overrated because of a lot of its move to 3D.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yet, I love what 3D has done to Mario here.
[SPEAKER_09]: I look at myself and I can't justify it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, it just works.
[SPEAKER_09]: and that's why I think it's one of the greatest games to come out this year absolutely Salacious Pop or Alan your number two pick
[SPEAKER_02]: Probably going to say Dragon Age Origins since you said this could be games that we played in this year rather than came out.
[SPEAKER_02]: One of the reasons why I'm going back to a game from 2009 is that a lot of the big A-list games that came out like Deus Ex, I haven't played them so I don't want to talk out of my ass and hype up a game I've never played.
[SPEAKER_02]: um Bioware ever since you know the original Knights of the Old Republic RPG has shown that they are one of the best narrative and character writers in the industry um I would say even better than Blizzard and Valve and the twists and the care like Alistair and Morrigan who's he's the um
[SPEAKER_02]: Other Grey Warden and Morrigan is the Witch of the Wild are the first two NPCs you pick up.
[SPEAKER_02]: They are so engaging and I was fascinated with each of them for completely different reasons and they were acted and written so well and I was very invested in how I manipulated the game to make sure that I got endings that were right for them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Origins is the spiritual successor to Baldur's Gate and a lot of the D&D engine based games that Bioware wrote in the 90s.
[SPEAKER_02]: and Dragon Age 2 if you play it which I believe that came out earlier this year the menu and the UI it's all very new school I'm not saying Dragon Age 2 is a bad game but you can tell right away even just by the menus that it's a different origins really harkens back to
[SPEAKER_02]: The 90s experience for me, but with a present day game or story.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, so even though you went with a game that's a couple years old, you can do that because this is your picks for best game of 2011 and sometimes you don't discover the games until later.
[SPEAKER_02]: So for anyone who overlooked Origins, yeah, it's still relevant.
[SPEAKER_02]: Play it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, your number two pick.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ultimate Marvel vs. Marvel vs. Capcom 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: Galactus Flick.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fling!
[SPEAKER_06]: Making My Hand Hurt, Awesome Cast, Firebrand, but I still go back and play Phoenix more than anything.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: And She-Hulk, of course, because She-Hulk is hardcore.
[SPEAKER_06]: But yeah, it's just a fun fighting game.
[SPEAKER_06]: It brought out all the DLC characters, plus more characters that people wanted to see, except for no freaking Mega Man.
[SPEAKER_06]: But other than that, perfect.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fighting Game Perfection.
[SPEAKER_09]: Didn't bother you that it was only six months after the other Marvel vs. Capcom that also came out this year?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't buy any of the DLC.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, there you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, you know, the tweaks in the gameplay actually made it worth it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It felt different enough.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: My number two game of the year.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's one that's already been named, but I think it's a game absolutely worthy of the list.
[SPEAKER_09]: I never expected to enjoy Batman Arkham City as much as I did.
[SPEAKER_09]: I like Batman all the way back to the Adam West Batman.
[SPEAKER_09]: I admit I'm not as into reading the comics.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm not as into the animated series.
[SPEAKER_09]: I watched it a little bit when I was a kid.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I don't know the Mark Hamill Joker.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know the characterizations of these characters as much as some of y'all do.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I'll be damned if I didn't just love this game.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, it's just the story in it is outstanding.
[SPEAKER_09]: The way they juggle all of the villains without making it seem like cheesy or over the top is great.
[SPEAKER_09]: I love the exploration.
[SPEAKER_09]: Love, love, love the Grand Theft...
[SPEAKER_09]: Batman style thing that they have going on I think the DLC is done rather tastefully the way you can have I mean the whole Catwoman debacle outside where some people didn't have their codes the stuff they kind of been doing beyond that like the Nightwing and everything I think is neat expansions to the game I love the side missions it's a rewarding experience and it's the total package when it comes to a video game absolutely is I have to ask you did you do the bit where Catwoman abandons Batman
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Isn't it great?
[SPEAKER_06]: Screw him.
[SPEAKER_06]: She's such a bitch.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, no, the way that I mean, just the way the characters are done alone, it makes the game outstanding.
[SPEAKER_09]: But just it's just I think you said it well when you said you didn't even play it.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it was like watching a movie.
[SPEAKER_09]: And that's how good it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, and then to even take it a step further and actually kind of like get your hands on it and be in control is just outstanding.
[SPEAKER_06]: I did actually play a little bit of it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, I'm not going to say I didn't play any of it, but it was Dan's save.
[SPEAKER_06]: And since I'd seen so much of it, I was like, there's no point.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I might go back and do it myself now.
[SPEAKER_09]: So much to go back for with the Riddler trophies and the little side.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's beaten the Riddler mission.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh my God.
[SPEAKER_09]: I barely dented that.
[SPEAKER_06]: which is actually pretty messed up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, and not that hard.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, so now we're going to go around and get the number one picks.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh my gosh, here it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: The game of the year according to us.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alan.
[SPEAKER_02]: Portal 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: narrative writing and it's a hilarious game it's an emotional game you feel sympathetic for both Wheatley and GLaDOS you learn so much backstory for pretty much everyone including even Shell if you know how to look for it and it's a very it really just holds on to you and it never lets go it's quick once you beat it once if you love the story so much you can run through it again in a couple hours and it never feels stale
[SPEAKER_02]: and it really um Valve especially with Half-Life 2 episodes 1 and 2 really have tried to increase their game as far as script writing and story being told through dialogue but Portal 2 is where they're really like you're gonna listen to this and you're gonna be invested in these characters and also here's awesome puzzle you know puzzle cracking too where you have to need to figure out what to do so
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, your number one game of the year.
[SPEAKER_06]: I will answer it with a sound from my phone if it will play.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hope that made it through.
[SPEAKER_09]: It might have.
[SPEAKER_09]: A little bit.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a little quiet, but it made through.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's Portal 2, definitely.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because for all the same reasons that Alan said, and I've beaten it ten times in single player mode.
[SPEAKER_06]: More than ten times now in single player mode.
[SPEAKER_06]: I keep playing through that game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've probably played through that game once a month.
[SPEAKER_06]: And poor Wheatley.
[SPEAKER_06]: and I love that actor so much I was watching him on Graham Norton one time where he was paid a thousand pounds to be donated to charity to do a somersault on stage and he had never done one before and this man is tall this man is like a moose
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, people would get my reference from Supernatural, but anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's tall.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's very tall, very lanky.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think he's taller than you, Alan.
[SPEAKER_06]: And just watching how good-natured he is, and the fact that he brings so much of himself into the character, I thought it was perfect.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you can really hear that fun part, even when Wheatley's being an evil bastard.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just awesome, so...
[SPEAKER_06]: That and, you know, the giant mutant potato and all of the reoccurring jokes.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I even went in and tried to find all the stuff that did make it into the final game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like the Garfield conversation in co-op mode.
[SPEAKER_06]: Where apparently the two little robots, Atlas and Peabody, were supposed to go and find a Garfield comic.
[SPEAKER_06]: And GLaDOS rewrites it to say that John Arbuckle filled the house with neurotoxin.
[SPEAKER_09]: Too bad it's not Garfield without Garfield.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll have to find you the little file to play.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: My number one game of the year might surprise some people.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I really had to sit back and go, I don't ever beat video games anymore.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I think a lot of it has to do with the fact that maybe I play these MMOs, games you can't beat.
[SPEAKER_09]: The fact that I do this show or I just love video games so much that I try to play as many games as possible so I never have that attention span to finish a game.
[SPEAKER_09]: and I know it's a notorious joke on this show what bad gamer ADD I have that I never finish games.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like, ooh, Sparkly, go here.
[SPEAKER_09]: But there was one game that came out this year that said, sit down and fucking play me till I'm finished.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just Dance ABBA.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was the best 30 minutes of my life.
[SPEAKER_09]: Contemplated it.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, no.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's not Just Dance ABBA.
[SPEAKER_09]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can't beat Just Dance ABBA.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I was absolutely sucked into this game start to finish, and it's an amazing fucking video game, and it's the best video game of the year.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's Portal 2, absolutely without question, is the best video game of the year.
[SPEAKER_09]: and it's everything these two said and I will emphasize the fact that this game probably still would have been the game of the year without the co-op or the shit that they've been adding to it since then I haven't even touched co-op I did play a little bit of the co-op I didn't beat co-op, I played a little bit of it and it's like, you know, that just further enhanced the experience of what was already an amazing game and, you know, the story was great
[SPEAKER_09]: I have to admit, the first game I liked, but I didn't love like DarkSakura did.
[SPEAKER_09]: But this game, I think as Alan said a minute ago, made the first game that much better.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was so good.
[SPEAKER_09]: Absolutely, Portal 2 is my game of the year.
[SPEAKER_09]: Interesting that all three of us have picked the same game.
[SPEAKER_02]: In Portal 1, 90% of the story happened in the last two levels of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: and the story up until then you could read the signs and a lot of it was really implied and then at the end the finale when you're doing the big escape that's where you figure out oh okay Portal 2 just hits the ground running you already know what the story is and it just keeps getting better and better and better and better
[SPEAKER_01]: You made it to one of the human habitats.
[SPEAKER_01]: We're looking for an artifact.
[SPEAKER_01]: Think of it as an archaeological dig.
[SPEAKER_01]: Their laughter centered around one of the objects in this room.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Scan it for me.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, this cat loves lasagna so much that he eats all of the lasagna in his house.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, apparently it's not the cat's house or his
[SPEAKER_01]: The man who owns the lasagna is furious.
[SPEAKER_01]: The end.
[SPEAKER_01]: The end?
[SPEAKER_01]: That's not funny.
[SPEAKER_01]: Do either of you feel like laughing?
[SPEAKER_01]: All right, I'm pulling you out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Welcome back.
[SPEAKER_01]: While you were dead, I reworked the cartoon.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's up on the screen.
[SPEAKER_01]: As you can see, in my version, the man points out to the cat that the house is equipped with deadly neurotoxin dispensers.
[SPEAKER_01]: Briefly.
[SPEAKER_01]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, and by the way, I was telling the chat room earlier, but Dan and I were at Disneyland in line for Space Mountain going in the best of space.
[SPEAKER_06]: Space!
[SPEAKER_09]: Again, I stand by what we said earlier.
[SPEAKER_09]: We did not compare lists, so I had no idea.
[SPEAKER_09]: I kind of knew DarkSakura would go for Portal 2 as number one.
[SPEAKER_09]: There was no question.
[SPEAKER_09]: I didn't know Alan was going to go there, too.
[SPEAKER_09]: Very, very interesting that we all picked the same game.
[SPEAKER_09]: I would say, for the first time in 10 years, I think we've all picked the same game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Consensus!
[SPEAKER_09]: Hold on, Loki's not here, and I kind of don't think Loki's going to go that way.
[SPEAKER_02]: He'll go Grand Theft Auto 4.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, that didn't come out this year.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think that was his game last year.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think he's going to go Saints Row the third, which admittedly... I thought it was going to be on your list.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was so fucking... How is Skyrim not on my list?
[SPEAKER_09]: How is Skyrim not on my list?
[SPEAKER_06]: It wasn't on mine.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was that good of a year for games.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, Skyrim absolutely should be in my top three.
[SPEAKER_06]: I kind of don't care about Skyrim.
[SPEAKER_09]: But you're not really into those types of games, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: I wouldn't expect you to like Skyrim.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, all the crap that people do in Skyrim, I try to do in WoW.
[SPEAKER_09]: 50,000 cheese wheels off the side of the mountain.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you can't do that, but I try to climb every mountain and try to get to places that no one can get to.
[SPEAKER_09]: But no, I will admit, for quite some time, Saints Row the Third, just because of the fun factor part of it, that I have not laughed that fucking hard at a video game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, except maybe Portal 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I don't even think Portal 2 I laughed as hard as I did at Saints Row the Third.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, it's just that fucking good.
[SPEAKER_09]: But it's just, I look back and I go...
[SPEAKER_09]: Your three favorites.
[SPEAKER_09]: Gotta make a commitment.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think Mario edges it out slightly.
[SPEAKER_06]: Combustible lemons.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was the part that cracked me up to no end.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think we'll be able to say Portal 2 is going to end up the official OLR game of the year, just looking at the feedback and so forth.
[SPEAKER_09]: But Loki needs to have his say, so we'll get his input next week on what he thinks the top three games of the year are.
[SPEAKER_09]: Any guesses for Loki games?
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, I think we have all said Saints Row the Third will probably be his number one, but what else for Loki games?
[SPEAKER_09]: Skylanders.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think he'll put Skyrim on there too.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think he'll put Skyrim in his top three.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's that Battlefield game?
[SPEAKER_09]: He loves Battlefield 3?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, not Battlefield.
[SPEAKER_06]: What am I saying?
[SPEAKER_09]: Like actual Battlefield?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, um... The 1840 or 1940 whatever that he plays with the ants.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, Modern War... But they play Call of Duty Modern Warfare 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, not that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: So...
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm thinking more of Dan.
[SPEAKER_09]: If he could fuck around with it and hack it and stuff, that's the type of stuff he likes.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think his list will be Portal 2, Skyrim, and Saints Row the Third.
[SPEAKER_09]: But we'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: I found you something else to play.
[SPEAKER_06]: You must play it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh!
[SPEAKER_09]: Actdeft.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think this is what you were thinking of.
[SPEAKER_09]: Earth Defense Force.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Good call, Actdeft.
[SPEAKER_09]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_09]: Earth Defense Force will probably be in there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, there's the last thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's short.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_00]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_00]: Alright, I've been thinking.
[SPEAKER_00]: When life gives you lemons, don't make lemonade.
[SPEAKER_00]: Make life take the lemons back.
[SPEAKER_00]: Get mad!
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't want your damn lemons!
[SPEAKER_00]: What am I supposed to do with these?
[SPEAKER_00]: Demand to see life's manager.
[SPEAKER_00]: Make life rue the day it thought it could give Cave Johnson lemons.
[SPEAKER_00]: Do you know who I am?
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm the man who's gonna burn your house down with the lemons.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm gonna get my engineers to invent a combustible lemon that burns your house down!
[SPEAKER_06]: Burning people!
[SPEAKER_06]: He says what we're all thinking!
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sorry I don't have the one that had GLaDOS on there because her comments make it extra funny.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, so there it is, our Game of the Year discussion.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hope you guys enjoyed, or if you didn't, well, you're welcome to your own opinion.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, well, we got plenty of your opinions on the... I was surprised that only one person said Skyrim.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was limited by the fact that I play games 2-3 years late and the fact that I'm playing Skyrim when it's only 3 years old is actually kind of amazing and it's thanks to you getting it for me when it was cheap
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_09]: More gaming news for you guys.
[SPEAKER_09]: We've got the Mailbag FUs of the Week.
[SPEAKER_09]: And, of course, your phone call is coming up in just a little bit.
[SPEAKER_09]: So let's go to Alan with some more news.
[SPEAKER_02]: So there's been a lot of wank going on lately due to a feisty Valve employee who was seen at an event wearing a Half-Life Lambda circle logo with a 3 on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And people saw that and were like, ooh, Half-Life 3 is coming.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm a huge Half-Life fan, and for those listening who don't remember, Half-Life 2 proper came out in 2004, nearly 10 years ago, and Half-Life 2 Episode 2 came out in the orange box, which I believe, when did, that was what, September of 07, when Portal 1 came out?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Chet Falasek who is a writer for Half-Life and Left 4 Dead and he also occasionally hits up the official forums has said that all of the rumors that the Half-Life community on the official forums has sort of dredged out and saying that Valve is working up to something there's an alternate reality game similar to what Portal 2 had when they updated the ending to Portal 1 where you call into like modems and you download all of these images all the Portal 2 stuff and
[SPEAKER_02]: It's all trolling.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's all trolling by Half-Life fans like myself, just trolling each other.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's no official ARG, or if there is, of course, it's one of those sort of, you can kind of see through the subtext of his response saying...
[SPEAKER_02]: This is his official response.
[SPEAKER_02]: You are being trolled.
[SPEAKER_02]: There is no ARG.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wheatley's speech was set in Portal 2 fiction.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is all.
[SPEAKER_02]: There has been no directive from Gabe to leak anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is all false.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I would imagine there is something to leak, but it's all under lock and key by Valve.
[SPEAKER_02]: Finishing his quote, I just want to say...
[SPEAKER_02]: It's all just trolling.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: Even if he did get disciplined for it, it's not a fireable offense for him to make a custom t-shirt that he knew was going to get the fandom to lose their minds.
[SPEAKER_02]: And even if he did get in trouble for it, we're not privy to that information.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's none of our business.
[SPEAKER_09]: How could Valve not be doing Half-Life 3 eventually?
[SPEAKER_09]: Like you said, it's their bread and butter.
[SPEAKER_09]: They probably just keep going back and changing stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I kind of think it's coming soon.
[SPEAKER_09]: What else is left for Valve to do?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, they're doing Defense of the Ancients.
[SPEAKER_09]: But that's in beta now.
[SPEAKER_09]: Defense of the Ancients is going to be out before E3.
[SPEAKER_09]: So what's Valve got to talk about at E3 this year?
[SPEAKER_09]: Left 4 Dead 3
[SPEAKER_09]: Give the Half-Life fans, throw them a fucking bone.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let this be their year.
[SPEAKER_09]: 2012 is the end of the world after all.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let them have their goddamn Half-Life 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because it was six years between 1 and 2, and now it's 8 between 2 and conceivably 3 if they would say anything about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's just like, we know that you're working on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: We just want, throw us a bone.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they're like, no, we're not ready.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're like Blizzard.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're not going to tell us shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: And this is all just trolling that's going on right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: At least you'll have Defense of the Ancients to hold you over.
[SPEAKER_02]: I no longer care.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Moving on to what I find to be kind of an interesting thing that happened.
[SPEAKER_09]: This has to do with the game Fallout New Vegas.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I guess what happened is that the lead designer behind Fallout New Vegas actually released a mod to go with the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's not an official patch.
[SPEAKER_09]: And of course now the source story isn't loading for me, but I read it earlier.
[SPEAKER_09]: And the official patch, or they didn't want to officially patch it because it was changing the games in ways that they may not want to subject everybody to in terms of balancing and so on.
[SPEAKER_09]: So...
[SPEAKER_09]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_09]: Slash J. Sawyer underscore FNV underscore mod dot zip But yeah, it's for Fallout New Vegas It will turn up the difficulty Putting it up there to what he wanted in terms of difficulty Hence part of the reasons why they don't want to put it out there for everybody
[SPEAKER_09]: and he also just kind of said, you know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: The game's over.
[SPEAKER_09]: The ship's sailed.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nobody's working on it anymore.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's no testers.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's nothing.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is just me doing what I want to do in my free time.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, Fallout New Vegas is done.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, hold out hope for Fallout 4, I suppose, which would I would think going to be their next game now that Skyrim's out there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fallout New Vegas is pretty good, I have to say.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: so there you go there is by the way an ultimate edition of Fallout New Vegas coming out on February 7th but that's just all the DLC from Fallout New Vegas originally all put together in one little package there
[SPEAKER_09]: Alrighty, let's go to the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_09]: No.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Every week, you guys send us emails at mailbag at orangelaundradio.com and DarkSakura threatens to not read them, but then we beat her until she does.
[SPEAKER_09]: Beat, beat, beat.
[SPEAKER_09]: Beat.
[SPEAKER_09]: Bat, bat, bat, bat, bat.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm gonna treat you like a Justin Bieber piata.
[SPEAKER_09]: Bat, bat, bat, bat.
[SPEAKER_06]: Those things were hideous.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just some paper plates and party hats.
[SPEAKER_06]: Paper plates and party hats is what they are.
[SPEAKER_09]: Stapled together.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, so the first email comes from Robert M. Somehow I get the feeling that Jamie, if she's in studio tonight, has already seen this.
[SPEAKER_06]: But were you anticipating what I was about me not being here?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, I wasn't really seriously thinking of calling in.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, if so, please post this link to the chatroom and stop reading this now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Otherwise, here's a pro-toy customizer's version of the Metal Slug Tank.
[SPEAKER_06]: Best of luck in the year ahead.
[SPEAKER_06]: And yeah, I did see this, and I will post it in the chatroom, and if Ranma will be so kind as to put this picture and the link to the article on our Tumblr.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's a little Lego.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a Lego.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's cute.
[SPEAKER_06]: Metal Slug Cute So I will post this in the chat room now
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, also this music makes me kind of wish I was going on the Matterhorn.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because it's kind of the same.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: So this comes from Holly D. Hey guys, I just wanted to share something that popped into my head when I heard about the poor guys on your show who have had their Xbox Live in-post screwed with.
[SPEAKER_06]: Particularly the guy who said he gave them information to investigate and then they said his credentials weren't right even though they hadn't changed since he opened the case.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was like WTF
[SPEAKER_06]: The first one pretty much hung up on me, so I called back again.
[SPEAKER_06]: This woman told me she could not access the account with me, even though I was calling about an appointment I obviously knew already.
[SPEAKER_06]: I argued with this woman for an hour, and she finally found that my account had been closed, and then the guy who set up the new service opened a new one and put in some BS number.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I had to reopen the old account, but she kept insisting that I had to go physically to one of their locations to fix it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I said, like hell I was, and I pointed out to her that if they weren't allowed to change the number, then who the hell gave him permission to change it in the first place?
[SPEAKER_06]: So she could clearly see it had changed.
[SPEAKER_06]: after that she put me on the phone with her supervisor who fixed it took about two hours total the basic point of this is to say try to point out the flaws in their logic and demand to know who authorized changing the information it gets results sometimes because you know if they're claiming they can't change it then they sure as hell know who authorized the first change I hope it helps and I hope they get their accounts back soon Holly D yeah
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what happened with Comcast with us?
[SPEAKER_08]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_06]: We were supposed to have everything fixed on Thursday, and the night before, Dan had a phone call, an automated phone call that said Thursday, and Dan had taken Thursday off work.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, then he goes to check it in the morning, and it said Friday, when Dan had to be at work.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, he called and he said, I told him to call his supervisor, but I was also, you know, seven in the morning and sleep.
[SPEAKER_06]: So...
[SPEAKER_09]: Sometimes these automations and computers and stuff just leads to trouble.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a problem.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fail is what it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: She had to talk to a human being to get anything done.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, no.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dan tried to talk to a human being and she wouldn't change it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey guys, it's Blade 3 again.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just wanted to say sorry about my grammar a couple weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_06]: I give everyone a hard time.
[SPEAKER_09]: She gives everyone shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: But use a period after a go, please.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was on a PSP 2000 semicolon and comma.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's wrong.
[SPEAKER_06]: By the way, I was wondering what studio equipment you use.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm setting up a recording studio and I was curious that should have a U in it about your mics and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_06]: Please keep it up, the awesome work.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, it's not as complicated as you'd think, the setup.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know for a show that's been around as long as we have, you'd think we'd have this fancy thing going on, but it's actually not that complicated.
[SPEAKER_06]: Our first board came off of eBay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, the first board came off of eBay.
[SPEAKER_09]: The board we're using right now, we did upgrade to a newer board some time ago, and I'll tell you, it's what's called a Eurorack.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's by Behringer.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, it's by Behringer.
[SPEAKER_09]: UB1222FX Pro.
[SPEAKER_09]: There are pictures, if you look at the new studio pictures at orangeonestudio.com, you can see the mixing board sitting there in the background.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's really as simple as we have three microphones, and they're all hodgepodge microphones.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll take a picture and put it up right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've got a radio shack in my hand.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, Loki's is from Radio Shack.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura's is a Behringer mic that I think she picked up when she picked up the board.
[SPEAKER_09]: Mine was donated by DDR Angel like eight years ago and it still works.
[SPEAKER_09]: She's like, this is an expensive mic and I want you guys to have it.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it still works.
[SPEAKER_06]: I bought this one because my old mic died.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, the DDR Angel mic is also a backup mic because it is sold.
[SPEAKER_09]: We actually had another mic that broke.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then you've got your Horde House one in the other room.
[SPEAKER_09]: Don't know what that one's from.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think it's another Radio Shack mic, but it's like a newer Radio Shack mic.
[SPEAKER_09]: So they all plug into the board.
[SPEAKER_06]: Every mic that I've bought, I've gotten at Guitar Center.
[SPEAKER_09]: And every mic I think I've got at Radio Shack, maybe one at Fry's.
[SPEAKER_09]: But anyway, they all plug into the board.
[SPEAKER_09]: We try to equalize things on the board.
[SPEAKER_09]: I realize our voices are not always equalized.
[SPEAKER_09]: We try best we can to adjust things on the fly.
[SPEAKER_09]: But unfortunately, sometimes some of my co-hosts, especially DarkSakura and Loki, tend to be very quiet if they're in a bad mood.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then they get very excited!
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki's worse, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: He is a lot worse.
[SPEAKER_06]: By the way, look at our website and our little photos at the top.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just sent a picture of the computer and the soundboard.
[SPEAKER_09]: By themselves.
[SPEAKER_09]: The computer was donated by the listeners.
[SPEAKER_09]: The monitor is from Dan's mom.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's... Okay, when Dan's grandmom got a new computer, we took the monitor.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that's one of our spare monitors.
[SPEAKER_09]: So it's just a simple flat screen monitor.
[SPEAKER_09]: And the computer was donated by the listeners, which was an awesome gesture.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was when I had the Diva Fit one episode and I stormed off the set because... What had happened?
[SPEAKER_09]: I think the show just kind of died in the middle.
[SPEAKER_09]: The computer... Didn't the sound card...
[SPEAKER_09]: The sound card went out and- Just crapped in the middle of the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think the graphic card went out too.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then somebody in chat just, you know, sometimes, and they, you know, the person apologized to me afterwards, so I don't mean to like dig up this four-year-old drama, but it was, you know, just unfortunately say the wrong thing at the wrong moment, and I just fucking lost it.
[SPEAKER_09]: And you know it was a moment when Travis called me the next day to go, that was the best thing that has ever happened on OLR.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: and Travis doesn't say nice things about OLR very often but he called me to say Rob that was the best thing you ever did on OLR but the listeners after hearing that actually pulled together and bought a new computer and we use it to this day
[SPEAKER_02]: I was in studio DarkSakura when the show computer before this one, it was going to be my second or third guest appearance on OLR, it was when we had just started dating, where the old show computer died.
[SPEAKER_02]: It went kaput.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_09]: No, no, no, that was my donation.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was yours, that's right.
[SPEAKER_09]: But that's the one that crapped out on that show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: That caused me to lose it.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, because it was 5.30 and you were firing up the computer and getting everything ready.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it just, it died, it stopped.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, yeah, something happened.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was right before we got, no, that was it.
[SPEAKER_09]: But we were able to fix it.
[SPEAKER_09]: We were able to fix it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Something, it was something we found out later on was like a setting or something was screwed up, but we were able to fix it.
[SPEAKER_09]: But it just screwed the show that night, so.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: and yeah and also the uh this soundboard that you guys have just goes into the line in on your sound card and then you guys use what audition for the yeah we use audition for the for the podcasting itself yeah the mixing board goes into the computer through the line in and then it's all recorded straight in adobe audition
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: My old laptop had the capability, except for that card, it was actually listed as speaker output.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_06]: So yeah, well different sound cards.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anything that came, you want to have it set to anything that's going to come out of the speaker.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think somebody explained it to me as you want a full duplex card and not a half duplex card.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because full duplex is what's capable in and out at the same time.
[SPEAKER_09]: So that's very important.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you're going to do podcasts from your computer, spend the extra money to get a nicer sound card and you'll be set.
[SPEAKER_06]: My nice awesome quad core computer doesn't have a sound card that does that, but my old crappy laptop does.
[SPEAKER_09]: In the chat, DarkTetsuya says, oh, I think he had that clip on Understation Live not too long after.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's a clip?
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, Lord.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, it probably was all recorded on Justin.TV, or did Justin.TV go out when the rest of it went out?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think we were using Justin.TV.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, because we were in the garage studio when that happened.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I think Justin TV was out, but... I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was so long ago now.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sure that clip will show up soon enough, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: And Ranma says it's Sound Blaster, Odigy, or Better.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's what you're going to want out of a card.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway, that's my very long-winded memory lane answer to that short question.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, we have one last email.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: And actually, it's from... Well, it didn't... I'm just going to say from Nigel.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's an article from The Guardian, UK national newspaper.
[SPEAKER_06]: I read The Guardian all the time, so yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: That might interest one DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_06]: And here it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: Playing video games makes me sick, is what it's called.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I scammed it over, and...
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll go ahead and read this bit of the paragraph.
[SPEAKER_06]: And he's talking about playing MW3.
[SPEAKER_06]: He says,
[SPEAKER_06]: For me, it was triggered from the first time I played such a game, the PlayStation Classic Doom in 1995.
[SPEAKER_06]: And for me, the pixel games don't do it to me that badly, like Doom, but the worst game that ever did it to me was...
[SPEAKER_06]: Crap, what was it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Goldeneye on Nintendo 64.
[SPEAKER_06]: That game would make me so sick.
[SPEAKER_06]: I couldn't watch, because Dan was playing through it at the time, and he loves that game, and I wanted to love it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I really did.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nope, sick.
[SPEAKER_06]: I couldn't play Unreal.
[SPEAKER_06]: I couldn't play the newer Quakes, because anything that was actually 3D would make me sick.
[SPEAKER_06]: Katamari made me super sick.
[SPEAKER_06]: Portal makes me way sick.
[SPEAKER_06]: because it doesn't have that fast reorientation the way that Portal 2 does.
[SPEAKER_06]: So Portal 2 made me sick at first, but I could get used to it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And now I can play it with no problem.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, I do have to stop every few levels and let my eyes readjust, but I can't play the first Portal for very long at all because it will make me very nauseous.
[SPEAKER_09]: Technically, you're supposed to do that with any game anyway, every 30 minutes or so.
[SPEAKER_09]: How many people do that, Rob?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I'm just saying, you're supposed to, and there's a reason.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I'm usually also multitasking.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm talking to people while I'm playing Portal.
[SPEAKER_06]: But yeah, basically, it's just... Here's another thing that he says.
[SPEAKER_06]: The U.S.
[SPEAKER_06]: Army Research Institute for Behavioral Social Science also studied flight simulators and found that slightly fewer than half of pilots using them reported symptoms similar to motion sickness.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, this is actually super cool, and I would also, in fact, I'm gonna link this in the chat room as well, because I think that other people will benefit from this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Spazinator, you can shut the fuck up.
[SPEAKER_09]: Spazinator, by the way, said, wanna play some GoldenEye?
[SPEAKER_09]: But to be fair, he did put colon P, which means he isn't serious.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I wasn't serious, although...
[SPEAKER_06]: but yeah I just would get so sick and I get a little motion sick in a car if I'm not driving but yeah alright that it for emails?
[SPEAKER_06]: you know what I do not complain every other second so AGN728 bite me bite me that's not a complaint that's a command you should complain about the fact that they can't be bothered to change your nickname
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wonder if that's for Angry Gaming Nerd, maybe?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, it's somebody that's coming from All Games Radio, All Games Network.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're in the All Games chat as opposed to chat.orange.radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dude, you didn't have to kick him.
[SPEAKER_06]: What'd you kick him for?
[SPEAKER_06]: I can handle my own battles.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm a grown woman and I can fight my own battles.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now look at that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Despite all that, she's got your back.
[SPEAKER_06]: Despite all that, she has your back.
[SPEAKER_09]: Despite all that.
[SPEAKER_09]: You need to slap Ranma with a trout right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I wanted to kick him myself.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, no, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wouldn't have done that because I'm a good girl.
[SPEAKER_09]: I will slap Ranma with a trout for you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_09]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: We need to, we actually, I wish we could change that to like with large boobs or something.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, moving on.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: We got to move on.
[SPEAKER_09]: FUs of the Week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, speaking of complaints, what a perfect time for us to do our normal segment of the FUs of the Week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, really, my complaint is fuck you to moving.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because moving is awful.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, I like being in the new house that isn't falling apart like my old house was.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hate paying rent now, but I really like being in the new place.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's just the soreness and the pain that comes with all the moving.
[SPEAKER_06]: And not really just the physical stuff, but the emotional side of it too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because, I mean, Dan and I lived at that old house.
[SPEAKER_06]: We got married living in that old house.
[SPEAKER_06]: We had lots of wonderful fights in that old house.
[SPEAKER_06]: We've done lots of other things in that house.
[SPEAKER_06]: Shermie's pooped on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, how many... Shermie hasn't pooped on this house yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: You've prayed in that house, is what you meant to say.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, Rob, I've prayed.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've prayed a lot.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh God, oh God, oh God.
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I mean, on top of that, that house before, you know, we rented from our friends and they got married in the backyard of that house.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, I mean, we have lots of memories of going over there to visit our friends, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, a decade of memories of that house.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, you know, we're going to miss our neighbors.
[SPEAKER_06]: We told them where we live.
[SPEAKER_06]: We literally moved three blocks away.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have to add a thank you to Dan for this morning.
[SPEAKER_06]: When he kind of woke me up when he was about to leave, he said, you don't have to do anything today.
[SPEAKER_06]: You have my full blessing to stay in bed all day or play WoW all day if you want to.
[SPEAKER_06]: I will not expect a single chore out of you.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I got up and did the dishes.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I did the dishes when I got up because I just wanted my coffee cup.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, Dan did all that, so... We have this kind of jack thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's got a big metal platform on top, and you put it under the table, and you jack it up like a car jack.
[SPEAKER_09]: He had to jack it.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it lifts the whole table up so that you can move it on this wheeled object.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that in and of itself isn't very heavy, and you can raise it to the level of a truck and slide it in.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a science to that shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: The refrigerator was harder to move.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because we had to take the doors off the house and the doors off the refrigerator to get the damn thing in.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, we gotta move on with the FUs.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alan.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh boy, um, it's a new year, it's when people set arbitrary expectations on life changes, you know, resolutions, and I'm like really fat right now, so I've ended up being really out of shape and weighing the most I've ever weighed in my life.
[SPEAKER_07]: I blame happiness.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's relationship weight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I'm so miserable.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it's being unemployed, and, you know, it's apparently done wonders for my appetite that I don't need, so... I just need to lose weight.
[SPEAKER_06]: That happened, though, when I first moved out here and moved in with Dan.
[SPEAKER_06]: I went from a size 12, which I don't care, I've always had some butt to me, to a 24 size.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, I think Rob's accurate.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it happens when you're not working, relationship weight, when you're... A lot of stuff involved, so... And you're certainly not a size 24 anymore.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I lost 60 pounds.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're not!
[SPEAKER_02]: When I was helping do volunteer crew for Umlaut, the rock band fundraiser, it's fine now, but for a day or two after, for a good two weeks, my right knee was hurting because I guess I picked something up wrong.
[SPEAKER_02]: Better than my back, which is injured, but it's okay now.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's like, that means you're getting old.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lift stuff up means you're out of shape and you're getting old.
[SPEAKER_02]: So just being out of shape and overweight.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, my FU of the week, I don't know, I don't really have a lot, because, shit, I'm on vacation right now, and I, I have an extra week off, I don't have to go back tomorrow like most people do, so, and I'm going to Disneyland, shit, life's pretty fucking good right now, so, FU to the fact that it all has to end sometime.
[SPEAKER_06]: FU for not taking me.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, F you to you for not being taken.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Heart, heart, heart.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's it for the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just a couple more stories for you guys, and then we're going to open up the Skype line and take your Twitter topics.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't think we have a lot of Twitter topics yet, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_09]: Twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_09]: But first, just a couple quick stories for you guys.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alan.
[SPEAKER_02]: Team Meat, who made the amazing sort of... God.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you see Actdeft in chat?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: That you took an arrow to the knee?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Die!
[SPEAKER_02]: I have a sneeze on deck, so I'm going to try and burn through this story.
[SPEAKER_02]: Team Meat released a game called The Binding of Isaac, and it's the same art as Super Meat Boy, which is a great retro-ish game that made a lot of top ten lists for this year.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Binding of Isaac, it's currently available on PC via Steam.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're in talks to bring it to the 3DS via their 3DS app store.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you are just playing VVVVV on the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: Different developer, but it's still a Steam indie game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now available on a handheld.
[SPEAKER_02]: Team Meat is trying to bring The Binding of Isaac, which I guess is a roguelike dungeon crawler game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It has some biblical story points to it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently it's really awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kind of gross, but Super Meat Boy was kind of gross too.
[SPEAKER_02]: It has the same art style.
[SPEAKER_02]: Look for it on the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe they're in talks.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: I kind of like where that's going if a lot of those indie games are suddenly going to show up on 3DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: They wanted to bring Super Meat Boy to the Wii, but the limitations on the patching and how big I think the max file size could be, they couldn't do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So the fact that they're still talking to Nintendo trying to get their next game after Super Meat Boy 2, the 3DS is a great sign.
[SPEAKER_09]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: And lastly tonight, a story that...
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: new copies have a code that comes with it but an online pass is purchased through the PlayStation Network if you have a used or a downloaded copy now this was amended later on because I guess at first they were like oh shit if you download it you have to get the online pass as well but it actually was updated to say that hold on the online pass is actually already included when you download it on PlayStation Network so you don't have to download it separately just to be fair
[SPEAKER_09]: So the online passes though, they are going over to the PS Vita.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now the online pass will cost 900 yen for Hot Shots Golf.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's about $11.50 US.
[SPEAKER_09]: So you can expect $10 probably to be about the same price here in the US.
[SPEAKER_09]: So...
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I guess it's probably not surprising to hear, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's go to the phones.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're going to open up the phones right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was doing my hair.
[SPEAKER_09]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're going to go to the Twitter topics real quick and read some of the stories and things you guys want to talk about.
[SPEAKER_09]: Not a whole lot of feedback this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Didn't get a lot through the week probably because of the holidays.
[SPEAKER_09]: But let's see.
[SPEAKER_09]: Redertainment tweeted us saying, voting is live for the fourth annual The Four Star Awards.
[SPEAKER_09]: What is that?
[SPEAKER_09]: Is that like your own personal... What is The Four Star Awards?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: And we're not nominated.
[SPEAKER_09]: Granted, there's no podcast category, but we should be nominated for Movie of the Year.
[SPEAKER_09]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_09]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's on Facebook.
[SPEAKER_09]: You want to check it out.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll pimp out any awards show.
[SPEAKER_09]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_09]: 1-877-GAME-OLR Our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, Tigerclaw sent us a couple quick tweets here.
[SPEAKER_09]: I read about one of these earlier.
[SPEAKER_09]: He sent us a tweet about dude turned Swapnote into an RPG.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have to admit, I didn't pick this story for tonight because I wasn't sure how to explain it.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a YouTube.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's nine minutes long, so I'm not going to play the entire YouTube for you guys, but some guy... If you don't know what Swapnote is, it came out on the 3DS this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's, um...
[SPEAKER_09]: A system that lets you basically exchange emails, except instead of written emails, they're little actual written handwritten notes that you can send to other people.
[SPEAKER_09]: But as you use Swapnote more, you can start to send five second messages or pictures.
[SPEAKER_09]: I actually sent to all the people on my friends list on 3DS, I sent a picture of Maruko, one of the cats here, and sent it out.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, you know, it's kind of like a fun way to share things.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like, oh, wow, Nintendo is actually embracing the Internet for something.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, somebody actually turned it into a full-fledged RPG in the vein of Dungeons & Dragons.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I guess there's even like a Dungeon Master template you can use.
[SPEAKER_09]: And he talks about all this in his YouTube on how he did it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Again, it's a little long for me to play here, but it's mncdover is the username on YouTube if you want to look that up for yourself.
[SPEAKER_09]: and one other tweet here from Tigerclaw Epic Games scores a victory against Silicon Knights in a two-human suit
[SPEAKER_09]: And I don't even remember what this suit was all about.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I'm loading the story now.
[SPEAKER_09]: He's linked us to a story at the multiplayer blog at MTV.com.
[SPEAKER_09]: And let's see.
[SPEAKER_09]: Too Human was supposed to be the start of the next great expansive RPG franchise and the reasons that gamers were wanting Xbox 360 back in the early days.
[SPEAKER_09]: the Silicon Knights developed game was supposed to be a big deal but the game was delayed for two years the critical response to the game was less enthusiastic and what was intended to be a trilogy was dead on arrival with just 130,000 units sold and Microsoft ending their agreement with Silicon Knights I guess Silicon sued Epic Games over 2Human saying that Epic misrepresented the functionality of the Unreal Engine which was used for 2Human resulting in the two year delay wow interesting
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, the case against Epic Games took a blow because one of the key witnesses was excluded from giving testimony after a ruling by Judge James Denver III.
[SPEAKER_09]: The testimony was going to break it down into dollars and cents terms what the negative impact of working with the Unreal Engine was supposed to have on Silicon Knights, but the testimony was found to be questionable and that the methods did not fit the facts of the case.
[SPEAKER_09]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: I didn't realize there was all this drama going on.
[SPEAKER_09]: Of course, this was a game that wasn't on my radar.
[SPEAKER_09]: And maybe the fact that it wasn't on my radar is part of the reason why it didn't sell so good.
[SPEAKER_09]: But there you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyhow, let's go to the phones and take some calls.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_09]: Ooh, hey, you don't sound so good.
[SPEAKER_09]: Try again.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_09]: Is it just me that doesn't hear that at all?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's really... You sound like a Dalek.
[SPEAKER_09]: I can't.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm hoping... Oh God, I hope that's... It was Zaku, obviously, that was calling in.
[SPEAKER_09]: He might have been able to make that out, but I couldn't understand him at all.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, neither could I. Now, was that his connection or was that ours?
[SPEAKER_09]: See, now all these things I'm going to question.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is it the new studio setup?
[SPEAKER_09]: So let me just see real quick here.
[SPEAKER_09]: Real quick here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello, welcome to Skype call testing service.
[SPEAKER_04]: See, that works fine.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hello, British lady.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's see if maybe this next call sounds a little cleaner.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_09]: Hello, Derek H. Hi, Derek H. See, I can understand Derek just fine.
[SPEAKER_09]: Our last call was a little weird.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, anyhow, Derek, what's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_03]: I would like to talk about video games.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've called you guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's this thing called Steam.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know if you've heard of it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, a friend was telling me about Steam.
[SPEAKER_06]: We don't play games.
[SPEAKER_06]: I play board games.
[SPEAKER_09]: We sure eat a lot of food though.
[SPEAKER_06]: Would you like to play some Risk?
[SPEAKER_06]: Or maybe Axis and Allies?
[SPEAKER_03]: I was thinking more about Wits and Wagers maybe.
[SPEAKER_09]: So Steam, yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, I've heard of Steam.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think the listeners do too.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've had Steam for a long time and I only buy games when they're like... Whoa, whoa, whoa.
[SPEAKER_09]: Derek, you cut out.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you can hear me, you like totally cut out.
[SPEAKER_09]: It sounds like...
[SPEAKER_09]: What the hell's going on?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like the void of calls.
[SPEAKER_09]: Your voice like dropped out.
[SPEAKER_09]: So did your mic come unplugged or something?
[SPEAKER_09]: Hello, trying Derek again.
[SPEAKER_09]: One, two, three.
[SPEAKER_09]: I see that we're still connected.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's not an internet thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: But he just, the voice dropped out.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't even know if he can hear us.
[SPEAKER_09]: He hung up.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's a bummer.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't even know what he was about to say about Steam, but I think it was like, I only buy games when... And I'm thinking it was maybe when they're on sale.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, dirt cheap.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe it was going to lead to a question about is that bad for the industry?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just want to make sure here real quick.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's just... Maybe this studio is a bad omen for calls.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_04]: Welcome to Skype Core Testing Service.
[SPEAKER_04]: After the beep, please record a message.
[SPEAKER_04]: Afterwards, your message will be played back to you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, I'm doing really professional internet radio right now, and I am testing a Skype connection live.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love you, British lady.
[SPEAKER_09]: On the air.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is all DarkSakura's fault.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, I'm doing really professional internet radio right now, and I am... See, it's fine.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what's up is this delicious stew.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's amazing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you so much.
[SPEAKER_09]: The delicious pop is just put in front of my mouth begging me to eat.
[SPEAKER_09]: What did you make here?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just stew, cubed stew beef, small red potatoes, carrots, and I actually cut up two blood oranges and threw them in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can taste the citrus.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can taste it too, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I used a peeler to get the rind, the orange.
[SPEAKER_02]: The zest.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's Orange Lounge Studio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god, we're breaking up.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've had that in my head like all night.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, let's move on to another call.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe this one will work.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, you're on Orange Ones Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's Shane.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, well, so far we can hear you and you're not a robot, so that's good.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, Shane.
[SPEAKER_10]: Awesome, I'm not a robot.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's on your mind, Shane?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was calling to see if your stuff would work, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, only the collar appears to be broken this time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Shane, you need to come play with me on the Horde server.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, but there's so much Star Wars going on right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: Poo on that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Then let's talk Star Wars.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because you were just telling me earlier, you do nothing but play Star Wars now.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, it's really sad.
[SPEAKER_09]: I came on here and I said, you know, I like Star Wars and I don't like Star Wars for these particular reasons.
[SPEAKER_09]: So what are your thoughts on Star Wars The Old Republic?
[SPEAKER_10]: well first of all I'd like to say I did not listen to what you said about why you like it and why you do not so I don't know if I'm going to copy you or anything but I like it because the story is really cool and I don't know anything about Star Wars so this is all new to me like every single last thing
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, I'm still there.
[SPEAKER_10]: I hear stuff in the background.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, we're just eating.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're stuffing our face while you're talking.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, that's what I was doing.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was eating crappy McDonald's.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm trying to ask you long questions.
[SPEAKER_10]: That wasn't a very long question.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't like it because it doesn't feel polished still, which is expected because it's such a new game.
[SPEAKER_10]: But that will come with time.
[SPEAKER_10]: WoW wasn't that great at vanilla.
[SPEAKER_10]: I played it a little bit.
[SPEAKER_10]: but I'm really digging it like there's plot twists and every single class so far has been really fun to play which I can't say the same for WoW but I do love WoW I'm in a year commitment with WoW I have it like fully paid off with time cards so I don't really care if I'm not playing it right now so but I'm really enjoying Star Wars I just got a ship on one of my characters and it's pretty cool I'm eating
[SPEAKER_06]: So describe the glasses for us.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh my god, you pigs.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, some of us haven't had dinner.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, that's what I was doing, and then I thought I would call in help to make sure your Skype was working.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wait, wait, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, hold on.
[SPEAKER_10]: I got another question for you.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: My question is, what is supposed to happen in the endgame of Star Wars?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know, because I can't even figure out the non-endgame yet.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like...
[SPEAKER_10]: There's no hand-holding for the most part, except for at the very beginning.
[SPEAKER_10]: And so I'm just kind of pretending I know what I'm doing, and it's not working out so well in some situations, like some quests I kind of suck at.
[SPEAKER_10]: But oh well.
[SPEAKER_10]: I haven't seen but maybe two level 50 characters, and their armor is ugly, so I don't even care about endgame yet.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just want story.
[SPEAKER_07]: Something just occurred to me.
[SPEAKER_10]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: We're sitting at a table eating.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: I know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who does that anymore?
[SPEAKER_02]: So Shane, have you had any problems with like leveling up, like keeping your crafting up to level with what level you are and using the auction house?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because Rob, I haven't played it myself, but Rob was saying that he has trouble with how auction house works.
[SPEAKER_09]: The auction house is pretty terrible.
[SPEAKER_09]: The auction house works like Final Fantasy XI's auction house in some ways.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like a hybrid between XI and WoW.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's weird.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't really like it, but the crafting, funny enough, I'm actually doing right now while I'm on this Skype stuff because I was not paying attention to it because part of the crafting aspect is that your companions do it and not you.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I now have two companions, so I can kind of do two things at once, but my companion, that's a...
[SPEAKER_10]: I can run around the world with and do stuff with and fight is my tank and I'm a healer so I kind of need him to not craft because he goes away when he crafts.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I'm just leveling up the little thing that makes lightsaber crystals right now because it's really, really far behind.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I like it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Are we going to get on our characters later and do flashpoints?
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: I like the starter flashpoints for both sides now.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's neat because you can completely change the outcome of that flashpoint story based on dialogue options.
[SPEAKER_10]: So all my characters, for the most part, are light side, even though they might be Imperial or Republic.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I save the captain from being killed.
[SPEAKER_10]: I save this general from being killed.
[SPEAKER_10]: I take this chick with me that the commander wants killed.
[SPEAKER_10]: So if my choice gets picked out of the random rolls, it affects the rest of the story for everybody for that specific flashpoint.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that's really neat to me.
[SPEAKER_10]: And they don't feel that long, even though I think they're like an hour long each.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I did just yesterday run a second flashpoint on one of my characters.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't remember who.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it was very dull.
[SPEAKER_10]: because it was all brown.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was like playing Gears of War or any other FPS that's come out in the last couple years.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was going to say I ask myself that a lot when I cry myself to sleep at night.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyhow, I should probably let you go soon so we can get other calls, hopefully.
[SPEAKER_09]: But do you have any other closing thoughts for us tonight, Shane?
[SPEAKER_10]: I was going to participate in that top three games of the year thing on Facebook, and then I got lazy and didn't type anything out.
[SPEAKER_10]: But Portal 2 would have been my number one as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: After thinking about every single game that came out this year, I didn't sit through any other game from start to finish this year except for Portal.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think what we should have done is a top three most disappointing games of the year because there were a lot of hyped games that did not meet expectations at all.
[SPEAKER_09]: My number one would piss people off.
[SPEAKER_09]: My top three would probably make lots of people angry.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can make people angry because they can't send hate mail to you.
[SPEAKER_09]: So what's your top three?
[SPEAKER_10]: Most disappointing.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: You said you like Strider, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, no.
[SPEAKER_10]: I like Phoenix Wright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, Phoenix Wright?
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, he can be wrong.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can choke on a potato, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: I agree with Dragon Age 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: I believe I've picked up every NPC that I can, I think.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just got off the mountain where Flemeth is there and you do the thing where Flemeth comes back.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't care about the side characters like I did in Origins.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, the story's just not as good.
[SPEAKER_10]: The combat's more fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: I own it on PC and PS3.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's how much I cared about Dragon Age 1.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was like, oh, I love 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's gonna be awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm gonna beat it simply because I'm committed to the world that they've built, but the writing isn't as good.
[SPEAKER_09]: No.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Shane, I got to let you go so we can get more calls.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: Have a good one, okay?
[SPEAKER_09]: You too.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're going to go to some more calls.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hooray.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's try this again.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_03]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's Derek H. from Virginia Beach.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nice to hear from you again.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know what happened before.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a weird internet thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I blame Skype.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it's free, so you can't blame Skype, but I still blame Skype.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, you were talking about Steam, and you were about to say, you were talking about, I only buy games on Steam when... They're on sale, and that is a huge mistake.
[SPEAKER_03]: I should only buy games on Steam.
[SPEAKER_03]: In fact, I'll say this about everybody.
[SPEAKER_03]: Everybody should only buy games on Steam when they're full price, because then you know that you actually want that game.
[SPEAKER_03]: because I have a... Now, after the last week, I have like eight games I'm never gonna play again.
[SPEAKER_03]: I bought two games.
[SPEAKER_03]: I bought... I looked and I said, oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's two flight sims for only $3 a piece.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then I looked and I have a flight stick that had fallen behind my desk like a year ago.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I never even bothered to reach it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so when I picked it up, it had a layer of dust on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I was like, oh, wait, I have a flight stick.
[SPEAKER_03]: I must like flight sims.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I bought those games, played them for 20 minutes and realized I hate flight sims.
[SPEAKER_02]: Raise your hand if you've been there.
[SPEAKER_02]: earlier this year I think it was the Thanksgiving sale they had Dead Space 1 and 2 in a combo pack for like 4 or 5 bucks and I was like alright Dead Space you know Resident Evil with aliens or ghosts in outer space I'll buy that I had already bought it completely forgot that I had bought the rights to download that on my Steam same with Mass Effect 2 Digital Deluxe Edition it's like oh yeah dirt cheap 3 bucks I get my credit card out oh yeah you bought that 6 months ago but you forgot about it instantly afterward
[SPEAKER_02]: So I definitely have that problem.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have Knights of the Old Republic on the Xbox version, but you can play it on the 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: I bought that two years ago.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, four years ago.
[SPEAKER_03]: A long time ago.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't like it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm one of the few people that cannot stand KOTOR.
[SPEAKER_03]: I saw it on Steam.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was only $2.50.
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually struggle with myself not to buy it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I own this game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't like it.
[SPEAKER_09]: But it's only $2.50 You posted on Facebook or Google or something about that Because I remember reading that One of my friends worked on that game Really?
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what she called it?
[SPEAKER_09]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: Scrotor But hey, while she was working on it, we got to go to the Skywalker Ranch Oh, that's when you flung the meatball at George Lucas No, when I wanted to fling meatloaf at George Lucas He walked by and I could have flung meatloaf at him I changed the story a little bit, I embellished
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what, Derek?
[SPEAKER_09]: I did something similar during this most recent Steam sale.
[SPEAKER_09]: I bought Quake Collection.
[SPEAKER_09]: I didn't just buy one Quake game.
[SPEAKER_09]: I bought Quake 1, 2, and 3.
[SPEAKER_09]: Quake 2 isn't even that good.
[SPEAKER_09]: And Quake 1 and 3 were good like 10 years ago, but playing them now, like my video card doesn't know how to handle Quake 3.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like I was having problems getting Quake 3 to even work.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why am I buying Quake 3 when I can just go play Quake live?
[SPEAKER_03]: I almost bought... When they had a thing where you can buy all the Star Wars games or something for like $14, I was like, that's a great deal.
[SPEAKER_03]: Even though I had no interest in buying these games when they came out or the years afterwards, all of a sudden I think I kind of need these games.
[SPEAKER_09]: But that's how they get people.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, this happens in our culture all the time, is that people want to see that they're getting a good deal.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, for example, look at all the hilarity that happened on Black Friday.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sure everybody here saw the video, Derek, I'm assuming you probably saw this too, of the people at Walmart that were practically jumping on top of each other and clawing each other's eye outs over $2 waffle irons.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's like, who really needs a waffle iron?
[SPEAKER_09]: How many days out of the year do you make waffles at home?
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yourself, you know?
[SPEAKER_09]: How many days last year did you make waffles?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I have a friend that makes waffles.
[SPEAKER_09]: But not you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Weekly.
[SPEAKER_09]: You make waffles weekly?
[SPEAKER_09]: I... Would you trust a $2 waffle iron to make waffles?
[SPEAKER_06]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: Unless it was a recognized brand and a Rudolph.
[SPEAKER_09]: But why do people want to kill each other over a $2 waffle iron?
[SPEAKER_09]: Because it's $2.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you waffle that much, then you don't want waffles from a $2 waffle iron.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: We won a waffle iron at a white elephant exchange and Alan actually tried to make waffles with it and he got so frustrated he was cussing at this cheap white elephant waffle maker that makes little circus animal waffles.
[SPEAKER_09]: But anyway, sorry, I'm totally going on a tangent.
[SPEAKER_09]: But you know what I mean.
[SPEAKER_09]: In our culture, people want to get things just because it's a good deal.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, so Becky just messaged me and says, I make waffles at least twice a month.
[SPEAKER_06]: But Becky is also a great cook.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, she has a really good waffle iron.
[SPEAKER_09]: I wouldn't be surprised at all.
[SPEAKER_09]: She probably has a lot of great cooking things that most people don't have.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alan, you look like you're dying to say something over there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm too lazy to look it up, but there's actually a clinical term culturally for when in times of financial hardship, like when the economy's in a shitter, just when people are broke, they'll go to the gas station when they fill up their car with a tank of gas and they'll buy a candy bar and they're not even hungry, but it's just an 89 cent thing that makes them feel good that they bought this little...
[SPEAKER_02]: this little thing that just makes them feel better because it's cheap and Steam is a great outlet for that impulse that we have where I need to buy something, I'm tired of being broke or this is only a dollar so who fucking cares Retail therapy, really, I mean, in the end So you're saying I bought Wings of Prey because I'm clinically depressed is what you're saying?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't think it's quite that.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't think we could make that conclusion here on the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: People are just driven if something is cheap.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sometimes it feels good to spend a little bit of money, even if it's something that you know that you ultimately won't.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know I do it all the time, but yeah, if you make something cheap enough, people will buy it whether they want it or not.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe it would be a good policy moving forward for people, before you buy a Steam game, you need to walk away for an hour.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: and then say after an hour, okay, do I still really want that game?
[SPEAKER_09]: And if the answer is yes, then you buy it.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can't do it because they have that countdown on the screen.
[SPEAKER_03]: The number's going down.
[SPEAKER_07]: What if I only have 57 minutes?
[SPEAKER_07]: Why do you think I just bought Bastion at the start of the show?
[SPEAKER_09]: and I even told you I said wait till you get home click done bitch alright Derek good luck with your Steam I don't want to say addiction but your Steam issues we'll say and hey at least I hope you're getting to play some great games out of it even if just for 20 minutes
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm gonna go play VVV right after the show
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, the big battles, the multi-community gaming tournament.
[SPEAKER_03]: You should do it because gaming is about having fun, and you have more fun, I believe, when you're competing, and even more fun when you're competing for something you enjoy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Basically, you get to represent your favorite podcast or whatever and say, hey, we're the best.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mortal Kombat players.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's not even we're the best.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not really you're the best, but it's something you can hold up over somebody else's head.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's kind of nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's always fun when you can compete against your friends.
[SPEAKER_03]: And also you get to meet new people.
[SPEAKER_03]: You get to play against people you probably wouldn't have.
[SPEAKER_03]: You've been playing games against the same 20 people for the last four years.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now you get to play against some other people who share the same interests as you.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a good thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: The big battle done.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think it's great.
[SPEAKER_09]: I signed up to play.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm not signing up because I'm not going to win.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who are we kidding here?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll probably get knocked out the first round.
[SPEAKER_09]: I may not be the best, but I can be the loudest.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think for the Mortal Kombat ones the ringers are the guys from Spooky Hour Horror Hour who love not only horror games but like everything about horror so they live and breathe Mortal Kombat so I think they're probably going to be the winners there but you know what it's good to take to like throw a knife in Tedekin's throat every couple of days that'll be fun alright well Derek I gotta let you go so we wrap up the show but thank you so much for the call
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for doing a show so late tonight
[SPEAKER_09]: We finished tweets.
[SPEAKER_09]: Last minute stories.
[SPEAKER_09]: Usually I turn to Loki for that.
[SPEAKER_09]: He's not here.
[SPEAKER_09]: I anticipate Alan probably didn't dig anything up.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have one.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's been a clarification about the Final Fantasy X HD remake that Squeenix announced in September.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess one of the developers or producers was asked for a timeline.
[SPEAKER_02]: And he's like, just to make this clear, the Final Fantasy X remake isn't just a texture cleanup and a resolution upscaling.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is a remake.
[SPEAKER_02]: So redrawing of 10.
[SPEAKER_02]: So redrawing of assets, cleaning up the script, new voiceover work.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is the real deal.
[SPEAKER_09]: So what everybody wanted from Final Fantasy 7... 10 is getting.
[SPEAKER_09]: 10 is getting.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's just do 7.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well...
[SPEAKER_09]: How about do six?
[SPEAKER_09]: So people thought... How about let's really remake a game?
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's take one like six or four.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, four I guess got the DS remake, but six.
[SPEAKER_09]: Six is begging for a really, really awesome remake.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: That just came out?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, story's dated today.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: I think a lot of that stuff got really out of control.
[SPEAKER_09]: Was it a slow news week or what?
[SPEAKER_09]: I think a lot of it's been discussed a lot and I don't know what else there is to add to that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Two, I think Loki really wants to talk about it because he's actually used that controller that's at the core of it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think although it's important to distinguish between the individual that doesn't know how to deal with customers whatsoever and the device itself, Loki has used the device itself and really wanted to comment on it.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I'm kind of pushing that back to next week so we can discuss that a little more.
[SPEAKER_09]: So just so you know, I just wanted to say, yes, I'm aware that that happened in the gaming world this week, but at the same time,
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I might get shit for this, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's not really gaming news.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's gaming community news and gaming community events, and I get why people are following it, but it's just horrible train wreck, Rikki Lake holding her hand against the face with the jaw dropped, all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: So...
[SPEAKER_09]: I can't believe you just made a Ricky Lake reference.
[SPEAKER_09]: Go Ricky.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: I will say, though, since Derek had just called in, Dead Pixel Live actually got the guy on the show.
[SPEAKER_09]: And from what I understand, he apologized.
[SPEAKER_09]: So at that token, what else is there to say if he's apologized?
[SPEAKER_09]: But I also kind of think... I feel bad because I have no idea what this is about.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll find out next week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or go listen to Dead Pixel Live show from Thursday.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: The whole debacle is interesting, but at the same time, I think had this happened in November when Skyrim and all these things were coming out, it wouldn't have been as big of a thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: They did a good job covering it in a more timely manner since they were able to get the guy on the day after it happened.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know what we could contribute to that conversation.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's been five days.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's an eternity in internet time.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think we're ready to wrap it up.
[SPEAKER_09]: So we can't really wrap it up and put a bow on it and call it done until everybody has given their final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_09]: So Alan, I'll start with you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you very much as always for filling in for a host who is not here.
[SPEAKER_09]: Appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_09]: And now that the show is in your house, maybe you'll stop by once in a while and say hello.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, or when Loki's here, I'll just play, you know, on the TV the whole time and ignore the show entirely.
[SPEAKER_09]: When we get the video going, we can have you playing a game and, you know, kind of talk about that and we'll see.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: So do you have a final thought for our listeners tonight?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nothing to plug?
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_09]: My final thought tonight is I haven't had Hanson's soda in a while, but now that I'm having this delicious black cherry soda, I've kind of missed it.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, your final thought tonight I love reading the stories on unicornbooty.com
[SPEAKER_09]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, I have another final thought.
[SPEAKER_09]: Last night, New Year's Eve, we watched a lot of Adventure Time.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is that what it's called?
[SPEAKER_09]: Adventure Time?
[SPEAKER_09]: Adventure Time with Finn and Jake.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, that show is pretty fucking funny.
[SPEAKER_09]: I will say that.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a good show.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, that's it.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're done.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll be back next week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki will be back finally next week and we'll get his top three and plenty more gaming news.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, we're into a new year.
[SPEAKER_09]: The news is going to start to come out as we get into the first quarter releases and E3 in the summer.
[SPEAKER_09]: all towards another Clusterfucker releases in October, November of 2012 right before the world ends.
[SPEAKER_09]: Have a wonderful week everybody.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll see you next time here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Good night.
[SPEAKER_05]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_05]: To join us for a live show visit www.allgames.com Sunday nights at 6pm Pacific Time.
[SPEAKER_05]: or allgames.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: But we're probably right anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: See you next week!