Orange Lounge Radio
Who's the hosts?
Dark Sakura, Sky, and the Low Crew
Tonight, January 8th, 2012
Could the next Xbox also be a digital video recorder?
One retailer suggests a release date for Diablo 3
and rumors of new consoles in E3 2012 are already starting
Orange Lounge Radio
Hello my friends out there on the internet and welcome back
to another week of the show where every gamer has a voice
Orange Lounge Radio
We are live as we are every Sunday night at All Games Radio
www.allgames.com
6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern
right after the Bobby Black Wolf show
My name is Rob Roberts and I'll be joining you over the next few hours
with my co-hosts
First off, the one, the only, Dark Sakura, Jamie Summers
I really like salads
Salads are delicious
I just tossed mine
No
Into my mouth
Oh dear, that's not better actually
I know
Alright, also joining us tonight, say hello
Welcome back and welcome to Studio 6, Techmaster Loki
Hi
How are you doing?
Really wish you could have been here last week
It's alright, you had family stuff going on
Yeah, I had to go eat dinner at some
Yeah, well I had to go get free dinner
It sucks, my life sucks
Alright, chat.orangelaundry.com is the place to be if you are listening live
Of course, as I mentioned before, we are live every Sunday night
at 6 Pacific, 9 Eastern
right after the Bobby Black Wolf show
Tonight, episode number 441
January the 8th, 2012
So Loki, of course you were out last week
This is the first time you've ever been to my place, I was realizing
That's correct
Because you needed directions on how to get here
Yes
So welcome
I wish you could have seen it before we created a studio
out of what literally was nothing
It's pretty awesome
So, Dark Soccer might be able to remember, I don't know
But, anyhow
How have you been?
This table was loaded with paper
Yes, it was
It was the paper table
How have you been, Loki?
How was your holiday?
Did you have a good time off?
Yeah, it was alright
I mean, we just
Hung around the house for the most part
Just, you know, Josh got a lot of gifts
And, um
In times that he's not awake, I'm playing Skyrim
Very cool
I'm going to our chatroom at chat.orangelaungeradio.com
And somebody just joined the chat named
I love OLR
Well, we love you
I love OLR and chat says
Swotore, or as I've been calling it on the other show
Hoard House, Sweatore
Sweatore leveling, which is of course
The Old Republic, Star Wars
Plus, OLR in the background equals
Best Sunday night ever
I gotta admit, that's how I like to listen to live shows
I've tuned into some of the other all-game shows a few times
Like Dead Pixel Live, Video Game Outsiders
And I'll play WoW
Because I've only been playing Sweatore for about three weeks
But like, I'll play WoW and do PVP and listen to
You know, Video Game Outsiders or whatever
It's a good time
I remember when my friend was working on Knights of the Old Republic
And she was calling it Scrotore
You know, it would be awesome if you could do that on the Xbox 360
You know, stream stuff in
Like, you know, one of our live stations
He has the custom, you know, playlists
Didn't somebody create an app that did that some time ago?
I can't remember there was an app years ago
There was, it's the thing for downloading podcasts, sort of
TVercity, TVercity
Didn't that do it?
Well, that, that you can
You can stream stuff to your Xbox 360
But not in the background while you're playing stuff
I believe
I don't know
I don't know about that, maybe you can
I thought one of them did internet radio
Maybe you can do that with TVercity
I know, I just use it for videos
So I don't really, I've never messed with the music part of it
I know this would never ever happen
But wouldn't it be nice if AllGames.com
Could get one of those little channel things
That you could install and have
I mean, iHeartRadio, the Clear Channel thing has one
I mean, they have millions and billions of dollars
But AllGames totally has a 20 somewhere
Maybe in the couch
I mean, AllGames should be able to get that, right?
Anyhow
Let's see, Loki, we gotta do some catching up here
You were out last week, and last week was the big show
We were talking about our top games of 2011
Because we never really had a proper year-end show
Because of the way the holidays fell this year
And we all were speculating
What is Loki's top three games of 2011?
Hey, come on, it's gonna be super easy
Dark Soccer and I guessed
We actually, we already have a listener of mine
I think I remember, I remember three and one
Oh yeah, yeah, I think, I don't remember
Maybe one of the listeners will remind us in the chat room
What we had picked, but I don't wanna say
Because I don't wanna influence, so we'll wait
Loki, let's hear your top three games
So number three, what did you think was the third best game of 2011?
You know, I don't know, because I didn't play a lot of games
In 2011, sadly, because I just
I was really playing a lot of Grand Theft Auto the whole
Well, for the most part, up until recently
But that's not, that didn't come out in 2011
So that doesn't count
We did allow, it was, the criteria was
Your top game of the year
And that might not actually be a game that came out this year
Because so many good games come out at the end of 2010
Or in Alan's case, he put Dragon Age Origins as his number two game of the year
Because he just started playing it this year
And we said, okay, you're allowed
Every gamer gets their voice, even if it's a tardy voice
Well, that's tough, and I would say
I mean, Grand Theft Auto was pretty awesome
And, I mean, it was nice to be able to play the mods again
Briefly, until they patched it again
I would say probably my number three would be
Call of Duty Modern Warfare, I guess
All right, we called it
Did we call it? I think we did, yeah
Yeah, Modern Warfare
It's just fun now
And especially because, you know, the whole reason we switched to that game
Is because my co-workers were very pissed
Or tired of me beating them in Grand Theft Auto
And they're just like
They're just like, oh, we gotta switch it up, we gotta play a game
You know, my boss
Oh, I've played Call of Duty, you know
I think I should be a little bit better than Loki is at that
Unfortunately, what they found out
And, see, I didn't play a lot of Call of Duty at all
I mean, I've literally, before we started playing it
I'd played Call of Duty Modern Warfare 1 once
Once split screen, and that was it
And I didn't really care for it the first time we played it
But I ended up being really good at it, apparently
And a lot better than them
And they are pissed
Because it didn't help
And it's actually been a lot worse now
Because I'm so stealthy in that game
That I'll just sneak up behind them and do something funny
And they'll be like, hey, hey
And then kill them
Alright, so you like this game because you can own the shit out of everybody
It's pretty fun
It's actually, Call of Duty, at least the Modern Warfare games and stuff
I mean, they really cater that stuff
Especially the multiplayer portion
But they really have it down pat
And it's smooth, it works well
And it's just very fun and streamlined
It's good
That's not a series of games
I'm not really into the war games
I'm terrible at first person shooters unless it's called Quake
But you know what though
And I agree, playing it online
Like free for all deathmatch
Not very fun
Playing it team deathmatch online
That's a lot of fun
Well yeah, I watched
I didn't talk about this last week
But I actually watched over the holiday
We were with some of Alan's family
And some of his brothers were playing
Modern Warfare 3
And I was kind of watching them like, wow, it looks really good
And they were doing this interesting playback thing
Where he was showing us a video
Where his whole team hid in a bus
And the other team was looking for him everywhere
And couldn't find him
And it took him like 10 minutes or something
To find the team that was in the bus
Because this one guy inadvertently stood up
I get why people are into this
It's actually a pretty fun game
There's a lot of haters
A lot of hate for Modern Warfare
And I can't really speak for 2 and 3
Because I haven't played 2 and 3
So I don't know how much they've changed
But I can only imagine it's about as much as they've changed
From Call of Duty 2 to 3
Which wasn't a whole lot
It was just pretty much
They have the game and that's it
I know a lot of it's catered towards multiplayer nowadays
But you know what?
It's pretty fun
I like what they were talking about
That they were doing with the elite services
I can see where people would like that
But my whole thing before was
Just getting into online actually playing free for all death matches
And stuff
It doesn't seem very fun
And I've actually played it
And I don't know, there's still a lot of people cheating online
You run into a lot of people running infection mods
And stuff like that
But Team Deathmatch actually doesn't seem to be plagued with that crap
So it seems a lot more fun that way
And I actually do pretty well
Considering I'm ranked 5
That's pretty low
When you consider there's 11
Well, 11 prestigious
Or 10 prestigious
And you can level up again on 10th prestige
And 55 levels per
And people actually do level up
I'm not sure if everyone does it legitimately
So it's fun
Let's move on to your number 2 choice
Number 2, best game of 2011
It's tough because this game
A couple weeks ago
Might have been number 1
But it's not
Because it's kind of like
It's kind of like an actual person
Sort of, Elder Scrolls Skyrim
2 for 2, Dark Sakura
And the reason why
Elder Scrolls Skyrim is number 2
And not number 1
Is because the longer you play it
The worse it gets
And it's not necessarily that the game is getting worse
It's just it's getting buggier
It's just it took an arrow to the knee
It's seriously getting buggier and buggier
That meme needs to die right now
Right now
It needs to self inflict an arrow in its own knee
I want to know why there's no representing the love
For, there's a guy that says
He took a sword to the chest
Huh? I don't see any sword to the chest
Yeah, let me say arrow to the knees guy, you sound like a pussy
Sword to the chest?
You don't come back from that
He did apparently
So
Yeah, it's gotten progressively buggier
In fact I was complaining about it the other day on Facebook
Um
There's a quest I can't finish now because
The NPC for the quest is spawned under the map
And
I can't get to them
It's literally in a spot that is inaccessible
Alan got a pretty amazing bug this week
I should have him come on and explain it
I'm gonna butcher this
Hopefully he hears, oh here he comes, yeah
Alan hears me struggling
What kind of Skyrim bug you got this week?
So when I go to
Whiterun, which is the main city in the center
The first major city you go to
I'm not a criminal
I don't have a bounty
I could talk to guards, they're like, oh hey sup bro
Like you're orcish armor
I go into Dragon's Reach where the Jarl is
And right when I go up the stairs
The Jarl and his bodyguard are like
Oh shit, get him
And like the whole room agros
And I'm like, I'm dead, I didn't do anything
So I left
And I just did other shit for like 8 hours
And I went back
And it's fine
It's fine now, so I can use the enchanting table in there
But I was like, that was weird
Magically fixed itself, fantastic
I love this comment in our chat room
Zenthral says, the guy that invented that mem
The arrow to the knee thing, needs to take a sack to the chin
Okay
The arrow to the knee thing, yeah
We get it, the NPCs
Repeat themselves a lot
Hell, I mean all the shopkeeps say the same thing too
Some consider this trash
I consider them treasures
Well considering how fucking vast that game is though
I mean
I don't know
It's just
It's
It's getting incredibly buggy
And to the point where it's actually breaking the game
But I mean
It's still fun, I'm still playing
I had to kind of force myself not to play this week
So I can get some other stuff done
Because I have over 85 hours in the game now
And although I have exploited pretty much every glitch possible in the game
To level myself up to the point where I can't die anymore
And I kill everything in one hit
And it's still fun
And I can sneak up right to somebody in plain daylight
And be standing right in front of them and they can't see me
Which is kind of fun
But yeah, the fact that I can't finish that quest
That sucks, and the fact that sometimes
Parts of the land don't spawn
And I can't, you know, I fall through them
Or uh
Other fun stuff, oh
Sometimes when you kill a dragon or whatever
It'll do one more lap around the sky and then crash epically
You know, it's just like
Really? You have to do that
You can just die and fall to the ground
Alright, so despite all the crappy bugs
It's still your number two game of the year because
I played it a lot
And I'm still playing
Alright, your number one game of twenty
I mean, come on
Seriously, you gotta ask
What is your number one game of 2011?
Let's say it's World of the Third
Ah, three for three, right there
Actually, didn't we go back and say though
That Earth Defense Force was gonna end up number three?
Yeah, but then we allowed the old game rule
Yeah, alright
See, if it wasn't the old game rule
I probably would have been number three
Only by default because
They sucked
And Earth Defense Force, it was all right
It was pretty fun for a while, but man
It's pretty boring now
They promised, oh, we're gonna deal with this TLC
It's gonna be so fucking awesome
And nothing
Why Saints Row the Third?
It's such an over the top game
It's just incredibly fun
It was everything I wanted that game to be
And more
Honestly, I wanna finish it
And get all a thousand achievement points
But I just, once again, there's
A buggy portion of the game
And it happens to be kind of like the terrible part of it
Where you have to do these car jacking things
And steal certain cars
To unlock stuff
It's on their Saints book thing
It's just broken
And if it wasn't broken
I probably would be done with that
Well, with all the achievements at least
Sad there wasn't any competitive multiplayer in it
I mean, that's kinda lame
I do really wanna play the
Co-op in it
I think that would be pretty fun
I do have to play through it again now
As a woman so I can get the other achievements
And the DLC
I'm looking forward to it
Although I'm not too optimistic
On if it being really good
Cause the new, like from the achievements
That were leaked out for the
Upcoming stuff
It just sounds like a bunch of extra excursions
And some of it, I mean, that would probably be pretty fun
But, you know
The activities
It's cool doing them sometimes
But I don't like being forced to doing them
I would rather have some actual missions to the game
But it just sounds like it's all activities
So, we'll try it
I mean, it'll be alright
But I'm not gonna be one of those persons
And I haven't been
I'm not gonna be one to buy every single piece of download content
Just because I like the game
That's not how I'm gonna do it
Alright, so you're number one game of the year
Number three, and then you proceeded to slam each game
There it is, your top three
Of the year
Can you get, Dark Soccer and I
Have the same game as number one, can you guess?
The same game as number one
World of Warcraft?
No
Good guess though
Star Wars the old
No, I'm not playing that
I showed Dark Soccer it for five minutes
And she was like, I don't get it
No, I got it, I just didn't really care
Number one game
Better not be something like The Sims Social
No, God no
Think more, it'll be easier to guess her
Here's a clue
Oh, it's you
How have you been?
I've been really busy being dead
Oh my God, I forgot Portal 2
Fuck that, Call of Duty is out of this
See, that's what happens when that comes out way too early
Call of Duty, fuck it
Move them all back
Portal 2 number one, all the rest can be
Skyrim number three
Saints Row the Third
So there we go, so after
Some coercing, we finally get Loki to agree
So it's official, the official OLR game of 2011
Is Portal 2
I played through that game what, four times all the way through?
It's great
I completely forgot that that game came out
This year, and that's really bad
Because I think a lot of the
Game of the Year stuff, I mean a lot of people
Talked about Portal 2, but
I literally forgot that that came out this year
Well, and you know
I actually have that, oh, it's you
Memorized very well, because that's my
Message tone on my phone now
Yeah, so I mean, yeah, Portal 2
For sure
I completely forgot
I feel so bad
But seriously, where the fuck is
Where the fuck is some DLC for that?
They had some of the stuff on the PC
Any other guesses
What might have been on our list?
Technically
Um
Final Fantasy XIV
Hell to the no
That would be in like three biggest
Disappointments of the year
Super Mario 3D Land
You got it, it was my number three
Mario Kart 7
Arkham City was my number two
Arkham City was my number three
What was your number two? I forgot
Um
Hold on, I actually have
No, I
I'll have to check on my hard drive
Because I
Spazinator says the number one game was Singstar Abba
L-O-O-J-K
I know what my, um
Wrong, it's not Singstar Abba, it's Abba, you can dance
He was so hilarious playing that
No, but they also have Singstar Abba on the PS3
I know that
I remember that Tiara was in town when you got that
And we came and played it at the old house
But, um
I know what my honorable
Mention was, Fractal
Because that game is cool
Fractal is a really neat puzzler
Alright, oh Marvel vs. Capcom
Yeah, Marvel vs. Capcom
Ultimate Marvel vs. Capcom 3
It just hit me, all of a sudden
Alright, let's
Uh, quickly, our intro is running a little long
I wanted to just quickly say something about this
Because, Loki, you tweeted it to me
I've had listeners tweet me more stories
About this whole Xbox hacking stuff
And, god, we've been talking to our
Blue in the face about it since August
You know, if you don't know by now
Uh, I was hacked back in August
And people were saying, oh, you let
Your password get out, oh, you got phish
Microsoft's saying, oh, you got phish, I'm like, no
I'm a little smarter than that in the websites I visit
But, no, apparently it was my own damn fault
Well, now that more and more people are getting hacked
And more and more people are having problems with Microsoft
Finally, it's getting out there, some gal has set up a Tumblr
Where she was sharing her experiences
For some reason, it caught wildfire
And I think a lot of it is because
She had screen caps with Xbox support
She was screen capping the emails
And it gave a lot of the gaming press, I guess, for whatever reason
They're really, really bored
What really was taking me off this week
And you linked me an article from IGN
That literally said nothing
Literally said nothing, it said, yeah
Xbox is claiming that they're getting hacked
But, Microsoft says
They have no comment on the situation
So, you know
And apparently
This guy on this website
Was the first to break the news
A couple weeks ago, and it's like
That's kind of insulting
When we were here in August, talking about
I'm not saying we should, that's not what I'm saying
Because there were probably way other people
Before me, in fact I know people who were hacked
Before me
It's just irritating
That it's not news until it happens to somebody
Who has
Listen, just because a dude works in an office
For a company that makes a lot of money
Doesn't mean he's any better than any other blogger
I mean, there's a lot of really stupid ass posts
That are on a lot of major websites
IGN
Especially
That have not a lot of research in there
And, I mean, I think they got
The comment from, what is it
Steven Toulouse, or whatever his name is
Support, I don't know what the hell he is
Something that Xbox put
That customer service related
I'm not going to touch on Blowing the Fate
Go listen to that last show from 2011
Episode number four
How old night are we on tonight?
Go listen to 439
Would have been the last one from, we had Justin on
Who was talking about how he got
Broken into twice
Go, I mean, that's really all you need to hear
And I don't want to keep talking about this
But seriously, if you have not changed your password
At this point, do not
Microsoft is swearing up and down
That they're doing everything
They're being ignorant
That's really the only word
Microsoft is ignorant
EA is ignorant
The higher ups in those companies are ignorant
To the situation that's going on right now
Your money is at risk if your credit card is on your account
I have been sitting here telling you this
Blue in the face since August
Change your F and password, it's not that hard to do
Use a unique password on Xbox
That you don't use anywhere else
Put, like, put XB at the end of it
Or something, or put, you know
MS with a dollar sign
Just make something that differentiates it
For the record, neither of us have been hacked
It's, it's, the thing is though
Is, once again, they
Um, but
They're right, and they're wrong at the same time
I think Dan always paid with points cards
And also, hundreds and thousands
Of people have been, you know
And including people I know that haven't touched
Their Xboxes in forever
Well, I'm just saying it's safer to
Pay with points cards
The only card I have ever had on there
Was one that I knew was gonna expire in a month that I wasn't
Gonna renew
I would still change your password
You might have people in there downloading
What they can do, they can transfer
They might not charge anything, but what a lot of them
Have been doing, have they been logging
In and then downloading the licenses
To their local Xboxes
And basically siphoning all your games
Which can cause you headaches later on
I'm just saying
Well, I've checked all my licenses and they're still on mine
But I've also never had gold on my
Account either
Now, Microsoft's not
I wouldn't say they're ignorant
But what their statement is true
It's just, okay
Here's what it is
They're saying basically two things
One, Live.com has not been compromised
And two, that
People are being phished
And that's how their
Credentials are being
Leaked out or compromised
There's two things that are
I mean, yes, true
They are not
Live.com is not compromised
But people are not being phished
The whole thing was
All this stuff is coming from the hacks
That happened a while back and I even think it was
The anonymous stuff where they were dumping
A bunch of, and it might not even necessarily
Be them, but something similar to
The fact where they dump the email passwords
Combos
From random forums
Or even gaming websites or whatever
EA may have even been one of those, I don't know
I think EA is the weak link
And I've been saying this for forever
Why does every single hack seem to come back
To one of the EA games
And I get FIFA 12's gold pack thing
Where they're taking the cards and trading with other accounts
That whole thing, I get that
But why, if
All these accounts are being sold on a Polish
Website or all these accounts
Are being bought and sold on there
Why are they not selling accounts
With other games too
Why does it always come back to FIFA
Because FIFA is a popular game
In other countries
There's other popular games in other countries
Why is it always freaking FIFA
But the DLC for FIFA is a lot more
Expensive than buying a map pack for Call of Duty
Or something
Where there's smoke there's fire and it seems like
FIFA is the common thing between
All this, there's something about that game
Or EA servers that are allowing this to happen
EA sells a lot of garbage DLC
People buy it
And it's worth more
That's really what it's coming down to
But it doesn't matter
You should be using a unique password
And email combination
On Xbox
That's pretty much what
You have to do
Let's assume that even
Right now they're claiming
Phishing
What evidence do they have that there's actual phishing
Going on? They have no evidence
They're just making assumptions
Because all they know is
It's gotta be phishing
But what they should do is
Listen, hey, you know
I think I've seen one of them say that
Someone that was associated with
Xbox said, hey, you know
There were these hacks that happened
A lot of this email password
Combos got out
And what they're doing
In fact, Anonymous said to do this
When they leaked this crap out
Try it in Facebook, try it in Yahoo
Try it in Gmail, try it in Twitter
Use these login credentials
To get in access to other people's stuff
Because these people should be changing their accounts
Because these websites got hacked
So that's what it is
You need to change that stuff
Because if you use the same email
And password combination
Or even username password
For every single website that you visit
Then you're gonna
If someone gets one of those, they've got them all
Alright, so again
We've spent way too much time talking about this
In the past on the show
If you tweet me and say
My Xbox got hacked, I'm gonna tweet you back
And say, I'm really sorry to hear that
But I told you to change your password in August
Now if you tweet me back and say, I changed my password
Back in August, I really do want to hear those
Because then that would prove
Something fishy's going on
I'm not talking fishing
But if you haven't
Changed your password by now
I don't know what else to tell you
Like, the evidence is out there
It's growing
And finally, the mainstream press
Is coming around
And telling you to change your password too
So just do it
Even though Microsoft and EA and all of them are refusing to admit there's a problem
It's clear that there's a problem
Alright
Let's see
Moving on
I want to talk about our gaming weeks
And we always like to start off the show
Even when it's really 30 minutes into the show
Talking about what video games have you been playing this week
There's been things that you've been playing
DarkSakura, what have you been up to?
Well, I have been playing WoW
But I've been reading books
WoW books
And I was at Goodwill
Someone had the first two books of the War of the Ancients series
And I was like, I'm kind of a lore nerd
I'll read them
They're really well written
I mean, I can
A lot of books that you get that are tie-ins to series
Are kind of like, oh meh
These are actually really good books
And that's just reading it
You know, in between times
Really good books
I also
Played some Fractal
And I installed Bastion
I haven't played it yet
But it's really been Fractal and WoW
And we picked up DJ Hero 2 today
The girl installed the game
But she couldn't find the time
We got DJ Hero 2 today
The bundle set
For 20 bucks at Big Lots
So that's what tomorrow was
Woohoo bargaining
I know, right
And I've also been playing Scare Shermie
Which was
I finally figured out how to sneak up on Shermie
Vacuum something in front of her
She's too busy staring at it
In absolute horror
You can actually sneak up on her
And she'll jump
I think I saw a tweet
Or a chat comment or something earlier
That said, I miss Shermie
There are two cats here
In this studio, but they're afraid of people
They like to run and hide
So they're currently probably under my bed
Maruko loves me
Yeah, but they don't know Loki
And so they're probably like, who's that guy
Maruko was sitting next to me, cuddling
While I was reading
He walks around with his tail in the air, showing off his butt
Look at my butt
And
I was getting the occasional stink eye
From Sanrio
Yeah, mostly, and I was reading those books here
By the way, reading them here
And looking at your video games, seeing which ones I was gonna run off with
Not really
I was out of town, by the way, Disneyland
Mostly, it's just been
That we've still been arranging a lot of stuff from the move
So we haven't had
A significant amount of time
Also, the issues with my hand are getting worse again
So I can't really sit down
And play for very long
Alright, well Loki, how was your gaming week?
Well
This week I didn't really play much
Because I play Call of Duty at work
Which is fine
Like I said, my coworkers are trying
Multiple ways to get me to
Not be as good
Including, as of Friday
They taped a piece of cardboard
To my monitor with a few random holes poked in it
And of course, you know
Blocking about 90% of the monitor
I still managed to stealth kill
A few people with a knife doing that
But yeah, I could not aim and shoot
At anybody because there was nothing in the direct center
So it made it very difficult to
Try to actually shoot somebody
Um
And then, um
Let's see what else
Oh, and I played Skyrim
Earlier in the week
But I, you know, stopped
Playing it this week just so I could get some
Other stuff done because every time I'm like
Well, I could work on this, or I could play Skyrim
I want to play Skyrim
And
I started going through
Some of the Thief Guild stuff
I started a
Quest in Winterhold
And
It crashed
Well, the quest crashed because
Apparently if you do something out of order in that
Quest, it breaks
You know, something that would be very obvious
To anybody that tested the game
But I don't think anybody tested the game
Or there's too damn much to test
That's also probably part of the problem
There's too much damn stuff to test
But you would think that the first things they would test
Would be, I don't know, the quest from the game
I mean, obviously
They can't test
If you step on this rock over here
And you get launched into space
Or something like that, because there's a lot of
Landmass to go wander around and test
Every single random event that would happen
But I would think an actual quest
In the game
Um, it would be very obvious
That it's not working correctly
But I don't care
I don't have to finish that quest
I'm not a necessarily completionist in this case
But it's just still annoying though
That something like that would break
I mean, I don't mind if like
You know, a
A character gets trapped in a wall or something like that
Okay, I did mind that a little bit
And I had to reload a few times, but
It's just, it's getting to the point now
Where I'm actually starting to get the
Frame stutters and stuff like that
Like, it's stopping
Going, stopping, and going
And I have to stop moving for a second
For it to catch up
That's not good, that's the PS3 crap
That, you know, is going on right now
I think I might try to get back into some Skyrim this week
We'll see, because I've kind of, I'm a little
MMO'd out right now
But I'll get to my own week in a minute
Yes we do
That would make WoW more interesting
And I'm not really sure if we want to talk about it right now
But I've also, like I told you
That I've been, my coworkers
Have been finding ways to try to
Hinder my gameplay in Call of Duty
Let me set this up a little bit
Because this is one of the stories we didn't talk about
A lot last week, because it seemed like it was everywhere
And it's not really a story
It was really something that caught
Fire in a non-news
Week, I mean, yes, the
Guy was an idiot, but it was just
That guy got taken to the cleaners
It was just like, really? This is how bored
We are, but it's
Obviously we're talking about the ocean marketing thing
And the whole controller that they were promoting
Was the Avenger
Now, I think we can all separate the controller
From the situation
And this one guy with the ego
However, ironically enough
Loki had procured a copy
Of this controller
We've had one of these for months now
And was ready to review it on the show
When this all happened
So, Loki, go ahead, the Avenger controller now
Okay, the Avenger controller
It's basically, I mean
Different spins I've heard on it
One, yes, it's created by a guy
I think he was a teacher or something like that
And his reasoning behind it
Was, oh, I wanted to make
Something that made games a little bit
More accessible for
People with disabilities or something like that
Because he knew somebody that had trouble
With a range of motion or something like that
So they had
Issues reaching
The buttons or something
I don't know what the case may be
But that said, though, the way they're
Marketing it is not necessarily
You know, oh, this is for people
That have disabilities
Or, oh, yeah, and if you have disabilities
That would be good, too, but no
It's supposed to be something that actually
Decreases the amount of
Latency
Between your reaction
And hitting the buttons
And the way they do that is by putting these
Extra arms above
The
X, Y, and
B buttons
These arms reach out over
Behind the trigger and kind of
On the middle of your finger
For the B button as well
Am I doing this right? I'm holding this right now
You kind of lift up?
Yeah, you're supposed to lift up and it's supposed to hit the button
It's a little interesting
You can adjust those arms, too
Because that's adjusted for me right now
You're supposed to hit up
And then for the triggers now
You can see on the triggers
There's a rubber band thing that goes underneath the bottom
You're supposed to pull up on the bottom
With your finger to pull the trigger
Because the way they have it
It's tightened to the point now where
It's just to the point where
It's going to trigger the actual
Button
On the actual trigger
That's supposed to cut down
The amount of time it takes you
To
Press the trigger buttons
It doesn't make you better in games
Because you're hitting buttons faster
And your reaction time is faster
That's all good on paper
But it doesn't work that way, unfortunately
Because you have to retrain yourself
To play games
And it's actually very fucking awkward
To play with that
It was harder to play Call of Duty
And I gave it
I think I gave it a fair amount of time
I'd say a total of about
About five hours worth of gameplay
That I played during lunches
On Call of Duty with that
I played during our
Morning and afternoon
And deathmatch games and stuff like that
And I still was alright
But it was just a hassle
Especially trying to trigger certain buttons
And I don't really
I mean, Call of Duty
I don't think a lot of people really need to hit
The face buttons fast
Because it's like, reload
Yeah, okay, reload
Or like switching weapons or crouching
You don't really need that
I'm really curious, though, about the
So obviously you just find it awkward
And I gotta admit, when I'm holding it
I don't really play shooters, though
For me, this would not be an advantage
But accessibility is a big thing
About this dark soccer
I'm really curious what you think
Having your hand issues
It's really my first two fingers
And the things that
I really don't like all this crap on top of it
But I like the two extensions
On the triggers
And you see how there's a rubber bandy thing?
You can also tug on that
And that triggers it, too
But this actually is much more comfortable
To my finger because I don't have to
Have it up and put my hand in an awkward position
The whole problem I have with the triggers
Is that
I have to move my hand
Much higher up to reach them
And if I had something that
Would work for
The top two triggers instead of the back one
Like this long piece
It would be very comfortable for me
So like a half Avenger would be really good
For dark soccer?
Well, unfortunately, the part that you can take off the Avenger
Are the actual trigger buttons
I don't know what they call them, paddles
Or whatever the hell on the back there
Those are the things you can take off
If you don't like
Pulling on the actual skis
Or whatever the hell that's called
Derek H. in our chatroom at chat.orangesonshade.com
Says, Loki should tape three of his fingers together
To simulate how it is supposed to be used
So
Honestly, it's a waste of money
To be honest
I think I want one
My opinion is it's a waste of money
See, it's very, very interesting
So like for you
The normal controller doesn't bug you
But for her, she's like
Okay, now I can see maybe something that might
Let me play games a little longer
You should just give her yours
But here's the thing though
Jamie, you're having trouble hitting some of the
These would need to be adjusted
Okay, but the buttons that you have trouble
Hitting are the shoulder buttons, right?
Yeah
Okay, well they have controllers that have
Remappable buttons that would be on the bottom
Of the controller that you would hit with
One of your middle fingers
You drop Siri
On the
On this controller
It's just the problem is
$50 first off
For not a controller
They call it a controller, it's not a fucking controller
It's a piece of shit that attaches to a controller
If it were a controller, I would be able to take this off
And play with just this
And it would work just fine
$50 for that's a little steep
I mean, and really
I understand that there could be uses for it
As far as
People
Like they said right here
The rocker
They said players with larger or smaller hands
May utilize the rocker for added
Comfort
With smaller or larger hands
What's it meant for? I mean, I don't understand
Comes equipped with an
Optional stabilizing stand
Tension straps and trigger skis
These are called trigger skis apparently
And they suck, they do not work
I've tried pulling the trigger using this
It does not work, I mean
Really what would make the controller
In general better for me
Is just to extend the top to where the two triggers
Are further back
They have also these
Sticker things that I pulled off of here already
Because I'm planning on reselling this
Because it's a piece of shit
They had one that plucked
And that's the other thing too
You'll notice that there's actually the triggers for all the buttons
Except for the A button
You still have to move your thumb off of here
To push jump
And it's recessed because now there's this hunk of garbage
On top of the controller
To hit the A button
So their solution is there's a sticky pad
That you can put on top of there
So not worth the price at all
It's not worth the price
But maybe an accessibility thing
Maybe if you have issues
You might want to try one
Honestly I think it could be done better
If it's an accessibility thing I think it could be done better
And if you're having trouble hitting
If you want something that's gonna hit these
Face buttons or whatever
I'd recommend if you're playing Call of Duty
They had one either for Modern Warfare 2
Or Black Ops
They had a controller with two
It was from Mad Catz with two buttons on the bottom
That were mappable to either the
Left stick, right stick, or L3, R3
And then the four face buttons
And you can hit those buttons
On the bottom
Using, I guess it would be
Let me see here
It would be probably with your middle finger
To hit those buttons on the bottom
And that's actually not too bad
Because the comfort goes
So that would be my recommendation
And that, for 50 bucks, you actually get a controller
That you can use straight out of the box and go
This is $50
Plus you have to have a $60
Controller to plug it on top of
So it's $110
And I love their website
And this is another reason for me to hate G4
But I love their website
Because they have a bunch of different
Reviews on it
And one of them was from G4
This and the controller from Evil Controllers
Which is ironic because this controller
I have in here is a modded controller
From Evil Controllers
Yes, and they're fucking expensive
So I don't recommend buying them because it's not
You can get it way cheaper and stuff
But they're still nice
They're like
Their review
And this is Adam Sessler on fucking X-Play
Their review was
We don't like the Evil Controllers because
The rapid fire controller is cheating
Well if you guys like cheating then
That was their negative
Review for Evil Controllers
But we like this Avenger one because it's not cheating
That was the reason they liked it
So there's
Your educated
Review for that
Interesting side though, did you hear
G4 has a new president now
It has to do with the whole Comcast
G4 is a Comcast network and the whole
Comcast NBC thing that's happening
Interesting
Because
They were trying to pull
With a lot of the stuff
Well you know
The Avenger was
It was meant for people with
Disabilities and stuff and they tried to swing
That whole emotional like
I've got to feel sorry for them and stuff
They donated a child's play and stuff
Because of this whole bad PR and the fact that
They still haven't delivered these pieces of shit controllers
Yeah I got one of these months ago so they were done
They just haven't manufactured them
I mean it's fucking plastic
So I don't know why it's taking so long
And that's
And that's the way that they were marketing it
Except the problem is
It's not Avenger
The controller to allow
All gamers to play games
Including those with disabilities
Avenger! The ultimate gaming advantage
And no I'm sorry it's not an advantage
It's actually quite a disadvantage and I seriously
I would recommend
You know what if you're going to spend a lot of money on controllers
Buy a professionally modded controller
Or you know those actual
The Mad Catz ones and they have the
Ones for the major league gamers
Or whatever that actually looked pretty cool
And so I'd pick up one of the nicer
Controllers instead of a $50 piece of crap
Alright
That's enough clearly we know how you feel
About that Loki so that's enough
Alright I gave it a fair share I mean
I played for that for five hours and trust me
I did not want to play for that
You know long a time with that controller
Which is terrible
Alright my gaming week quickly I don't have a lot to really add
Because there hasn't really been any new games to come out
So it's been basically more
Sweat Tour, Star Wars The Old Republic
And Warcraft of course
Because that's every week
Randomly got an urge to play Super Mario World
Am I weird?
I have a Super Nintendo sitting right there in a Mario World cart
Yet I've been playing it on the Wii
I've been playing on the Wii with the classic controller
And I've been doing that because you can
Remember in Mario World you can only save after you beat
Like a ghost house or a fortress
But thanks to Wii save states
Not really save states but you can just kind of hit the home button
Anywhere and it remembers right where you're at
So that's pretty cool
Yeah so I've been playing that just old school
A little bit and finally tried PVP
In Sweat Tour
And it was actually really fun I love the commentators
Oh my god that part was really funny
As you're playing there's actually live commentators
Like you know oh they just killed
A guy on the frog pants team
They took him down it was just really funny
Is Greg Proops in there again?
No it's not Greg Proops
Such a missed opportunity I mean he's not doing anything
The frog knobs or something
I don't know the teams have funny names
What's he doing now he's like hosting some like
Some weird news on Yahoo
Or something like that I mean come on
The guy's not doing anything right now
No no no he's got his podcast it's great
Smartest man in the world I would endorse that podcast
I have to say I listened to it in Rob's car
He can squeeze out some more voice work
For a game come on
Come on just throw some money his way he'd do it
Alright um
Let's see so that was really my gaming week
We've been going on a long time
We gotta get into housekeeping real real quick
Now I have to admit I'm changing my tone
Here a little bit because I was about to come on here
And really point the finger and shake it
At the listeners because we have not had a lot
Of people signing up for the big battle
Over at thebigbattle.net
Where they are doing Super Street Fighter 4
Arcade edition
Ultimate Mortal Kombat 3
Fighter 3
And Mortal Kombat the new one Mortal Kombat 9
They are doing competitions these are all on Xbox 360
You know fighting game
Competitions and up until the show
Started there was only two people signed
Up two representing OLR
Myself and Tiger Claw thank you Tiger Claw
However I just reloaded the site and I did
Notice a couple more have signed up
For Super Street Fighter 4 I see Vid Power
And Sponge Twang have signed up to represent
OLR so I'm feeling a little better
But if you guys want to make me really happy
This is and you can't
Procrastinate in fact for podcast it's too
Late you can't register for this anymore
But those of you guys listening live this is literally
Your last chance because today is the last
Day and I posted the link there
In our chat room you can go sign up on the forums
To participate and represent
OLR you don't have to be good at these games
Just represent OLR just you know
Do your best because I
Signed up for Ultimate Mortal Kombat 3 which is the
Only game I have on 360 out of these
And I am prepared to get my ass handed to me
Although I will try I will put up a fight
Literally
So go sign up there on the forums and represent
OLR there's tons and tons of
Shows participating in this now and not just all games
People now there's like Twitch TV communities
Martini Gaming the Unfocused
Podcast there's lots of people
Participating in this so check that out
At TheBigBattle.net but you got to do it tonight
Sunday sorry podcast listeners
You had your chance last week we even had
Derek on and everything was talking about it and you had your
Chance so hopefully
You guys will be signing up
And kicking some butt on behalf of
OLR alright
Let's see moving
On I guess that's it
We'll get into some news I'll just quickly say follow us
On Facebook facebook.com slash orange
Launch radio and we're also on Twitter twitter.com
Slash OLR
Alright let's get into
Tonight's news Loki why don't you start
Us off alright let's talk a little
Bit about Atari
And some of their
I guess witch hunts
Over
Infringing
IOS games apparently they're going after
Everybody that has games that look like theirs
And whether that you know they're just
A blatant rip off of like say
Asteroids or Breakout or something like that
Or if it just happens to be you know
A tank game with vector tanks you know
In fact
One indie app creator
Black Powder Media
They have a game
That's been pulled
Off of the
App store because of
Claims from Atari of
Copyright infringement of course their game
Is very similar I guess it looks
Similar to Battlezone
Vector tanks is the game
And apparently
They're going after everybody
And you know Atari
You know release the same instance
For companies like Atari our intellectual property
Portfolio is our
Most valued asset
While we have a great respect for any
Development community and greatly appreciate
The enthusiasm that they have for
Our renowned properties we need to vigorously
Protect our intellectual property
And ensure that it's represented
In a highly innovative
Represent highly innovative
Games okay well I gotta stop I'm right there
Highly innovative games I'm sorry
Your remake of centipede
What is it the last the one that came out
In the fall
Last year it's terrible
And not innovative in the least and
What test drive Ferrari
That's innovative to the you know test
Drive franchise I'm sorry
That's not true this is a
Slippery slope though because like I
I want to say okay yeah I
Get it we see these knockoff games
On the iOS devices and especially
Android stuff all the time but
Where do you draw the line because if you think
About it couldn't any
Shoot them up game any
First person shooter couldn't anything
Come back to combat
If you really think about it
Well like see I have a problem with
The fact that you know okay it's a vector
Game that has tanks in it I'm sorry
But even I think in the arcades they had
More than just battle zone I remember
I remember an awesome
PC game awesome awesome PC
Game called specter that was
Like a vector tank game but it was
It was not I mean
It was not battle zone like
It was a step I remember the big thing about it
Is you could do modem play and all this stuff which was huge
You know when I was growing up and the whole reason
They're doing this of course is because
Because they have their own games that they're
Releasing on the iOS marketplace
And that's what it really comes down to I think
Is that they just want to release it and
Actually get some money for it but
I mean let's be
Serious here you know like Arkanoid
And stuff like that I mean which Arkanoid isn't really
There's actually was it Breakout
Taito was
But Breakout I mean that's
Pretty much like Arkanoid
Well Arkanoid is just a souped up
Version of Breakout if you will
It's got the falling things that you pick up
That change the paddle
I would say that that's more of like a genre
Of games now less
Of a you know because
It kind of goes back to saying well
You know there's fighting games
And they're all clones of Street Fighter
Well it's a genre now
It's not necessarily yeah a lot of
Stuff you know is inspired by
Or is a clone of something and then they
Kind of throw their own unique spin on it and there's
That or there's the
Games that are on the iOS a lot
Of games out there that there's guys
Trying to make a quick buck and they put some with the Angry Birds
Characters they literally rip the assets
From the game and then they create something else
Or you know something that's like it's
Angry cats and then there's dogs or something
Or you just you know to the point where
That's a rip off don't the masses
Kind of know how to tell a cheap rip
Off though well the masses do but see
It reminds me of those
CDs they sell at Target for like
$5 that are like you know
Top 40 hits and all it is it's like
Really bad cover songs
Of the stuff that's on the radio right now
But like a lot of it
Though it's kind of like
One of those things you they have to try to
Protect their rights or they lose their rights
You know it so they kind
Of have to do this but at the same time
I think the reason they're doing this is because they're putting games
Up on the iOS you know platform
That you know
I mean they recently released updated
Versions of Breakout and Asteroids
So I mean maybe that's why
They're doing it but
I mean okay
I can't fault them for trying to do that
And let's be honest there's a lot of shit
On the app store that's
Fucking just ripping off
All sorts of shit I mean there's a ton
Of rip off games out there
And there's a ton of games inspired by
Stuff like I would say Vector Tanks
Is probably
Somewhat you know
Original game I mean yeah
It's inspired by the old vector graphics
And maybe inspired by Battlezone but it's not
Like they're not calling it Tank Zone
And you know it has you know basically
All the same gameplay as Battlezone
I just
I don't know I think that
They should be going out through the right people but they're
Going out through everybody instead
And at the same time why aren't the people there
Making the Mario games and shit like that
You know getting that stuff taken down
To turn this a 180
A little bit this is what really worries
Me about SOPA and that whole thing
And why you know people are really scared
Because if you allow corporations
To kind of draw the line they're gonna draw
It too far in the sand one way
Oh they're gonna take out everything
It's gonna be crazy
If something like that actually passes
You know I mean and all this
Stuff that we see is just evidence of that
Because Atari may overreach
In trying to protect
Their stuff and who's to say
You know other companies do you trust
A lot of these companies to draw the line
Of course and here's
A funny thing too like say for example
I make a game or something that's pretty
Original and I release it out there
And Atari goes
And I consider ripping
Off some of my ideas
Or something like that and that's not necessarily because they do that
This game is too much like Custer's Revenge
That Loki made and so
We have the rights to this game
Even though it was really a third party
Let's say for example
Here's an example that's not necessarily accurate
But
Was it the ferret tossing game
Let's just say the ferret tossing game comes out
And it's too much like
Defender with the whole
Scrolling left and right
Too much like Defender or okay
That's a bad example let's just say
Say I release the game out there
And all of a sudden you know Atari comes out
Or not even necessarily Atari just some company
Comes out and you know a major
Company and puts out a game
On iOS or something like that it's very
Similar to my game like as far as all the
Original aspects of that game it's very
Similar to that I myself
Go to Apple and say hey I want
You to take this down are they gonna
Do it probably not because this
Major company that you know has a
Lot more money invested into the app
Store than I do and they're just probably gonna
Ignore what I say yet if
Apple comes and says hey we don't like
Ferret tossing or whatever like that
Even though it
Vaguely resembles something that they may have done
They will take it down without
Who's gonna know where to draw the line
Nobody is that
Do you trust the government to draw the line
Do you think senators
And all them play video games
I think one senator came out and said
Well a lot of my staff does play Mortal Combat
Like that was the most
Video game keen thing I've ever heard
No it was a
Justice it was that
Court case about the
ESA versus
The California law and all that that's where that
Came out well I think you know to be honest I have
A problem with you know if a lot of the
People in government that
They don't play games I mean honestly
That's
I understand that not everybody
Plays games out there but I would
I would assume nowadays that the vast majority
Of the populace plays games in some
Form or another not necessarily console
Games but at least on the internet you know the
Occasional
Phone game or something like that
And if these people representing us
Don't have any fucking clue about
What's going on out there
They just don't care they'd be like well I don't
Watch TV so why should I protect the rights of the
People that want to watch TV I mean
That's just not good
We need to get these people out
Anyhow tangent sorry about that but it's
Important it's kind of stuff that's going on
Right now anyhow
Kind of going in a completely different direction here
We mentioned earlier in the show that it
Is kind of a slow release period there's not a lot
Of games coming out until closer to the end of the month
Of course you know Final Fantasy 13 2
It's slow release like B12
Yes but one game
If a certain Best Buy store
Is to be believed might just come out of nowhere
And steal the spotlight for this first quarter and that's
Diablo 3 according
To Best Buy
And this is again to be fair
It's not the whole damn corporation it's one store
That apparently was in Minnesota
Where the Twitter user was
That had a standee that said Diablo 3
Midnight opening available for
Purchase 1201 AM on February
1st as the launch day and
February by the way was spelled wrong
Well there's been this whole
Was it missing an R? There's this whole back
F-E-B-U-R
Instead of R-U
February yeah which granted
February's a tricky word is probably one of the more
Common misspelled words but still
Clearly not an official Blizzard
Product if that's the case
Now there was this whole back and forth that went on
A UK retailer
Kind of clarified the date too
And showed a February 3rd date
And then there was this whole
Other back and forth where the Best Buy
Was actually called by the gaming
Press and that the sign was
Actually taken down and then
Bashyok one of the community
Managers over at Blizzard actually said on
Twitter lol
We can't stop shops from doing whatever they want
To do I'm paraphrasing here
But retailers will find out when the rest of you do
Basically when it's in an official
Press release but certainly there's a lot of back
And forth going on about the release date
Loki you're on the inside a little bit
You're shaking your head over there and then there's
Micah Whipple
That's Bashyok
No they have not announced an official date yet
You'll know when they do
And I said this on Hoard House
I truly think
First off if they're going to street date something it's going to be on a Tuesday
And not a Wednesday
It's going to be March 27th
The very last day of the quarter that they could do it
I said
I firmly believe that
Because at this point with all the auction house back and forth that's been going on
And that beta is still going
They're going to want plenty of time for people
To be able to pre-order
Get those in and it's going to be carefully
Timed with the Blizzard blood pact
For Warcraft and the fact that
You're going to have these
Probably a million people getting it for free
Because they're committed to WoW
And they're going to drop it at a time where
It's going to distract them from WoW
Because nothing is going on in WoW
So I think end of March is reasonable
And they're also going to be starting
Their marketing campaign which will be massive
And so
One month lead time is not enough
So you will be
You'll bet your ass that
And know about it way before it comes out
Guys, you know in our chatroom at chat.orangelandradio.com
Says, why do we have
All this secret release date stuff?
Just tell people, it's silly
It's not secret, it's the fact that it's not done yet
It's, Diablo 3 is fucking done
It's fucking done and the problem is
It has to do with the whole, it's the auction house thing
That's getting tied up in Korea is part of it
And now they're using this as an excuse
To put more into the game
Which is yet to be revealed
But I think a lot of this is to
Make sure that legally that auction house thing
Gets clearance in all the countries
I honestly believe that, I think this game should have been out
Last year and I think they were going to announce it
At Blizzcon for a December release
And change their tune when Korea happened
So, we'll see
Virtual M in our chatroom says
The website does list it as February 1st
If you go to bestbuy.com
But placeholder dates are super common, right?
It's probably, if I remember correctly
The last update we got from them
Was Q1 2012
And that's kind of an
You just place a placeholder date
Usually, like, I used to put it on a weird date
Like a Saturday or something like that in our system
So that, you know, I know it's a placeholder date
But yeah, there's no date for it yet
In fact, from
Yeah, I'm
I'm 100% sure there's not an official date for it yet
Although I haven't gotten an update from Activision in a while
So probably next time I get it, you know
Well, rumors are it could
The release, the news of a release date
Could be coming out
Next week, as early as next week
But I think a lot of that's wishful thinking
On the community and how sometimes
That snowballs into, oh, this is news now
So, we'll see
Probably what it was is a store jumped a gun
And they built some, you know
POP for the store
And plus, if, and Virtual M says
The website lists it as this
That's actually, Virtual M probably just explained
Where the issue came from
Best Buy didn't get that date from
From Blizzard
They got it from themselves
Probably in their own system
And the store manager was like, oh, we gotta make sales for this
Let's get a sign made up
And we're gonna push more sales of this
And it's February 1st in our system right here
Props to them for being, you know
Way to take initiative, but at the same time
You need to spell
Alright
Let's move on to Dark Soccer
With some other gaming news
This is not a rumor
Not a rumor
It's about
Kaz Harai
Guess what? He's being promoted
To president of Sony
That was actually put up by Nikkei
By the Japanese Stock Exchange
He's going to be replacing
Howard Stringer
The theory is
By April
It should be going on, but they have to finish everything
Through a board meeting
And Stringer is staying on as
The chairman and CEO
Yeah, we get a lot more
Ridge Racer and
Giant Enemy Crafts
But man
Sony's kind of in
Relatively crappy shape
Well, first off
Let me play this and then we'll come back
In honor of Kaz Harai ascending to the throne
At the top of Sony
I think we have to play our very favorite clip
From 2006
Please welcome Kaz Harai
Ridge Racer
The essence of the PlayStation DNA
Is real change
And the consumers are ready
Genji 2
Is an Ashen game
Which is based on Japanese history
Ridge Racer
Being based on history
The stages of the game
Will also be based on famous battles
Which actually took place
In ancient Japan
So here's this giant enemy crab
Ridge Racer
And you
Attack its weak point
For massive damage
It's Ridge Racer
Ridge Racer
PlayStation 3 will retail for
$599
Giant Enemy Crab
It's Ridge Racer
Ridge Racer
Don't forget old. That's Makah45
On YouTube by the way
That has that clip up there
I gotta, I gotta put this out there though
There's actually a reason why
I play that clip
Because it does tie in all this
It's not on the show role tonight
But this story makes me think about
How there's all of those news about the Vita
Over in Japan
is exhibitionally not doing well
Like to the point, this was on Yahoo.News
Where I saw this, so we're
pretty, you know, mainstream site
they're saying the Vita is bombing because the PSP outsold it in Japan last
week so in other words that's pretty bad they sold more PSP's last week and they
have the sales numbers to back it up that doesn't bode well for the Vita
however look at that clip this is just history repeating itself all over again
isn't it well it's too expensive the games are you know well you know hit
miss I gotta well I gotta give them credit there is a lot of interesting
stuff and I think a lot of people are really turned off by the price right now
and in some ways I kind of see history repeating itself here I don't think I
would write off the Vita as a horrific failure yet I mean it hasn't launched
here in the US for one I don't know if it's gonna I think it'll sell more than
PSP's do in the same week but I yeah I there's nothing I but I think the 3ds
is gonna stare is nothing coming out for the PSP nothing I mean okay one game but
it's it's a visual novel if I can also point out something last fiscal quarter
Sony lost 1.6 billion yen which is about 20 million dollars or 13 million pounds
so I mean I but but in my age well you never know like the PlayStation 3
everybody gave it shit in the beginning everybody gave it shit but it's come a
long way and right now you know especially with everything we were
saying with Microsoft at the top of the show PlayStation 3 is it's a pretty good
system right now you know it really depends on the games you want the
exclusives and all that but it's it's a worthy competitor the Xbox 360 I don't
think anybody would have said that in 2006 and honestly I think we're like the
3ds and stuff I don't see them squeezing out a lot more power out of that system
then the stuff that's out right now I mean sure there's gonna be some games
that look pretty nice and can do a little bit more but if 3d is all they
got I mean if you don't like the 3d you got a DS I mean that's pretty much it
I'm not being a defenseless or a defensive or whatever or being a fanboy
but I am saying hold on a minute because you know although I will great yes that
looks very bad that the PSP was out selling the Vita but didn't I could be
wrong but didn't the same thing happen with 3ds at first where eventually a
couple months later the older DS was we're out selling the 3ds and now look
where the 3ds is yeah I mean all it took was a few powerhouse games and now that
nobody's joking about the 3ds everybody's like within a matter of months
everybody's like okay yeah 3ds here to stay I mean no happening no one's
arguing that the fact that the 3d the 3ds launch versus the Vita launch I
mean the launch games are way better on the Vita there's actually stuff that
people would like on there I'm probably not gonna get one at launch because it
is too damn expensive and honestly I I don't I don't play my 3ds enough I mean
fuck I've only played Super Mario 3d land once and I'm not gonna buy a new
system game guru in our chat room says well yeah 3ds stole Monster Hunter which
is what everyone bought the PSP for in Japan so you know that those few key
games can really sell a system I mean you cannot deny that Mario 3d land and
Mario Kart 7 is the reason why 3ds nobody's you know joking about it
anymore and Monster Hunter in Japan certainly mm-hmm you know so anyhow all
right so cause her I I mean it'll these things happen you know but don't buy
Ridge Racer do not buy Ridge Racer for the Vita if you're going to buy a game
for the Vita I seriously if you're trying to buy a cheap game if you're
looking to buy a cheap game from Namco by touch my katamari because that's 30
bucks and you get a full game versus 30 bucks and get three tracks and five cars
all my eyes and chat says but Sony doesn't have a system seller like Mario
or Mario Kart they do have uncharted which is pretty big deal over here they
have uncharted they have wiped out if you like wipe out they have well hot
shots golf actually did pretty well in Japan it's not right I won't wipe out on
the same level as Mario Kart I really wouldn't it's not at launch but well
they have Modination Racers that's a launch title but that on the same level
as Mario Kart I'm like Sony's big within our God of War uncharted well within a
month a little big planet that that'll be big yeah luminous for me and and
third-party games luminous I don't see as a launch sales well I haven't gotten
Ubisoft updates yet but I haven't seen any there to launch stuff but in third
party stuff I mean you've got ninja Ninja Gaiden Sigma I mean that's a
pretty hardcore game ultimate Marvel vs. Capcom 3 blaze blue extent or blaze blue
continuum shift extent there's the MMA game from 505 supremacy MMA I know
there's a FIFA game and you know Ridge Racer touch my katamari which looks
pretty good there's a lot of good games it's it's not like where huh well let's
see there's Nintendogs and a submarine game oh and pilot wings steel diver all
right Rama in our chat says if Sony knocked the price of the Vita down to
$1.99 they wouldn't need a system seller per se that maybe losing a lot of money
yeah that's I guess that's true but don't isn't it common to lose money on
systems you make it back up with the games yes the Vita the Vita does have a
lot that's not just games that's another thing you know it does have strengths in
just like the PSP had the web browser had the mp3s people call into the show
on their PSPs I mean you know let's see ah my eyes agree is true if they knock
the price down to $1.99 I would buy it and Yuki follows it up with same so the
price is yeah they're not gonna lose $100 in every system I mean that's just
stupid I mean it's stupid but at the same time I think it's fucking retarded
that I've got to buy another memory card that doesn't come with the system I mean
help the original PSP I think came with a 32 megabyte memory card I agree that
if they wanted to get they would put a small memory card in yeah like I really
need to even half not even half a gig but like let's do a 1 gig card I mean
those things cannot be the price to manufacture that they're charging I
don't think they would be taking a big loss by throwing one in and I think
they were really sweet in the pot because I sir I kid you not every single
one of those games requires a memory card and so here's here's a fun
situation I go buy a Vita and they're sold out of memory cards fuck I can't
play anything all right we got to move on we're running long in part a let's
move on with some more news Loki it's just like a great plan right there I
guess what apparently there's some insiders that say that there's going to
be the new unveiling of a new Xbox and new PlayStation this e3 and they
apparently have it from a very very very very very very very very reliable source
and this is MCV reporting this as well that both of their these new consoles
boom will be making their debut at e3 I'm not surprised I'm not sure if
obviously though that doesn't necessarily mean they're gonna be out
this year or even next year I mean it could be I could see him coming out
maybe fall next year I call bull on this story because I I would believe the Xbox
I I think it's about time for the Xbox to show off their next console but I
don't think PlayStation 4 I don't think we need it yet I feel like PlayStation
3 took so long to get to its prime I I almost kind of believed the whole 10
year cycle thing I think I think PlayStation 4 coming out this this soon
is showing it this year I don't know I I Rob I think it's it's a Vita they've
got to push the Vita they've got to push that through the holiday you don't
understand though Rob a 10-year cycle doesn't necessarily mean that boom after
10 years they would launch a new console it means that they launch a new console
and it overlaps for three years I just III in my gut you know just says they
either can't be the PlayStation 4 this early it's just too damn early for the
PlayStation 4 it's a reliable source so it's so reliable the stories in the
reliability I mean it's so reliable I want to get their quote because it was
it was hilarious
ah nope don't have the quote oh well there's one guy's like I can guarantee
it a hundred percent it's gonna be there you know it's gonna be there the Wii U
and my disappointment actually you know what I'd be interested easy with this
what's gonna happen next week during you know the whole cuz CES stuff CES is
never really gaming I mean well no it was gonna be there with the Wii U yeah
but they swear up and down it's just the same the exact same thing they showed at
e3 for people who weren't able to wait in that horrifically long line yeah and
I don't think they need to I mean CES really isn't a gaming show what the
biggest game news I can think of that ever came out of CES was the Microsoft
Game Room was a big thing that came out it and unfortunately Microsoft Game Room
didn't last which is such don't get me on that game room had so much freaking
potential and now it's like ruined it for everything else like I'm just I'm so
mad about game room because it could have been so much more awesome and
really should have been but anyway no I think I think the big things Windows 8
you know you'll see more stuff about PC and in bigger TVs and 3d TVs and all
that I don't I don't think it's a lot about gaming consoles you might see
little things especially from Microsoft and the 360 because they're really
trying to make the 360 this whole like centerpiece I think they're gonna be
showing off some new channels and if you want to take a total shot in the dark
maybe something akin to the one versus 100 thing getting out some type of some
type of entertainment channel how you dig into those channels because I've
stopped downloading them because I just don't give a shit about them anymore
they're they're kind of pointless I hate to say it the only one I could ever see
myself using is that maybe I would use I heart radio if I was hosting a party
because there are some decent stations on there with very few commercials some
of the HD simulcasts you know that play like dance music or comedy on loop it's
kind of like having the satellite radio that's the one that I'm kind of like I
could see myself using this but the rest not really I don't know it that whole I
don't like the new interface to be honest it's just oh yeah I hate the
interface but that doesn't mean I don't like the point of some of the channels
and the Netflix channel certainly although actually I I find it better on
my ps3 so I used to think now the other we have the technology where we could I
don't know select the interface we want thought maybe hmm I'll be nice we have
the technology we can select it all right well speaking of rumors there are
some rumors about the really good Fleetwood Mac album there are some
rumors about the Xbox lube because remember that's what we're calling it
now if you don't know why we're calling the new Xbox system the Xbox lube you
have to go back and listen to some old episodes but apparently the Xbox lube is
supposed to be this sounds really slick it's supposed to be a DVR as well okay
that makes it worthwhile this is according to some patents that are
floating around out there that apparently on December 27th the US
patent office gave Microsoft a patent for a device that would be a game
console and a DVR a digital video recorder application running alongside a
television client component allows users to record media content on the gaming
console the DVR application also integrates itself with the console menu
once integrated users can record media content while playing games
alternatively users can record content when the gaming console is turned off
the recorded content can include television programming gaming experience
whether local or online interesting music DVDs and so on when in the
recording state users can also switch between various other media modes whether
gaming television and so on I would rather I think this would be more
something that would be integrated into a television set or integrated into a
Cosep top box that would be from a cable provider here's my other thing I mean
although I could certainly see this being feasible for the next system why
does it have to be the next system isn't it feasible they could release a 360
that has a DVR built in they could do that but I mean I think that by saying
it's in their next thing that makes it a selling point true true I mean it is the
kind of the big a big thing but I that's the type of thing really how well did
HD player hypothetically let's say it was in the 360 that I could see coming
out of CES but here's I think dark soccer it's gonna be the next it's never
I'm telling you it's never gonna happen on its own it's gonna be something from
a cable provider because why are they the cable providers are hey we're
providing content to you and you're gonna offer a DVR so now we can't charge
people that fee the cost to rent the DVR system out you know and and they don't
have to buy our you know our higher tier programs to get a you know DVR you're
gonna pull this shit on us fuck that we want some of that money so that's not
gonna happen they're gonna put that shit out themselves and it's gonna be kind of
like hey you can get Comcast and you get a game player as well you know a Comcast
box and you get games and you can do all this stuff or it's gonna be integrated
into a TV you know something like that because I'm telling you they're not
gonna I mean I I would love it it'd be great you know if we could have a DVR
because then I can DVR shit without having to pay my cable writer to do it
but I just don't see that happening it's kind of a pipe dream I mean there's
Divix or not Divix there's TiVo but you know who fuck uses TiVo anymore yeah you
got some support in chat room Loki a lot of folks agree with you Derek H says
Loki is correct I think he's saying it about this I don't know because of the
delay there's like a minute delay but Rama in the chat says the console is a
DVR will cause a problem because cable providers will not support it you're
right there are cable providers in agreement with Xbox Comcast our local one
is supposed to come on board in early 2012 because if you think about that
will be shown at CES for sure like if I can if I can DVR like whatever I can DVR
X show or whatever you know it can do like let's just say I can set it up like
a TV you know like I can set it up okay I want to record season of this why would
I buy the content off of their service I mean because I already DVR did I mean
they're losing sales that way they're not gonna do that I mean come on they're
gonna lock that shit out and so it's gonna either come from them or it's
gonna cost something to you know do that yeah I'm I could see where it's gonna
cost Microsoft points to DVR stuff you know it well and I wouldn't say it's
necessarily in costume to do so maybe you need a membership or something I
don't even know if you need members it's got to come from the cable provider it's
it's seriously that's something that would be like okay because now they have
these partnerships with these cable companies and stuff where you can do all
this on the man crap it's got to be something that's coming from them like a
new set top box what if it just worked with over-the-air TV though I mean
remember you can hook an antenna to your TV and these magical channels and it
works fantastic I can tune in zero channel it depends on where you live in
your connection it's it's terrible I need like a big old retro in order well
no they don't look like that anymore now they're like square they're I mean
seriously I I tried to hooking one up to I was like yeah I'm gonna put this up
I'm gonna get on my HDTV for free it worked like crap I got nothing not even
a Spanish channel that came in correctly although when I was programming it
actually got worse every time I tried to find stations all right listen I
actually have to say to be perfectly honest I have no use for DVR I don't
watch TV Dan doesn't watch TV everything that we watch is streamed I was to say
BBC America maybe I Supernatural on CW I download my shows on the internet
because I hate commercials mm-hmm and besides that you know the commercials
are what provide your free television I don't watch the TV I mean Dan the only
shows that he watches is like Sons of Anarchy and Top Gear and guess what he
streams them from other places we were I mean we're paying for cable we rarely
use we'd actually downgraded our TV cable and upgraded our internet cable
see I'm thinking about it but then then that'll be when the next season of
RuPaul's Drag Race starts it's like I gotta have logo I can't wait till the
next day gotta have it you could well I cannot sashay away my cable is that by
the time it airs at its normal time someone's already uploaded it from an
eat from the East Coast showing I got friends that'll spoil Drag Race so then
five minutes of it airing on my Facebook anyhow all right I'll just let's move on
with some more news Dark Sakura I'm not a hipster I'm just hip anyway so media
molecule is spending a lot of money and it's on new stuff they're actually
trying to innovate wait it's not LittleBigPlanet 3 they basically they're
trying not to rely on LittleBigPlanet as their primary you know safety net if if
you will they are trying to actually expand into different audiences so
they've been spending about and this is from a British news source they're
spending about three point forty four million pounds well that's how much
profit that they made in 2011 but they're spending four point one million
on research and development so they're keep trying to put their resources into
new kinds of games to keep innovating so that they don't have to just rely on
LittleBigPlanet to keep them around because I mean I think it's really smart
too because you know say that you've got a company that's good for just one thing
and that's all they've been doing but after a while the franchise is stale
because I honestly think LittleBigPlanet before too long is gonna hit that place
where people are gonna expect the same thing and there's not gonna be able to
pay but for them to put much new into it I think a big problem is it's it's more
I mean LittleBigPlanet is really a limitless game there's so much you can
do with it but I think it's the saturation that's gonna be an issue and
that's not really on media molecule but it's like you know you have your PSP
version and your Vita version and you're you know it's it's coming out on
everything well here's a quote on here they say that their investments are
going into and this is the quote leading edge physics and dynamics rapid world
creation from laser data innovative routes to marketing no to market via
web-based interfaces 3d stereo optics for advanced simulation and use of high
def data capture and processing techniques hmm so it looks like just
from what I can seeing on here they're trying to branch out but try to work on
stuff it sounds like they're really working on immersion they're making the
holodeck basically they are making a holiday at clay station holodeck they're
trying to make it where I think it's not just they're extending to immerse but
they're actually trying to draw in your feedback into the game to make it
customizable into whatever they're working on Derek H in our chat room at
chat dot orange laundry calm says 1.5 million to find new games come on that's
just another way to write hookers and blow I don't think so perhaps you know
that's just kind of I would buy a game hookers and blow which especially if
it's that whole 3d immersive experience like you know you see her nose that's
about to snort the cocaine just jumping right out of the TV I want man horse
then you need to play Saints for the third all right somebody would lend it
to me alright I could play it I just lazy let's move on and travel the world
with some release dates and Loki start us off with the u.s. although I don't
like last week there was literally nothing so I don't know if this week's
the same thing but uh yeah there's pretty much nothing um this week there
is well not much I believe my pet puppy 3d from five five games I want to say
that I got laid I can't honestly well here I will get you the definitive list
here okay but yeah I seriously it was like nothing I think was actually this
week we had like three releases of some UMD games hmm there were from well that
was actually like this week but um let's see coming out this week ah yes there is
pretty much nothing so let's start off with four and one action pack from South
Beach games it's four games that were featured on the PlayStation Network and
they're all terrible including mushroom wars digger wave wave was it a
smash cars and wakeboarding HD all for 20 bucks so I mean that's pretty good
right national geographic challenge for PlayStation 3 as well this week and that
is it those are the two games you can expect this week except I bet you
anything foreign one action-packed doesn't come out this week so maybe one
game that's all you get and they're all terrible uh yeah well I mean I don't
know if they're absolutely I'm looking forward to mushroom wars because they're
for five bucks I mean for five bucks a game I mean that's not bad I mean I
would think this is no one's looking for this game in the series so instead of
being diarrhea it's just solid poop stop all right let's move to the Japanese
release dates it's a there's at least a couple things this week in Japan on the
PlayStation 3 there's a game called time leap coming out I'm not sure what time
leap is of course I want to think time crisis but it's actually time leap is a
romance dating game yeah I've played one of those really animates the characters
in real time I don't know what the hell is going on but it was easy achievement
points really well timely how did you play it if it hasn't come out yet it has
come out there's a version of it has come out okay well it's coming on the
Xbox 360 that could maybe that's a price reduction it might be it might be oh I'm
sorry it's on the PlayStation 3 not it's a port all right going to the PSP super
robot Tyson og saga comes out this week that's really it more robot wars you
know what do you know which one was actually cool was the one that had the
Ava's in it and you know when I hear og saga I'm thinking like you know some
old-school rappers 50 cent games are huge in Japan don't figure dog in a
fucking mech that'd be awesome all right Nintendo 3ds get ace combat 3d cross
rumble I know there's some ace combat the adventures of tin tin the game gets
its Japanese release this week yeah and I I think that's it nothing on the old
school DS or anything else so a slow week in Japan yay how about the UK we
have some stuff on the 10th Gotham City imposters on the 11th we have Amy that
game was delayed I it was like delayed at the last minute so it might not show
on the calendar you're using but Gotham City imposters was delayed to February
like I remember reading a story doesn't look like poop it just looks like it
looks like not fortress to what she got on here last week and talked about how
horrible it looks okay um on the 11th is Amy for Xbox 360 and PlayStation 3 and
chop lifter HD for Xbox 360 PC PlayStation 3 shop lifter HD so awesome
it has a Duke Nukem cameo nice everyone cares about Duke Nukem nowadays on
January 13th is crushed on the 3ds or maybe crush 3d it's crushed but they
3d in their house you can go so it's it's crushed through the crush the I mean
it's crushed it did it crush three days crushed I don't care done our release
dates have been crushed all right just a couple more news stories for you guys
in the classic game of the week you know we kind of sounded like what was that
anime club thing I didn't even watch that I watched it because of John and I
was like you know what was said is that I know people like that all right low
key so there's been some or there's gonna be some changes coming to Xbox
Live indie games this includes that they've now allowed people to you know
increase the file size of games from 150 megabytes to a new maximum of 500
megabytes and also they've removed I guess the restriction that all games
exceeding 50 megabytes in size were required to be priced at either $3 or
$5 making them hard to position I guess against Xbox Live arcade games but now
the minimum price has been reduced to $1 or 80 Microsoft points all across the
board so now you can see a lot more $1 games which is awesome and then of
course they've also raised the number of caps of titles that any developer is
allowed to host on Xbox Live indie games originally it was 10 now they can have a
total of 20 games at a time so neat I guess of course none of the changes that
they made have made it easier to find Xbox Live indie games on the actual
service so that's too bad we'll be posting lots of direct links when bungee
ferret tossing comes out which now with the expanded space I'm expecting Aaron
to include video clips of ferrets and clips from our show and I'm just kidding
he can do whatever seriously you need to get some of that ferret b-roll you need
to be able to put in the Konami code and just get get actual videos of ferrets
would be great ferret b-roll and it plays the Benny Hill theme oh wait that
would be copyright stuff maybe there's like maybe there's like one of those
really bad music free free things that sounds like the Benny Hill theme but
it's not yeah it's something alright I was suggesting from the kitchen that it
be played backwards alright one other story for you guys before the classic
game of the week we were talking about the Vita a minute ago and oh you know
the old saying on this show hackers gonna hack so how long did it take the
did Sony ever claimed that the Vita was unhackable was that claim ever made I
don't think they did this time no I think they just assumed yeah well it's
been done the Vita's already been hacked and the first thing that's been running
on it Genesis games yay Linux not a bad idea Sonic and knuckle why are you
cheering not Linux because I'm kind of getting I see the quintessential thing
is to install Linux yes when you when you hack the system you put Linux on it
write your hello world program I'm sure I'm sure someone did that but this is
something that people will want to download and use a lot of as the Genesis
games on the PlayStation Vita Sonic and knuckles now apparently running on the
PlayStation Vita it's been out less than a month apparently it's a homebrew
Genesis emulator that was originally built for the PSP it's running on the
Vita's PSP emulator yes that's right it's an emulator emulating an emulator
emulating a Sega blast process and I've gone cross-eyed so there you go Sony apparently
has put in some security that is going to meet that exploit moot as soon as it
is made available according to the video's uploader but how long is that
gonna last watch the PSP they patch new exploit they patch new exploit watch the
Wii they patch new exploit they patch new exploit and then they just forget
the patch and the cycle continues at some point they just say fuck it all
right remember back in the day when you didn't hack your no because you were
playing a Genesis if I hacked it I used an axe remember when you actually were
playing Sonic enough Sonic and knuckles on an actual Genesis what like two weeks
ago so so do we here at orange lounge radio we like to revisit the classic
games in a segment we call the classic game of the week every week dark soccer
dives into the vault and now she brings a little piece of it over because it's
not down the hall anymore yeah so she brings a little piece of the vault with
her in a segment we call the classic game of the week dark soccer what should
the kiddies be playing this week in America it was known as Rastan in Japan
and England it was called Rastan saga ooh it was put up by Taito and he played
a barbarian beaten shit up let's have some of that music Rob roll that
beautiful bean footage I've been hearing this game music play endlessly because
Dan has decided he's on a Rastan kick and has been watching video playthroughs
of Rastan we turn down the audio there so we can hear you yeah so much Rastan
anyway so it's sort of inspired by Greek mythology so you've got monsters coming
out and you have to beat them up with your sword or an axe or hammers some of
the weapons are also jewels and you get shields and mantles you also can get a
goat's head I think it gives you a one-up or something was it an
advertisement for God of War maybe like seeing into the future um anyway as far
as the background got graphics for the arcade version you actually had sunlight
effects and it was fairly innovative for its time like look at the background on
that video for a minute mm-hmm make sure that you send a link of that Toronto for
our tumbler okay oh I forgot Rama was queen of the tumbler now yes
congratulations on your promotion I have a hard time hitting the tumbler on my
little dinky notebook listeners get Jamie laptop I'm getting no no no you can use
that guy that rock over there that Alan was using that's okay I want anyone
anyway um with the Japanese version actually did get a full dedicated
cabinet but the North American and European ones never did there's rakit
conversions so you could convert an existing cabinet to whatever the kit was
you had any buttons joysticks decals marquees blah blah blah blah blah also
the opening to the story as what's on this particular version it was not
included in any versions but the Japanese version so here is sort of in
a nutshell I'm just gonna read from the article here the game explains that he
would be given all the treasures of an empire in exchange for a terrible
dragon's head and when you beat a stage or the rounds as they're called you
actually get a victory screen that goes with the storyline in the American
version there's just sort of the generic story you were a warrior you cleared
this crap hooray for you here's some money and some bitches it kind of the
opening scene I have to say makes me think of Conan you know the end of the
movie when he's sitting on his throne but that is another story he also just
looks like Conan yeah I mean you know this was the 80s the whole barbarian
thing was totally rocking on you know and I believe that this came out in I
want to say 87 don't quote me yet as far as the ports that came out there were
there's a Sega Master System version which I've got they actually had decent
music believe it or not the master system had pretty decent music there's
an MSX version a game give version in 91 oh for the record the Master System and
MSX versions came out in 88 there was a PC one in 1990 Commodore 64 version in
1987 a spectrum version 87 CPC version in 88 an Apple to GS in 1990 and the
Commodore 64 version the game was impossible to finish Rob what how did
they manage that had a bug in the game yikes the bug would prevent a player for
making a particular jump from one platform to the other he would always
fall short I could never make it across I don't remember that I mean I didn't
play this game on 64 but that's that's uh that's got to be irritating to say
least well for anyone who wants to play it now there is it was included in title
legends with ps2 and Xbox and PC in 2006 which funny enough is how I played this
game I do have title legends so didn't you get it for free no what it no that
was the year that you bought it when the title thing was going on it yeah I know
that was the gaming if you're thinking classic gaming Expo was the Midway
arcade treasures that was it because I batted my eyes and I flirted with a
Midway lady yeah okay so anyway who was very nice I'm very sad to see the
Midways no more well there were two sequels there was a game called Rastan
saga 2 that came out as nastar in Europe and nastar warrior in North America and
then warrior blade Rastan saga episode 3 there was a 3d fighting game that was
put out by Titus software for ps2 and Nintendo Gamecube that was called
barbarian in the u.s. the game was licensed by Taito and called warrior
blade Rastan versus barbarian when it came out in Japan it also did come out
in Europe later it didn't really have Rastan in it though it wasn't really
related to the universe it was just oh we could put Rastan on this and it will
sell and he also made the character Rastan made an appearance in a title
game called champion wrestler as miracle Rastan and now this game it came into
some censorship issues that while it wasn't really that adult content it had
blood splattered effects when you uh you know beat things yes red pixels yeah
they're right and in the Sega Master System support it actually had some
boobage in it the Gorgon and harpies were very booby and pubey and the Medusa
itself is actually just is all boobies so but I mean that was before we had
the ESRB so probably today it might have had an M rating how about that but no we
got boobs in the 80s and that's it all right there's your classic game of the
week Rastan not to be confused with Rygar which is it's especially the
arcade was somewhat of a similar looking game I mean the NES version was way
different but indeed not the same game Rastan and now that we're coming up to
our break Rob you know what I think it's time for what Polish chocolate cake I
brought a chocolate babka awesome it's Jewish eat it all right I'll have a
little bit it sounds delish all right so while we feast on cake we're gonna take
a break here but don't go anywhere there's plenty more of orange launch
ready to come lots more news still in part B your emails your tweets if you
tweet us right now at twitter.com slash olr your phone calls and so much more
when we come back on the show where every gamer has a voice orange lounge
radio
welcome back everybody to orange lounge radio we are live with this episode
number 340 no not 300 441 for January the 8th of 2012 the whole new year here
we are live of course talking about video games gaming lifestyle all that
stuff with you guys in our chat room at chat orange laundry calm a lot of folks
asking what we were playing live during the break now the podcast listeners
don't really hear this they just hear that ten seconds a little musical
interlude we do usually take a break of about six minutes or so we're actually
live taping you know to to run to the restroom or in this case get cake the
dark soccer brought or what have you and we played some music from OC remix
during the break I don't usually talk about this on the podcast but I had so
many live people asking what those songs were and the fact that you can go to OC
remix and just download these for yourselves I'll go ahead and tell you
what it was that first song was will rock was the artist from Mega Man 3 it
was called magnetic fireworks and the second song we played there was a remix
from the goonies to password music screen believe it or not but I like that
mix a lot that was TJ neko with two K's any any EK KO with I'm taking it all
back was the name of that so those are the two songs from OC remix we played so
if you want podcast listeners what you could do is is you stop right when you
hear the music interlude go listen to those two songs then come back and it's
it's like you were listening live but you know obviously for copyright reasons
and so forth even though those songs are free to download on OC remix it just
isn't right for us to put them into our own darn show we're gonna be getting
into some rapid-fire news here in a minute but first I thought I would talk
Disneyland because you know I went to Disneyland this week I didn't miss any
shows because of it because we went in the middle of the week I've had like 18
days off of work it's been the best thing ever I sat on your cat yes so dark
soccer was cat sitting which of course we're incredibly thankful for and we
well we took some pictures we took some pictures they actually had the Tron bike
out at electronica so I was able to get that and electronica was open during
the week go figure I don't think it will be moving for it was it was the most
crowded I have ever seen if I get to go to the bonus day thing oh the February
29th thing yeah I don't know that's Disneyland not
California ventures I don't know if they're gonna do it I think it's just
weekends and yeah they're they're definitely replacing electronica come a
spring but you were looking at the pictures and dark soccer was commenting
that she really enjoyed the picture of Alan and I with Duffy because Duffy's
your favorite Disney character why is Duffy your favorite Disney character
it's fucking cute for those who don't know who Duffy is who is done Dan calls
Duffy a focus market bear he's like okay he was created at Hong Kong at Hong Kong
Disney um okay I was chewing I was in the most of cake so anyway it was made
by um Hong Kong at Hong Kong Disney and he really picked up big in Japan as you
know we got Jamie a pin and we got her a Duffy sticker nice there you go so but
Duffy's just like this cute little bear that many made for Mickey so that he
would always have a companion when he went on his travels now you don't have a
Duffy bear yet though right I have a purse you don't have the actual Duffy
bear no well what if I told you right behind you I love you that's mine leave
it alone I'm just kidding of course we got that for you thank you thank you
thank you you're welcome all these time was you you do you do cat sit for us and
feed the kitties and give them pettings and drink our juice and eat our food I'm
just kidding we do appreciate it so so finally this time we said let's just get
her the damn real Duffy let's just do it I have a Duffy hat a Duffy purse and a
teeny tiny Duffy the dance that he would never buy me anything Duffy and he got
me a keychain did he and now I have a real Duffy oh he's so soft Dan's gonna
be thrilled I'm taking a picture of him right now all right I hope Dan's not
listening I hope he is Tiger con chat says Rob you go to Disneyland so much
you will need to go to Disney World after that you should take it to the
extreme and go to Euro Disney I would actually love to or it's Disneyland
Paris now by the way but I would actually love to go to Disney World it's
just it's a little more expensive to go cross-country and you have to go just
the right time of year because I don't want to be super crowded but I don't
think they have a picture I'm gonna get blown away by the hurricane either and
then I'm putting it up on the on the orange challenge picture thingy
spazzinator that's not a Duffy beer it's a Duffy bear it's a big difference all
right okay the picture is going up on our sorry Loki I know you really want a
Duffy bear more than anything maybe next time look his little feetsies have me
I'm taking a picture oh I was about to take a picture of his feet well many
made this for Mickey so yeah yeah that's fantastic all right I was buying time
for Alan to get that out for Jamie so let's move on let's get back into some
gaming news get into some rapid-fire news thank you Alan for doing that by
the way all right thank you Alan for doing that let's go back to some gaming
news so I can eat some cake all right so the game by notch mini craft it's the
you know one that he created in 48 hours last year some important to the Android
devices and apparently it's not an official port of the game but it's been
done by a group called full stad consulting and has touchscreen controls
and all that fun stuff and apparently I believe it's free from the Android
marketplace so go check it out if you're interested in that this I have no idea
why people would buy this but there is a new device called the retro 2 it's a USB
device that allows you to play Super NES and Genesis games and emulators the
actual thing costs $85 but will allow you to plug in your controllers and what
not into it and play it through an emulator or you could probably buy a
real console for that price just saying I mean I don't know why you would bother
to try to play these through emulators just just last week we were talking
about flea markets and like how some of the old systems still were like the
Super Nintendo I have over there still works so you know just go get the old
console seriously for 85 various spent $85 on something you can you can
literally I think you can buy those like portable handheld systems or whatever
that play you know Genesis and Super Nintendo games and stuff like that for
like less a lot less than that so I mean why would you bother to spend $85 on
that I got a text from Dan Duffy the focus group bear so I I just don't know
why but if you're interested you can check it out it's retro dot-com I
believe yes r-e-t-r-o-d-e if you want to purchase that and then of course a Bobo
you may remember him or not from the oh I know I can't remember the goddamn name
double dragon yes I was like dragon age dragon to dragon twin drag got wolf
something I know it has dragon isn't twin dragons like a plate no that's twin
Cobra and that was a helicopter game yes yes so about was big adventure is a
free-to-play flash game and of course features one of the characters from
double dragon this game reminds me a lot of oh what was the one that they did for
there was another one it was I can't remember now maybe it's this game
actually them thinking of anyways the game will be coming out on January 11th
and I guess it's a firm are confirmed on the official website about was big
adventure calm and you can play the game when it comes out and of course it
features a bunch of old NES settings and parodies so should be fun all right
moving on to some other rapid-fire news you know I love this series kid Icarus
of course there's the new uprising game that's coming out mmm what this quarter
at some point right do we have a firm date for that yet yeah it's in March I
just don't remember what date so at the end of this quarter but in the meantime
you can play with some fan remakes there's a fan remake out there called
super kid Icarus it's what they're calling a 16-bit remake but that's a
little bit deceptive because basically it's a PC version of kid Icarus that
uses 16-bit style sprites but very clearly a lot of the fonts and things
that are used or PC but whatever you can play it in your emulator and it's
basically kid Icarus was souped up graphics and easy mode so if you uh you
know kid Icarus is kind of a fucking hard game so if you want to play it a
little easier you can do that in this I did play a little bit of it just to I
wanted to see if there was more than just the first level in there and yes I
got all the way to the second level so there you go so they're playing now
before Nintendo pulls it down that's right you want to do that now before
they pull it down this is interesting because the website that actually has it
is home.com cast net slash tilde super kid Icarus so enjoy it now before it
gets pulled because I'm sure Comcast will get that cease and desist from
Nintendo any minute now meanwhile speaking of Nintendo a lot of folks very
excited about the Zelda 25th anniversary symphony that's going on the symphony of
the goddesses this is very similar to Final Fantasy dear friends video games
live that whole thing where they're gonna be playing Zelda music live it's
gonna be coming hopefully to a town near you at least if you live in the States
or certain parts of Canada January 10th is the first show in Dallas Texas March
14th in Vancouver March 26 in Seattle San Francisco on March 28th Denver on
April 7th April 20th 21st in Phoenix Atlanta on May 12th Montreal on May 31st
Austin on June 22nd Orlando on July 14th and Toronto on September 29th they are
saying that there are more tour dates that are planned very interesting what's
not on the list so Cal so it's interesting to see maybe they'll do an
LA show possibly an LA show like around e3 who knows but yeah they're gonna be
playing music from all the different Zelda games so it's not just the new one
so if you'd like live symphony I think you'll enjoy that God of War 4
apparently has been spotted on a composer's resume it's the first bit of
anything God of War 4 that we've seen was on the resume of Timothy Williams
who is the God of War series composer apparently it's on his resume but really
is it any fucking surprise to the God of 4 God of War 4 is in the making I
didn't think so God of 4 God of 4 I think that's that's what they should
actually call it so there you go God of 4 all right Dark Sakura no I will not
hold on you're not the boss of me sorry I was I was replying to something in the
chat room because our list I will take that Duffy away no no I will smear
chocolate on its butt and you'll have a poopy Duffy how do you like the cake by
the way the babka it's very good babka chocolaty isn't it like eating a
chocolate cinnamon roll yes video game news okay show how about some stuff for
Tekken well actually this is specifically new characters leaked for
Street Fighter across Tekken and that is shall you and M bison or as he is known
overseas Balrog or Vega sorry Vega because they switched them around Balrog
is the Vega over here whatever now I've gone cross-eyed so yeah shall
Lou and M bison are involved as far as rock band news it's Rob's absolute
favorite band ever Hall & Oates I was gonna say Abba has an exclusive thing
with a SingStar franchise so it can't be that there's a Hall & Oates pack Oh one
which has private eyes I can't go for that and man-eater I would I would get
man-eater I kind of privatize is awesome and actually man eaters pretty awesome
to it every time I think of Paula notes I think of Patton Oswalt talking about
if they had those surgery shows back in the 80s people would want to look like
Hall & Oates I'm gonna look like Steve Gutenberg I like what spazz nator
suggests in chat here god of guar god of war that would be awesome they should
have a guar mod for God of War don't they have guar songs in rock band I got
to have something that would be awesome yeah and the last but not least House of
the Dead three and four are both coming to PSN but no typing of the dead so
therefore failure guess what I have two copies of typing of the dead for like
Dreamcast I don't even know where the fuck my Dreamcast keyboard is if I even
have I have the Dreamcast version and PC version you need to have typing of the
dead day you know what we need to do cuz Mavis Beacon ain't got shit on typing of
the dead you know we need to do what we need to get Jessica iguana girl she was
really good at that one she and we need to have a typing of the dead a thon
because when I got Michael when I got my copy I took it to her apartment the the
apartment that she was living in when I met her and we'd play typing of the dead
for like three hours I bet I bet I know what apartment that was she lived there
for ever several yes yes I remember that one yeah but the one that I stayed up
for three days without sleep making a costume with Evan anyway anyway anyway
but yeah how's the dead three came out in 2002 and how's the dead four has only
been in the arcade so this is an exclusive to PSN nice now how about the
Silent Hill game I know different company but that Silent Hill arcade
game seriously why haven't we seen this released somewhere for the home because
they have a stick up their ass oh okay that answers everything and they're
currently stuck on it and the moment that they learn how to stand up without
taking the stick up their ass with them we'll probably see it I'm having to hide
poor Duffy's version Virgin Disney ears is it too much to ask for some Duffy
come over here is too much to ask for some fucking silent hill arcade game
and I think that Rob has a potty mouth and he should eat so God this is just
like a little Santorum on Horde house this week I'm not even gonna explain it
what I'm not even gonna explain it horde house calm little centaur yeah that's I
can just imagine it ha at Rick Santorum asshole all right look yeah for the
record that was an authentic southern accent I know was it oh I couldn't is
that dark soccer is it George Bush I'm not sure moving on Loki maybe you can
bring some video game news back into this program that used to be about
gaming talk about piracy all right whatever I'll take what I can get so of
course a report came out talking about the most pirated games of 2011 this is
coming from torrent freak I would think that they would know a little bit about
piracy now now Loki Tory isn't it's just a bit torrent news site how dare you
well they should still be up to date with you know what's going on including
piracy I mean come on I'm not suggesting that they are pirating themselves or
facilitating party in any way I am just saying that you know they should know
something about it anyways the number one game that has been downloaded 3.9
million times since its release in March of 2011 the crisis to crisis to the
game sequel to the game that killed PCs around the world you know but yes
crisis to number one game of course modern warfare 3 was downloaded an
estimated 3.6 million times since November so you know modern warfare 3
had come out in March and they would probably been number one but oh well
don't wait battlefield 3 coming in third with 3.5 million downloads and then of
course that ring rounding out the top 5 piva 12 and portal to there you go
surprised what's not on the list maybe anything I mean that was all PC stuff
let's talk a little bit about how about Xenoblade well I'm surprised more people
didn't pirate that to be able to play it in the US now now you spoke too soon the
top Wii game downloads on bit torrent in 2011 Super Mario Galaxy 2 Mario sports
mix what the fuck are people down the Mario sports mix that's a terrible very
good question I get galaxy 2 because that was on a lot of the best list and
Xenoblade Chronicles was number 3 Lego Pirates of the Caribbean number 4 and
FIFA 12 number 5 weird list yeah Xbox 360 downloads Gears of War 3 number 1
Call of Duty Mario warfare 3 number 2 battlefield 3 number 3
Forza Motorsports 4 number 4 and connect sports season 2 number 5 not that we're
advocating piracy but you know it's it happens we'd be naive to sit here and go
oh it never happens that's all don't pay no attention behind a curtain it is
interesting to see what gets pirated and what doesn't because certain games don't
show up on the list at all because of maybe the DRM that's in the game like
for example or like a game like SWTOR can't be pirated that much because you
have to have an online connection to play so hmm Starcraft 2 big PC game no
more on that list I think because of the whole battle net tie-in of course a lot
that drives a lot of people bonkers because they don't want to be on the
internet to play the game so where's the happy middle ground I don't know all
right anyhow moving on to a system that I'm sure nobody's gonna pirate any games
on at all the Wii U there's a new rumor about the Wii U because you know rumors
about the Wii U or are everywhere and it's a slow news week so why the hell
not apparently Wii U will also double as an e-reader this is apparently via a
friend who Nintendo approached to do iOS software ports over to the Wii U system
which doesn't surprise me at all that you know the Wii U would probably be
going after things like Angry Birds cut the rope tiny tower the stuff that's
really big on iOS to be able to be played on the you know touch device I
wouldn't surprise me at all but apparently Nintendo is also looking at
doing digital books magazines comics and so forth on the Wii U and the 3ds
apparently instruction manuals could be done this way to strategy guides and
Nintendo power you know it'd be really funny hmm but there's no way this is
ever gonna happen is if the Wii U controller actually became its own
console but it can't I mean because all the processing is done on that I
understand that they could put an ARM processor in there and how like its own
tablet yeah I'm kind of deja vu-ing what we talked about a little bit last week
but yeah we talked about how maybe one of the big things that they're gonna
change you know because the system could change a lot but until next t3 is that
maybe they're gonna put the its own processor a little or processor in the
Wii U controller itself it's gonna drive the price of those things up even more
but processors are cheap really yeah I guess it's true it just depends on what
they put in there so DDR dollar bill in our chat room says we you trying to be a
tablet yeah tablets are terrible well here's the thing though I think a lot of
it would be the fact that Nintendo would have a big audience with kids like maybe
kids are too young to have their own iPad Rob what how well did the Pico do
really but but kids could use the Wii U controller I see that's the thing though
is I don't think kids are too young to have an iPad well let me put this way a
lot of parents don't think kids are too young to have an iPad and they will buy
them an iPad or an iPod or something I mean I remember seeing on some gaming
blogs a stupid iPod you know touch freak out you know Christmas videos and stuff
like that I mean come on parents are willing to buy their kids that kind of
stuff there are cat games on iPad I mean there's there's games for toddlers on
the iPad so I'm not surprised that they would do that and I mean seriously with
an iPad 3 coming out probably soon I mean it's only gonna drive the prices of
the older models down so why wouldn't they you know parents buy an iPad I'm
not surprised parents will let their kids play with an iPad because people
are letting their frogs and lizards play with their iPad that ant smasher game
well people are dumb well as long as the as long as the Wii U gets swap note
that's all I care about which by the way if you could smile big cuz I'm gonna
take a picture for Bobby here maybe I'm not smiling big maybe I'll send it to
Tiger Claw to their little 3d picture there of all our life all right with
Duffy adorable hey swap note is actually pretty cool it's like it's it's like
it's like Nintendo is finally understanding email well I'm glad they
got that bad bank bandwagon if I can only speak now I'm yeah man I'm really
looking forward to them understand you know patching games in 2021 or something
like that you know maybe with the Wii U that we'll get some actual game
patching fantastic Nintendo and for the record I'm putting a picture of Duffy's
butt on the olr thing orange launch radio.com all right let's take a moment
to visit the mailbag every week you guys send us emails mailbag at orange lounge
radio.com and dark soccer dives into the email bag and read your favorite emails
I was gonna say we should start taking emails over swap note but you'd have to
have my friend code to do that Duffy should start reading them no Duffy
should not read them all right anyhow while I work on my swap note I'm gonna
send a swap note to Bobby and I guess I'll send it to Tiger Claw I don't know
who else listens to olr on my friends list but I'll send it to them too well I
wanted to announce that we do have three winners for the Master System contest
wieners wieners that means I have to do I think I've got games enough to divide
amongst them as well someone is from will and I will be logging into the
email when I get home another one is where is it from Rico and one of them
was hit stun so congratulations to our winners Congrats to all you wieners and
I'm gonna try to send you ones that you don't already have so and I know who's
about getting wet and if you get a duplicate sorry eBay we can autograph
them though if you want us to so back to the the mailbag I just played the worst
game in history of Nintendo DS I asked for it for Christmas because I love
Puss in Boots and a sexy Antonio voice well unfortunately the reviews I were
looking at were for the Wii version of the game which apparently is decent this
however this abomination should never have been made it is surely the spawn of
Satan and all copies should be destroyed seriously the graphics look like
something back from early early PlayStation 1 or Nintendo 64 back when
their characters look like they were made of Lego blocks no voices and the
gameplay tap the screen to the beat no seriously that's the whole stupid game
and that's what I get for buying a tie-in game I guess but I really thought
the treat puss with some respect sad face Holly D haven't we warned you
about tie-ins that's right game tie-ins can be pretty bad but or movie is game
times movie tie-ins games can be pretty bad next email bummer though hi olr crew
I've never seen the tester on PSN not the first season of the second mostly
because I'm over reality shows I also thought the grand prize of being an
entry-level tester was kind of stupid though a great way for you to get your
foot in the door but I think I'm going to start watching the new season because
I just found out a friend of a friend is a contestant we were chatting on
Facebook and I asked her if she'd be interested in appearing as a guest on
olr but only if you're interested she seemed very interested and I would have
to get but would have to get back to me to see if corporate folks would allow
her to do so so my question is would you be interested why the hell not sure I
want to know who beat dark soccer for the position no dark soccer went through
herself right I'm not gonna give any more of her information just because
because it's included in the email sure sure but we are interested yeah why not
if corporate PSN will let us then we're happy for it I would love to ask some
questions about the stuff I want to wait till the show debuts though so we can be
like okay how bad did they misrepresent this well maybe there is at least one
person it's somewhat internet celebrity that's actually in there oh really yeah
the guy does I don't know if you've ever seen them the the awesome games like
Metal Gear awesome they're like great he's actually in in the contention there
that's funny so rooting for him because he's the only person they recognize
vaguely anyway says thanks and keep up the good work and thanks for putting the
podcast up on Mondays they're not so blah anymore that's from Stan I had to
show up within an hour last week this is great having it at my house good for you
just saying okay by the way I sent that I sent that message on spa pass or was
it swap note see how long it takes to get to tiger color this is good evening
dark Sakura sky and Loki Saurus I am writing to you from a pseudo email
account for our conversation you can call me track slur I'm a longtime
listener here is my plight I am a 34 year old male gamer living in northwest
Florida I play everything from Batman Arkham City on Xbox to swo tour and while
on PC I make a decent income from working full-time technical job in the
Network Operations Center I'm suffering probably from maybe a newer condition
called gamers loneliness or gamers depression I am an okay looking guy
average weight and height I have money in a car I'm having problems finding a
companion I like women so I'm not alone I've tried POF okay cupid geek to geek
with no success I think it might be my age and the single gamer women are ultra
rare maybe the fact that I don't drink or go to clubs slash bars I do know my
schedule is bad I work Friday to Monday 12-hour shifts with a two-hour commute
to work each day but it's my job to deal with this I've been buying tons of games
that go into my never-ending backlog and buying lots of gamer where my room looks
like a gamers cache now I can have any game I want and have three days off a
week I can game but I'm not any happier I even stopped playing DDR in the air I
kids because I was tired of playing by myself and I stopped getting any
enjoyment in fact I don't feel happy you're doing anything I've been trying
to do changes from but the results end up the same I don't want to be something
I am NOT just to conform to find someone to be with I wish I could find a
companion like you guys I would marry Dark Soccer's clone thank you I don't
have a clone Dark Soccer is married however I wanted to let you all know
this information because there could be other gamers out there that could be
feeling the way I feel I'm not sure if this is just how the world world
balances us gamers out of future equations reduce population your loyal
listener track slur this message is brought to you by Shermie Skylander
Emporium Wow DB mail okay um that threw me for a little bit of a curveball I I
think it's one of those things where when you kind of let it go that you kind
of have all that hanging over your head like oh my god I need this perfect life
and I need this companion and I need I need all this to happen ABC to happen so
I can be happy no no no you have to learn to be happy with what you've got
and you're kind of like your current situation and then once you kind of have
that about you that that confidence the rest of it will come I think I think I
always say it happens when you stop trying to force it I mean yeah I also
say things happen when you make them happen but that's like stuff that you
have tangible control over you know like I I can't do this well then go to school
and learn how to do it you know that type of thing in this case you know like
with and I know I've told the story million times we Dan and I hooked up is
that we had just been friends we weren't trying to do anything and he just called
me to cheer me up and we kept talking because it worked and I moved out here
and we worked you know that's just that's like a really rare success story
on top of that you know it was just sort of a faded thing I guess but like I
really think that that a good relationship will find you when you're
not looking for one if that makes sense yeah I mean Alan and I were friends
online for probably four or five years via live journal just you know and you
know I'm sure he thought you know I was attractive I thought he was attractive
but it's kind of like yeah he lives in San Francisco it's it's like he lives in
China you know so far away and we never really gave it any thought until one day
it just kind of let's go out sometime and and we did and then it was kind of
like well we're gonna make this work and we did so you know it just it just
happened like I never thought it would and it did you know oh there's somewhere
in the back of my imagination I imagine Nelly going after Loki with the club
isn't that what a girl but you know for real like I I wouldn't like just don't
stress about it like that's I you're only gonna cause yourself like hurt to
do that and I don't think you need to go out to bars or clubs I think you're
doing the right thing just kind of put yourself out there online I would say if
you really feel like you need to go out and do something try maybe like I know
this sounds really weird but try like joining a club or maybe there's a
nonprofit in your area a political cause you can get behind the volunteer you
know something where you you force yourself to get out of the house well
when I lived in Alabama and keep in mind this is when I was effectively single
you know I did a lot of stuff I larped yes I played live-action vampire shut up
there's not else to do in Alabama I I was in band I did jazz band I was in
orchestra you know because I was still a big band nerd I would do ensembles with
other friends I would I played the end oh god that was when I was in eight
games a week for a while and I did there was even I gamed every night every night
I was in different gaming groups so I mean and I even dated a couple of people
that I gamed with like there was one guy who I was really into for a while but we
just kind of never sort of fun to make out with and you know fun to make out
with good friend you know never that's that's exactly the type of people I met
doing Rocky Horror for so many years it's almost the same kind of thing but I
mean you know if if you're making yourself into some kind of hermit I mean
you're not gonna meet anybody unless you find ways to branch out you have to make
it yourself and so okay so clubs aren't your deal you know what I hate clubs too
I sometimes go just because I like booze and I like goth music so I'll go hang
out but I don't you know go because I'm well then again I didn't really start
clubbing until I moved out here at all but if that's not your thing then find
you know I I've made friends through my temple for example after I converted and
I don't know if you're religious or anything but you know there's always
something you can do with like-minded people you know or you know if check out
actually check out YMCA because sometimes they offer not just you know
the little fitness things that they do but they'll have workshops and classes
or you know find something that you're interested in and then put in that topic
and your location and see if you can find groups for it but for and coming
back to this point is I think this is very important I think the first thing
you have to do then we'll stop the advice show I promise but I think the
first thing you have to do is you have to really sit down and say I have a good
life I mean you do have a job you you I don't you know you right but you know
but you you have a lot of stuff that's going for you for you right now you know
you have a you know the things that you're proud of and you know I don't
know this person so it's hard for me to say you know whatever they are into but
there's probably a lot and in the person who says his email you know I'm I
consider myself good-looking you have a lot going for you then you know so love
yourself yeah find the stuff that makes you happy and focus on that you know if
if the games aren't doing it for you anymore then there's another gap mm-hmm
distract yourself but I'm not saying distract yourself in a don't work on the
problem kind of way but I'm sorry reading chat but I was gonna say you
know find new things you know if if your current hobbies not doing it for you
find a new hobby but you have to be out there is the thing if you're gonna try
to meet somebody you have to be out there and I'll be a hermit
Loki won't be your dating advice my advice is hey you're gonna have a lot of
hookers sometimes it's actually nice to have a lot of free time to play the
games you want to play because you're not gonna have that because once you
have a baby that all goes away it's all gone that's good advice that's you know
what and that's that's another way to look at it like I'm not saying like you
know hate on kids or whatever cuz you know but enjoy the life you have while
you have it right yeah so there you go anyway I mean sometimes you know yeah
it's just like you know however if you want to incorporate sex life and your
video gaming you could try jlist because they have lots of stops honestly I just
go to cons that's not a bad idea why not Chris and Megsy did they meet at a con
that online oh how funny I went to conventions we went to we had that
three-day thing it is it is a social going out meeting other people yes just
I've known people who've met for the love of God use protection and you know what my
lesbian parents met at a convention oh there you go back in the day all right
we got to move on move on this is becoming the dating dating game here
orange lounge DDO hi olr less than three makes a return hi olr this past week
I've been on a nostalgia trip did you come back I ended up digging up my mega
drive and playing castle of illusion and streets of Rage 2 now I'm getting on
a list full it's it's I in there so I'd actually side on a completely different
subject sing as dark soccer has been raving about the game I just thought I'd
point out that fractal is now available in indie royales New Year's bundle and
that's an indie royale calm I n di e r o y a le calm also Nintendo seems to be
going out of their way to make getting the circle pad add-on as awkward as
possible is being released exclusively through savvy and on time online only
retailer here in the UK and that looks like a very unhappy face hear you later
catastrophic Moggy you know I love castle of illusion and I love streets of
Rage 2 so I would say great gaming I've been actually talking about fantasy zone
with people and I really need to sit down and hook up the master system in
place of fantasy zone um yeah fractal awesome game everyone needs to play it
so go get that bundle oh yeah it's in that that yeah there's like a new bundle
I was thinking about getting that actually get it okay and then someone
sent us a video but I can't watch it on my computer sorry this is a great comment
spazzinator making a comment on the last email the dating advice email he
needs a cupid arrow to the knee that I as much as I hate I thought was pretty
good that's pretty good pretty good congratulations congratulations to our
winners for the three of you that emailed me email me your address and you
will get a game in the next couple weeks master system game at random however I
will make every attempt to send you something you don't already have so all
right I texted Dan to remind him he's like don't give away my games I was like
I talked about this all right stop being so stingy is that it for emails that's
it all right mailbag at orange lounge radio.com if you have an email for us I
mean literally we'll read anything I mean we that one email was about dating
not even totally about games but whatever and guess what well Duffy Duffy
better not send emails to the show hi I'm Duffy all right it's time to get
into the F use of the week every week we are angsty why because we can
I'm not at all upset anymore because I have Duffy the end
Loki if you do Microsoft Excel that constantly try to outsmart it in order
to get to do what I wanted to have visual basic yeah but see I don't want
to be visual basic that's why music sell all right I don't know I'm actually in a
pretty good mood like I should be giving an F you to the fact that I have to go
back to work tomorrow after being off for like two and a half weeks but I'm
like seriously this is the longest vacation I've had since I started
working there which was ten years ago which didn't involve me being in the
hospital or having surgery or having the swine flu which happened once and even
that it wouldn't have had the swine flu I'm still sorry about that Rob I was
only out for like two weeks not to have so but I actually like I'm so well
rested and feel so good I'm like I'm actually this weird looking forward to
going back to work so in reality we'll say yes so F you to that all messing
with my mind I do you know what though I'm lucky I'm very fortunate I really do
enjoy my job it's not I I teach people for a living it's a it's a great thing I
love my job I really do and they're not small children it's just sometimes some
of the others you know stuff everybody gets annoyed with their job at some
point you know because anytime you put a bunch of personalities together and you
know one's in charge or whatever you know things might go but I I have a
great boss I really do my boss is awesome we work so well together I can't
really complain so F you did the fact that I don't take two and a half week
vacations more often because I really should and F you did the fact that the
only way I was able to do it before was getting the swine flu you know what I'm
sorry I need to reward myself more often that's what I I guess that's all right I
didn't know I had it I rubbed AIDS all over the bear I'm just kidding let's
move on Loki all right so Nintendo being the forefront of digital and online
they apparently slapped the wrists of the owner director of icon games
entertainment and Richard Hill Whithall he apparently has released several games
in the last year on various platforms and he recently shared some sales
numbers on the website gamasutra but then was asked by Nintendo to take down
the numbers for its platforms according to Richard Nintendo doesn't allow
developers to share digital sales numbers for self-published we were in
downloadable ds titles that's kind of interesting and apparently I guess it
hurts smaller developers who I guess need to make those sales numbers known
in order to secure financing and plan out business models and stuff like that
yeah apparently though you can still kind of figure out his numbers because
he gives a total number and then you know the other platforms and do the math
I have to do math and and and on top of that the numbers weren't so good on the
Nintendo platforms unfortunately so maybe that's why they don't want numbers
out there there's a lot of saturation on the Wii marketplace too and it's really
hard for games to stand out because the Wii store isn't set up very well you
know yeah all right well we talked a little bit earlier in the show and I
know Bobby talked a lot on his show tonight of course Bobby black wolf was
on before us at all games radio talked a lot about SOPA and you know the
Internet's been talking a lot about SOPA and I'm sure most of you you know
listening they're gonna scrub it clean of content most of you guys who are tech
savvy enough to download this podcast and listen to it and understand it
probably already have a general awareness about SOPA but this is how
the message might be communicated to those that don't understand SOPA I find
this very interesting apparently they're talking about a huge what they call the
nuclear option to protest SOPA and this is rumored to be happening on January
23rd because the Senate is going to debate this on the 24th and what we're
talking about is major major websites shutting down essentially for a day you
know replaced with a black screen generally talking about how you know how
soap is bad and all that stuff we're talking AOL, eBay, Facebook, Etsy, Google,
Twitter, Wikipedia, Yahoo, Zynga game network this out ties into gaming and
really I mean this is just just anybody who cares about tech has a vested
interest in SOPA and I don't I think I've made this pretty clear as as Loki
as a start soccer but olr is obviously against SOPA and based on the reason
that it gives companies way too much power I understand that people want to
do something about piracy but there has to be I think more accountability in
that regard and SOPA is not really gonna do anything for some sites it's if you
know the numbers you're gonna be able to get on the pirate bag I just don't
understand so I know does it hurt I don't understand that it's almost like
to me like a really terrible web filter that's at like someone's office or
something like that where it's like oh I can't go to Facebook oh but if I type in
the near the IP address I can go to Facebook if that's all they're doing to
block this and that's kind of stupid you're not supposed to censor the
internet you know what I mean you're not that that's what that's what we read
about and go how can China stand that to have the web censored I mean I
understand it's just a part of you know that country and all that but you know
is that what we want to become here it's just it's it's yucky and I I personally
I I I think the Atari story you kicked off the show with illustrates it per
perfectly there's gonna be companies that are gonna overreach and the little
people aren't gonna be able to fight them and that's wrong that is so not
what America is supposed to be about well then again we can also detain
people for no good reason well you know that's that's a whole nother Oprah or
so they say but yeah but it's I think it's all related it's it's screwed up
how much power companies have in this country it really is it's getting this
well I don't get political on the show not nearly as often as she does but this
is something that really irritates me and especially when you have all these
video game companies where the ESA has stood against it you know because no
piracy bad so the ESA stands against it but most of the gaming companies like we
don't a lot of the gaming companies were reached out to for comment and basically
came back with we don't we don't really do politics we just make games so the
ESA kind of speaks for us what what educate yourself well that's fine if you
don't if you're gonna let someone else but it's for you and it's gonna be those
morons the people that don't understand why this is very bad that are gonna ruin
it it doesn't really affect them I mean as far as their product goes the fact
that they are these big companies that are gonna be able to pull Justin TV
feeds and things that might be critical about their game that ought to be legal
under fair use when these little reviewers are gonna be able to fight
them that is when they don't even fucking understand the law they just
know they can do it exactly bothers me exactly why do they care then that's the
point it was all you're gonna give us a bunch of power to take down all these
people that we don't like sweet why would I oppose that but of course they're
not gonna say oh yeah we were strongly for that because then people backlash
against them so they got to take you know the on the fence approach or oh
we're just hands off we'll let them do whatever you know that way they can't
let you know well I think that first sites that can't if people want to add
though I think to the sites that are gonna be down on that day but you can't
necessarily take down you know your server or anything if you've got a blog
or something you know say I've got a couple blogs on blogspot put a big
notice no activity on this day you know don't post on Facebook that day don't I
mean Facebook's gonna be dumb I'm saying don't blog do it because maintain web
silence you know there if you imagine if you can't use Google for a day I mean
that's gonna piss some people off I think that's necessary I think it's
necessary they should all be they should all go down so now let's see what did I
want to say here Oh frisbee in our chat says may I suggest these companies use
ocean marketing to speak for them I realize you're making a joke there but
think about how did that whole thing really how did that whole thing happen
the guy represented himself as something he kind of wasn't right anyway
Tiger class as I recall two years ago take to send DMCA notices to several
Justin TV channels that were showing GTA 4 when it first came out I believe this
is because they didn't want spoilers being leaked spoilers are gonna get out
there if not in text forms it's just it's silly anyway if you want to do
something about it that's my problem right there though that's not because
your your copyrights were violated or because someone's you know posting it as
like their own thing it's because oh we don't want spoilers coming out that's
not a reason to go and say hey I need these videos taken down I'm sorry but
that's like you know review spoiling the end of a book or something like that you
can't you can't force them to take it down because you don't like the fact
that someone spoiled the book all right so anyhow if you want to do something
about SOPA I gotta give props to destructoid to compile this pretty good
article that they have on their website they was posted January 7th talking
about SOPA and they even have kind of some form letters that you can copy
paste although I would kind of encourage you to put your own thing on it I mean a
lot of them prior aren't even gonna get read let's be real but send this to put
on our tumblr to okay I'll do that send that over to you know I'll get props to
destructoid they did and one other thing I like they compiled a list this is very
useful a list of all these game companies where you can contact directly
emails and websites and I thought that was pretty cool so you know you can take
your case to the companies themselves that are supporting this I am do I need
to even say like look at what happened to go daddy and that was who that was a
bit of a mess and talk about a backpedal there I mean seriously oh actually no
we're not a we're against SOPA now yeah right so let me send that over to Rama
and you can put that on the tumblr if you want to read more about that orange
launch radio tumbler calm alrighty let's move on with some more news getting into
some phone calls very soon at 1 877 game olr or a username on skype orange launch
radio but not just yet a few more emails dark Sakura you Suzuki who my husband
has met I have a photo of Dan with you Suzuki
it's very faded now but he said something in an interview with the Toulouse
game show so this is in French and I'm going to read it in French if I can
remember my pronunciation right no pool no to near a license party the Sega
which means we can obtain the license from Sega do you know what they're
talking about Shenmue so he's not saying that they are actively going to do it
but I think it means that there might be an interest in them trying to obtain it
for a YS net which is his company so maybe it'll happen that would be kind of
cool if it did don't you think very cool if you want I think he should play a
game of lucky hit uh-huh you know all I ever knew that game was play space
Harrier anyway so you can the interview is actually up on YouTube if you want to
find it it's the you Suzuki interview on Shenmue so all right I would be great
I'd love to see that series come back I think a lot of people would I think he
wants to finish it true no it's like he's got a story that's like mostly told
it's got like one chapter left really and what's it out all right Loki you
know I'm actually surprised that this took this long to settle but you
remember way back when I'm back before you could use USB drives and you know
near Xbox 360 you're limited to their overpriced hard drives and their memory
units which you know really didn't have a lot of space on them and they were
really expensive and a company day tell came out and you know had this wonderful
max memory device you plop a micro SD card into and be able to save your games
to that and everything was peachy keen until Microsoft patched the Xbox 360 to
block these from being used on the device and of course then there was
lawsuits filed and all that fun stuff well they've settled out of court
probably because at this point even if that were to be allowed to be used on
their you know system no one's using the memory cards anymore because it doesn't
work but the consumers who bought these didn't get anything no they got nothing
well hooray to these companies for settling but the consumers got screwed
didn't they yep what do they get out of it for buying these products that don't
work the satisfaction knowing that you know the US justice system has triumph
well golly gee willikers Loki now I can sleep at night I'm glad you can all
right somebody's celebrating a birthday this week in fact they're turning 30
years old if you can believe it it's the Commodore 64 that's right the Commodore
64 celebrated its 30th birthday this week and all I have to say is man I feel
old because I grew up on the Commodore 64 I remember having one of these I
think we got it Christmas like 83 but the Commodore 64 actually came out in
1982 I love this the whole machine would hold the equivalent of one one hundredth
of an mp3 file $595 is how much these systems cost back in 1982 they say that
is now with inflation $1400 today is how much these things cost it was first
introduced at the 1982 Consumer Electronics Show in Las Vegas and yeah
boy Commodore 64 now 30 years old and man I love my Commodore 64 so many good
games and those sit chips man so much chiptune stuff the year today is just
directly influenced by the Commodore 64 I wish I still had a working one of
these I had a Commodore 64 C we actually broke our original Commodore 64 and we
got a 64 C the white one and that was a pretty awesome machine I was five did
you have when it came out no I told you I didn't have a Commodore 64 I had a
click Oh Adam with the cassette deck by the way on a related note would you like
to feel old for a minute here are some other games that are turning not systems
but games that are turning 30 years old this year in 2012 you're ready these
games came out in 1982 making them 30 years old bag man bump and jump burger
time on my favorites dig dug dig dug Donkey Kong jr. gravatar joust by the
way this list is from arcade heroes.com upset with you joust for influencing
that horrible part of Wow jungle hunt or jungle King depending on where you live
kangaroo I freaking love kangaroo I played this 30 years old but the crap
out of that at godfather's pizza when I was little liberator that's the one
that's the first one I don't really recognize that was an Atari game
millipede moon patrol Oh God I used to love moon patrol we have this a local
arcade mr. dew I love mr. dew pango you love pango fucking love pango that's a
great game that's the little penguins you know they had one at Pasquale ace
and it finally broke Oh pole position love pole position Popeye remember that
and they did a game out of it because Nintendo made it a reactor robotron 2084
they had a version of that on Xbox Live that was one of the first arcade games
that came out on Xbox Live Q Burt that's another game I played the crap out of
them I know the swearing guy with a long nose everybody thought this had an
awesome name Satan's Hollow it's actually kind of a derpy game but you
know it was a it was the Midway it's on the arcade treasures for Midway and all
that and it's kind of kind of see in collections but it runs on that same
hardware as like journey and timber and some of those old classic Midway games
sin a star beware I live space duel Star Trek the Sega one time pilot tutankham
Tron is 30 years old and Zaxxon by saying 30 years that's what I need to do
for classic game mm-hmm so there you go now we can all feel old together just
think in 30 years when we're sitting here on our show celebrating the 40th
anniversary going hey remember you remember the Xbox 360 fucking bastard
stole all my money fucking thing broke after only having it a week I had to
send it in but damn there was some good games all right hopefully by then we're
all playing the holodeck though because remember gaming is just inching forward
slowly to the holodeck all right one eight seven seven game olr or our
username on Skype Skype is orange lounge radio if you want to give us a call
right now and talk to us meanwhile let's do some tweets we will start with a
tweet from ramaditya night says sonic and knuckles I remember back in the day
I used the cheat that allowed me to change sonic to whatever item I want and
cross the wall I found a lot of bugs like a place you were not supposed to be
able to go there spikes all around I wonder if that was so is that like a
code in the game or is that something like a game genie remember the game
genie where you could like hacks or the game I'm sure that is something that
Loki had to own the game genie oh yeah well he's talking about on the game
gene he was talking about sonic and knuckles and some of the things you
could do with that yeah I used to actually sit down all night with my game
genie and my SNES mm-hmm and just try to figure out what different codes by
altering other codes hmm and I found a few ones like ones that turn Mario green
that was it all it did was turn Mario green that's all it does yeah makes
Mario Luigi but not really it turned his skin green all right let's go to the
phones cuz we're getting some calls hi you're on orange launch radio who's this
hey what's up guys you know hey guys you know what's on your mind buddy not
much I just want to talk about this sober thing I think a lot of us over
reacting first off I don't think it's gonna go through and if it did go
through I don't think it's gonna be that big of a deal I think that a lot of
people are getting worked up and they're freaking out all over nothing I think
pretty much what uh what these companies want to do you know the game companies
movies music whatever they they just want to make money so pretty much this
law going out is just gonna be a way for them to protect their content and be
able to put it on their sites and make their type of money that they want to
make I don't think they're necessarily trying to shut down the internet or stop
us from talking on Facebook or any of that kind of stuff well I it's it's a
fair viewpoint and I understand that but but could it happen to one person I mean
I like again I have to refer to the Atari thing at the beginning of the show
that they're pulling down all these games that they may or may not have the
ability to do and I worry that legal departments of companies who don't
really understand things might go a little batshit crazy and the problem is
if you leave the door or what's the expression you give them an inch and
they take a yard I I worry about putting that much power into a corporation's
hand because people you and me can't fight it
yeah true that is I can see a point there I'm not clearly I understand why
they want to do something about piracy I get it but can you ever really stop
piracy I'm not sure there's no way they can stop it this is I mean I mean I
don't mean to cut you off but I mean if you if you look at the record like as
far as piracy goes like when it comes to um movies and video games a lot of the
stuff that's like highly pirated or also the stuff that sells the most you know
I think music is the only place that actually has a they should really do
something about piracy because I mean you don't have to mod anything on your
system to be able to play the illegal download of music that you download right
so I think the music industry is the one that's taking the real heat from it but
not necessarily the games and the movie industry right you know and I again I
understand they want to do something but I just think this is going to do more
harm than good because what's it really gonna fix that the IP for the pirate Bay
will be out there within within minutes of this thing passing and everybody will
have it and there'll be add-ons for Google Chrome and Firefox it will lie
there already are there already are so I mean I just it's not gonna do any good
so I buy but I understand why they want to do something but I think at the end
of the day it's gonna be accountability you want to prove that someone stole
money from a bank they got to go to court have a trial it's kind of what's
got to happen in this case you know yeah they just they just need to understand
the internet more like they're still trying to treat the internet like if
it's the the real world where it's not doesn't necessarily work like that you
know so I think that they need to seriously look this over they come up
with you know with the better law the better soap or whatever else you want to
call it but um I'm not really that worried about it well I don't know I I
I hope you're right but I I do worry about leaving that opportunity there but
you're a little more optimistic than I so I I applaud you for that so I hope
you're right optimistic to a fault all right anything else you want to share
listeners you guys have a good night all right you too buddy take care of tonight
bye all right you know what it's it's cool that he has a differing opinion and
you know I again I I hope I think he said it best at the end there maybe he's
optimistic to a fault but you know we'll see we'll see actions speak louder than
words so we'll see but I just have a feeling the first time a website gets
shut down incorrectly it's gonna just all hell's gonna break loose all right
one eight seven seven game all our username on Skype is orange lounge radio
meanwhile we have some more tweets tiger claw on Twitter sends us a tweet one of
them is already about that media molecule thing you already talked about
earlier but the other one is about PlayStation 3 video editing app play
memory studio apparently leaked ahead of CES this might be something that they're
Sony's gonna show at CES and we'll get to that in a minute but we're gonna take
another call while the skype lines lighting up higher on orange launch
radio who's this hey guys do you know DDR dollar bill what's on your mind
buddy first of all I wish you guys happy new year we're getting some feedback
back on your speakers buddy back away from your speakers if you can we're
getting bad feedback happy new year to you how's this now I'm still hearing it
but it's not it's not killing me get out your question or comment fast we'll try
to make this quick call oh okay which is a quick story a while back I don't know
if I posted by look I said that I stopped playing Wow because I got sick
of all the jackasses kept bitching about everything I kept doing in the game can
you hear me yeah yeah we can hear you yeah people are people are assholes on
the internet unfortunately yeah so for once a long time I pretty much just
quit like whole mmorpgs then I try try a couple other free ones out there and
then I tried out DC Universe when it came out for free uh-huh
to the point of loving it so much I actually brought the down I should about
DLC sports so you're saying the community in DC Universe online maybe
not so bad um consider that one time I played 130
more and Ruth making to me we're making jokes about um let's see 16 year olds and
an all women's squad and everybody's dueling in the middle of nowhere it was
a lot more fun you know sometimes it's just about finding the right fit for you
and although you know unfortunately a couple jackasses probably ruined Wow for
you and I would argue there's other people in there maybe it just wasn't a
fit for you after all maybe DC Universe is just you know kind of better I don't
think you have to play one MMO just because it's the popular one you like
what you like there's people out there that fucking play Hello Kitty island
adventure and they fucking love it so you know what let them have their thing
yeah but it goes back to well for one last thing cuz I'm not gonna keep it
short okay after when I got to my finally hit level 30 and DC Universe the
final level I found out that I actually have to group and it made me realize
that maybe it's okay to group with people once in a while just gotta find
the right group so I went back on Wow I quit this one guild I was with and I
joined up with another guild and was a whole different experience well I have
to perfect story I got I got to hang up on you to your dollar bill though cuz
like the chair I'm saying it sounds like you're living in a hunt bees nest but
thank you so much buddy have a good one yeah well here's what I was gonna tell
you and just message me in the chat room um is when I started playing well when I
finally liked it again I did not play with other people at all all I did was
chat with the guild and quest by myself and yeah and I've done two characters
that way I did Rebecca black and Iressa both that way but now I've actually got
a character that I am doing nothing but instances with and and maybe you know
seasonal quests and little things but the point is is that I'm actually trying
to group with other people and I found that actually not every group is full of
idiots a lot of them are many of them don't have proper grammar and they're
very hard to understand but for the most part it's it's partly your support your
support group outside of your pugs you know and people people sometimes just
are kind of weird online like I admit like okay I play with my friend Matt who
is grandpa Warcraft on Horde house if you ever listen to him and when we
group together he does the weirdest shit in instances like he's a friend of mine
and I love them but oh my god like we'll start an instant so like we roll in
instance together and it's the two of us and three random people and as soon as
the instant starts he'll go like he'll say in party chat he'll say something
like sassy I'm really sorry to hear about your abortion this afternoon are
you feeling okay you know you gotta understand a lot of these people are
just doing it to get their rocks off you know they mean that night oh yeah you
know yeah yeah yeah well he's been on this oh he and me and John were running
an instance and decided to completely troll the people that we were with
and Mary uh-huh decided to completely troll our fifth person yeah and we had
a poor person doesn't know that you're just fucking with them you know we
finally had one person hang out with us now keep in mind and and people who play
well will know it is it was in halls of origination huh we got to the last we
did all of the bosses all of them all of them in halls of origination we finally
get to the last guy and we get a person who's just really cool and playing along
with us we're like that's what we wanted we wanted the person who will play with
us someone who will rag on people with you okay I got it I gotta go to the call
we picked up another call hi you're on horse entree who's this hey this is
SSJ 100 Matt hey SSJ 100 Matt haven't talked to you in a while how you doing
I'm doing good I'm doing good all right what's on your mind buddy calling and do
a con report con report who had a who had a con at New Year's actually it was
a mag fest this weekend oh this weekend okay I guess this weekend is not so bad
so all right mag fest how was it it was pretty good it's down it was down in DC
and basically it's just a big arcade festival okay I was gonna say is this
the Sony game mag or is this like a okay so it's it's arcade game okay it's
arcade games they a lot of people bring arcade machines and it's also a big show
for video game music mm-hmm Oh so this year their guest of honor was Nobu Matsu
and his his band oh the the black mages no earthbound papas oh I didn't know he
had another one okay very cool and but yeah you know they had it was the thing
is it's a 24-hour convention so at any point you know if you have a if you feel
like you know you want to play DDR or pong or killer instincts to arcade
machine you can go down three o'clock in the morning you could play wait so if
you're saying like it's a 24-7 like for the weekend or it literally is 24 hours
it's literally like 24-7 from Thursday okay okay well that's still really cool
that's got to be a bitch to staff but that's awesome I kind of wish
California extreme would do that yeah but no you know what it actually is
kind of like California extreme where you know they there's about like 150
arcade machines I mean I got to I mean my whole goal mm-hmm was to try to get a
high score on one classic arcade game and I managed to get the high score on
road blasters road blasters oh my god I was awesome yeah good times it's also
hell's hard amen to that did you get to play anything new that you'd never
really played before that you were like wow how did I miss this growing up you
know what I was you know a lot of old games like narc and bad dudes that
really took me back because I have net I haven't seen those things since the
early 80s but you know I'll also I was introduced to a lot of old games that
you know I've never seen or heard of um this crazy game ice-cold beer sounds
like a pepper no it's not it's not really like that it's like you uh you're
playing like two with two lovers and you're trying to put a ball into a hole
so a little like it's kind of dirty yeah it sounds kind of sexual I've been to
that party the internet seen that party Rob all right but no I get what you're
saying that's yeah huh very cool but you know it's definitely cool and did they
have speakers or anything oh I guess just the musicians that's well no they
had they had less because they had you know the angry video game nerd brentalf
loss you know a lot of people I love you you're gonna nerd huh that's awesome I
know it's a very you know very small convention but you know it's big so you
know not only were you able to play classic arcade games you're also able to
check out you know console games and play and play stuff on like a TV well
damn if I'm able to get another two and a half weeks off work next holiday I
might have to come out there that sounds like an awesome con I love DC I'd love
an excuse to go back yeah but I guess I need to get to New York City first huh
yeah I guess that's got to stop going to Disneyland you guys are gonna have to
confiscate my annual pass for that to happen just they move to see you know
they Disneyland burned down sorry to say all right s2100 Matt thanks so much for
telling us about the con I had no idea I'm on the wrong coast so I had no idea
this is happening but I'm definitely gonna check it out for next year
definitely all right take everybody's all right thank you guys so much for the
phone calls we're gonna go ahead and shut down the skype line for now so we
can wrap up the last few topics here and close up shop for the night but if you
didn't get through tonight and you have something you really want to say be sure
to send us a tweet at twitter.com slash olr or you can email us mailbag at
orange laundry calm speaking of tweets I wanted to finish Tiger Claws thought
here apparently this is coming from a leak at the Sony booth at CES is showing
on the PlayStation 3 something called play memory studio which will be excuse
me well we're seeing it happen on radio a video editing suite for the PlayStation
3 apparently you can put effects in video and kind of do some editing live
on the PlayStation 3 that's kind of cool I guess I already thought the PlayStation
did kind of allow some limited video stuff but that's cool if they're
enhancing it especially if it's free I wonder if it'll be free I somehow doubt
it Tom and one on Twitter sent us this and I saw this earlier this week cuz
somebody posted some Facebook it's fucking hilarious it's a macho man
dragon mod in Skyrim Loki have you seen this oh yeah yeah it's great
this is the beginning again did you have that I said next prisoner to the block
prisoner nice and easy this is actually being rendered from the game it's not
like a fan-edited thing with the mod of course
it is a thing pure terror
I got it the giant much yeah the dragons wearing a macho man hat
that's great with the beard and everything I'm making Alan installed as
one
it's really free I fucking love that that's amazing you
wanna know something Rob I need that on the tumbler that song here's your
stories from Jamie's childhood mmm disco inferno which keep in mind I had two
copies of this of the Saturday Night Fever soundtrack on vinyl used to stand
on my bed dancing in my pajamas to disco inferno okay I gave that to Rama for the
Twitter cuz that that video is just too damn good if you haven't seen yet I also
posted the link in chat so there you go enjoy guys it's the one that says tico
because I got it from Twitter cuz Tom and linked that so there you go all
right and lastly a couple tweets here from Zen monkey 69 tweets us hey 69
tweets us saying it's 2012 and we have a shitload of video game sequels coming
what games do you think don't deserve a sequel and should just die what games
don't deserve a sequel and should just die how about the Imagine series imagine
babies there was one last year for the 3ds that was it one I think Holly would
say the puss in boots game the puss in puts puss in boots series absolutely
puss in puts tiki a tight tiki I hope I'm saying that right and chat says
Elder Scrolls just throwing it down saying there's too damn many Elder
Scrolls games I'm gonna go on next year is pretty fun yeah you won't have
another Elder Scrolls game 2012 that's you'll have expansions for Skyrim that's
for sure yeah for sure I franchises that need to die oh god I like part of you
wants to be cynical and say the Just Dance series but parties they can be
kind of fun so I can't really think of anything because honestly if I don't
want to play them I just don't know that they exist that's kind of where I'm at
is like I don't think a lot about the games that I don't want to play you know
I could be super cynical go Call of Duty because I don't play those games but I
realize other people do play those games I'm kind of looking over at my own
collection how about Tetris remakes yeah that's another one I'm getting sick
last dress was kind of fun but that's back in the super scope days apparently
that 3ds one's pretty good but it's still the same fucking game we've been
playing forever it might be time for the need for speed series to die maybe that
would be another answer I would have well or at least of all that or
something I don't know I can't yeah I really can't think of anything offhand I
wonder what our chatters think it chat maybe Saints Row car her her no no yuki
says cooking mama that's actually a really good answer yeah just the mama
series in general it it's not doing well I that's a very good answer I can stand
with yuki on that one yuki also says sonic games no because generations yeah
I need this game but then I need sonic generation there's admittedly there's
been a lot of crap yeah and I don't I think that sonic 4 was kind of a I will
give you one that's just and it is a somewhat major game coming out this year
okay Silent Hill I think I kind of agree non konami Japan produced Silent Hill
games specifically me today yes to go back in house to Konami Japan I agree
Silent Hill is kind of done and karaoke revolution American or karaoke revolution
glee needs oh there you go winner everything how about everything to die
but glee needs to get canceled all right last another tweet from Zen since I
haven't read tweets from Zen before I will read two tweets tonight Zen says if
PlayStation 4 Xbox lube and the Nintendo Wii U were all coming out on the same
day and you could only get one which system would you get too early I how can
you answer that because we don't we don't know what the Xbox lube and the
PlayStation 4 have to offer and we only know about half of what that we use
really bring into the table so you'd be asking me to base that decision based
off of the current consoles and the problem with that is the jump we made
from the last realm of consoles right because when the systems first came out
I would say the Xbox 360 was in a better position than the PlayStation 3 was when
they first came out but yet if I had based my choice completely off that
generation before this one the PlayStation 2 I think was better than
original Xbox you know so it's just it's it's it's way too early to call I in
here here's also the realistic in me is like well I'm going to end up with them
all anyway because I have the sick addiction of video games and do this
show and everything so it's kind of like I'm going to try to show some restraint
at least maybe not buying one of the consoles if not to the console luck you
know what though honestly with you would have played on the Wii and stuff I think
it's gonna be pretty easy for the Wii U I think I say that now I guess I will
humor the question and I'm going to say PlayStation 4 and the reason why I
because I just have the feeling out of the three systems it's going to be the
most advanced because I think it's going to be the one that's in the incubator
the longest meaning I think it'll be the last of the three to come out so I think
it's going to have the best processor in it and all that but again that doesn't
necessarily make it the best but I literally have nothing else to go off of
right now you know so that I'm going to say PlayStation 4 just to humor the
question but that could change absolutely so alright that's it for the
Twitter's tonight at twitter.com slash olr oh actually I see one oh never mind
that's somebody new following us thank you on Twitter it's Twitter combines the
followers and the app messages now it's really weird all right anyway um last
minute stories Loki dark soccer anything for last minute stories um no Loki um my
story is that I had trouble finding a cage man sock thankfully I downloaded
one a while ago so that'd be fine and not my preference I they've had some
better songs but I'm gonna put it in anyways all right that's gonna do it
them for another episode of orange lounge radio hey thank you guys so much
for downloading your show and checking us out you know going sorry this rude
it's a step wave way way back to the beginning of the show here and we're
talking about best best games of 2011 mm-hmm it's not really a game but I have
to recommend ready player one seriously if you haven't read it yet you need to
read it because it's awesome and I mean if you're a fan of games especially a
fan of classic games you're gonna love this excuse me and I need them to
actually sign my book that'd be pretty awesome if he's gonna hit a con or
something well I'm getting coffin fit again I got to say this I think I'm
allowed to say this because it's it's out there post on the internet but
apparently in Sacramento there's gonna be a group that is going to do a live
shadow casting a la Rocky Horror of Scott Pilgrim versus the world I want
pretty awesome and I can't wait I mean as much as I have kind of a love hate
with that movie there are things I loved about things I didn't like about it I
think that's gonna be awesome because you know that theater is gonna be full
of nerds that are into it you know and I think it's gonna be a great showing I
want to I definitely I'm gonna see cuz I know the guys that are behind it through
some of the stuff I did last year so I'm gonna see if we can get all our Oh coin
it or something oh from the movie I get it all right anyhow that you talking
about ready player one we're gonna throw quarters ready player one is it has been
option for a movie but I don't see how the fuck they're gonna be able to do
that but seriously though I'll get you I'm get you ready player one legend
Zaku and chat says oh wow rocky or a picture show finally has competition now
hold on Becky wants to go to there's there Rockies kind of like it's just
there can be more than one movie in the theater at a time and Rockies just
always there's always more than one cult movie repo the genetic opera for example
is really big on the midnight circuit right now how do we in the area inch was
for a while I think still is in some places clue the movie will always show
up once a year somewhere you know there's there's other movies that show
up too I don't think it's necessarily about competition usually the same
people that are in a rocky or in all the other stuff too so anyhow anyhow off
subject we're trying to wrap up the show I was gonna say thank you very much for
downloading the show and tuning in to us hey if you like what you hear all we ask
you know we don't put commercials in the show we don't make you buy things or
whatever all we ask tell people about the show spread the word because we're
not a multi-million dollar website we rely on you guys to help spread the word
of orange lounge radio and we really really appreciate it orange launch radio
comm is the website the forums are there if you want to post on the forums I have
to say though right now it's locked down to new accounts because yeah we were
really getting killed with spammers there so I just shut off accounts all
together so hopefully within the next month or two we're gonna just totally
revamp the forums and hopefully be able to avoid the spam bots if you really
want an account on the forums in the meantime email the show directly and
we'll set one up for you mailbag at orange launch radio comm if you don't
already have one and legend Ozaku I totally agree what's that Priscilla
queen of the desert is the closest thing that can take on Rocky Horror Picture
Show um that's a Broadway thing now so yeah they it's I it was supposed to come
out on Broadway I'm pretty sure it did so all right anyhow that's it now we're
talking Broadway we're way off the subject of video games we'll be back
next week to talk more games and gaming news with you guys so have a wonderful
week everybody we'll see you next time here at orange lounge radio good night
you've been listening to orange lounge radio orange lounge radio is an orange
lounge production to join us for a live show visit www.allgames.com Sunday
nights at 6 p.m. Pacific time the views and opinions expressed on orange lounge
radio do not necessarily reflect those of the entire staff of orange lounge
radio or all games comm but we're probably right anyway see you next week