[SPEAKER_09]: Tonight, February 22nd, 2009, a new American McGee's Alice is announced, DSi and Rhythm Heaven get release dates, and will we soon be seeing more Red?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello everybody out there on the internet and welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: We are that show that broadcasts live every week on allgames.com Sunday nights dedicated to video games, video gaming, gaming culture, and the gamer lifestyle.
[SPEAKER_05]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm here with you every week as well as the one and only DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hack.
[SPEAKER_05]: How are you doing?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hack, cough, die?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Any predictions for tonight's Oscars which we're competing against apparently?
[SPEAKER_07]: Um...
[SPEAKER_07]: Fart.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, fart, the motion picture for best picture.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also say hello to Tech Master Loki, who's chowing down on a sandwich over there.
[SPEAKER_05]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not a sandwich, it's a burger.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, a burger, sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: You guys are making me hungry.
[SPEAKER_05]: I haven't eaten dinner yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm doing fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, good, good.
[SPEAKER_05]: Any predictions for tonight's Oscars?
[SPEAKER_05]: Slumdog Millionaire is going to win.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_07]: My gaming week was fantabulously uneventful, but hey, I did actually play stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: I played some City of Heroes and more like made a whole bunch of costumes because it was fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I... Actually, Dan and I were watching videos last night comparing the...
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, played some more Order of Ecclesia, the Castlevania game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I need to actually go back and work on my Symphony of the Night game since I've started it and got, like, to one save point and was like, haha, going to bed.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, did some thinking about doing tabletop gaming and then went, meh.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, that's really about it for my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_07]: What about you, Loki?
[SPEAKER_02]: I played Eat the Burger.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, actually, I played a few things this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mainly Lost and Damned.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just wanted to add the other the in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: The new Grand Theft Auto expansion is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's short.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, I kind of like the style of it, more gritty.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some of the things that they've changed are good, some not so good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Especially with the multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_02]: For one, the helicopters, they really tweaked.
[SPEAKER_02]: They gave the helicopters explosive rounds, and they made them fragile.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you run into one little thing and your helicopter's on fire already.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, because they have explosive rounds, you can blow up a car and people really quick.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's kind of annoying that they had to go and tweak all that.
[SPEAKER_02]: They really did the explosive rounds for that Chopper vs. Chopper online mode, which is alright, I guess, but they could have just limited the explosive rounds to that mode instead of fucking everything up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then they did some other stuff that doesn't make any sense whatsoever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now they have different preferences where you have to set your preferences on your phone before you can actually go into an online game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Say, for example, you're hosting one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Your preferences for auto-aim, for the cops, and for, well, if you're doing free mode, friendly fire on or off are locked into whatever your preferences are.
[SPEAKER_02]: and you can't change it on there, which is really retarded.
[SPEAKER_02]: I understand why they did it for, you know, if you're searching for a game, but as far as hosting the game, you should be able to change those options without having to back out of everything and it's really retarded and caught us off guard with that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: And for free mode, they took out the helicopters.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's no fucking helicopters for no reason whatsoever.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that makes no sense at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know why they did that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But other than that, it's pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, you know, what we normally do at lunch, me and my friend, we just kind of shoot each other with the helicopters anyway, so we just play a deathmatch just at free mode, and big deal, it's the same thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know, the game itself is pretty fun, and we'll be getting into a little bit more of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's some stuff they did for Controversy that I don't get it, and it's stupid, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: I had store credit, so no actual money was being spent.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then, other than that, I also played Nobi Nobi Boy, or like I'd refer it to Baby's First Tapeworm.
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically, this game, I haven't really figured out, I mean, obviously the point is to stretch as far as possible.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know how you do that if you eat things.
[SPEAKER_02]: From what I found, eating things didn't really seem to do anything, but hey, maybe it does, and I just don't notice it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, um, basically you're this kind of weird tube-like creature that looks like it could have been straight out of, you know, um, I don't know, just, um, of course the Katamari universe.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then everything that's pretty much in this looks like it's straight out of the Katamari universe.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, it's a weird game.
[SPEAKER_02]: You kind of get bored with it after a while, but I've been trying to stretch my character out.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've gotten to the point where I'm so long that I actually, if I stretch out up or down, it'll go so far that it thinks I've fallen to my death, which, you know, you can't really die in the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: You just kind of pop back out of your chimney.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you can eat things, and then you'll poop them out.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's funny, because stuff will explode out of your ass.
[SPEAKER_05]: The auto shotgun's pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_02]: But yeah, they took out helicopters out of free mode.
[SPEAKER_02]: Only free mode, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that doesn't make any sense.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't get it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Comment from Tigerclaw.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, Noby Noby Boy is like Snake.
[SPEAKER_05]: You get bigger as you eat stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I don't know if that's the case.
[SPEAKER_02]: You just stretch.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have to, like, kind of... Wouldn't stretch imply getting big?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, you stretch by getting bigger, but it's not necessarily eating things.
[SPEAKER_02]: You basically stretch out.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if it's eating things that does anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't even know what the eating things part does.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: Please explain!
[SPEAKER_02]: You're a guy standing there and you have to take a shit and you have to not shit your pants.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a text adventure game.
[SPEAKER_02]: And basically you type in what you need him to do.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have to tell him to take off your pants, pull door to bathroom.
[SPEAKER_02]: Where did you find this game?
[SPEAKER_07]: You have him take off his pants before he opens the door to the bathroom.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have you played this too?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can do it in any order, but yes, that's what you have to do.
[SPEAKER_07]: Take out pants, take off pants, pee, go in the bathroom.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you can like, you know, you can shit on the ground.
[SPEAKER_02]: The basic object of the game is not to shit your pants, but you can shit on the ground, shit in the toilet.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have ten different achievements for different things you can do.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um.
[SPEAKER_02]: But yeah, that's pretty much my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, what is it though with... Did you find this game, because I noticed kind of a theme on PlayStation Network recently that a lot of their big games don't give you much explanation on what the hell to do with them.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I didn't know what the hell I was supposed to do with them.
[SPEAKER_02]: It says there's no objective whatsoever, but...
[SPEAKER_02]: You see the girl stretching out into space, but you don't see how close she is to another planet or something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because she's just really fucking far out there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Has she hit the moon yet?
[SPEAKER_02]: She's probably gone beyond the moon, but the only planet you can play is Earth.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you can kind of generate new maps and stuff, but they're all kind of the same.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I didn't really get it, what I was supposed to be doing.
[SPEAKER_02]: If I was supposed to be eating stuff or, you know...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll play it during the break.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, alright, I'll have to check it out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see, I also played a pretty big release on the PlayStation Network this week that also gives you very little explanation on what the hell you're supposed to do.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's called Flower.
[SPEAKER_05]: Flower, I'd honestly best describe it, honestly, it's a racing game, in my opinion.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a very, very different type of racing game, but it's kind of a racing game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know, maybe that's not the fairest way to describe it, but you certainly have an acceleration button...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: www.DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe three, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: The game does leave some elements to be explored, such as there are secret petals that you can find in stages.
[SPEAKER_05]: There are secret areas to go in in different stages.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, the game is very open.
[SPEAKER_05]: It doesn't give you a lot of description as to what you're supposed to do in the game, so there is a lot of exploration.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a very big element.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's really a seventh stage, too, that's the credits, which plays slightly differently, in which when you're exploding the flowers, basically, you're also collecting the letters of the staff in the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: All in all, I think it's a pretty good game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Title for download and $10 is a fair price considering it's just the sheer beauty of the game and I think it's something that's very easy to pick up.
[SPEAKER_05]: You use the X button and you use 6 axis to play the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_05]: You tilt the 6 axis to move which doesn't play as bad as you might think and you use the X to accelerate.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's basically the controls.
[SPEAKER_02]: as the controls for Flow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which was their other game.
[SPEAKER_05]: The same developers who made Flow.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's actually a Flow reference in the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: And one of the trophies you collect is Flow.
[SPEAKER_05]: A Flow trophy or whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, yeah, I enjoyed Flower.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would say pick it up.
[SPEAKER_05]: I could see that they're probably going to expand this game later on maybe with some extra stages and things.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that would be okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: I do think they need to put a demo out for it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: But it is difficult, especially with some of those characters that really rely on rolling motions for their moves.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: and Arcade Joystick if I'm really going to want to be able to be any good at this game, especially online.
[SPEAKER_05]: When I play characters like Chun-Li, I don't have a problem at all, because most of Chun-Li's moves are back and forth, or up to down, or back to forth.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, that's, you know...
[SPEAKER_05]: That's easy on the Xbox 360 stick.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm looking at chat room, chat.orangelaundry.com, and Gunstar in chat says, get an arcade stick, Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm thinking... Hey!
[SPEAKER_05]: Is that your husband?
[SPEAKER_07]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_05]: Might be.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know that's the name he'd use.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, I might need to invest the money to get it.
[SPEAKER_05]: But here's the question.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do I love Street Fighter IV that much?
[SPEAKER_05]: And I, granted, I could get use out of this on other fighting games I play, like Soul Calibur 4 is pretty awesome, and I'm sure they'll be, like, maybe I'll enjoy Super Street Fighter 2 Turbo Super Edition High Def a little more if I actually got an arcade stick.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, yeah, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a lot of money to drop on a controller.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm just worried I won't be playing this game that long.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some very obvious modes I think were left out of the game, which is a disappointment.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's kind of cool that you can turn on the mode where you, like, seek other players while you're playing arcade mode, basically.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you might, like, it gives that old, very old-fashioned feel of somebody walking up to the arcade game and just dropping a quarter in and challenging you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: Being able to set that to friends only is something I would really think would be an obvious mode they did not choose to enable.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, I would love to play with that mode on if only my friends could challenge me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because, you know, and you might be thinking, well, why do you want to set it that way, Rob?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I...
[SPEAKER_05]: Like to play with friends on Xbox Live more than I do random a-holes that sometimes, you know, I don't really want to play with.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Tiger Glass says I have it turned off.
[SPEAKER_05]: I do most of the time, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: I spend most of my time with it turned off as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it would be cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'd probably leave it on more often if friends could just walk up and challenge me.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a lot of money to pay.
[SPEAKER_05]: And this whole accessibility.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think the game is accessible if you've played Street Fighter 2 before.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know it's been taking a little bit of crap for not being as accessible as they say it is in regards to the difficulty.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm not going to lie to you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Seth is a cheap bitch.
[SPEAKER_05]: He sucks, even on easiest mode.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sucks a lot.
[SPEAKER_05]: And some of the opponents start to really suck too when you get up there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Even in medium and some of those other modes.
[SPEAKER_05]: However, what I loved about it
[SPEAKER_05]: Street Fighter 3, Street Fighter Alpha, Capcom SNK
[SPEAKER_05]: Marvel, Capcom you know all those games kind of came out in that Dreamcast era that I kind of didn't play a lot of games through and so for me I didn't play a lot of those games I was able to pick up Street Fighter 4 no problem no problem because the moves are pretty much the same so
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I had a good time with the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: $60 though, that's a lot to ask for somebody that's based on nostalgia only.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would honestly recommend you play it at a friend's house first before you drop that kind of money.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you envision that this is a game you would play online a lot, if you are a fighting game fan at all, then definitely Street Fighter IV needs to be in your collection.
[SPEAKER_05]: But if you're a casual fighting game fan like me...
[SPEAKER_05]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_07]: I do have to admit that Gil's a bastard.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're all bastards.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, that's going to do it for my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't want to go on forever.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have some news we want to get to tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's get to some housekeeping.
[SPEAKER_05]: And there isn't a lot right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: I do want to point out at OrangeLoungeRadio.com, very cool new feature where our podcasts, when we get them to the feed...
[SPEAKER_05]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: They said Justin TV was down.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if it came back up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: But again, remember folks, Justin TV is priority number two.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because we are a radio show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Disconnected again.
[SPEAKER_05]: Weird.
[SPEAKER_05]: We are a radio show, not a TV show.
[SPEAKER_05]: So Justin TV is not priority number one.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it is going to go down occasionally.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that just sucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: So make sure you always tune in at allgames.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, also our LiveJournal community.
[SPEAKER_05]: All the communities are right there on OrangeLoungeRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you want to find other Orange Lounge Radio listeners, very cool community, just nice people.
[SPEAKER_05]: We don't like jerks in our community.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or if you want to find us, look at the little box that says Extended Play on OrangeLoungeRadio.com in the bottom left-hand corner.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: It directly links you to Facebook, Last.fm, MySpace, YouTube, even though we haven't updated YouTube in forever.
[SPEAKER_05]: OLRPSP.com, it's awesome so check that out I have to ask something and I'm going to actually put this up on our gallery is that your printer?
[SPEAKER_05]: That one on the floor, yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Your printer looks like an ice chest.
[SPEAKER_05]: It does, doesn't it?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm putting this up on... Go to our gallery, because we've been putting pictures up on it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've been taking tons of pictures.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I'm taking a picture of the messy floor.
[SPEAKER_05]: And other people can submit pictures, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I swear to God, the first time somebody submits a picture that is inappropriate, we're pulling the plug on that thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: No boobs.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, no boobs.
[SPEAKER_05]: We should have a special...
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, I'm okay with boobs as long as they're covered boobs.
[SPEAKER_05]: We do have young kids that look at the website.
[SPEAKER_05]: But dead or alive boobs are fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, let's get into some gaming news, shall we, Loki?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: So there was, of course, the release this week of Lost in Damned, and with it was a little bit of controversy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Starting off, the bit that I don't really get why it was in there, but it was.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently there was full frontal male nudity in Lost in Damned.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, one of the characters that you talked to, Mr. Stubbs, is in a... I'm sorry, that's just funny right there, that the character's name is Stubby.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mr. Stubbs, yes, he's actually... Is Stubby Chubby?
[SPEAKER_05]: I have not seen the scene.
[SPEAKER_05]: Contrary to what you all might think, I have not went and looked at the scene because I think the whole thing is a little silly.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just whatever, you know, it's full frontal, whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, yeah, he's there, you know, completely naked because he's in a bathhouse, and...
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, he's all hanging out.
[SPEAKER_02]: And everyone's like, oh my god, why'd they do that?
[SPEAKER_02]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: I have to say, why did they do that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because here's my thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: If they can put full frontal male nudity in this, why aren't the strippers topless?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what I want to know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, because that's the lesser of two evils right there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't get why that's the case, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, yeah, that's in the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's really minor.
[SPEAKER_02]: No big deal, but just in case.
[SPEAKER_02]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some other stuff that was interesting, there was some censorship tweaks on the European and Australian versions of the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: First off, the European versions, apparently their versions of Grand Theft Auto 4 have been censored with the update.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is, of course, by accident.
[SPEAKER_02]: However, Rockstar is working on it right now so that it will be
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching, and I'll see you next time.
[SPEAKER_02]: And basically, the censorship that's going on, there's no blood pools.
[SPEAKER_02]: The camera, when you get, you know, services from a prostitute, you can normally move the camera around to get better angles and stuff, but in censored versions, it's not.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, apparently, yeah, the Lost and Damned actually reverted the censorship on the Australian version, so that's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whatever, it's a cock.
[SPEAKER_05]: Obviously, they're just trying to ruffle some feathers with this, and they've succeeded.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, I like, though, that at least it's not, like, sexualized.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's there to accomplish one thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's there to get people talking.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, mission accomplished, because here we are in our little crappy podcast talking about your full frontal male nudity in a game that, you know, is completely random.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just say it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Cock!
[SPEAKER_05]: Exactly, it's just a cock.
[SPEAKER_05]: It shouldn't be that big of a deal.
[SPEAKER_05]: But at the same time, I would not suddenly want there to be random cocks in all my games.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_05]: Suddenly it's, oh my god, a cock monster in Final Fantasy.
[SPEAKER_07]: We need more penis in video games.
[SPEAKER_05]: But to be fair, if we're going to have more penis, then we need more vag.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't talk right now Hi We have Danny
[SPEAKER_07]: Camara?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rob has salvaged my laptop because I'm actually trying not to move my laptop, so that was me last week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did Joe say hi?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I didn't.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_07]: But they know you better as DarkTetsuya.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Welcome, DarkTetsuya, and friends, everybody's here tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: If my laptop catches on fire, it's Rob's fault.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, well it's not my fault, you spilled something on it.
[SPEAKER_07]: You startled me, Rob, with your Rob-ness.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not my fault if you got excited.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now my laptop smells like Propel.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is not my fault if you got excited at us talking about the story about Cox and Vag, okay?
[SPEAKER_07]: But we need more games like this.
[SPEAKER_05]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: If they're going to have this game with ultra-violence, then why not ultra-nudity?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, they have Pacey's.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just a little bit more flesh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, if you're going to show cock and balls, they can seriously just put boobies in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I don't get it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I agree they should be fair and have some boobs in it too, but you know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just don't even care.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know why people care so damn much.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I understand it's because we've never really seen this in a game before, OMG.
[SPEAKER_07]: Someone's got to do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: May as well be them.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Street Fighter 4 Street Fighter 2
[SPEAKER_05]: T-Hawk was awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: See, Gunstar agrees with me in chat, because DJ and T-Hawk suck.
[SPEAKER_05]: However, all hope may not be lost for DJ and T-Hawk fans.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yoshinori Ono, who is the producer of Street Fighter IV, has kind of teased the idea of these guys appearing later on.
[SPEAKER_05]: And this was in Famitsu Magazine.
[SPEAKER_05]: He actually said that some 3D models were created.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'd like to see pictures of that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I bet that would be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: They actually went so far as to actually plan out the combat style for T-Hawk...
[SPEAKER_05]: But they got cut before the game actually came out.
[SPEAKER_05]: However, Ono did say if the fans want it bad enough, the characters could be added at a later date.
[SPEAKER_05]: How would that happen?
[SPEAKER_05]: Could that be download content?
[SPEAKER_05]: Could that be a re-release of the game?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that's more likely.
[SPEAKER_07]: I actually see download content.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then a gold edition later like how they did with Marvel Ultimate Alliance.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right, but here's the thing with download content.
[SPEAKER_05]: If they didn't already plan for these two guys to be download content, what happens if one of my friends downloads it and has T-Hawk and then fights me online?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't have T-Hawk.
[SPEAKER_05]: What happens?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because, yeah, Drew, you have a thought?
[SPEAKER_12]: or have a light pack downloaded where you have the characters there you just can't select them
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, kind of like you could get to... What was it they did for Fable 2 where you could go to that area but you didn't have all the stuff that went with it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Can I say something a little controversial about Street Fighter 4?
[SPEAKER_05]: And maybe I'm going to get shit for this.
[SPEAKER_05]: It needs more cock?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's honestly something I noticed.
[SPEAKER_05]: Especially talking about DJ getting cut from the game and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Where are the black people in Street Fighter 4?
[SPEAKER_05]: Really?
[SPEAKER_05]: This is an honest question.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's Balrog.
[SPEAKER_05]: Balrog, that's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: One out of... He was for the longest time too.
[SPEAKER_05]: How many?
[SPEAKER_07]: Most everybody in the game is Asian, Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's like white people beating each other up the game, is what it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, it's Asian people beating up the white guys the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Where's, like, you know, well, I guess you have one Indian guy, too, and, you know, I don't know, it just seemed like these guys, you know, DJ and T-Hawk, T-Hawk especially was a little more ethnic, like, not a type you see in, like, other games, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, he's like, um...
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I realize it's a little bit, it's a small world-ish, but what?
[SPEAKER_12]: It's a Japanese anime-ish fighting game.
[SPEAKER_12]: Do you really expect that much racial diversity?
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm just saying.
[SPEAKER_12]: Listen, there was Def Jam.
[SPEAKER_12]: The game's a little white.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's all I'm saying.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, the game's a lot Asian.
[SPEAKER_02]: Listen, okay, you have 50 Cent Blood in the Sand coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: It evens itself out, okay?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's A-Z-N for reals, yo.
[SPEAKER_05]: Chat room, am I wrong?
[SPEAKER_05]: Am I a bad person for thinking this?
[SPEAKER_07]: Tell him he's wrong and he's a bad person for thinking it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Biohaze says black people are non-existent in the Street Fighter universe.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's not true.
[SPEAKER_05]: Balrog is... Yeah, since the beginning.
[SPEAKER_05]: Gunstar says Sagat is kind of like a brother and he kicks ass.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's Thai.
[SPEAKER_05]: and GameGuru says DJ was created by Capcom USA.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's something I didn't think of.
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember when they did Super Street Fighter?
[SPEAKER_05]: He was the character the USA made.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good observation, GameGuru.
[SPEAKER_05]: UnfoldedRaptor wants to point out there are green people.
[SPEAKER_05]: BioHaze says no more Mexicans.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can we have someone from Central or South America for once?
[SPEAKER_07]: We have Blanca.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's kind of a pity.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jimmy!
[SPEAKER_07]: Rolling and rolling.
[SPEAKER_07]: Go look at Dan's ending for Street Fighter 3, you'll know what I'm talking about.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know, and then I could also say, you don't really have a gay fighter either, but then people would say Vega, but Vega's not gay, he's just an asshole.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I think he's very gay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's the thing, he's not gay, he's just queer.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a difference.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think that Vega, actually I think Vega, well, off camera, really is a major, major crossdresser.
[SPEAKER_07]: A drag queen.
[SPEAKER_07]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_07]: With all that attention to his face, drag queen.
[SPEAKER_07]: Those shoes, look at the heels on those shoes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Drag queen.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actdeft says he's just metrosexual.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_07]: They're saying that it will not be out for a while, but it's going to be out for PC, PlayStation 3, and Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_07]: Basically saying that EA is behind it along with American McGee and we should be getting it out.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, yay.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they said it's going to be darker.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, the picture that they... More darker.
[SPEAKER_02]: More darker.
[SPEAKER_02]: The pictures they were teasing it with were like a bunch of snails trying to attack.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's the racing snail.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you think this could be because... I don't know if you guys know, but there's a new Alice in Wonderland movie coming out next year.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's being done by Tim Burton.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Johnny Depp is the Mad Hatter.
[SPEAKER_05]: The guy from Little Britain is Tweedledee and Tweedledum.
[SPEAKER_05]: They have some pretty interesting casting.
[SPEAKER_05]: The big guy from Little Britain is Tweedledee.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tim Burton Movies
[SPEAKER_07]: There's very few Tim Burton movies I don't... There's a man, though, who has gotten too full of himself and too stuck on his style.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I don't... Okay, I don't listen to him in interviews.
[SPEAKER_05]: Granted, I don't know the person.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just know his movies.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, you know, I like the movies.
[SPEAKER_08]: At least he's not George Lucas.
[SPEAKER_05]: At least there's always that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Going to chatroom, chat.orangeloungeradio.com VXJasonXV says, I like how Dark Sakura is personifying a made-up character.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hence Vega.
[SPEAKER_05]: DJ Ranma S asks, okay, Sky, would you date Vega?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, but I have dated guys that were that self-centered, just so you know.
[SPEAKER_05]: But no, I would not date Vega, based on previous experience.
[SPEAKER_05]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the City Vampire simply says, Tim Burton needs a haircut.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: That I would agree with.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, more gaming news, Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: First, a bit of random stuff while you guys were talking.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was trying to figure out exactly what you have to do in Nobi Nobi Boy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which apparently is eat things.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the other thing I found out is that you can eat a human and an animal or a human and a fruit or something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it will create hybrid creatures when it poops it out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you want... You can actually create ManBearPig?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: In your anus?
[SPEAKER_02]: In your anus.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, something not quite as exciting as anus ManBearPig.
[SPEAKER_02]: EA has announced a port of Dead Space for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's actually Dead Space Extraction.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be an on-rails shooter because obviously the Wii can't really hold up the...
[SPEAKER_02]: graphic detail of the 360 and PS3 versions but it will be kind of I guess a little bit like I guess Resident Evil Umbrella Chronicles but you know with Dead Space stuff so new weapons new enemies puzzles co-op multiplayer sounds kind of cool
[SPEAKER_02]: I like light gun shooter games on, uh, you know, I still haven't played the House of the Dead one that just came out.
[SPEAKER_02]: That looked interesting, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: That one didn't just come out, did it?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's been, it was a little while ago, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, House of the Dead Overkill, that came out a couple weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I didn't realize it was so recent.
[SPEAKER_05]: Was there another?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, no, it was like a compilation of prior games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, that's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was a year ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: Got it a little mixed up.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, uh, alright, well, you're a fan of rail shooters, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is this something you might get?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
Eh.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: All righty.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, hey, moving on to a completely different type of game, Leisure Suit Larry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember the old Sierra series, Leisure Suit Larry?
[SPEAKER_05]: You want to talk about the original boobs in video games, you got to go all the way back to Leisure Suit Larry.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, you know, they tried to bring the series back a couple years ago with a game that was kind of, eh, it was like a lukewarm reception game.
[SPEAKER_05]: And so we kind of thought, oh, this series is probably gone and best remembered in our memory.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, guess what?
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently, Leisure Suit Larry, Box Office Bust...
[SPEAKER_05]: It was a game that was kind of cut to the side after Activision and Blizzard merged.
[SPEAKER_05]: You might remember people were talking about Ghostbusters and Brutal Legends, some of these games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not a lot of people were talking about Leisure Suit Larry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, um...
[SPEAKER_05]: apparently Codemasters has actually jumped in it's one of their other branches Funsta which is a casual game branch of the company so that's a little interesting in my opinion but they have picked up the publishing rights to the game and the game is going to come out in April it's going to be on the PC, Playstation 3 and 360 and yes it's been rated mature by the ESRB no word if there's cocks um
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: It'll probably be... Let me see.
[SPEAKER_02]: The last game that came out, the casual games that they had in there, they had... I don't know if they had streaking in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I remember there was quarters, and they had this little... It was fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was a little minigame that you had to... You were a little sperm, and you had to dodge... That was the minigame I played at E3 a couple years ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, you had to dodge something.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't remember what it was.
[SPEAKER_02]: Stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: During the conversation, depending on how well you did, your conversation would be smoother or whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: You'd talk her out of her clothes.
[SPEAKER_02]: But if you hit stuff, you'd fart or make stupid comments and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it was pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I kind of liked the last game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, this one, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll check it out, but who knows.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: More information, I guess, on this to come.
[SPEAKER_05]: Probably a little closer to the release date in April.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, other stuff that's happening near April is a particular game that was very, very popular on Xbox Live Arcade coming to PC on March 31st, and that would be Braid.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's getting a price markup to $20.
[SPEAKER_07]: Think it's worth it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it...
[SPEAKER_02]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: You said you hadn't played the game, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you think you might check it out on PC?
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was worth asking.
[SPEAKER_05]: No!
[SPEAKER_05]: When do I have time?
[SPEAKER_05]: And the chatroom is confirming for me that Braid was 15.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, it came out a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought it was 10.
[SPEAKER_05]: So sue me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actdeft begs to differ in our chatroom.
[SPEAKER_05]: Chat.ArmstrongsRadio.com says Braid isn't really worth it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a very different type of puzzle game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mario is a puzzle game.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was very entertaining to me.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: I liked it a lot.
[SPEAKER_05]: And yes, I agree with Acidic Vampire.
[SPEAKER_05]: The soundtrack is beautiful.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, I'll stop interrupting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Speaking of the 360, there is more confirmation of a rumored Red Xbox 360 system coming soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently, the Red Xbox 360 Elite system was mentioned in a Microsoft press release from New Zealand.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it was saying that there was some sort of deal going on where you buy a 360 and get a free copy of
[SPEAKER_02]: Halo Wars, and that the red Xbox 360 Elite console, which is exclusive to EB Games.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I guess it's exclusive to EB Games there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe there's a red system coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe it's going to come out with Resident Evil.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe soon.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe they're doing red so that you don't notice the rings.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the joke I think that has to be made there.
[SPEAKER_05]: The rings blend in with it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Red seems like a really weird color for a video game system, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is it just me?
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, I get black, I get white, I get gray.
[SPEAKER_05]: I even get pink for the DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: I actually understand that.
[SPEAKER_05]: But red?
[SPEAKER_05]: It worked for the Virtual Boy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, no, it didn't.
[SPEAKER_05]: You saw nothing but red on the Virtual Boy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I could see them putting something like this out for a limited time or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: People might buy it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Even the Xbox being green, that made sense, actually.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have the Xbox that was green, the Halo one, not the regular black one.
[SPEAKER_05]: But yeah, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Red seems like a strange color, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: But okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe I'm just saying that because I know it would totally clash in my house.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sure if this were to actually exist, that they're going to be probably making an announcement very soon on it, since Resident Evil comes out in a few weeks.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, just assuming that it's actually going to be coming out with Resident Evil, not that I would know or anything, but I'm just saying, it's got to be soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hypothetically, I mean, that something like this would be coming out with Resident Evil, we'd have to know about it very soon, since that's only a few weeks away.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hypothetically speaking.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, evening in Japan?
[SPEAKER_05]: Dead Rising 2
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, because we've kind of had the hype for it the past week and it's been confirmed.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is it really that big of a secret?
[SPEAKER_05]: Or do we really think something new is going to come out of this?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because when I read this, I was like, it's just going to be Dead Rising 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or it could be something lame like Sheep.
[SPEAKER_05]: Was Capcom making the Sheep game?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, they're publishing it.
[SPEAKER_10]: They should do Black Sheep, the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Captain Commando HD Remix.
[SPEAKER_05]: They are 17 hours ahead, so they are about noon.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's about noon in Japan right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see more in a little while.
[SPEAKER_02]: I, for one, support the Captain Commando HD Remix.
[SPEAKER_05]: You think?
[SPEAKER_02]: Dude, I dumped so many quarters in that game, it's not even funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe Mega Man 10.
[SPEAKER_05]: I somehow doubt it.
[SPEAKER_02]: How about Area 50?
[SPEAKER_02]: What was that game?
[SPEAKER_02]: UN Squadron on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: UN Squadron.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have to interject.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've gotten the best reaction out of Drew ever.
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: I've shown him a copy of the Amazon page for the book I'm going to be ordering, Pride and Prejudice and Zombies, the classic Regency romance now with ultra-violent zombie mayhem.
[SPEAKER_05]: That would kind of tie into the whole Dead Rising thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wish.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dream on, I hate to say it.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, let's travel the world and look at some release dates that we actually know about.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or another Monster Hunter game, because they like making Monster Hunter.
[SPEAKER_05]: That would make sense for Japan, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: They didn't advertise that the trailer was going to be here, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, let's travel the world and look at some of the release dates that we know about.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll start off in Europe, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, coming out for the gaming systems and PCs and stuff in Europe.
[SPEAKER_07]: On the 27th, we have Castlevania Judgment on Wii, Cryostasis for PC, Dead Rising Chop Till You Drop on Wii, Family Ski and Snowboard on Wii, Halo Wars for Xbox 360, Killzone 2 for PlayStation 3, Men of War on PC, Necrovision on PC, um...
[SPEAKER_07]: Onei Chambara, Bikini Samurai Squad, and Bikini Zombie Slayers.
[SPEAKER_07]: First for 360, second for Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: Silent Hill Homecoming on Xbox 360, PlayStation 3, and PC.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Ultimate Band on DS and Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: The end.
[SPEAKER_02]: And remember, Flock was a sheep one by Capcom.
[SPEAKER_02]: Boring!
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think that's that, but, you know, you never know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways, next week's actually pretty exciting for game releases.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's some pretty good stuff coming out, including Star Ocean Last Hope on Xbox 360, which should be pretty epic.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pretty good reviews so far.
[SPEAKER_02]: 50 Cent Blood on the Sand on PS3 and Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hell yes!
[SPEAKER_02]: Shellshock 2 Blood Trails on PS3, Xbox 360, and PC Legacy of Ys Book 1 and 2 on DS Puzzle Quest Galactrix on DS Dead Rising Chop Till You Drop on the Wii
[SPEAKER_02]: Stoked on Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a pretty fun snowboarding game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Imagine Ice Champions on DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: Supposedly, EAT led the return of Matt Hazard.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hope that comes out that week, because I thought it was the week after, but you never know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Killzone 2 on PS3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Peggle on DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: My Personal Diary on DS, Puzzle Challenges and more on Wii.
[SPEAKER_05]: UnfoldedRaptor in chat says, Blood on the sand is going to be game of the year.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just watch.
[SPEAKER_05]: Chat.OrangeLaunchRadio.com live on Sunday nights.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm tempted to buy it just to see.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a part of me that wants to buy it, but it's probably going to be $60, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: It is going to be $60.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't buy it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll wait for it to hit the bargain bin.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dude, do you know what I saw at Best Buy the other day?
[SPEAKER_05]: A Rock Revolution bundle for $30.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's drums and game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I think that's just slightly under what they normally cost now.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's that bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought about it, because you can use the drums with other games, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, but they suck that bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, I mean, hey, if you want, get the game for the download content, because they have some of the Guitar Freak stuff in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ah, that's a good reason.
[SPEAKER_02]: Think about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Samurai Dough 3 Samurai Dough 3
[SPEAKER_05]: and Rainbow Six Vegas 2 also gets a price reduction.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it's a good week for some sales over there in Japan.
[SPEAKER_05]: Moving on to the PlayStation 3, NBA Live gets a price reduction.
[SPEAKER_05]: Otherwise, as far as a new game goes, Ryu Ga Gotoku comes out, number three in the series.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not sure what this is.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Yakuza 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just Yakuza 3?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Looks like you can get some romance on in this one.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll get some screenshots from that.
[SPEAKER_02]: If they have chicks, you can pick up.
[SPEAKER_05]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: I know there's some King of Fighter fans in the house.
[SPEAKER_05]: And on the Nintendo DS, kind of a range of games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dragon Dance, Game Center CX, Arino no Chosenju comes out as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: A voice chat DS application comes out as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: As Kameko Deluxe DS, Yome Tomeka to Otoko to Ona comes out.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that is...
[SPEAKER_05]: Looks like a little girly adventure game, but there's bowling in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if it's like a mini game collection or what, but there's like a little bowling mini game in that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Probably not something we're going to get over here.
[SPEAKER_05]: And lastly, on the PSP, again, in Japan, because sometimes they get stuff before we do, you get a port of Dragon Dance, and Common No Maid Guy, Boyoyan Battle Royale comes out.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's an adventure game, not to be confused with the Battle Royale movie that we all know and love, but it does have girls in schoolgirl outfits, and it looks like they're fighting each other.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's based off the manga series.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is it?
[SPEAKER_05]: And they attack each other with brooms.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is this like maids fighting each other?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what it looks like.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know what it... Yeah, it's in the title.
[SPEAKER_05]: Common, no maid.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maid games are like... Anything maids are like major, major big fetish deals, so... Well, there you have it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you fetish fans, get that on PSP.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, your memories off, girl style.
[SPEAKER_05]: At least that wasn't called your panties off.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow, that's an adventure game.
[SPEAKER_06]: If it was, that'd be an instant purchase.
[SPEAKER_05]: You might want to go women's style, not girls' style for that.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then lastly, Shin Sangoku Musou Multirade comes out on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's an action game that looks a little Final Fantasy-ish, but with some live-action elements in it, it looks like.
[SPEAKER_05]: So check that out on PSP if you're in Japan.
[SPEAKER_05]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_05]: That does it for your PSP release date.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or if you want to get it for your friends in America who do a show for you every Sunday.
[SPEAKER_05]: And DJ Ranma S in chatroom says, yes, maid games do sell.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know I sell a lot of hentai maid games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, how about something that has absolutely nothing to do with maids?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, please.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bobsleds!
[SPEAKER_05]: How about maid in a bobsled?
[SPEAKER_07]: You know there is someone out there who has a fetish for maids on bobsleds.
[SPEAKER_07]: But no.
[SPEAKER_05]: If so, this show's for you.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is high speed bobsled racing from Sega.
[SPEAKER_07]: God, Sega, why do you do this to me?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's called Storm G and it's a deluxe cabinet set where they've got them all lined up.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's supposed to have you bobsledding in rocket-powered blobs, blobs, bobsleds.
[SPEAKER_07]: Boob sledding?
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Each sled, though... That would be cold!
[SPEAKER_08]: Too cold!
[SPEAKER_07]: Each sled, though, accommodates two people, and it has twin joysticks, and each person controls different aspects... Boobs and twin joysticks.
[SPEAKER_07]: Each joystick controls different aspects of it to do 360-degree rotation and increase your speed.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think the maid fans would like this game.
[SPEAKER_05]: It sounds pretty hot.
[SPEAKER_07]: At any rate, it's like a 10 minute game and you pay about 650 to play at 600 yen.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's already at the Joyopolis in March.
[SPEAKER_07]: For any of our Japanese listeners, go there and take pictures of it and get signs of it in play.
[SPEAKER_07]: We really, really want to see what it's like.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have fun boob sledding with your twin joysticks at Joyopolis.
[SPEAKER_05]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, if Rocket Bob Sledding isn't for you, there are some other games coming out as well that are equally epic, including the brand new game running on Sega's new hardware, Ring Edge, and the game's called Border Break.
[SPEAKER_02]: You may remember it as, well, it's sort of like Virtual Lawn, actually, but played a little bit more linear, kind of like Armored Core.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's a mech action fighting game.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: Got two out of four right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, there is a little twist to this because I don't actually... I'm not pooping money.
[SPEAKER_05]: I actually would be buying these new toys that are coming out.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's coming out from... Organic is the name of the toy maker.
[SPEAKER_05]: They are taking classic Sega arcade cabinets and shrinking them down to like four inches in length.
[SPEAKER_05]: And those are the four cabinets they're going to be releasing as these little figurine toys.
[SPEAKER_07]: These are like little gachapon, basically.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: But the capsule game stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, no, they're actual arcade cabinet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like they're toys that look like the little cabinets.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what I'm saying.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're little capsule toys.
[SPEAKER_07]: You buy the box and you get a random one out of each box.
[SPEAKER_05]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_05]: It doesn't say if they're actual capsule toys or what the thing is going on.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I don't think they're playable.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's for sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: But those little things, those are very, very, very popular.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, getting all the various character and goods that come up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Capcom's actually got a series of little figures for some of the female characters.
[SPEAKER_05]: By the way, there is a fifth cabinet that's a secret, according to the website.
[SPEAKER_07]: Secret my ass.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what that is?
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's a... Well, no, it can't be a... Could it be Afterburner?
[SPEAKER_07]: It can't be an Afterburner, because Afterburner is a closed machine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yeah, because it went a little high.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, actually, no, I think it might be an afterburner if they had the cover off of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe it's a House of the Dead.
[SPEAKER_02]: No?
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I don't think you sat down with that one.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, these are all classic cabinets, so it can't be... Space Harrier?
[SPEAKER_07]: It can't be the... There you go, Space Harrier.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, no, you know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: Honestly, I think it is an afterburner because Space Harrier, if I'm right, had the closed top, too, and this figure doesn't.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it just kind of makes sense, too, with the other games.
[SPEAKER_05]: It would fit in.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll probably see when these things come out in the future weeks.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, it's one of those Sega 360 machines.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I don't know about some of these.
[SPEAKER_05]: Acidic Vampire says, WTF?
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't play it if it's four inches.
[SPEAKER_05]: Game Guru says, next up, a miniature Mega Drive.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_08]: Metal Gear Movie
[SPEAKER_07]: And you know how pissed off I was that they were taking my man off of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, guess what?
[SPEAKER_05]: And your man is?
[SPEAKER_07]: David Hader.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's back on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, he didn't come right out and say it, but he danced around saying everything, but yes, I'm back.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, at an interview, and actually, I'm going to go ahead and actually post a link up to the article, because there's a copy of the interview on there.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's on Kotaku.
[SPEAKER_07]: But in an interview he was basically saying that there's a possibility of involvement in being back on it instead of just saying no.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I'll be posting that in the chat room so everyone can watch the interview.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Makes me happy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know you love David Hayter.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, hell yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, he gave us the first X-Men movie.
[SPEAKER_07]: And he's the voice of Solid Snake, so it makes sense.
[SPEAKER_07]: He should just play Snake.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, another movie that may have been at one time, but I don't think it's coming out anytime soon, if at all, Mega Man, the movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently, Warner Brothers, at one time, was trying to acquire the rights for the Mega Man series to turn it into a feature film.
[SPEAKER_05]: God, no, please don't.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know this would be terrible.
[SPEAKER_05]: It would be absolute shit if they were to do this as a movie, unless it was animated.
[SPEAKER_05]: You could not do a live-action Mega Man movie, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, Capcom, the creators, are wary, letting anyone touch the project after a few disastrous licensing moves with the property as well as the recent so-so reaction to other movie adaptions.
[SPEAKER_02]: The most recent movie made that the suits...
[SPEAKER_02]: The most recent move made was that the suits asked Capcom for a wish list of directors, and Shyamalan, that's right, as in M. Night Shyamalan, was one of the names they came back with.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: M. Night Shyamalan movies have gotten progressively worse, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but here's the thing, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's trying to break out from doing... I did like The Village.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Enough of the actual M. Night Shyamalan movies that he writes and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's actually trying to break out from doing those types of movies, and that's why he's doing the live-action Avatar movie, which is based off the Nickelodeon animated series.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, if that turns out okay, then maybe he can...
[SPEAKER_02]: GameGuru in chat says Avatar the movie will flop
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, granted, a lot of it is still just palette swapping, but they've actually been able to insert some cutscenes into it that fit with the Final Fantasy X story.
[SPEAKER_05]: The water scene between Tidus and Yuna is in there, which is kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: And look at that title screen just alone.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like, oh my gosh, I can't believe they actually worked that into an 8-bit cartridge.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's very impressive.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, but seriously, you've got a lot of time on your hands if you're doing that kind of detail.
[SPEAKER_10]: Seriously, I'm actually going to play through this.
[SPEAKER_10]: Totally.
[SPEAKER_10]: Looks better than that Chinese Final Fantasy VII that was out a little while ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it does look a lot better than the Final Fantasy VII, I'll give you that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Looks a lot better than that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, in GameGuru it says, wasn't there a Final Fantasy VII NES ROM hack?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, there was.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, there you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, so let's move into the classic video game of the week.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, every week here at Orange Lounge Radio, we tell you guys, go into your classic archives and find an old game to pay some respect to.
[SPEAKER_05]: And DarkSakura digs through her own huge archive of games.
[SPEAKER_05]: You told me how many systems, you and Dan counted, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: I think we came up to 30 to 32, something like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Systems?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's crazy.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you've dug through all those archives.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's non-import, non-duplicate systems.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's crazy.
[SPEAKER_07]: With the imports, we get up to 40.
[SPEAKER_07]: 40-ish.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you still don't have a Pippin.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's up with that?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, anyhow, let's go ahead and look at the classic video game of the week, which if I'm not mistaken is pretty topical this week, right DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_07]: But before we say the name, you've got to play the music because I know people are going to get it right away.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, then let me fire up the music here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here's a return of video game music to you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, now we all get it, don't we?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, it's the Puzzle Fighter theme.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bite my butt.
[SPEAKER_07]: The game is Street Fighter Alpha 2 or Street Fighter Zero 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I don't mention the first one because as awesome as the first one was, the second one was the best.
[SPEAKER_11]: The first game is no longer canon.
[SPEAKER_11]: The second game replaced the first game's storyline.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, what he said.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, Street Fighter Alpha 2 basically was the game that gave us the annoying things called Alpha Counters, which I actually kind of like, but I hate doing them by accident.
[SPEAKER_07]: We have the three-level super combo gauge, air blocking, and fall breaking.
[SPEAKER_07]: And thank God we didn't get parrying in that one, like in Street Fighter 3, because parrying while cool was a pain in the ass.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, so basically, it's, uh, and I honestly think this is pretty much the pinnacle of the Street Fighter series, because Alpha 3 was kind of ass, except for some of the characters in it, and I hated the A-ism, B-ism, I hated taking all that shit.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, anyway, this also had Akuma as a regular character, or as he was in the Japanese version, Golki, which I think is a better name, especially if you consider the current storyline that it was Golki versus Golken.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, anyway, so you actually got Shin Akuma as your secret opponent.
[SPEAKER_07]: Everyone brought in the rival thing, which I was really glad they put that in Street Fighter IV, the whole...
[SPEAKER_07]: And then, um, you also, um, have, uh, Instantly Selectable, you have Bison, um, who was...
[SPEAKER_07]: Vega in the Japanese version, Akuma and Dan.
[SPEAKER_07]: You also got three characters who are returning from other games.
[SPEAKER_07]: You've got Zangief and Dhalsim, and then you got Gen, who was from the first Street Fighter game.
[SPEAKER_07]: You also got Rolento from Final Fight, and Sakura, who was the first original new character for that series, and I thought it was really cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, even for the second one that came out, for Alpha 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway,
[SPEAKER_07]: I was very happy though when they started bringing in the Final Fight characters because I freaking love Final Fight.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've been collecting every version of Final Fight, except for the American-made crap versions.
[SPEAKER_11]: Didn't Dan count as an original character as well?
[SPEAKER_07]: on top of that, for anyone who doesn't know he's totally a parody of Art of Fighting because Rio and Robert Garcia were combined to make Dan, he was a big joke however, if you can beat the game with him mad props to you if you can beat Puzzle Fighter with him, mad props to you so Drew says real men play Dan
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, so you've got all your characters.
[SPEAKER_07]: You have, you know, basically different versions of them.
[SPEAKER_07]: You've got arcade versions on the consoles.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, this is going to be me bitching for just a moment.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Super NES... Well, the other two ran out.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like Chun-Li.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is a game where I decided that Chun-Li is a bitch.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, there was a Super Nintendo version of this released in 96.
[SPEAKER_07]: I had this for a while before it was removed from my possession without me knowing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Die.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was the version that made use of the SDD-1 chip for graphic decompression.
[SPEAKER_07]: So guess what it put into a cartridge game?
[SPEAKER_07]: Load time.
[SPEAKER_07]: It had, now loading, in a freaking SNES cartridge, it had to decompress and load.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I'm like, damn, this is slow.
[SPEAKER_07]: There was also a PC version that was based off the PlayStation version.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was okay, I actually have that somewhere in my house.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, there was the home versions that came out of Street Fighter Alpha 2 Gold, um, which in Japan came out of Street Fighter Zero 2 Dash.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, um, it was also part of the Street Fighter collection that was a big compilation.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, and then there was, um, the, uh, in the Gold version it had Kami based on her X-Men vs. Street Fighter appearance.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um.
[SPEAKER_07]: and it was she was actually a hidden character character that was selectable in the versus and training modes so that was pretty cool also on PlayStation 2 we got Street Fighter Alpha Anthology which is more like the arcade version of the game it was pretty cool
[SPEAKER_07]: I've actually got both the Saturn and the PlayStation versions.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the Saturn version, way better.
[SPEAKER_07]: Way better.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's far better than the PlayStation version was.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, anything 2D, practically, the Saturn version is going to be better.
[SPEAKER_07]: Better colors, better... It can handle 2D graphics and sound so much better than the PlayStation version.
[SPEAKER_07]: At any rate...
[SPEAKER_07]: They actually... In 1996, Dan won number one video game character, and Sakura won number three video game character, which I thought was funny.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was actually in Gamest Magazine, which is a Japanese magazine.
[SPEAKER_07]: Got best fighting game, number nine best in graphics, number six best direction, number four best video game music.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: And...
[SPEAKER_07]: it's seriously oh you got roses roses in Street Fighter 4 I thought it was cool yep um but it's it's just a really it to me it is the pinnacle of the Street Fighter series I mean I love Street Fighter 4 and I actually I like Street Fighter 3 for just playing as Ibuki um but other than that I mean Street Fighter Alpha 2 is like the top of it for me it does not get better than that
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, well there you have it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Your classic video game of the week, Street Fighter Alpha 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: A very good topical pick, considering the game that's on everybody's mind this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have to take a minute to respect the classics that help inspire some of the appearances you see in Street Fighter 4, such as Rose, and Sakura, and Dan, and so on.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's going to do it for Part A of our show.
[SPEAKER_05]: But don't go anywhere.
[SPEAKER_05]: Darn it.
[SPEAKER_05]: We've got plenty more of our show to come up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Part B. Since Drew and Joe and everybody joined us late, I'll ask them about their gaming weeks at the start of Part B. And then we have some stuff to get into as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to talk about the DSi.
[SPEAKER_05]: Finally got a release date in North America.
[SPEAKER_05]: Confirming some earlier rumors that were floating around out there.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's so weird.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's so weird how that happens.
[SPEAKER_05]: Going to talk about some video game law here in California and some other Wii rumors.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't go anywhere.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll be right back with more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Welcome back, everybody, to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here on this lovely Sunday evening, February the 22nd of 2009.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're watching Loki playing Noby Noby Boy on Justin.TV and just giggling at the little farting noises it's making.
[SPEAKER_07]: The secret word, Rob, is parakeet.
Ah!
[SPEAKER_05]: Space Squirrel in the corner What kind of games have you been playing lately?
[SPEAKER_12]: Pretty good.
[SPEAKER_12]: Kim came to visit, so brought over the PS2, played some Karaoke Revolution, some Guitar Hero, King of Fighters 06, and surprisingly, a little bit of the original Naruto Ultimate Ninja.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know why we were playing it, but we were playing it.
[SPEAKER_12]: I wanted to because I was bored.
[SPEAKER_08]: You asked for it.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're the one who suggested it, not me.
[SPEAKER_12]: I just so happen to bring it with me
[SPEAKER_10]: I actually picked up Need for Speed Underground.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, how's that?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want to get the second one.
[SPEAKER_05]: How is it different from other Need for Speed games?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's a lot of emphasis on tuning your car.
[SPEAKER_10]: Making it look cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it's like pimp my ride?
[SPEAKER_10]: Pretty much.
[SPEAKER_10]: Only more fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: We got you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Cool, cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, it looks like Loki's got everything switched back on Justin.TV from our break.
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_05]: What happened?
[SPEAKER_05]: We not getting audio over there?
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_05]: There might be some feedback.
[SPEAKER_05]: Live radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course, we do tape live on Sunday nights at allgames.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: They don't see video, just audio for some reason on Justin.TV.
[SPEAKER_05]: But again, Justin.TV is not the top priority.
[SPEAKER_05]: We are trying to do a radio show, so we'll figure it out one way or another, I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, I want to get back into gaming news, but we need Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Nintendo DSi was announced this week that it would be coming out in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_05]: and the rest of North America on April 5th.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which is pretty close to estimates made by certain media outlets.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it will be coming out in the North American region in two different colors.
[SPEAKER_02]: Both black and kind of a light blue.
[SPEAKER_02]: And will be retailing for $169.99.
[SPEAKER_02]: Neat, I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not probably going to pick one up myself.
[SPEAKER_02]: But...
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Super Game!
[SPEAKER_05]: Swap cartridges, I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: The problem with the blue DSi for me, and we have Actdeft in chat, says, I like the blue DSi.
[SPEAKER_05]: The problem with the blue DSi for me, it's one of my high school's colors.
[SPEAKER_05]: My old high school, that was actually one of their colors.
[SPEAKER_05]: That gross, light blue type color.
[SPEAKER_05]: Blah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not my favorite.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also coming out on April 5th, a game that I'm sure a lot of our long-time listeners who are into music games, since that's what we started on, would be interested in.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rhythm Heaven, also known as, of course, Rhythm Tengoku overseas.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rhythm Heaven is going to be coming out on April 5th as well as the DSi systems.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just so you know, this game was made by the same people that made WarioWare.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's something like that, but it's more with music.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's really hard to explain this game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I played it at PAX.
[SPEAKER_05]: So this game has kind of been ready a little while, but it's kind of some cool little musical mini-games.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I think there'll be a lot of folks that enjoy that.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I love this little alien character in the game too, and I've seen that on people's live journal icons and stuff, so there you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that is coming out as well on April 5th, and I'm sure there'll be plenty of folks getting copies of that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, there's actually supposed to be more games coming out.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're saying that they're working on an adaptation of Katamari Damacy and Mr. Driller for the DSiWare, according to Famitsu, anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's also going to be a Wii game of Mr. Driller, Mr. Driller World, that has a DS version that's supposed to be called... Oh my god, how am I going to pronounce this?
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, I'm going to try...
[SPEAKER_05]: I butcher names all the time in the Japanese release dates.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sekuto Hamureru Horihori Action which will have 17 levels to be out in Japan next week.
[SPEAKER_07]: So there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alpha Catanagram in chat says that Katamari game is just a re-skinned pack attack.
[SPEAKER_05]: Cheap.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not surprising.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, they better make these releases good or people are going to say all these DSi things are cheap.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know why, for whatever reason, I guess us Americans can't handle white.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's gotta be blue.
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting as well that Europe usually gets screwed by Nintendo on release dates, but now it's...
[SPEAKER_05]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: They finally signed a budget middle of last week after what, like 106, 109 days, something crazy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, maybe they didn't pass the budget on time because they were too busy dealing with video game laws.
[SPEAKER_05]: And guess what?
[SPEAKER_05]: The Ninth Circuit Court of Appeals came down this week and said that the California game law has been stricken.
[SPEAKER_05]: Basically, they came out and placed a permanent injunction on it and it's no longer there.
[SPEAKER_05]: The ESA President Michael Gallagher says this is a win, saying it sends a clear signal that these types of reckless legislations, it's wasting taxpayers' money, government time, and state resources.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course, Leland Yee, who has been heavily involved in this bill and everything, is pushing for California to appeal the ruling to the Supreme Court.
[SPEAKER_05]: By the way, I believe as a part of this, we will have to pay the ESV fees.
[SPEAKER_05]: or ESA fees for this, just like another state had to do not that long ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: I remember we covered on the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: What a great thing for a broke state to be doing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe you guys should just give up on that whole thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: So whenever we talk about these video game laws and them trying to censor video games and all this stuff, we get angsty.
[SPEAKER_05]: And when we get angsty, FUs of the Week happen.
[SPEAKER_07]: Believe it or not, I don't have any FUs.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I take that back, I do.
[SPEAKER_07]: FU to people who don't know how to grow the fuck up.
[SPEAKER_07]: And before anyone says anything, it's not who people may think I'm talking about, so... I knew you were talking about me.
[SPEAKER_05]: I knew it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bitch!
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm gonna cut you.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, shoot, okay, I'm not gonna go into detail, but I have...
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, I'll go into a little detail.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have a friend who, as long as I have known this person...
[SPEAKER_07]: All righty, Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Happy for the second week in a row to the weather for ruining yet another Airsoft outing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was supposed to be going on Sunday today, this morning.
[SPEAKER_02]: However, it is raining and will continue to rain until next Sunday.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's so retarded.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was clear all week long and then fucking rained on Sunday.
[SPEAKER_02]: The day that I'm going.
[SPEAKER_02]: So fuck you, Mother Nature.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fuck you right up your ass.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is it possible to fuck Mother Nature in her ass?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, I just, I'm gonna say an FU to the fact I'm kinda hungry, and so I'm gonna eat something soon.
[SPEAKER_05]: FU to hunger pains.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh, Drew, you got any FUs?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: First off, FU to shitty service at... Huh?
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, FU to shitty service at the Arden Fair Mall today.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: 20 minutes to prepare a meal at the Hibachi.
[SPEAKER_12]: What the fuck?
[SPEAKER_12]: I order.
[SPEAKER_12]: Somehow there's a line formed.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, let's not go to Panda Express.
[SPEAKER_12]: Let's go to Hibachi-san.
[SPEAKER_12]: Let's go to Hibachi-san, I said.
[SPEAKER_12]: There's no line, I said.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_12]: On top of everything else, we try to get portraits taken.
[SPEAKER_12]: And that shit takes an hour and a half.
[SPEAKER_12]: Causing us to be late for the show.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm not too pleased.
[SPEAKER_12]: Also, fuck you to the weather.
[SPEAKER_12]: Fuck it in its fucking ear.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm sick and tired of it.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's sunny and then suddenly it rains.
[SPEAKER_12]: Way to end the week on a good note.
[SPEAKER_12]: Kim, did you have anything?
[SPEAKER_08]: F you to being sick.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hate being sick on vacation.
[SPEAKER_08]: It sucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Being sick does suck.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Joe, do you have anything for our listeners for angst?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, fuck being hungry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fuck being hungry.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, let's get back into some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dark Sakura.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was a very interesting way that you just said my name.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, Disney!
[SPEAKER_07]: Disney is bringing Spectrobes Origins to Wii, supposed to be coming out in the fall.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's motion sensing, you know, large real-time battle thing, full 3D RPG world, blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah.
[SPEAKER_07]: So there are the two DS versions, Spectrobes and Spectrobes Beyond the Portals, are already everywhere, so it's more Spectrobes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yay?
[SPEAKER_07]: The end.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay, the end.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's supposed to be pretty good.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's not a game I'm remotely interested in, but from what I hear, it's supposed to be pretty good.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's been popular, I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is it maybe just for a particular audience?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, well, what they're doing now, they're actually launching, I think, a cartoon as well, which will help because it's kind of like Pokemon.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, the game is very Pokemon, Digimon-esque, so...
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, really not from my age group at all.
[SPEAKER_12]: Wait, Refresh Memory Spectrums, wasn't that gimmicky bullshit game where you had to yell at the things to turn them into little monsters?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't remember that, but it was the one that had the special cards that you place over the DS touchscreen where you tap the spots and it will unlock different things.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, so anyways, it's supposed to be pretty decent.
[SPEAKER_02]: At least they're trying to be innovative with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, you know, I don't know, maybe they'll bring their D-Gamer service over onto the Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: That'd be pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I doubt it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I doubt it a lot.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways, if you're not interested though in Spectrobes, there are some rumors of other games that are coming out that might be worth it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Brutal Legends is rumored to possibly coming out to the Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's some other stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently this is all from EA and Activision's 2009 lineup.
[SPEAKER_02]: Activision's DJ Hero is tentatively scheduled for July.
[SPEAKER_02]: It seems like a weird time to put that out if that were actually the case.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently, DJ Hero will feature a three... The peripheral will feature three colored buttons, a turntable, and a fader.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, if that's the case, they're in for a lawsuit.
[SPEAKER_02]: This second LEGO Indiana Jones game will be out apparently before Christmas.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can see that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Activision will release a new Guitar Hero song pack around the holiday season.
[SPEAKER_02]: That kind of goes in line with, I think there was a Guitar Hero Greatest Hits or something like that they're planning on putting out.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that might make sense.
[SPEAKER_02]: Star Wars Battlefront 3 is still live but probably won't be out until 2010.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, of course that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because, you know, even though, was it...
[SPEAKER_02]: Not Pandemic, who am I thinking of?
[SPEAKER_02]: Ah, whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Still, a game like that, very epic.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course they're going to make another one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Those are all rumors for right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rumors.
[SPEAKER_05]: Things that we might see a little more of at E3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, well, going to the DJ Hero thing, you know, I've seen prototypes of the other DJ game coming out in...
[SPEAKER_02]: If that's the case, if it's got a crossfader and stuff, that makes me kind of wonder if there might be a lawsuit because their controller looks very similar.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, Lego.
[SPEAKER_05]: Gosh, those Lego games.
[SPEAKER_05]: They sure know how to sell.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Lego Batman, the Lego Star Wars, Lego Indiana Jones.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, guess what's next?
[SPEAKER_05]: Lego Prince of Persia
[SPEAKER_05]: But you never know, could be a game later on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lego Harry Potter's the next one, for sure.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, other than Lego Battles, but in Lego MMO, maybe Lego Racers.
[SPEAKER_05]: No Lego Prince of Persia game yet, but Lego Prince of Persia toys are definitely going to be happening.
[SPEAKER_02]: I could see them doing a Lego Harry Potter game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I could really see that too.
[SPEAKER_05]: The audiences kind of go hand in hand.
[SPEAKER_05]: Veto Veto Veto Veto Veto
[SPEAKER_05]: Me giving DarkSakura the finger makes for great radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Although Justin TV can see it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bob's a cheeky monkey.
[SPEAKER_07]: Cheeky monkey.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, males.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, one's kind of a plug.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sure you saw this email.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to go ahead and plug it.
[SPEAKER_05]: A plug.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: We hear from Redertainment.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Hawk by Hunter Red Novel
[SPEAKER_07]: Free distribution online.
[SPEAKER_07]: Advocate literacy.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, first actual email.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can see DarkSakura doing a PSA for reading.
[SPEAKER_05]: Read, goddammit!
[SPEAKER_07]: Read or you're crap!
[SPEAKER_04]: Read something, you idiot!
[SPEAKER_07]: Illiteracy is stupid!
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, now...
[SPEAKER_07]: Additionally, with regard to you and your wind complaints tonight, it could be worse.
[SPEAKER_07]: At least you folks don't have planes crashing in your area, just in case other listeners don't remember me mentioning it before.
[SPEAKER_07]: I live in Buffalo, New York.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, we do have planes crashing in our area.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was one that crashed, I think, in Elk Grove or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't hear about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: The guy was doing takeoff and touchdown landings and one of those landings he forgot to lower the landing gear and caught the plane on fire.
[SPEAKER_02]: So no one got hurt.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was only one pilot.
[SPEAKER_02]: But still, it's a plane crash.
[SPEAKER_02]: It counts.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's a crash due to stupid.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, in case you haven't read, seen, listened to the news for the last past few days, there was a commercial plane crash, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, Buffalo, last Thursday night, specifically in the suburb of Clarence, at least, you're just dealing with wind.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, you've been negated.
[SPEAKER_07]: If I may, and if DarkSakura has time to read this, I'd just like to say hi, in quotes, to the Dark Fury link shell on the Alexander server in Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_07]: Add it!
[SPEAKER_07]: And specifically to Jaden, Nagiko, and Digby Reloaded.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now go play a real game.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was from Spazinator.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm always so rude.
[SPEAKER_07]: Go play a real game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Play Perfect World.
[SPEAKER_05]: I spent years and years and years on Final Fantasy XI, just in case you guys don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: And City of Heroes, I'm sorry, is WoW without the suck.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's WoW with Barbie.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's WoW with superheroes.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's WoW with Barbie mode.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's fun!
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh my god, making the superhero, and you can save them.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just let me know when the hell I can debate it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's so great.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've made so many superhero costumes in the last week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because every time I would actually try to log in and play the damn game, lose connection, log out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dope.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, that's another story.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, was that it for mailbag?
[SPEAKER_05]: Last email.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh no, one more, yay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jeez, Rob, I could just not read it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, when I went in there earlier, there was only like two emails, so I'm happy to hear there's more emails.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, it's actually from the same guy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because he sent the email late.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, there we go.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll just read it anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi, folks, I just wanted to comment on a few things.
[SPEAKER_07]: Firstly, firstly is not a word, okay?
[SPEAKER_07]: Just say first, or first of all, or...
[SPEAKER_07]: In the beginning, no, FYI, I sent you an email last week during, during, only should have one R in it, thank you.
[SPEAKER_07]: But apparently, I sent it too late.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not T-O-T-O-O, thank you.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry, you send late emails, you get grammar-nated.
[SPEAKER_07]: Needless to say, that it can be disregarded simply because I ended up calling in and repeated what was in the email.
[SPEAKER_07]: Secondly, like, okay, Rob, your name is not Robb.
[SPEAKER_07]: I ended up getting Flower too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe he was drunk when he did the email.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_07]: I agree, it's a great game and very beautiful.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not only that, but it's rather relaxing.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hate to call it a casual game, seeing as the term doesn't quite seem to fit the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rather, I think calling Flower a zen game seems to describe it a bit better.
[SPEAKER_07]: By the way, here's an easy way to get two trophies for it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Play a level as normal, go do something for 10 minutes between levels, and bam, one trophy unlocked.
[SPEAKER_07]: Another one can be unlocked by simply backing out of the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fast forward the system clock by a week and re-enter the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Then you'll get the second trophy.
[SPEAKER_05]: What do you think though about the analogy that it's a racing game?
[SPEAKER_05]: Flowers is just a big fruity racing game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sure the email, if it could grow sentience and speak on its own on behalf of Spazinator, it would probably tell you boobs.
[SPEAKER_07]: On an unrelated note, Rob commented that $60 for a game is kind of expensive, especially if you're only somewhat into a given series.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I would just like to point out that with the previous gen systems in their games...
[SPEAKER_07]: When taking inflation into consideration, the older games are just as expensive as current-gen games, and in some situations, even more expensive.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, thank you for allowing me to throw in my two cents.
[SPEAKER_07]: Inflation, dude, it should be two bucks, and better bring chocolate with that.
[SPEAKER_07]: This email is sponsored by GTA 4, Lost in the Damned, and Oscar Mayer, home of the never-ending supply of wieners.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like being a rampaging bitch.
[SPEAKER_05]: Quote Flower No, I didn't play Flower until this week No, I was talking about the $60 No, I was reading the comment in chat
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_05]: Next week's show is on the server.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just need to push it to the podcast feed.
[SPEAKER_05]: We do it a little differently now on the new website.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I kind of botched the first one, I think.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'm being a little careful before I do 3.13.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I am trying to get the podcast all caught up so people don't complain anymore.
[SPEAKER_05]: So there we go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, let's move back into some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_05]: More emails though.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com Don't send them.
[SPEAKER_08]: Send them, please.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm being silly.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, apparently, once again, there's more rumors pointing to the next Tony Hawk game using a brand new skateboarding controller.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sure we're going to see this at E3.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it only makes sense that they're going to pull this stuff out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Variety is confirming this, saying their sources show a new controller along with some details.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently, it won't be about precise balance.
[SPEAKER_02]: Instead, it will be about grabbing and manipulating the board to pull all sorts of tricks from which Tony Hawk games are known for.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Something tells me that this... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why can't we just have the Tony Hawk Pro Skater stuff where it was fun, it was whimsical, you're pulling off tricks in a mall or something ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or why can't we just fire Tony Hawk out of a cannon at this point?
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I'm just kind of done.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not Tony Hawk's fault, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: This is just like the same argument that an actor ruins a movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, that may be the case sometimes, but it's not Tony Hawk's fault.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Activision's fault.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why can't we fire Activision out of a cannon?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: None of cannons.
[SPEAKER_02]: Will it blend?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, it will blend.
[SPEAKER_07]: It will blend because the blending blades are made of the hairs from Chuck Norris' legs.
[SPEAKER_05]: Great.
[SPEAKER_05]: Baron's chat has leaked into Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you know that that's not true because there's nothing that could cut a hair on Chuck Norris' leg.
[SPEAKER_02]: Die!
[SPEAKER_07]: But he can make them out himself and market them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good point.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: VIRTUA COP
[SPEAKER_05]: And this was in an interview with Cube3.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is the producer, Neil McEwan.
[SPEAKER_05]: He said they would love to do Virtua Cop or another light gun game for Sega.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, there you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently, the whole House of the Dead thing came to be when they were meeting with Sega about possibly doing a game in one of their franchises, and House of the Dead is what was settled on.
[SPEAKER_05]: However, if they continue, and you know this game does well, and they decide they want to do another game, could Virtua Cop be a possibility?
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know how y'all feel about that, but it could be interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do I gotta... Yeah, and GameGuru in chat says, Sega, let them do Virtua Cop.
[SPEAKER_05]: Shadowchari says, yes!
[SPEAKER_07]: Virtua Cop would actually be pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: I had a lot of fun playing it when it was new.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: The whole Virtua series, they should just rename Virtua Fighter to, oh look, another 3D fighter.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or Virtua Cop 2, look, another gun game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Something like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, there's something wonderful that came out to Club Nintendo members in Japan.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was special.
[SPEAKER_07]: They could get a Wii controller that looked like an SNES pad, and now you can get one too for $75, courtesy of PlayAsia.
[SPEAKER_07]: But hey, it looks just like a real SNES pad.
[SPEAKER_07]: Even though it's really a Wii Classic controller.
[SPEAKER_07]: Whatever the fuck.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, I'll probably get one.
[SPEAKER_05]: The real deal.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or I'll just probably break out my paint.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ooh, it does look pretty cool, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, it's kind of expensive.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: You could totally either rewire...
[SPEAKER_07]: I bet you anything, because keep in mind, the classic controller actually is in the shape of the Super Famicom controller, which was slightly different shape than our Super Nintendo controller, as you'll recall, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: You can, though, get Super Famicom controllers at, like, eBay, anywhere, really, and probably just reshell it.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, that's not hard at all.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'd do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm a cheap bitch.
Ha ha ha ha ha!
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm kind of over the whole Wii Virtual Console stuff until they put something really good on there.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't really need this controller.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: I definitely don't need this controller because I don't play virtual console games anymore.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, you don't.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, which is too bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: But there are some other retro games that might be interesting, including some fictional ones.
[SPEAKER_02]: D3, the publisher behind the new parody game Eat Lead the Return of Matt Hazard, is actually planning on releasing some of these retro parodies on Xbox Live Arcade and the PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_02]: um supposed to be coming out this summer at some point no word on exactly what it is but it'll probably one of the in joke um games that are going to be you know part of this game itself I thought I heard a rumor though that there was going to be some of those games unlockable in you know eat lead so I don't really know what they're going to be doing there but I don't know that'd be kind of neat if they're good but otherwise you know if the you know I think also it kind of
[SPEAKER_02]: Hopefully Eat Lead does well, because otherwise you're going to have some spin-off of a game that sucked.
[SPEAKER_02]: No one's going to really want to play it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know much about this series, but I'm assuming this chat comment is in reference to this.
[SPEAKER_05]: GameGuru says, Has Matt Karts will be interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it's a fictional game series.
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, speaking of, like, fictional games and stuff, what is that retro game that came out on DS this week that sounds really interesting?
[SPEAKER_05]: Or last week, I think it was, the Retro Game Collection or something like that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, Retro Game Challenge, the Game Center CX.
[SPEAKER_05]: That sounds kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to check that game out.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have the sequel just came out in Japan, too, and it's actually one of the retro games, and it's actually like a 16-bit game now, which is supposed to be a big deal.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, um...
[SPEAKER_02]: It's interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like that they had old magazines and stuff in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's all made up.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's another one.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't remember what it was called now, but it was that PSP game, the one that you play 30 seconds at a time.
[SPEAKER_02]: I saw a video on that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it looks awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's so cheesy.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't remember the name of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: We covered it in a previous show.
[SPEAKER_05]: I remember talking about that, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: Musha30 looks awesome looking forward to checking that out you had to go to towns and stuff like that and you really had 30 seconds in between each thing but you can get more time if you visit certain people
[SPEAKER_05]: and AcidicVampire in chat says retro game challenge is really good I just got it this past week this is why I like having a live chat room during the show you know not a lot of podcasts can do this there's some out there you know some of the others that are on all games but not a lot of podcasts can do this kind of interacting and get answers live when we're stumped like I don't remember the name of that game somebody usually knows it or we get instant game reviews on these games we haven't we're too poor to check out so
[SPEAKER_05]: Quake 3 Quake 3
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it is Quake 3, yes, but Quake Live is apparently going to start the open beta this next week.
[SPEAKER_05]: All the statistics that are on the server now, they're going to be kicked out from the closed beta.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tuesday, February 24th is apparently when the open beta testing period is going to be announced.
[SPEAKER_05]: Quake Live, again, is a web-based version of Quake.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sure they're going to change some things.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think it's just a port of the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: All you have to do if you want to check this out, just go to www.quakelive.com on February 24th and check it out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe I'll be there playing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oregon Trail
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: And you can die of dysentery!
[SPEAKER_05]: I know, I was going to say, now I can ford the river wherever I go.
[SPEAKER_05]: It'd be awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Great.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what UnfoldedRaptor in our chatroom says.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dysentery on the go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Somebody in our chatroom, I don't even know if I should say the name, because they were in the NDA beta, says, everybody play it, the Quake Live.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, apparently it's really good.
[SPEAKER_05]: and I'm hearing a lot of endorsements for it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just a couple more stories.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to open up our Skype line at 1-877-GAME-OLR or use name on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll be opening that very soon.
[SPEAKER_05]: We just got a couple quick more stories for you guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: Speaking of beta testing, Sony is looking for some new game testers as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: What will you be possibly playing?
[SPEAKER_02]: A new game machine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hmm, people are thinking that it's going to be either part of the PlayStation Portable Series or possibly maybe even like a PlayStation Phone or something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Could it be possibly the PlayStation 4?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm thinking a little early for that, but I can see maybe like the PSP 4000 or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: Could it be a new enhancement to PlayStation 3?
[SPEAKER_05]: Could it be like a new home, I don't know, like a home type thing, like an expansion that all PlayStation users will have?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is that a possibility?
[SPEAKER_05]: Or is this like hardware?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be hardware.
[SPEAKER_02]: New game machine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's probably PSP version 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically, they're looking for someone.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a job listing on Sony Computer Entertainment Japan's website.
[SPEAKER_02]: It says it's asking for someone to evaluate and assess a new game's machine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ponzi in our chatroom suggests it will be the PS2.5.
[SPEAKER_05]: Could it be yet another reiteration of the PlayStation 2, you think?
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, not the PS2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe a new PSP, kind of like DSi that's enhanced but plays the old stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: They just had a new PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but I'm talking about when it actually redesigns the PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like a PSP Part 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not like something that, oh look, now it has a microphone on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's retarded.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or, oh look, now it's a little bit slimmer.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm talking about something that actually, oh look, it's another analog stick.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or, you know, now the screen's bigger and shinier.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now I can make phone calls with it.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: I actually liked that game that I played on the Gizmondo, the guitar game.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Johnny Whatever, was that what it was called?
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow, how do I remember that?
[SPEAKER_07]: It was actually a fun little game when I could hear it at E3 years and years ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: One of the wonderful downsides to E3.
[SPEAKER_07]: Acidic Vampire says he wants the PSP to make dinner and bring a beer.
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: GameGuru, you were like, do you have an iPhone?
[SPEAKER_07]: If you have an iPhone, you're allowed to make that assessment.
[SPEAKER_07]: It said the iPhone is a lousy gaming device.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're allowed to make that assessment if you've actually played games on one for a significant amount of time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, let me move on.
[SPEAKER_05]: I got one more story, then we'll open up the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe they'll call in, who knows.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hideo Kojima is going to get another Lifetime Achievement Award.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's only 45 years old, by the way, but he has met his Lifetime Achievement from the Game Developers Choice Awards, which are happening on March 25th.
[SPEAKER_05]: So Hideo Kojima is going to be getting that award.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, because he kind of made Metal Gear and all.
[SPEAKER_05]: So... Kind of makes sense that...
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, random story.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now let's take your random calls at 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Skype line is now open and we'll get to those calls momentarily.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a little gap between when we say something live and when they actually go out over the radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, nope, we're getting a call already.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we'll take this call and then we'll get some last minute stories.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_05]: Deathwishing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello, Deathwishing.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_05]: Street Fighter 4 It was a Street Fighter cabinet, that's all I know
[SPEAKER_05]: Dan's homo What?
[SPEAKER_05]: If you can kick somebody's ass with Dan, then you are awesome
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, the AI in the game is ruthless, though.
[SPEAKER_14]: Holy crap.
[SPEAKER_14]: Seth, my god.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, we were talking about how Seth is a bastard.
[SPEAKER_14]: All I know is just don't use the 360 controller for it.
[SPEAKER_14]: I have to use that.
[SPEAKER_05]: It sucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: I almost got it on PlayStation 3 based on the controller alone, but then I realized I think I know maybe two or three people playing it on PlayStation 3, and I know far more on the 360, so I finally caved and got 360.
[SPEAKER_14]: All I know is if you want to play, invest in a fight pad, because I heard those are really good, and they're like the Sega controller.
[SPEAKER_14]: And then the tournament edition stick is super accurate.
[SPEAKER_14]: You can just pull off the same move over and over.
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: How was that?
[SPEAKER_05]: I've heard some reports coming in from plenty of those around the country.
[SPEAKER_05]: How did you do?
[SPEAKER_14]: One beat five people, then got beat by a guy who's ranked three in California.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you've not played the game since you were like five, yet you did that well in the tournament?
[SPEAKER_14]: Because I chose a place to go to that I knew people would walk in to be like, oh, look, a tournament.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, like at the mall or something?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_05]: That makes sense.
[SPEAKER_05]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_05]: Deathwishing Killzone 2 JTV
[SPEAKER_05]: You can get those demo codes, though, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: But only if you, what, pre-ordered it?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, if you pre-ordered the game, you could have got the multiplayer demo or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I think that's just the normal demo, actually.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I saw some people giving away codes on Twitter for it, so I know it must have been kind of hard to get.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not hard to get.
[SPEAKER_05]: You just create a European account and done.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have it on my PS3 right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sneaky, sneaky.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you, British people.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, then maybe we need to fire up Killzone and compete with the other channel.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I have no idea who else is showing it.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's hot-blooded gaming or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's so interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: When we first started on Justin.TV, there really was not a lot of gaming stuff on there at all.
[SPEAKER_05]: But now there's tons of people just kind of showing what they play on there.
[SPEAKER_05]: But hey, props to them.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's definitely expanded the community over there on Justin.TV.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, well, we're going to let you go so we can get some more calls.
[SPEAKER_05]: But thanks for the call, buddy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright?
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, thanks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have a good day.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio, who's this?
[SPEAKER_00]: Hello, Actdeft, how are you doing?
[SPEAKER_05]: Awesome, awesome, we have a little bit of lag probably because of the fact that you are in another country So why don't you go ahead and ask us your question or whatever you called in about tonight
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, I basically wanted to talk about Street Fighter 4 here in Mexico because something pretty bad happened, especially with the collector's edition for PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_00]: Please, tell us about it.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's a pretty big shortage.
[SPEAKER_05]: How did it happen?
[SPEAKER_05]: How did the shortage happen?
[SPEAKER_00]: Well...
[SPEAKER_00]: Nobody knows how it happened.
[SPEAKER_00]: It just happened.
[SPEAKER_00]: Basically, most of the stores that had pre-orders for the Street Fighter 4 version on the PS3, the first edition one, basically got cut off by Capcom.
[SPEAKER_00]: And they didn't get sent all the pre-orders they had in stock or they had planned to sell.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's so strange.
[SPEAKER_05]: Were they redirected to the US to maybe meet demand?
[SPEAKER_05]: And they were like, well, we could screw over other countries if we meet the demand here.
[SPEAKER_05]: It seems a little odd.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, most people are thinking that.
[SPEAKER_00]: And that's pretty much it because it got sold out in the US.
[SPEAKER_00]: Screw Mexico, possibly.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm sorry for the PS3 owners that
[SPEAKER_00]: If I'm correct, I'm pretty sure it's around
[SPEAKER_00]: 1,500 pesos for the collector's edition and 1,000 for the regular edition.
[SPEAKER_00]: Though most people on the, not to call it the black market, but on the maybe what we call here at the Angles,
[SPEAKER_00]: That would be a flea market or a swap meet.
[SPEAKER_00]: They could sell it for over 2,000 pesos.
[SPEAKER_00]: That would be like around $150 on the US.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just looking at conversion rates right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's about 10.8 pesos to the dollar.
[SPEAKER_05]: So let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: He said it would be about 1,500 to get it legitimately.
[SPEAKER_05]: Divide that by 10.8598.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's actually 1,450.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow, that's like $138 or $130.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: So sometimes we're a little spoiled here, so we have to remember that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you know, maybe next time you need to get some friends in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_05]: and just mail you the game or something, you probably get it faster and cheaper.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, most possibly.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's a good thing that I got the 360 version over at Amazon.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm not going to worry about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Out of curiosity, I don't know if you know the answer to this or not, but are you able to order games from the U.S.?
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, say, you can order a game from Amazon.com in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_05]: and have it shipped to Mexico, or do they not do that?
[SPEAKER_00]: Basically, I'm getting some help from my friend.
[SPEAKER_00]: The game is going to be delivered over the U.S.,
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm pretty much next to the border.
[SPEAKER_00]: You can go and pick it up.
[SPEAKER_00]: I just paid with my Mexican credit card.
[SPEAKER_00]: That I can do.
[SPEAKER_00]: But I cannot ship games over here.
[SPEAKER_00]: I can get movies and I think books, but everything else, no.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's actually like that for Amazon UK.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can order books and they'll ship here, but I can't order a game or a toy from the UK.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'd have to ship it to a UK address.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, plus you'd get into region issues at that point, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, even though we got screwed on the pre-S3 version of the collector's edition of Street Fighter 4,
[SPEAKER_00]: Basically, the rest of the world, Mexico, Japan, and Europe got the 360 ring controller, that it has a definitely better D-pad.
[SPEAKER_00]: I have two controllers here with me, and they definitely work.
[SPEAKER_00]: And it's basically the same controller as the white one that comes with the console, though the D-pad, you see it, and it's the same, but you feel it, and it's definitely better.
[SPEAKER_05]: I really hope they think about it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Super Street Fighter Turbo with it, and it's definitely better.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, thanks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, if you want to give us a call, we'll take another one.
[SPEAKER_05]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: But wait, we already have a call dropped in.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a kind of exhausted Jason.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jason, am I exhausting you from all my needy tells about the podcast feed?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm like, I don't understand.
[SPEAKER_05]: I followed Deep Man's instructions.
[SPEAKER_05]: That just put it on the website.
[SPEAKER_05]: It didn't put it on the feed.
[SPEAKER_05]: Help me, Jason.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's actually kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_03]: I haven't... It's...
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then it disappeared from the website.
[SPEAKER_05]: I need to talk to Deke Man about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm confused.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I have one more episode to get us all caught up.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then I'm going to try and get tonight's episode up.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if it will realistically happen tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tomorrow is my mother's birthday.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I have to go out and spend some time with her.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which, by the way, if I am not mistaking, this is 68.
[SPEAKER_05]: My mother is going to be.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, yep.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not that everybody cares.
[SPEAKER_05]: But anyways, Jason, what did you call in to talk about tonight?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm on the phone.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was going to say that your parents are old, but at the same time, you are also older than me by a fair margin.
[SPEAKER_05]: But my parents had me late.
[SPEAKER_05]: My mom had me when she was 38.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, wait, that wouldn't make sense.
[SPEAKER_05]: She'd have to be turning 69.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow, I'm a bad kid.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't even know how old my mom is, but it all starts to blend together after 65.
[SPEAKER_05]: So yeah, I guess she's going to be 69, actually.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, what did you call in about?
[SPEAKER_05]: Surely you didn't call in to talk about my mom.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Tony Hawk story is kind of interesting because the only thing that comes to mind, there's only two things that come to mind when they talk about a custom controller.
[SPEAKER_03]: The first one is the arcade cabinet, the skateboard that Topskater had in the entire arcade cabinet set up.
[SPEAKER_03]: and then the only other thing that comes to mind is that since we have wireless controllers now, something resembling like those tech decks that were really popular between 5 and 10 years ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow, I haven't heard about a tech deck in a long time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Exactly, exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's just kind of... I'm trying to envision myself... First of all, I sucked with those things.
[SPEAKER_03]: I couldn't do anything on those stupid things.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: and I think the angle might make a difference too or something like that or the way that you shift the skateboard on its mount but it's just it sounds so stupid to me because we have a controller that works for this stuff already it's the same thing that I said with Home on the PS3 we have an interface we have a system that works you come up with a stupid gimmick like this and it's going to artificially inflate the cost and be stupid this game is on the Wii right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Nope, PS3 and 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was going to say, because if it's not the Wii, it's another... There used to be stupid gimmicks over there.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just really weird to think about.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the unfortunate downside to Guitar Hero and Rock Band being very popular, and the Wii.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, all three of those things getting popular roughly around all the same time has put this stigma out there that, wow, all these extra peripherals can sell like crazy!
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not that the power pad is ever really something to legitimize at all, but rather the power glove.
[SPEAKER_03]: The power glove, the track and field mat, the...
[SPEAKER_03]: Whatever that Sega Genesis controller, Beam, Octagon... Activator.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wasn't it the Activator?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I had an Activator.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know, they were awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just want to say, though, about the Power Pad.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Power Pad was badass when I was a kid.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I was probably like...
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm a little older than the rest of you, and I was probably like 9 or 10 when the Power Pad first came out.
[SPEAKER_05]: We used to have a blast playing frickin' track meet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, first off, I remember for the long jump, the trick was you jump off the pad and then jump back on so you can fly just like so far.
[SPEAKER_05]: But also the other thing would be short order and eggsplode.
[SPEAKER_05]: A game was awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have never heard of that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm actually kind of glad to see somebody talking about Prop Cycle.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was a big, expensive rig, but that was a really good game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love Prop Cycle so much.
[SPEAKER_03]: Prop Cycle gets props.
[SPEAKER_07]: Look online.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did you ever see the Prop Cycle that hooked up to an Addams Family pinball?
[SPEAKER_07]: Trust me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just look it up.
[SPEAKER_05]: What a pointless fucking combination.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's brilliant and stupid at the same time.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just look it up.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll find a link and put it in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sounds good to me.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, we need more content on the website and I'm thinking one thing you ought to do is a brilliant but stupid column and that should be something that you put in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like in gaming.
[SPEAKER_05]: Brilliant but stupid.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jason, any other quick thoughts before we let you go, buddy?
[SPEAKER_03]: The GTA 4 Lost in the Damned controversy you guys were talking about before.
[SPEAKER_03]: The debate, I am so tired of it in general.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know they did it just to see what would happen.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course you do, because they don't make every layer.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you make a person, the texture is closed.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's the other thing, and I should have brought this up earlier in the show, because who knows how many people have actually listened this far two and a half hours into the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I bet they did it this way because the peen isn't really on the disc.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not in the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's in the download content.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's almost like the reverse of Hot Coffee where you had to hack the disc or whatever, basically use the little code to unlock the sex scene.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like the complete reverse of that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I feel like they almost did this just like they knew This is the finger.
[SPEAKER_05]: They knew in the beginning they wanted to put
[SPEAKER_05]: the um peeing in the game but they thought no let's do it in the download content because then people who get mad and want to take this game off shelves well it's not really in the game you have to consciously pay to download or whatever a little weird Jason did you see the picture
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I haven't.
[SPEAKER_03]: I tend to stop clicking around and whatnot when I'm on a call.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll let you go so you can go check that out and post your things in chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for the call as always, Jason.
[SPEAKER_05]: And thank you for my venting earlier when I couldn't get the podcast up.
[SPEAKER_05]: People sometimes forget you're a big part of this show as well, even though it may not be your voice they have to hear for three hours every Sunday.
[SPEAKER_02]: So how the hell would you play that game?
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, take care, Jason.
[SPEAKER_02]: Night.
[SPEAKER_02]: Codemasters wants you to name your baby Jason in the UK.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: Brilliant and stupid.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not brilliant at all.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just stupid.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, if you name your kid Jason for other reasons, you know, you have a grandpa named Jason or you just like the name.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: But if you name it Jason because of this.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do it for Friday the 13th.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Look, we got another call on the line.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't want to keep them waiting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, you're on Orange Lawns Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yo, what up, guys?
[SPEAKER_13]: It's Xenocore from the Ultimate Quest.
[SPEAKER_13]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_05]: Xenocore, how you doing?
[SPEAKER_05]: We haven't heard from you in a while.
[SPEAKER_05]: How are things going at Ultimate Quest?
[SPEAKER_05]: We haven't heard from Footy in a while either.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, lots of real world stuff is kind of hitting us all at the moment.
[SPEAKER_13]: I moved and got a new job.
[SPEAKER_13]: Foodie's in the middle of finals.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, this, that, the other thing.
[SPEAKER_13]: We are planning on coming back, but we've got to get our real lives in order first.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was going to say, I think you've got Star Ocean this week, so you're going to need to get things together because that's a big RPG.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, that's true.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_13]: But I've been focusing in other areas since I was cut off from the interwebs.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, you sort of need an internet connection to do the MMO thing.
[SPEAKER_13]: True.
[SPEAKER_13]: So I went back to some of my older conquests and dug up a copy of Falcon 4 after I heard Hendrick's mate mention it on his show the other day.
[SPEAKER_13]: And on top of that, the new release of 40K Dawn of War 2 just came out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Warhammer RTS Game
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, not so much now.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, things are pretty well balanced.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's just online you really have to pay attention to what you're doing because there is no base building in this.
[SPEAKER_13]: Everything is done by putting your troops out in the field.
[SPEAKER_13]: So where you position them and what areas they're looking in are a lot more important than what they used to be.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, if you look at it, the guys who built Warhammer Mythic, I mean, they're known for their PvP stuff from Dark Age of Camelot.
[SPEAKER_13]: And that's pretty much what this game is built towards.
[SPEAKER_13]: So if you're not into it for the PvP, you may not want to last as long because there's only a 40-level cap.
[SPEAKER_13]: The endgame comes a lot sooner, mainly to get you into PvP stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: So if going up against other players isn't your thing, then you're sort of going to get turned off from it after a while.
[SPEAKER_12]: You run out of PvE content pretty quickly, or at least so I've heard from my friends who play it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was playing it for a little while, and it's not that I disliked the game, but at the time I was so sucked into WoW I couldn't balance two games.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I had to cut one of those.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, look, another public quest.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, look, it's the same public quest.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, I thought those public quests were actually a pretty neat idea.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, that was kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: It had some neat ideas.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's why I'm a little sad to hear it's bleeding out users.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, you know, at the same time, if not everybody's in it for PvP...
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't think that it's going to go away, though.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think it's going to stay above Critical Mass.
[SPEAKER_13]: It'll just be one of those other ones that are just sitting quietly in the corner, like EverQuest and EverQuest 2 and Planetside and all these other classic ones that are still running.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's another game I played this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't talk about my gaming week, but I actually went back and checked out Phantasy Star Universe for a little while, and you would be surprised.
[SPEAKER_05]: On the Xbox 360, Block 1 and Block 2 are still full a lot of the times, especially during primetime gaming hours.
[SPEAKER_05]: They still have... You would think that game would be completely dead, but they still have a very loyal user base in there, which was amazing because they still have Christmas decorations up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Although I think they get away with it because they call it Winter something, so technically it's still Winter, but...
[SPEAKER_13]: One other thing.
[SPEAKER_13]: Did anybody in your area or anybody listening happen to get into the GameStop Street Fighter 4 competition that happened this weekend?
[SPEAKER_05]: I did not go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did anybody in the room go?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_05]: But we did have a caller just a little bit ago talk about his experience there in Southern California.
[SPEAKER_05]: But did you go?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, there was one in Jacksonville, luckily enough.
[SPEAKER_13]: I went in, got the round two, and I got my ass... Well, not handed to me.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was a 3-2 victory for him.
[SPEAKER_13]: But he's an old schooler like me, so I didn't feel too bad about it.
[SPEAKER_13]: And he actually ended up winning the store.
[SPEAKER_13]: So I was content with that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, if you're going to lose to someone, lose to the eventual winner, I suppose.
[SPEAKER_13]: Exactly, exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what I felt like.
[SPEAKER_05]: Back in the days of DDR, I don't know if a lot of people know, but I used to do Perfect Attack in DDR in tournaments and stuff, and
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, like, I came in fourth, which was probably as high as I would go in some tournaments, but, you know, usually when I would lose, I would lose to the person who would eventually win, so it didn't feel so bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: But those were the days.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, man, I wish I could do some of that now, but now if I probably played a nine-footer on DDR, I'd be like, where's my inhaler?
[SPEAKER_05]: So, Xenocore, anything else you want to share with our listeners tonight, Xenocore, before we let you go?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, just that feeling of being in the tournament, everybody talking smack, all waiting for their turn and getting sent home crying.
[SPEAKER_13]: I miss that from the arcades.
[SPEAKER_13]: That needs to come back.
[SPEAKER_13]: But that's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's all I have, guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe they'll do some more of this.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, Xenogor, take care, buddy, and have a good one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Take it easy.
[SPEAKER_05]: And good luck with Ultimate Quest.
[SPEAKER_05]: Come back soon.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, we're gonna go ahead and close the Skype line for now because we've taken lots and lots of calls tonight and we still have a cage match we gotta get to at some point.
[SPEAKER_05]: And yeah, I heard one of our frequent listeners and callers, TheRobD, apparently did pretty well in this tournament.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if he won his store or runner-up or whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, what are you laughing about, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_07]: Just the prop cycle.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, you nerd.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, so yeah, I was just reading about that in chat and it reminded me because I saw a live journal post of his that said that he did pretty well, so congrats to him.
[SPEAKER_05]: And apparently he's got, he's like, I'm sure he's number one on my friends list and stuff online.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's pretty insanely good at Street Fighter.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have to play him once and lose to him just for the little factor.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, Loki, any other last minute stories you want to get to?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it's rumored that, or I guess Sony is saying God of War 3 and MAG are coming within the year.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course, MAG being that massive action game, and these will be like blockbuster exclusives.
[SPEAKER_02]: And yeah, no word on when they're possibly going to come, although if I were a guessing man...
[SPEAKER_02]: Perhaps God of War 3 might be coming out around July-ish.
[SPEAKER_02]: But we don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, it's just a guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: Summer's a good time to release games.
[SPEAKER_02]: July, especially.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's, what, NCAA football and NCAA football.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: At least for July.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, Braid, we talked about that earlier in the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: And if you thought $15 was too much for Braid, well, you're in luck.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're dropping the price this week to 800 Microsoft points or $10.
[SPEAKER_02]: Great for sales.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you haven't played it yet, you get a chance to play it now.
[SPEAKER_07]: I had a story, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, well, DarkSakura, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just jump right in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Cut Loki off.
[SPEAKER_07]: He does it to me all the time.
[SPEAKER_07]: I thought it was fair.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_07]: Go ahead with your story.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was actually just trying to remind you that I had one later.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently Microsoft overpaid some layoff severances and now they want their money back.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess in...
[SPEAKER_02]: In an administrative error, they had meant to pay off their 1,400 employees that they had just recently laid off, but they actually had put a little bit too much money in their severance packages.
[SPEAKER_02]: They now want it back and says, according to this, we ask that you repay the overpayment and sincerely apologize for any inconvenience to you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I know it's just a minor inconvenience.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's kind of messed up.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, you know what's funny?
[SPEAKER_05]: I actually had something like that happen to me once.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't want to say at what job, it was a long, long time ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: Long, long time ago, like I was younger.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they totally overpaid me on my last check.
[SPEAKER_05]: And not by much, but like a hundred bucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: But when you're like 18, that's a lot of money.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, you know, thankfully they didn't ask for it back.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because at that age, I don't know how I would have paid that back.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, Jamie, why don't you go ahead and do your last minute story?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a little dumb story.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sure, go for it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was actually, it was not dumb because it was linked to me from Alpha Cananogram in chat that they're selling Noby Noby Boy shirts.
[SPEAKER_07]: at Panic.com
[SPEAKER_05]: Let me look at that right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is at panic.com slash goods slash nobynoby.php Free advertising for them.
[SPEAKER_05]: Look at that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: I see.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're hilarious.
[SPEAKER_05]: They look like a giant scribble on a shirt.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, do you have any more?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that's it for right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: and it would boot Xbox Live people off of the network actually.
[SPEAKER_05]: Microsoft has responded saying that basically you should contact your internet provider if this is happening to you.
[SPEAKER_05]: However, they are threatening to ban any hacker that gets involved in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Quote, this problem is not related to the Xbox Live service but to the player's internet connection.
[SPEAKER_05]: The attacker could also attempt to disrupt other internet activities such as streaming video or web browsing using the same tool.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Microsoft just kind of wants to remind people that, hey, Xbox Live is like any other internet service.
[SPEAKER_05]: So if somebody is attempting to hack you in that regard, or I guess more like spam you, I think would be a more appropriate term, it could affect Xbox Live just like it would affect anything else you do on the internet.
[SPEAKER_05]: So be warned.
[SPEAKER_05]: And if you're doing that to people, unless they really deserve it, you're lame.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you're doing it to people just randomly, then you're lame.
[SPEAKER_05]: But if you're doing it to people because they really deserve it, then okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: But just be careful.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently they're doing it to people because they lose to them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, see, that's lame.
[SPEAKER_04]: Get over it.
[SPEAKER_04]: You've lost.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't like you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to DDoS you.
[SPEAKER_04]: QQ some more.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cry me a river.
[SPEAKER_05]: Die in a fire if that's you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why are you playing games online?
[SPEAKER_05]: If you can't handle losing, don't play games online.
[SPEAKER_12]: Why else do people play games?
[SPEAKER_12]: To piss other people off.
[SPEAKER_05]: I fucking hope Seth, for real, comes into your house and beats you up.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what I hope for those people.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, if that's it for the last minute stories, let's go around and get everybody's final thought for the evening and wrap up the show for tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: We can get to the live afterbirth.
[SPEAKER_05]: Drew, thank you for being here tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry you didn't get to say more on the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: And happy Pi Day.
[SPEAKER_05]: You guys brought pie and we'll probably enjoy it during the afterbirth, although I don't know if we have a lot of forks, but I can't have any, but you guys can all have some.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is episode 314 or Pi Day, so happy Pi Day.
[SPEAKER_05]: Drew, any final thoughts?
[SPEAKER_05]: Kim, thank you for being here and I hope you feel better.
[SPEAKER_05]: Take drugs.
[SPEAKER_05]: Lots of drugs.
[SPEAKER_05]: And any final thoughts for our listeners tonight?
[SPEAKER_07]: I hope you guys enjoy the pie.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, we do.
[SPEAKER_05]: Punch and pie.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't have punch but I have apple juice so it'll be juice and pie.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Joe, thank you for being here.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkTetsuya, thank you as always for your contributions to the website.
[SPEAKER_05]: And a lot of folks don't know, but you actually contribute a lot of the stories to the show every week.
[SPEAKER_05]: So thank you for being here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_05]: And do you have any final thoughts?
[SPEAKER_10]: I hear you're popular on the Internet.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm popular on the Internet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, I am popular on the Internet, you bastard.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, what's your final thought for tonight?
[SPEAKER_02]: Final thought is I need to play more Noby Noby voice now that I actually know what I'm supposed to be doing in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although, my only complaint, that camera fucking sucks in Noby Noby Boy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Poop more.
[SPEAKER_02]: I do need to poop more in that game.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, last but not least
[SPEAKER_05]: Your final thought.
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: No is your final thought.
[SPEAKER_05]: No means no.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you guys so much for tuning in to and listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: We really appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's true.
[SPEAKER_05]: This isn't just a line.
[SPEAKER_05]: Without you guys, we wouldn't exist because it's all about independent podcasts.
[SPEAKER_05]: So if you enjoy what you hear, all you have to do, help us spread the word.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tell two people about the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: Leave us a nice review on iTunes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Help us spread the word.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's all we ask.
[SPEAKER_05]: We don't put advertising in the show or any of that stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: We just give up our time on Sunday nights because we like it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's fun, and we like attention.
[SPEAKER_05]: and we like to be popular on the internet, right Joe?
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you guys so much for listening to us tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have a good one and thanks for listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see you next week.
[SPEAKER_05]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_09]: To join us for a live show, visit www.allgames.com Sunday nights at 6pm Pacific Time.
[SPEAKER_09]: The views and opinions expressed on Orange Lounge Radio do not necessarily reflect those of the entire staff of Orange Lounge Radio or allgames.com, but we're probably right anyway.
[SPEAKER_09]: See you next week!
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to do something we don't usually do in the afterbirth here.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to make an outbound call because I saw someone join chat and I want to talk to him.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe I'll leave this in the podcast for fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Usually we do a little live only thing after the show and play some copyrighted music, but tonight we'll do something special.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_05]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_01]: A little bit surprised that this is the first time Orange Lounge Radio has called me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, it doesn't happen very often, but I saw you join chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: You had incredible timing in joining chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: And my first thought was, were your ears burning?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because we were just talking about you.
[SPEAKER_01]: Street Fighter IV Tournament
[SPEAKER_01]: I moved on to the second round.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've got that little blue sheet that says KO first round.
[SPEAKER_01]: You get to go to the second round, so yay me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Does that mean you won the store, or did the top three get to go, or what?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, here's what happened.
[SPEAKER_01]: I actually lost in the winner's bracket to the guy who eventually won it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Then I won the loser's bracket, faced him again in the grand final, so to speak, and lost to him again.
[SPEAKER_01]: The sad thing is I won three rounds every time.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was gonna ask who your character of choice is.
[SPEAKER_01]: So it's Ryu, is your guy?
[SPEAKER_01]: Let me put it this way.
[SPEAKER_01]: My aim screen name is RyuRobD, so yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: See, I don't know what it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm trying to feel out different characters.
[SPEAKER_05]: Back in the day, I used to be Chun-Li.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know I love Chun-Li, and that was the one I used to use all the time.
[SPEAKER_05]: But now, after Super Street Fighter 2 and everything, I think I really like Fei Long, especially after playing him in Street Fighter 4.
[SPEAKER_05]: But here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I am so challenged by the controls.
[SPEAKER_05]: in freaking, you know, the Xbox 360, because it's really hard on that little D-pad to do three fireballs all in a row.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I was going to actually ask you next, how do you get around the control issue, or have you stuck it out with the D-pad?
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you have to use the D-pad in the tournament?
[SPEAKER_01]: I've stuck it out with the D-pad.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm really used to it at this point.
[SPEAKER_01]: It really has calloused my thumb entirely, but I'm used to it at this point, so I can actually do pretty much anything.
[SPEAKER_01]: I can do even Zangief's Spitting Pilot Driver.
[SPEAKER_01]: The double quarter circle forward motions are still...
[SPEAKER_01]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_01]: All of the opponent is flying up in the air and coming down.
[SPEAKER_05]: You just fucking lost me, but that's all right.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm assuming that's just massive death right there, some type of massive death.
[SPEAKER_05]: Pretty much.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: Congratulations to you.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I wanted to hear about the whole how it went because we had a couple people calling in saying, yeah, I lost, yeah, I lost.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, well, good luck in round two.
[SPEAKER_05]: Are you going to be able to make it out there for round two, you think?
[SPEAKER_01]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_01]: I have a couple people saying that they'll actually drive me, which, as a poor college student with no car, is a good thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, the funniest story I heard about the tournament this weekend is, this could just be someone bullshitting on an internet message board, but supposedly someone was at a tournament and he's like, oh, we're just in some small little town, this will be easy to win, and then all of a sudden they're like, okay, first round we've got Justin Wong, can he come to Station A?
[SPEAKER_01]: And if you don't know who he is, he's a famous Marvel vs. Capcom 2 player.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think even I've heard that name.
[SPEAKER_05]: Even I've heard that name.
[SPEAKER_05]: We used to have an arcade here in Folsom that did huge Capcom events.
[SPEAKER_05]: We had a DDR tournament there years ago and it was still open.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is funny.
[SPEAKER_01]: How unlucky do you have to be, really?
[SPEAKER_05]: How funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, one other question I want to ask you, since you're the best Street Fighter 4 player I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: We don't have a lot on the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: My question is, what are some tips for those of us that consistently get our ass kicked by Seth, who suck at the game, any advice for us to get better?
[SPEAKER_01]: Certainly stay out of throw range when he wakes up, because what he likes to do is do that stupid Shoryuken spinning pile driver move, so
[SPEAKER_01]: Staying a couple steps away from him when he wakes up would help a lot.
[SPEAKER_01]: Really wait for him to make a move and then sweep him because the computer is very vulnerable to that, especially on the easier difficulties.
[SPEAKER_01]: Really just use your safest moves against him.
[SPEAKER_05]: Any tips for online in the non-Seth type battles?
[SPEAKER_01]: Online, for the Ryu players, let them make mistakes because they're usually aggressive and most of them can't even shore Yuken, so they're vulnerable to air attacks.
[SPEAKER_01]: Most of their game usually revolves around just
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, she's interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: I like how she resembles Vanessa a lot from King of Fighters.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have no idea if you... I'm telling you, does she not look like an SNK character?
[SPEAKER_05]: We were talking about this at the beginning of the show.
[SPEAKER_01]: She absolutely does, especially since she's got the red hair.
[SPEAKER_01]: She's a special agent type character, that sort of thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's funny for her, I think, but hey.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, well, Rob, we're going to let you go and get to the rest of our after show or actually close the podcast at this point.
[SPEAKER_05]: So thank you very much for letting us harass you and surprising you with a phone call and telling us about your experience.
[SPEAKER_01]: Always a pleasure.
[SPEAKER_01]: Have a good night, guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: Take care, Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now the podcast is really over.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good night.