Orange Lounge Radio
With your hosts, DarkSakura, Sky, and LocoCade
Tonight, February 15th, 2009
A landmark Sony store says goodbye
Mario and Sonic get ported to the Winter Olympics
And is Namco Bandai about to acquire D3?
Orange Lounge Radio
Hello everybody out there on the internet
Welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio
We are that podcast dedicated to video games
Video gaming, gaming culture, and the gamer lifestyle
My name is Rob Roberts
And joining me every week here in the OLR Studios
In Sacramento, California
Is the one and only DarkSakura, Jamie Summers
Who's feeling a little bit under the weather apparently
Yep
Actually, we're all under the weather
It's one thing, one kind of common theme
I've been pretty sick
I'm above the weather
I had, you're above
I'm over it all
I'm above the weather
No one is above the law
The weather is not the law
The weather is chaos
I've been kind of sick the past few days
I had a horrible Valentine's Day because of it
And Loki's a little bit sick as well
Say hello, Techmaster Loki
Loki's always a little sick
I'm a little sick and a little eating sandwich
That's right
And then some of the folks on Justin TV are already commenting how messy the studio looks tonight
Yeah, well that's what happens when you're sick
You don't really feel like cleaning
Plus, we're presented in widescreen tonight
So you can see even more of the mess that is usually off screen
I was wondering why his lightbox is in there
What's that?
I really didn't notice
All the crap that's around?
It's not that bad
This room has been way, way worse
It's usually not live during a show
So
Anyhow
Also joining us tonight, you know why he had so much freaking fun last week
He decided to come back one more time for you kids
Say hello to the one and only Dan the man
Hello
How are you doing, Dan?
Back for more
Did you miss us that much?
Yes
I have no place else I'd rather be
You're lying
Your internet's out at home, isn't it?
True that
Dan's internet's out at home
So, you know, he's here
Probably back on by now
That's right
But you're here
Nice talking to you
With us
Yeah, there's storms going on out in California right now
Which is, you know, for most of the rest of the world
The storms here are actually pretty pitiful
You know, compared to the rain they get like back east and stuff
But it's just not built out here to withstand some of the wind things we get
So when we get it a little windy, internet goes down left and right
It's pretty sad
People forget how to drive and start ramming their car into things that we need
Yes
Which I don't understand anyways how, you know, wind causes the internet to go down
Since the cables are underground
Sometimes, I don't know, like ours
Underground wind
Ours runs from the top
There's a big wire that comes down and it's weird
It runs like next to the phone line
Cable modems, son
Yeah
When they're underground, yet they still go up
Oh, whatever
Anyhow, we're going to get started tonight talking a little bit about our gaming weeks
And since I finally remembered the presence I got Dark Sakura like a month ago in Hawaii
I finally am going to remember to give her tonight
So I'm going to go in the house and get those while Dark Sakura tells us about her gaming week, Dark Sakura
I had a relatively busy gaming week despite school stuff
We played, I started playing City of Heroes this morning just on the trial
Started playing with Sauce
And it was pretty fun
You know, I picked an electric power user who was a pretty cool character
And of course the most fun part is actually designing your character, making costumes and stuff
So that was pretty cool
I also finished, well I
I'm trying to think, what all did we play last night on the Genesis Collection?
Last night being Valentine's Day evening
My husband and I decided to do something super romantic
And we played Xbox all night after I got us a lovely dinner prepared at Whole Foods
So we played a lot of Genesis Collection and some R-type dimensions
And I played some Symphony of the Night
And played a little, a couple of DS games but I don't remember what
Oh yeah, I downloaded and installed Perfect World but I haven't started that yet
So I'm thinking City of Heroes is going to be the game of choice
I've heard some interesting things about City of Heroes
I think one of us OLR peeps needs to get on that
That would be me
Go for it
Is it in Tiara on City of Heroes? Or was that a while ago?
We were playing together
Oh okay, cool
Yeah, we played together today
Because I know the new website is launching very very soon
And we're going to have Tiara hopefully doing some articles for us there
That'd be good, that'd be good
Anything else for your gaming week?
Not that I can think of
Then how about presents?
I like presents
Alright, some presents
I'm going to show this to JustinTV before I give it to Jamie here
So I got Jamie an authentic hula girl for her dashboard
To match the one that Loki had
So that's from Hawaii
Even though these presents are like a month old I'm just now remembering to give them to her
And because I know Jamie's a tea drinker
I got her different types of tea that are very Hawaii
One of them is a coconut macadamia herbal
Ooh, yum
And the other one is pineapple Waikiki
Dude, that's great, I love pineapple
So there you go, some tropical teas there for a dark soccer
I could totally use it because my voice is dying
I know, I'm almost kind of wishing I brought some more home for me
But that's okay, I have other stuff
Loki, you already got your presents a few weeks ago
So he doesn't feel left out
But he got a matching hula girl
Anyway, tell us about your gaming week, Loki
You picked the perfect time when I have my mouth full of food
Sorry, I have to go take these presents over to dark soccer
Anyways, so I played lots of Grand Theft Auto IV
And since it's actually working on the PC
I've been playing around with modding the different files and seeing what that does
So I've been playing with making different weapons
And I have the typical stuff, a weapon that has way too much physical power
So you shoot it into somebody and they bounce around like a ping pong ball
Or the grenades that create an explosion that's so big that it covers a four block radius with fire
And kind of blows everything apart
And that's fun
So I've been doing that
And the game of course is very unstable when you do that, so it's been crashing a lot
And then just playing regular Grand Theft Auto IV on consoles
Doing the deathmatch stuff there
Actually thinking of picking up Lost and Damned this week
Actually I'm in a couple of them so I can try the multiplayer in that
And if that's really good then I may pick it up on all five consoles
And then that way we can play multiplayer in Lost and Damned
Then other stuff I've been playing, I played the Killzone 2 demo which is actually pretty good
Very similar to Resistance as far as I'm concerned
The game itself, not so much, not as hard as Gears of War of course
Although the game itself, the AI is very intelligent it seems
So I can't just easily kill them or just run up on them and stuff like that
But it looks cool and I think it'll be very entertaining
I'm not sure if I'm actually going to pick it up right away because I still haven't even played through Resistance 2
But maybe soon after
Then the other game I played was Street Fighter IV
And I've been playing that quite a bit
The game is actually quite easy to beat, obviously un-easiest
Because I'm no good at the game at all
So it was easy enough to beat on it, not as easy as some videos would make it seem
You can't just go high-kicking everything around
Because the AI is smart enough to know, hey I'm going to kick your ass now
Because you're just doing the same move over and over and over again
Some people it works like the women with the long legs of course
It works pretty well but it's not just like you can put on auto-fire and leave the room
They will kick your ass
But the stories are kind of neat in there, like the little anime cutscenes that they have
I don't know, it's not really a game I'm into
Just because it's a fighting game
Actually Tatsunoko vs Capcom was kind of entertaining for me
I like the little theme song though that's in there, it's kind of cheesy
And the voice acting, I like what's kind of cool about that is
After you beat the game the first time through you get an option to toggle the Japanese or English voices per character
Hallelujah
So if you like some of the English dubbing then you can go ahead and leave it English
Or you can just switch it to Japanese per character
So that's pretty awesome
That also has cutscenes and all the other stuff too
So I thought that was really cool
And then other than that, it's just kind of fun
I was playing with some of the new characters, Rufus is kind of funny
And then El Fuerto is pretty cool
Repeat what your wife said about Rufus because that made me laugh
Yes I was playing as Rufus and then Nellie's like
That looks like me but with blonde hair
I'm like come on, that is ridiculous
And Rufus is the big guy right?
Yeah he's the one that has his belly flap physics
Nellie is one of the tiniest people I've ever met
Her beard also totally isn't that impressive
She was talking about herself
No Rufus is like me if I were to be in a fighting game pretty much
What I want to see now, I want to see Rufus versus
Ok I'm going to go way back here everybody, ready?
Raiden from Fatal Fury, that's what I want to see
I want to see that fight
Just got to wait for the next round of crossover
Or Chang from Fatal Fury 2
From Art of Fighting
Oh and Seth is a bitch
Seth the final boss who has moves from all the other Street Fighter characters
He sucks, even on Easy as he's fucking cheap
Let's get some comments from our chat room
chat.orangelandrated.com
Chat is pointing out you sound different tonight
VSTRNSV says Loki sounds weird
Tigerclaw says you sound slightly deeper
It's because I'm congested
He's been sick too, like all of us
Literally every host in the L.R. is sick tonight
It's my sexy voice
That's ok, I feel ok
Just in time for Valentine's Day
Loki wants you to get down this week
With Street Fighter IV
I'm gonna stab women on the
I'm waiting by their phones for your call
Some comments from chat
Leo Shen wants to know how's Crimson Viper
Pretty good, I like her a lot better than like say
You know, Chung Li
Some of her moves are interesting
You know this is, you're asking the person's opinion
Who doesn't play this game, I mean hardly ever
I played through her once
How did the tits compare to Ivy?
That's what guys really want to know
You know, ok, here's the weirdest thing
Which fighting game has the best tits?
Dead or Alive, Soul Calibur, or Street Fighter IV?
Dead or Alive, by far
Soul Calibur
And then we'll go to, you know, Street Fighter
Because Street Fighter, they don't really seem to have any boot physics
Although, I swear to god, I saw this during like
A little in-game cutscene
Because there's a point where you have to fight your rival
That's the second to last character you fight before Seth
And, I swear to god, she was walking away and she turned
And her boobs snapped
Like, it was like, they got stuck in some place and all of a sudden it's like
Wham! And like went back
It just like threw me off
Because she isn't, they don't like move when you're actually fighting
You know, it's not, the only person that has any sort of physics like that
Or, that's Rufus, you know, with his big flap
But, um, so Rufus has booby physics
Rufus has booby physics
It's, no, it's like gut physics
I don't know
Okay
But, um, yeah, it's okay
I mean, like I said, I'm no good at Street Fighter
And, you know, I don't pretend to be, you know, winning any arcade game
I mean, hell, I lose to the computer on easiest sometimes
So, that's pretty bad
You just need to do what I do at Chun Li and just hit the kick button repeatedly
It doesn't work
Even on easiest that the like computer would be just like
Okay, you stop doing stuff, I'm gonna walk over and punch you now
No, they're actually, it's pretty hard
I don't know if it ramps up based on how well you're doing
But, you know, easiest isn't the cakewalk that I thought it should be
Tigerclaw in chat says
Every time I hear the word Rufus, the first thing on my mind is Bill and Ted's Excellent Adventures
I was thinking Rufus Shinra, but I was, I watched that pretty recently
Alright
Um, okay, so if that's it for Loki's Gaming Week
Then I'll talk about mine
Mine was pretty much the same as Jamie's
I played a lot of the new Sonic Ultimate Genesis Collection
Except I played it for the Playstation 3
Um, they didn't have it on 360 when I went
And I actually was thinking, you know what
For the classic games, I think I'll want the D-pad on the Playstation 3 controller
And why not, I don't have a lot of games that offer trophies
So if I feel like being an achievement whore on the PS3, why not, it makes sense
So I picked it up
And I'm pretty sure I'm getting the exact same freaking thing on the Playstation 3
That 360 users are getting, it's really not a big difference at all
Um, but overall the game collection is pretty awesome
I mean, you cannot beat the value
It's $40 for, what, no sorry
40 games for $30 and then like 9 unlockables in there
And some of the unlockables are pretty awesome
You get some arcade games like Altered Beast, Fantasy Zone, Shinobi
Which was awesome, and Dan had pointed out a fact I didn't think of before the show
But they have never released an official port of Shinobi Arcade for the home systems
I mean, you had the dumbed down
There have been lots of Shinobi ports, but you never see them on these collections
And not the authentic arcade version, like a lot of them were dumbed down for the 8-bit systems
Like they had Shinobi on the NES from Tengen if I remember right
But it was pretty dumbed down, you know
It was different, at least they did
They tried to at least emulate the actual arcade version unlike
Do you remember like Ninja Gaiden on the NES was completely different from Ninja Gaiden Arcade
But for the better in that case
Way better
Anyhow, random tangent
But I just remember being a kid like it was Shinobi over here and Ninja Gaiden over here
Like the two big Ninja games he had
So, anyhow
The collection is great, it's definitely worth the money
A slight disappointment that they didn't do more with the online functionality
Especially when they've had us buy this collection before on the GameCube
And these collection, you know, or I shouldn't say the same collection
But you know, Sonic games at least all bundled together and so on
Little disappointed that they didn't do at least leaderboards, online multiplayer
Something that brought in the extra functionality
Who knows, downloadable games
Why not, I mean we all noticed Revenge of Shinobi was missing from the collection
And some other big Genesis titles from back in the day are missing completely
So why not have these as like download content
That would be actually kind of rad
I, but I somehow doubt that's how they're going to do it
Why should they?
They released Sonic 1 and they released
Didn't the original Streets of Rage come out for download 360
And one of the Sonic 2 was download content for Xbox Live Arcade
Streets of Rage 2 dead
Yeah, Streets of Rage 2, not 1
Way better
Yeah, so
Yeah, but wouldn't it be cool if they perfected their Genesis emulator with this game
And then it's like virtual console but with all Genesis games on the 360
That's really interesting about this that you say virtual console
Because like seriously, if you own a Wii and a 360
Or a Wii and a PS3
Like this game invalidates the need for like almost all those Genesis games on virtual console
That you would have paid what 8 dollars times 40 is what 320 dollars for
Again for a tenth of that, not even
It's just amazing
So I don't know
I mean some could claim it's not 100% authentic
But at the same time I think it's really as close as you're going to get
Short of bringing out the old Genesis system
And blowing off the dust and hooking it up and plugging it in
You know what I mean
I don't see it ever getting any closer
So there it is
That's the reason to have a CDX though
For more games?
Because there's no CD games in this
No Sewer Shark
It's just small and easy
Or Nomad, you know
Gotcha
Maybe that's the next Sonic's Ultimate CDX collection
And we'll have freaking Night Trap
You really want to play the Dana Plato game?
I don't know why I want to play the Dana Plato game but I do
There's microcosm in Sewer Shark
Microcosm I actually liked
There was Dragon's Lair
Where's my Jaguar collection?
Where it should be non-existent
It would just be Tempest 2000
That's pretty much it
I think there's one other good Jaguar game I can't think of right now
Defender?
Going to comments from chat
Acidic Vampire says they need some tougher achievements in that collection
Yeah the achievements are a little easy
But again that's why online leaderboard at least would have been cooler
So you have something else to obtain
Yeah the achievements are a little easy
They're a little on the easy side
Some of them will take you a little bit of determination to get
Yeah it was on the easy side
Same thing with the trophies
The trophies and achievements are the same thing
It's just that on the Playstation instead of worth points
They're worth either bronze, silver, or gold depending on what it is
But I unlocked a gold trophy easy
I got the Sonic Spinball
No maybe it's just because I love Sonic Spinball
For whatever reason don't laugh
But I got 10 million points on stage one that's all you have to do
And that's like beating stage one pretty much
This is probably unlikely but can you combine games together
Like you know with Sonic Spinball and all the Sonic games
You can do the Sonic and Knuckles stuff
Sadly no
And actually you couldn't do that with Sonic Spinball I don't believe
Yeah you can
You could play as Knuckles
No you couldn't
You could do Blue Sphere
Yeah there was something I think like one little extra thing it gave you
No you could play as Knuckles in Spinball
What?
I don't think you can
I thought you could
You think you thought wrong
My Genesis collection which I mean is not a CD for my Xbox
But it's a box full of Genesis crap
It's sitting by my TV
If you want to come on by we'll walk on
But you get something with it
You get something you get the blue
Just like all the other games it does the Blue Sphere game
Not even the complete one I think it's only with Sonic the Hedgehog
Yeah it's kind of dumb
But interesting
Let's see I'm still looking at comments in the chatroom
GameGuru says it was Sonic 2 that gave you Knuckles
Some of them gave you the extra character
Alright I guess that's it for gaming week
Unless Dan I don't know if you played some stuff that Jamie didn't
That you want to share with us but Dan do you have anything?
I've played nothing new this week
Nothing new
I'm still playing HD Remix
I played R-Type Dimensions
And I played Sonic's Ultimate Genesis Collection
For Shinobi mostly
There you go
And here's what I have to say
Online leaderboards suck
I don't know why you like them
All they do is serve to remind me
That the games that I think that I'm good at
I really really suck at
But it gives you something to work towards
All I know is go to the online leaderboards for R-Type Dimensions
And see the people who have beaten that game without dying
Every one of those people I want to kick in the balls
I thought I was good at R-Type I am no good at R-Type
I hate you all
There was some game it was the Midway Collection I think
One of the first that came out and it had online leaderboards
And like for a while I was in the top 10 for Wizard of War
That old ass 80's game and that made me feel pretty cool
Even though like nobody probably fucking played Wizard of War
I dominated Roadblasters on that
And the Xbox for months
See they can be fun
But you know what eventually somebody owned me
And that person when I find you
I wish I remembered your gamer name
I will kill you
Rob you did though play Streets of Rage right?
Yeah
You did listen to the pretty cool soundtrack
Yuzo Koshiro absolutely
That was like my whole incentive for playing Streets of Rage
Because I don't know I'm kind of sick of those side scrolling
I had forgotten that you did it
Oh yeah you can tell too
It's very
It's all about playing Blaze in that game though because you guys suck
Nice
Alright let's get into some housekeeping real quick
There's a couple things on the table right now tonight
If you are listening to us live on AllGames.com or on Justin TV
Hello by the way again to the Justin TV listeners
You can look at us on camera at Justin TV
I don't know why you'll want to watch a radio show
But that's what the listeners ask for so we gave it to them
Keep in mind we still don't have our issue fixed
Where you can hear all the sound that goes out over air
So you only hear what goes through the microphones
You don't hear any of the music
I forgot to bring the adapter for that
It's not a huge deal
I would hope that everybody is still at AllGames.com to get the full experience
But I know there's some people that because of firewalls and stuff
They can't so they have Justin TV
Which seems very odd to me that you would be able to watch Justin TV
But not all, whatever
Some people have claimed that happens so it's interesting
But that's interesting
The only other thing I want to say is that by the way
Speaking of Justin TV stay tuned tonight on Justin TV
Because we have something special after the show for you live folks
And if you're listening live tonight
OrangeLaunchRadio.com is down
It's not there
It's a big black screen with a Moblin that says it's a secret to everyone
Something is in the works
And if you've been listening to the show for the past couple of weeks
You know darn well what's coming
That's going to happen live tonight during the show a little later on
They're just crossing all the T's and dotting all the I's right now
While we're taping
So in the meantime you can still join us at chat
There is still a link on OrangeLaunchRadio.com to go to our chat room
That is not being affected by the side outage
Just check out OrangeLaunchRadio.com
Some folks in chat sharing their online leaderboard experiences
ActDeaf says I was at one point in the top 20 users in championship mode of Pac-Man CE
That's a tough one
That is an achievement
Achievement unlocked
That is, you have a big EP for that one
Because that is not an easy game to be doing that with
So, alright
Anyhow, let's get into some gaming news
And all that
And talk about what's new in the gaming world this week
Are you done with your sandwich, Lowkey?
No, I'm not done with my sandwich, but that's okay
Alright, we'll make it work anyway
The show must go on
With or without sandwich
Oh, let me say this real quick
I am going to give a quick shout out to our buddy Brad from Pod Culture
He started a new podcast for that show Dollhouse
I meant to watch that
I did watch it
Because Joss is the man
Hopefully he has more listeners than there were viewers for the Dollhouse
Oh, did it not do well on the ratings?
No, it lost to Supernanny and I will have to say
I was part of the Supernanny crowd, unfortunately
You know what, the whole...
Rude
They just can't screw this up the way they did Firefly
Hopefully it will make up some listeners on like
Or, you know, with, not listeners
Viewers from like TiVo and iTunes and all that stuff right now
It's just on a bad night
I mean, most people don't stay home and watch TV on Fridays
The whole problem is that they screwed up Firefly so bad
That people are going to have a bad impression
Those who never went back to watch the DVDs
I mean, Joss is the man
I mean, I'm serious
If you put this show on any other day in the week
I think you'll be fine
Seriously
Fox does have this tendency to give Joss Whedon the death spot
I mean, Friday nights
I mean, not to knock Fringe because I love Fringe
But if you want this show
If it's kind of tanking for you guys
Why don't you just throw, you know, Dollhouse right after American Idol
I mean, then that way you get a really big lead in
Hopefully they will one night
They'll give it a shot after American Idol
I don't know, because the show is pretty decent
Look, let me put it this way
I know I'm like the gay guy you hear on the podcast or whatever
But seriously, like, if I was straight
Elijah Dushku
You betcha
She is pretty hot
She's very hot
Yeah, that's happening for real
So anyway, I didn't give the website
Support our buddy Brad's podcast
It's thedollhousepodcast.com
If you're a Whedon fan
You should check that out and support that show
But Joss is owned
Buffy just doesn't strike twice
He hit too big too soon
It's all downhill from there
Well, you know
Firefly was awesome
Ten times better than Buffy
And it got screwed off of TV
So I don't see what the fans are hoping for
Brad's actually saying in chat
We started a Deadpool on pod culture
About how long it'll take Fox to axe it
That's pretty morbid, but sad, but true
I know there had been talk about them actually
Doing a Faith spinoff
But this was a different idea
And I think that it was that he and Elijah Dushku
Came up with the idea together, so
Honestly, the show's not bad
It was a little hard to get into
Because I think the first episode kind of hits the ground running
But it's not bad by any means
Mark, put it on sci-fi
I mean, shit
They just got, you know, what?
Reruns of, you know
Some Stargate spinoff
I mean, seriously, just put it on there
Yeah, but Stargate Atlantis was crap
Alright, look, we gotta get into gaming news
We suddenly have turned into the nerdy podcast
Sorry
We don't want to infringe on pod culture's territory
Rock turned into?
Excuse me, what?
Turned into?
You know what I mean, alright
I watch a lot of TV during the week, okay?
That's true
Ever since I stopped playing WoW
I have watched a shitload more TV than I used to
I would never have watched All House
Before it used to be, okay
House and NipTuck or whatever
Now it's like
Like, eight shows I'm watching
It's like, too much
But anyways
Amazing Grace starts tonight
One show, one show
TiVo it, don't
Supernatural
I watched Wife Swap last week
That's how pathetic I was
Not Supernanny, but what?
I actually watched Wife Swap then Dollhouse
We don't, like, watch Supernanny religiously
It's just, if it's on, it's like
Okay, so
Rob, got more news for us
Loki wants to start us off with a story tonight
Alright, well
You know, after all the assumptions that
The viral video wasn't necessarily a viral video
And it was, you know
Or it was a viral video, but just not leaked out
Um, yeah
Apparently that video that was out last week
You know, showing zombies
In, like, a Las Vegas type of
You know, setting with
You know, a giant atmosphere and stuff like that
Yes, that was actually
Dead Rising 2
And Capcom did announce Dead Rising 2
Which will be coming out on PC, 360, and PS3
It will take place
In a brand new
City
Fortune City
It's kind of like Las Vegas
And it will be a gambling paradise
No longer will you be playing Frank West
But some guy in a jacket
And there's, um
Boo to that, I'm sorry, Frank West is awesome
Okay
But they've got, you know, different pictures
You know, they have everything from
Him beating up zombies with a giant cell phone
To a dirt bike
To a roulette wheel, so, um
But has he covered wars?
Maybe
But see, here's the thing, though, maybe
We're only talking, like, four screenshots
And everyone's assuming that Frank West is not there
Maybe Frank West is there
But maybe there's two player co-op
Maybe it's multiple characters
Maybe he's a zombie
And he's like the super zombie
And you have to run over him with a riding lawn mower
I don't know
But, hey, you know, it looks pretty awesome so far
So, um, I'm sure we'll hear more about this
During E3
I need to go back and play more Dead Rising
Because I had the first one, and that game is just fun
To just fuck around with
Well, you can not do a lot of anything
Play the sub-par Dead Rising chop till you drive
No, I can't, because I just will not be able to put up with that
After playing the 360 version
But they have new costumes
The entire fun of the 360 version
Is taking pictures while you're doing these horrible
Things to the zombies
They took that out of the Wii version, I'm sorry
But I would watch that for two player co-op
Same screen or something, I don't know
Talking about TV shows
In the chat room
And video game potential
Acidic Vampire suggests Supernanny the game
I don't know, I get the sense that would just be Imagine Babies
Or something like that
What the hell is Supernanny?
It's this show where
They call the 800 number
The producers of the show
If their kids are just out of control
You should watch this show because it would piss you off
Are they Poppins modern day?
Yes, actually the lady
Her name is Joanne or something, she's from Britain
So she has the accent and everything
She even carries a little umbrella
And she comes and she restores harmony
To the household
You know how to restore harmony to a household with unruly children?
What?
Duct tape, ceiling
Basically this last episode that I missed Dollhouse for
It had this guy
This abusive dad who's like
Slapping his kids and stuff
You can't slap the baby
That's not the way to raise your baby
And it's like an hour of that
You cannot slap your baby
I'm so glad
I don't watch that show because it sounds retarded
It's just frustrating
And you know the thing that pisses me off the most, Rob
Is watching people be stupid
That's why I like
I think your own personal hell would be shows
Like you'd be strapped to a chair
Forced to watch this and Wife Swap
And I don't know, some of these
Feel good reality shows
Feel good my ass, watching people be stupid
Is the worst form of torture ever
Do you know what I like to do?
I like to watch The Biggest Loser while eating
Oh my god, now that would be crazy
This food is so tasty and you can't have any
It's all mine
It's my chocolate
I ate an entire cup of
Low fat ice cream
Just for a medical thing I do low fat
An entire cup of low fat ice cream
Which I know makes a lot of sense
It's not really low fat when you eat the whole fucking cup
You're holding it out and going
Oh don't you want some?
It's full of sugar
Sugary goodness
It is, anyway
I'm sorry, we need to get back to gaming news
Can we please?
One place I will not be eating ice cream ever again at
Is the Metreon
And we know the Metreon here at Orange Launch Radio
We actually have a lot of very fond memories of the Metreon
I have no memories of the Metreon
Other than it used to exist because I've never been to the Metreon
Hold on, let me say it
The Metreon is not closing
But the Metreon has gone through a lot of changes in the past few years
For one, it's not owned by Sony anymore
And the reason why I say the Metreon holds a special place in our hearts
The very first Dance Dance Revolution tournament
If you've been listening to this show for any length of time
You know Dark Soccer, Loki, and myself
We all met playing DDR at the arcade
The first Dance Dance Revolution tournament I ever went to was at the Metreon
And do you remember that the Metreon
We went to the Metreon the day we decided to do the radio show
We came up with the name and everything
OLR was born on a trip to the Metreon
The third mix that was half-faded
The fifth mix that was half-faded
Yep, I remember that
At that cool little arcade
And that was when they had the little oops I went to hell store
Or whatever that chick was
Oh, I can't remember the name
Oops I went to hell store
No, the chick was on all these shirts
That say oops I just ran over or something
Or oops I had sex with your boyfriend
That was like the little niche on all these shirts
And I just remember getting one that said oops I went to hell
Oh
I don't remember the name of the character
It wasn't an Emily
I don't think so, I don't know, anyway forget it
But I've seen Nightmare Before Christmas there twice
Yeah, they have the IMAX theater and everything
Well now it's owned by Westfield
That happened a couple years ago
It got changed over, but here's the thing is that they still have the Sony store
Well, guess what
Apparently in an interview with GameSpot
Sony has said the lease for the Metreon
For the Playstation store will expire this summer
We have chosen not to renew it
They are saying the lease expires on March 31st
So the Sony store is going to be closing
It's kind of sad in a way
I mean it is and it isn't
I mean the Sony store was a little you know
A little overpriced and glamorous
I mean well they charge
They charge the same price you pay in any store
But they didn't really have sales
Or anything like that going on there
Everything was very high end or whatever
It was very nice
But it was still kind of nice that Sony had an official place
You know what I mean?
And they did all their launch parties there
There were some Final Fantasy things that went on there
It's kind of sad
It is the end of an era in a way
Anyhow
By the way speaking of the launch parties
Sony has apparently said
They are still always looking at new avenues
For additional retail exposure in space
But they felt it best not to continue with a dedicated
Playstation store at the Metreon at this time
Again if you haven't caught on yet
The Metreon
Is right off of 4th street in San Francisco
Gonna be closing
The Sony store is closing
Not the whole thing
There are a couple of other notable things about the Metreon
Apart from having a pretty decent arcade there
Is there is the
Video game
Walk of Fame
I don't know if they still have that
I thought it was still there
I don't remember
I thought it might have changed hands when it went to Westfield
But I'm not sure
It's been there since it changed hands
Was it? Okay
I haven't been since it was Sony
It's been a couple of years since I've been
And it was still Sony last time I went
I went not too long ago
You could tell the place was hurting
Because this was right when the first arcade they had closed
It was empty
It was hurting
I mean this was a couple of years ago
Before everybody said the economy was going to crap
And now just double that with
A bummer
There's not much good news left anyway
You know in other
Square related news
The Squenix boss
Yoichi Wada
Said that
Dragon Quest 10
Since it's being delayed it would cause problems
For the release of Final Fantasy 13
Well
It's just that they can't
Really be sure
If it's going to affect it or not
But Dragon Quest 9
Is going to be
Delayed from March to July
And they don't know if that's going to cause
Final Fantasy 13 to get pushed back
It's actually supposed to be out
In Japan this year
And
Over here and in Europe
Next year sometime around
April 2010
It was also reported that
3D Realms mentioned that the
Delay on Dragon Quest
10 also
Is going to be delaying Duke Nukem forever
Oh gee
Even though the games have nothing in common
Hey
It's very much in common both are going
Through delays
But there is though a brand new trailer for Final Fantasy 13
Out so look for it
Another new one or is this the same one
That was out a couple weeks ago
I think it's the one that's been out for a couple weeks
The one that shows some of the battle and CGI
Yeah
Boy oh boy
So Final Fantasy 13 needed another delay
The slimes Rob, slimes
Well at this point though
I'm just kind of used to it
Final Fantasy 13 it will be out when it's out
I take it back I don't think it's Dragon Quest 9
Or Dragon Quest 10
It's 9
Oh I said 10
Never mind
Dragon Quest 10 will be delayed until 2012
I'm sure 10 is also delayed
I'm sure 10 will be out eventually
So therefore they can't start working on 10
That makes sense to me
I bet you anything 10 is on the Wii
Or whatever it may be Nintendo's next system
Because the last Dragon Quest game that they had on the Wii
Was so awesome
I'm just saying
They'll go for wherever the big market is
We'll see
Well then the next Dragon Quest game
Would be in my pants
The biggest market out there
Oh shush
I don't want to know about that because of slimes
Yeah
Because Activision
Has talked about their
2009 lineup
It probably will surprise you that there is
Call of Duty Modern Warfare 2 coming out this year
I know shocking
Seeing as that was pretty much
Going to come out this year anyways
And then apparently
There's some sort of
Racing game that Bazaar is
Working on
Some unannounced racing game
That's kind of Mario Kart meets Forza
Which that'd be kind of cool
And then of course
Prototypes sometime this year
Probably around June
And you better believe
That there's probably going to be tons of freaking
Guitar Hero games
Because they already said there's going to be a ton
Yeah there probably will be a ton
I don't think they're going to renege on that
Hmm
But only
Half the company is going to E3 right?
Yes
There's no Blizzard in this
Activision Blizzard
Which doesn't make any sense to me because you can't
You're one company you can't have half your company not go
No they can get away with it because everybody
Knows about Diablo 3 and Starcraft 2
Which is we all know what Blizzard will be showing
So what the hell
Nobody wants to see those
Well they know everybody already knows about it
Everybody wants to see Guitar Hero greatest hits
Or how to run a franchise
Into the ground without ever even really trying
Well I think the reason why they're probably
Not going to be obviously going to E3 is
Because then if they show all this stuff off
All their big announcements for Blizzcon
Will be ruined
Because they're going to PAX
No they're going to Blizzcon
And seriously if they show it at E3 it has to come out
You know like Starcraft Ghost
I'm
I'm looking at some comments from chatroom
Tigerclaw says
Tigerclaw is talking about the whole Dragon Quest thing
Yeah because Dragon Quest made you just in my pants
A little reference to the Saturday Night Live sketch
Get it?
Your album just came out
I'm on a boat
Can you imagine though if Dragon Quest X really was in Loki's pants
A wild schlong approaches
Just in my pants
Alright
I'm selecting run
Well something
Something that has run away
Far far away is the release date
Guild Wars 2
Sad
I know Guild Wars 2 originally was supposed to be out
Like in 2008 remember that
Like it was supposed to be out in 2008
I remember 2008 like it was last year
Yes it was
And then it got pushed back
And now it's been pushed back
2010 to 2011
Is the new time frame for when Guild Wars 2
Is supposed to be out if you can believe it
That's a huge release window
I'm assuming that sometime in the fiscal year
Let's wait until people you know have jobs
Or forgot what Guild Wars 2
Is about I don't know
I got devastated on Kotaku for saying it
Doesn't matter
Nobody buys Guild Wars
The people who play Guild Wars care
Nobody new is playing it so
It's not wow so nobody cares
The people playing Guild Wars
Are the people that bought it way back when it came out
So they didn't have to pay the monthly fee
And they're still playing it after all this time
But I think their new subtitle
Or not Gears of War
Guild Wars 2 will actually
Improve you know their
Client base
Guild Wars 2 now with rampant nudity
Ooh naked
Big booby adventure
Well how about
How about something a little bit different
I just want to say real quick though the delay
Possibly because of the layoffs that NCSoft
Has just had and to note
They're also skipping E3 this year
NCSoft kind of has some issues going on anyway
Going out of business
Let's hope not because there's a lot of
Guild Wars fans will be very upset
Just as long as if they go out of business
Not a lot of Guild Wars fans
The standalone
City of Heroes player creator
For all the updated outfits
And stuff
I just want to say though like at PAX
I remember we were live one night remember how we did the whole
All games thing live at PAX and we were all at the table
I'm sorry Rob I don't remember that
Going through the memory banks and find it because I remember
One night we were sitting at the table
And there was a line coming out the door
For the panel and one of them
Had to do a Guild Wars I remember
I distinctly remember it was a Guild Wars panel because I think we were making
Fun of Guild Wars a little bit while all the people were in line
And getting scow that
But of course every panel at PAX had a line
Going out the door and around and down the stairs
So we had like captive audiences
The piracy one was hilarious
Anyhow sorry
I almost pirated the game during the piracy panel
I remember Loki trying to do that
He was trying to pirate a game during the piracy panel
Just to be ironic
You're such an ass Loki
So
Jackassery
So how about
People who are Warhammer 40k
Fans which is not
Me because I get tired
Of the stupid little figures
I'm sorry I had a bad
For our listeners who don't know I had a bad
Experience with an ex who was addicted to Warhammer
40k and his stupid retarded little
Lead figures and having to paint them
But I'm not bitter
My sister's ex actually is really into Warhammer
40k and he does paint the figures
And he also
Larks and also
Plays Vampire the Masquerade
I LARPed but then I grew up
I just want to point out on wife swap
This week it was a LARPer
No
They swapped with
What what
They're tasty
This explains a lot actually
This is why Dan's not allowed to eat
Anything that I don't approve of
First
Anyway
So they're working on
A beta now for
Well actually they had the beta out for
Dawn of War 2
And that it has
Already prompted
A big massive
Patch lots of changes
To go into the game
So it is
Supposed to be
Going through so if any of the
Beta players can actually say anything about it
And I'm sure there's NDA's and
Whatnot about that
They need the patch since it comes out what like
Next week I mean
Seriously
Who knows we might be seeing a delay if it's big enough
But it was it had to be
Enough that you know if they're gonna
In fact actually
I think this is kind of a fun quote put out
By Relic
Sometimes we just make mistakes
We're only human after all
But other times there are very good and well thought out
Reasons behind the changes
Oh we forgot to put legs on the goblins
Now they can't move
Shoot naked
How about a hug we're only human after all
I want them to leave in naked
We are the world
You know what
What
It's war hammer just go
Play with the lead figures instead
And make real friends
Eat the lead figures
Nice
Seriously get out of your house and
Eat some lead figures
They're not candy
I know
See that's what they should do war hammer
40k gummy figures
That way when you destroy their army
You can literally bite off their heads
Yeah you're just like oh battle damage
Why don't you just use goldfish
That would actually be a pretty awesome type of role playing game
Like I want to come up with a role playing game
That's like gummy bear warfare or something
You could why not they have fuzzy heroes
I mean it would be awesome
Fuzzy heroes the game you use with stuffed animals
Out of jello wigglers
TM
Oh my god I like want to create my own
Role playing game now that involves me eating
It's gotta play like advance wars
Figure this out
Or totally make it out of chocolate shell and ice cream
Or even better a role playing game
That's you know comprised of completely
With snack food and like you could build
Units with different snack foods
Dark Tetsuya says OL RPG
I'm starting to like this idea
Maybe our fantasy
Yeah I was gonna say maybe our dream game company
Can not just make console games but will make
Table top games too
And OL RPG will be
All based around food
Just fat princess with RPG elements
Yes I like this idea it's fat princess for real
This is a good idea
I approve of this thought
Apparently there's a new
Game coming out that was
Revealed during Nintendo
Of Japan's fall media conference
Of course there
Was it wasn't
Really a big title it's a game called
Kensax and what this is
Is actually a first party game
That is tied
With a search engine
Basically you have
Different games that are in there
That require
Looking for you know
Making searches on the search engine
And based on the amount of hits
That you get you get points
So for example
You know they may have like
You know battle search panel 9
It says task players
Or four players with combining the words
From a stock
Of words with a 3x3 board
And you conduct different search terms
And whoever finds the
Highest hit count wins
And then they have some
Finding a certain amount
Plus you can also update it I guess
It has a library of 3000 words
And you can add more to it
And then of course you go online
To increase
The vocabulary plus
Update search results
I would think if anything had sex or porn
In it you're gonna win
This game sounds stupid and boring
It sounds like something that you do
When you're at work
And you're on a firewall connection
Where they've locked out anything good
And all you can do is just find something
To amuse yourself
That's exactly what this sounds like
Dan's got it
Yeah I know all about that
This is so bad it makes me want to punch myself
Right in the face
Let's see
Punch yourself in the face
How many search results do we get from that?
A lot
The question is
How many results down do you have to go
Before you actually hit porn?
Punch yourself in the face
265,000 results
Porn? How many results for porn?
245 million for porn
Porn wins!
The internet is for porn
How about boobs?
Only 60 million for boobs? What's up with that?
Anyway, sorry
Because one thinks if you've got porn
Boobs come with it
I mean seriously
Where there's porn there's boobs
Hey! Where there's Mario and Sonic
There's bound to be the Olympics
Or something like that
Of course Mario and Sonic at the Summer Games
Ended up being pretty much a sleeper hit for Sega
So it's probably no surprise
That Mario and Sonic at the Olympic Winter Games
Is official
And Sega did announce it earlier this week
Nintendo's Mario and Sega's Sonic
Will once again compete on the Wii S
And the DS in Vancouver
The Wii S?
I said the Wii and the DS, right?
You said the Wii S and the DS
Works fine
The Wii S
In Vancouver
Is where of course the 2010 Olympic Games
Are being held
Just in case you want to know how big that first
Mario game was, Mario and Sonic at the Olympics
The first one, 10 million units globally
By the way, the new one
The Mario and Sonic at the Winter Games
Is going to support the Wii Balance Board
Some of the events that will be in it
Speed skating, alpine skiing
So on and so on, no news about curling
But I hope to hell they did not forget curling
So there you have it, Mario and Sonic
At the Winter Olympics
They are making a deck of sporta too
Are they really? Yes
You need to branch the whole and Sonic out
Of the Olympic Games to other mascots
Like Master Chief and Sonic
At the Olympic Games
Game Guru suggests the next game should be
Mario and Sonic at the Special Olympics
I don't know about that
That might be
I don't think that got picked up
Dan was off mic
Dan said it had to be
Tails and Toad
At the Special Olympics
All the characters there
But he doesn't care about it anymore
Toadette, I can't stand Toadette
Toadette definitely is in the Special Olympics
Game
They need to do an evil one with
Waluigi and Shadow
He's trying to destroy the Olympics
Okay sad trombone
Sad trombone
Hey release dates, happy trombone
Actually can I do a plug? No
Of course you can do a plug
Just because
I am true to my word
I would actually like to
Plug a
Website
That my
Only teacher this semester
Happens to have
Because I'm sure that we've
Got other designers
And people listening to this show
So I did want to go ahead and give his website a little
Plug
If you go to mahalo.com
Go look at his fonts
They're great
Now see
Was that painless?
Wait spell that again?
M-E-H-A-L-L-O
I put me hello
Oh okay
He has some very excellent fonts
He designs fonts
Oh very cool
We have a new web page
On the way
That's right
How about release dates
How about release dates?
Well those are the games that
Stuff is released on
Anyway how about the
20th? Because that's really the only
Date this week
That we've got stuff coming out in the UK
We have 50! 50 cent
Blood in the sand
On Xbox 360
Oh the hell with Street Fighter 4 then if this game is coming out
Oh wait this is Europe
On 20th Cryostasis
On PC
More we have
Elodie's
The adventures of
Kai and Zero on DS
Men of War on PC
So I guess it's you know sexy man
Calendar and camo speedos
Necrovision
Okay that just sounds kind of gross
Necrovision on PC
Race Pro on Xbox 360
Sega Mega Drive Collection 2
On
PlayStation 3
Street Fighter 4
On PS3 and Xbox 360
And remember
In the PlayStation 3 version you get
Ken
A figure of Ken
In the US
Over you
Which was the one we got Ken
Oh it was Ryu nevermind
No we had a conversation
About that
Oh yeah and also that Warhammer piece of shit
Yeah hell yeah
Of course Dan will argue with you
Until he is red in the face
Ken's cooler
Just cause he wears red
Which is why I said red in the face
Not blue in the face
But yeah that Warhammer crap comes out too
Not a big
Warhammer fan are ya?
No
This week in the US we have the
standalone Guitar Hero World Tour
Instruments so you can stock up on your guitars
And drums hopefully these work
This time
Today actually Fire Emblem
Shadow Dragon will be coming out on DS
Or actually wait a second
Today is not the 16th
My mistake that's tomorrow
But still close enough
Dragon Quest 5 The Hand of the Heavenly
Bride will be coming out on DS
As well
Prini8 can I really be the hero
On PSP
Oh god this is that game they keep telling me I need to play
It looks funny
Warhammer 40,000
Dawn of War 2
Coming out this week as well on PC
That's not your sort of thing
Then
Disney's Sing It High School Musical 3
Will be coming out as well
On all four systems
Race Pro on Xbox 360
Will be coming out as well
And then the big one Street Fighter 4
Coming out on PS3 and Xbox 360
Some other stuff
Battle Rage on the Wii
Which sort of looks like
A virtual lawn but
Probably crap
And
That's pretty much it
Busy week in Japan for the Japanese release
Starting off on the Xbox 360
Sonic World Adventure comes out as well as
Shooting Love 2000X
Shooting Love
Get this
It's from a company called Triangle Service
Right
I am not
You cannot make this stuff up
And it is a shooting game
Just so you guys know
There's the cover
It looks like it's a compilation of other games
I'm not sure but
It looks like it's those old school type of shooting games
That are so popular in Japan
Sonic World Adventure as well
Star Ocean The Last Hope
What the hell is Sonic World Adventure
Sonic World Adventure is
Sonic Unleashed
Then
I just closed
My release dates trying to look up
That Sonic thing for
Loki
Star Ocean as well on the 360
By the way they are releasing a premium pack
On Xbox 360 with Star Ocean
Coming out in Japan over there as well
And naturally they are getting
Street Fighter 4 as well
From around the world although I believe the Japanese release
Just came out for them actually
This past week
A lot of Japanese stores
Are going to be importing the other countries
Versions
For collectors
Playstation 3 Sonic World Adventure
Also comes out over there
Otherwise not a lot on the Playstation 3 this week
Nintendo Wii
Metroid Prime with Wii controls
Is coming out in Japan this week
Dead Rising
They are calling it Zombie no Ikine
Dead Rising Chop Till You Drop over here
Sim Animals also comes out on the Nintendo Wii this week
In Japan
On the Playstation 2 Biohazard Code Veronica complete
That would of course be Resident Evil
Sacred Blaze is a big game coming out this week
From Flight Plan
That's pretty much what you got coming out
On the Playstation 2
Taking a quick look at the Nintendo DS
Lock's Quest this week
Sarusaru DS Sim Animals as well
Simple DS Vol. 46
If you can believe it
The Hikio Takentai
Shotoko Special
Force Feather is the big release from Sega
This week on the DS
And lastly on the PSP
Grand Theft Auto Vice City
Stories gets a price reduction
Idol Master SP
Perfect Sun looks to be the other big release
Perfect Sun, Wandering Star
And Missing Moon all come out
From Namco Bandai on the PSP this week
In Japan
Remember the good old days when the PSP got games
And wasn't just used to emulate old consoles
Yeah but Idol Master
Is a huge thing in Japan
I don't think it caught on over here
I don't really know how you would describe Idol Master
Never came out over here
I was totally looking forward to that new Idol Master game
Isn't it like a take on
American Idol type thing
But it's not actually a singing game
You guide your contestants through these games somehow
I don't know
It's like a sim game
There was a game that I used to have on
What?
I used to talk about something irrelevant
Anyway
I was actually talking about Dreamcast
It was a game called Super Producers
That I never got very far in
But the way that it was
There were different mini games in it
That you would manage a pop idol's career
I don't think it sold very well
Over there though even
But it was a weird game
I'm telling you, you need to bring back
CNC Music Factory
Make the video thing
Or something
Some other type of
Make the music video game
Dan was talking about a Cliquavision game
That was here
No
I don't recall
A manager game
Maybe a football manager game
I remember those guys
I had one of those on the Commodore 64
Of course I didn't know what the hell I was doing
Anyhow
Let's go ahead and move on with some gaming news
That's going to do it for release dates
Well, Midway
Weren't we just singing the joys of Midway
Last week
I don't know if you'd say the joys
Well we were talking about how
Midway was the
Pretty cool
Especially back in the day
Their arcade collections will really show you
How awesome they are
They haven't had a lot lately going for them
Even more than that now
They have filed for Chapter 11 Bankruptcy
Sad trombone
Basically the CEO
Matt Booty
I'm trying not to laugh
Said that it was a difficult but necessary
Decision
Basically for those who don't know
Chapter 11 gives you
Relief from your creditors
So that you can regroup
And get your financial plan back together
So
Some of those creditors that they
Owed money to
At the tune of $281 million
In liabilities
And of course they only have
$167 million in assets
Wells Fargo Bank
They owe $150 million to
National Amusements
They owe
Close to $20 million
And apparently they paid for the manufacturing
Costs during the
For Midway's Holiday lineup
NBA Properties Inc
Almost $17.3 million
In licensing and royalty fees
Warner Brothers Interactive
$6.6 million
And Epic Games
$1.975 million
For licensing and royalty fees
Probably for Unreal Tournament
Kind of interesting
That they are
Doing so horribly
I also read another story
That apparently somebody had purchased
Controlling shares of Midway
For only $100,000
So some dude out there
Owns like 80% of the company
Now with $100,000
The mystery investor
Yes
They inherited like
Millions and millions of dollars in debt
And basically paid
Virtually nothing for
Tons of the rights
But yeah it's like the mystery investor
Well supposedly he's supposed to be protected from the debts
But he's still gonna make more than
$100,000 on the deal
Oh yeah cause he's gonna get all the rights
Then he's gonna make
Mortal Kombat out of his basement
Mortal Kombat
Versus like the Care Bears or something
Mortal Kombat versus your mom
Nice
This doesn't mean though
That Midway is like shutting its doors
Or anything it just means
But it's not a good sign
They might as well
Just sell Mortal Kombat to somebody else
Really other than like
Mortal Kombat there hasn't been a lot that they've put out lately
That's been any good
That's not the purpose though of Chapter 11
Chapter 11
Is meant for a company
That they see recovery in their future
This just gives them
Momentary relief
Well I have to say though what I think of
When I think of Chapter 11 in this day and age
Is like remember what happened with Mervins
The big clothing store chain here in California
Mervins filed for Chapter 11 and not even a week later
They were gone
Like the liquidators were coming into town
So you have to worry a little bit
It's still a preemptive step
I mean look at a claim
Chapter 11 bankruptcy basically
Gives a company a chance to come to terms
With its creditors
And if the financing is not out there
They're hosed
Circuit City closed down after being in Chapter 11
I mean if you go back to
The 80's
This is 80's style
Worlds of Wonder who made Teddy Ruxpin and laser tech
Yeah
They were in Chapter 11 for years
Because they had strong properties
And people were always like
Man we got to extend these guys some credit
Because they're going to pull it up
No they just kept nose diving like 1991
And if only they had combined
Teddy Ruxpin and laser tech together
They would have been an unstoppable force
I bet you they did
I bet you that somewhere
At Worlds of Wonder there was a laser tech
That you could like shoot at Teddy Ruxpin
And he'd be like stop stop
Aren't you my friend
Were they the ones that made my buddy
My buddy
No that was Galoob
What happened to Galoob are they
Micro machines
Galoob I think got bought up by Hasbro
Or Mattel or somebody significant
Yeah I think because they're still
Making micro machines and those are Galoob
As well if I remember right
I actually think micro machines are now put out under the Hasbro
Label I think
No they probably bought it up
So
If it doesn't say micro machines
It's not the real thing
What ever happened to that guy that talks really fast
Is he still alive
No he's alive
I'm confused with the guy who is the scat man
That guy died
John Machito isn't that his name
I get them mixed up they not only look similar
But you know
The scat man guy looks like
The micro machines guy
Oh I see you mean the one from the video
That one
Scat man carter
He's like massively dead
Am I crazy surely people remember the scat man song
John Machito is still alive
Alright good
Thank you Stufra
Speaking of companies
And all this crazy bankruptcy
And whatever is going on
This isn't bankruptcy but it's an acquisition
Apparently Namco Bandai is looking to
Acquire D3
They're going to buy all of D3 stock
Apparently
Namco has already apparently made some deals
With the board over at D3
They're going to have a 70% stake in the company
I guess they already have it
They're going to purchase the remaining 30%
At about $680 a share
They're going to have controlling interest
In the Naruto property
Doesn't D3 also make
Onichibara
Yeah they do a lot of the ports of the simple series games
Which really I don't know who the
Japanese companies are that make these
But they need to pump out more of them
I want to see zombies vs ambulances over here
Remember when Namco was great
Now they're just watering it down
First they poured in a big bucket
Of Namco or Bandai
And I mean
I know Bandai is huge in Japan
And they make toys and everything but they make crappy ass games
And Namco made awesome games
And now Namco Bandai makes kind of crappy games
And now you're just going to pour another company in there
And it's funny you bring that up
Because they're actually saying that
D3 could benefit from
Especially the Bandai arm, they make the toys
TV, arcade
They make all this other stuff, movies and stuff
That could actually
Maybe help D3
Maybe we could get, I don't know, Oni Chambara
The TV show, that would be kind of awesome actually
Bring the movie over
Maybe we could get some Bikini Samurais and Tekken
There you go
That'd be kind of cool
That'd be very cool
But anyway look for that to happen very soon
Why can't we have another Klonoa?
Aren't they bringing the Klonoa remake to Wii or something?
Yeah it's coming out
We need a new Klonoa
Next few months, May I think
Klonoa is awesome
More acquisition news
You know
Squeenix
Is trying to make a purchase
And Squeenix
Has done a lot of things
That have made us go
What? Over
But they are trying to purchase
Eidos
And they're trying to
Basically buy it
More than it's worth using
129%
Over their current market value
So
We're looking at
Grabby grabby Squeenix
80's style takeover
So
If they want it, they're gonna get it
You know what Squeenix does
It's ours
However
I do have to say
That Kotaku is my hero
For using a picture of dead Eris
To advertise this
So
That makes me quite happy
Kind of an interesting merger
If you think about it
With the whole
Tomb Raider series
Going
You know
What else does Eidos have over there?
I can't remember some of the other big stuff they publish
Hitman
They have Just Cause coming out
At some point
Well Just Cause 2 at least
Interesting because those are the
Types of games Squeenix never really seems
To get involved with so that would be a very interesting
Sort of merger especially if Squeenix is really wanting
To get into the western development or whatever
You know
You guys are killing me with this Squeenix thing by the way
It's Squeenix
We like to call it Squeenix
The god damn company is called Enix
It's Squeenix
Actually it's Square Enix
It's the whole thing
They don't abbreviate it at all
But we say Squeenix
Squeenix is terrible
That's the most bizarre merger
You wonder why Square Enix would even bother
You know
Any decent franchises that Eidos had
Any good development studios that they had
They're pretty much flushed
I mean
I guess you might get a
Kane and Lynch, woo!
Kane and Lynch, yeah!
Battle Stations
I think that series
So the Battle Stations Pacific or something
Is coming out
Yeah, it's nothing that's really exciting
You know, Tomb Raider is kind of what they have
And like I said
Maybe Hitman
Although you gotta wonder about the viability of the Hitman
Franchise because they didn't even bring out a game to go with
It's really crappy movie
You know, what are you
Gonna do with that company?
Tomb Raider RPG?
You know, I don't know
Maybe it would save the franchise a little bit
AlphaKananagram in chat suggests
It's called Square Anus
Is actually what the chat
Actually it's
Don't even guess on NX, because NX is an awesome company
And Square used to be great too
It's the bizarre combination of them that just
Has fallen into RPG hell
Remember when Square made Einhonder?
Remember when NX made fucking Actraiser?
Yeah, and NX made Actraiser
And Illusion of Gaia
And that whole series
Secret of Mana
Bust a Move
Dude, NX made Bust a Move
Those companies just made
Great games, now it's just
Rehash for old RPGs
Bring out new crappy JRPGs
You know, what? Come on
This is what I demand out of Square Enix for
Penance, is a new Bust a Move game
That's what I want
None of this Dance Summit 2001 crap
No, Burn in Hell
It's got to have Hero-kun
And it's got to have Heat and Sprite
I want a reboot of the Bust a Move series
It's got to be completely uncensored when they bring it to America
So people are smoking and drinking and shooting each other
And then they dance their way out of it
That game was awesome
That game was beyond awesome
I love the fact that one of the attacks was that Strike was shooting you
In fact, I just gave you
We should put it right now
Squenix, I gave you the new tagline
Bust a Move 3, Beyond Awesome
Bust a Move
Dance or Bust a Cap on your end
Bust a Cap
You got served
Rama says God dammit Square Enix
I want Rad Racer 3
Yeah, Rad Racer rules
Only if it has
3D when you hit the select button
Yeah, and you've got to be able to change the tracks
And the Nintendo music has to be there
Which in this day and age, it might actually be
Kind of doable with this whole stuff they're talking about
3D, can you imagine
Remember when they were talking about that the Wii's top secret thing
Was going to be 3D projection
In your room and all this fucking bullshit
Why did we ever believe that fucking shit
Because that would be super awesome
And really innovative
And then they're like, no, we don't want to do that
People love to give Nintendo
Way more credit than they deserve
Anyhow, forget it
Let's uh
Let's get into some other stories
Sorry
Because remember it's only good for Nintendo
To innovate unless it will benefit their
Casual audience
That's what it really comes down to
Yes, indeed
So if you're a casual
Game purchaser
Perhaps you're looking for a rental
Solution, in which case
You know, of course there's Gamefly
Out there for you, but if you don't want to do
Gamefly, maybe Blockbuster Total
Access. They actually
Had Total Access for a while now with
Movies, but now they've incorporated games
Into their subscription plan
And basically it will work
Kind of similar to
You know, how it does with movies
Except it'll cost a little bit more if you rent a game
I think it's like, it upsets five
Additional dollars
The plans are $19.99 a month
You know, for the movie side and of course
$5 if a game is
Rented as well
And then what's kind of different with
The Total Access plan versus
Gamefly, is Gamefly
You can only mail your stuff back
With Total Access you can actually take it into a store
And swap it in a store
So you can do it in the store or over the mail
So, that's kind of neat
I'm thinking about switching to the Blockbuster thing
Only because they have this whole in the store thing
That you can do, and sometimes I don't want to wait for
Netflix, you know
Well, in the store is not a bad thing
Especially with Gamefly and stuff
It's a good program to get stuff mailed to you
But sometimes you want the instant gratification
Where you can just go to the store
Okay, I want to rent that game, done
But I don't want to lose instant Netflix
Like, I also like instant Netflix
That would be ultimate
But the Netflix streaming is awesome
There is a rumor though
That they're going to somehow incorporate this
Into the Playstation Network
Oh, please let this be true
So, I don't know if that's actually going to happen or not
But it's rumored that
Maybe they're thinking about it
Sony can't do anything that cool anymore
So, don't bet on it
Sony will find a way to screw it up
I wish they would prove you wrong on that
It would be great though if you were walking around at home
And you could walk up to your TV and turn it on
And like, you know, your total access menu
Would come up and you had streaming
Or I could just bypass that home bullshit
Just hit a button
You could make your dude sit down and watch it
And look bored, I think that would be awesome
And then smoke a bowl
That's what I think
Watching Cheech and Chung on Blockbuster
So, it would be really interesting
If they had, you know
Context sensitive reactions
So, if they watch a sad movie
They'll sit there and cry
If they watch Cheech and Chung, they'll sit there and neck toke
Which would be hilarious
Not likely, but hilarious
But I just think that would be pretty cool
Yeah, somehow I don't think that would get by
Like the Sony sensors or what have you
Well, I don't think the smoking dope thing would happen
But I think that, you know, having your little dude watch TV
I mean, come on
A bajillion freaking people play The Sims
So, you know, and they watch
Their Sims do nothing
I don't want that home bullshit
Then don't use it, you don't have to
I'm saying it would be cool if it was there
God damn it, you're missing the point
Just so I could see it that one time and go
Wow, that's fucking cool, okay, I'm done
There you go
It's like a stream saver for your life
It's called how many millions of dollars does Sony have to spend
To get me to say, wow, that's fucking cool, next
Well, if it makes someone say
Wow, that's fucking cool enough for me to buy a PS3
I mean, come on
How many systems has Nintendo sold with the controller
For the Wii
People are like, ooh, I can wave my hand
This is great, oh wow, it really sucks
For actual gameplay
That's really sad
I don't know
I don't know what to tell you
But yeah
You can look for that blockbuster
Thing coming soon, I guess
Or is that now, that you can do the game thing now
I think it's very soon
If not now
I kind of want to do that, but I still want Netflix too
For streaming
Just quandary
I don't want both, it's too much money
Or just, I don't know, go rent a movie
Here's the other thing
If you change your address
Hollywood Video will send you a bunch of these
Welcome to the neighborhood
Free game or free movie
My sister has moved apartments
In her complex a few times
She's got a ton of those things
She keeps bouncing from different Hollywood videos
Because they'll let her do it over and over
Or if she doesn't rent anything
From a Hollywood video for a while
They'll eventually call her and say, hey, do you want free rental
Come back in the store type thing
So she bounces between three different Hollywood videos
And they keep sending her those
That sounds like entirely too much effort
To save the five, six bucks
She's poor, so yeah
She's poor
Entertainment? However I could get it
Alright
Hey the DS Lite Onyx version
That would be the black one for most of us
Call it the Black DS Lite
Apparently, shut up, apparently
It has been discontinued
At least
That is the rumor
Going on
And Loki is confirming
It's happened
Nintendo is discontinuing the Onyx DS Lite
I have a rare system then
Black DS Lite
Is coming out the door
The only four colors left
Metallic Silver, Metallic Rose
Black in Cobalt Blue
And Black in Crimson Red
Pink, Pinker, Pinkest, and Very Pink
Are the four colors that are left
Of the DS
Is this because
This is kind of the thought process
Going around
That a DSi is coming relatively soonish
And that the DSi is going to be black
They did the same thing
With the White DS
After a while they just want to stop
Making
A certain color
I don't know
Because five colors is too many
But four is just right I guess
I guess
Anyhow, let's get into
A segment of the show we like to do every week
Here at Orange Lounge Radio
It's a moment for us to respect the classics
We need to pay tribute to those games
That came before the ones we're talking about this week
It's a little segment we call
Dark Sakura's Classic Video Game of the Week
Dark Sakura has dug through
The Classic Game Archive, I'm assuming with Dan's
Help a little bit this week, and has picked
One game to highlight
For you folks on the show tonight
What game have you picked?
Today's game is The Revenge of Shinobi
And Dan did inspire me to pick it
We had
A little bit of a conversation last night
About copyrighted characters
Making their way into
Different releases of this game
So I thought it would be worth mentioning
Plus it does have some pretty cool music
As I was about to say
This soundtrack is
By Yuzo Koshiro
And
It's actually
You can also find it in the Mega Games 2
Mega Drive 6-Pack, Sega Classics
Arcade Collection for Sega CD
And the Sega Smash Pack for PC and Dreamcast
But not on Sonic's Ultimate Genesis Book
Also the
Is saying that the introductory game screen
Has
Sonny Chiba
As Hattori Hanzo
From the Kage no Gungan series
So that's pretty cool
Anyway
It is a side schooling platform
Game
You control Joe Musashi
And go through 8th districts
And you actually have to
Defeat the head of Mio Zeed
There's three scenes in each level
With their own boss characters
And you use the D-Pad, A, B, and C buttons
To do your
Ninjutsu attack
Your regular attack, and your jump
And you also have a somersault
Move
That you can press the jump button
And then press it again
At the height of your jump
So that you can jump more
And throw eight shuriken in the air
At the same time
So
You can actually go
Over different layers
In the area
Like you can be in the foreground
In the background, indoor, outdoor
Or on the highway
You have
You have different
Ninjutsu techniques
You've got
Ninjutsu no
Ikazuchi
Karyu, Fushin, and Mijin
And respectively
The first one is lightning
The second one is flame
The third one is more jumping
And the last one is explosions
It actually costs you one life
But
If you don't have a life
Then you can't do it
You also have bonus crates
That have stuff hidden in them
So you can just go beat up stuff
It has easy, normal, hard, and hardest
Just meaning more enemies
And a shorter life bar
The Japanese version called
The Super Shinobi
There are options
For no death
And level select
So
The different stages
Is Ibaraki
The province of Japan, Tokyo
The military base, Detroit
Area code 818
Chinatown
New York, and Neo-Z Marine
Stronghold
So now we come to the different versions
As I was mentioning, there are different copyrighted characters
In the different versions
And I think you had one
Don't we have one?
This game, just so everyone knows
Was fucking awesome
It was the reason to buy a Genesis
Back in the day
And one of the things that was so great about it
Besides the fact that it's got
Brutal, unforgiving difficulty
If you don't push it out and play on easy
Is that as you play through the game
You ran into
Like, classic movies
There was a boss
Who was Spider-Man
And he stayed as Spider-Man
Sega had a Spider-Man license
He would crawl on Spider-Man for a while
He would crawl off the screen
And he would come back and it was Batman
And I mean, if it wasn't
You know, it wasn't a licensed Batman
But it would just like Batman
And in one of the subsequent re-releases
Of the same cartridge
It was the same game
They replaced him with, you know, a Batman
Not Batman
One of the enemies looked like Rambo
They took off his hair
So he didn't look like Rambo anymore
And there's a guy
Who looks like, there's a Terminator
I mean, he looks like Schwarzenegger
When you hit him, his skin starts coming off
And he's a cyborg underneath
And he blows up Terminator style
And finally, there's Godzilla
And it's, you know, Godzilla
You know, towering
And breathing fire
And they replaced him with a
Like a weird skeleton
Not Mechagodzilla
Which would have been even cooler
That might be part of the reason why it missed out
On the Mega Genesis collection thing that just came out
Is that maybe these strange licensed
Bosses kept it out of the collection
Well, it's strange enough
Because Revenge of Shinobi
If you heard it, it's been on like six collections
It was on all the ones through the Dreamcast
It was on
PC collections
I mean, I'm sure that that's one of the things
That knocked it down, probably honestly
The Spider-Man license
Because even in the
The Shinobi for the
For the
Sonic's Ultimate Genesis collection
They recolored the quote-unquote
Spider-Man enemies from
Red and blue to yellow and blue
So, you know, probably a little bit of
You know, hey, don't want to get sued by
Marvel this time around
But I'm sure that that's what it is
But the real pity of that is
Is this would have been just an awesome
Chance, you know, to
To have the Shinobi
One, two, and three
All at hand
Yeah, that is the one bummer because with so many
Complete Sega
Franchises there, it's kind of a bummer to have this
One missing, but did you notice there's one other
Big franchise that's missing, Strider
Was missing
Oh, it's Capcom, oh, that's right, it's not Sega
I thought Sega did it
I've been thinking about this
And this is something that I can kind of go off about
Because on Ultimate Genesis
Collection, I mean, it's far from the
Ultimate Genesis Collection
It's a great, great collection
But it's got some clunkers that they could have
Replaced with way better Sega games
And I'm sure that that's being saved for Sonic's
Even more Ultimate Genesis Collection, too
But, I mean, there was no Shadow Dancer
The Secret of Shinobi
You know, you could have had
More arcade unlockables, like
You had, you know, if you played Shinobi 3
You unlocked Shinobi 1, which was great
I was so happy, but wouldn't it have been really cool
To have been able to play Shadow Dancer
The arcade version of Shadow Dancer
Wouldn't it have been great to have been able to
Have unlocked, you know, maybe
Had Outrun on there
Oh yeah, that was missing, huh
You know, just Thunder Blade
You know, they had Super Thunder Blade
But not the way better arcade Thunder Blade
After Burner, I mean, there were
So many significant, I mean, that thing could have had
30 more games
And then arcade versions of those same games
And it just would have been just fantastic
But I guess you can't expect Sega
Company for 30 bucks, I expected
Though, so they should have done it
But yeah, it would have been really cool to have
Just had the whole Shinobi franchise
In one place, you know, had the lock on
Technology with the Sonic and that, but
You know, back to Revenge of Shinobi
It's awesome, if you have a Sega Genesis
Kicking around, it's a super common
Cartridge, you might get lucky
Find that you have one of the early release cartridges
With all the, all the bosses
Even the one I had back in the day, had the Rambo
Guys edited, the one I have now
Actually does have the Rambo Guys
So I was pretty stoked when I was playing it
Super, super awesome game
Really hard
There's more changes actually
They also did
For a release
1.02
Which was the last release
They also did put up an
Acknowledgement of the Spider-Man copyright
And there was only
One ending you had to
Save now, go to win the game
Yeah, the way that you get the ending in that game
Is totally cool
You get into the final level
And I think, I mean I'm sure a lot of people
Have done it, because again, when you play, when you talk to people online
You always find out that the game you thought you were a
Bato at, people are better
But to get the final ending
You had to fight the boss
While your girl ran around in the background
And a giant cement block
Lowered towards her
And if you couldn't beat the boss fast enough
She got smooshed
And you got a cool, solitary, ninja-like ending
And if you won
You know, you're standing there on the edge of the cliff
With your girlfriend, it looks like something out of Castlevania
But you have a girl with you
And it's awesome, so
You have to have some techniques
You can't just slop through the final boss battle
But yeah, I guess one of the later releases
You couldn't win if you didn't save your girlfriend
Also
There was
In the European version
The shuriken is replaced by throwing knives
Because of legal status at the time
It's
Pretty cool, actually
A bunch of the music was performed
At the fourth symphonic
Game music concert
In Leipzig
And it was also performed
At two of the concerts of play
And
It's
It was also at the
Same play concert
In Singapore in June 2007
So there you go
That's super
That's for Revenge of Shinobi
I was
Alright, there you got it
As far as game music goes too
This made Yuzo Kishiro
So if you're into game music
If you're really interested in his work
And you haven't played Revenge of Shinobi
What are you doing?
So definitely one of the most notable
Missing games from the
Genesis collection just recently came out
Revenge of Shinobi is the classic game of the week
So you'll have to check it out somehow else
Besides the classic game collection
For those of you guys checking that out this week
Good pick Dark Sakura and Dan
This week on the classic game
Of the week
And that is going to bring to a close
A new program but don't go anywhere
We'll be right back after a little break
With some more of Orange Lounge Radio
And in part beats tonight we're going to be talking
A little bit about the new website
I know it's some exciting new information
Talk a little bit about Fear 2
Grand Theft Auto 4
More Sega if you can believe it
Some very interesting trademarks
Persona 4
And Konami getting a little taste
Of their own medicine this week
We're going to be talking about that also a little bit
More of Orange Lounge Radio
Welcome back everybody to Orange Lounge Radio
On this Sunday evening February the 15th
Of 2009 the day after
Valentine's Day
And here in studio unfortunately JTV
Stopped working
We were having problems on the server end so we just
Decided to say screw it
And we hooked up Street Fighter 4
Which is what we're playing right now on the in studio TV
We will try to get it up on Justin TV
If we're able to get back on there
We already tried reconnecting it didn't work
It's on there and it's something
Some JTV channels are up but not us
But we'll be back on Justin TV hopefully soon
And it's just going to be footage of Street Fighter 4
With us talking so that should be interesting
When people tune into that
But wow this game looks pretty awesome
Although this is not the TV to be demonstrating
That was the best ever
Dan of course is playing Dan
His namesake character
He did a little special move
He's fighting El Fuerte right now
And did this little special move that knocked him up in the air
But right at the end he did his signature little thumbs up
And tooth shining pull thing
That was great
Nice
I love that like one of the best characters
In the game
Well one of the most fun characters in the game
Is just a total joke
Very very nice though
I want to say this as well in the chat
And SSJ100Matt reminded me of this
At the top of part B as well
We got a swag bag from our New York
City contingent
Specifically SSJ100Matt I believe
Put this all together for us I don't know if he had some help
Or what have you but we want to say a big
Big thank you to them for getting
Us some of the swag including lots of
Grand Theft Auto Chinatown Wars
Stuff which Loki took it all
But we have like a Splatterhouse poster
We're going to put up here in studio and some other cool stuff too
So we're going to fill some of the blank space on our wall
With some of those posters from
The New York Comic Con
So thank you guys very very very very much for that
Yay
Alright so I'm just like hypnotized
By Street Fighter IV now I don't even know if I can do news
I just kind of I really want to play it
I can do news
Alright Loki why don't you start us off with some news
I actually want to run in the house and get some tea
So Street Fighter IV will have to wait
And I think Dan doesn't want to give it up anyway
So why don't you get into some news Loki
He has unlocked me and the other two characters
Anyways
Fear II they had some pretty
Interesting advertisement
For Fear II in the UK
Actually they had trained
Black cats that were
Walking around and
Advertising with Fear II little
T-shirts on it's cat-vertising
So
It's pretty awesome actually and
You know I didn't know you can
Train cats so I think that's even more
Amazing right there
You can train cats? Yeah but
Cat shows really do tricks like dogs do
To be your minions of advertising?
I mean I'm surprised
But you know they didn't have their own agenda
But anyways
What's even cooler is if you happen to live
In the UK there's a number you can call to get your own
Fear II cat shirt
I totally okay
For our UK listeners somebody get me a shirt
For Shermy
Yeah
Make sure it's a 3XL cat size
And I'll
Get a fat fucking cat
I love my cat I know
And I will put it on her and model her
With the fear shirt on
You could just probably get like a
I don't know if you could
I want an official fear shirt for my cat
Oh
Well I don't know who knows
And then later on it's probably Dolphys sized
Pose
Oh sweet
See now we're just going to be distracted by Street Fighter
It's going to be terrible
Apparently yeah it's um
If you live in London
During the next few days you know you might have
Or seen you know
It was actually going on from mid-week to
About the Friday the 13th
You might have seen these cats walking around
Catpartizing
I think it's awesome I would put
One of these on my cat if she wouldn't you know claw
Me to death but
Biohaze20 in chat asks
My cat talks and smokes a lot of pot
Is that eligible for cat shows?
I don't know that might get it disqualified
Does the cat actually
Smoke pot or do you blow
Pot smoke in the cat's face?
That would be for the stoned olympics
Remember Eddie Isher talked
About the stoned olympics
What's that?
I've not heard of this
Well you're tested for drugs to make sure that you've taken enough
I see
Drugs are bad
Drugs are very bad
I think they're badass
What else is bad for you but Grand Theft Auto 4
Is very very bad for you
But that doesn't stop many of you
The Lost and the Damned of course is coming out
This coming week
The 17th
A lot of people are going to be
Very busy when that comes out
The hell with Street Fighter 4
Good thing you were able to get Street Fighter 4 early
You're going to be ready to move on
This level is beautiful
What stage is this?
This is the Midnight Jungle
Anyhow
It's going to be like this for the whole second half of the show tonight
It's okay
Grand Theft Auto 4
Lost in the Damned
Not only is it coming with
Of course all the great
Download content
A free week of multiplayer
From the 17th to the 22nd
It's called a Game with Rockstar event
You can play Lost in the Damned online
For free if you don't have Xbox Live Gold
Although I'm surprised there's that many folks
Out there that have this game and not have Xbox Live Gold
But I guess there's enough
There you go
Yeah really you need it online anyways
Because there's not much to do if you don't have it
And you beat the game
I don't know
It's weird though because even this game
When Saints Row 2 came out
I'm going to be playing Saints Row 2 a lot more than Grand Theft Auto 4
Not the case
It's so weird
I don't know
Alright
I'm going to have to interrupt here
I know that Dark Sakura is dying to do
A story here
But I have an OLR special bulletin
If you will
I need the theme music
For when we have special bulletins
I used to have a little trumpet announcement thing
We used to do
How about this Rob?
What?
That'll work
The new website is live
So check it out
Orangelaunchradio.com
And there it is
Orangelaunchradio.com is up
So check it out
You know what that earns?
What?
No in all reality though
I'm actually loading it up right now
In all reality we want to say a big big big big big
Thank you to
Deakman
And VXJsonXV
For their hard work on getting the new website up and running
What do you mean it isn't?
For everybody that put that together
It's amazing
It has a little space invader
As Tigerclaw says in chat
It's much easier on the eyes than the old site
Well maybe there are some
Splashes of other color
We're going to be adding light
When we add new stories
We can upload pictures
Do reviews work?
You can just add a review
It's a new story
So I have
I know I'm going to miss the old photo too
And in other announcements JustinTV is still networking
Alright so
Thank you guys again very much
And yay for that
So we'll talk more about the new website
I am posting photographic proof
Hold on hold on
I forgot about that there's that little thing
The gallery
If you check this out there's a new gallery on Orangelaunchradio.com
And you can go into the OL army pics
And you can look at pictures that our people have uploaded
Please don't abuse this
But Dark Soccer right now
Is taking pictures of us playing Street Fighter 4
Here in studio
And she's going to upload them to
The OL army pics gallery
There's Dark Tetsuya with an old ass
Pinball table
There's our messy floor
Some people have been uploading random stuff
Alright so Dark Soccer is working on that right now
It's like JustinTV but ghetto
So there you go
Alright let's try and go back to
Gaming news if we can
Oh we're on
Dark Soccer's turn
And she's up and taking pictures
Rezz
Hi
Rezz an 18 wheeler
What do these two games have in common?
Sega re-registered the trademarks
For Rezz an 18 wheeler
American pro trucker
And they were Dreamcast titles as you might recall
But hey we've also got
The Rezz
Remix thingamadookie right?
Thingamadookie
Rezz HD Remix thingamadookie
Yeah for MatchingService
Dot com
But no we've uh
So they've uh
Renewed those so who knows
We may have
New truck in action with a
Really poppy soundtrack
Yeah that's what I'm hoping is that they actually combine
The two games and we get 18 wheeler
Ooh ooh ooh ooh
Uh oh
It's Sakura vs. Dan on Street Fighter 4
So
This is
Just going to bug us all night
Why are you Sakura?
Oh
Anyhow
Who knows what interesting games
Could come of these remake trademarks
I don't know
This picture is going up because this is our
Daily life at home
Dan vs. Sakura
What's interesting though
And this is kind of a rumor that's been around for a while now
In fact I remember another story about this
The Sega vintage collection
Is rumored to be coming to
Xbox Live Arcade
You may remember a while back
They had some screenshots of
The Sega vintage collection with like
The Sonic the Hedgehog games or something like that
Well apparently this vintage
Collection is supposed to be bringing
Some of the old Genesis games to
Xbox Live Arcade
Some of these games you might expect
Are Gunstar Heroes, Comic Zone
Altered Beasts, Shinobi 3
And Sonic the Hedgehog 3
Okay but
I just bought all of those games on the Mega Genesis
Collection so what's the freaking point
Gunstar Heroes not on it
Okay one game
And I also
I already bought Gunstar Hero because it was one of the first
Virtual console games on the Wii
I don't get it either but you know then again they also released
Hedgehog and stuff by Stand Alone
So maybe people
Want just one game and
It just, I don't see the value in that
And you know
I see Game Grumps says it's on PSN as well
Maybe I have the
Collection thingy on PS3 so
You know and sadly the only way that this would actually
Work as far as being you know worthwhile
Is if they had those like say 4 or 5
Games and charged like maybe
5 or 10 bucks for it or something like that
And then having it kind of like a mini
Version of that collection but at the same time
It's like what's the big deal, what's the point
Cause you can just go purchase you know 40 games
For you know 30 bucks
Or you can wait for the price drop and you'll get
40 games for 20 bucks
I don't know
I don't know either it's a little interesting
But it's a rumor right now it's coming from a
Dutch gaming site but
It's kind of weird though that we see two of these same types
Of rumors happening you know before
So I don't know
AcidicVampire in chat says achievement whores will
Buy it that's true achievement whores
Will definitely buy it
Very very true
Well
Another fighting game going on
Out there in the world not just street fighter
4 but how many of you guys
Are fans of wrestlemania
Nobody? Ok
I used to be a fan of wrestlemania
But you miss the classics right
You miss the classic wrestlemania like Hulk Hogan
And all those people well the good news is there's a
Game coming out that's just for you
It's called Legends of Wrestlemania
And this game is actually
Going to have wrestlemania greats
From like the 80's
Including look at this screenshot Andre the Giant
And Hulk Hogan
And it's going to be like a battle game
Where you can fight all these people
And just to give you a sampling
Of the 42 characters again this is a rumor
It's coming from NeoGaf
Those forums but hey
You know what if you want to put together a hell of a
Wrestlemania game this sounds like a good place to start
Andre the Giant, Bam Bam Bigelow
Big Boss Man
Bret Hart
The Hammer, Hacksaw, Hulk Hogan
Jake the Snake Roberts, Jim the Anvil
Nate Hart
King Kong Bundy
Million Dollar Man
Mr. Fuji, Mr. Perfect, Rick Flair
Sergeant Slaughter
Stone Cold Steve Austin
Undertaker, Yokozuna I mean just tons
The Rock of course
Just some awesome awesome
Most of which are dead
Sadly most of which are dead
SHJ100Matt says
I played this at Comic Con it's a lot of fun
I wouldn't doubt it
That's an ultimate fighting game right there
That's going to be a lot of fun
Even though I'm not a big wrestlemania fan
I do remember the old school wrestlemania
On the NES that was like one of the first
Fighting games ever
That had like six of those characters
In it I remember like Macho Man was in it
And Hulk and Andre
There were like the Million Dollar Man
Had a little dollar sign he had to get
That was a power up
There was just these dumb little things in it
That made it awesome
It's kind of cool that wrestlemania lasted all this time
Didn't they just have their 25th anniversary
Or something like that?
Which one?
Wrestlemania had like a 25th anniversary or something
Just recently? I don't know they had something
It was a big anniversary for it I know
Anyhow I'm sure somebody in chat that's a big wrestling fan
Will correct me momentarily
WWF Wrestlefest
I thought it was Wrestlemania
Wrestlemania is the big one I'm thinking of
Well at any rate
How about some news from
Squenix
Squenix? Sure
Well
At any rate
The
Playstation 2 game
Persona 4
Is going to be out in the UK
On March 13th
And the PAL box is going to have
A special CD
Soundtrack
With 24 tracks
It has a new plot
New places to go
New stuff to look at
New things to kill
New spookies
And it is the same stylized
Manga pop culture art
To go in the game
So
Go check it out for when it's out
And actually it's supposed to be
Not too far off
From the style of Persona 3
So
Go for it
They're just using the same engine for Persona 3
If I remember right
Just milking money out of it
But hey you know what actually
There's a lot of love out there for Persona 3
And I haven't played it personally
But I hear it's very in depth
And it's pretty cool
Very very cool
Well you can check it out now
It's already out
In the US at least
At some point
Alright so
Some other cool stuff
Well actually it isn't very cool
It's kind of typical for Nintendo
People trying to exploit them
For any sort of class action lawsuit
This time it's not really related
To wrist straps or throwing stuff through TVs
Apparently
This guy Michael
Tortilla
Not Tortilla but Tortilla
He's a fitness expert
And apparently a host of some
AMTalk radio show called
Shape Up America
And he has announced plans that he's gonna
File a class action lawsuit against Nintendo
Claiming that they're injuring
Or that people are getting injured
Playing Wii games because
Nintendo isn't telling people to properly
Warm up before doing exercise
He claims that
Wii Fit has led the people
Sustaining injuries in their knees
Back in risk because
Overuse of improper warm up
And
Just
I don't know I think this is kind of a stretch
I mean that's just like saying
Oh well you know
I got up and walked down the stairs
But my TV didn't tell me to warm up
Before I did activity
On top of that actually
This is something that people have been doing for years
Before you do any physical activity
It's a good idea
Even before stretching it's a good idea
To warm up your muscles
Before you even stretch
Or you're at risk for injury
In the tendons and tissue
I mean that's just
Should be common sense stuff that they teach you
When you're in school
Well I think this is kind of pointless anyways because
The Wii games aren't necessarily
High impact I mean
Wii sports tennis does not need
To be high impact it doesn't sense
You swing the
Wii mote like a tennis racket
You know you don't have to do that
You just have to move your wrist I mean
That's not
Their fault it's the fault of people playing it
That are getting way too into the game
And hurting themselves
GS68 in the chat room has a good point
At chat dot orange lounge radio dot com
He says DDR doesn't tell people to stretch either
And it's been getting you know away with it
For so so long right?
Yeah it just
It shouldn't even be a thing it's a frivolous
Lawsuit it's gonna get thrown out
I agree and you know what frivolous lawsuits
I don't know about you guys but frivolous lawsuits
Make me angry and uh
When we get angry here at orange lounge radio we cue
That nasty music and say some nasty things
Music
I have two FUs
Um the first one being the internet
Connection at my house
Because of the damn wind
Which this really isn't like
Wind but unfortunately
Sacramento has no idea
What to do when a tree moves
To be fair California in general
Yeah
But I mean
Plan for the fucking wind
We get wind storms here every so often
So just plan for it
And be prepared
For everything constant vigilance
And then um
My other FU goes
Towards um
Half dot com
The school book that I ordered
That still hasn't arrived
But um I will say that I don't think I got
Charged for it so
I have to go find the damn thing again
And I don't want to buy it from school
Because school is fucking expensive
I would rather
Be frugal because I have
Things that my money is better spent on
The end
Um
Loki do you have any FUs of the week?
Yeah FU to the rain because for the second
Week now in a row it has ruined my
Plans to go airsofting
And it's really pissing me off because
I wanted to go like weeks ago now
I have all the equipment all the ammo
Everything I'm ready to go
And it keeps fucking raining and
It always rains like on the weekend
It's dry through the week and then it starts
Raining and then wind and ugh
But so now this next
Week I'm hoping to be able to go
Airsofting it might actually have to be
That Saturday instead of Sunday morning
Which is annoying but
Actdeft in chat has a suggestion for you
He says blame it on the rain
Yeah yeah
Forget it
Ah that's funny but right now
Um I have a feeling
Though it's gonna still be raining next week
Fucking weather yeah sure it doesn't rain
All you know before this and now
All of a sudden it's just like oh rain rain rain
Rain rain rain more rain
Alright well my FU of the week
Goes to having the worst Valentine's
Day ever ever
Because I was sick and I was having what you call
Horizontal day that means I was lying on the couch
All day long so yeah made Valentine's
Day kinda suck so
And I was just bored and lonely
And sad so
You know I just wanted a hug is that so wrong
But yeah Valentine's
Day sucks but what is this just another day right
Uh Dan do you have any FUs of the week real quick
Just wanted to say FU to Ryu
Keep kicking my ass
And that's about it
Alright there you have it FU to Ryu
Alright
That's gonna do it for the FUs of the week but let's get back into some gaming
News and guess what the lawsuit stories are
Not over that's right uh
Guess who got sued this time though it's almost
A twist of fate you know how like
There's this running inside joke that like
Konami will sue like you know ever
Since they sued Rockstar which I still think they
Were in the right to sue them
I agree they were totally in the right
But some of the lawsuits since then have been
A little interesting well now
The tables have gotten turned Konami
Got sued this week yup
So now it's not Konami will sue it's
Konami got sued uh Viacom
And Harmonix sued
Konami over the game
Rock Revolution they say
That Rock Revolution violates their patents
For musical instrument peripherals
But wait a minute
Um didn't Konami kind of
Invent the well nevermind
Anyhow uh the complaint was
Filed this week in a federal court in
Boston which is where Harmonix is based
The complaint wants to stop the sales of
Rock Revolution and wants cash compensation
Well please the sales were already
Stopped I don't know I don't think you need it
Done Matt done there you go
You win congrats
Um I don't know
But I guess well more so they probably want
Cash for it and they probably want
Uh I don't know some type of
Uh I would say you know
It's sad to say I would say that Rock Revolution
Impacted the sale
Of Rock Band in no way whatsoever
I know for real right
I can't say I can't honestly say there has been
One person on the face of the earth that said
Ooh Rock Revolution that's way better than
Rock Band
But this is so strange apparently
Even though the Viacom patent um
Says that it improved on earlier
Video game music controllers and even kind of references
Beatmania uh
They're still but this is the weird thing
About it Konami didn't put out
A new guitar with this game
They put out a new drum set
Which probably sold five of them
Unless the internals of the drum set are you know
Something similar to what's you know
Put out there but their drum set
Looked like their old drum set for Drummania
I mean it
Looked like crap and it
Apparently played like crap so I don't understand
I don't know
Other than maybe it's like well fine you
Sue us but we're gonna sue you back
We'll sue you too
SSJ100 Matt
SSJ100 Matt in chat says uh
Aaron or YYR takes pride
That Snake 360 has outsold
Rock Revolution
That's probably a true fact I wouldn't doubt that at all
I wouldn't doubt it
He does have gut mechanics
We got um Rufus
Rufus now fighting by the way they're saying
Justin TV's back up you might want to try to connect one more time
On the thing then the folks can see this
And at least the live listeners
Will get to understand what we're talking about
Even if the podcast listeners are screwed
Nope still not working
No that's a bummer
Alright well anyhow
Yeah it'll be interesting to see how this one
Turns out I wonder if they'll settle I wonder if
Somebody's just trying to make a point I have no
Idea yeah frisbee in our chat room sums it up
Lawsuit ping pong that's
Exactly what appears to be happening here
I cannot see
There's no case here I mean it's just
You know it didn't affect
Their sales at all I mean
It really the sales of rock revolution
Were so friggin poor
That I don't see how they can say
Oh well our sales were impacted
You know if it's guitar hero rock band
Maybe there's you know something there but
And I know it seems like we're always
Siding with Konami on this show but
You know don't take that too
Much because honestly we're just saying
That having to put your name on
Rock revolution was punishment enough
I mean it's not good
You know financial
Liability I don't think
Is warranted but what do I know I'm not a judge
I mean I can say maybe that
They I don't think they
Do they have vocals in rock revolution
I don't think they did I don't think they're the
Actual songs I think they're
Oh yeah no you don't sing along I think it's
All cover bands
So
Hell I don't know
Whatever it's what the point it's what's the
Point the game yeah
Something like that well here's something that our
World of warcraft listeners will be more interested in
Yay
Have you actually gone back to play
Not yet but what you're about to tell us might
I'm very proud of you
Oh my god it's still moving
Sorry I'm very proud of you
If you've resisted the urge
I have it's been like three weeks now
Ooh tap that vein
Well
There's more about the dual talent
Stuff in case
You were interested
Um you know the dual talent
Spec system is coming out in the game
Um
And it's going to have
It to where you can switch
Your characters between your
Customization setups
One for rating one for pvp
And possibly one you know
Between you know one for healing and one for
For damaging
Um the option is only going to be available
Um
If once you have hit
Level 80 first
And um
Basically the reason
Is um according to
Greg Street who is uh
Ghostcrawler
That they didn't want to make the game more complex
For lower levels who are still trying to learn
Their class
Um but there
He said if it proves popular then they will
Consider expanding it
She'll basically pay a one time fee
Um to your in game
Class trainer
To access your dual specs and after
That you can switch between
Um the two at any lexicon
Of power in any city
Um
Also if you
Have the inscription profession
You can sell portable lexicon
Of power that will require
A group of players to summon and use
Anywhere but during combat
Or in arena
So nice
So you can switch roles in the middle
Of a raid
Basically like if you need
For instance I'm thinking in Naxxramas
You can get through most of the um
Event with just two healers but it's really
Nice to have a third healer
For four horsemen so just imagine
Before you engage four horsemen okay let's summon
The lexicon of power and we're going to have our druid
Switch from uh Boomkin to resto I mean that's
That's going to be a that's going to change
The dynamics big time
Well with the specs themselves
You'll get um the dual setup
With your action bars and your glyphs
That will just switch automatically
When you change over to the other spec
Um
There will also be a gear manager
That will allow you to change between
Your equippable items
Um for or you know
Whether they be individual
Or entire equipment sets
Between the two specs
So
So it's it seems pretty complex
Um
But they're actually saying that it's
Going to be on the public test server soon
But not immediately
Available um
And that the gear it they said though
That it would be starting off with
Possibly the next content patch
But the gear manager is not going to be
Um at the same time it'll fall later
Yeah it'll probably
It'll probably be a little while before we actually see this
Go into the game but I think they're doing the
Star patch is what 3.1
And so that's probably when we'll start seeing
Dual specing but the gear thing will probably
Be a little while so
There you go and uh
The chat
The chat is uh making fun
Of me for knowing exactly all this
WoW talk and all that
I was sitting here wondering if you were speaking another language
Oh shut up
Somewhere out there there are listeners of this
Program that play WoW that understand perfectly
Well what I just said
There are some people who quit
Who understand what you're talking about
There you go there you go
Alright so then we better talk about another gamer
I'm going to get right back on the WoW bandwagon
Luckily I have Street Fighter 4
To ogle over and Dan is right now on the last boss
Seth who looks like um
He looks like the glowing guy
From the Watchmen trailers to me
That's what he looks like
Uh yeah and he's a cheap bastard
That has like the um specials
From a whole bunch of different characters
Um I don't know
This is not Doral
Thank you Tigerclaw
Doctor Manhattan that's what I was trying to think of
He looks like Doctor Manhattan to me
He also has very um
Abnormal muscles
In a true anatomical sense
He ate a spinning ying yang
No no no no I'm talking about
He has got like um
Going down from a solar plexus
In between his ribs
To between his major abdominals
He's got a whole ridge of like
Bonus muscles
That don't exist
Sorry I noticed this stuff
I'm just messing
Alright sorry Loki
He's got extra muscles in his ass
Anyways
There's a game coming out on
PC and
In April and possibly
Well in the PS3 I guess in
Quarter 3 this year
Free Realms it's a free mmo RPG
And it's uh I guess
Kinda geared towards kids
And uh you will be able to play it for free
On the Playstation Network
Um whenever that happens to come out
So that's kinda neat
And it's um I guess
I don't know if it's gonna be I'm assuming
It's one of those free to play but you have to
Pay for upgrade type you know things
But uh hey free's good I guess
It doesn't look that bad
But I don't know I haven't really played it
Well okay then
Well Street Fighter 4
Mania is sweeping not just
The US but Japan and
When do I say Mania I mean
Mania 86,000
Copies sold in the first day alone
In Japan and if that doesn't
Sound like a lot of copies you need to
Understand this they are sold out in
Japan you can't find this game in Japan right now
86,000 was the first pressing
And uh it's gone
Uh apparently they are gonna try and crank some more
Of these guys out as fast as they can but uh
Right now they're like Nintendo Wii's
Trying to find these guys
Not easy I wonder if the same thing
Is gonna happen over here in the US I don't think fighting games
Are as big here but I
Definitely think this is the type of thing that you're probably
Gonna be hoping you had a pre-order for
Or you're gonna have to run to Best Buy when they open or
The stores that don't do actually even Best Buy does pre-orders now
Huh who doesn't do pre-orders
Circuit City well look what happened to them
Kmart doesn't do pre-orders so you'll have to run
To Kmart at noon that's true if you ever want to get
A game on launch day go to Kmart because no one
Shops at Kmart if you remember the old
Orange launch radio piece of advice
No one shops at Kmart
Actually I shop at Kmart now
You know why? Because the target
Right over here by the house
Is closed for remodeling till October
They're turning into an Uber
Target or whatever
Yeah I think it's turning into a Greatland
So the target is closed
For the foreseeable future
And I will not go to Walmart
So and
The other target Greatland is kind of a ways away
Why won't you go to Walmart? I'll just go to
Because it's dirty in its ghetto
Well that's because it's the Rancho Cambodia
Walmart because it makes you hate humanity
For real
So I would rather go to Kmart honestly
So there you go
How's that for some rule reversal?
Misty says hey I shop at Kmart right after Christmas
Got some cute jeans
There you go
They came from the 80s?
Are the jeans bedazzled
In the back
That type of 80s style
No they're stonewashed
Rob
They're acid washed
Nice
Alright
Can we move on?
Why am I actually explaining
The difference between Target and Target Greatland
Greatland has more shopping
I'm not even being paid
More grocery shopping
Not a full grocery store
It's like a Super Walmart without being awesome
Without the produce and without the beef
Anyhow sorry
I'm done with Street Fighter IV
Did you want to talk about the next game Dark Sakura?
Well
How about some Star Trek Online
How about it?
We were talking about the character trailer last week
And it's pretty
They're saying the O.L.Aureans
The official alien race
Of Orange Dodge Radio and yes
They are orange
Well maybe
But they're actually saying
There will not
Be
Any famous
Star Trek personas
Available in Star Trek Online
They're basically saying
It's in the future where the majority of the
Known characters have passed
On except for the ones that are robots
Holograms, ghosts
Etc, etc
Or Spock
So we could see data?
No he died
Oh that's right
Damn it
I don't remember
Ok trackies help me out
What happened to Lure?
I think he got disassembled
There's always more of them
I want Q
I want there to be a freaking Q mission
And I want a Q mission
Ok
However they have actually
Been talking to
Some
Other folks
And
They don't really
I don't think they've ruled it out
Cryptocast hasn't ruled it out
It's not likely
Although who knows what might happen
With those transporter accidents
Oh Dan's
Bringing out the big guns
Dan is still trying to fight the last boss
Of the game and is having trouble
He's a cheap bitch
It's why he can't beat him
It's massive jaw
Did Seth suck you in
His stomach and then shoot you out?
Because that's what it looked like in that one part
That's disgusting
It's massive jaw
Versus person with
Who's been taking too much collodial silver
You know that turned you blue for real
Wow
You're a chemistry nerd
I'm not I just happen to know that because
I have an odd interest in skin diseases
Right we're going to get to the mailbag here soon
But a couple more stories for you first
Well guess what there's a new artist coming to
Rock band
Is it someone good?
No it's not Miley Cyrus
Danny Minogue
It's Snoop Dogg
Just when I think of
Rock band I think of Snoop Dogg
Yes Snoop Dogg
He is coming to Rock band
Download content
No word on what
Songs they're actually going to put in Rock band
But I don't know many of them
That are rock-ish
I don't know
Who cares let's just play Gin and Juice
Act deaf says
Faux shizzle
You want to go riding with the homies
Wasn't that Coolio?
Coolio is rolling with the homies
Coolioer
Sorry
Please tell me there's some other bands
That make more sense for Rock band
Yeah there's some other stuff coming too
White Zombie
Which makes me happy
There's two songs from White Zombie
Black Sunshine and More Human Than Human
More Human Than Human
I love that song
Wasted Again by Turbo Negro
Those are coming this week to
Rock band
The only bad thing about White Zombie is they really make me want to break things
Like when I listen to their music
Don't you want to break stuff?
No but
Going back to the whole
Hip-Hop artists being in Rock band
There was actually a remix of
Some
Not Tupac
Some actual
Puff Daddy song
I think that was
They did a Rock version of
That would be pretty
Fit for Rock band although I think it's kind of old
I remember seeing this back when I was playing
Qzar
Years ago
You know what song I'm surprised they haven't put in there?
Is the Public Enemy Anthrax
Bring the Noise
Where is that?
Or I was going to suggest
The Run DMC in Aerosmith
But that was actually in the Aerosmith
Guitar Hero wasn't it?
That was in Guitar Hero Aerosmith
We need actual rocking out
We need Anthrax
Anthrax and Public Enemy
I still say we need GWAR
We need GWAR
GWAR
We need Rock band GWAR
Or Rob Zombie
I'd be good with Rob Zombie even though White Zombie
They have some Rob Zombie
Anyhow
Let's do some more news
I have one more story here
It's about G.I. Joe
Naturally they're making a game
Out of the new movie
Which I'm sure a lot of folks saw
It's coming out soon
EA was actually showing off the game
At the little convention that was going on
Apparently MTV blog
Actually interviewed
The folks behind the G.I. Joe game and found out
Knowing is half the battle
PSAs
They're going to be in the game
If you do well as you play the G.I. Joe game
You will unlock vintage
Educational clips
Where G.I. Joe comes out and does
This little spiel and says
And now you know and knowing is half the battle
So that's pretty amazing
So awesome
Now you have a reason to get this
If you don't have them all
On Beta Max tape or something like that
I don't know
Anyhow let's take a minute
To open up the old mail bag
And see what you guys have to say
Every week you guys email us
At mailbagorangelaunchradio.com
We rip open the email bag
And see what you guys have to say
Nothing no mail
That's a lie I saw at least three in there earlier
There's three
Sup lords of O.L.R
As you maybe know
I listened and wrote this
Misg
On my iTouch
Last Sunday I wept because
I tried to listen live on allgames.com
But it didn't work
FOUNTY FACE
How can you guys broadcast live to iTouch
And hell even PSP listeners
Other than that I told you I got
Endwar last week
And beat it in five hours and lied to Blockbuster
About it being broken
LOL I'm just cheap like that
The game was basically Company of Heroes
On the PC with mic support
Which was state of the art
And worked
My brother just picked up four kickass games today
Random capitalization
And this weekend is gonna kickass too
The games were
Gears of War 2, GTA 4,
Rainbow Six, Vegas 2, and Lost Planet
I've got an ass ton
Of games to play
I'll tell you what I thought of them next time
Until the next email you hear from me
Goodbye
This is from RJ
Um
I am gonna say this
Given how much texting I do
On my iPhone
It is possible to
Capitalize and use proper grammar
And spell shit correctly
Especially when it fixes it for you
Other than that
Really the only way
To really listen to the podcast
Through your
iPod or iPhone
Is gonna be
To download the
Podcast
We don't have it available live
And the PSP is the
I thought we had a live player on PSP
We do, you have to be on
The PSP to see it though
So yeah
You gotta
Next email
Um
Rini here
With greetings to the three hosts
And Ferret
He says hello as well
I'd like to
Take this particular email to hype a game
It's not necessarily
About the gameplay itself but more the
Experience
I initially meant this towards Sky and Dark Sakura
Loki may not get it
But he may be mildly amused
But I thought oh well let's get your listeners in this
Before I say the name of the game
I'd like to ask for any chat room listeners
Who have played it to not spoil
Anything about the game
I guess that was in caps so I screamed it
Thank you
The name of the game is Aversion
To compel everyone to play this simple
Game here are a few reasons
It's free and played on your PC
With low system requirements
It's two hours
It's a platformer but it's not very hard
And lastly it's cute with a secret
Oooh Navy Seals
And again it's meant to be
An experience
And worth it for the true ending
And there are two endings
Here's the link for everyone
It's zarat.us
Z-A-R-A-T dot U-S slash T-R-A
Slash offline dash games
Slash eversion E-V-R-S
I-O-N dot HTML
Hold on
Rob
Sorry
I'm dying here
And
They're doing other things
He's
He's working on Disney TV
Because it says it's working but it's not working
It's the
Phantom working
See Seth
Is a cheap bastard
You know
The first round you can hand him
He's like oh I suck
And then the second round he's like eh you're dead
And they're like well you might win
Aw
See that's why you have to switch it to one round
Per battle and then
The first round he was like
I can't even fight
I'm like yeah
Alright
Extra credit to Sky
If he'll make a video of himself playing the game blind
Never playing it before
Not literally blind
Now I'm going to poke his eyes out
With audio commentary and uploading it to the neglected
OLR YouTube channel
Just saying
Although it's not worth it if someone doesn't
Make sense of the proper reaction
And a random question
Will OLR support the DSI with podcasts
In AAC format
For those too lazy to
Lazy to confront them from MP3
I'll give you the generic answer
Maybe
Thank you for your response
You're welcome for your response
This email brought to you by the Mirror Room from Silent Hill 3
With a weird
Scrunchy face
Last email
Mike
In Australia again
Hey
Just wanted to say thank you to Rob
And All In Chat a fortnight ago
That recommended Chrono Trigger
Although it's not a game I generally
Would play I got the game on
Rob's and the OLR's recommendation
And have been really enjoying it
Might have to try Super Metroid if Rob picked it as
The number one game above Chrono Trigger
Hey
If there's
If there's any
Other DS games you can recommend
Regardless of type of game
I would like to hear your suggestions
Hope everyone in the OLR world
Is doing well and look forward to getting the podcast
Updated soon. Thanks Mike
Um
Well I know I've
Said this is Castlevania Order
Of Ecclesia is a lot of
Fun
I do really like Cooking Mama
Um
There is
Of course the western
Release Elite Beat agents you can maybe
Find Osutetaki, Oendan
Or Oendan 2
From Japan
Um
There's a number of good RPGs out though
I mean there's just a bunch of really good
Games out there
Um
But I do um
I do totally recommend
Order of Ecclesia I mean if you really want to know
What I'm playing
I'm grabbing my DS case
Right now while Rob
Is fixing Justin TV and I'll let you
Know what the hell's in it right now
Let me grab this
Monstrosity of a case
Right there
Uh which of course half of them fell down and
Sorry if you hear the random noises
I'm trying to fix Justin TV I'm not having much luck
Though
I think I just lost a game in your couch Rob
I think us trying to upgrade
The encoder thing
Woo hoo! Dan finally did it
Broke Justin TV so I don't know
With Dan! Dan beat Seth with Dan
Nice
And of course right as
Dan beats the game
With Dan
I can't get stupid Justin TV to work
I'm pissed
If I meet someone named Seth I'm just gonna punch him in the face
Oh I think I know why
Because
Well anyway the games that are currently in
My um case at this point in time
Um and then maybe this will
Give you an idea
Yes
Oh Dan's got a fun ending with Blanca
Aka Jimmy and
Sakura and Ryu
And um
Oh my god spoilers
I'm not gonna say anything else
So the games in my case right now are Final Fantasy 6
For Advance
Um Polarium
Um Trauma Center
This is currently in my DS
Um I have
Castlevania Order of Ecclesia, Cooking Mama 1 and 2
Um
Puyo Puyo Fever
Or sorry Puyo Pop Fever
Animal Crossing Wild World
Otsutataki Oendan
And um Doctor Who
Top Trumps from um
The UK which given that you're in Australia
I'm sure that you won't have a problem
Getting that so that's what's currently
In my uh
System right now
So maybe that'll give you some ideas
Um by the way
I want to go back since I was futzing with Justin
TV I wanted to kind of correct one thing one listener
Was saying and that was about um being able to listen
To Orange Lawn's radio on your iPhone
Oh here's the other game
You actually can listen live you have to use an app like
Tuner um tuner is what I use that's a pay
App but I know there's a free one as well
Out there that you can use to tune in to like
All games radio when we're live on Sunday night
So you can listen on the phone iPhone
Just like you can on the PSP I just wanted to uh
Correct that uh the other game that's in here
The one that I lost to your couch
Yes the world ends with you
Oh you don't want to lose I mean you do want to lose that one
On my couch no I don't Rob
Woohoo
Alright
So anywho I'm just looking at the new website
The OL Army Picks and I finally see the
Asakura vs Dan that's not the greatest quality
Though if Justin TV stays down
We'll try to make a YouTube after the show
Um of like a
Ten minute review of Street Fighter IV
Maybe that can be a fun thing we can do
I don't know Loki's trying to work like mad to get Justin TV back up
We'll see what happens
Anyhow meanwhile if that does it for the mailbag
I'm going to say send us more mail
Mailbag at Orangelandsradio.com
Also if I'm not over
This by next week someone else is reading
Mailbag
Alright we'll see I can always do that I guess
If my cold goes away
Loki uh we've got some couple more news stories
And we're going to open up the skype line at
2007 game OLR not just yet almost there
Couple more news stories for you guys
Yeah
Um anyways
So there's um an interesting
Lawsuit taking place here
Or about to take place
Apparently Activision is threatening
EA with a lawsuit over
Brutal Legends
And Activision is saying that
Um
Basically that you know even though they
Abandoned the publishing rights
You know
That somehow they're you know do some money
It doesn't make any sense actually
If you think about it but um
Apparently
You know uh you know after the merger
With Vinvidi because they were originally going to
Purchase or publish Brutal Legends
Um you know Activision didn't
Bring it on because they wanted to keep their core franchises
Like Spyro
And Crash
God
Anyways stuff that they can make you know multiple
Um releases for
Well EA picked it up and now you know
Activision wants money
So I don't get how that's possible
But okay
Um and it's actually funny because um
EA had put out a comment too about it
As well
Regarding the whole Brutal Legends
Thing they um attributed
To it's like um
You know we doubt Activision would try
To sue that would be like a husband
Abandoning his family and then suing
After his wife meets a better looking guy
That's the most awesome
Comparison I've ever heard but I mean it makes
You know what they're saying makes sense it's kind of like
Well you guys didn't want to put out this game so
We're giving them an outlet and now you're saying
No you can't do it
It's weird
I mean they want money
They do but then why won't they just put out the game
Because they're afraid of
Someone else making money I don't it's weird
The whole thing's weird
Yeah basically saying that they were still in talks with
Them about putting out the game
Well too bad or is that
One of the things that's like oh well shit
If it's going to be such a big deal maybe we should
Put out this game after all
Well yeah exactly it's like
Oh well we were in talks you know but
That's like saying you know I was about to buy
A car and some guy you know I've been dicking
Around oh I'm looking around at some other
Things I may buy that car I'll let
You know and then some guy comes in and buys a car
I'm not going to go sue the guy because
He bought my car if you
Stop dicking around for it you know and you
Didn't think that you thought that Spyro
Would do a lot better than this
Which I can tell you right now when they
Made that announcement originally I was like
Are you fucking kidding me that they're going to drop
Ghostbusters and
You know Brutal Legend because they want
Spyro and Crash
What?
So in other words stop dicking around Activision
Stop being retarded
You know what big fucking whoop
Oh no now you can't sell Brutal Legend
You know what it's not going to break you
You've got like 50,000 Guitar Hero
Games coming out you've got Call of Duty
What's your problem you have plenty
Of IPs that are coming out that are going to be
Successful just get over it
Alright our old buddy Bobby wants to make a point here
Bobby Black Wolf in chat says
Activision doesn't want to publish it but they want the money for it
Like they got from Atari for Ghostbusters and Riddick
Yeah Atari paid Activision
For the rights to publish the game
EA is not paying Activision to publish Brutal Legend
EA is not that beat down yet
It'll be interesting to see what comes of this
We'll see
Sadly the person that's going to get hurt here
The folks behind Brutal Legend
Including the same gentleman who is responsible for Psychonauts
Bummer
It'll get published
Eventually
It was never going to be a big hit
I hate to tell you this it's a
It's a niche-y title
It's not going to sell a gajillion copies
Of Activision passed on it
But I mean
The thing is you got to go
You got to go with the
Safe titles
And then you got to go with the titles that are
Going to get you some acclaim
And EA is kind of learning that
Because they went from doing
All the safe bets
All the time and everybody was like
Fuck EA
Their games are horrible
I mean what else can they spew out of
And crap and then they started bringing out
All these great games like
Dead Space and Mirrors Edge
And
These games that have kind of more
Limited audiences but
You know they're getting EA some
Recognition as hey
I remember when EA could make a game
I freaking sold a copy
Of Mirrors Edge last week practically
I remember Matt was here last week
We played the demo after the show and he totally
Was like oh I got to get this game this is awesome
I was like I sold a copy of Mirrors Edge
Where's my sales money
It's a fantastic game and
You know they're going to build new
Franchises and Activision sold
Their future franchises
For old tired franchises
That
Aren't with the developers that made them famous
Anymore and are pieces of
Crap you know Crash
Is done I mean yeah
Every Crash game is going to sell
250,000 copies
Consistent the kids know the brand
I sold a Crash game the other day
It hurt my heart but you know
Crash of the titans
Boy that's family entertainment
You know but you look at like
This Ghostbusters game which has had
Screenshots out for like what a year
I have demo discs saying that I could get it last
October it looked great
Then and
Atari I think is going to have a
Hit on their hands that they need and
Maybe they can break out of that
You know yeah we make Dragon Ball Z
And it keeps us in business
That they've been in for the last few years
Yeah
Black Wolf brings up a good point it still has the
Ghostbusters lanyards from PAX
All of us that went to Penny Arcade Expo are lanyards
Were Ghostbusters games
That was like the day before they pulled the plug on it
You know and really Activision
Just for whatever reason they sent out the nicest
Little Ghostbusters pre-sell
Kit it came with an Ecto-1
License plate that I shanked
It came with Ghostbusters lanyards
A demo disc a t-shirt
I mean it was a nice little kit and the box
Looked like a trap
And it had like goo
Oozing out and it says do not open until
October 2008
It was pretty sick you know you gotta wonder
It's just like why put all that energy into it and then just be like
Oh yeah we got Blizzard on our side now
F this game
I mean Activision published Ghostbusters
Back in the day for the NES
And the Sega and the Commodore
And they figured it would be you know poetic
That they're gonna carry it on
No not so much
We're gonna just let it go
It's kinda weird
It'll sell it'll be just like
Psychonauts where it'll be that game
Nobody buys when it comes out except for the enlightened few
The unwashed masses
Don't understand it won't get it
And then it'll be expensive on the secondary market
As somebody who wants to be newly hardcore
Figures out that it's out there
And has to get their hands on it
You know
It'll be one of those titles
Alright
Well we got one more news story for you guys
And we're gonna open up the skype line
Take some quick calls at 1877 game OLR
username on skype orange lounge radio
And it's about the Beatles game that's coming out later this year
This
It's not Rock Band Beatles
It's just the Beatles that will probably look a lot like
Rock Band
Well finally we have some insight as to what this game might be like
It's from an interview with Entertainment Weekly
It's Paul McCartney
Actually has talked about the Beatles music game
Saying 45 Beatles songs will be in this game
From different periods of the Beatles histories
Including early days tracks
Liverpool, Psychedelic
And on from there
Because you know McCartney really knows what this game is all about
He's probably right down there
With the dev team jamming out on the plastic guitar
You know what though
He probably has him and George Harrison
Probably have control and Yoko
Has control over everything
Oh they got mad control
I mean this game like every pixel that goes out on this game
Has to be signed off by Yoko Ono
Yeah they got mad control
I'm sure these are gonna give you you know
Deep compelling you know gameplay tidbits
You know what though this could be
This could be pretty awesome
I mean the Beatles
Oh this is necessary
This is so necessary
Next to Rock Band Journey
This is the most important title they could possibly do
Nope
I made a bad faux pas George is the one that's dead
I meant Ringo Starr not George Harrison
George Harrison has control from hell
Ringo's got nothing
And actually it's you know
Yoko
Yoko's got all the power
McCartney's got all the money
And Ringo's like I was a Beatle once
Sorry about that
That's alright
Your British accent is probably better than mine
But anyway yeah
This is a game that's very very necessary
Because like what
There hasn't been a big
Beatles thing for this generation
You know what I mean
These kids today
Don't have anything to respect the Beatles with
If that makes any sense
Well I had a conversation the other day
With actually a couple people
And over the course of like two weeks
I talked to two people about
What do the Beatles mean anymore
And obviously
We're all old enough
With probably the exception of my lovely wife
Who's you know a young
We're all old enough
Just giving you some credit there
She's 26 doesn't look a day over 22
Old enough to realize that
The Beatles mean something
It's not that we were
Listening to the Beatles
Avidly you know when we got into
Whatever was our popular music
But you know we knew that the Beatles
Were super important to our parents
They were super important to music
And everybody we listened to would claim the Beatles as an influence
Right it trickled down
And we knew that the Beatles were important
What do today's
Music listeners
Today's 14 year old what do they know about the Beatles
Pretty much what they hear from the older
Generation or just that
There's the fashion fad going around again
You know they have the
You know merchandising happening again
I mean but really
They
This is one thing that I'd actually like to consider
Is that our time we don't really know
War
On the scale of what was going on
During that time listen to me
We don't know war of that type
We don't have people being
Drafted and forced to go into a war
That they don't believe in
We don't have
You know being stuck in such
And true we do have
The religious right trying to
Keep us in that phase
But we're going from a time of completely
Stodgy
Everyone's the same into complete
Individualism and the you know
A massive revolution
We're not talking the message
We're talking the music and the band
The music is the message
Just strictly
What do kids today know about
The Beatles and I'm not trying to diss on the Beatles
I'm not trying to diss on today's kids
I'm really just trying to make the
Point that they're not really
So much into
The Beatles I mean it's
Definitely an example of gaming skewer towards
Skewing towards the older demographic but
It's like yeah it's gonna bust
You know maybe some younger
Players some Rockman players into the Beatles
But I mean this is a huge deal
I mean everyone's making the fucking
World of how important this is
You can't even get the Beatles on iTunes
Cause the control over the library is that tight
But what is this really gonna mean to your
Average guitar hero Rockman player
You can't get it on iTunes
Because of the big spat between
Apple computer and Apple
Core
But you know
I don't think it's gonna matter cause I think everybody's
Parents are gonna buy it I think all these kids
I think the parents are all gonna
Buy this stuff up and even some of the kids
Although I gotta say though a lot of you know
You said earlier a lot of the bands we
Grew up on were influenced by the Beatles
A lot of these bands today I hear in
Interviews I've heard a lot of them say they were influenced by
David Bowie this is not a bad thing at all
So
Yeah I'm just you know
I'm looking forward to
Rockman the Beatles or whatever it's gonna be
Except for the fact that
They're probably gonna screw us and won't let us
Import the music into Rockman 2
But I mean come on you know you wanna do it
Like the ACDC that would be the only thing
That made it worth buying is the fact that
I could just dump it all into Rockman you know
And add to this stupidly awesome playlist already
But I wanna see
You know from the standpoint of
Of someone who works
In the absolute bowels of the
Industry I wanna see
How this game's gonna sell when it gets to stores
Cause there's not really any buzz about it
I don't have people standing in line to
Reserve the Beatles I don't have people standing in line to
Reserve even Guitar Hero Metallica
I think the Guitar Hero fad is kinda starting to die
Um and I
Like I said earlier in the show you know
How to run a franchise into the ground I think that
I think they're barking up the wrong tree
I think this is gonna be the last
Ah out there is this Beatles game
And then it's gonna be all downhill from there
I think this is gonna be the last hurrah
Well I just think it's actually
Pretty sad that
With the current generation
Is starting to lose relevance
I mean it's
Hideous but
I mean I understand it but
I still think it's horrible
Who influenced the Beatles?
See that's the thing is it's just the passage
Of time we don't know why they
Became what they became you know
Um and
I influenced the Beatles
Drugs influenced the Beatles
What bands did the Beatles listen to?
I mean I know we could go on the internet and look it up
And find out but I mean you know it doesn't have
The relevance because it's not
It's not as important anymore
You know we know that all the great bands
That we listen to listen to the Beatles when they were growing
Up and so we're like man the Beatles must kick ass
What did the Beatles listen to?
The answer is who cares?
It's too far back for a story about your average
15 year old player ain't worried about
The Beatles hell Guitar Hero Metallica
Like I said is not really making as big
A deal as I think they need to come up with
Something newer and popular
And topical that's
Gonna get you know the dollars
Out of the pockets and
So far it's like really I think
All of the track packs the
Band editions whatever
Have been sort of
Sort of fail
Couple comments from chatroom I gotta read
Chat.orangelandrater.com Black Wolf says
I don't want it to be something that I can say hey
I wish I could just import these into rock band
I hope it's different enough to see it on its own
Merits rather than just another track pack
Sure and that's cool
But once you're in a party setting
And you wanna play
Some Beatles and then you wanna play
You know some Casey and the fucking
Sunshine band and you wanna play
Some Metallica and you wanna play some
Who and you wanna play some this and you wanna play
Some that you're not gonna bust out the rock
Band 2 disc that has 500
Songs on it and put in the Beatles
Disc that has 40 songs on it
To play a couple songs that's gonna sit on the shelf
If you're hardcore enough to own it
Unless they do a disc swap thing like
Singstar does that could happen
Still you don't jump up and just go I'm gonna switch
Discs yes you're gonna be like
Man I'm gonna play some other song
We do that with Singstar
Singstar's awesome
Bullymania in chat says Singstar Abba
Went back in time and influenced the Beatles
Yes
Remember though when we used to play
We used to play
What the hell game was it
No
Beatmania when we used to
Switch out our Append discs
Oh yes the Appends
It was kind of a pain in the ass though
That was a good point
But it was all we had and now there's a better way
I will own
The Beatles
Whether it's the rock band Beatles whether it's what
Because I'm of not that generation
But the generation after and you know
I have the Beatles on my
iPod even though I don't own any
Vinyl you know
I like the music
Especially some of the later stuff
You know the earlier stuff just doesn't do it for me
But it's just like you know they're important
You know you should own it
If you're into
If you're into the niche
I mean it's not really even a niche but if you're into the part of the industry
Which we are which is music
Games
If you own Drummania controllers
You should probably own this fucking game
And if you don't
It's gonna depend on how big of a
Beatles fan you are
Unless they completely bastardize it
Which is a possibility sadly
Which totally is but I don't
I don't really believe that
With Yoko having control I don't believe it either
Well it's not just Yoko having control
Cause take Yoko and John Lennon
And the dead Beatles and the living Beatles
And all that out of it
Harmonix
Is gonna have such reverence
For the source material
That there is no possible way
That's true if they fuck it up
There will be no forgiveness
Yeah exactly if they mess it up
There will be pitches
There will be torches and pitchforks
And people will be dying
And I mean well you laugh
But that's all there is
It's gonna be brutal the fallout
Plus you know
If you thought the ET game fallout was bad
There's money
Being thrown at this
This is an expensive project
This is a
This is a deal breaker for harmonix
If they mingle this
You know it's
It's over
But act deft has a point harmonix never ever fails to deliver
Harmonix has very rarely
Failed in any way shape or form
Amplitude was a little
Disappointing after frequency
And I know I'm gonna get some people being like
F you pal for that
But frequency was just better
Alright F you pal
We're gonna open it
Hey if you wanna tell Dan F you pal to his face
F me
You can call in right now
Flip me off
I'm flipping myself off
Amplitude was a great game
Our username on skype
Is orange lounge radio
And you can tell Dan F off right now
Let's open up the phones
We have a caller on the line
Hi who's this?
Hi this is Spazinator
Just
Two or three really
Quick things
Regarding tonight's show
Yes
Regarding the whole using
Of trained cats for
advertising
What if something goes
Wrong with the cats
What if there is like a catastrophe
Using I'm sorry using the what?
Using the trained cats
For the advertisement
You mentioned in part A
I believe of the show
Oh the cats what if something goes wrong
What if something goes wrong with the
The trained cats
That are doing the
PETA's gonna write a nasty letter
I'm sorry
What was that?
I said PETA's gonna write a nasty letter
For one I don't know I guess I'm assuming
These things are under watch I don't think they
Just have these kitties all roaming the streets
Aimlessly I mean there's gotta be
Something where
They've got the cats tracked
Somehow or the cats are
They're being watched
Which seems like a lot of fucking
Work for a stinking ad campaign
But there's gotta be something they're doing
No doubt that's easy
I don't know if I was like
I don't know if I had a mic when you guys were talking
Yeah I was playing Street Fighter
Yeah that's the worst thing I've ever heard
I don't understand what the point is
Most people see a cat
Running around and they're just like hey it's a cat
I suppose if I saw a cat wearing a fear t-shirt
I'd be like hey it's a cat wearing a t-shirt
But I wouldn't go man
Fear I gotta buy that fucking game
That gets me in the mode to play some MF in 360
BlackWolf in chat wants to point out
You can see the leashes in the pictures
They're on leashes that's how they got it
Cats hate leashes by the way
You know those cats are pissed
That's a water spitting leash
That is right there
So what else did you want to call in about Spaznator?
Secondly
I know that
You guys have been complaining about
The wind out there in California
It could be a whole lot worse
I didn't know
If you guys have been paying attention
To the news
Within basketball days
But just in my
Neck of the woods
We just had kind of a semi
Major plane crash
In Buffalo don't you
I just remembered
You got this all wrong by the way
We probably actually kind of like the wind
Because wind is cool
We hate the fact that at the sign of a stiff breeze
Our internet goes down
People forget how to drive
And shit starts falling over
The storms here are nothing compared to the east coast
I'll tell you nothing compared to the east coast
We don't have hurricanes here
If we had a hurricane here we'd all die
We would be dead
If we can't deal with the hurricane winds
It's because our buildings can't
They're built for earthquakes not winds
Seriously
I swear
I really
Don't have a problem
With driving in wind
Because I have driven
In heavy wind
It's just seeing
How many people can
People running around with chickens with their heads cut off
It's nuts
I definitely have seen the news
I heard about that plane crash in Buffalo
What a tragedy
There's really no other word to describe it
Nobody was drunk
It wasn't carelessness
Everything I've heard says it was an ice thing
Causing a malfunction
It was just a tragedy
Very very sad
I can just imagine there's just reporters
And the media and things swarming
All over that town right now
Plus everybody having to deal with that
It was a flight
A lot of people were from Buffalo
So it's just very very sad
They need one of those pilots
Who managed to land a plane in the river
And not have anyone get killed on every flight
Just some sort of goddamn miracle worker
That guy is from California
He's from the wonderfully named
Town of Danville
I remember that
I'm really sorry to hear about that
You're calling us
You must be okay
Not at least
Before I let you guys go
Would you be able to give
A really really quick shout out
To my link show in Final Fantasy 11
Sure why not
We've had a lot of plugs tonight
Shout out Suck, don't do it
I just want to say hi to
Doc Scarry link show on the
Alexander server
Specifically Naggy
Naggy and
Meg and
Axl0
And everyone else
Who is online right now
Just want to say hi to everyone
Alright shout out you guys
Now go play a real MMO
Dude you so stole the words out of my mouth
I'm going to be like now please
Sell your copies
You know I'm just bitter because I spent so many years on Final Fantasy 11
But you know what
I've heard they made a lot of good changes for the better
I need to not give a shit
I would like to see them
You know because Final Fantasy 11 is over
Like what it's almost 6 years old now
I would like to see them do it
I would like to see them do a new one
Mine and Jamie's new computers absolutely
Destroy the benchmark
The benchmark program
The benchmark program is awesome it's just loaded with Taro Taro's
I know they're just like
I will say Final Fantasy 11 did bring us Taro Taro's
Alright Spazinator we're going to let you go buddy
Sure sounds good
Have a good one later
And yes I'm reminded by the chat room
That the Hello Kitty Online beta opened yesterday
So that's something I might need to check out
Hello Kitty Bob
There's the MMO you ought to be playing
Oh man we got to be all over
We need an Orange Lounge clan on the Hello Kitty Online
We need to like
But we need to be like bad people
I don't know how that works
All these great companies are going to have a business
And Sanrio just keeps plugging along
Oh got to love them
Hey you're on Orange Lounge Radio who's this
It's Hello Kitty Jason clan member 3000
Awesome what's up
Do you remember the clan
What's up Hello Kitty
Kitty klutz clan
Are you responsible for what's happening with the black DS
Cause I don't think that's right
I'm going to back away slowly from these comments
Jason please put our show back on track
What did you want to talk about tonight
That confused me a whole lot but that's okay
It's interesting that Dan talks about that pilot
That did the water landing being brought up in California
Because our news was all over the place
Cause he went to school in Colorado
There you go see
That's why he's good
Cause he moved somewhere else and learned something
What did you call in to talk about tonight Jason
Did people really believe
That Nintendo on
You mentioned in part A
That the whole
3D room environment
Of the Wii
Was still code name the revolution
Did people seriously believe
You know there was people that believed it
And I will even admit
There was a period of 5 minutes
Where I kind of wished it was true
It wasn't true believe
Actually there's something really funny
You can say about that because the first 5 minutes
Of the trailer you can completely believe
The first half of that trailer
Was beautiful
It was amazing
But when he
We just believed that Nintendo
Was going to fuck us up for life
That they were going to come up with something that was so
Bad ass
Like a video game system that you play
And it sucks your dick while you're doing it
Yes you just couldn't resist
It's awesomeness
And then they gave us the Wii
Because it was supposed to be totally revolutionary
That it's like
You know you have a system called the revolution
It's going to be
You know something very awesome
But a game system that fucks me while I play it
That's revolutionary
It was going to be something completely different
And instead
We got the last generation of console again
With
A controller that gets
Grandmas don't want to play
And that's I guess good
For everybody
Grandma would play a fuck me revolution
Who would Konami sue then?
Seriously though
It's just
It's a great console
For everybody but gamers
Or
It's a great console for gamers
With really low standards
And low self esteem
Okay
Well yeah
Because of course it's low self esteem
Because your Nintendo keeps telling you you're fat
Nintendo goes you're fat
You're ugly
Have you ever set that up? Do you half Wii Fit?
Yes I do
And you make your Mii stand there and he's looking all nice
And confident and then you jump on that board
And it detects what you weigh
And then the guy just sort of slouches
And then gets fat
And then yeah it starts harassing you
I'm sorry this is more accurate for
What you are
Exactly I played brain age
And my DS told me I was stupid
You have the brain of an 85 year old Alzheimer's patient
Your brain is 65 years old
It's tired now
You can't understand the word blue
Stupid
The next time I see Reggie I'm going to punch him in the face
Which gets hundreds of thousands
Of hits on the entire web
So I mean I don't know
It's not that what Nintendo's done isn't
Quote unquote revolutionary
To you know
The mass market video game
Public who hasn't played a game system
Since they played the 2600 from Atari
But it's not
You know the next generation for gamers
And when Nintendo was telling us
The Wii is going to mess you up
The Wii is going to be something that you will never
Expect
We're going to redefine video games
The Wii is going to take your mother out to date
And then sex her
The Wii is going to get your mom out the house
So that you can have orgasmic video game experiences
We were ready for that
And what we got was the Wii
And so I mean did we believe it?
No
Did we speculate about it? Sure
Instead we've got my mom
Who won't get off the fucking TV because she's playing
Elibits
We didn't know it was going to be
The GameCube 2
You guys talking about it
Just made me think about that trailer
The first half of it was great
But as soon as it said Nintendo on
The music changed and he actually tried to
Make up what the system
Was going to be
If
I don't know
What to do
I don't know how to describe the people that believe
The second half of that trailer
Mario looked like Luigi for crying out loud
Nintendo has never
Done that
Has never made concept art that looks that bad
Mushroom Kingdom was in a forest
The video just cut out abruptly
And
Virtual environments don't exist
You don't make games
I guess there's RPG Maker but
Yeah that made good games
Anyways
It was Nintendo trying to convince you that the world
Was going to change
If the fanboys believe it's strong enough it will come
Exactly
They were going to say look the 360 you think that's great
Maybe you see what we got for you
That's something that Sony was the master of
In the last generation
And they used that to bury the Dreamcast
Sony was the master
In the last generation just like rumble was
That's what PlayStation 2 does
Because the PlayStation 2 is going to mess you up for life
And they were sort of right
But they used it to bury the system
Nintendo just did the same thing
And it worked
It fucking worked again
From Nintendo, Nintendo watched Sony and just learned
They were like look
We're going to sit out this generation with this little GameCube
And we're going to put out some good games for the hardcore
But the next generation, we're going to dominate again
And you know what, they did
Because that's what Nintendo does
They make mistakes
And they conquer the god damn world
And you know the DS has done it
And I remember when the DS came out
Everybody was like wow
They replaced the GBA with this
This thing sucks
And look at the DS now
It's standard gamer equipment
If you don't have one
There's something wrong with you
And the Wii is kind of the same way
Except for the fact that gamers own it
Then they look at me and they go
What am I going to have to buy for it?
And I'm like Mario Kart and Smash Brothers are both worth owning
And Zelda's always fun
And if you don't own Mario Galaxy
You may as well sell your Wii
And that's it
Oh, Metroid Prime 2
That's still at least five games I guess
Those are all the Nintendo franchises
Well Jason, thank you for the lively discussion
And also thank you
While I have you on for all the hard work you and Digman did on the new website
It looks great
And I know the chatters are loving it
They're filling it up with articles
We're very excited
I know what you have to thank me for
Dan was the one that carried that whole segment
And Digman was the one doing the whole website
Practically doing all the website work
You were the one calling
I know you helped him
So thank you for the help
I know Digman probably did the biggest chunk of that
But he used to get some props
Alright well Jason we're going to let you go
Because we're going to wrap up the show
We've got to get out of here
Especially if we're going to try and do some stuff with Street Fighter 4
I don't know if Justin TV is up again
But we'll at least try to get YouTube or something
I restart my computer because
I figure maybe restarting the computer
Will make it work
Now my desktop likes to refresh itself
Over and over and over
And over and over and over
My Mac
Stopped working after I did an update
My laptop is sitting in there
I can't do a damn thing with it
I restart it and I just get the logo with the little spinning thing
And my friends online told me to use the shift
Use the S key, it still won't work
I'm not worried about that because
I haven't really done any actual updates
With this in a while so I need to do
Service Pack 3 and that kind of stuff
But it's just
It's still kind of funny
Because it's annoying
Because all my icons disappear and then they come back
And then they disappear and come back
And disappear and come back
But I'm trying it one last time here
And restarting it didn't anything
I did search on the problem too
And there was some guy that had the problem back in 2007
And no one seemed to have an answer
Except shut down
Flash Media Encoder and restart it
I'm like okay I've done that eight times now
It doesn't do anything, stupid
Alright we'll try to figure out
What's going on there but
For the meanwhile we are going to get the hell
Out of here, we're going to pack it up
And get on out because we still have the after birth
We got to do too so we got to fly through that
And get out of here so
Let's go around and first we'll get some last minute stories
Before we close up shop
Do we have last minute stories tonight?
Yes
Nice, anything else?
Loki do you have any last minute stories for us tonight?
No I don't have anything ready because I've been trying to get
Flash Media Encoder to work
Alright wow a night with no last minute stories
Then we'll go around and hear everybody's final thoughts
Dan thank you so much for being here once again
And contributing
We always love your
Opinions and such
Especially being a long time gaming fan
Come back again sometime
Yeah four or five years maybe
Alright
Any final thoughts for listeners?
Yeah Street Fighter 4
Is absolutely legit
Although
The Xbox controller
Is a way of making fighting games
It's like
Slamming your dick in a door
It's just not any fun
If you buy Street Fighter 4 for your 360
And you're not going to invest in an arcade stick
You're high
I'm thinking about getting it for PS3
Just on the controller alone even though I know more people on 360
I don't know
Dark Sakura since you're right over there
Enjoy the tea and the parting
Gifts from me
I so will enjoy the tea
I might make you save me a bag
Which I know is a dumpy thing to do for a gift
But I really want to try it
Shut up Dan
Do you have any final thoughts for listeners?
I'm glad I have tomorrow off
Because my voice hurts
Rub it in why don't you?
Loki do you have any final thoughts?
No I'm just
Pissed off now because explore keeps
Crashing and reinstalling
I just have to actually go do real
Updates because I've been
Just letting it do its crappy automatic updates
Stuff and you know
Whatever
And my final thought is I would like to be
Over having clogged up sinuses
Now
Alright there you go just approve it
Alright
That's brisk baby
Alright thank you guys so much for downloading
And supporting independent podcasting and supporting Orange
Launch Radio you know we do this for free
And we don't have any ads or any
Real source of income
It really is a labor of love like look at the new website
That was done for nothing
And everything and it's just amazing
It's your guys' support and the community that keeps us coming
Back week to week
So what do you say we do it all again next week?
Okay why not
We'll do it anyway
We'll see you here next week for Orange Lounge
Radio one more time see ya
You've been listening to Orange
Lounge Radio
Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange
Lounge production
To join us for a live show
Visit www.allgames.com
Sunday nights
At 6 p.m. Pacific time
The views and opinions
Expressed on Orange Lounge Radio
Do not necessarily reflect those
Of the entire staff of Orange Lounge Radio
Or allgames.com
But we're probably right anyway
See you next week!