[SPEAKER_02]: Tonight, February 1st, 2009.
[SPEAKER_02]: Could Wii Photo Printing come to the US?
[SPEAKER_02]: Gears of War PC breaks down and multiplayer comes to the next Bioshock game.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_05]: So yeah, she's been updating her Twitter.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you follow DarkSakura on Twitter, she's been updating her Twitter pretty regularly.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's basically the equivalent of help me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Please send help.
[SPEAKER_05]: I miss Wi-Fi.
[SPEAKER_05]: Help me.
[SPEAKER_05]: So joining us tonight, we have a different female perspective.
[SPEAKER_05]: Say hello to the one and only Rice Princess.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_05]: How are you doing, Rice Princess?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, I'm all right.
[SPEAKER_10]: How about you?
[SPEAKER_05]: Not bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Are you caring about the Super Bowl that's going on right now as we're doing the show?
[SPEAKER_10]: Resident Evil 5 Resident Evil 5
[SPEAKER_10]: I've played all of the games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Even 4 and 1?
[SPEAKER_05]: All of them?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: And if I were like a billionaire, I'd recreate the mansion.
[SPEAKER_05]: How about the movies?
[SPEAKER_05]: Are you a big fan of the movies?
[SPEAKER_10]: I actually do like the movies too.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: I heard some rumor, I don't think it made the show roll tonight, some rumor there's a fourth one that's going to be made pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you think it should keep going or do you think they need to pull the plug now?
[SPEAKER_10]: It depends on where they take the story.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know, because this last one that they came out with was an original story, and it was just, I don't know, it was alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: If they go back to the game story stuff, that would be cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll also say hello to the one and only Techmaster Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: Lou, how you doing, Loki?
[SPEAKER_06]: Fine, I'm trying to find the Transformers 2 trailer.
[SPEAKER_06]: And apparently the link that we had in our chatroom, it's not working, or at least it works, but it's not playing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I see the real reason why people watch the Super Bowl, the commercials and the movie trailers.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, if the smart people would realize that you can actually watch commercials before they come out on the Super Bowl, or at least for most of the trailers, well, not trailers, but commercials.
[SPEAKER_06]: They actually have a website that had some.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was watching them earlier.
[SPEAKER_06]: They suck.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, some of them suck, but most of them were not good.
[SPEAKER_05]: Regeneration
[SPEAKER_05]: I do want to give a special shout out to the chatters tonight because they are here during the Super Bowl.
[SPEAKER_05]: And so, you know, they're either football haters or they are very loyal listeners of Orange Lawn Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: We only have probably about, you know, there was no Bobby tonight to lead into our show.
[SPEAKER_05]: He took the night off for the Super Bowl.
[SPEAKER_05]: And we probably only have, between everything that's been going on, probably about a third of the usual listeners we have.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I want to really thank those folks that were loyal and staying tuned tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: I also want to thank, joining us tonight in studio, say hello to Silent Nathan is here again.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, seriously, how are you, Nathan?
[SPEAKER_05]: How are you doing?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm fine.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have a motorcycle.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have a motorcycle?
[SPEAKER_05]: What game do you have a motorcycle in?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I know you don't have one for real.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I would have wanted to ride in the sidecar.
[SPEAKER_05]: World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nerd.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_05]: Describe to the listeners what having a motorcycle means in World of Warcraft, and how exactly does it fit into the lore?
[SPEAKER_07]: It goes vroom, vroom, vroom, and then you can make it jump, and it's lore-wise...
[SPEAKER_07]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a motorcycle.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a motorcycle.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm Horde, so I usually have to kill the princesses and destroy the castles.
[SPEAKER_07]: But yeah, it's at least 12,000 gold just for Vendormat.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it's a lot of money.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, congratulations on your motorcycle.
[SPEAKER_05]: One day I will come back to WoW and I will ride in your motorcycle in the sidecar.
[SPEAKER_05]: It'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: You have to come back within a month, otherwise you can't.
[SPEAKER_05]: But if I stay away for three months, then somebody can use the Scroll of Resurrection on me.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that's the whole plan, actually.
[SPEAKER_07]: You should actually cancel your account, start a whole new account, and we can be the leveling buddies and we'll get awesome mounts.
[SPEAKER_05]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, let's talk a little bit about our gaming weeks in a segment we always like to start off the show with called, How was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, we'll start with you tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: How was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_06]: It was still not that eventful, but more eventful than last week.
[SPEAKER_06]: More Grand Theft Auto 4 on Xbox 360, still playing stuff, which is, you know, it's fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm looking forward to the new expansion they have coming out in the future.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: So which, of course, that person posted that everywhere on the internet.
[SPEAKER_06]: So now there is literally an official no DVD patch for the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: So they've made it pretty easy to pirate the game, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, technically you're not supposed to be able to pirate it because you still have to authenticate it and the serial number and everything like that to play online.
[SPEAKER_06]: But trust me, you don't really have to because it's
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: XBOX 360
[SPEAKER_06]: I would have to do a system restore to get a game to work.
[SPEAKER_06]: Any game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Even Crysis I had less trouble running.
[SPEAKER_06]: And goddamn Crysis is a bitch to work.
[SPEAKER_06]: And sadly enough, Crysis actually runs better than Grand Theft Auto 4.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that's telling you something.
[SPEAKER_06]: And trust me, Grand Theft Auto 4 is not... Crysis is definitely not pushing the graphics that Crysis was.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think AcidicVampire in chat sums it up very well.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a love-hate relationship for Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is a love-hate relationship.
[SPEAKER_05]: You love to hate it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anything else for your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_05]: Um...
[SPEAKER_05]: I have to ask for our spinoff show Orange Lounge Foodio.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're pretty excited about the food you brought to the show tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can you tell our listeners about this fine new cuisine of yours?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not fine cuisine, but they have these new things at Burger King called Burger Shots.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they're basically... Like when you first said the name, I was like, what popped in my head were the dessert shots from Applebee's and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm like, ew, that does not sound appetizing at all.
[SPEAKER_08]: Putting a hamburger in a glass.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, putting hamburger and ketchup and mustard in a shot glass.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's disgusting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ew.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, they're sliders.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're little mini hamburgers, basically.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can buy them.
[SPEAKER_06]: They have a two-pack and a six-pack.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why would you want a two-pack?
[SPEAKER_05]: You don't want to get fat?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: But they're okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're all right.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is the second time I've had them, and it's just kind of okay now.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not as good as their normal burgers.
[SPEAKER_06]: You don't have the smoky, flame-broiled taste to it.
[SPEAKER_06]: But they're okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: Tell us about your gaming week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Back to gaming, Rice Princess.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I'm going to play the demo of Resident Evil 5, and that's going to be my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because that's all you're going to play.
[SPEAKER_05]: I might turn around and suddenly Rice Princess is gone, and so is my Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or your PS3, because I wouldn't... I don't think they have the demo on PlayStation 3, actually.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wait, what?
[SPEAKER_10]: I thought it was on your PS3.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, it's on my Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: Aww.
[SPEAKER_05]: I used to be like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm still like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then there were a lot more games that came out.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it was a lot cheaper.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm still going to play it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm just going to put on gloves or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just pretend it's something else.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know why you have this rampant hate for Xbox, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm like, Xbox hate is so like five years ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, we're all kind of over it now.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just extreme dislike.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: My gaming week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, I didn't play a lot of new stuff in my gaming week this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kind of a lot of the old stuff, you know, Fable 2 and same stuff I've been playing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Next week, though, thanks to a very, very, very kind listener, I've got a code for Left 4 Dead now, so I'm going to be playing that on PC this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm very excited.
[SPEAKER_05]: and to follow up a question that came up last week there is an Orange Lounge Radio Steam community out there and I was able to find it very easy by going into Steam and just searching for Orange Lounge in groups so I joined it so there's about like 30 some odd people in the Orange Lounge Radio Steam group so if you are a Left 4 Dead player you're listening to this show I encourage you to join our Steam group because I'll probably be playing Left 4 Dead and I want to play with listeners but you have to promise to be nice to me because I suck at first person shooters so even
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: You never know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Pirate server that you can play on for free and I'm okay with talking about it on the show because Sega kind of turns a blind eye to the whole thing because they turned their servers off a while ago so they just kind of let this thing run so it's interesting it's kind of tough to play because I can't do a lot of the quests because they're all in the Japanese text still but it's Phantasy Star Online and it's free so I can't complain I don't think I'll play it forever but ah memories wow how long ago did that come out?
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see, if the Dreamcast is about 10 years old, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Dreamcast came out in 1999, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: I would say the first Phantasy Star Online is probably about 9 years old.
[SPEAKER_10]: Holy crap.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know, it's an old game.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: But still, there's not a lot of action-based MMOs like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't even really call Phantasy Star Online an MMO, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, it is and it isn't.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not an MMO like, wow, you go off, everything's like Instance.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's more Guild Wars, I guess, than anything.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's not even like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is pretty cool, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's really stood the test of time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Even though a lot of people hate on Universe, I don't mind Universe.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think I have Phantasy Star Online for my Dreamcast because I remember I always would play it offline.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would never play it online because I had dial-up at the time, so it didn't really make.
[SPEAKER_10]: That'd be kind of hard, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I mean, they did have a dial-up modem in Dreamcast.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, apparently this server will let you connect the Dreamcast one, the PlayStation, wasn't there a PlayStation one?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know, the GameCube one I know was on there, and the PC one.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can connect all those together on this one server.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is Blueburst, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: You can use either the Blueburst client or the Dreamcast client, and it's episode one, two, and four.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can play them all together.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, which I thought was kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just not the Xbox one, because the Xbox one was through Xbox Live, and so there's no way you can play that anymore.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because Sega shut down the server, and you can't really hack Xbox Live servers without a lot of problems.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you can, but... Again, it's not something I think I'm going to play a long time.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just, you know, nostalgia is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because, you know, honestly, the cave level gets so boring after a while.
[SPEAKER_10]: It totally does.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have you even played PSO?
[SPEAKER_10]: No.
[SPEAKER_10]: I see.
[SPEAKER_10]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: Aw, poor Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, everyone else had PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, the only reason I had Dreamcast is because I wanted to accuse our all-nighter event.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm like, oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, Dreamcast are still awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, because of the fact that you can boot, like, there's a lot of homebrew stuff for Dreamcast.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, I was actually, I'm looking to find a, because I'm not going to try to buy it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Screw that shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm trying to find a copy of Super Runabout for the Dreamcast.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because for some reason, like, I thought of this one game that I played before.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's called Felony 1179 that was on the PlayStation 1.
[SPEAKER_06]: and it's a pretty fun game.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's kind of like...
[SPEAKER_06]: Not really like Burnout, but it's a racing game where you're supposed to crash into a lot of stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, cause a lot of property damage.
[SPEAKER_06]: And as you'd play through the game, you'd unlock more cars, kind of like Burnout.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, ridiculous stuff, like, you know, meter-made cars, buses, and just all sorts of crazy stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: But Super Runabout was kind of the same game, same type of thing, and it was just really stupid fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a game they should really, you know, make a new one of, because you'd be left on Burnout with...
[SPEAKER_06]: Collateral Damage.
[SPEAKER_06]: I need to find that so I can play that again.
[SPEAKER_05]: Quite a bit of Dreamcast love coming from our chat room.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have Leo Shen saying, I still play Marvel vs. Capcom 2 on my Dreamcast all the time.
[SPEAKER_10]: I love that game so much.
[SPEAKER_10]: Did you own a Dreamcast?
[SPEAKER_10]: We did own a Dreamcast, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: TGM-GS6, there's no easy way to pronounce that, says, I need to revive my Dreamcast so I can play Border Down.
[SPEAKER_05]: They keep releasing these homebrew things every year for Dreamcast.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was just thinking today, actually, while I was playing PSO, because it got me thinking about the Dreamcast.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Dreamcast isn't even 10 years old yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not that old of a system, all things considered.
[SPEAKER_05]: Still pretty interesting, all the things you can do on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let me ask Silent Nathan real quick how his gaming week was, and then we'll move into tonight's news.
[SPEAKER_05]: Silent Nathan, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_07]: It takes a long time to make enough gold to buy a motorcycle.
[SPEAKER_05]: So wow wow and more wow?
[SPEAKER_05]: See, enough said from Silent Nathan.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Justin.tv.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I want to say thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: The problem with it though, when we tried to hook it up, we were able to get video but no audio because the video and audio was separate on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we thought it would be kind of lame to just have the video thing on Justin.TV.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I have a cord coming that's going to fix our problems, but it's just not going to get here until this week sometime because it's coming from New Jersey.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'm really, really, really, really hoping we will be back up on Justin.TV next week.
[SPEAKER_05]: And yeah, very excited about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, and then when you come over looking all pretty in the future, Rice Princess, it won't be for nothing, as you did a couple weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_05]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, also, of course, there's no DarkSakura tonight, but she will be back next week on the program, and, uh,
[SPEAKER_05]: No shows off or anything coming up for us.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're just cranking right through up until our 7th anniversary this June, if you can believe it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Possibly some conventions in our future.
[SPEAKER_05]: I am toying with the idea of going to ASEN.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you know it's very cheap to fly out to Chicago right now on Southwest?
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to go.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to do the panel and the whole nine yards.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think I'd have a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sure DarkSakura wants to go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki's wife probably won't let him go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I don't want to go either.
[SPEAKER_05]: But who knows?
[SPEAKER_05]: We will see.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to try.
[SPEAKER_06]: Trust me, if I'm going to go to one show this year, it's going to be E3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, E3.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know E3 registration opened up this week, actually.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we got to talk offline about that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: Before the end of this year.
[SPEAKER_06]: We were saying we're going to go originally to Seattle.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not really much that we really want to do in Seattle.
[SPEAKER_05]: Go to Prosser.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's where the party's at this weekend.
[SPEAKER_06]: We were going to go to possibly LA to go to Disneyland, that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: It would be around her birthday, and her birthday is the 4th of June.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's like the week before.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, that is the week of E3.
[SPEAKER_05]: E3 is like June 2nd through 4th, I'm not even kidding you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ah, fuck that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hold on, let me look.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought it was like the 13th or something.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just be like, happybirthdaybabe, you get entrance into E3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Look at all these video games I got you.
[SPEAKER_05]: I got you a goodie bag from E3, yeah, June 2nd through 4th.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ah, you ass!
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, there's no way I'm going to E3 now.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll just be like, but babe, you can get a bunch of swag.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that's not going to fly.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can walk around a bunch of smelly nerds.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that will not fly.
[SPEAKER_05]: You should at least try to get down for one day, get back in time for her birthday or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_10]: I know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, you can pull some strings now.
[SPEAKER_10]: You have connections, dude.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yeah, right.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, seriously.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, back when we went in 2005, we were still kind of fledgling.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_05]: But we also had friends that worked at a certain game company.
[SPEAKER_05]: Different places.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if I should say, because I don't know if the game company knows that they inadvertently let us in E3, but we got those tickets.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_10]: We could bring our old badges from 2005 and be like, look, we went in 2005.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, they specifically have made it like you have to reapply even if you went before.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: Damn it.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll worry about that in the upcoming weeks.
[SPEAKER_05]: We got time.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have at least till May.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, we got to get into the gaming news tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, get us into some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, it's not that exciting, but we may be getting a new channel soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently...
[SPEAKER_06]: There is a trademark.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, this is, I think, coming to Europe first.
[SPEAKER_06]: There was a trademark on the European Trademark Database that suggests that Nintendo is looking to bring its Digicam print channel to Europe and potentially elsewhere as the photo print service channel.
[SPEAKER_06]: And basically what the Digicam print channel is in Japan is it's a service offered through Fujifilm.
[SPEAKER_06]: That of course allows you to print photos that you save to an SD card and you can upload them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Off Your Photo Channel
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I think it's kind of useless, but, you know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: New service is, you know, new.
[SPEAKER_10]: That it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is that something, you know, you're a Nintendo fangirl, Rice Princess.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is this something you'd want to use?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, no?
[SPEAKER_10]: I have a printer at home.
[SPEAKER_10]: But if I didn't, I might consider it.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some other things coming to the future in Nintendo's world is the Wii Fit Body Check channel.
[SPEAKER_10]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: The Wii Fit Body Check Channel It's going to be something that's launching on the Wii in April I guess what this game does, it uses your BMI data That's your body mass index that you get from Wii Fit And you get the step data from personal trainers walking pedometer This is in Japan, by the way, because I don't think we have that game here yet And you get some personalized guidance from health experts Walk more, fatty!
[SPEAKER_05]: Stay healthy!
[SPEAKER_10]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_06]: I think Active Health might be the DS game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Instead of Personal Trainer Walking, it's Active Health or some sort of... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I could see it tying in with Wii Fit and stuff and maybe them doing an update to Wii Fit.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, incorporate data from that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: What extra kind of tips are you going to get from these health professionals who don't even see you?
[SPEAKER_05]: These games do nothing about your diet, do they?
[SPEAKER_05]: If you really want to lose weight, it has to be an eating and exercise thing, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Everything I've ever heard said that.
[SPEAKER_10]: You just have to eat less calories.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's where personal trainer cooking comes into play.
[SPEAKER_06]: Personal trainer cooking, mama?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, personal trainer cooking.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then they'll give you recipe ideas and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then somehow your being fat will be attributed to your not being good at math.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's where personal training math will come into play.
[SPEAKER_10]: No!
[SPEAKER_10]: I knew that was the reason why I was fat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Acidic Vampire in chat says, So, Nintendo is releasing this, but not Mother 3.
[SPEAKER_10]: Jerks.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just kidding, I live in Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, is Mother 3 going to get you in shape?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_06]: Think of the greater good.
[SPEAKER_05]: Think of the children.
[SPEAKER_05]: Would soccer moms be interested in Mother 3?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_10]: Probably not.
[SPEAKER_05]: But a personalized health coach?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what every soccer mom prays for before they go to bed.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, there's some pretty cool news.
[SPEAKER_06]: This week they announced that there's going to be a sequel to Boom Blox coming out, Boom Blox Bash Party.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to have some additional levels and some other fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: But what's also kind of neat is they announced... That sounds really close to Boom Blox Bachelor Party.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: and there will not be any additional security measures as far as friends codes go but then again this is an EA game so you know maybe they're going to have that stupid way to sign up for like EA servers or something like that but still that's not friends codes and
[SPEAKER_05]: It's interesting it's taken this long for somebody to finally defy the friend code system.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think a lot of us thought it was impossible that if you wanted to do the online Nintendo thing, you had to do friend codes.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think what makes this story notable is not necessarily who or what game is doing it, but the whole fact that it can be done.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, and the other thing that's interesting, you might remember that there was that rumor before that there was going to be a major game that would not use friend codes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_10]: Boom Blox is a major game?
[SPEAKER_06]: It actually is.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is a pretty major game.
[SPEAKER_06]: It sold really well, the first one, and it's been a pretty fun puzzle game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm telling you, though, the puzzle games need some tits in them.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like Gal's Panic.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know I've gotten into this on the show before.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, Gal's Panic I fully approve of.
[SPEAKER_06]: Me too.
[SPEAKER_06]: But not all puzzle games need tits in it.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you will remember, Bubble Bath Babes, not a good puzzle game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Nobody bought it.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it was a start.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, Rome wasn't built in a day.
[SPEAKER_05]: They tried, and I don't know why that was never further explored, but why did Miss Nude World have to stop at 96?
[SPEAKER_10]: I know.
[SPEAKER_10]: And remember in Leisure Suit Larry they came out with one a couple years back?
[SPEAKER_10]: I thought that did pretty well, didn't it?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: How did Leisure Suit Larry do?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know, but I thought that was like a cult franchise or something.
[SPEAKER_10]: Really?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's on hold right now because Sierra, which is part of Vivendi Universal, well, Vivendi Universal got bought up by Activision, and all their properties are kind of being sold off and redirected.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's still in the works.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it's supposed to be... Well, right now, I think we had it dated for...
[SPEAKER_06]: April, but I don't think it's going to come out in April, but probably this year, and it's Leisure Suit Larry's box office bust.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because, see, this is the little, you know, Larry, and he has to help his uncle, Larry, who's the original Leisure Suit Larry, and...
[SPEAKER_06]: and they're in Hollywood and oh, it's funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: And there's like cartoony women with big boobs.
[SPEAKER_10]: That'll have sex with him eventually.
[SPEAKER_10]: They get drunk.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was trying to find an audio clip of that song from Miss World New 96.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know we used to have it years ago on this show.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, we've played it before.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know, it's been years.
[SPEAKER_05]: It fits the mood so well too for a puzzle game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, here's a puzzle game that's going to be coming to WiiWare.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Bubble Bobble on WiiWare.
[SPEAKER_10]: I love Bubble Bobble.
[SPEAKER_06]: The NES game pissed me off, especially when you had that special, was it level 99?
[SPEAKER_06]: They had to do something special to get to the levels beyond that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, here's the interesting thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to be 400 stages in this new WiiWare version.
[SPEAKER_05]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to have a full recreation of the original Bubble Bobble, some higher difficulty levels if you are so inclined.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's the other cool thing, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently the new WiiWare won four-player local co-op, because you might remember the original was only two, and a brand new enemy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just one, but a brand new enemy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently there's going to be download content for this game as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: 200 points a pop for the download content.
[SPEAKER_05]: No word though how much the game itself is going to cost.
[SPEAKER_05]: I imagine probably like $800.
[SPEAKER_05]: $4 million!
[SPEAKER_05]: But yeah, the download content will be 50 additional stages of high difficulty.
[SPEAKER_05]: and a unique boss character in each one.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that they should go all out with this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Release an external peripheral that you can attach to the Wii via USB and it would be a bubble blowing machine so that as you're playing the game it would blow bubbles at you.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've seen those in Home on PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have you seen those?
[SPEAKER_05]: Randomly in the mall on Home there's bubble blowing machines for no particular reason.
[SPEAKER_06]: Every time you blow a bubble in the game there should blow another bubble out
[SPEAKER_06]: at you.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, that would be kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: That would be pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: That would be very immersive if you did that.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's like a whole 4D type of gaming I don't think has been explored yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Totally.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like Bubble Bobble featuring real bubbles.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's like Smell-O-Vision, but better.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'd say.
[SPEAKER_05]: You need to patent that idea, Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: Quick.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think that I'm really going to get my feelings hurt if someone actually releases a bubble blowing machine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course then, the bubble blowing machine, it breaks after 30 bubbles.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the downside to it.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's very limited.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, Nintendo revealed their launch schedule for the second quarter.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have to read this comment.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know I've been reading this guy a lot tonight, but the stuff he's been saying is funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: Acidic Vampire says, Bubbles are fabulous.
[SPEAKER_05]: Makes me feel like Amy Adams in Enchanted.
[SPEAKER_05]: or Glenda the Good Witch.
[SPEAKER_05]: Never mind.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I get it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, read the damn next story.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well anyways, not really, I mean, I guess the second quarter, but everything that they've announced so far for 2009, not a big surprise.
[SPEAKER_06]: Japan, they've got some pretty cool stuff coming out.
[SPEAKER_06]: They have a sequel to...
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, what they call over there Famicom Wars, which is Advance Wars over here.
[SPEAKER_06]: DS2 is coming out sometime in 2009.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's going to be a Tomodachi Collection.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's coming out in 2009.
[SPEAKER_06]: New Picross game is coming out in March.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mario & Luigi RPG 3, which is scheduled to come out over there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, finally an interesting sounding game.
[SPEAKER_06]: February 11th.
[SPEAKER_06]: and then on the Wii of course they've got their new play control games Mario Power Tennis coming out actually it's already come out over there that was January 15th
[SPEAKER_06]: This week, there's another code, R, which is Trace Memory, is what they called it over here on the DS, but that's on the Wii now.
[SPEAKER_06]: New Play Control, Metroid Prime, also Pikmin 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: Metroid Prime's coming out in a couple weeks there, and Pikmin 2 in March.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wii Sports Resort sometime in the spring.
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course, that's going to be over here as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sin and Punishment 2, of course, sometime this year.
[SPEAKER_06]: Endless Ocean 2, Hoshino Kirby, Lion Attack Heroes.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a weird name.
[SPEAKER_06]: Chibi-Robo, they're going to do a new play control for that in Metroid Prime 2 as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then they have some really weird names.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, Cosmic Walker, I guess that's a space version of Endless Ocean.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're kind of space walking.
[SPEAKER_06]: and then Dynamic Xan, Spurn Smashers and Punch Out.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that's interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, that's the one game that had a lot of people excited previously was Punch Out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sometime it's going to be coming out.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then, of course, in the U.S., some of the stuff's already been announced.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fire Emblem, Shadow Dragon, that's going to be coming out in a couple weeks.
[SPEAKER_06]: Pokemon Platinum in March.
[SPEAKER_06]: Personal Trainer Walking.
[SPEAKER_06]: Remember on the DS?
[SPEAKER_06]: That might go in with a whole rumor there that that's actually going to come out over here, that update.
[SPEAKER_06]: Coming out sometime in 2009.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rhythm Heaven coming out sometime in 2009.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, early April for that one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mario & Luigi RPG 3 coming out at some point.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to guess probably May for that.
[SPEAKER_05]: How long does it freaking take to localize a game?
[SPEAKER_05]: Rhythm Heaven's not coming out until April?
[SPEAKER_05]: They were teasing that one at PAX last year.
[SPEAKER_06]: April 5th, whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then the DSi sometime spring or summer of 2009.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that April rumor might actually come true.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then on the Wii, we've got Mario Power Tennis coming out in March as well as Pikmin.
[SPEAKER_06]: Those are both coming out actually I think the same day.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wii Sports Resort sometime in the first half of the year.
[SPEAKER_06]: Punch-Out also in the first half of the year.
[SPEAKER_06]: So probably Wii Sports.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to
[SPEAKER_06]: Walk With Me, Do You Know Your Walking Routine?
[SPEAKER_06]: Which comes with two activity meters.
[SPEAKER_05]: At least it wasn't Twin Peaks Firewalk with me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you know your firewalking routine?
[SPEAKER_06]: They're getting Mario & Luigi RPG as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: Pokemon Platinum sometime in the first half of the year.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who killed Laura Palmer?
[SPEAKER_05]: You better moonwalk to find out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Kirby Superstar Ultra is also coming out over there.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then DSi Hardware sometime spring or summer.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then of course they're getting almost the same stuff as far as the...
[SPEAKER_06]: Play Control Games, Pikmin coming out February.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's surprising that they get Pikmin way before us.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mario Power Tennis is coming out in March.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fire, walk with me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Stop it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Punch Out the First Half of the Year, New Play Control Pikmin Sorry, I just don't give a shit about Nintendo right about now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wii Sports Resort is coming out in 2009, right in the first half, and Sin and Punishment 2, another code R, so they're getting another code, and Endless Ocean 2 also coming out over here.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm guessing anything that will probably have some more stuff that's unannounced.
[SPEAKER_06]: Obviously they haven't announced what they're going to be talking about yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: E3 and just a thought, probably not going to be interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, I guess there's a couple Unless they announce Excite Truck 2 in which case I will give them I will apologize for everything I've said but unless there's an Excite Truck 2 that's really the only stipulation Excite Truck 2 or they can get the hell out
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: Nintendo DS!
[SPEAKER_05]: and defacing property at Nintendo World in New York City.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's how they decided to get back at Nintendo for not sending Bob a development kit is that he got some of his friends together who, for some strange reason, look like a bunch of foreign tourists that were probably recruited.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you see the picture of Bob?
[SPEAKER_06]: When they showed him?
[SPEAKER_05]: In the very beginning.
[SPEAKER_06]: In the beginning of the video.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I saw him.
[SPEAKER_05]: Isn't he look like a tool?
[SPEAKER_05]: He just, he does just kind of, he does, yeah, he just, he looks like an asshole.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, honestly.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, um, you just, yeah, you see these girls are going into the Nintendo World store and everybody's filming things going on here.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know why they didn't call security.
[SPEAKER_05]: But they tape posters to the side of the store that say Bob's Game.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they end up, I don't know, handing out flyers to all these people, just interrupting this
[SPEAKER_05]: Being generally rude.
[SPEAKER_06]: They slip in business cards into a bunch of the different games.
[SPEAKER_06]: They put mock boxes up onto the shelves.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they just basically generally harass people.
[SPEAKER_05]: And just act like assholes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really.
[SPEAKER_05]: If Jamie was here, she'd be having a field day right now, honestly.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't even imagine.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let me add that, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: For one, Bob's Game, great that you made a game all by yourself.
[SPEAKER_06]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: Lots of people have done that, and they have taken their game online, whatever, and we don't really hear too much about it, but the fact is, just because you made a game by yourself does not mean it needs to be played.
[SPEAKER_05]: Look at that, he just dumped a bunch of business cards on the floor.
[SPEAKER_05]: What an ass.
[SPEAKER_06]: I gotta know what the chatroom thinks about this.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then let me say the other thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: His game does not look good, and trust me, he doesn't seem that creative.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bob's game?
[SPEAKER_06]: Really?
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that what you're gonna call it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Bob's game?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know there is a game actually coming out by Graffiti Entertainment.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're the ones publishing it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is a game called Black Sigil.
[SPEAKER_06]: I forget what it was originally called, but it was a homebrew DS...
[SPEAKER_06]: Game Boy Advance
[SPEAKER_06]: I think, you know, his game could probably get published by the same company if he really tried, but he's an asshole.
[SPEAKER_06]: And honestly, you know, at first I felt bad for him because he couldn't get development kit.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't give a shit now.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think he's an asshole and I fucking, his game looks like shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: It looks like something made with like the old RPG maker and it really does not look good at all.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would not buy this game, especially after all this shit he's been pulling.
[SPEAKER_05]: SSJ100 Matt in our chat says fucking douchebag even if his game came to the DS I wouldn't buy it GS68 says for fuck's sake look at Pixel or Nigero or whatever they don't get paid for their shit and they don't care and says this should be an OLR stupid award of the year and Acidic Vampire says he's being a whiny little bitch
[SPEAKER_10]: He pretty much is.
[SPEAKER_10]: What is he hoping to accomplish by doing all this?
[SPEAKER_05]: For real!
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, do you think anybody at Nintendo, like executives, is actually going to hear about this?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh my!
[SPEAKER_10]: You're doing all of this stuff!
[SPEAKER_10]: We should publish, or, you know, put your game out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I know!
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like he doesn't get the cops called on him.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's probably going to release it as a ROM or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: And still no one's going to download it.
[SPEAKER_05]: He put the video on the internet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you know how stupid that is?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because now there's video out there of you essentially vandalizing the property and making the scene here at the Nintendo World Store or whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: You don't think they might come after you?
[SPEAKER_10]: I want you, Miyamoto, to come out with the Master Sword and just chop them in half.
[SPEAKER_10]: That'd be awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sorry, this guy does not need any more of our time.
[SPEAKER_06]: And to be honest, I don't give a shit if your game ever gets published.
[SPEAKER_06]: And really, release it in the homebrew community or something like that, because you know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think anyone's going to give a shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: The game doesn't look that great.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, it has all this gameplay and stuff in it, but it doesn't look that good.
[SPEAKER_06]: It really doesn't.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's no reason that this should be published.
[SPEAKER_05]: GameGuru in chat says, Bob's been blackballed from the video game industry.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think the blogs need to stop giving this guy any attention at all.
[SPEAKER_10]: We should too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Go ahead.
[SPEAKER_10]: He's a dickface and he's a crappy game developer.
[SPEAKER_10]: The end of the story.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just want to say though, I want to put a request out there to the OL Army.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you see this guy getting any more coverage on blogs out there or whatever, please...
[SPEAKER_05]: Leave a comment, email the blog, and ask them to please stop giving this guy attention.
[SPEAKER_05]: It starts here.
[SPEAKER_05]: No more.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bob Chat is banned from Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't ever want to hear about this stupid idiot again.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I hope to hell his thing gets him in trouble and whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: And if you see him on the street, you should kick him in the junk.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_05]: So the OLR banishment of Bob begins here and now with our favorite segment.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki would you like to start us off with the FUs of the week tonight?
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_06]: so what you're one person that you made a game oh my god you're the first person on earth to make a game before there's a lot of people that make games by themselves you know and they put it out on the atari and shit like that that's how the whole fucking game industry worked it's how it became um just because you're one dude that makes the game doesn't mean like the nintendo has to give you a dev kit because you think you're awesome that you did what one person you know
[SPEAKER_05]: Rice Princess, your FUs.
[SPEAKER_10]: Fuck you to Lieutenant Felix Gata I don't know who the fuck you think you are but you just pissed off a whole lot of people and I hope you fucking die and that's it I feel so sorry for that actor
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I'm sure he's a great actor.
[SPEAKER_10]: He did a lot of voice work for Ranma.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know there's people that don't know how to tell the difference though.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm not like crazy.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just don't like him as a character.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I hope he fucking gets airlocked or some shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: That must be like the first gay guy you've like really just wanted to beat up.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I do.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_10]: I would never be his hag.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'd be like, go fuck yourself out of an airlock.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: But yeah, I'm mad at him.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Does Silent Nathan have any FUs of the week, or is he sleeping?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, he's shaking his head no, a simple no.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, SSJ100Matt says, you don't see Aaron from Snake360 pulling that crap.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, there's so many great ways for folks together.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm serious, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: That guy is not the only guy that's programmed a game by himself.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hell, there's been people that have made, I think, a whole anime movie by themselves, and you don't hear them bitching and stuff, and their movie gets made and looks fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I do want to clarify for the chat room because they were asking, even though Bob is banned from OLR, you can still say Bobby Blackwolf.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can say it as part of a bigger word.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just Bob as far as Bob's game.
[SPEAKER_05]: There might be a CEO or something of some company named Bob, but that's all right.
[SPEAKER_06]: And if Bobby Blackwolf makes a game, you can call it Bobby's game.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can shorten it to Bob's game, but that doesn't really work.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh my god!
[SPEAKER_05]: LittleBigPlanet!
[SPEAKER_06]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a rope backwards!
[SPEAKER_05]: For those that don't know what the Snuggie is, we have to talk about this for a minute because this is important.
[SPEAKER_05]: The hell with video games.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want one of these for when I play video games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Buy a rope and turn it backwards!
[SPEAKER_05]: Done!
[SPEAKER_05]: The Snuggie is a blanket, but it has sleeves on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because you know how sometimes your arms are just like they're under the blanket.
[SPEAKER_10]: And you can't pull them out and do things.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, because then your arms get
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_06]: And guess what?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not a fucking Snuggie that probably costs a lot of money.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they ripped off the Snuggie off of some other guy.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Slinket.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Slinket, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, then I'll buy a Slinket.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't give a shit what the name is.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just want a blanket with sleeves.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's a brilliant idea.
[SPEAKER_10]: Did you see the What the Fuck Blanket, the parody?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, I saw that.
[SPEAKER_10]: You posted it on your live show or whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, that's like the best thing ever.
[SPEAKER_06]: And while we're at it, CashForGold.com is a complete rip-off.
[SPEAKER_06]: If anyone can't figure that out, I mean, yeah, you send us your gold first.
[SPEAKER_06]: Then we'll tell you how much it's worth.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, we'll wait for you and everything.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll give you a top...
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks!
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll give you a top dollar for it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, and by the way, if you want your gold back, it's already melted down, so too bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tired of using regular blankets like this asshole?
[SPEAKER_03]: Do they somehow destroy your heating bills?
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you struggle when trying to figure out how to put them on?
[SPEAKER_03]: Are mundane tasks like answering the phone now impossibly difficult?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, morons, now there's hope with the new What The F*** Blanket.
[SPEAKER_03]: The blanket that'll ruin your sex life.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_03]: She looks like a monk.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think I actually posted a reply on Rice Princess' live journal with a picture of one of the happy, happy cultists because it just reminded me because they talk about how it looks like a cult robe or whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Somebody actually replied, my parents bought one for everyone in the household.
[SPEAKER_05]: That shit is on the ground in the corner.
[SPEAKER_10]: Where it belongs.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like that idea.
[SPEAKER_05]: Give it to me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't let it sit in the corner.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was like, you should give it to Rob.
[SPEAKER_10]: He'd use it, I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, let's move on with more gaming news.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry for the... The only thing that I don't like about the robe, though, is it conducts a lot of static electricity.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, a lot of static electricity.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's not funny.
[SPEAKER_10]: and what about the ShamWow?
[SPEAKER_10]: That guy's annoying too.
[SPEAKER_06]: But that's an actual product that's good.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I've never used it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whatever happened to Silit Bang?
[SPEAKER_10]: Silit Bang or the Magic Bullet.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like Orange Glow or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, enough, enough.
[SPEAKER_05]: Games, video games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Games, games, games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyways, Gears of War PC.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently if you have it, it's not working right now because there was a little problem.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently there is a Verisign code that has expired.
[SPEAKER_06]: And because it expired, the game will not work past the date January 28th.
[SPEAKER_06]: So if you want to play it, you have to set your date back to before the 28th and then it will work just fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: Epic is aware of the situation and is working on a way to fix it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So soon it'll be fixed.
[SPEAKER_06]: But right now it's a minor inconvenience.
[SPEAKER_05]: Super.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a pretty fucking big inconvenience, actually.
[SPEAKER_05]: What if you just got this game in the bargain bin at a store or something?
[SPEAKER_06]: Then you would go online, read about it, and set your date back to before the 20th.
[SPEAKER_06]: What if I'm not smart enough to do that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, then, too bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: Then you go back and take it back to Walmart and go, this game no work, and then they'll give you your money back.
[SPEAKER_10]: Can you give me a Snuggie instead?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right, I'm going to go take back my copies of Gears of War PC and get a Snuggie.
[SPEAKER_05]: Gears of War Snuggie
[SPEAKER_05]: But with sleeves, Loki, you're missing the point It needs sleeves I have an idea Why don't you get pajamas?
[SPEAKER_06]: Or a jacket Or a robe Pajamas make me feel old Or like some socks What are you saying about pajamas, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: I have a pair of flannel pajamas that are fucking comfortable, okay?
[SPEAKER_10]: And they're warm And they're warm
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, look, Gears of War didn't just make the mistake of not making a Snuggie out of their collection or flubbing the PC version of the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently, also, the Gears of War 2 Gold Lancer went up on Xbox Live for everybody earlier this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: This was something you were only supposed to get if you actually got the collector's edition of Gears of War 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: And when I say Gold Lancer, I don't mean a car.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the type of gun.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the type of gun that you use in the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Boom!
[SPEAKER_05]: Although that would be pretty awesome if you suddenly could use cars to run over the monsters.
[SPEAKER_05]: And here's the other interesting thing about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: According to a representative for Xbox Live, everybody who actually got the Gold Lancer during the period that it was available, they're going to have the item removed from the game in an upcoming fix.
[SPEAKER_06]: Right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just like they said the Fable 2 exclusive code or whatever for people to have the collector's edition.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to find out who doesn't have the collector's edition.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to take it away from you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, that never happened.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently, also, the way they fixed this temporarily, they put the Gold Lancer... I mean, they weren't able to remove the Gold Lancer from Xbox Live Marketplace.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently, it was still there late last week, but it was being charged a price of 99,999 Microsoft points.
[SPEAKER_05]: They do that.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was like that before, because they actually have that available, and then there's also some map
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: You'll be able to download it onto your system or something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Something that would be exclusive.
[SPEAKER_06]: They did this originally with... There was also the Banjo-Kazooie thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Xbox Live Arcade game that was available only for a limited time.
[SPEAKER_06]: However, they caught that too and they also put it like $9.99 as the amount for it.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have to wonder if anybody spends the $150,000 or whatever it would take to get it anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, there are people that buy stupid iPhone programs that cost thousands of dollars just to have a stupid gem on there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, objects in there.
[SPEAKER_06]: They have a little slime object that's kind of angry-looking and a cross that looks angry.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a whole lot of angry stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, it's like in Super Mario Bros., how everything has a smiley face on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Everything has an angry face in this game, so that's interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some other games, of course, that are going to be coming as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Crystal Defenders, which of course was originally a mobile game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some other stuff...
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I wonder if they're still making money on that, you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_05]: Nah, I doubt it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, it's kind of free money at this point if they do have anybody playing it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I'm sure it takes like one server to run the whole thing, but, you know, they could release that as like a $10 Xbox Live arcade game.
[SPEAKER_05]: They wouldn't even have to charge a monthly fee, and they'd still make a pretty penny off it.
[SPEAKER_06]: They had a game, and I can't remember what the hell it was called.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was, and I'm not even sure if it actually came out, but it was for, I think, the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: Might have been the PlayStation 1.
[SPEAKER_06]: and it was on a demo disc that was I think it was a Playstation 1 now if I remember correctly it was on a demo disc with like I want to say maybe it would have been Final Fantasy 7 there might have been some other stuff on there as well and it was a street racing RPG but I don't remember what it was called though but I remember it had racing in it and it was from Square Enix but that would be another cool game to bring out
[SPEAKER_05]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm sure there'll be some type of Final Fantasy milking at some point, which is not necessarily a bad thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, they do have Crystal Defenders, which is a Final Fantasy game, so... Alright, I guess there is that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, if you are downloading a lot of stuff on Xbox Live Marketplace for popular role-playing games, perhaps you've checked out some of the content for Elder Scrolls Oblivion.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Bethesda actually put out a list this week of what some of the top downloaded Oblivion content is.
[SPEAKER_05]: And funny enough, the top downloaded content is Wizards Tower is the number one most downloaded content that they have.
[SPEAKER_05]: Knights of the Nine is all the way down to number seven.
[SPEAKER_05]: Shivering Isles, number eight.
[SPEAKER_05]: But what's interesting, I mean, because those are pretty expensive if I remember right.
[SPEAKER_05]: But what's interesting, remember all the shit that Bethesda used to get for the horse armor?
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember the horse armor download they put?
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently that content's all it was.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whereas all this other content I'm mentioning is new levels, new areas to explore, new quests and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Horse armor was just armor for your horse.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it was just a visual thing only.
[SPEAKER_05]: It did nothing special.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they actually charged a lot of money for this.
[SPEAKER_05]: At the time, it was an insane amount.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_05]: How much was horse armor?
[SPEAKER_05]: It was like five bucks, I think.
[SPEAKER_05]: for stupid armor for your horse.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, the thing is, that checks in at number nine.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they claim they still sell some horse armor every day.
Wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Still, even after all this time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fighter Stronghold is the dead last entry.
[SPEAKER_06]: You want to hear something off the top ten list?
[SPEAKER_06]: You can get Elder Scrolls Oblivion, the Game of the Year edition with the expansion on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: 20 bucks.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm thinking about buying it again.
[SPEAKER_06]: For PlayStation 3?
[SPEAKER_06]: Fuck that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't catch which system it was on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Game of the Year edition is on both.
[SPEAKER_06]: Both of them are $20 now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fighter Stronghold is dead last.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently, though, that could be because this thing only ranks the bot download and pay for it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Fighter Stronghold was free for a little while.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's why I have it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So probably a lot of people grabbed it when it was free and they never needed to get it again.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have an Xbox Magazine disc that actually has two of those on there that were paid download content for free.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you want them.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know if you still play Oblivion, but you know.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's just so much to do in Oblivion.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, God, even without the expansions, I felt like they can't.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, literally, you can just walk around the world and just walk into random ass dungeons and explore them.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, there was just so much in that game.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's crazy.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't wait for the next one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, Raiden Fighter Aces, I believe, came out in Japan, and it's rumored to be coming out over here as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: Raiden Fighter Aces actually is a collection of three different Raiden Fighter games.
[SPEAKER_06]: They have Raiden Fighters, Raiden Fighters 2, Operation Helldive, and Raiden Fighters Jet, all on one disc.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, the rumors are that Zoo Games is actually publishing the game in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_06]: for $29.99.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: No, these are coming out in the US.
[SPEAKER_06]: And what platform?
[SPEAKER_06]: Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_06]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: And yeah, Raiden 4 will be coming out at the end of March.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sure there will be a lot of people that are very interested in that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also some folks interested in everything Banjo-Kazooie related.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's Banjo-Tooie.
[SPEAKER_05]: Banjo-Tooie is going to be coming out on Xbox Live Arcade apparently a little later this year.
[SPEAKER_05]: Probably about 1,200 Microsoft points, although that hasn't been confirmed yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it is confirmed.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is coming out.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's slightly upped graphics and upped frame rate as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Stop and Swap is coming over.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently this is something from the Nintendo 64 days where if you got some items in Banjo-Kazooie, they will show up in Banjo-Tooie as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: So,
[SPEAKER_05]: Not too big of a surprise since I'm assuming the first one did pretty well for them and the game was already done.
[SPEAKER_05]: They just have to do some upgrades and sell it all over again for $15 and people will buy it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Where there's horse armor, there's Banjo-Tooie.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, maybe it's not that bad, but you know, there's a lot of people who love the Banjo series and I'm sure excited to play it all over again with the updated graphics and widescreen and all that stuff, so good for them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, well, if you're not waiting for Banjo-Tooie, there are some other things coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: That might be something you want to pick up.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, not a whole lot this week, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_06]: Starting things off, let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: We have, for the Wii, Rygar Battle of Argus.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, it's a port of the Playstation 2 game and then they've added like some Colosseum levels or something like that so yay, a port of something that came out like what five years ago?
[SPEAKER_06]: yeah, it was a while ago so that'll be coming out and then this week I know there's some miscellaneous DS games like some Imagine crap um
[SPEAKER_06]: Imagine crapping.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's really pathetic, the lineup this week, I swear.
[SPEAKER_05]: Could that be because we have Street Fighter 4 coming out the week after?
[SPEAKER_05]: Or is that two weeks?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's two weeks.
[SPEAKER_06]: Two weeks.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, the week after would be Fear 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, there's people definitely excited about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's for sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: Street Fighter 2 is next week in Japan.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I'll get to that in a minute.
[SPEAKER_05]: Are you done with the US dates?
[SPEAKER_06]: This list I'm looking at is not very accurate.
[SPEAKER_06]: It actually doesn't even have next week.
[SPEAKER_06]: It just skips over next week.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's how pathetic next week is.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm trying to think if there's... I think Tenchu Z... Tenchu 4 on the Wii is coming out, I believe, as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't remember if that got delayed or not.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, Capcom typically releases stuff in the first quarter.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, this year they're releasing stuff first quarter and second quarter, which is good.
[SPEAKER_06]: But they are pretty smart to do so because there's not much competition this time of year.
[SPEAKER_06]: Although this year there's pretty good stuff coming out.
[SPEAKER_06]: But yeah, not too much.
[SPEAKER_06]: This next week is really dead.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we'll wait for the week after that where we actually get into the meat of things and it'll start picking up from there all the way through March.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, let's talk about Japanese release dates.
[SPEAKER_05]: Luckily it looks a little better over there for the Japanese release dates.
[SPEAKER_05]: On the Xbox 360, Burnout Paradise, the ultimate box set, makes its way.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm assuming that's just all the special download stuff we got here.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's the Burnout plus the ultimate party thing that they've got that's going to be a download next week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Basically all the extra crap.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can get that in Japan this week on February the 5th for the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, Midnight Club Los Angeles comes out on the 5th.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you head over to the PlayStation, it's racing fun on the Xbox 360 this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: By the way, Street Fighter 4 is next week, but I'll remind you about that next week.
[SPEAKER_05]: On the PlayStation 3, Burnout Paradise, The Ultimate Box, also there, as well as Midnight Club Los Angeles.
[SPEAKER_05]: You also get Shaun White Snowboarding, and Demon's Souls is a game that's coming out from Sony on the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: What are you laughing at over there?
[SPEAKER_10]: and Demon's Souls.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's apparently a pretty big release.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's an RPG coming out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Demon's Souls!
[SPEAKER_05]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_05]: For that, I'm not going to tell you anything more about Demon's Souls.
[SPEAKER_08]: It will forever be a mystery.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's an RPG made by Sony.
[SPEAKER_05]: On the Nintendo Wii, another code are Kyoku no Tobira is coming out from Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_05]: D-Terminal and AV Cable.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you need a new AV Cable, you can get that this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: D-Terminal is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, the D-terminal is cool because, I mean, you know, if you want to hook it up to a PC monitor, that's the only way you can do it, really.
[SPEAKER_05]: I got to say, though, this Another Code R game actually sounds kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is this just Lost in Blue?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, this is Trace Memory.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, it's Trace Memory.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, okay, because I got confused when I looked at the thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: This game actually sounds kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what's weird is I thought that game has been out for a while.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it's just coming out again.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I've seen it floating around for a while, but, you know, I could be wrong.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm even thinking of the DS version.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think you are.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think you are.
[SPEAKER_05]: Coming out on the PlayStation 2, nothing.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's one game getting a price reduction, Momotaro Densetsu 16.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's it, and nothing else is new.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nintendo DS is a little different.
[SPEAKER_05]: There is some new stuff coming out, but it's mostly like covers and pouches and things like that, but there is a game called Destiny Links coming out from Bandai Namco, and it's an RPG, of course, and...
[SPEAKER_05]: You get your character and you sail forth to Amazia, the island of happiness.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, that sounds like a destiny I want.
[SPEAKER_05]: DJ Max Fever DJ Max Fever
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, let's go to Europe real quick.
[SPEAKER_05]: Since Jamie's not here tonight, I'll go ahead and read the Europe dates for you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, Japan and the U.S.
[SPEAKER_05]: were kind of slow, but Europe has a big week ahead.
[SPEAKER_05]: For February 6th, they're getting Burnout Paradise on the PC, Castlevania Order of Ecclesia on the DS,
[SPEAKER_05]: Chrono Trigger finally hits on the DS for those folks in Europe.
[SPEAKER_05]: Gauntlet on the DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: Lost in Blue 3 on the DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: New Play Control Pikmin comes out on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_05]: Raven Squad hits the Xbox 360 and PC.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rise of the Argonauts hits PS3, Xbox 360, and PC.
[SPEAKER_05]: Shellshock 2...
[SPEAKER_05]: Fucking tongue twister.
[SPEAKER_05]: Shellshock 2 Blood Trails comes out on 360, PS3, and PC.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Walk With Me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you know your walking routine on the DS?
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you know that you're walking right now?
[SPEAKER_05]: Isn't it funny that even when we get the crap games, so do Europe.
[SPEAKER_05]: But when we get a great game like Chrono Trigger, they have to wait like three months for it.
[SPEAKER_05]: You poor guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: We got Pikmin.
[SPEAKER_06]: See, they're going to get the port of Pikmin now, and we're going to get the new Zelda months before they will.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's fair.
[SPEAKER_06]: Go Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_06]: Boy oh boy.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what else is equally awesome as delays and stuff like that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Rock Band receiving some brand new tracks from Nickelodeon's
[SPEAKER_06]: HighSchoolMusical-esque movie Spectacular.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, there's two songs from the film, Break My Heart and Don't Tell Me.
[SPEAKER_06]: They'll be both available for the equivalent of $1 on your Xbox Live Marketplace or PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_06]: And of course, if you happen to wait until March 31st for the DVD release of Spectacular, there will also be a redemption code for a free download of the two songs via the Rock Band Music Store.
[SPEAKER_06]: And if you're curious what this sounds like...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: Dark Tetsuya pours bleach on his speakers.
[SPEAKER_05]: Leo Shen, my ears are bleeding now, damn it.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess there's not a lot of people that are going to be downloading the spectacular songs.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it's spectacular.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's spectacular.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also spectacular is a segment we like to do here every week on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: We like to pay a little respect to the classic games.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's a little segment we do here on the show called the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: I decided to pick one for us, but you know, I kind of picked one collectively for all of us to kind of match, you know, there is a certain something going on right now in the world, you know, there's that big game, I guess they throw a ball around and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, no, of course, we are taping the same day as the Super Bowl, and when you talk football and you talk video games, there really is one classic video game you have to recognize, and that is this week's classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Blades of Steel.
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tecmo Bowl is this week's classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right, the wonderful 8-bit sounds of Tecmo Bowl on the NES.
[SPEAKER_05]: I chose purposefully not to do Tecmo Super Bowl tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: I did Tecmo Bowl, the old school one, because this is a little more of a classic.
[SPEAKER_05]: I played this game a hell of a lot growing up.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know...
[SPEAKER_05]: We like to think that Rob plays like no sports games and hates them all, but there are a few.
[SPEAKER_05]: Few and far between that will come along once in a while to get my attention, and Tecmo Bowl was one of them.
[SPEAKER_05]: So let's learn a little bit about Tecmo Bowl.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tecmo Bowl was actually based off an arcade game, an arcade version of Tecmo Bowl.
[SPEAKER_05]: I should be noted, that's not what we're citing as the classic game of the week, because I've played the arcade version in a compilation that was on the Xbox, Tecmo Classic Arcade, and it stinks compared to the one on the NES.
[SPEAKER_05]: It doesn't seem to move as quickly, I just don't care for it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, um...
[SPEAKER_05]: Tecmo Ball on the NES is our classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_05]: You've probably seen this before.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was released on the Wii Virtual Console on March 12, 2007.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the original came out in 1989 after the original arcade version was released in 1987.
[SPEAKER_05]: The arcade version had this big two-monitor setup so that four people could play.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the NES version was way scaled down because it was only two players.
[SPEAKER_05]: You could do three modes, one player, two player, or just a coach mode where you would pick all the plays.
[SPEAKER_05]: The playbook only has four offensive plays, or if you're on defense, you kind of try to pick the play that you think the offense is going to pick.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you did it with this combination of the controller and the buttons.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tecmo Bowl isn't a perfect game, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was a little better than 10-yard fight, which was one of the only other football games that was out at the time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently, almost any pass that you throw to a covered receiver is going to end up in interception.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you use the New York Giants and you use Lawrence Taylor, apparently you can pretty much block almost all kicks.
[SPEAKER_05]: and apparently San Francisco has a play that is usually unstoppable against almost any defense and I used to win every time with San Francisco and I think that's probably why by the way you wouldn't actually be playing as the New York Giants though in the game because they didn't have the licensing from the NFL to actually use the names of the teams so when you selected teams you were just Indianapolis or San Francisco or New York
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know enough about football to understand the whole thing behind that, but you do get the players, and they are all in the game, and, you know, it was the old 8-bit NES days.
[SPEAKER_05]: They didn't really look any different.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just that you had the different names.
[SPEAKER_05]: However, if you downloaded this on the Virtual Console version, you didn't get the names because the licensing had expired, so they actually removed all the names from the version that came out for Virtual Console, which kind of stinks.
[SPEAKER_05]: by the way, there was also a version on mobile phones that was released in 2004 and apparently they are bringing this series back Tecmo Bowl Kickoff I don't know if this came out yet, but that was supposed to be coming out on the DS I don't know if that ever did actually come out or is still on its way out I can't remember if it came out in November or not it was originally going to come out in November
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: It just isn't the old school 8-bit version.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I know there's a lot of people very partial to Tecmo Super Bowl, but I have to take a minute to just recognize the greatness of the classic NES version.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're actually nodding your head, Rice Princess.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, it did come out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, it did come out?
[SPEAKER_06]: When did it come out?
[SPEAKER_06]: Not too long ago, but it's available for $20.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently it just price dropped.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rice Princess, were you a fan of Tecmo Bowl?
[SPEAKER_10]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: No?
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Were there any sports games that you played?
[SPEAKER_10]: Um...
[SPEAKER_05]: I like this about Tecmo Bo2 is that it had like little cinematics when you got a touchdown it was like high five in super slow motion because we don't really have movies and this halftime show
[SPEAKER_08]: Whoa, a halftime show.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know, a cinematic halftime show.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was like Ninja Gaiden, but with football.
[SPEAKER_10]: I love Ninja Gaiden.
[SPEAKER_10]: See, I was nodding my head because I'm concurring with your point about paying homage to the older, original versions and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Personally, if I were to pick an NFL game that was going to be my pick for something like this today, NFL Blitz.
[SPEAKER_10]: I knew it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nobody likes that game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe next year.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe during next Super Bowl.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: But that's it for now.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's your classic game of the week, Tecmo Bowl, here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: And with that, it's going to bring Part A of our show to a close tonight, but don't go anywhere, because we're going to be just right back in a few seconds with Part B. If you're listening on the podcast, it only takes a few seconds.
[SPEAKER_05]: You hear that little do-do-do-do, and then it's right back into Part B. But if you're listening live, this is the point where we take a little bit longer of a break to, you know, get a drink of water, use the restroom.
[SPEAKER_10]: Toilet bowl.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or...
[SPEAKER_05]: Not the Toilet Super Bowl.
[SPEAKER_05]: And this will actually be, it's very special this week, our break, because this will be try to restrain Rice Princess from my Xbox 360 for 10 minutes during the break.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we'll see how that works.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll be right back in just a little bit with more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio on this lovely Sunday evening, February the 1st of 2009.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, there's a big football game going on today, but we're here doing a show anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's over, actually.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Steelers won.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently, it was really exciting.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess there was like a big run to a touchdown or things like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can totally tell I don't know dick about football.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know that thing that happens when you play football?
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura is not here tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: or at least attempts to do.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Silent Nathan is also here, but he wouldn't know because he doesn't say much.
[SPEAKER_05]: But he is here wearing his Horde hat, showing his pride for the Horde.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I'm wearing my Alliance sweater.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, do you two like fight for real?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I punch him in the face all the time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, too bad we don't have a webcam, but we will have it next week because there's a cord coming from New Jersey, I found out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_10]: Woohoo.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, let's get back into some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki's here to deliver the news as always.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's up, Loki?
[SPEAKER_06]: Not much.
[SPEAKER_06]: There will be some new download content coming out for the new Prince of Persia game.
[SPEAKER_06]: This takes place after the end of the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to be the epilogue download content.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it will kind of further develop the relationship between the two main characters and also have them going after a new enemy, the Shapeshifter.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are they going to do it yet?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently the Shapeshifter is an enemy that takes the form of the two of Ahriman's most fearsome lieutenants, the Warrior and the Hunter.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's as though their physical form is familiar to our heroes, and the player will require particular strategies to defeat the Shapeshifter, rewarding the player that takes advantage of the new sprint feature exclusive to the epilogue.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I get to have more conversations with the chick that always saves me from falling to my death?
[SPEAKER_06]: Possibly.
[SPEAKER_06]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, of course, you know, they're going to have the sprinting offensive and Elika is going to get the new energized power which will allow her to temporarily restore a piece of destroyed environment.
[SPEAKER_05]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_05]: That'd be interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Will the game still help me every step of the way by telling me what buttons to push?
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_05]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: The download content will be available though on February 26th.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, check that out.
[SPEAKER_05]: How much do they have priced for that?
[SPEAKER_06]: No price yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Somewhere between $5 and $10, I'm guessing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, something that does have a price, a pretty high price, 8,190 yen they are going to charge for this.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's $90 American dollars they are charging for The Last Remnant on PC.
[SPEAKER_05]: And this is according to Famitsu Magazine.
[SPEAKER_05]: There is a PC port of The Last Remnant.
[SPEAKER_05]: This was a
[SPEAKER_05]: A roleplaying game that was put out on the Xbox 360 They hit kind of mixed reviews Some of our listeners have been saying pretty favorable things about this I haven't checked this game out myself yet But if you don't own an Xbox 360 and you want to check this out on PC You might be in luck because it is coming in Japan on April 9th But it is going to have that pretty high price tag And then when you count importing fees on top of that or what have you Although of course I'm sure if you wanted to go to darker places on the internet You could probably get it for free But I don't know, it's going to be all in Japanese, so who knows Anyway
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently, though, it's going to actually give you some extra stuff in the PC version.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can speed up battle animations now.
[SPEAKER_05]: It will have more leader class characters.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can preview equipment in the menu, and you can actually switch between Japanese and English.
[SPEAKER_05]: So maybe you won't need to patch much more than the menus to get this.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Ranma is in chat and says it's a great game.
[SPEAKER_05]: He says, Last Remnant, great game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Comment coming from our chat room, chat.orangemonstrady.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you're just joining us post-Super Bowl, you should come join us.
[SPEAKER_05]: As long as it's easier to install and have run than Grand Theft Auto 4.
[SPEAKER_05]: By the way, one other quick thing I want to say about this game.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is the game that Square Enix took the Unreal Engine for.
[SPEAKER_05]: You might remember a few years back, there was a big news story that Square Enix had purchased the Unreal Engine for something.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is that game.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you can see it in motion on the PC.
[SPEAKER_05]: In The Last Remnant.
[SPEAKER_06]: And apparently it was un-really disappointing.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a mixed bag of opinions.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, something that might be a little bit better, hopefully, are some sequels to some well-known Capcom franchises.
[SPEAKER_06]: There was some talk about a brand new Dead Rising game and a Lost Planet game, and that they may possibly be...
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: Not a big surprise since Capcom, Dead Rising did very well for them and they're making a Lost Planet movie for God's sake.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not a big surprise that we'll see some new games and the fact that they'll be multi-platform is not a shock either.
[SPEAKER_06]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hopefully those are soon.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hopefully we'll see those at E3.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's interesting to think about what kinds of stuff we're really going to see come out of E3 this year because it's been fairly quiet, all things considered.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm thinking this year's E3 is going to be pretty big, especially the whole return to E3's roots, even though they say not really, but that whole thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, but Capcom's all about the multi-porting too, so I'm sure if these things are coming out, they're going to be everywhere on every platform, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bioshock 2 Sea of Dreams is going to finally add something that was missing from the first Bioshock.
[SPEAKER_05]: What was missing from the first Bioshock for being a first-person shooter?
[SPEAKER_05]: Multiplayer!
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently this is all according to some recent job listings that were discovered.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Bioshock team is looking for some multiplayer gameplay experts.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're looking for some people who know how to extend and enhance the Unreal Engine 3 with proprietary networking technology to address gameplay performance and so on.
[SPEAKER_05]: as somebody who can deliver a robust, scalable, and responsive multiplayer gameplay code and backend services for the PC, PS3, and Xbox 360 platforms.
[SPEAKER_05]: So unless there's some top secret unannounced project going on here, you can almost count on the fact that Bioshock 2 is going to have
[SPEAKER_05]: multiplayer in it which is something the first one was pretty lacking although honestly I mean it didn't need it Bioshock was a hell of a first-person shooter game um you know that even people that don't play a lot of first-person shooters like me can get into because it was almost like Silent Hill-ish in how scary it was at least for me kind of the psychological element of the game so it's gonna be interesting to see what a multiplayer does to all that
[SPEAKER_05]: Then that gets me thinking, since I invoked Silent Hill in that last story, why did we never get a multiplayer Silent Hill?
[SPEAKER_10]: Wouldn't that be kind of interesting?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, because they tried.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't think it would work out.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess it wouldn't, because Silent Hill, a lot of times, is somebody's personal interpretation.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's usually a very personalized story, so I don't think anything like that would really work.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's fun to think about.
[SPEAKER_10]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_05]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Guitar Hero World Tour is going to be getting some brand new download packs in February.
[SPEAKER_06]: The first pack is going to be the Acoustic Track Pack, which is available for 440 Microsoft Points.
[SPEAKER_06]: Included with that will be the Songholic.
[SPEAKER_06]: That makes me angry.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the Acoustic Track Pack, which will be available for 440 Microsoft Points or $5.49, will include three different songs, including Drive by Incubus, New Slang by The Shins, and Wonderwall, the Oasis cover by Ryan Adams.
[SPEAKER_06]: Those are each also available for 160 Microsoft Points or $2 each.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ryan Adams covered Wonderwall like wow that's gonna be bad I'm sorry I saw Ryan Adams once in concert and he was kind of a douche so I mean he's a douchey guy covering a douchey song from a douchey band I mean this is just like oh it's gonna be terrible
[SPEAKER_06]: Wings Track Pack Wings Track Pack Wings Track Pack Wings Track Pack
[SPEAKER_06]: Bob Seger Track Pack, Her Strut, and Get Out of Denver
[SPEAKER_05]: Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_10]: PC Game Purchases are in fact digital.
[SPEAKER_05]: GameStop for PC Games
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently, according to the survey, 93% of PC gamers bought at least one game digitally in the past 12 months.
[SPEAKER_05]: 71% bought four games digitally.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: But then I think about some of those games like PopCap and those types of games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I bring this up because obviously they're huge, casual PC games.
[SPEAKER_05]: And a lot of people go to the site, download the trial game, and then you can put your credit card number in online and get the full version.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a digital distribution right there.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think that necessarily means half of all games are bought off Steam.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think that's necessarily what it means.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it goes a little deeper than that, especially when you filter in these classic games from a site like Yahoo Games or whatever, where you can click now and put in your credit card number to get the full version of Diner Dash 5.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's kind of not surprising in a way, but interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, very interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Know what else is interesting?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sure that means the shelf space is going to continue to shrink.
[SPEAKER_05]: What else is interesting, Loki?
[SPEAKER_06]: People finding different things about LittleBigPlanet, including some upcoming patch details.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently this was leaked out from a photo that was on...
[SPEAKER_06]: Media Monocles Flickr page.
[SPEAKER_06]: And if you look very closely, you'll notice that there's a whiteboard with a bunch of different information about download content and updates.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the next one that's on the list there, which I can't quite see the code name for, but it will include new tutorials and online creation mode, where you'll be able to work with other players and create your own levels online.
[SPEAKER_06]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: apparently there's also going to be a new arcade pack at some point I don't know what exactly that is arcade pack?
[SPEAKER_05]: that could be all kinds of cool but something else I'm trying to see code name what are your thoughts on LittleBigPlanet, RicePrincess you haven't talked a lot about it on the show but I know you love Wii, you hate 360 so PS3's got to be a nice neutral ground what do you think about LittleBigPlanet?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know, I've never played it
[SPEAKER_05]: Really?
[SPEAKER_10]: Really.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's actually a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was my favorite game that came out last year.
[SPEAKER_10]: Really?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I love it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't have a PS3.
[SPEAKER_05]: You gotta see how cheesy some of the user levels are.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that's how you will like it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Go on there and play the Warcraft-inspired Onyxia's Lair level.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: No word to the time frame?
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, no.
[SPEAKER_06]: But then again, this is, you know, based off information that's coming off of a picture of a whiteboard.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean... Well, still, you know, if the studio themselves put up the picture, I would actually say that is a pretty respectable source.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I don't think they're going to think to quick erase the whiteboard, we're spilling all our secrets.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_06]: You're spilling your secrets onto the whiteboard.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ha ha!
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, I'm laughing at chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: AcidicVampire in chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're getting read a lot tonight, buddy.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's saying a lot of funny things.
[SPEAKER_05]: It says, Sky, play the Parker Posey level.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not popular, but it's great.
[SPEAKER_10]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a Parker Posey level?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh my god, I want to play it so bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think I'm going to do that right after the show.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, because I'm going to play Resident Evil 5.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to push you if you don't let me.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have to...
[SPEAKER_05]: Do I get to unlock stickers of Parker Posey?
[SPEAKER_05]: If so, I'm so sold.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like Party Girl and everything?
[SPEAKER_05]: Amazing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Silent Nathan is now suddenly interested in LittleBigPlanet?
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe I'll go play it right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, speaking of games that I want to play right now, I can't play this right now, but apparently it's going to be in development.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tron, a new game, a new Tron game.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, they showed that trailer for Tron 2 or TR2N.
[SPEAKER_05]: What they showed at Comic-Con.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently there is a game coming out for this whole thing as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is according to Variety.
[SPEAKER_05]: Even though there were some issues with the Disney video game company, Variety Magazine is reporting that apparently Disney is shipping to game developers a concept for TR2N or Tron 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course, no idea what it's going to be like or anything.
[SPEAKER_05]: But of course this makes me think, okay...
[SPEAKER_05]: There was a Tron 2.0, and it wasn't very well received.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the original Tron game was awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: Never played it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: They have it on Xbox Live, and it was one of those games that was better in the 80s.
[SPEAKER_05]: And when you play it now, you're kind of like, oh, this game is better left in my imagination.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it still was pretty cool, especially for an 80s game.
[SPEAKER_10]: What do you think about reinventing franchises?
[SPEAKER_05]: Such as Tron?
[SPEAKER_10]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm okay with it, I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think especially a series like Tron needed a sequel a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: It seems a little late.
[SPEAKER_05]: But then when you look at a series like The Goonies, or there is no series there, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: They don't need to make a Goonies 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, if they made a Goonies 2, you know it's going to be stupid.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it was Goonies.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or The Karate Kid?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, just no.
[SPEAKER_10]: Are you talking about the movie or the game?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, the movie.
[SPEAKER_05]: The game was amazing.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's another classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love that game so much.
[SPEAKER_05]: That game was amazing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Heck yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought you did that as a classic game already.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if DarkSakura has ever done it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'd have to check the wiki, but I don't think it's ever been a classic game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'd have to check the wiki on our own show.
[SPEAKER_05]: Look, we've done the Classic Game of the Week for at least a year now, so I don't know every single game we've highlighted.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a lot.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thankfully, we have a wiki and the fans update the wiki because they're awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did Silent Nathan run in the house really to go play PlayStation 3?
[SPEAKER_10]: Probably that jerkwad.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, Nathan, you're cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: And not a jerkwad at all.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, so yeah, Neutron game in development.
[SPEAKER_05]: Probably to come out with a movie.
[SPEAKER_05]: If they can find somebody to take the financial hit for all the development, I guess, in this economy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Disney does have their own studio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, but it's been hurting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, because they put out Turok.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_06]: I could have told you that Turok's going to suck before they even put Turok out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Seriously, really?
[SPEAKER_06]: You're going to put Turok out?
[SPEAKER_06]: Really?
[SPEAKER_06]: This is something you think is a great idea?
[SPEAKER_10]: The economy is going downhill.
[SPEAKER_10]: What game should we make?
[SPEAKER_10]: Turok!
[SPEAKER_10]: That's a great idea!
[SPEAKER_05]: Amaze Satsuma in chat wonders if Sky wants a Showgirls 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know there was supposed to be a Showgirls 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because at the end of Showgirls 1 it alludes to the fact that Nomi Malone is going to Hollywood.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Showgirls 2 was supposed to be a parody on Hollywood.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like the first one was a parody on Vegas.
[SPEAKER_05]: But then the movie came out.
[SPEAKER_05]: and they decided to can a sequel.
[SPEAKER_05]: Never mind.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would be in full support of a Showgirls 2, but not now.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, Elizabeth Berkley's not going to do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's the point?
[SPEAKER_06]: The point is that we have all these wonderful porn studios that can develop a movie now.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, they're doing more theatrical movies and hell, they have all the knockoffs, like all the TV show ones, like Not the Bradys, Not the Monsters, Not Bewitched.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know what the other ones are, but
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean... Not My Three Sons?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not sure about that one.
[SPEAKER_05]: How come porn studios don't get into gaming?
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, you see all these legitimate movie studios getting into games.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's porn actresses that are in the gaming, but, you know, not... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a lot of people that love World of Warcraft...
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know why, but there are.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Plus, think about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you're a stripper, you're working nights, you're probably home during the day with a kid.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm kind of reminded, I don't know if you've ever seen The Guild, but I'm kind of reminded of Carla from The Guild.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, she's a nerd.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who, by the way, is by far my favorite character on that program.
[SPEAKER_10]: But the stripper that's local that plays WoW, she's a nerd.
[SPEAKER_10]: She's an Asian girl, and her stage name's Katana.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, that's the one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, that's totally the one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Freaking dork.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do we just have a six degrees of stripper here in the studio?
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: Like we just found out that Loki and Rice Princess know the same stripper?
[SPEAKER_10]: Do you know that stripper?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know her, but I've seen her boobies.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I know her that well, but... I know her in the biblical sense.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, you know...
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: about games and shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, you mentioned that you do a game podcast.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's like, oh my god, I play games too!
[SPEAKER_10]: That's so funny.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, how does that even come up in conversation?
[SPEAKER_10]: So what do you do?
[SPEAKER_10]: And you're like, well, actually, I have a game podcast.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's because, you know, to get into how strip clubs operate, they have to wait until the new song begins.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because when you're paying for a lap dance, it's for X number of songs.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they're not just going to start...
[SPEAKER_06]: If it's in the middle of a song, you have to sit there and wait for the new song.
[SPEAKER_06]: During that time, it's you, so what do you do?
[SPEAKER_06]: How's it going?
[SPEAKER_06]: That kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's where the games come up.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's all I do is games.
[SPEAKER_05]: The time I got a lap dance, because I went to the strip club once, and my friends, you were there, Irene, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: My friends made me say which stripper I thought was the hottest.
[SPEAKER_05]: Naturally, I said the one that looks like Buffy the Vampire Slayer, because there was a stripper there that looked just like Buffy the Vampire Slayer.
[SPEAKER_05]: And she...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Honey, it's nothing against you.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just gay.
[SPEAKER_05]: And she says, oh, I can kind of tell.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then she's just sitting there and she's talking to me.
[SPEAKER_05]: And she's like, oh, my roommate's gay and I love him.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's the best.
[SPEAKER_05]: And so she's talking to me for like a whole nother song.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it was really awkward because she had no clothes on except a thong.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it was kind of strange.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was just kind of like, just put a T-shirt on or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: And acidic vampire says, Rob loves the boobies.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, especially when he's drunk.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Rob might be gay, but he loves titties.
[SPEAKER_05]: All gay guys like boobies.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know what it is.
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess everybody really likes boobies.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who doesn't like boobies?
[SPEAKER_05]: Women like boobies.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, women do.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like me.
[SPEAKER_10]: But, yeah, you were going to say something, Nathan?
[SPEAKER_05]: I just want to point out, though, some props in chat for the strip club with the wife.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because some folks in chat are like, Game Guru says, wait, wait, wait, you go to the strip club with your wife?
[SPEAKER_10]: She loves going.
[SPEAKER_06]: And GameGuru says, your wife is the coolest.
[SPEAKER_06]: We seriously thought we were going to do this, but we were so fucking tired from the wedding day.
[SPEAKER_06]: We were seriously going to go in our wedding garb.
[SPEAKER_06]: to the strip club we were almost going to do it but we were so exhausted like during the wedding we were like dude yeah we should totally go afterwards just dressed up in the tux and everything because that would be hilarious but we were just like so beat at the end of the day it's like fuck that we're not going anywhere nice go sleep yeah boobs are awesome
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ranma says, Sky, you're a hypocrite.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have a problem with a woman in a bra and panties at a strip bar.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hold up.
[SPEAKER_05]: She had no bra on, okay?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just panties.
[SPEAKER_05]: Full titties.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wouldn't even call it like panties.
[SPEAKER_05]: When you say panties, I think of like granny panties, you know?
[SPEAKER_10]: Or like regular panties, not a thong.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, she had like a thong on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not a G-string.
[SPEAKER_05]: But she'll happy go to a Rocky Horror Picture Show convention full of women in bra and panties.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, that's different.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, that's not why you're going there.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's theater.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's art.
It's art.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's funny that you're laughing at that.
[SPEAKER_06]: But anyways, yes, there are a lot of people in all occupations that play World of Warcraft, even strippers.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not like, oh, I strip, therefore I cannot play games at all.
[SPEAKER_06]: But yeah, porn stars, strippers...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: Marissa is in chat again saying, they make all sorts of terrible porn games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember how I said earlier, why don't porn studios make games?
[SPEAKER_05]: They make all sorts of terrible porn games, but they're usually multiplayer online.
[SPEAKER_05]: I learned this by working in the porn capital of the world, Chatsworth, California.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, two comments to that.
[SPEAKER_05]: A, I should have figured that out because on porn websites, so I've heard, you see a lot of times ads for those multiplayer sex things.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you've heard.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I just heard through Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: Through your eyes.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what you see on those sites.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I guess you're right.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just don't think of them because they're not really out there and about.
[SPEAKER_05]: And B, I did not realize Chatsworth, California was the capital of the porn industry.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it doesn't surprise me.
[SPEAKER_05]: But if you've ever been to Chatsworth, California, it's, you know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Is it better than Buttonwillow?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's better than Buttonwillow.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would say Fresno is probably better than Chatsworth.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I like how we're only laughing because everybody else doesn't live in California.
[SPEAKER_05]: No offense to the people there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wink wink hint hint.
[SPEAKER_07]: My grandma's from there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Her movie comes out next month.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ew.
[SPEAKER_05]: Gilf.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then Marissa also says, Rob can have some of my boob to play with.
[SPEAKER_05]: Stress toys.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have too much anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: Marissa has some nice big boobies.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would definitely help relieve some stress.
[SPEAKER_10]: Your own stress all day with her boobs.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can we move on back into video games?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know how we got on the whole topic of strippers from Tron.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was the last story we just did was Tron.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just want to point out.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then suddenly it's about strippers playing World of Warcraft and boobies in Chatsworth, California being the porn capital of the world.
[SPEAKER_07]: I definitely would pay good money to see a stripper that's glowing in the Tron outfit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, there's that guy on the internet, the Tron guy, who wears that outfit.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, no, no, not him, but imagine if a woman wore that outfit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is he hot?
[SPEAKER_05]: I just don't want to see a woman the size of the Tron guy wearing that outfit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't process this much data.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dark Knight in chat says, thank God Jamie's not here for this one.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know...
[SPEAKER_05]: It probably would have derailed even if she was here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because it's not the fact that Jamie's not here, it's the fact that Rice Princess is here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_10]: I didn't bring up... Wait, yes I did.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes you did!
[SPEAKER_10]: La la la, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember, you and Loki have this whole six degrees of strippers thing going on here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or we just both live in the same town and both go to the same strip club.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why am I not being invited to said strip club?
[SPEAKER_10]: I haven't gone in like three years.
[SPEAKER_05]: I haven't gone in like a year or two.
[SPEAKER_06]: We need to...
[SPEAKER_06]: Fix this.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's been a long time.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just because you go to the strip club and afterwards you're like, that cost me a lot of money for very little time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why the fuck did I do that?
[SPEAKER_06]: And then you forget about it after a while.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you have Guilty Gear news, right, Loki?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, speaking of guilt for spending all that money at strip clubs.
[SPEAKER_06]: Guilty Gear XX Accent Core Plus
[SPEAKER_06]: And then I almost vomited.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, so Guilty Gear, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it'll be coming out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Too bad it's not the new Guilty Gear.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or, wait, that wasn't, it was something blue.
[SPEAKER_06]: I forget what they called it.
[SPEAKER_06]: The new game, it's not Guilty Gear, but it's done by the same people.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's all, like, HD, or not cel-shaded, but, like, hand-drawn animation stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: No idea.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, well, let's move on to the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the part of the show every week that you guys can send us an email, and we'll read it here on the show and respond to whatever's in it or make fun of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: One of the two will happen.
[SPEAKER_05]: We invite your emails to be sent in to mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: Although we didn't have a whole lot this week, that's probably because our podcast feed was behind a little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: But by the way, it is getting caught up.
[SPEAKER_05]: A new show just went out today, so go look for it.
[SPEAKER_05]: We do have at least one email to read, and it's from Australia.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is from Mike in Australia.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mike in Australia says, Hello to all in studio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rob, Loki, Silent Nathan, and Rice Princess.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, he must be listening right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because he knew exactly who was on the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, hello.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've had the opportunity to listen live two weeks in a row, which is a treat considering during your halftime Puppy Bowl music break, it's coming up to 2 p.m.
[SPEAKER_05]: So generally, I'm at work.
[SPEAKER_05]: Firstly, I want to ask your thoughts about some good platform games on the DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't have an Xbox 360 or PS3, so I'm stuck with the DS Lite, which is good enough at the moment.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've acquired Castlevania Order of Ecclesia, but haven't really gotten into yet, played the first level or so.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm slowly playing through Yoshi Island DS, so if you can suggest anything similar, that would be good.
[SPEAKER_05]: Before I finish, I just want to say great show as always, and really enjoy listening to your shows.
[SPEAKER_05]: Take care, and hope to listen live again soon.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mike.
[SPEAKER_05]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_05]: This email is not sponsored by anyone, but for you guys to learn a new Australian term,
[SPEAKER_05]: Budgie... Bud... Budgie Smugglers.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess the email's brought to us by Budgie Smugglers.
[SPEAKER_05]: Explanation from Urban Dictionary.
[SPEAKER_05]: Australian slang term for men's tight-fitting Speedo-style swimwear.
[SPEAKER_05]: The lump in the front apparently resembles a budgie when it is stuffed down the front of someone's shorts.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's a budgie?
[SPEAKER_10]: That's what I want to know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Is that like a Snuggie?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, I bet it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's like the Australian version of a grape.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Look, look, back to the question at hand.
[SPEAKER_05]: How about some DS platform games?
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, I haven't played a whole lot on DS as of late.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just, I have this thing against playing games on DS for some reason.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like playing games on the TV, but to help our poor guy out, what are some games?
[SPEAKER_05]: See, even when I'm playing the DS, I'm playing a lot of RPGs, like Final Fantasy IV or Mario.
[SPEAKER_05]: You want to just know good DS games?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, well, platformers specifically.
[SPEAKER_05]: Things like Castlevania, Yoshi Island.
[SPEAKER_05]: What are some other good platformer games?
[SPEAKER_05]: New Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_05]: is definitely one of the classics.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you don't have that yet, you've got to get that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to look to chat, too, for some hints.
[SPEAKER_05]: Chat, what are some good ones?
[SPEAKER_06]: New games that have come out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course, there's a new Kirby game, Kirby Super Star Ultra, which is port.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then there's... Was it...
[SPEAKER_06]: The Chase, Phoenix meets Felicity.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's supposed to be kind of like Kirby's Canada's Curse.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then other platformer games.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sure there's a lot of crappy games that have come out that have been like platformers.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wasn't N out on the DS?
[SPEAKER_05]: Didn't they release a version of N?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, that's kind of a neat little game.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's coming out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or that's already out.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then...
[SPEAKER_05]: GameGuru in chat suggests Sonic Rush.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's better than the console Sonics.
[SPEAKER_07]: You would definitely also have to pick up the Chrono Trigger for the DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not a platform game, but it's way better than any of the games you've already mentioned.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, a budgie is a bird.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like a parakeet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, thank you.
[SPEAKER_10]: Seriously?
[SPEAKER_05]: I feel like I learn new things on this show every day.
[SPEAKER_10]: The more you know.
[SPEAKER_05]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_05]: And some other folks in the chat room do agree with Sonic Rush, so there you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you don't own that one yet, you should probably check out Sonic Rush.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hitstun, though, suggests Tony Hawk's American Skateland.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's kind of a platform game, sort of.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_05]: So there's some suggestions from us to you.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you have an email you want to send us, mailbag at orangelongerator.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'd like to hear more international slang terms, like budgie smugglers.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was definitely educational.
[SPEAKER_05]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: What'd you say, Nathan?
[SPEAKER_07]: Next time you put on a Speedo, look down and it will resemble a parakeet in your pants.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think there's going to be a next time I'm going to put on a Speedo.
[SPEAKER_05]: All natural.
[SPEAKER_05]: If I go swimming, I wear swimming trunks.
[SPEAKER_05]: In this country, it's not appropriate usually to wear Speedos to the beach unless you are really good looking, and I'm not really good looking, sadly.
[SPEAKER_05]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_10]: People do it anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tron guy wears that whole thing in public, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: He does.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's go on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's move on with some more gaming news.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll get to the Skype line soon also, by the way, guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: Skype line opening up a little later.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, here's a game if you're a fan of the Jump Superstars games that they have on the DS.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a new Konami PSP Brawler coming out.
[SPEAKER_06]: And no word on... Let's see here what the title is on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it's got... Oh, Sunday X Magazine is the...
[SPEAKER_06]: and all the other characters.
[SPEAKER_06]: Project Arms, Inuyasha, Jump Ultimate Stars,
[SPEAKER_06]: was okay, it was a neat fighting game on the DS it was kind of like Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_06]: a little bit but the way that you use they had a bottom portion of your screen that you can align different manga panels and you would get different abilities and assist characters and stuff like that based on what you had in there and you had to fit them in so it's almost like the sticker system on Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_06]: Brawl it's kind of neat I see
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: More PSP the merrier, I suppose.
[SPEAKER_05]: 20 players in this game 10 on 10 robot battles
[SPEAKER_10]: That's crazy.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want to play it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It sounds awesome, but I don't think you'll ever see one on these shores.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just arcades aren't popular enough over here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe a Dave & Buster's would be like your biggest bet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you may not have to have 20 cabinets, but I mean, it still could be, you know, cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: It might be cool, but I don't know if you're going to see it.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's all.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's probably going to be expensive.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think there's enough arcade stuff to justify it, sadly.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, you know, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: But anyway, it is in development.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_06]: Block Peepo
[SPEAKER_06]: But it's very unique looking and it's got a lot of the block things that are going to be in this bin.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I just have a feeling, you put that in an arcade, kids are going to be stealing that shit left and right.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it's neat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why can't kids just be more responsible?
[SPEAKER_10]: That's a good one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, Leo Shen agrees.
[SPEAKER_05]: Those blocks would get stolen so fast if it was in the US.
[SPEAKER_05]: They'd have to be all put on those cords.
[SPEAKER_06]: That would be a mess.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're like, crap, I can't put these blocks in there because of all these cords.
[SPEAKER_10]: I got stuck and tangled in these cords.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Help!
[SPEAKER_05]: Amplitude DS Amplitude DS
[SPEAKER_06]: There we go, there's a little clip of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's definitely a scaled down, I know, all I can hear is the audio, but I'll tell you, it looks like a very scaled down version of Amplitude.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because you don't really have the hypnotic backgrounds that a game like Amplitude had.
[SPEAKER_05]: It looks like you only have three tracks, but still, it's a start.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's something.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's bound to get sued.
[SPEAKER_05]: Especially if that rumor from a few weeks back that Harmonix might be making a comeback with this stuff is true.
[SPEAKER_05]: There it is, Supersonic Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you can download it now.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's available out there.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, I mean, if you want to check it out and you've got a homebrew-enabled Wii system, you know, definitely check this out.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, of course, if you have a homebrew-enabled DS, you can check out Amplitude DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course, homebrewing any of those systems might violate your warranty, so be careful and don't say OLR told you to do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Warranty's warranty.
[SPEAKER_06]: You don't need that crap.
[SPEAKER_06]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: More like this game, I think.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's basically a combat racing game.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it'll have 18 different levels.
[SPEAKER_06]: It'll feature 7 different cars, all with giant guns and weapons on them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like any other car should have.
[SPEAKER_06]: And this is a brand new game from a company called Team Six Studios.
[SPEAKER_06]: And this is their first Wii game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Looks okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: But hey, we need a good combat racing game.
[SPEAKER_06]: And since they're not making another full auto game...
[SPEAKER_06]: DT Racer DT Carnage
[SPEAKER_05]: Some other games that got really cheap lately were the Need for Speed games because apparently they did not sell very well, the recent games they released.
[SPEAKER_05]: So EA decided if it worked for Batman, it's going to work for us.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're going to reboot the franchise.
[SPEAKER_05]: So they're hitting the old reset button on the Need for Speed franchise, and they're going to release three new Need for Speed games in the year 2009.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's interesting, though, is that the whole kind of concept behind it, one for the core gamers...
[SPEAKER_05]: One for the casual gamers, one for the online gamers.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's an interesting approach to take with the games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Need for Speed Shift is the game that's coming out on PlayStation 3, 360, PC, and PSP, and that's the core game.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's like Project Gotham.
[SPEAKER_05]: Coming out in the fall as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: Need for Speed Nitro, that's coming out on the DS and the Wii, which you can probably guess is going to be the casual game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that's more like the original Need for Speed games.
[SPEAKER_05]: It also is supposed to have giant head racers and car vaulting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Lame!
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait, car vaulting?
[SPEAKER_05]: God, I hope this is not another fucking... Wait, wait, wait, that might just be like a vault to actually put your car in.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, that's car vaulting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, stupid!
[SPEAKER_05]: No!
[SPEAKER_05]: Why?
[SPEAKER_05]: Wouldn't you like that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I do like that, but, you know, the fact that Car Vaulting reminds me of the stupid Cruisin' game that they had come out, and that Cruisin' game was a rip-off, or actually a port of the, was it Not Need for Speed, the Fast and the Furious arcade game.
[SPEAKER_06]: The crappy Cruisin' USA-based one.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: TigerClaw says you mean Fast and the Furious Tokyo Drift Arcade.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've seen that at Walmart.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it's awful.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's where it belongs, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that's what Cruisin' came out of.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's actually what Cruisin' was.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, a third game in the Need for Speed series.
[SPEAKER_05]: If the other two don't sound interesting to you, Need for Speed World Online.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's supposed to be a free online title.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's coming out in Asia first over the summer and then we'll get it in Christmas time.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm assuming you probably have to pay for car upgrades or something, probably based off the Asian model for MMOs where it's free, but then you have to pay for the good stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's free, but your cars have no wheels.
[SPEAKER_06]: Pay extra for the wheels.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like, go!
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, crap.
[SPEAKER_06]: Can't go.
[SPEAKER_05]: by the way the games are all being developed by different studios even though Black Box apparently kind of got you know kind of well pink slipped a lot of them did Black Box is still working on Need for Speed World Online at least who's left with EA Singapore Need for Speed Nitro the casual one is by EA Montreal it's Arcade Racer is what they're calling it Need for Speed Shift coming by Slightly Mad they're the guys that made GT Legends and Blimey apparently is on it too GTR 2 Blimey
[SPEAKER_05]: Blimey!
[SPEAKER_05]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Lots of Need for Speed in 2009.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, if you're a Need for Speed fan, that is exciting news.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkTetsuya in chat, I believe, is a Need for Speed fan and says there's supposed to be a fourth one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, there's a fourth secret one, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hopefully that's the good one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Need for Secret.
[SPEAKER_10]: Burnout Paradise Burnout Paradise Burnout Paradise
[SPEAKER_06]: But it's a Burnout Paradise Police Cars, and they've got the actual link for it, but it says coming soon on the actual in-game store.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they do have some screenshots, I guess, I don't know if it's preview pics or something like that, of the PCPD cars.
[SPEAKER_06]: So maybe new game modes, some sort of chasing stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, Burnout Paradise is getting fucking awesome and now you can get the game for like 20 bucks.
[SPEAKER_06]: All the free download content and all the paid download content that's coming out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Much love to those folks for just continuing to support a game that might have gotten bashed as mediocre when it came out, but they're still just expanding and expanding on it and making it pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, good for you guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Any time frame on when that could come out?
[SPEAKER_06]: No word, but a lot of the stuff that they're talking about, like there's the Burnout Paradise...
[SPEAKER_06]: The New Cars.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that's coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Probably later on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe this month.
[SPEAKER_06]: Possibly next.
[SPEAKER_06]: Probably relatively soon.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: One more story tonight, and it involves a company we talk about a lot on this show, PopCap.
[SPEAKER_05]: PopCap is finally bringing some of their games to the PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_05]: It actually happened this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bejeweled 2 finally showed up on the PlayStation Network, and there also are plans to release Zuma, Heavy Weapon, Feeding Frenzy, and Peggle.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know, Peggle's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Peggle hasn't even showed up on Xbox Live yet, so I'm curious if it'll beat it to the punch on PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: I kind of doubt it.
[SPEAKER_05]: They'll probably be released simultaneously.
[SPEAKER_05]: But there you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: $9.99 if you want to check out Bejeweled 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's one penny less than what you'll pay on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_10]: I go where the bargain ends.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, so we're going to go ahead and open up the Skype line now.
[SPEAKER_05]: 1-877-GAME-OLR, toll free in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_05]: and Canada.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or you can call us on Skype.
[SPEAKER_05]: Our username is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: While we wait for some calls to come in, because we do have a little bit of a delay between when I say, hey, call in, and...
[SPEAKER_05]: When people actually hear me say that on the radio, Loki, do we have any last-minute stories tonight?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, speaking of football, apparently there's that whole deal where the retired NFL players were not getting any money from the new NFL games, and their likenesses were being used without any sort of compensation.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, they have now finished that whole lawsuit, and they are going to be getting paid out on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: In the tune of $28.1 million by the NFL.
[SPEAKER_05]: Only, let's go to the sky flying.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_00]: Hi, this is Spazinator.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, Spazinator, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, two things.
[SPEAKER_00]: First off, I just want to double check and make sure I heard you correctly in part A. Did you see that he had...
[SPEAKER_00]: The collector's edition of Gears of War 2, you're going to lose your Golden Lancer.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, only if you were one of the people that downloaded it while I guess it accidentally went up on the marketplace for free and so a bunch of people downloaded it.
[SPEAKER_05]: They want to restrict it so that only the people with the collector's edition actually have it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I don't know how they're going to figure that out.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're not going to.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not going to happen.
[SPEAKER_05]: You don't think they'll actually be able to figure it out?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, they're not going to figure it out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki's convinced they're not going to be able to figure it out.
[SPEAKER_05]: But if you legitimately have the gold gun from the collector's edition, you're not who they're trying to remove it from.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm kind of glad about that because if I were one of the people that had bought the collector's edition, I'd just hate to lose my fee, you know?
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait, hold on.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not much of a Gears player.
[SPEAKER_05]: What is so special about the gold gun, or is it just that it's pretty?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just a gold gun.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's just bragging rights more than anything.
[SPEAKER_00]: Something to say, hey, I got the special edition.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's kind of like the Iron Rich application for the iPhones.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know, I kind of thought maybe it fired gold bullets or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, what was your second question?
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, it's not so much a question, it's more like a stupid statement.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, we make a lot of those on this show, so go right ahead.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, I was just thinking, with all the talk about strippers in movies during Part A, I doubt it'll ever happen, but someone should make a
[SPEAKER_00]: Game for Xbox 360 and PlayStation 3 where you go up to a strip club and have boobies splash in your face.
[SPEAKER_00]: Kind of like, I don't know, like Showgirls type of game.
[SPEAKER_06]: That would be called This is Vegas.
[SPEAKER_06]: Coming out for Midway later this year.
[SPEAKER_06]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: What about that Playboy game that they had?
[SPEAKER_05]: The Playboy Mansion?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, that was actually supposed to be pretty good.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was popular.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know...
[SPEAKER_05]: The problem is, a lot of these games, while you might see some boobs here and there, you're never going to see anything pretty much more hardcore than that on the PlayStation 3 and the Xbox 360 because of the whole standards thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Where if your game gets rated adults only, your game can't come out on any of the consoles.
[SPEAKER_05]: The consoles basically forbid it because there's too many people out there who don't understand...
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a developer who makes for the publisher who puts that on the system.
[SPEAKER_05]: People think, oh, Nintendo Wii has got this disgusting vagina-eating game that's out on the system.
[SPEAKER_05]: When is that getting released?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not, because it's rated adults only.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not like it used to be back in the day.
[SPEAKER_05]: You get it on the Homebrew channel?
[SPEAKER_05]: That Nintendo seal of quality.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember how those other companies would put out their own games without going through Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was kind of like a whole bootleg thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: They can't really do that now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sadly, I don't think you're ever going to see real hardcore games get released.
[SPEAKER_05]: You would wish one of them would just let up.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, I don't know, porn on the internet's great, but I can see a lot of potential for the new Wiimote technology in a porno game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_07]: Especially if the vagina-eating game was either pigs-in-a-trough type eating or knife-and-fork.
[SPEAKER_05]: Frisbee has a great name in chat for the game, Muff Chomp.
[SPEAKER_00]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, since you kind of touched on it earlier for a second, you know, now this is just me, you know, speaking out by yes here, but what I'm thinking is that, you know, console owners should be afraid of AO games, you know.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, you know, if you mean, like, there should be no problems with it, you know, it's kind of like, you know,
[SPEAKER_00]: The best analogy I can give you is with M-rated games.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's two out there that are complete opposites.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's the Grand Theft Auto series and the BMX XXX.
[SPEAKER_00]: Obviously, the Grand Theft Auto games are really great.
[SPEAKER_00]: There are a few naysayers out there, whereas BMX XXX.
[SPEAKER_06]: I gotta get BMX XXX again.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love that game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, I think my sister has it because I had it for the GameCube.
[SPEAKER_05]: That game is awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki really has the best family ever, doesn't he?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, she has my GameCube.
[SPEAKER_05]: The sister plays BMX XXX.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was a funny game!
[SPEAKER_06]: It's seriously, it's Tony, it's not Tony Hawk, it's like Matt Hoffman's Probium X, but with like nudity and stuff, and just a ridiculous plotline, but it's basically like the old school Tony Hawk game.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what though, Spazinator makes kind of a good point though, is that you know, we have, especially we have this whole duel thing in this country which stinks, this whole double standard where
[SPEAKER_05]: You could chop people in half and chop their heads off and have a completely violent game.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's R or it's M-rated.
[SPEAKER_05]: But heaven forbid you show a cooter or a penis and it's going to be an NC-17 or AO-related thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: But he makes a good point that a lot of the sex games that we've had that have come out, like the guy game, BMX XXX, they've all been kind of crap.
[SPEAKER_05]: What we need is a good artistic...
[SPEAKER_05]: and Pussy Eating came to come out.
[SPEAKER_05]: And we just needed to have, you know, a little bit of art.
[SPEAKER_08]: It'll be like Master Pussy Theater.
[SPEAKER_05]: Master Pussy Theater, exactly.
[SPEAKER_00]: And if you want to really take it over the edge there, you know, throw all that stuff in there and then just, you know, have like a side mission where you blow up a certain ex-fluoridian lawyer.
[SPEAKER_00]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_00]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_05]: AcidicVampire wants to remind us there's boobies in God of War in a sex minigame.
[SPEAKER_10]: There is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, you're on Boobie Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, Boobie Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: How exciting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whoa.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Jason.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, Jason.
[SPEAKER_05]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_05]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, now that you mention it, I don't know that I want to explain on air what's on my mind.
[SPEAKER_05]: What did you call in to discuss tonight with the Orange Launch Radio host on this family program?
[SPEAKER_04]: As long as Rush Limbaugh and Bill O'Reilly are alive and spewing their shit, your dreams will never come true, I'm sorry to say.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, that's not why I called in, but it was very funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was a very funny anecdote to add in to everything that just happened.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm hoping somebody can answer me this because...
[SPEAKER_04]: Obviously, I heard this just recently, and it's the stupidest thing I've ever heard.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why does Gears of War need SSL, and why does it stop the game from working?
[SPEAKER_04]: The whole Gears of War broken, blah blah blah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Does anybody know the technical reason behind that?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's because the certificate expired.
[SPEAKER_04]: What is the certificate actually used for?
[SPEAKER_06]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it blocks the game in its entirety?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, sure.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't play Gears of War on PC and it's such an easy fix to set my date back.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is it some type of thing to prevent cheating or the connection to multiplayer mode is secure?
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe to authenticate that it's a legit copy of the game?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's got to be something like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Authenticating the legitimacy of the game or something like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think it has a direct impact on the game itself, Jason, or I think the 360 ones would have stopped working too.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it has specifically to do with some type of authentication thing on the PC.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that's kind of what I was thinking.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some kind of a phone home connection, something or other.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's just, that's the most ridiculous thing I've ever heard.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, we've heard of some really stupid DRM, but for crying out loud, people.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's laughable.
[SPEAKER_04]: You put the situation where you have to have a patch.
[SPEAKER_04]: One of two things has to happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: You either have to buy a ridiculously expensive certificate for, I don't know, 10 years, and then you piss off all the nostalgia players.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or you have to issue a patch every single year with a new certificate.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I think this is going to be a tough lesson learned because this is a pretty big fuck up to have your game completely stop working.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a bad setup.
[SPEAKER_04]: They need to get rid of that entirely.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is a bad mechanism.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, enough computer geekery.
[SPEAKER_04]: You guys mentioned that and I just kind of...
[SPEAKER_07]: They've been having trouble with this sort of thing way back from Monkey Island.
[SPEAKER_07]: They have yet to get this right.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you remember way back on the really old DOS games, you used to buy a game and it'd come with a little booklet and at certain times you'd have to refer to page 193, line B.
[SPEAKER_04]: or you'd have some awful little card you have to match up with the moon on the solstice of winter just to prove that you did in fact buy the game and if you lose it you're fucked some of those things weren't so bad and with the internet I've had a lot of things be subtly replaced anyways Space Quest the Space Quest series came with a brochure of sorts to explain about the game and it had
[SPEAKER_04]: In the case of Space Quest V, which was one of my favorite ones, it had like a star chart with constellation codes or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you had to use those codes to actually warp to different locales in the game as the story tells you to go there.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that was their DRM, and it was good.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was cute.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jason, what I didn't like about that whole thing is that then console games started doing it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And like, you know, if I didn't have that letter from home to dip in the water to see the secret code...
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't have that letter because I bought my game used and I had to call their helpline I'm like, uh, they'll dip the letter in the water I'm like, what letter?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, the one in the manual I don't have the manual Okay, the code's 747 Well, was it that hard?
[SPEAKER_05]: Couldn't you just tell me that the first thing or do you not get your 99 cents a minute if you give it away that fast?
[SPEAKER_04]: People will say that DRM is a necessary evil I'll tell that person you're full of shit
[SPEAKER_04]: By the way, Space Quest V... It's self-serving and it only serves to fuck people over.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hold on, Nathan wanted to say something about Space Quest V. Did you also enjoy blowing up an android with a banana?
[SPEAKER_07]: A space banana?
[SPEAKER_04]: That was... When I was a lot younger, the BBSs were around, but that was the extent of my online life.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love Space Quest IV.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was as far as I could get.
[SPEAKER_04]: I never got to the R&R world.
[SPEAKER_04]: So as many times as I played the game, I always...
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I don't even remember what that planet is called anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: I always got that far, and then that was the end of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that was the whole game for me for about five years of my life.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was more of a King's Quest player, and I wish to God those games would come out on Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_05]: Although they're on GameTap and stuff, so you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're entirely wrong in your preference, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: A lot of people were.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, King's Quest has that rabid fandom.
[SPEAKER_05]: I remember about a year or two ago on this show, we had those guys do a silver lining, which was originally like a King's Quest-inspired thing, and then they were allowed to put it out if they ditched the King's Quest thing, and that whole mess that was going on there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't say anything bad about King's Quest this year.
[SPEAKER_04]: Adventure games in general were really impressive.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just never had one.
[SPEAKER_04]: I never played one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Space Quest wasn't my series.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's something sadly lacking in gaming today, unless it says Telltale Games on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're the only ones doing anything, you know?
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, anything else, Jason, you want to talk about tonight before we get some other calls?
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you guys really think that Bioshock really needs multiplayer?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: I personally don't think it needs multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think the first one was good enough as it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I can see why they want to put it in the second one to definitely make it not feel like more of the same.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because, you know, I think otherwise some people might start to say, well, it's more of the same.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, it's...
[SPEAKER_05]: It's another sci-fi.
[SPEAKER_05]: No matter what the story is or what they do with it, there's going to be people out there that say it's more of the same.
[SPEAKER_05]: But if they throw this multiplayer curve at it, people are going to be like, oh my gosh, it's like the must-have game of da-da-da.
[SPEAKER_05]: It almost makes me think they left it out.
[SPEAKER_05]: It makes it just like every other first-person shooter with a different weapon set.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's, I mean, the one thing, as much crap as I gave Bioshock, because the ending, the last hour and a half or so of it just absolutely pissed me off.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was so boring, and then it ended with the easiest boss battle I think I've ever seen in a game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bioshock, what made, the best thing about Bioshock was the story.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was interesting, it was scientific fantasy, sci-fi, and
[SPEAKER_04]: It was a good story.
[SPEAKER_04]: Being able to find the story, and if you actually sat down and paid attention to it... I mean, I'm not an ADD gamer, so maybe I have a little bit of a different look on the game than some other people.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the story made that game incredible until the end.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that was the best part about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you lose all that in multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's more...
[SPEAKER_04]: I really shouldn't say this, but it's more humdrum.
[SPEAKER_05]: It doesn't necessarily mean, though, Jason, that the focus is going to be on multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_05]: They might still have a very solid single-player mode in it, and the multiplayer might just be an afterthought type thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's very true.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just... A lot of... When you guys mentioned it, and I went article surfing, it was just like, they're finally getting multiplayer!
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my god!
[SPEAKER_04]: And...
[SPEAKER_04]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, because there's a whole audience out there that does play first-person shooters to do the multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, you know, it was missing for them in the first Bioshock.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe they don't see the same thing in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't knock it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just kind of... It seems overbearing in the pre... Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, Jason, we've got to let you go so we can get some more calls.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you have a good one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks, buddy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jeez, come on.
[SPEAKER_05]: We try to keep it to five minutes, and you're on eight.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: See you, buddy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you want to give us a call, 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_05]: Our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: SSJ100Matt says, apparently not having multiplayer in a game hurts a game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry if Legend of Zelda doesn't have multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, but there was that Four Swords game.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was kind of awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember that on the GameCube?
[SPEAKER_05]: I like that game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's GS68.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, GS68.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_01]: So I found out I'm playing DJ Maxx Fever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, the new one in the U.S., the one that just came out?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, the American one.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I know you're a big...
[SPEAKER_01]: But if you're already into the series, I can't really recommend it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, you might as well just get Portable 1 and 2 and get the full silence from both games.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm kind of interested in your review here, because I know you're a big DJ Maxx fan, so it's kind of interesting to hear you give this a negative review, but what if I'm somebody, because I am somebody, personally, who's not really played a lot of the DJ Maxx game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have a friend that's obsessed with it too, so I've seen it, I've seen a couple of the videos, I've not really sat down and spent any quality time with the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's say I'm a person who's never really seen or heard of DJ Maxx before, is this a good introduction game?
[SPEAKER_01]: Um...
[SPEAKER_01]: I can't really say.
[SPEAKER_01]: I haven't played much, but... It's pretty decent, but there's one thing that's bugging me about this game, and it's the whole autocorrect feature.
[SPEAKER_05]: What is this feature?
[SPEAKER_01]: Basically, if you press the wrong button for a node, but at the right time, if all is on the same side of the screen as the node is, you still get the full percentage for it, and you still get some points for it.
[SPEAKER_01]: And...
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm on a GameFAQ with DJ Max Feverboard and I'm seeing newbies saying, oh, so you can just press any button to play the game?
[SPEAKER_01]: So what's the point of the notes and such?
[SPEAKER_01]: And that's why I think this thing is a bad idea.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is kind of strange.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, because then you can just go like, do, do, do, do.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can't turn that off?
[SPEAKER_05]: It seems a little silly.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, yeah, you get 80% of the points, but you still get full credit as far as your percentage goes, which means you can go on pressing the wrong notes at
[SPEAKER_01]: All the time I still get 100%
[SPEAKER_01]: percentage at the end of the song.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not as bad as they say, but and groovy.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, it is pretty good for a release on its own, but when you compare it to the other releases, it feels kind of outdated, and there's only one or two exclusive songs, and they're not that good.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, that's unfortunate, I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe if it sells okay, they'll do another one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe not.
[SPEAKER_01]: I guess a few licenses would have hurt.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, hey, they did Classic Edition, which is a licensed game.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, yeah, kind of saying that, yeah, maybe a few licenses wouldn't have hurt the game.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, Digimix Portal Classic Edition is licensed.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was saying that last week on the show, it just needed a little bit of Americanization to help it penetrate the market, even though it might have pissed some of the hardcore fans off.
[SPEAKER_05]: It would have, in the long run, benefited the game because it would have sold more copies, but nope.
[SPEAKER_05]: What do I know?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, anything else on your mind, GS68?
[SPEAKER_01]: Not much, really, I guess.
[SPEAKER_01]: I got Poppin' Music 13, but eh.
[SPEAKER_01]: And, yeah, I was going to say this, but
[SPEAKER_01]: Maximum 2 and 3 DX came out, but I don't want to talk about it because no one cares about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not that great?
[SPEAKER_01]: It just adds a new course and has 20 more stages and that's about it, basically.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, well, if fans of the series then should keep an eye out for that for more stages and all that good stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, GSX-8, have a good one, buddy.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright, you too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Our resident DJ Max fan calling in to give us the update on what's going on there.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think we're going to go ahead and close up the Skype line for now, so sorry to those that didn't get through tonight, but we will always open it up again next week to take more of your phone calls.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think we're going to go around and start to wrap up the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know it's been kind of a quick show tonight, but you know, there wasn't a whole lot in the gaming news, and of course with the Super Bowl and everything else going on.
[SPEAKER_05]: At least you got stripper talk, if nothing else, tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, it was a good show.
[SPEAKER_05]: I had
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you have fun, Rice Princess?
[SPEAKER_10]: I had a great time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, thank you so much for being here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you have any final thoughts for our listeners tonight?
[SPEAKER_10]: Resident Evil 5.
[SPEAKER_05]: Resident Evil 5.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I should go to Loki though first and ask if there's any last minute stories or he'll yell at me.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not going to yell at you.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't really care.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was going to say, there's a couple things real quick.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you have a launch date 360, it's no longer under warranty.
[SPEAKER_06]: As of February 2nd, year 360, if it gets the three rings of death, you're screwed.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you've got to pay $99 to get the unit fixed.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or...
[SPEAKER_07]: just buy a new one you know or you can just pay someone else to fix it for you for probably less if you pay the $99 to get it fixed is it a new warranty or do you have to pay $99 if it breaks the next day I think it's a one year warranty after that if mine red rings of death again although I didn't get mine I mean I would still be covered I think for a couple more months I'm not sure actually
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: Pluckly I think all mine have crapped out the ones that were going to crap out I have one left that's of my original and I have my other one that I fixed so the one that fixes is actually still working very well and then I have one more that like I said that hasn't been replaced yet but all the other ones have so you know four out of six is not a good good ratio no anything else last minute stories tonight
[SPEAKER_05]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, then Silent Nathan, thank you for being here and being so quiet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you have any final thoughts for our listeners tonight?
[SPEAKER_07]: You're gonna want to stick with lanolin and not that aloe vera bullshit.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: My final thought for tonight is vitamin water is awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, do you have any final thoughts tonight?
[SPEAKER_05]: My head hurts.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I'm sorry, Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hope it feels better.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, thank you guys so much for tuning into and supporting Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: You guys are awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: We really appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Every week, you guys listen to our show.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, if you like what you hear here, since we don't have commercials as of yet or anything, it's all free and stuff, it's really word of mouth that helps spread the word about our show.
[SPEAKER_05]: So please, tell two people you know about Orange Lounge Radio and it really helps us spread the word.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or leave us a nice review on a place like iTunes or something like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: So until then...
[SPEAKER_05]: have a great week, we'll see you next week DarkSakura will be back next week, got plenty more game news Street Fighter 4 will almost be out
[SPEAKER_05]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_05]: To join us for a live show, visit www.allgames.com Sunday nights at 6pm Pacific Time.
[SPEAKER_02]: or allgames.com but we're probably right anyway see you next week