[SPEAKER_13]: Tonight, February 8, 2009, will Netflix on the 360 get a premium upgrade, Time Crisis debuts on the iPhone, and is President Obama a new character in Street Fighter?
[SPEAKER_05]: I like fire Wait, we didn't hear you, is the mic on?
[SPEAKER_05]: It is now!
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, there we go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Back from the dead to join us here on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because she's been out a couple weeks.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was gray.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_09]: Very gray.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh yeah, you went to Prosser, Washington.
[SPEAKER_05]: Party Central America.
[SPEAKER_05]: How was that?
[SPEAKER_09]: I went roller skating.
[SPEAKER_05]: People did roller skating to be cool like 20 years ago.
[SPEAKER_10]: I love roller skating, but I found out something very depressing, Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hmm, what's that?
[SPEAKER_10]: Since I had... The last time I went roller skating was four years ago.
[SPEAKER_10]: I went with Jessica, of all people.
[SPEAKER_12]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_10]: And, um...
[SPEAKER_10]: Oddly enough, having two car accidents where your hip gets injured means it's really hard to roller skate.
[SPEAKER_10]: Especially, you know, when you're going one way and you're having to balance with your right leg and it hurts and ow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ow.
[SPEAKER_10]: So yeah, I murdered myself.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I played lots of stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll talk about that in just a minute, but I have to introduce everybody else who's here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Say hello to the one and only Techmaster Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, how are you doing, Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm doing fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_03]: Fine?
[SPEAKER_01]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was in Oakland all day, so you can't really recover from that.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see you next time.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you want to hear everything, you still probably want to watch Justin TV, but actually listen through All Games Radio at www.allgames.com where we tape every Sunday night right after the Bobby Blackwolf show at 6 o'clock Pacific Time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's introduce other people we have in the studio tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have some very special guests tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to start with this guy behind me here who has not been to the show before, but he's someone I've kind of gotten to know a little bit recently and had listened to a few episodes of the show and I was like, well, why don't you come be on the show?
[SPEAKER_05]: And so say hello to...
[SPEAKER_05]: Other Matt.
[SPEAKER_05]: Matt number two.
[SPEAKER_05]: Matt two.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: How are you, Matt two?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm good.
[SPEAKER_05]: How are you, Rob?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm pretty good.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for asking.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's good to know.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you've actually listened to a couple episodes of the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not an OLR virgin.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you weren't freaked out.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, not too badly.
[SPEAKER_05]: We first met when somebody brought you over to my New Year's party.
[SPEAKER_05]: We kind of were talking and found out we had some things in common and so on.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you actually went away and listened to the show and weren't scared off.
[SPEAKER_05]: You still are talking to me, which is awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: The next day, I went to iTunes and I downloaded a recent podcast.
[SPEAKER_07]: So within 24 hours, I was already listening.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, sucker.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really quickly, what kind of games do you like?
[SPEAKER_05]: Since you've never been on the show before, we usually like to ask new people, what kind of video games do you play, if any?
[SPEAKER_07]: I play a few.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mainly PC gaming for right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: I do have an Xbox 360, but I mainly do the PC gaming.
[SPEAKER_07]: Everything from first-person shooter to...
[SPEAKER_07]: MMORPGs, everything else in between Puzzle games, Prince of Persia, things like that But lately it's been WoW and Rock Band 2 have been dominating my time Nothing wrong with that Nothing wrong with that at all WoW was dominating my time for a little while too Yes Yes, but then I quit But then we have Rock Band 2 I play a lot of as well I have a question for you Okay Do you like old PC games?
[SPEAKER_07]: What do you mean old?
[SPEAKER_07]: Are you a fan of Loom?
[SPEAKER_07]: Never played Loom, but I go back as far as my online gaming experience goes back to X-Wing vs. TIE Fighter, X-Wing Alliance, and organizing online gaming clans, if you will, with IRC Chat, and organizing that on the old school MSN Gaming Zone, if you remember that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do you ever do MUDs?
[SPEAKER_07]: Do which?
[SPEAKER_07]: Do MUDs.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't remember MUDs.
[SPEAKER_10]: Old RPG.
[SPEAKER_07]: Old?
[SPEAKER_07]: Old school.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Back in the day, so.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Descent, when Descent was one of the first 3D games.
[SPEAKER_10]: I remember Descent and having it over 14 floppies.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Doom 2 had 6 floppy 3.5 inch diskettes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Heck yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: I still remember all my cheat codes too.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, nerds, we got to introduce somebody else who's here tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's say this is somebody you always hear a lot about, but he hasn't been on the show too many times.
[SPEAKER_05]: But just in time for Valentine's Day, you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to let Jamie introduce tonight's special guest.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think Jamie would do a much better job introducing.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is my personal parasite.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_05]: Say hello everybody to Jamie's husband Dan is joining us tonight on the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dan, how are you?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for that wonderful introduction, wife.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dan is the king of gaming in our house.
[SPEAKER_09]: He has more knowledge of classic games than I do.
[SPEAKER_05]: Next time I want Rob to introduce me, by the way.
[SPEAKER_06]: Street Fighter 4
[SPEAKER_06]: I prepaid for my $150 fighting stick.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, baby.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, if you're playing it on Xbox 360, though, you kind of have to have one of those.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I'm seriously contemplating getting it on the PlayStation 3 simply because I can't picture playing Street Fighter 4 on the Xbox 360 controller.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm getting it on the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not even just because of the controllers.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's because I'm not going to play fighting games on live.
[SPEAKER_06]: www.DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: I have the collector's edition pre-ordered I'm going crazy I'm watching the World Warrior on loop I'm watching the Street Fighter cartoon I'm going to watch the anime movie the night before Try working in a game store where we've had nothing but Street Fighter on all the demos for like a month
[SPEAKER_05]: What kind of game store work do you do?
[SPEAKER_05]: If you don't mind me asking.
[SPEAKER_05]: You don't have to say what company or whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know what you can say or can't say, but what kind of game store stuff do you do?
[SPEAKER_06]: I manage a game crazy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyone who's listened to this show forever knows I used to manage a GameStop.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, it's not that there's anything wrong with GameStop, other than the fact that they're corrupt and evil and hate you.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I jumped to the other side.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's not that it's any different.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just smaller and hates you less.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I do want to point out now, tonight, we do have the whiteboard in studio.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we can now start, finally, our list of things that suck about GameStop.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm going to have Dan starting off the list tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: They hate you.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'll be writing that on the whiteboard here.
[SPEAKER_05]: They hate all of us.
[SPEAKER_05]: We get into our gaming week.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, DarkSakura, why don't you tell us about your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, my past two weeks of gaming have been fairly diverse.
[SPEAKER_10]: I actually finally got past the stupid dialogue portion of Ragnarok DS and actually got to kill four porings.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ooh, four porings.
[SPEAKER_10]: Blink, blink, blink.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's pretty fun so far.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's really cute.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm just like, dude, how do you get to Prontera?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because that was the only word I could read.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because I know some Japanese.
[SPEAKER_10]: I can't read that much kanji.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then I also finally got through the damn forest on Castlevania Order of Ecclesia.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because it was exactly what I said I had to do.
[SPEAKER_10]: One more level and I could do it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Um...
[SPEAKER_10]: and then I played, we played R-Type Dimensions last night and I have to say that it's really, really, really freaking sweet especially having unlimited ships because R-Type is like freaking hard.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's R-Type.
[SPEAKER_10]: And this is actually harder than I remember R-Type being.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I wasn't really all that great at R-Type to begin with.
[SPEAKER_10]: But Dan and I played co-op last night.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was really fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, it wasn't last night.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was the night before.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway, it was really fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: I saw something that depressed me.
[SPEAKER_10]: I saw the trailer for Marvel Ultimate Alliance 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's Civil War crap.
[SPEAKER_10]: We hated it the first time, Marvel.
[SPEAKER_10]: Stop it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Stop it, stop it, stop it, stop it.
[SPEAKER_10]: It sucked.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was an awful storyline.
[SPEAKER_10]: Stop it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do you hear me?
[SPEAKER_10]: I read your Twitters.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll tell you all.
[SPEAKER_10]: So anyway.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then... What else did I play?
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh yeah, I did actually play some Ragnarok Online for like, you know, an hour, and that was it.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I also had a minor fangasm over Star Trek Online's character trailer.
[SPEAKER_05]: That looked hot.
[SPEAKER_10]: But when it comes out, I'm making the official alien race of OLR.
[SPEAKER_10]: The OLRians.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: Are they going to be orange people?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, probably not.
[SPEAKER_10]: Orange is a good color.
Copper.
[SPEAKER_10]: Copper.
[SPEAKER_05]: I insist I don't wear a red shirt.
[SPEAKER_10]: It depends though.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you are original Star Trek, red shirt is the kiss of death.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you in Next Generation, yellow is the kiss of death.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you're Voyager, prepare to suck.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey now.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like Janeway.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm the one.
[SPEAKER_10]: And if you're DS9, it's the most awesome of them all and Enterprise doesn't exist.
[SPEAKER_10]: Quantum Leap to the Future
[SPEAKER_05]: I've never heard of Perfect World.
[SPEAKER_05]: Give us a brief description of what this is.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, well, then I'm sold.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's the same type of game, though, but it has some pretty gorgeous environments, and it's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: And you can actually ride a tiger.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can ride a white tiger.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want a white tiger.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can you get the eye of the tiger?
[SPEAKER_10]: I've also decided something else completely unrelated to gaming.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want a pet goat.
[SPEAKER_05]: She doesn't even acknowledge it.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I'm not.
[SPEAKER_10]: I also decided that I want a pet goat while I was out of town.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can have my sister's if you want.
[SPEAKER_03]: Really?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, she can't.
[SPEAKER_03]: She has four.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do they have the cool rectangular pupils?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait, in real life, IRL, she wants a goat?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Where the hell are you going to put a goat?
[SPEAKER_10]: In the backyard.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, well, you know, my sister is looking for a place to store her four goats.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want one goat so I can walk it on a leash.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, they suck.
[SPEAKER_05]: What are you going to do with a goat?
[SPEAKER_05]: Keep it as a pet!
[SPEAKER_05]: What, are you going to take it out and walk it around the block?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_03]: My sister collects animals, apparently.
[SPEAKER_10]: Are you going to ride it to work?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, goats are too little to ride.
[SPEAKER_03]: They suck.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's nothing cool about goats.
[SPEAKER_03]: They just eat shit and then shit.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, they'll eat anything, so I'll just feed it, you know, Jaguar games.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's all they do.
[SPEAKER_03]: They just process grass into shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: That is it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dan's Dad's Goats are Cute
[SPEAKER_03]: No, this week I didn't play hardly anything other than Grand Theft Auto 4.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I've been prepping my experience of Grand Theft Auto 4 on the PC, putting the right mods in place so that I can go in and hopefully film something funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just a little hint, I found a skin to reskin Niko to look like Adolf Hitler.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, it's going to be fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: And let's see what else.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some other mods, like flood stuff and crazy weapons, so it's going to be the wacky world of Adolf Hitler.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or maybe another Hitler, you know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hitler on ice.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hitler in the Matrix or something, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyways, can I say some chat comments real quick?
[SPEAKER_03]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now they're on a goat kick.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bob Coffee, away, I think, who forgot to change her name to Bob Coffee, because they're obviously there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bob Coffee says, zombie goats would be the best thing ever.
[SPEAKER_05]: That might be like a video game involving zombie goats.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, they did have Black Sheep, which was zombie sheep.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was an awful movie.
[SPEAKER_10]: They had the trailer for that at the beginning of, was it Death Proof?
[SPEAKER_10]: And it was actually a real movie?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Actdeft in chat says, sheep go to heaven, goats go to hell I just posted a picture of the goats in chat because I love them
[SPEAKER_03]: Chat.orange.com My sister seriously has her goat on her Facebook as one of her pictures.
[SPEAKER_03]: I am not kidding.
[SPEAKER_03]: She had four of them.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think she has three now because one of them got attacked by dogs and died.
[SPEAKER_03]: She has three goats.
[SPEAKER_03]: This just proves goats suck.
[SPEAKER_03]: If a bunch of dogs can take out a goat...
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: It was her boyfriend's dogs, actually.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is like Animal Farm for reals.
[SPEAKER_03]: They don't take care of them, and they start going feral.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's why they attack the goats.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, because they're hungry.
[SPEAKER_03]: So she also has a bunch of birds and hamsters and shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: She's studying to be a veterinarian, though, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: So we kind of let her get away with it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, but she shouldn't have goats.
[SPEAKER_03]: She's in an apartment.
[SPEAKER_03]: She has to store them in Rio Linda.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which, you know, for Rio Linda, they fit right in.
[SPEAKER_03]: But anyways... Yes, they do have names.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't remember what the names are.
[SPEAKER_10]: Rio Linda is to Sacramento, as Atmore is to Mobile, Alabama.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh yeah, that's going to help a lot.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, it's the boonies of California.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, so yeah, that's my game week.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was just Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_03]: I meant to download Killzone 2 because I don't have it pre-ordered at GameStop.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, how will I ever get the demo that seems to be region free?
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe I'll create another free account in the UK.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh no!
[SPEAKER_03]: I've bypassed their security.
[SPEAKER_05]: So yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't have a whole lot to share.
[SPEAKER_05]: After last week's show, you might remember Rice Princess was going crazy over the fact that I had the Resident Evil 5 demo.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we actually went in and played the Resident Evil 5 demo, and it was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, I'll give my impressions on that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was just like, eh, that's okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Was that your impression?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, it was just like, eh.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's kind of how I felt about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Resident Evil's not a series I've ever gotten into.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I love zombies and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's another zombie series, of course, that I really got into that we'll be talking about later.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have to get this off my chest.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: I need to stop talking about this because I have to get this off my chest.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've been waiting all night to say this.
[SPEAKER_05]: I played the absolute worst Xbox Live arcade game in my entire freaking life this week.
[SPEAKER_10]: Worse than yours?
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh my god, this game was awful.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wasn't that actually a TV show?
[SPEAKER_05]: It is a TV show.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hope it got cancelled like five times because the setup of the show was stupid.
[SPEAKER_05]: The AI in the game was stupid.
[SPEAKER_05]: If they got an answer wrong, they would misspell words.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't even understand how the game worked and the clues were terrible.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh my god, this game was awful.
[SPEAKER_05]: I felt myself slowly dying.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: I know, for real, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Bring us some good game shows.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Frisbee in chat says, this game, S-U-C blank S. Exactly how I feel.
[SPEAKER_10]: I wouldn't even be upset if they brought back Bumper Stumpers.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bumper Stumpers was kind of like, how can you have Bumper Stumpers go on and on and on forever?
[SPEAKER_05]: It was great.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, forget it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: I demand that they bring a...
[SPEAKER_05]: Game of Double Dare VXJasonXV in chat says The game show itself is interesting Games based off of game shows tend to suck though Look, I would rather play the Are you smarter than a 5th grader game All day long Than have to play 5 minutes of Merv Griffin's Crosswords ever again
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, with zombie Jeff Foxworthy.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't even... Actually, all things considered, the Are You Smarter Than a Fifth Grader game wasn't bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, for what it is, you know what it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's an adaptation of the TV show.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you don't like the TV show, then whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're probably not going to like the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: For what it is, that live game is not bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: But this game was just not fun at all.
[SPEAKER_05]: at all.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe because you weren't a fan of the TV show?
[SPEAKER_05]: I never watched the TV show.
[SPEAKER_05]: I loved the Scrabble show back in the day.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like word game shows.
[SPEAKER_05]: What other word... The Scrabble show was awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Lingo.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love Lingo.
[SPEAKER_05]: These are two games I would rather see on Xbox Live than Murder, Grim, and Traverse.
[SPEAKER_03]: You should have a game that you're an audience member at one of these shows, and you can yell at the contestants and get them to do stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it may or may not affect the answers.
[SPEAKER_05]: This whole 1 vs. 100 thing that's coming to Xbox Live or whatever that... What are they calling that?
[SPEAKER_05]: The whole...
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: and Deekman in chat says, did you mention Left 4 Dead?
[SPEAKER_05]: I did check out Left 4 Dead finally.
[SPEAKER_05]: One of our listeners was very, very kind and gave... I guess they bought a four-pack together but only used three of the codes.
[SPEAKER_05]: So they gave me a code.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was very, very thankful.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I did check out the game for a little bit but not enough to give impressions yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: I haven't played enough at all.
[SPEAKER_05]: I got raped in like five minutes.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's how horrible I am at first-person shooters, okay?
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, I was going down the stairs and then some big fat guy comes down the stairs and rapes us all because I don't know what I'm doing.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I...
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just a big square and I play a little bit of WoW.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm on that ever...
[SPEAKER_07]: LongQuest to hit 80, because I'm a noob.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you have like 20 characters!
[SPEAKER_07]: I do not have 20 characters.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have one of every class on Narzul, which is my main server.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's funny, because we do have Trekkie nerds on the show tonight, and I think every time.
[SPEAKER_07]: Most of my characters are named after what I have affectionately called obscure Star Trek characters.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, for example, Kes, Seska, Neelix, Gumtu, Darmok, and if you're a Trekkie, you recognize hopefully a handful of those.
[SPEAKER_07]: my main mages I recognize two of them as Voyager names that's right Darmok and Jameelix was really obscure he was on for like six seasons he cooked but he cooked and he didn't he was a main character he was in the opening credits he was on Voyager he was a morale officer Voyager was awesome he was a morale officer that became a security guy under Tuvok anyway so obscure because you never really think of it you think of Janeway you think of Trekkies 3 yeah Trekkies 3 exactly what's that?
[SPEAKER_10]: I have to ask, do you like Warp 11?
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sadness.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: My main mage is Malak, but I had to rename him to Valerian since someone took the name when I had the transfer service.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hopefully one day Valerian will be 80, and then I will have to work on my other, as Rob calls them, 20 characters.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bob Coffee in chat says, I recognize all of those I fail at life, lol.
[SPEAKER_05]: We both fail at life, lol squared.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Dan, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_05]: What kind of stuff have you been playing?
[SPEAKER_06]: It was awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: I pulled down HD Remix, the Super Street Fighter Turbo HD Remix, and at first I played the demo and I was like, ah, super janky, no thanks.
[SPEAKER_06]: But as Street Fighter Mania gripped me, it was like, okay, I'll download it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's actually not too bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a little bit easier than Super Turbo is normally, so that's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: See, Rob, these are the people that encourage this kind of behavior, re-releasing games.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I'm terrible, because I also downloaded R-Type Dimensions.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which was... It kicked ass.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I've got... I've got the remake of Bionic Manor.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm a remake whore.
[SPEAKER_06]: Seriously, if it's a good remake, if it's a game that needs to be remade... Some of them are really good.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Bionic Manor... I mean...
[SPEAKER_06]: I fully say remake it, but you gotta be real faithful and real respectful of the original material.
[SPEAKER_03]: R-Type, I'm not really sure if they changed anything to it, but Street Fighter, they just made the sprites prettier.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, that was basically what they did with R-Type.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it's R-Type 1, R-Type 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's got the 3D graphics.
[SPEAKER_06]: They added a two-player simultaneous mode, which was actually kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: But if you're an R-Type god and you could blaze through the whole game with no problem, yeah, it's still just R-Type.
[SPEAKER_05]: You are an R-Type god, though, from what I remember Jamie saying.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I could totally dust, like, the first three levels of R-Type 1, then you get to level 4 when the game gets hard, and I mean, I don't care who you are, R-Type gets real, real hard.
[SPEAKER_06]: I could beat it on the consoles, but this, R-Type Dimensions is a hard version of R-Type.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know if your hitbox in that game is bigger or what, but, you know, there's a lot of shooters and stuff that deserve remakes, and so, I do encourage that, you know, as long as it's respectful to the original game, and it's a game that needs it, you know.
[SPEAKER_05]: TigerClaw in chat makes a good case.
[SPEAKER_05]: He says, Bionic Commando remake was awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: You get the Hitler head explosion in full 3D.
[SPEAKER_05]: True that.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is true.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very true.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, we're going to go ahead and get into some housekeeping tonight real quick, and then we'll finally get into some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hold on, hold on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, what?
[SPEAKER_05]: I have a few more things I want to add.
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, I don't think we're talking about this tonight, so I'm going to mention it anyways.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Warriors on Xbox Live Arcade
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh yeah, definitely.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think actually it's already coming, the gaming.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're going to show that off at E3 this year with Avatar by Ubisoft.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to be in 3D as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I wouldn't be surprised if it's polarized because that would make sense to me because it doesn't look that bad when you're not looking at it without the glasses.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I was really surprised before.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just used to either the really weird blurry glasses or the red and blue stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_03]: So, you know, old school 3D stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, I mean, the polarized glasses, it was weird because I put them on and I thought, oh, this is going to hurt my eyes and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm like, wow, it's just looking like through normal glasses.
[SPEAKER_03]: But then, you know, the effect on the screen is really awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, a question for you.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do you ever, I think it's on the WiimoteHack website.
[SPEAKER_10]: There was the guy who did sort of the reverse by using the infrared sensors.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, the, I forget what they call it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I haven't done that just yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't get my Bluetooth stuff to work right.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I mean you can see the full 3D effect even just watching a video of it.
[SPEAKER_10]: They should do something that would utilize that type of technology.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well they were supposed to in Boom Blocks if you remember the developers wanted to do that but they somehow someone said no and they had to take it out.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's crazy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because there was going to be a little Easter egg in there where you could do it that way.
[SPEAKER_03]: I forget what they called it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um
[SPEAKER_03]: I know Trackmania does some sort of 3D thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know if it's with the red-blue glasses or if it's the polarized glasses, but that would be fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because Trackmania is a sweet game.
[SPEAKER_03]: But that's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, that's alright, that's alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's talk about, really quickly, housekeeping.
[SPEAKER_05]: I pretty much said all I wanted to say about the new website.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hopefully that will go live for everybody, not just during the show, but everybody will get to see that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hopefully in the next week or two, it's going to be awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Regular content, again, I'm so excited.
[SPEAKER_05]: We can actually do reviews and all that fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: It'll be great.
[SPEAKER_05]: Otherwise, just make sure to keep following us on MySpace and Facebook, at the Oil Army on Facebook, and LiveJournal as well at Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_05]: What, Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: I was just thinking, because it is sort of housekeeping.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hope I can get in.
[SPEAKER_03]: Special guests in is going to be difficult, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, possibly this year we will have Nelly coming in to do her Woman That Hates Gaming review of E3.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because we're going to go there for a couple days.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're actually going to a trip for Disneyland as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because E3 happens to fall on her birthday.
[SPEAKER_03]: So she said, you know, I'm going to be...
[SPEAKER_03]: you know very loving and I'm gonna I'll go with you you you can go to E3 you know
[SPEAKER_03]: and all you know as long as we go to you know Disneyland stuff so I'm fine with that and go in the E3 maybe a day or two or something like that I'm very excited to get the wife that hates gaming interviews it's gonna be amazing all right so we'll see we'll see all right anyhow let's get into some gaming news like a half hour into the show and haven't gotten to gaming news yet so Loki please take it away all right well speaking of E3 um the exhibitor list has been revealed and uh
[SPEAKER_03]: Some people that had dropped out before are back, including Activision Blizzard.
[SPEAKER_03]: They are back after dropping out of the last E3.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, I mean, who can blame them?
[SPEAKER_03]: The last E3 was kind of... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's interesting, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: Even though Activision Blizzard may be there, the Blizzard portion of Activision will not be there.
[SPEAKER_01]: But, I mean...
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess they did have a few things they could have shown off, like Diablo 3 and StarCraft 2, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I don't really know when all that stuff is supposed to come out, so they don't really necessarily need to show that, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: What does Activision have that you want to see without Blizzard?
[SPEAKER_03]: Without Blizzard?
[SPEAKER_06]: Blizzard has everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: They've got StarCraft, they've got Diablo, they've got whatever's next for WarCraft.
[SPEAKER_06]: Activision's like, well, we've got Guitar Hero!
[SPEAKER_06]: Call of Duty Modern Warfare 2
[SPEAKER_03]: It's the new Tony Hawk game where they're going to have an actual skateboard that you use for the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that'll be interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Something else they can try to sell us for $200.
[SPEAKER_03]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe you'll see what they're going to do to innovate with Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then maybe Call of Duty Modern Warfare 2 and possibly the new Transformers game just to see if it's really sucky or not.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, hey, I know the first game blew, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you watch the trailer that's up on Kotaku for it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, and it doesn't look any better than the first game.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's a different developer, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a movie game.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to suck.
[SPEAKER_06]: It'll be bad in a different way, and not all movie games suck.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, wonderful.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, Wanted looks awesome, and that's going to be a movie game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, but it's not going to be awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're watching a trailer, and you're like, ooh, that looks like it might be good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, yeah, Transformers, the new game trailer, there was nothing that said, I'm going to buy this.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just kind of, I mean, look at it.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you even spend money to rent that game, you're high.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's for seven-year-old boys who love the movie and have to keep on living it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not for gamers.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I want to keep on living the movie.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: Pirate it like the rest of us.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: But seriously, Activision has got nothing without Blizzard.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, and it sucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, it started off as a port of the GameCube game, and they fucked that up, and so they made it into this new game where they renamed it, and it still sucked.
[SPEAKER_06]: Man, speaking of porting GameCube games, who's not bitter that Pikmin is just the GameCube version with Wii controls?
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: Even if it's just GX, because that game was brutal.
[SPEAKER_05]: That better be the secret in Reggie's pants at E3.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what they should be doing as one of the new play control games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Falcon Punch!
[SPEAKER_03]: Seriously, they should do a new play control version of F-Zero GX, because that would be perfect.
[SPEAKER_03]: But instead of this Mario Power Tennis, really, was that such a great game that it requires... Mario Power Tennis was pretty pimp.
[SPEAKER_06]: And come on, like Strikers?
[SPEAKER_06]: Strikers is awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mario's aggressive death soccer is like the best game to ever happen.
[SPEAKER_06]: I still, still can't, you know, believe that that game is that good.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hate soccer, but I love that game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, it...
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't get that mental image now of Reggie Fils-Aim coming out at E3 and Falcon punching us with his cock.
[SPEAKER_10]: I issue a challenge now to our listeners, especially the ones who were kind enough to do the Kutaragi Crayon eating picture.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, no.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't make a picture.
[SPEAKER_10]: We now want the Falcon punch picture.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, no.
[SPEAKER_10]: I will send someone a shiny silver dollar.
[SPEAKER_05]: Keep it clean.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: That I write on in Sharpie.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is Falcon Punch.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's move on to something depressing to try and sedate the show a little bit here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sadly, THQ has laid off about 100 people on their staff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sad trombone.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, sad trombone, but it was the mobile gaming division.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I don't mean to sound crass.
[SPEAKER_05]: I feel sorry for those people.
[SPEAKER_05]: It sucks to lose jobs and stuff, and the economy stinks and everything, but...
[SPEAKER_05]: You know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Does THQ make anything besides SmackDown?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, they make a bunch of Spongebob and Nintendo licensed games and Saints Row 2, which I love.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh yeah, they did make Saints Row 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: That game was not so bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, well, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: They are actually going to be restructuring the wireless subsidiary.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently, though, they actually closed completely the San Diego mobile studio as well and some offices in UK and Germany.
[SPEAKER_05]: They are still going to be cranking out some wireless games, though, out of Finland.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're Uni Versomo Studios.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I guess this means, I don't know, more Worms Mobile, things of that sort.
[SPEAKER_03]: They did a mobile version of Saints Row.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think it was any good, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: If they did, like, Worms World Party...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, we will.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who likes Netflix?
[SPEAKER_05]: Me.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have watched seasons 1 and 2 of 30 Rock on Netflix on demand on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_10]: See, speaking of Netflix on the Xbox 360, they did a survey that went out to a few members that was asking them if they would pay a little bit extra for premium content like from cable channels like HBO.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it's sort of, I guess, rumored that it's going to be around $10 extra.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't encourage them.
[SPEAKER_10]: But, um, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think some people would be excited by it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nobody will be excited by it.
[SPEAKER_10]: There are consumer whores.
[SPEAKER_05]: Look, I like the idea of offering some more of this premium content.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, being able to watch the tutors on demand and all this kind of stuff sounds kind of awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I like...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: but independent documentaries about strippers that went to stripping because of Hurricane Katrina which yes is an actual documentary I once watched on Netflix 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's all that's going to be left is Hurricane Stripping.
[SPEAKER_06]: Premium content, good.
[SPEAKER_06]: Paying more, bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's already $9 a month for like the super basic level with the unlimited streaming which is great through the Xbox.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's...
[SPEAKER_06]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's got me watching more TV than ever, which is, you know, really what society needed.
[SPEAKER_06]: But at the same time, it's like, oh man, don't give them any reason to charge us more.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's given us Doctor Who.
[SPEAKER_10]: We've got up to season four now, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: No.
[SPEAKER_10]: No?
[SPEAKER_06]: Not only don't we have season four, but we're not paying extra for it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It just came with the next season.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'd be curious if you sign up for premium membership at Takeaway Subscribership from HBO, Cinemax, all that stuff, from cable subscribers, because now they can just download for a whole lot cheaper the main shows like Big Love, Tudors, other Sopranos from back in the day, those types of shows.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm curious about the Takeaway Subscribership.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a good question, but I wonder if they would care, because they're still getting money from you watching their shows, so maybe they don't care.
[SPEAKER_05]: They still get their money one way or another.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's true, or the cable companies are maybe losing revenue.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know about the hell with them.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm sure that Netflix is actually paying a certain percentage to the premium channels for content.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, that would make sense, or else HBO would be like, bitch, please.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, they pay a licensing fee for the movies that they use, but I mean...
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not like they're going to show The Sopranos every night after it comes on like they do CSI.
[SPEAKER_05]: Xlink in chatroom says, gives a very honest response.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is why I torrent.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a very honest response, whether legality is questionable or whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, Dan says, why pay for what I can steal?
[SPEAKER_05]: But also, there's something to be said.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just like iTunes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why do people actually use iTunes when you can go out and find the downloaded MP3?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because sometimes it's a pain in the ass to find the actual MP3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I have an iPhone.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, and the fact, how convenient is it that you can just sit there, tap a button, and you will have the full song for just a buck.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's legal.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you get the warm fuzzies, legal, supporting the artist, all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: I get the warm fuzzies doing the opposite.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you're evil.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's because you're a prevert.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, that's not true.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's move on with some more gaming news.
[SPEAKER_05]: Netflix isn't really gaming, but at the same time, that's what people use their 360s for lately.
[SPEAKER_05]: At least I do.
[SPEAKER_06]: One million subscribers.
[SPEAKER_05]: I spend more time on my 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: Seriously, if you look what I've done the past week, on the 360, I played that horrible Crosswords game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I played Netflix.
[SPEAKER_05]: My PlayStation 3 is actually where I've been gaming lately because I have Prince of Persia on PS3.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've been playing that and LittleBigPlanet.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've been playing the hell out of.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's been my...
[SPEAKER_05]: PS3 I'm actually using my which is weird because I always thought PS3 was supposed to be the system that was going to be my all-in-one entertainment center but like I'm the complete opposite lately I don't know what the hell's up with that I use my PS3 for streaming stuff it works pretty well
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, who cares?
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, let's move on with gaming news.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, Gauntlet DS is potentially cancelled.
[SPEAKER_03]: And this is coming from, I guess, various retail sites that have been telling their customers they had a pre-order that's been cancelled.
[SPEAKER_03]: That it's been removed off of GameStop and some other retail websites.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, well, I know from a distributor's standpoint, I think it was...
[SPEAKER_03]: It was locked and basically put out of print, which either means that it's got a to-be-announced release date, or actually it's cancelled.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, it's pretty much cancelled.
[SPEAKER_05]: Could it possibly be in limo?
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, might the game be changing hands or something?
[SPEAKER_05]: It could be.
[SPEAKER_05]: It happens a lot.
[SPEAKER_03]: In fact, with Midway going through all the problems it's been having too, you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for reminding me too, that that was something I gotta touch on
[SPEAKER_03]: Anything four player on the DS would be really cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anything that you're waiting for from Midway, don't hold your breath.
[SPEAKER_06]: It pains me to say it because I love Midway.
[SPEAKER_06]: Me too.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love Mortal Kombat and a lot of their IPs, but that company is boned.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is too bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: They owe twice what their company is worth.
[SPEAKER_06]: The only solace that you'll get is the fact that probably the big studios that they own and the franchises will be snapped up by bigger, probably more stable companies.
[SPEAKER_06]: They'll all belong to EA.
[SPEAKER_06]: and, uh, or ActaBlizzard, uh, before, uh, before it's all over, but Midway is, is going down the tubes.
[SPEAKER_05]: You gotta wonder how much Midway lost on that, uh, Strang, what was that, Stranglehold or whatever that game was?
[SPEAKER_05]: They brought in that big, huge name director and they spent all this money marketing it and I didn't, I think the game made a, a poop when it landed, you know?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not just Stranglehold, they've just had flop after flop after flop and...
[SPEAKER_06]: It's tough.
[SPEAKER_06]: They have all these great franchises and they would try to bring them back.
[SPEAKER_06]: They did Spy Hunter for the PS2 back in the day.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Spy Hunter was great.
[SPEAKER_06]: So they're like, oh man, we'll do Defender.
[SPEAKER_06]: Defender wasn't a bad game, but nobody cared.
[SPEAKER_05]: And their Treasures collections are awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Midway Treasure collections they did on Xbox, like the 20 old games, like Rampage.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, they sell hand over fist.
[SPEAKER_06]: You gotta wonder how they could be in that much trouble.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess the development budgets on their not whoring out their old franchises have just been out of control.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mortal Kombat vs. DC Universe is kind of their last hurrah, I think
[SPEAKER_05]: The DS isn't the most powerful wireless networking device.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: They said they had it working, or maybe they couldn't get it working.
[SPEAKER_06]: If they could make it work.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't really see how much you're going to need voice for Gauntlet.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it's nice, but it's Gauntlet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hit that thing with an axe!
[SPEAKER_06]: Quick!
[SPEAKER_06]: Grab the treasure!
[SPEAKER_06]: No, my treasure!
[SPEAKER_06]: Quit dying!
[SPEAKER_06]: Elf shot the food.
[SPEAKER_04]: Call it, people!
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not that complex!
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a Lego-based strategy game, basically.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I think Loki's kind of talked about this a little bit on the show before.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really?
[SPEAKER_05]: Did I?
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's officially now out there that you're going to be having bases that you're building and defending.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Lego castles, Lego's pirates, Lego's space-themed.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're going to have units that you can actually have pirates and space people in the same team.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you can mix and match all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Until there's Lego ninjas, it just don't matter.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, actually, apparently, in the press release, you can have pirate swordsmen fighting wizards and aliens, dragons battling ninjas.
[SPEAKER_06]: and that's going to be the greatest LEGO game to ever happen.
[SPEAKER_05]: And pirate ships launching broadsides against spacecraft and knights.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you can also play this game local multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sadly, no VIP.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pirate ship fighting a spaceship.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's just ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, seriously.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's a pirate ship got cannons and shit?
[SPEAKER_03]: The spaceship's like, I'm just going to fly higher, bitch.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, you're dead.
[SPEAKER_05]: They need to make a game like this, but like not LEGOs.
[SPEAKER_06]: you need to go old school and get like the Blacktron Legos in there no offense against the Legos but I want to see like dragons versus spaceships for real I want fucking Duplo in this shit Duplo would totally dominate because they'd just be giant indestructible blocks it'd be like tech level low but resistance is like super high and cost well cost of anything Lego is just through the roof
[SPEAKER_05]: Boy, it's like Construction Fighter.
[SPEAKER_06]: Lego versus Mega Bloks.
[SPEAKER_06]: Legos and Duplos and Tinker Toys and Lincoln Logs.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have you seen the Mega Blok Halo toys that they're doing?
[SPEAKER_06]: Uh-uh.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can get like Warthogs and Scorpion Tanks and stuff all made with Mega Bloks.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a franchise that someone should have jumped on.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know it was April Fool's joke, but Lego Halo would have been sweet.
[SPEAKER_05]: The chat room is talking about like a Lego fighting game, and the Rob D says you could lose parts as you fight.
[SPEAKER_05]: That would be fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just knock the blocks off of somebody.
[SPEAKER_05]: It'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Lego Street Fighter.
[SPEAKER_03]: Speaking of Legos, did you see the pictures someone did of the StarCraft II?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: That person is my hero.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was the most awesome thing I've ever seen.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, so Lego Battles coming to the DS, I believe the release date is summertime, so we'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: April.
[SPEAKER_09]: April.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's in time for my birthday.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ninjas and Dragons on Jamie's birthday.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who could ask for more?
[SPEAKER_10]: Rock.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, for our UK friends, I'm so sorry.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just that this game is coming out as making me laugh.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're bringing out a Coronation Street game on the DS, which is sort of like, as far as I know, it's sort of like a weird soap opera-y type show out there, kind of like, what is it, the other one, EastEnders, I think?
[SPEAKER_09]: What?
[SPEAKER_10]: You look...
[SPEAKER_05]: That wasn't on the mic.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dan didn't say it in the mic so you guys didn't hear it, but he went way to cover the gaming news that matters.
[SPEAKER_10]: We have listeners in the UK.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I also want to point out when Loki reads release dates, he reads things like Imagine Teacher and Imagine Babies Dance Party.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, I want to cover everything.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we have to cover everything.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we can make fun of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: There would be a hundred more people interested in what she's talking about than imagine, you know, sitting around and fucking yourself.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: If we were going to read release dates that mattered to me, we wouldn't be reading anything.
[SPEAKER_10]: Can I do my story, please?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, you may.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is the official STFU from me.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway, yeah, Coronation Street is really, really popular.
[SPEAKER_10]: It has 78% of the UK's television audience.
[SPEAKER_10]: So basically, it's like, if you're going to watch TV and it's on, that's the only thing to watch, I guess.
[SPEAKER_10]: But they're doing a DS game by, I don't really know too much about what's going into the game exactly as far as the play of it will be.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it's supposed to be out for Christmas this year, so...
[SPEAKER_10]: Yay, you get Coronation Street.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, they should do a little Britain DS game.
[SPEAKER_05]: That PlayStation 2 one was awful.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, they did a PSP and PS2 game.
[SPEAKER_10]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: Do not want.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that Top Gear and Doctor Who are the only things that justify the continued existence of the BBC.
[SPEAKER_10]: Torchwood and the Sarah Jane Adventures.
[SPEAKER_06]: Torchwood and the Sarah Jane Adventures.
[SPEAKER_06]: Whatever that is.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, and Primeval.
[SPEAKER_10]: Is Primeval still on?
[SPEAKER_10]: Primeval, that's a good show.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I haven't seen Primeval.
[SPEAKER_10]: The new series after Life on Mars, Ashes to Ashes, that's pretty decent.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is, yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: So there's actually lots of good stuff on BBC.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it really is about Doctor Who.
[SPEAKER_10]: The staple of British television, in my opinion.
[SPEAKER_10]: And Top Gear.
[SPEAKER_10]: Top Gear.
[SPEAKER_03]: going from something on the BBC to something that's very American Godfather 2 EA has delayed the release of the game because apparently releasing Godfather 2 on the same day as Killzone 2 not a good idea so they decided to hold it off a little bit I believe now it's coming out the second quarter beginning of April probably
[SPEAKER_03]: So, cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not too excited about Godfather.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't play the first one.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it's my type of game because it is like a Grand Theft Auto sandbox type of thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: You owe it to yourself to pick it up and try it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It actually is a pretty sick game as long as you don't get too much respect because then you stop being able to shake the crap out of people and make them bend your will.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can just walk into a store and grab the dude and beat him up until he gives you what you want.
[SPEAKER_06]: You'd be like, oh, that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sweet.
[SPEAKER_06]: See, I'm wondering if Godfather 2, because I haven't read much about it, if it takes place further in the past, like when Vito Corleone was a kid, or if it's going to be just like, oh, there's more Godfather.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's a continuation.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's not as cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they basically have now online multiplayer as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that's probably mostly...
[SPEAKER_06]: Mostly the whole attraction.
[SPEAKER_05]: Multiplayer would be fun, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: Then you can slap your friends.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want a Scarface, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know they did Scarface, and it was kind of like, oh, he didn't die.
[SPEAKER_06]: He didn't die, and he did it all again because he was so happy the first time.
[SPEAKER_06]: I told him a tenner, and I'm an idiot.
[SPEAKER_06]: Jesus.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: As long as this time when they do the portable versions, they don't make them into strategy games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because seriously, everyone comes to my store and wants to buy the portable Scarface game.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm like, fine, buy it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Then they bring it back like 10 minutes later.
[SPEAKER_06]: What is this crap?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a strategy game.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I wanted to run around and shoot people.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm talking right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is why people need to read the reviews and look at the back of the box.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dumbasses.
[SPEAKER_10]: All we have is a disc.
[SPEAKER_10]: Look at the back of the disc.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm saying in general, Dan, and people, you can look online and find reviews.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's a safe assumption that if the box looks the same and it's on the PS2 and the PSP, it should be largely the same game.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it's not.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you're right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, and I was going to say too, I mean, we shouldn't, you know...
[SPEAKER_03]: I'd be harking too much on the UK for having a TV drama being turned into a game because after all Ubisoft is bringing out Grey's Anatomy for the DS and the Wii It's better to play a trauma center It is supposed to play a trauma center but with more drama Aren't they downsizing that team?
[SPEAKER_05]: Good developers are getting fired Sadly there's an audience for that too There are plenty of people that will probably buy that game I sold one copy of Hell's Kitchen on the Wii Once
[SPEAKER_06]: There's not an audience for that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, unless they're buying it somewhere besides game stores.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's terrible.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why are they making all this crap?
[SPEAKER_03]: I like cooking and yelling.
[SPEAKER_06]: Honestly, the Nintendo Wii, and you heard it here.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you're listening, one of the dozens and dozens of listeners on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you're listening, I'm saying it now.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Nintendo Wii is going to cause gaming Armageddon.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's the return of the Atari 2600.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's shovelware.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're putting anything they can on it to try to make a quick buck.
[SPEAKER_06]: Come on, they're making Grey's Anatomy.
[SPEAKER_06]: No!
[SPEAKER_06]: That's terrible.
[SPEAKER_05]: It will probably be better than E.T.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Nintendo DS is probably that too.
[SPEAKER_05]: It will probably still be better than E.T.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Really, if you played E.T.
[SPEAKER_06]: when that game came out on Atari, it had music and the character was animated.
[SPEAKER_06]: And when you were young and you didn't understand, it didn't suck that bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: All the people who bag on E.T.
[SPEAKER_06]: now never even played it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I did play it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I fell in the hole 50 gazillion times.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's because you suck at video games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_06]: E.T.
[SPEAKER_06]: was not that bad a game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, Atari was arrogant.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, they made more copies than there were 2600s, which is terrible.
[SPEAKER_10]: Give, give, give.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dan.
[SPEAKER_06]: We get it.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you even beat E.T.? ?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I never did.
[SPEAKER_06]: No one ever has.
[SPEAKER_06]: In the existence of mankind.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a YouTube video of someone beating E.T.
[SPEAKER_06]: YouTube videos can be fixed, sir.
[SPEAKER_06]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, when you beat E.T., the real E.T.
[SPEAKER_03]: comes out, and it's actually a good game.
[SPEAKER_06]: The real E.T.
[SPEAKER_06]: comes out, shakes your hand, and goes to space.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I was going to say... I realize E.T.
[SPEAKER_06]: is a notorious bomb, but that's because Atari produced more copies than there were a dying system.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have ghosts.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh my god, I seriously think we're about ready to have Armageddon live here in studio.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a storm going on outside.
[SPEAKER_05]: Weemageddon!
[SPEAKER_05]: That last burst of wind almost blew over the garage door.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's going to be scary.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is what we hear outside.
[SPEAKER_10]: Whenever you get the little awning piece from the roof, it's like...
[SPEAKER_05]: It'll be live on Justin TV, too, when we all get blown away.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't think we're in Kansas anymore.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm controlling the apocalypse.
[SPEAKER_10]: You're all fucked.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can I read a Turok story?
[SPEAKER_10]: Rob, do your story, please.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, I'm going to read a Turok story.
[SPEAKER_10]: E.T.
[SPEAKER_10]: is officially banned on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: No way.
[SPEAKER_06]: Vetoed.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll have to say a word that I just heard.
[SPEAKER_06]: Weemageddon.
[SPEAKER_06]: You should copyright the word.
[SPEAKER_05]: Copyright, dude, Matt, you should copyright that.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's my word.
[SPEAKER_05]: I said Weemageddon.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, they're right.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Mats are fighting over Weemageddon.
[SPEAKER_10]: Weemageddon out of here.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can have Weemageddon.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can we go back on the tape, please?
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, no.
[SPEAKER_05]: Look, moving on, Turok.
[SPEAKER_05]: Turokageddon.
[SPEAKER_05]: Turok, of course, was reinvented recently on the 360 and the PlayStation 3 and all that, and I don't know, I didn't play it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you play it?
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a franchise that needs to come back.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, wait, no, it didn't.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, apparently some folks agree with you, because apparently Turok 2, rumor is, it's been canned.
[SPEAKER_05]: Before it was even announced.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently, this is because of some layoffs that just happened to Disney.
[SPEAKER_05]: Again, this is all kind of rumored.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nothing to do with the poor sales of the first game.
[SPEAKER_05]: But they say maybe Turok 2 will return to development someday, but a bunch of the core people that were doing it are no longer there.
[SPEAKER_05]: But here's the sad thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently, Propaganda Games that was making this game were also the people that were supposed to be doing the Tron game for the new Tron title.
[SPEAKER_05]: So they all might have been sacked.
[SPEAKER_10]: They better find people to do the Tron game, or I will personally go there with steel-toed boots and kick every last one of them in the nuts.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here, you want to make some money, I'll tell you how you do it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's very simple, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: You take the Left 4 Dead concept.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jurassic Park, you're surviving dinosaur attacks, and that's it.
They did that, it sucked.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, that would be pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: They did a first-person shooter Jurassic Park game.
[SPEAKER_10]: They did a first-person shooter Jurassic Park game, and it blew...
[SPEAKER_05]: It was scary.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, that was the one on Super Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_05]: That scared the shit out of me.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was crap.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was the Sega CD one, but the arcade one blew too.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I'm talking Left 4 Dead Dinosaurs.
[SPEAKER_06]: That would be cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm down for that.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is the game that they need to make.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is the game that they need to make using the Left 4 Dead engine.
[SPEAKER_10]: They need to do Marvel Zombies vs. Army of Darkness.
[SPEAKER_10]: They did comics.
[SPEAKER_05]: How about goats versus dogs?
[SPEAKER_10]: How about I do my story?
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait, how about I read a chat comment real quick?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because there's actually some insightful stuff from chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: TheRobD actually says something a little bit insightful, so I have to go to chat for insightful comments tonight because no one in the studio is saying anything.
[SPEAKER_05]: TheRobD says, Is it funny, or it is funny that we take it for granted that a game will have a sequel, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Transformers
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, it's because I think if the first one makes any remote amount of money, because people aren't willing to do anything original because they want to stick to those franchises that they think are going to sell.
[SPEAKER_10]: And, I mean, thank God we have the freaky guy bringing us Noby Noby Boy or else we'd have nothing original.
[SPEAKER_05]: And yet they still won't bring us Guardian Legend 2.
I know!
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry, Noby Noby Boy isn't that original looking.
[SPEAKER_06]: It looks just like Katamari.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you know the video games industry is doomed.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because they made another Turok after Turok Evolution.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Turok Evolution, for anyone who played that game, was bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: Really, really bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not a good game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Was it as bad as Superman 64?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then they went and made Superman Returns, which was not very good either.
[SPEAKER_06]: But that wasn't a sequel to Superman.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, there's a difference between a sequel...
[SPEAKER_03]: It was a reboot.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that's kind of like what Turok, this last Turok was.
[SPEAKER_06]: And actually, the last Turok reboot was Evolution, and it was horrible.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Superman Returns, which was not a bad game if you only paid $10 for it.
[SPEAKER_06]: 60 bucks?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: 10 bucks?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, you could be Superman and you could like blow cars around and tear up Metropolis and that'd actually hurt you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, here's a better example then.
[SPEAKER_05]: Activision.
[SPEAKER_05]: I did not play Superman 64 expecting Superman 2600 where you would fly and then be chased by the Kryptonite.
[SPEAKER_05]: Superman for the 2600 was sweet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Superman 64 managed to be worse than that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because the expectations were higher.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because the 64 should have had a good game where you flew around and did interesting things.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_05]: We've got to keep the news moving because we're like an hour into the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's my story.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, Hugh had a quick thought, and then we'll move on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, I was going to say Activision, you know, the purveyor of fine games, decided that, you know, Pimp My Ride the game was so awesome that they're going to put out Pimp My Ride Street Racing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, Pimp My Ride the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Awful, awful, awful.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: Deadly Creatures on Wii, Eternal Sonata on PlayStation 3, Fear 2 Project Origin on PC, Xbox 360, and PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_10]: King's Bounty, The Legend on PC, Last King of Africa on DS, Mushroom Men sounds hallucinogenic, that's for PC, Shellshock 2, Blood Trials on Trails, sorry, on PS3, PC, and Xbox 360, Star Ocean, The Second Evolution on PSP, and The House of the Dead Overkill on Wii, because you can't kill enough zombies.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: In the U.S., there's actually quite a bit coming out as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fear 2, Project Origin on both PS3, Xbox 360, and the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: X-Blades coming out on PC, PlayStation 3, and Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: Deadly Creatures coming out on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sonic's Ultimate Genesis Collection on PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360
[SPEAKER_06]: We did it all at that last Genesis Collection.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like you play so many games and you unlock the arcade version of Altered Beast.
[SPEAKER_06]: This Genesis Collection looks really awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like 40 games, some really good stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: 40 games for $30.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, and they're Genesis games, and the Genesis is the superior 16-bit system, so obviously you don't see a lot of Super Nintendo collections.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have to say, I'm sometimes not a big fan of these remakes and stuff, but this looks pretty hot.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not really a remake, it's just a collection.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a repackaging.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, sure, but I mean, a remake is, you know, when they think of 3D or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: LocoRoco 2 on PSP.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then on the Wii and the Xbox 360, we have Onichanbara Bikini Zombie Slayers Yes!
[SPEAKER_03]: And on Xbox 360, Onichanbara Bikini Samurai Squad Have you seen the cover art for that game?
[SPEAKER_03]: This game is so epic that they made a movie for it in Japan A theatrical movie I'm going to be so broke this week I'll bring you some cover art, it's fantastic Let's see here
[SPEAKER_03]: Jake Power Fireman, NASCAR Kart Racing, Retro Game Challenge, 8-Bit Games,
[SPEAKER_03]: That's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_03]: House of the Dead Overkill, which will be truly epic.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mass Effect is getting re-released as a two-disc edition.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're going to have the download content in it as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's going to be $19.99, so that's pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_03]: And let's see here.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's actually it.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's kind of interesting, though, is also this week... Isn't Street Fighter 4 this week?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, that's next week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, damn it!
[SPEAKER_03]: Ha ha!
[SPEAKER_03]: Lame.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, also, actually, technically still this week, Fire Emblem Shadow Dragon, I believe, will be coming out next... 16th?
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, well, no, never mind, that's supposed to be Tuesday, so that's next week.
[SPEAKER_03]: That game's going to be great.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then, I think Lost and Damned is this week, or Lost and Damned for Grand Theft Auto 4, so that is what I'm really looking forward to.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: PS3, Street Fighter 4, Skate 2, Mobile Suit Gundam, Gearan no Yabu, Axis no Kui 5, DS,
[SPEAKER_05]: It doesn't look like there's actually a lot of stuff coming out.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a game called Hidamari Sketch, Doko Demo Sugoroku X365.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I have no idea.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm trying to look at screen caps for this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just saying it is fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just saying it is fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: It looks like another minigame collection on the DS made up of little WarioWare-ish minigames is kind of what it looks like to me.
[SPEAKER_05]: So...
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess that could be cute.
[SPEAKER_05]: But they're all cute little Japanese schoolgirls on there.
[SPEAKER_05]: And on the Sony PSP this week, not a whole lot, but you do have Tenchu 4.
[SPEAKER_05]: Looks to be a pretty big release coming out over there this week, as well as a port of the Gundam game that's on PS2 this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Otherwise, a pretty quiet week in Japan.
[SPEAKER_05]: Probably because of Street Fighter 4 pretty much dominating.
[SPEAKER_05]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's your release dates for Japan.
[SPEAKER_05]: So let's get back into some more gaming news.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, we have our Virtual Fighter Virtual Console UK news coming out actually should already be out as of Friday is Clayfighter which is on there for 800 Wii Points the equivalent of 6 pounds or 8 euros and another game that's on there is Sonic Chaos which was a Master System game and
[SPEAKER_10]: is 500 Wii Points.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it was actually the first Sonic game that had Tails playable.
[SPEAKER_10]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is Clayfighter on the US Virtual Console?
[SPEAKER_06]: If you can pull that down, that game is great.
[SPEAKER_05]: I stopped following Virtual Console a while ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if we ever got Secret of Mana either.
[SPEAKER_10]: Secret of Mana is supposed to be on the UK one, I thought.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jeez, I don't think we got that here yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Seriously though, Clayfighter, you can be a Clay Elvis...
[SPEAKER_06]: Fighting a clay like Norse Valkyrie chick Helga Fighting a blob Clay fighter Come on fight them if you dare Clay fighter, great
[SPEAKER_03]: There was a viral video making its rounds this week that supposedly was a leaked Dead Rising 2 trailer.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we know all about leaked trailers, that they sometimes tend to be not leaked by someone stealing it, but they're leaked on purpose.
[SPEAKER_03]: This was shot off of a screen, apparently, off a TV.
[SPEAKER_03]: and it showed what looks to be a teaser trailer basically looks like an overrun Las Vegas type area with casinos one scene they showed someone in a giant American Gladiators hamster ball thing rolling over zombies
[SPEAKER_03]: So, to be honest, I think it's actually authentic.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I think it is purposely released by Capcom because the audio in it, if you notice, is actually a direct feed from the trailer.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, it's not just like shot off a TV audio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Any idea if we're going to get some multiplayer co-op in this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because that's what Dead Rising needed.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was a great game, but man, if it had like, sort of like Left 4 Dead, multiple players in the Dead Rising kind of gameplay against millions of zombies.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, dude!
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, no idea what it is exactly, but I know at the very end of the trailer it actually flashes the number two really quick, and there's also another scene that you see Frank West in the Mega Man outfit again.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've been in a war.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can I say, though, that Capcom has a really good pulse on where we want to kill zombies?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because when I saw this trailer and saw that the next one is in Vegas or whatever, I was like, that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: No doubt.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just like when I saw the first one, it was killing zombies in a mall.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's one company that knows killing zombies, that knows slaying the undead.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's Capcom.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let me put it this way.
[SPEAKER_03]: If this is fake, it's an amazing fake.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe Capcom should do this if this is a fake.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will be willing to bet that you'll see this at E3.
[SPEAKER_03]: Easy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Start the buzz now.
[SPEAKER_03]: What better way to get people talking about it than put out a trailer that's supposedly stolen.
[SPEAKER_06]: Make a demo for E3 of E3 infested with zombies.
[SPEAKER_05]: That actually would be pretty badass.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you killing people are zombies.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or maybe the reverse.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're a zombie and you're killing people.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, the buzz is also starting on this game.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Saw.
[SPEAKER_05]: The game.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, this is weird because I heard before that Saw was supposed to be coming out.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was in development.
[SPEAKER_05]: It got canceled.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, apparently now Konami has picked up the rights to do Saw.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess Brash Entertainment had started this game and stopped it Now Konami has actually picked up the rights since that other company closed down Variety was the one to actually report this The game is now going to be developed by Zombie Studios And it's supposed to come out right when the sixth Saw movie comes out this Halloween And I'm like, they really are on Saw VI?
[SPEAKER_03]: It doesn't seem like something you can adapt into a game at all I mean, it just doesn't work for me I don't see how you're going to be able to do it
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: To the dismay of fans of it in the room, I can foresee this.
[SPEAKER_06]: If Konami makes Saw and it's a hit, it will kill Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the sad thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I'm thinking in my head, I'm like, well, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: But wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_05]: Konami's done Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_05]: Granted, these are two completely different developers.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've never really heard of this Zombie Studios before.
[SPEAKER_05]: They haven't done anything to do with Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I'm like, well, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Silent Hill is actually a pretty rad game.
[SPEAKER_05]: So if they made Saw, kind of like a game like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I'm like, I just don't see Saw...
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think it's going to work.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it's just... Silent Hill's been on skids since 2 or 3, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's sad.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think Homecoming did well.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're doing everything they can to stem the tide.
[SPEAKER_06]: They tried to action up Homecoming.
[SPEAKER_06]: They tried to do the...
[SPEAKER_06]: The remake, the Origins one, and, you know, that's all Konami needs.
[SPEAKER_06]: If they come up with another horror franchise, they'll probably put Silent Hill out to pasture.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I don't know how well Homecoming did, but I'm worried that there may not be a sixth one.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, I hope you're wrong, but sadly, you might be right.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, don't buy the Saw game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Weemageddon.
[SPEAKER_03]: But honestly, though, I mean, I don't see how they're going to be able to do it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just, it's not...
[SPEAKER_03]: It's Saw isn't a franchise that's really action-packed or anything, and I mean, it's... Hey, there's Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's, it's, well, Silent Hill's easy... They'll just do the same thing, except for you'll be dodging, like, traps made by the Saw guy, and, you know, every once in a while you get yourself into some sort of weird ethical dilemma where you have to kill somebody.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, actually, it sounds like they might be able to make a pretty cool game.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll buy it.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll check it out at E3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just to kill Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jamie, you expressed a lot of displeasure at the news of a Saw game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Are you excited about it?
[SPEAKER_10]: I will stab you in the face if you buy the Saw game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Saw in real life.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, because first of all, the concept of Saw is, well, retarded.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry!
[SPEAKER_10]: And not very interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: And how can you... I guess, you know, if Nightmare on Elm Street did... You know, this is, I guess, our Nightmare on Elm Street for the modern age, except, you know, Freddy Krueger was funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the fact that they're now rebooting Friday the 13th, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: There's that new movie coming out.
[SPEAKER_09]: But Jared Padalecki's in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it does look cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Nightmare on Elm Street, they're also doing without Robert Englund.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which will not work.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can't have him without Robert Englund.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's not doing anything.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, seriously.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's slowly dying.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's why they can't put him in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's old.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's dying of old.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway, my point is that Saw is a gimmick.
[SPEAKER_10]: Silent Hill, basically, a lot of thought went into the psychology of the game and it created its own sort of mythology around what made that universe work.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, in other words, Pyramid Head is not a gimmick.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's a fucking rock star.
[SPEAKER_05]: They should stop putting him in every single game.
[SPEAKER_10]: But my point is that, I mean, sure, if you want mindless bullshit in a game, get Saw.
[SPEAKER_10]: Go for it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Buy mindless bullshit.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you want a game that's going to make you think a little bit and actually use your brain.
[SPEAKER_05]: And possibly pee your pants.
[SPEAKER_10]: And possibly pee your pants, yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Go for Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_10]: Besides that Silent Hill 2, Chainsaw.
[SPEAKER_10]: Perfect.
[SPEAKER_06]: Silent Hill is superior.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, let's move on with some other gaming news.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're like an hour 15 into this show.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're not even close to the end of it.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is why Dan comes once every five years.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you didn't want to hear from me, you wouldn't have invited me.
[SPEAKER_04]: We like Dan.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's funny.
[SPEAKER_10]: I invited my sweetie here and cuddled with him and said, come be on the show.
[SPEAKER_10]: He goes, okay, and then lost his phone.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, so the... We gotta go to Jamie for our next story.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't realize she hadn't done the other story yet.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway, anyway, anyway.
[SPEAKER_10]: We were speaking earlier about series getting a reboot, so guess what's next in line?
[SPEAKER_10]: Splatterhouse!
[SPEAKER_10]: Which totally makes sense with Friday the 13th getting its reboot, because then you've got Dude in a Hockey Mask!
[SPEAKER_10]: and freaking Splatterhouse is awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: I love the picture on the little article because I was the guy with the chainsaw hands.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway, and as we all know, the game is actually out on virtual console right now, but they're talking later this year, Namco Bondi is planning quarter three for doing a new Splatterhouse game, and there actually is an official site up.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you go to splatterhousegame.com, you can see some of the images from the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is the first game that lets you use your own severed limbs as a weapon.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, your arms and stuff and your skin will get ripped off as you're playing the game or as you're getting damage done to you, and your limbs will grow back, and you can actually beat people with your limbs.
[SPEAKER_05]: This won't be rated M or anything.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a lot of controversy about this, because apparently Namco just whacked the dev team for this game, which was a California-based developer, and...
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know if they handed it to another team or if the game's going to be put back or in limbo.
[SPEAKER_06]: I heard the Afro Samurai people might be taking it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or the arm of the developer got cut off and given to the other team to use in developing the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: This news, though, is coming right out of New York Comic Con, which was going on this weekend.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it's interesting that we hear the dev team gets sacked, yet they're showing it at New York Comic Con going on this weekend, which is crazy.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it's interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, that's the corporate world.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fast-paced, ever-changing world of video game development.
[SPEAKER_05]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: But that's okay, because in Splatterhouse, they'll grow the limbs back.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's all right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, a couple more stories, then we'll get to the classic game of the week in a break.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, there is a brand-new update that they did to fix the HDMI audio issues that they were having with the HDMI audio cable for the 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: However, as with most updates, it seems there are some problems.
[SPEAKER_03]: And apparently a lot of people are reporting that after this update was downloaded to their Xbox 360 system, that they received the brand new present of an E74 error message, which is one of the one red light problem.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's funny because that also happens to be not covered by their warranty.
[SPEAKER_03]: D'oh!
[SPEAKER_03]: Sad Trombone.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so, yeah, a lot of people are pissed off at that.
[SPEAKER_06]: You mean Microsoft developed a game console with a problem?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've taken back six Xboxes in the last week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Was it all because of this update?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, those things just break.
[SPEAKER_06]: They don't have to update them to break.
[SPEAKER_06]: Microsoft, don't even worry about updating them.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're just going to break.
[SPEAKER_05]: You look at them funny and they'll break.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like the Xbox has feelings.
[SPEAKER_06]: You looked at me funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: You used me to do all your gaming and bought stuff for me.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just want to cuddle.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love when they ask you on the phone, was it plugged into a surge protector?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh yes, it was the surge protector's fault that my console broke.
[SPEAKER_06]: I made the mistake of hooking it up to my TV.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's why we have to give out a stupid award.
[SPEAKER_05]: This week's Stupid Award goes to Daniel Alvarez.
[SPEAKER_05]: He lives in Austin, Texas.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why does he get the Stupid Award?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because he got arrested on charges of assault.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because what he did, he assaulted his girlfriend with a Wii controller.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, and possibly the even more hideous crime, as reported, he's also suspected of eating her cookies.
[SPEAKER_06]: He seriously jumped up behind her with the nunchuck strap and like super spied her with it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like it's like a rat line.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really?
[SPEAKER_05]: Christina Alvarado, who is the girlfriend what happened is that she actually told the police that she was attacked by her boyfriend and the thing was she was pissed off at him because he ate her Girl Scout cookies
[SPEAKER_05]: And he was pissed off because he got woke up to get yelled at about the Girl Scout cookies.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I guess to teach her a lesson, he choked her with a weed cork.
[SPEAKER_10]: Don't you dare.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ever.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because I wake him up all the time for eating my stuff out of the fridge.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was going to kill you.
[SPEAKER_06]: It would not be with a weed cork.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, the unofficial city motto of Austin is keep Austin weird.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's freaking weird right there.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, I might go ahead and lean on that one to be true.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, that's wild.
[SPEAKER_05]: And FYI, it does not appear to be made up.
[SPEAKER_05]: They've linked to a source here that apparently says, yes, an Austin man has been
[SPEAKER_05]: been accused of trying to choke his girlfriend with a cord of a Wii video game controller after she became angry that he had eaten all of her Girl Scout cookies.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what the gag is, though?
[SPEAKER_06]: For the people who don't know about the way that the nunchuck works, is that all Wii controllers are cordless.
[SPEAKER_07]: I bet that damage that any cords would not be covered under the warranty.
[SPEAKER_07]: I wonder if that's what the defense attorney will try to say.
[SPEAKER_10]: All you have to do is yank hard and unplug it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Caramel sucks a lot.
[SPEAKER_06]: I need to know one thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Was he wearing the wrist strap?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, no, even better.
[SPEAKER_06]: Even better.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did it have the condom on?
[SPEAKER_07]: That's exactly... See, the match think alike here.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was going to say the exact same thing before Loki took the mic away.
[SPEAKER_07]: So... Yes, we need to know if it had the Wii condom on and the safety strap.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because if it didn't have the safety strap on, Nintendo would have... They're not... It would have been even funnier if somehow during this whole struggle of him strangling her, that somehow the remote flew into the TV.
[SPEAKER_06]: You guys are sick, sick people.
[SPEAKER_06]: and it pains me to be associated.
[SPEAKER_05]: They fought over fucking cookies.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you think that was serious?
[SPEAKER_06]: At least there were no tacos thrown.
[SPEAKER_06]: People have been trying to kill each other with game controllers for years.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know if you know this.
[SPEAKER_06]: It dates back to the 2600s.
[SPEAKER_05]: Back when we had the NES Advantage, I could see someone getting killed with an NES Advantage.
[SPEAKER_10]: He's got a scar on his back in the shape of a Clicca vision controller.
[SPEAKER_06]: Then there was this one time that I woke up and Jamie was just...
[SPEAKER_06]: stuff and a power pad down onto my face.
[SPEAKER_06]: She's been trying to kill me with the game control.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now she knows.
[SPEAKER_06]: Use a Wii remote.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm dead.
[SPEAKER_05]: You fuckers have killed me.
[SPEAKER_05]: SSJ100 Matt in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_05]: SSJ100 Matt in our chat room has a great idea for a new video game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Cookie Guy versus Taco Kid.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dark Knight asks, does Miyamoto have to choke a bitch?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, boy.
[SPEAKER_10]: So.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, we need to get to the classic game of the week and take a break and try to find our souls.
[SPEAKER_05]: So every week here on Orange Lounge Radio, DarkSakura likes to dig through the archive of great gaming and find a video game she believes all of you should be playing.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's our classic video game of the week.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, what should the kids be playing this week?
[SPEAKER_05]: Gorf!
[SPEAKER_05]: Bless you.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I didn't throw up yet.
[SPEAKER_10]: G.O.R.F.
[SPEAKER_10]: stands for Galactic Orbiting Robot Force.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it's a very bizarre little game because it's like a version of three games in one.
[SPEAKER_10]: Basically, your first level, you've got different missions.
[SPEAKER_10]: So going through different missions will set up your rank.
[SPEAKER_10]: And...
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess what you're hearing is just a bunch of shooting.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's basically Space Invaders.
[SPEAKER_05]: The first stage of GORF is Space Invaders.
[SPEAKER_10]: The first level is Space Invaders with a big circular shield that you kind of have to shoot through.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, the second...
[SPEAKER_10]: The second level is, well, like my husband was saying behind the scenes, is like Galaga, where you have to shoot the little planes that shoot down.
[SPEAKER_10]: It had the crappiest collision detection ever.
[SPEAKER_10]: It wouldn't even shoot you and you'd explode.
[SPEAKER_10]: Stupid game.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then the last...
[SPEAKER_10]: The last level was another... Well, at least in the arcade version you had the Galaxian-type level, and you had a Space Warp-type level after that, which was the Gyrus-like level, where it's...
[SPEAKER_10]: Sort of weird perspective as if you're going into the war.
[SPEAKER_10]: Kind of tempesty, as far as the perspective.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then the last one is the flagship one, where actually you're going and shooting the alien ship, and it has a shield around it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like a semi-circular shield, so you have to shoot through it.
[SPEAKER_10]: And the game was actually supposed to be a tie-in with Star Trek The Motion Picture, but it didn't fit in with the script, so they said, uh, no.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, they put all these great 80s space games in a blender, and out comes gore.
[SPEAKER_10]: Pretty much.
[SPEAKER_10]: On top of that, it was actually saying here that it used the Votrax speech synthesis chip in the arcade version.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it had the robot voice in it, too.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: I only played this in the arcade a couple times.
[SPEAKER_10]: I had this on the ColecoVision, which to me is just the best version of GORF ever.
[SPEAKER_10]: I love the little music it plays.
[SPEAKER_10]: Um, but, um, the, uh, it's also saying that the, uh, the GORF, um, hardware actually, uh, was compatible and, uh, you can switch it out for other games like, uh, Wizard of War.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm gonna do something here with the music.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm gonna switch to the Commodore 64 version just because I love Commodore 64 and I see that there's one here on, uh, this.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the GORF was out on, like, a million different systems, it seems.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, it was out on quite a few.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think I played this on Commodore 64.
[SPEAKER_05]: This looks familiar to me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, I remember the circular shield and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_10]: But, um... Basically, though, as you go through the levels and get to the end of it, and I've gotten to the end of it on the Clique of Vision, you get Space Cadet, Space Captain, Space Colonel, Space General, Space Warrior, and Space Avenger!
[SPEAKER_10]: Um... There was a sequel planned, called MISBORF.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Does Ms.
[SPEAKER_05]: Gorf have a bow in her hair?
[SPEAKER_05]: Is that what differentiates her from Gorf?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was actually, I think it's cool, it was programmed in fourth language.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is that like fourth meal at Taco Bell?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, the programmer of Gorf owns the source code, and it apparently only exists in a set of 8-inch floppy disks.
[SPEAKER_10]: There were versions on the Atari 2600, Atari 5200, Clicca Vision, the Atari 8-bit, BBC Micro, Commodore 64, VIC-20 in 1982.
[SPEAKER_10]: The Galaxian mission was removed from all home ports.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was given an Atari Jaguar port just by some guy.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, did it as a hobby.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it was taken off of the market because he didn't go for any of the copyrights.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, bastard.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm bored.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think I want to remake GORF.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: Also, the current world record for GORF, recognized by Twin Galaxies.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, I watch King of Kong.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just realized a giant fart was enough to make the high scoreboard on GORF Here, let me make the scoreboard right now As Rob puts the microphone towards his crotch Anyway He also made the Guinness Book of World Records by a guy named Todd Rogers on November 24th, 1982 at Haunted Trails in Burbank, Illinois He is?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, apparently he's in the King of Kong And my husband says he looks like Ron Jeremy
[SPEAKER_05]: The Rob D's in chat going, I hate Todd Rogers.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know it's Todd Rogers.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hate him.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm paraphrasing.
653,990.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want someone to break it.
[SPEAKER_05]: That would involve playing GORF.
[SPEAKER_10]: GORF is fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: I am putting out a personal challenge to someone to break Todd Rogers' score on GORF. 653,990.
[SPEAKER_10]: it would actually be pretty awesome if you could break it with a score of 666,000 if someone whoever manages to break that will get a no prize from me will be interviewed on Orange Downs Radio and will win a shiny penny you also get in the Guinness Book of World Records though
[SPEAKER_05]: It might.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, look.
[SPEAKER_05]: Enough GORF.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wrong.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, good choice.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's definitely a game I think a lot of people have not heard of or forgot about, so bringing GORF back to the spotlight.
[SPEAKER_05]: And hopefully that old record can be shattered.
[SPEAKER_10]: How about a little anecdote regarding me picking that game?
[SPEAKER_05]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was actually trying to think of a good epic RPG, and I was like, I'll fuck it, GORF.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whatever works for you.
[SPEAKER_09]: It just stuck in my head.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, anyhow, we're going to take a break while Dan and Jamie get into an argument.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to take a break.
[SPEAKER_06]: Everything she knows about classic video games she stole from me.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then she flipped me off.
[SPEAKER_06]: Right on the air.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to take a break, you guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll be back with plenty more Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have more to come in Part B tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to talk about Indiana Jones and a great Indiana Jones game that might be making a comeback.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to finally talk about iPhone gaming, which I promised Dan we could do earlier, and a new project from Rockstar Games, which I'm sure has Loki pretty excited.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll be talking about all of that in Part B right after this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Stay tuned, guys, with more of Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: And welcome back everybody to Orange Lounge Radio on this lovely Sunday evening, February the 8th of 2009 Where we are doing the 312th episode of our show, Orange Lounge Radio We always tape live Sunday nights at allgames.com Of course, if you were listening live tonight, there was a little bit of mad stuff going on during the break We've kind of been joking throughout the evening, there's a lot of wind and rain type stuff going on outside It seemed to have knocked our network out for a little bit, because we dropped during the break Our podcast listeners won't notice a thing, because they just get that little break in between there So, um...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_10]: and I know not everyone has different things so I'll pick different consoles and arcade or whatnot but I will be putting something up very soon for a high score classic game contest
[SPEAKER_05]: And talk to our web guy about that because with the new website and everything, there's now a thing where you can upload pictures directly to our website by sending this particular email address so people can send their scores.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe we can do a little widget or something with the scores.
[SPEAKER_05]: We could probably put something together pretty easy.
[SPEAKER_05]: It would be fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm still working on it.
[SPEAKER_10]: But, you know, I used to do the game knowledge quiz back when I had Pump Up the Volume.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I'd kind of like to do something like that again.
[SPEAKER_10]: That would be fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Indiana Jones, Staff of Kings
[SPEAKER_03]: Adventure Game, Indiana Jones, and the Fate of Atlantis.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, you didn't hear that music on the feed.
[SPEAKER_05]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: So yeah, Indiana Jones and the Fate of Atlantis on the Wii version.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pretty good if you don't have, you know, a Scum emulator on there.
[SPEAKER_03]: or ScumVM.
[SPEAKER_05]: And this is like one of the all-time classic, you know, click-and-point games, so it's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are they not doing that 360 and PS3 one that they announced?
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe not right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: It might be later on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Weak.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, this is also on the Wii, so maybe just, you know, multi-platform.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it's on the Wii and everything, but yeah, Wii, PlayStation 2 and PSP because, you know, they can port that crap easy, so...
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, there may be another one coming out for the PS3 and 360 they're still working on
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I don't know if you would file this under WeMageddon or what you'd do, but apparently EA, they made a lot of announcements this week because they had a financial call going on this week, and apparently they are going to be porting Dead Space to the Wii.
[SPEAKER_05]: Says a quote from the call, the CEO, John Riccatello, says, Unfortunately, what you don't know is that it's going to be Dead Space Party.
[SPEAKER_03]: and it's actually going to be a party spinoff because they couldn't really do an actual legit hardcore game for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I don't know, but the interesting thing about this is that they actually say also this from a magazine interview.
[SPEAKER_05]: Quote, go look at Dead Space and imagine playing that game with a wand and nunchuck.
[SPEAKER_05]: If they improve the precision, then you could have a good experience.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hmm, is it a hint that Motion Plus could be supported by this?
[SPEAKER_05]: And imagine that the graphics look slightly worse.
[SPEAKER_06]: Slightly worse.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like this.
[SPEAKER_06]: If EA pulls this off, and they're a company on the upswing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, I know that profits are down and they're laying people off.
[SPEAKER_06]: But creatively, while that's a great word, you've got to give EA credit.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're head and shoulders above where they were last year this time.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're coming off of Dead Space, which was amazing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mirror's Edge, which was a heck of a game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just a bunch of great titles coming out of EA.
[SPEAKER_06]: If they pull this off, props.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, because...
[SPEAKER_06]: We need super cool games, but man, I don't know how you're going to do it without the graphic power.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because Dead Space is a game where the visuals are just so important.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, granted, if Dead Space really is about the graphics, then whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: But should games really be about the graphics?
[SPEAKER_05]: Not necessarily, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, maybe, maybe not.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I mean, play Dead Space.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have you played Dead Space?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, because it's first person.
[SPEAKER_05]: That game will fuck you up for life.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll check it out, but I just know not yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's atrocious.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I think so much of the atmosphere in that game is it's just super, super good visuals.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I will say, one of the other games you mentioned, I'm not usually much of a first-person gamer, but Mirror's Edge is pretty hot.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that game's pretty hot.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's one of those things where it's like, if they tried to do that on Wii...
[SPEAKER_06]: and they could do it right and have motion controls and stuff hey you know great more power to you the Wii needs these games you know even even if it's not about graphics which it's not about graphics if they can bring uh this game in a meaningful way to the other system uh to the Wii it would it would validate the Wii's existence because there are too many mini game collections and don't get me wrong I know for the Wii's uh mainstream target audience that's I guess what sells but uh
[SPEAKER_05]: Again, if you're just joining us live tonight here on All Games Radio, Orange Lounge Radio, live on All Games, I just want to point out, that's Dan, Jamie's husband, often talked about on the show, but rarely heard from, but he's here tonight and telling it like it is from his experience working in game stores for many years.
[SPEAKER_10]: In other gaming news, especially in iPhone gaming news, which, you know, as a person who has an iPhone and actually plays the games on it, I still don't know what I think about having this one on there because it just seems like it would be cheaply easy.
[SPEAKER_10]: But Time Crisis is supposed to be coming on to the Apple App Store, actually already on there, where you can play with the finger of death.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: Very interesting, though, at this rise of console gaming franchise classics coming on the iPhone.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I don't know if it's just because it's kind of like all Namco and Konami, but just within 2009, we've had news of Katamari, Time Crisis, Silent Hill, Metal Gear, DDR.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, there's a Silent Hill iPhone game now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, you weren't here last week.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have it if you want to check it out before you buy it and spend $7 on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: But there's a Silent Hill iPhone game now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not Fog Adventure Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like a Dungeon Explorer type thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: So just try before you buy.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's all I'm saying.
[SPEAKER_05]: But yeah, there's a Silent Hill game on iPhone now.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's crazy.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just interesting, this whole barrage of stuff we're getting.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think the Metal Gear Solid game is out yet, but we know it's coming.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is in the works at least.
[SPEAKER_05]: Metal Gear.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just interesting, I suppose.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you know, I was going to say another game we didn't talk about because it wasn't our show role, but Rolando.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know if you remember that game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who made Rolando?
[SPEAKER_05]: That I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: No idea.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just know Aurora Faint is a hell of a puzzle game that I'm enjoying on iPhone.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is LocoRoco.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's crazy.
[SPEAKER_03]: But one thing that you won't find anymore on the iPhone App Store is the iPhone Duck Hunt game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, the Nintendo lawyers have finally swooped in like a duck and plucked the game off the...
[SPEAKER_10]: Anything about the Game & Watch?
[SPEAKER_06]: And then the dog rose out of the bushes and laughed at him.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know the Nintendo lawyer, after he laid the smackdown on that stupid little company, did the Nintendo dog laugh.
[SPEAKER_10]: What about the Game & Watch games that were on there?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know, those may still be on there.
[SPEAKER_10]: I downloaded a couple of them.
[SPEAKER_05]: I downloaded the one that was free, but I didn't download any of the others.
[SPEAKER_06]: Reggie's going to show up at your house and personally delete them off your iPhone.
[SPEAKER_10]: He's going to Falcon Punch us with his cock.
[SPEAKER_05]: I did want to give a quick shout out real quickly because we were talking about iPhone games and Namco and all their franchises not on the iPhone but on the Playstation 3 I believe a Namco collection is being released or has just recently been released and I hear it's pretty cool and you want to check it out, the Namco Museum on PS3 I think that's only in the Japanese store remember because they were tying those in also where you can get like t-shirts and shit for home I think it's going to be on it's way here pretty soon and I hear you want to check it out
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't come out for the 360 like last Christmas.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, they had the Namco, it was a Namco arcade something for the 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: They had like a bunch of the Xbox Live Arcade games and then they had some other classic games and remade stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that was supposed to be pretty good and I think it's probably pretty cheap now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it had some live, it was like 30 bucks and it had like 30 games or so.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I mean, it had, it was this really weird thing because it had games you could play off the disc, then it had games you had to import on your hard drive and play as like live arcade games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um...
[SPEAKER_06]: Pac-Man Championship Edition
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, well, we're going to get to the mailbag in just a minute.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mailbag at OrangeLaunchRadio.com with your emails.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I have one more story about iPhone gaming, and this ties in kind of exactly what you were saying a little bit ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: And this is iPhone is growing and growing and starting to become mobile gaming.
[SPEAKER_05]: In fact, right now,
[SPEAKER_05]: They are saying that iPhones are accounting for 14% of mobile game downloaders, and that was in the month of November.
[SPEAKER_05]: 32.4%, that's like a third of all iPhone users, say that they have downloaded a game.
[SPEAKER_05]: In the month of November, they downloaded some type of game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just to put that in perspective, across most mobile phone companies, you're looking at 3.8%.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you're talking like 10 times as many people on the iPhone check out games.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know, is that because the iPhone games... Go back a year on this show, just go back one year on this show before iPhone apps started coming out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mobile phone gaming was kind of the butt of many jokes on this show.
[SPEAKER_10]: In other countries, mobile gaming has been just fantastic.
[SPEAKER_10]: But we haven't had a phone until the iPhone or the Trio or the ones like that came out that was capable of handling an actual game with solid gameplay.
[SPEAKER_05]: And let me say this too.
[SPEAKER_05]: The chatters, chat.orangelawnradio.com, we always look at that here on Sunday nights.
[SPEAKER_05]: Catacos in chat room says, well, let's get serious.
[SPEAKER_05]: What other phone can play games on them that are that good?
[SPEAKER_05]: Might I mention the N-Gage?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, seriously, the iPhone.
[SPEAKER_06]: The iPhone, you know, it amounts to what, like 3%, 30%, whatever, of games downloaded.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it amounts to 100% of the decent phone games to download.
[SPEAKER_10]: I will say this, that I did have a couple of cool games on my old phone.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was intensely hard to play, but I did have Super Pac-Man.
[SPEAKER_05]: Once in a while, even as hard of a time as we gave them in the past, the Luminous one that they had on phones was pretty freaking good for a phone game.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the Doom RPG and stuff, they had some pretty intricate stuff even on the old-ass phones.
[SPEAKER_10]: I did play Bejeweled on my old phone.
[SPEAKER_05]: So...
[SPEAKER_05]: But most of it was a joke because it was cashing in on the Spongebob and all that crap.
[SPEAKER_05]: They were just crappy little games.
[SPEAKER_10]: Speakeru says, I have an N-Gage and does NES and Mega Drive emulation pretty well.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's the only thing it's good for.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess that would be a reason to have it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tony Hawk on N-Gage was not that bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, let's get to the mailbag here, guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mailbag at OrangeLawnTrader.com if you have questions for us.
[SPEAKER_05]: Every week you guys send in your emails and we like to open up the mailbag and read through them.
[SPEAKER_05]: And DarkSakura's going to do it right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do we actually get some emails this week?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, we did.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: We had a poor showing last week, so I'm glad people listened.
[SPEAKER_10]: Rob with two Bs says there's new box art on NeoGAF.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's NeoGAF?
[SPEAKER_10]: G-A-F?
[SPEAKER_05]: Neo games are fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, these huge forums that tons and tons of people look at.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, I just haven't been there before.
[SPEAKER_05]: Probably because there's like a million different gaming forums on the internet.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Supposedly, he says, supposedly the Williams Pinball Hall of Fame is being ported to PS3, Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes it is.
[SPEAKER_10]: He says, I actually bought this for PSP Wii and PS2.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm curious to see the graphics.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm curious to see if they add some more tables.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Wii, you know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh god, Funhaus is on the freaking cover.
[SPEAKER_10]: I hate that game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Call Wii Mageddon as much as you want, but that Wii game was pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: The pinballs.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dan's giving his thumbs up approval.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, that was a pretty awesome collection of games, I gotta say.
[SPEAKER_06]: You like pinball, you have a 360, download Pinball FX.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: But Pinball Hall of Fame is great.
[SPEAKER_06]: If they go crazy, add some new tables with the 360 PS3 versions.
[SPEAKER_06]: That'll be awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's actually a really good pinball collection, really good physics.
[SPEAKER_06]: And honestly enough, my vote's for the Wii version because of the non-checked remote controls.
[SPEAKER_10]: Our next one comes from Geekboy2424.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi guys, I have come to a conclusion.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have ADHD.
[SPEAKER_10]: along with a little bit of OCD my question for the week is how do you guys stop yourselves because the only thing that works for me is playing games when is okay I guess when I sit at my desk I can't concentrate because I can't sit freaking still help Dr. Orange Lounge sincerely Geekboy2424
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: but if like you're for real real like you have to play video games to get around your ADD that you think you have you might want to see a doctor I'm just saying we can't diagnose that and that's a huge liability if we even tried to now that Rob has said something responsible I say self-medicate play games all the time just it's not going to kill you or anything just just play them when you're at your desk whoop out your game boy um you know if it calms you down and it makes you feel good it's not like you're doing drugs or something hook it up man
[SPEAKER_05]: Just remember to go to the bathroom once in a while.
[SPEAKER_10]: When I was a young hyperactive child, they used to make me drink coffee to calm down.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because caffeine, when you're already wired up and hyper, actually can be a sedative.
[SPEAKER_10]: What?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm not giving medical advice.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm just saying what I used to do.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just saying coffee's delicious.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's not medical advice, by the way.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's just what I used to do.
[SPEAKER_05]: Liability, liability, liability.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I understand.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway, um... But you know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: ADD is in your head.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_10]: Next email.
[SPEAKER_10]: Um...
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi OLR, I'm sending this message from my iPod Touch with a cracked screen because my smart self dropped it on the ground while going from a friend's house to mine.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway, I came to say hi because I've been listening to the podcast lately and laughed about the kid that threw a taco at his mom.
[SPEAKER_10]: By P.S.
[SPEAKER_10]: He didn't put any spaces or anything.
[SPEAKER_10]: This message came from your friendly neighborhood MySpace friend, Aroka7.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sent from my iPod.
[SPEAKER_10]: The end.
[SPEAKER_05]: the team at Konami of Hawaii and he was the audio director of the Xbox series and part of the reason why I'm stopping the whole show to mention this and
[SPEAKER_05]: Just kind of take a minute to kind of soak this all in is that I don't know if you guys remember back when we would do the podcast and the show itself, the radio show itself as separate shows.
[SPEAKER_05]: But one year we had a big, big score that we had the Universe soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_05]: We premiered those songs here on Orange Lounge Radio and I think it was like Ultramix 4 at the time before anybody else got to hear them.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was Stillwind who coordinated all that with us here over email and was a big part, I know, of the fan community as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: so I'm just kind of it does not I'm just kind of shocked and saddened to hear it and I'm sorry to depress everybody with this news but I'm just finding it out myself and this is sometimes the problems that you have when you do a live radio show is that you get live news I don't know, you know, Babani Style is a pretty respectable site, I don't see why they would lie about something like this and just, no, that would be in very poor taste, so I'm pretty sure this is legit and very sad and
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know what else to say.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm very sorry to hear this for his family and everybody and for the community that have really lost something with this.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's really sad news.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm very sorry to derail the mailbag with that sad news.
[SPEAKER_05]: He died from a ruptured aorta.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, that is very sad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, but he did a lot for the show a couple years ago and did keep in touch a little while here and there, so I just wanted to pass that news along.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Please tell me the next email has a dick and fart joke or something to bring the humor back to the show because I really just killed it right there.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, well, hi folks.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just thought I'd throw in my proverbial two cents regarding the subject of rampant fanboyism that is often seen quite a lot on the net.
[SPEAKER_10]: Personally, I think that no matter what systems one promotes or trashes, fanboyism in any form just makes us gamers look like the mouth-breathing cheetos dust encrusted in bread Neanderthals that non-gamers perceive us, and quite frankly, this kind of thing really needs to stop.
[SPEAKER_10]: Big, long sentence, wow.
[SPEAKER_10]: Speaking as someone who has both the 360 and PS3, and a whole shit ton of other systems from previous generations, I can honestly say the following.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's no such thing as a perfect system.
[SPEAKER_10]: Either there's a flaw in the hardware itself, or there's a feature service or some other aspect that another system does better.
[SPEAKER_10]: Additionally, just because a given game isn't on one system of choice, that doesn't mean it's a crap game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Conversely, just because a game is exclusive to one's favorite system, that doesn't make the game the greatest thing since the invention of breast implants.
[SPEAKER_10]: Simply put, each system has strengths as well as weaknesses, good games as well as total turds.
[SPEAKER_10]: It helps to have multiple consoles so one has that much more options for gaming.
[SPEAKER_10]: Amen to that!
[SPEAKER_10]: Because you know what we always said on this show, a system is only as good as the games that are on it.
[SPEAKER_10]: That sums it up right there.
[SPEAKER_10]: And that's from Spazinator.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dreamcast, yo.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dude, Dreamcast is turning 10 this year.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can you believe it?
[SPEAKER_05]: I was just thinking about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's crazy.
[SPEAKER_10]: I remember standing in line on September 9th, 99.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's interesting, though, that we do have three very distinct consoles that are out there right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: And all of them have decent games on them.
[SPEAKER_05]: And all of them have some pretty crap games on them.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have two consoles and you have the Wii.
[SPEAKER_05]: But even the Wii, you know, the Wii's got, for a particular audience, it has games people want.
[SPEAKER_05]: Soccer moms and families, it's got a ton of stuff that people want.
[SPEAKER_06]: But the console war right now, and while it's not a war for first place because Nintendo's got that, the console war, the culture clash in gamers right now is PlayStation 3 versus Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just like last generation, GameCube was there, but it was really Xbox versus PS2.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, I've been hitting the gaming forums for a long time.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't just work in a game store, but I work in a game store because I'm a gamer.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, you know, the fanboyism is always going to be there.
[SPEAKER_06]: I own every system.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I mean every system.
[SPEAKER_05]: They really do.
[SPEAKER_10]: In our defense, we do not own a Jaguar.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would if I found one.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, hey dude, Tempest 2000 is sweet, and Aliens vs. Predator is good, Cybermorph is not too bad, but back on the subject of fanboyism, I always have my favorites.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, when it came down to Genesis vs. Super Nintendo, I would argue Genesis for hours.
[SPEAKER_06]: And my wife says Super Nintendo, they're both great, don't get me wrong, Genesis.
[SPEAKER_06]: But,
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: They win because we refuse to acknowledge our competition, therefore we are the victors.
[SPEAKER_05]: We win because our system is made by Sony.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's also not making that up.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're also eating too much periwinkle.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's paraphrasing, but he's not making that up, what he's saying.
[SPEAKER_10]: And they're also eating too much burnt sienna.
[SPEAKER_03]: We are the number one Sony system on the planet.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: The company is going to try to brainwash you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sadly, no.
[SPEAKER_06]: The PlayStation 2 is.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the PSP.
[SPEAKER_06]: But pick
[SPEAKER_06]: Pick the system that you like and fight for it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Get on the forums and tell everyone who likes the other system that they are ass close.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to see more rap and fanboyism.
[SPEAKER_06]: Be into what you're doing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Jamie's dying to read the last email, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dear lord.
[SPEAKER_10]: Last email.
[SPEAKER_04]: You brought him.
[SPEAKER_03]: You brought him.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm loving it, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dan, I love Dan.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll tell you one thing that Sony does win in, and this is absolutely, you can't really, I think, argue this.
[SPEAKER_03]: If the systems were used for blunt force trauma, they definitely would win because that system is heavy and quite solid.
[SPEAKER_03]: 360, it is pretty heavy, not quite as solid in the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, that's not very bad or not very good.
[SPEAKER_06]: You come after me with a PS3.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll come after you with a 360 power supply.
[SPEAKER_06]: And we'll see who gets who.
[SPEAKER_10]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: Fanboyism.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, last email.
[SPEAKER_10]: At least Dan's rambling has mean I've gotten to eat more bread and get more crumbs in my cleavage.
[SPEAKER_10]: Excuse me.
[SPEAKER_10]: No?
[SPEAKER_10]: Are you done?
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, last email.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, OLR, love the show.
[SPEAKER_10]: I never miss an episode on the podcast feed.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's tough for me to catch the live show because I live on the East Coast and have young twins.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm early to work on Monday morning, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Basically, what I'm saying is that I have a tough time staying up as late as the show runs.
[SPEAKER_10]: Also, I love the fact that you guys, in podcast form, help me through the monotonous parts of my office job.
[SPEAKER_10]: Amen.
[SPEAKER_10]: Lately, I've been sad that the feed has been so far behind.
[SPEAKER_10]: Is there any way that you could update the feed more regularly?
[SPEAKER_10]: I've been missing my OLR fix every week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, it got updated twice last week and will be updated twice this week and will be caught up.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we're slowly catching up and, you know, again, it's kind of just the side thing of having two computers running this thing off of and I just get far behind and I'm only one person.
[SPEAKER_05]: But we're almost there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Regardless, I appreciate your efforts as an independent podcast and wish you many more great episodes, Boston OLR fan.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I hear that a lot, that we help people through the work week.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I know it's kind of depressing when your three-hour show you relied on isn't there.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'm trying, guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll get caught up.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're almost there.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, great.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for the emails, guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: Send us more.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com I'm hijacking this, mother.
[SPEAKER_05]: Next week's mailbag.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you love Dan?
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you hate Dan?
[SPEAKER_05]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Red Dead Redemption Red Dead Revolver
[SPEAKER_03]: It's actually going to be using the Rage engine again, so very similar to what they did with Grand Theft Auto 4.
[SPEAKER_03]: And of course, they say that there's going to be the complete open world with strong plot lines in a massive, vibrant, rural environment.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's supposed to be coming out on PS3 and Xbox 360, no sort of time frame though.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that one out of left field or what?
[SPEAKER_05]: A little bit, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Red Dead Revolver
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, that's true.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was like four years ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, I mean, you know, Bully's still got two, three more years before we need a sequel for it.
[SPEAKER_05]: But then remember when we got Excite Truck?
[SPEAKER_06]: Excite Truck was like great.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dude, I know Excite Truck was awesome, but I'm just saying like, dude, how many years ago was Excite Bike?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't even see Excite Truck and Excite Bike as even remotely similar games.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're not.
[SPEAKER_05]: The games play completely different, but they are kind of like, you know, they do.
[SPEAKER_06]: It makes me happy that Nintendo used the prefix Excite again.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because it did excite me.
[SPEAKER_06]: For the third time.
[SPEAKER_06]: You got Excitebike, Excitebike64, which is sweet.
[SPEAKER_06]: And if that's on a virtual console, it should be.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Excite Truck, which is actually the best driving game on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: Right there with Mario.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now they need Excite Tank.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, dude, sweet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because nothing excites me more than the thought of driving a tank.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or actually Excite Truck with like a battle mode would be pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: Excite Humvee.
[SPEAKER_03]: or, hey, let's take it even better.
[SPEAKER_03]: Instead of an Excite Bike or Excite Truck sequel, just do another Excite Truck game, but like with Mario stuff, like making it like a Mario Kart off-road racing game.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, shut up.
[SPEAKER_06]: It doesn't need, we don't need, Mario's everywhere already.
[SPEAKER_05]: Excite Truck 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: It'll be very simple.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or just a new F-Zero, for God's sake.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry, yes, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_10]: Excite Jet Ski.
[SPEAKER_05]: Isn't that in Wii Sports?
[SPEAKER_05]: Isn't the new Wii Sports, what do they call it, Wii Sport Resort or whatever it's called?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Doesn't that have a jet ski thing in it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, it does.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it does.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wave Race 65.
[SPEAKER_05]: SSJ100 Matt is flash forwarding to E3 this year.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nelly, that's Matt's wife, Nelly interviewing Reggie, why the fuck aren't you making Excite Truck 2?
[SPEAKER_05]: I would totally... Sad thing is, Nelly will have no idea who the hell Reggie is, so if that were to actually happen, it could.
[SPEAKER_10]: GS68 suggested excite butt.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, you can't drive a butt.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, look.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll show you.
[SPEAKER_03]: He has some serious buck teeth.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dark skin, short hair.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just the whole, you know, like, but it's just...
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: So this is like a Capcom thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is like an official product.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sort of, but in another country.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, you know in Japan, in Marvel Super Heroes vs. Street Fighter on the Saturn, there was a character that they couldn't have anywhere else in the world because he was copyrighted, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: Norimaro, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: He was like a comedian.
[SPEAKER_06]: Man, wouldn't it be sweet if there was a hidden American character and it was Obama?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: What would be Obama's special power in this game?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, according to DJ Dark Knight in chat, a veto uppercut.
[SPEAKER_06]: He would have all Sagats move, so he'd immediately be God tier.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I mean, he would just be like, veto, veto.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just had this image of Sagat, but actually it's Dick Cheney, like in a special movie, waterboarding.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or shooting you with a gun.
[SPEAKER_07]: He was Dick Cheney.
[SPEAKER_03]: He would start off like in Which game was it where Sagat started off holding Mike Dan and then he'd throw him aside but he'd start off and be like Bush Wasn't there like a guile move that it was a rumored guile move they'd pull out a pistol or something and shoot somebody That was like an urban fucking legend Some kid at the arcade knew a kid who saw a kid pull out a gun But now with Dick Cheney Yeah, Dick Cheney But he'd only shoot his partner in the face
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, a hidden character in this, would Hillary Clinton come out of the woodwork and mix some shit up with this?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know what her special character is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sarah Palin might come out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ariel Wolf shooting right there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's the thing, the chatroom is quick to point out, there is an Obama Japan.
[SPEAKER_05]: There is an Obama Japan, according to chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I do remember seeing that on TV when he won.
[SPEAKER_05]: They were showing how excited they were in Japan and all that, so...
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, if you want to join the festivities, chat.orangelauntrader.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I apologize to the folks on Justin TV because I just clicked over there and I see like the chat is filling up there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like you have a death wishing says Excitebike64 is my favorite game on the N64.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was a good game.
[SPEAKER_05]: And sorry, guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just really hard for us to watch two chat rooms at the same time and do a show.
[SPEAKER_05]: So sometimes Justin TV gets ignored.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I apologize.
[SPEAKER_05]: But definitely join our main chat room, chat.orangelauntrader.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll read more of your comments as we can.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, let's get into some more gaming news, shall we, Jimmy?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: World of Warcraft!
[SPEAKER_05]: There's gonna be some changes.
[SPEAKER_05]: In the next World of Warcraft patch, we'll have some class changes, actually.
[SPEAKER_05]: Again?
[SPEAKER_10]: Um, there is a no more consumable ammunition for hunters, a boost of protection spec paladins.
[SPEAKER_05]: For real?
[SPEAKER_05]: Like you don't have to get arrows anymore or whatever?
[SPEAKER_05]: That makes me happy.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's strange.
[SPEAKER_10]: Major improvements to the priest class, especially in group healing, general buffs for rogues and shamans, efficiency improvements for warriors and warlocks, with penalty for warriors changing stances being much lighter, plus mana regeneration being reined in across the board.
[SPEAKER_05]: Somewhere in Arms Warrior is rejoicing.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can actually find more information on it on WoW Insider.
[SPEAKER_10]: They've got the specifics listed.
[SPEAKER_10]: But basically, they're trying to just streamline all the classes, trying to bring all the tanking classes in line.
[SPEAKER_10]: Basically, just trying to balance the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: And also make the boss fights more challenging by...
[SPEAKER_10]: decreasing the mana regeneration the content has not gone into testing yet it should be going in before the release in the next couple of months so keep your eyes out if any of our readers find out more let us know also in patch 3.1 there will be a new raid dungeon called Ulduar with an introduction of dual talent specializations thank god about fucking time that's the rumor
[SPEAKER_07]: Matt2, do you think this will be enough to get me back to WoW?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, short of me paying for your account again or whatever I have to do to get you playing back to the World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_10]: I actually kind of think that I want to start playing again just for a little bit.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Even though my last character was level 10.
[SPEAKER_07]: But as Rob pointed out at the beginning of the show, all 20 of my characters, which is really 9 of them, are all Narzul.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have you been gone for more than 3 months?
[SPEAKER_05]: Let me get you a Scroll of Resurrection because then we can get the Uber item that lets us level up really quickly.
[SPEAKER_05]: You'll get my scroll.
[SPEAKER_05]: Stay strong.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't start playing again.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's because it's not cool to say that things cause cancer because people are dying of cancer.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I started saying that things cause cancer too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, wow causes electric boogaloo.
[SPEAKER_05]: It makes sense.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow causes electric boogaloo.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's serious though.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't start playing.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know so much more about games when you don't play wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_05]: I play so many more games when I'm not playing wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: You don't even know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sad trombone.
[SPEAKER_05]: Low key.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, this is totally as far away from World of Warcraft as possible, but Battlefield 1943 is now slated to come out on Xbox Live Arcade, PC, and PlayStation Network this summer.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is going to be based on the same engine as...
[SPEAKER_03]: Bad Company, and will feature 24-player battles, and they had a few different maps, including Wake Island, Guadalcanal, and Iwo Jima, which are based off of actual world locations.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think they actually used some of the top topography maps and stuff like that for that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Neat, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, around the same time, I believe they announced...
[SPEAKER_03]: Was it Battlefield Bad Company 2 as well?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because really, if gaming needed anything besides more MMORPGs, it's more FPSs.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank God.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think, if I remember correctly, Bad Company 2 is right now for September.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, TigerClaw says it's nice for them to go back to the World War 2 roots.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Since obviously they can't really do the modern warfare stuff now because Call of Duty has owned it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I do want to go back previously because this comment is pretty funny on the past story about WoW.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ranma in chat says, WoW may not cause cancer, but it can cause breakups, cheating, and marriage counseling.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have heard that.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the family that raids together stays together.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, that's my counter argument.
[SPEAKER_10]: I am not going back to WoW.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to play Perfect World.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because I said I was going to play Perfect World.
[SPEAKER_05]: For 30 days and you'll come play WoW.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've been off of WoW for how long?
[SPEAKER_10]: Addict.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not even playing right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why am I trying to recruit people?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I know Matt2 is going to succeed in his efforts to try and get me back.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, I am.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're a follower.
[SPEAKER_05]: Going back to EA.
[SPEAKER_05]: I am, really.
[SPEAKER_05]: and their conference call they had.
[SPEAKER_05]: News about Battlefield was not the only thing to come out of it and some of the things we talked about in Part A, but also Mass Effect has been confirmed that Mass Effect 2 is going to be multiple platform.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not going to be Xbox exclusive.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's straight out of the mouth of CEO John Riccatello.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mass Effect 2 is going to be multiple platform.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, Bad Company, the other Battlefield game, will be back on consoles in the year 2010.
[SPEAKER_05]: So some point like January to March, but who knows.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really?
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought it was 2009, but I guess it's going to be delayed a lot more.
[SPEAKER_03]: Probably even more than that.
[SPEAKER_03]: What, Mass Effect?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, the other one, the Battlefield Bad Company.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought Mass Effect was a Microsoft Game Studios-owned franchise.
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't think Bioware carried it over with them.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, here's the thing, and I bet BlackWolf in chat is right.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's saying it right.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's saying exactly what I'm thinking.
[SPEAKER_05]: Multiple platform equals Xbox 360 and PC.
[SPEAKER_05]: I bet you that's exactly what it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Doesn't mean suddenly we're going to see PS3.
[SPEAKER_05]: And plus, we've also seen, you know, who knows, you might get a Mass Effect spinoff on the DS because we have seen that Microsoft is not opposed to letting their stuff go on, yeah, less effect.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dual effect.
[SPEAKER_05]: Seeing things go on the DS, Viva Pinata had a game on the DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it's possible.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, not Viva Pinata, Mecha Assault.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would be an awesome game, like a mech game, but they're just giant pinatas.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, they've done Mecha Assault on the DS, and it was not very good.
[SPEAKER_03]: But they did it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was a Microsoft franchise.
[SPEAKER_03]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: They did it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was a Microsoft franchise.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's all the same.
[SPEAKER_03]: but I was completely different game but it's kind of big like some of these Mass Effect games Borderlands, I actually watched some gameplay footage of and that thing's going to be epic and I think it's going to catch a lot of people off guard because it's almost like Oblivion and Fallout with just a lot more fast paced first person gameplay and vehicles and Mad Max Alrighty then
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: to sometime in early June.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're actually speculating June 2nd with the non-PC versions being sometime later than that.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're also saying that the games they'll be released on PC and Mac and iPhone, iPhone Touch and other mobiles.
[SPEAKER_10]: But the release date only really goes for the PC version.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh well.
[SPEAKER_03]: F.U.S.
[SPEAKER_03]: of the Week
[SPEAKER_10]: F you to my work for deciding that I need to help back up people on the phones even though I don't get a single damn call and it'll really suck because I've been having a really bad sore throat from my sinus infection so F you to the phones and talk to the people
[SPEAKER_03]: FD the person that parks next to me at my apartment complex because they're parking right on the line and they haven't moved their car in like four days.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so it makes it almost impossible for me to get out of my car.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would really do some damage to their car, but someone's already keyed it.
[SPEAKER_03]: So apparently they do this other places as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: So fuck them.
[SPEAKER_05]: I actually don't have a lot of FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_05]: I had a pretty good week, so FU to me being so happy, I suppose.
[SPEAKER_05]: FU to, I'll say this, FU to sleeping in until noon and still feeling tired.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hate that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have you ever had that where you sleep so freaking much, although that's not the case because I can go to bed until 5 last night, but I have had this happen before where you sleep so much that your eyes hurt and you're still tired.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've had that happen.
[SPEAKER_05]: That sucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: FU to that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dan, do you have any FUs of the week you want to share?
[SPEAKER_06]: FU to people who get bent about pushed release dates.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's other shit to play.
[SPEAKER_06]: Find a different game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_06]: Those dates don't even exist for you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Those are for retailers like me.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I know when they're coming out and I know when to start pushing the product.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're not even supposed to know them!
[SPEAKER_05]: F you all.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dan, we just have to work in this segment somewhere in the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: You die.
[SPEAKER_05]: You die twice.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hope you get Electric Boogaloo.
[SPEAKER_05]: FU to being alive.
[SPEAKER_05]: Matt, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you have any FUs of the week you'd like to share?
[SPEAKER_07]: I haven't thought this far ahead, but I guess FU to Weemageddon, the potential
[SPEAKER_07]: and Penny Weemageddon that may cause more console wars with each other.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the Jerry Breckenheimer movie that will follow called Weemageddon.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Whatever his name is.
[SPEAKER_07]: It'll make millions upon millions of dollars.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I do agree that there are two main primary consoles in the Wii for that one special demographic.
[SPEAKER_06]: F you to you for stealing my stolen work.
[SPEAKER_07]: F you because you thought of that first and I happened to say it.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's not even copyright.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what I said.
[SPEAKER_06]: I stole it, and then you stole it from me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, F you both.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you stole it from him.
[SPEAKER_05]: F you both.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're getting back into the news.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki doesn't even want it anymore.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll add a prefix to F you.
[SPEAKER_10]: S-T-F-U.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, snap.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do we have any more gaming news?
[SPEAKER_05]: I hope so.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was going to say, I'm going to now copyright Super Weemageddon.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Super Weemageddon.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, a game that will not be featured on the Super Wii Mageddon 64 will be...
[SPEAKER_03]: Puzzle Quest Galactrix.
[SPEAKER_03]: Really?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because they do manage to port those Puzzle Quest games to everything.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is sad.
[SPEAKER_05]: It could be on Super Wii Mageddon 64 already.
[SPEAKER_03]: It will be coming out on DS, PC, Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_03]: Apparently the PC version is coming around on February 24th.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Xbox Live Arcade date is unconfirmed, but you know me being the guessing man that I am.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would say since the... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe...
[SPEAKER_06]: Puzzle Quest is cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was really afraid you were going to say it was cancelled.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's cancelled.
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: What, no Atari 2600 port?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's cancelled for Christmas, and Christmas is cancelled as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: Puzzle Quest is awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Happy Hanukkah!
[SPEAKER_06]: Although where the Galactrix thing comes from, I don't even know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Galactrix comes from the fact that the game is different and it's set in space now.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they changed the engine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now it's the whole hexagonal thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's pretty cool, actually.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you've played the demo, it's pretty addicting, I think.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just put friggin' Puzzle Pirates on Xbox Live Arcade games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's really meant to be a portable game, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: Puzzle Pirates would be an awesome DS, like MMO.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't see playing Puzzle Quest on my 360s.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I could totally see playing that on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also out of EA, some other news, it's not related to Puzzle Quest, but one other little piece of news that's out of EA, apparently they are now going to be getting the Bourne series over there, or I guess what's going on, it's not just really the Bourne.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's happened, they've picked up the rights to publish games that are based on Robert Ludlam stories.
[SPEAKER_05]: He is the guy who made the Jason Bourne series.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently the first game in the series is going to be made by Starbreeze Studios.
[SPEAKER_05]: No word on exactly what that game is, but
[SPEAKER_03]: Matt Damon!
[SPEAKER_05]: They all do very well, yes, because of Matt Damon.
[SPEAKER_03]: What other books has he written?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I'm not really familiar with... It is a Bourne title they're working on, by the way.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll start with The Bourne and end with, like, something.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Bourne Cakery.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Bourne Cooking Mama.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, there you have it.
[SPEAKER_05]: EA has picked up the Bourne rights and who knows what else from the same author.
[SPEAKER_10]: The Bourne Oven.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like this idea of picking up rights to authors' stories, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: Could you imagine J.D.
[SPEAKER_05]: Salinger rights getting picked up?
[SPEAKER_05]: We'd have the Catcher in the Rye game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, we've had Discworld games before.
[SPEAKER_05]: Roald Dahl gets picked up.
[SPEAKER_05]: We could finally have Charlie and the Great Glass Elevator, the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: It'd be pretty amazing.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was certainly better than that shit-tastic Charlie and the Chocolate Factory game they put out a couple years ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm picking up the rights to the Bible.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry, those little offshoot companies already did Bible Adventures.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if, like, God's rights are for sale.
[SPEAKER_10]: I pick the... Call it a thought.
[SPEAKER_05]: I pick the... I'm so glad you didn't have a mic when you said that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I pick the rights to the Gospel of the Flying Spaghetti Monster game.
[SPEAKER_10]: I am going to do a Flying Spaghetti Monster game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fine, I'm buying the rights to the articles in Playboy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Seriously, if you want to make a badass game, license the Oblivion Engine and the Bible.
[SPEAKER_06]: And just combine them.
[SPEAKER_03]: How fucking nuts would that be?
[SPEAKER_03]: Or as Frisbee puts in the chat, SuperChristPuncher64.
[SPEAKER_05]: FlyingSpaghettiMonster
[SPEAKER_10]: Final Fantasy VII, Advent Children I said not religion For some people, Final Fantasy VII is a religion Because people need lives At any rate, the Blu-ray edition of the movie will have a dub soundtrack Which is why I'm importing that bitch And not because Final Fantasy XIII demo is going to be on there at all Oh no, not for that or anything
[SPEAKER_03]: No, never for that.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, it's going to have it option.
[SPEAKER_10]: I do want the Final Fantasy XIII demo.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it actually, if you do buy that Blu-ray version though, it's going to have the English voice track.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you download the HD Final Fantasy XIII trailer on PlayStation 3?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: I seriously think I got a boner from watching that trailer.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was pretty hot.
[SPEAKER_05]: Noise.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm hearing way too much about cocks on this show tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: At least we've had a mention of boobs.
[SPEAKER_03]: Speaking of cocks, Guns N' Roses Chinese...
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow, Loki just won Best Transition Ever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_03]: Guns N' Roses' Chinese Democracy album is coming to Rock Band this spring.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, no word on the price, but it's coming.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't worry, it's going to be delayed.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to be coming, actually, February 28th, so...
[SPEAKER_03]: And then, also, Rock Band is going to be getting some new download content with the re-release of Pearl Jam's 10 album.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're going to have a code for three bonus tracks in Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_03]: Brother Alive and State of Love and Trust
[SPEAKER_06]: Rock Band has cost themselves some serious cool points.
[SPEAKER_06]: First was the janky way you had to pay $40 for ACDC Live, which you can get for $30 now.
[SPEAKER_06]: The second is the whole Chinese democracy thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Quit trying to stuff these giant packs on us.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's terrible.
[SPEAKER_06]: Terrible stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Making us buy CDs.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just put them up on the network.
[SPEAKER_06]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Chinese democracy thing is going to be on the network.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, but see, that just sucks.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm excited about Pearl Jam.
[SPEAKER_06]: That is their single best and only fantastic album.
[SPEAKER_10]: That is one of the last CDs that I have ever owned that every damn track on it was fantastic.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can we seriously get a Journey album right now?
[SPEAKER_10]: No shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Seriously?
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's not that Pearl Jam isn't good.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just that Journey's better.
[SPEAKER_06]: Right.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I don't want to buy 10 again so I can get three rock band songs.
[SPEAKER_06]: And yes, there's an egregious dearth of Journey.
[SPEAKER_06]: There needs to be way more of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Every Journey song would be great.
[SPEAKER_05]: For real.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what they need to be selling at Walmart is the Journey game.
[SPEAKER_06]: What is the one that's on...
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway you want it, that's the way you need it.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's great, but I mean, there's so more, so much more.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, one more story for you guys, then we're going to open up the Skype line, and you know, you know we love our music game roots, and we have to mention music games whenever we see new ones, but I don't know if this one exactly would qualify.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a game called D-Pad Hero.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right, there's so much love out there for Guitar Hero and everything that this whole thing started that they have actually made a
[SPEAKER_05]: Retro D-Make.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not a remake.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know how you feel.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know you love remakes.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know how you feel about D-Makes, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: D-Pad Hero.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Guitar Hero, but you use the D-Pad to play the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: And actually, there's actually a little video that leaked on YouTube here.
[SPEAKER_05]: I shouldn't say leaked, but they actually put it out here kind of showing how the game works.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you're hearing the noises in the background there, that's what I'm trying to load here in studio, although it's kind of having a hard time buffering.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was so sure you said D-Bag Hero at first.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like Douchebag Hero?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think that would play exactly the same way.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was like, what?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, not D-Bag Hero, D-Pad Hero.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Annunciate.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or I just need to clean my ears or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, I don't know why the video's not working, but it's not.
[SPEAKER_05]: But apparently you have all these different... But the thing is, is that you actually... You guys know he's making that up, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: You actually get these music things in NES style.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it actually has, you know, speaking of Guns N' Roses, Sweet Child of Mine, that you can actually play in, like, it's NES style.
[SPEAKER_05]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: I really want to see if we can get a... Because they actually have this, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: They have...
[SPEAKER_05]: They have Harder, Better, Faster, Stronger in this game as well by Daft Punk.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let me see if one of these other videos will work here a little better.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see, here's a little... And these little things fall down.
[SPEAKER_05]: Looks like you actually hold the D-pad in a certain direction when you push the button.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it does have a little bit of a challenge to it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And there actually is a little audience that rocks out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like see, there's like one guy bobbing up and down there in the background.
[SPEAKER_05]: This song is awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is actually a pretty faithful remake of the song.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Amaze Hatsuma in chat says, once teabag hero.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Featuring an all Madonna soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: New York Comic Con
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I had a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, this is the first Comic-Con I went to, because this is the first time I've been back in New York for a long time.
[SPEAKER_08]: But Comic-Con has kind of turned itself into a normal comic convention, into just a whole geek fest of everything.
[SPEAKER_08]: And now, this year, they kind of expanded the game section.
[SPEAKER_08]: So now half the convention is more so video game stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: They had a lot of new games there that I was excited to play.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sounds like it's practically turning into the San Diego Comic-Con, because they don't really talk about comics at the San Diego.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, they do, but a lot of it is Hollywood panels.
[SPEAKER_05]: When I heard there was a Sarah Silverman show panel at Comic-Con, I'm like, what the fuck does that have to do with comics?
[SPEAKER_05]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_05]: We read comic books, so we should have a panel.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Comic-Con has long since been perverted away from comics.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently.
[SPEAKER_05]: But that's okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: We like gaming, so that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I just want to point out, guys, as well, since we are kind of getting used to this whole new Skype setup, they can't hear the Skype calls on Justin.TV, and that's just one of the downsides to the way things are wired now and having the better sound quality.
[SPEAKER_05]: So sadly, if you want to hear both ends of the call, you have to be tuned in to All Games Radio where we're tuning in live.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see if we can fix that in the future, but can't do it right now while we're on a call.
[SPEAKER_05]: So tell us about the types.
[SPEAKER_05]: What games did you guys get out there and actually play?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, there were, actually, you know, to tell you the truth, it was very, very easy to play a lot of the games.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was surprised because, you know, I went there on Saturday where it was a busy, busy day where everyone was there.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, I actually, you know, I had to wait about like 15 minutes probably per game to hit up a game, but, you know, I could spend the entire call talking about every single game there, but I'll just talk about three.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: The three that I got a chance to play were
[SPEAKER_08]: MadWorld, which is coming out for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_08]: If anyone hasn't seen it, it's kind of like if Sin City was a Wii game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: So this is a nice departure from Wii Mageddon, which has been talked about earlier.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've heard about this game before.
[SPEAKER_05]: MadWorld, Dan?
[SPEAKER_05]: MadWorld.
[SPEAKER_06]: We got to check it out last September.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's pretty hardcore for a Wii game.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's kind of got a Killer7 vibe, if anyone's checked out Killer7.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it's hyper-violent.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's all black and white except for when you're laying out some carnage and then you get a lot of blood.
[SPEAKER_06]: Definitely one of the coolest titles for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: What did you think, Matt?
[SPEAKER_08]: I thought it was great.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, the first... They had a challenge in the game where...
[SPEAKER_08]: you basically have to shove guys into a pit and every couple minutes a giant thing just drops down and crushes everything in the pit so it was funny like every single time you throw a guy in they get crushed like a pool of blood slowly fills up and more guys you throw in there they start drowning in the blood it's a pretty brutal game you know it might get me to buy a Wii game interesting alright that's a pretty hearty endorsement what else did you check out?
[SPEAKER_08]: Another game which I think Loki would be interested in is Grand Theft Auto Chinatown Wars for the DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: I heard this was out on the floor.
[SPEAKER_05]: What did you think?
[SPEAKER_08]: When I originally heard they were going to make a Grand Theft Auto DS game, I was kind of skeptical, but
[SPEAKER_08]: One, I got a chance to play it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I got to admit, it's a pretty good game.
[SPEAKER_08]: It kind of goes back to the old top-down GTAs, like GTA 2.
[SPEAKER_08]: The animation is very smooth and everything.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's got a lot of cute gimmicks in it.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you're calling for a cab, you basically whistle into the DS for the cab.
[SPEAKER_06]: it's got a lot of cool things like that is there any special thing for like when you want to like get the hooker to blow you in the shooter you gotta like hold some money up in front of it and crinkle the dollars together seriously though if you want to see what Grand Theft Auto is going to look like when it's like on Nintendo 64 there you go Chinatown Wars baby they got a little thing in there where it's like Dope Wars if you kind of remember that from old handheld calculators and all that
[SPEAKER_05]: Dope Wars was awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, anything you want to say about the Grand Theft Auto Chinatown Wars?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm planning on playing it.
[SPEAKER_05]: What was the third game?
[SPEAKER_08]: The third game, which I consider was the best game there, was the Ghostbusters game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've heard some good things about this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tell us a little bit about the Ghostbusters game.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's it like?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, what they had, well, you know, it's kind of like what everyone seems to think it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: It looks, it feels like Gears of War, but with Ghostbusters.
[SPEAKER_06]: What version did they have there?
[SPEAKER_08]: They had every single version.
[SPEAKER_08]: They had the PS3, the 360, and the Wii version.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Wii version is the only one that looks different.
[SPEAKER_08]: It kind of, like, looks a little more cartoony than the others, but it's just as fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, I managed to get to play the Wii and the 360, so.
[SPEAKER_06]: See, I heard that the Wii was like an FPS version where you use your remote to capture ghosts and your nunchuck for movement.
[SPEAKER_06]: And yeah, the 360 version is more like a third-person shooter.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, you basically use the nunchuck to throw the trap.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, Matt, I've been letting you do all the talking, but Ranma, did you go too?
[SPEAKER_05]: What did you check out?
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, I was mostly in the dealer's room, but I was able to check out one game.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think it's a game that everybody loves, Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles, Turtles in Time.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was there to celebrate the 25th shelliversary of the Ninja Turtles.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Shelliversary.
[SPEAKER_05]: I heard there was like an old school Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles arcade machine there.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, there was.
[SPEAKER_14]: And there was crowds upon crowds for people to jump in and play.
[SPEAKER_05]: Isn't that sad that with like all these new games that are making their debut there, like, you know, you have what, like Jumpgate and Prototype and Mad World and WrestleMania and Conduit.
[SPEAKER_05]: People are like lining up to play TMNT 2, the arcade game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because quality persists.
[SPEAKER_05]: For real.
[SPEAKER_05]: Damn right.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's an amazing game.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'd be in line playing that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ooh, Star Trek Online.
[SPEAKER_05]: Supernova 2 New York Con New Turtles
[SPEAKER_14]: The new Turtles game, I'm not sure if they had it on out front.
[SPEAKER_14]: I didn't think so.
[SPEAKER_14]: They just kept advertising it.
[SPEAKER_14]: I do know it's pretty much from the people that did on Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_14]: Bro, so I think this is going to be a good title that they're working on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm a little skeptical because some of the Teenage Mutant Turtles games are kind of ass, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did anybody see Hawks?
[SPEAKER_05]: It was on display.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I got to play Hawks.
[SPEAKER_08]: How was it?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's like a very polished Ace Combat.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sweet.
[SPEAKER_08]: and yeah, it's a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like shooting things with jets.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, so really quickly guys, then we're going to let you go because we've got to get some more calls because we're kind of running long tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: But best thing you saw at Comic-Con.
[SPEAKER_05]: Matt.
[SPEAKER_08]: Aside from the Ghostbusters game, this new game called Prototype, which is coming out for the 360 and
[SPEAKER_08]: it's everything what Spider-Man Web of Shadows should have been it's just really brutal and free roam New York City mutant thing, it's really great alright, and Ranma, best thing it has to be a tie number one, the Ninja Turtles arcade machine and number two, the attempt at breaking the Guinness Book of World Records for the biggest amount of video game cosplayers in one setting did you break it?
[SPEAKER_14]: No.
[SPEAKER_14]: The record was 342.
[SPEAKER_14]: There was 90 of us.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_14]: Street Fighter 4 there?
[SPEAKER_14]: Maybe next year.
[SPEAKER_14]: I suppose I think it was.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't see it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wasn't your favorite?
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait, what?
[SPEAKER_05]: You're saying Street Fighter 4 was there and it wasn't your favorite?
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I didn't see it there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Runtime.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: We need to do that at Fonamay.
[SPEAKER_14]: I was going to talk to him and see if we can get that done because that title's got to come back to the US.
[SPEAKER_10]: We need to do this in front of me.
[SPEAKER_14]: Break the records.
[SPEAKER_14]: Before I go, if you see pictures of us at the video game shoot, you'll be seeing me in the background holding up a giant Super NES.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, two quick last things.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm posting pictures in the chat regularly.
[SPEAKER_08]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also, one very last thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Expect a care package of swag.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, you guys are the best.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love the fans.
[SPEAKER_05]: We don't even have to go to these events and we get goodies.
[SPEAKER_05]: Love it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you guys so much.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not a problem.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have a good one, kids.
[SPEAKER_05]: See you later.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Speaking of our fans doing nice stuff for us, I would like to personally thank IkumaJP for the box of puka.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which, by the way, I do still have some of the nom-noms in the house if you guys want some of the nom-noms.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, we're going to go to the phones.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_00]: Hi, this is Spazinator.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, Spazinator, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_00]: Two quick questions.
[SPEAKER_00]: With the Xbox 360, do you know if there's a hard drive available that's bigger than 120 gigs?
[SPEAKER_05]: Not yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just a matter of time, though.
[SPEAKER_00]: The reason I ask is because I hate to see it, but my hard drive is running out of space as it is.
[SPEAKER_00]: Also,
[SPEAKER_00]: Secondly, can you think of any retro games that you would like to see released for any one of those three systems, or are you pretty much all set?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry, run that by me one more time?
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, while retro games are kind of big, and they're constantly getting released for all three of those systems, whether it be Wii, Virtual Console, the PlayStation 3, or...
[SPEAKER_00]: and XBLA.
[SPEAKER_00]: Can you think of any game that you would like to see released for Y03 or are you pretty much all set?
[SPEAKER_05]: Mega Man 10.
[SPEAKER_06]: What, that will be released or that was released?
[SPEAKER_06]: You would like to see released.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mega Man 10 at some point would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: As long as they stay with the Mega Man 9 series and do a Mega Man 10, that'd be great.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mega Man 9 was awesome for all three systems but of course was the best on the Wii because it was just the most...
[SPEAKER_06]: Authentic, retro, like new retro experience.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm surprised that, I mean, I'm not surprised, but Bionic Commando Rearmed would be really nice on the Wii, you know, if they decided to do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I really think the game that needs to be remade that was out before its time and I mean I know that I hate this game and I hate the fanboys for it you know like although I approve of fanboyism and go for it love what you love I really think that the game that needs a remake needs it for anything powerful enough to run it is Final Fantasy 7
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I definitely agree with you.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'd love to see a remake of VII, you know, because...
[SPEAKER_00]: I used to love that game.
[SPEAKER_00]: Unfortunately, I don't have my copy of it anymore.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, you know, if they ever do release the game again, you know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Make it for anything but the DS.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, because the DS would just basically be able to do it as it originally was.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, thank you for taking my call.
[SPEAKER_05]: You are welcome.
[SPEAKER_00]: You have a good one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Take care, Spazinator.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if Final Fantasy 7 would fit on Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the only problem I see going on with that.
[SPEAKER_05]: But who knows?
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because you know if they wanted to make it, Microsoft wouldn't make an exception.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, we got another call.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hello, this is DSMaster25.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_15]: Not much.
[SPEAKER_15]: I got a PSP 2000, but it's kind of fluky on me.
[SPEAKER_15]: I buy it used.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait, I find this ironic because your name is DSMaster yet I'm looking at your logo on Skype and your call is about a PSP.
[SPEAKER_05]: Please explain.
[SPEAKER_15]: Basically, I was desperate for one because I wanted Skype and everything.
[SPEAKER_15]: So I figured, why not buy a PSP?
[SPEAKER_15]: So basically I did.
[SPEAKER_15]: You wanted what game?
[SPEAKER_15]: I wanted to use Skype, reportedly.
[SPEAKER_15]: But the Skype zones were not in America, so the only other option was a PSP.
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: So basically, I bought one used.
[SPEAKER_15]: Now I have this crack in my screen, and now my start button, my select button, my home button, all that doesn't work.
[SPEAKER_06]: It sounds like you have a broken PSP.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would recommend replacing it with a new working one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Preferably a 3000 series, because if you want to use Skype... He said he bought it used.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm curious.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you buy it used at GameStop?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_12]: Sad trombone.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, did you buy it like that, or did you buy it nice and you've made it like that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because if you bought it like that, take that puppy back.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hopefully you were smart enough to buy the extended service on it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Unfortunately, I was dead broke by the time I bought the PSP, so I didn't have any money to buy the extended service.
[SPEAKER_15]: I was pretty much screwed.
[SPEAKER_12]: What was wrong with the PSP now?
[SPEAKER_12]: This is just a sad trombone call.
[SPEAKER_00]: Basically, the home button.
[SPEAKER_15]: The volume buttons The screen brightness I'll repeat what I said Do they not test these things?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, do they not notice Scratch on the screen Or a big crack on the screen I mean, because I know when you have to go trade stuff in There's like, does this shit work?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, and here's the deal You're about to get an education As to the inside workings of used game stores They get ranked
[SPEAKER_06]: On how much they get traded in.
[SPEAKER_06]: So a lot of times they'll let crap slide.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then they get ranked on selling you stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: So they're going to try to foist it on you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now there are game stores like mine where if you bring me a system, man, I'm looking for a reason to say no.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I'm a jerk.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: and many more.
[SPEAKER_06]: and then maybe they'll get some good people in there and you can have another good game store.
[SPEAKER_05]: Orange Dawn Strider does not actually endorse this thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: They may not endorse it officially but you know they're all down with it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm down with it.
[SPEAKER_15]: So what you're telling me is basically go back in there because my 30 day guarantee is already passed.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because I bought this on December 22nd.
[SPEAKER_03]: Otherwise, you know, the buttons and stuff not working?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, which buttons are not working on there?
[SPEAKER_15]: The home button, the volume buttons, the screen brightness, and the sound equalizer.
[SPEAKER_15]: Wait, wait, wait, hold on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Stop, stop, you guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, so basically all the buttons on that bottom row, right?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, except for start.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's the only one that works.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, if you chopped it game crazy, we give you a 90-day guarantee without you even paying any extra money.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nice, nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Plug, plug, plug.
[SPEAKER_05]: For what it's worth, your call sounds great.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it'll be funny with the PSP system.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know if you could do one on them where you buy a new system and swap it for the broken one.
[SPEAKER_06]: You sold me a busted system.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're serial numbered, but I mean, you know, if you want to try a fast one that's on you, I can't tell you to do that or not tell you to do that.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's up to your quality of being a human being.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, oh, hey, I won't say I've never done anything like that.
[SPEAKER_15]: I think I'm going to wait until I get money and then I'm going to buy a 3000.
[SPEAKER_15]: Go back.
[SPEAKER_15]: And then I'll use this one for emulators.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a good idea.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think the advice, too, would just be, you know what, go in, anyone else that finds themselves in this situation, go in, be nice about it, don't be a dick, because no manager is going to want to do favors for you if you're a dick.
[SPEAKER_05]: Go in, be nice about it, and see if they'll do a favor for you.
[SPEAKER_05]: And if not, run them over with your car.
[SPEAKER_05]: But your other idea was great.
[SPEAKER_06]: Especially if, like Loki says, there's a ribbon cable in there.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you like taking crap apart...
[SPEAKER_06]: and you're out of warranty and can't get any help, take that puppy apart.
[SPEAKER_06]: PSPs are awesome inside.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's all sorts of cool stuff you can do with them.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can like blow up their batteries and like lose pieces, change the color of the buttons.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, just turn them into lasers.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: That might be the issue, because all of a sudden the buttons won't just die, it's the ribbon cable.
[SPEAKER_06]: One of the janky things about used PSPs you gotta watch out for.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, but basically what happened was, I bought it and all the bottom row buttons were working just fine.
[SPEAKER_15]: And then a month or so after, I was listening to you guys in the shower, okay?
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, so now it's our fault.
[SPEAKER_15]: basically I'm trying to change the volume and I'm reaching through the shower curtain and I think I might drop some water but I don't know okay now wait a minute now this is all on you buddy you broke your PSP okay keep this one for you in the shower and keep it away from the water I'm just curious is this an OLM verse that you've been listening to in the shower I'm just curious
[SPEAKER_03]: If you do want to use it in the shower, they do sell waterproof cases you can put on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, DSMaster, we gotta let you go to get some more calls.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just saying, if that's your thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Were you all soapy?
[SPEAKER_05]: DSMaster, good luck to you.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you do get a new PSP, keep it out of the bathtub.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, by the way, the only reason why I bought this one was because I was speculating about the scan lines on the 3000 model.
[SPEAKER_15]: Now I figured it's not so dangerous.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's all the same, it just has a lock.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good luck, PSP, DS Master, whoever you are, and have a good one, okay?
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, bye.
[SPEAKER_05]: Later.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if that guy's ever called in before.
[SPEAKER_05]: I might have been a first-time caller, so that was a good call.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like the...
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, good times.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll try to do at least one more call here and then wrap up the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Deathwishing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, hi, Deathwishing.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're a first-time caller too, aren't you?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm kind of disappointed with a lot of stuff I see in this year for gaming.
[SPEAKER_05]: In this year of gaming?
[SPEAKER_05]: In 2009 in gaming?
[SPEAKER_05]: How so?
[SPEAKER_05]: Just because it seems like there's nothing to look forward to?
[SPEAKER_02]: I know it just started, but like...
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just, I don't know, this summer seems a lot more droughted.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, I can already tell this summer's going to be a major drought for gaming.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you think it might be that everybody's trying to keep it in their pants until E3?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's kind of one thing I've been trying to tell myself, as much as I might be lying to myself, is that maybe people are trying to keep it in their pants until E3.
[SPEAKER_06]: You gotta remember, games and game developers are like plants.
[SPEAKER_06]: And their water is money.
[SPEAKER_06]: And there's no money out there right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, things are quiet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um...
[SPEAKER_06]: You gotta actually think, this summer there's not gonna be crap anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: You gotta look towards the fourth quarter and, you know, they're not gonna be making announcements about the fourth quarter until mid-spring when they've gotten through the Street Fighter 4 and the Resident Evils and the Killzone 2s because we got some... I mean, if you actually think about it, this is a great spring for games.
[SPEAKER_06]: There are some just...
[SPEAKER_06]: Nice, AAA titles for every system.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nintendo had a great Christmas, at least in the States, with the Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know they're having a lot of trouble in Japan.
[SPEAKER_06]: But really, I think that, you know, if you look at a lot of the release lists and whatnot, there's a lot of cool stuff coming out for everybody.
[SPEAKER_06]: Skip the summer.
[SPEAKER_06]: There'll be a big title or two, but I mean, it's not going to blow any wind up your skirt.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then just start.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_06]: Look to the fourth quarter, man.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's where all the big games are.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dan does have a point because our economy is in such shit right now in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if you're calling for the U.S.
[SPEAKER_05]: or wherever, but the thing is that it seems like on this show, week after week after week, we've been reporting this studio has closed, this studio has closed, this studio has closed.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, damn, we're kind of lucky to be getting any games at all at this point.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, you know, I do kind of agree.
[SPEAKER_05]: I feel that same frustration as it's like, you know,
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: Gamers get spoiled.
[SPEAKER_05]: They expect big releases every month.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe because Hollywood spoils us.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a big movie every week.
[SPEAKER_02]: So don't get me started on movie chains.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're not in the first two years of any console's development cycle now.
[SPEAKER_06]: They've all proven what they have to prove, except for Sony.
[SPEAKER_06]: Look at Sony's lineup.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: But there's Ryu and Ken and one's Hadouken and one's Hadouken.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got a Hadouken.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to take off a third of your life.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mike Tyson takes off all your life with one punch.
[SPEAKER_06]: And if you don't dodge all those punches, you can't even block them.
[SPEAKER_06]: He makes Shang Long look like a sissy.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what we have now?
[SPEAKER_07]: We have Obama with the veto uppercut.
[SPEAKER_06]: I fought Akuma last night in HD Remix, and I got beat uncontrollably hard.
[SPEAKER_06]: But at least I could hit him.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mike Tyson, punch out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Your ass is grass.
[SPEAKER_06]: Put in 007-373-5963 in the password.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fight Mike Tyson.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you beat him, then I'm going to give you your props.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait, let me ask this as well real quick for what it's worth.
[SPEAKER_05]: Are you a 360 owner?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, I do own a 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: Does it still work?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, honestly, I'm on my second 360 and I had it from release.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_05]: and you know when you consider that in the retail world you know we get poop as well like Fusion Frenzy and that fucking Crosswords game that I played this week it was god awful you know you get a lot of that stuff there's some pretty cool stuff that comes out too so if you're feeling like damn I need a fix of something new check out the community games you might not see anything that's going to blow you away but you might see something that you know a neat concept for a game that keeps you entertained for a little while which is you know what a game should do and when you consider those those community games are dirt cheap
[SPEAKER_06]: it's something and look past the big franchises Bionic Commando which is coming out in a couple months a month or so looks great Mad World which we talked about a few minutes ago is mind blowing Halo Wars is actually pretty fun you know there's a lot of stuff coming up this year but maybe it's not Devil May Cry 5 maybe it's not Halo 4 just you know let that stuff let that stuff lay for a while you know they're going to rehash it they're going to spit it at us there's going to be a marketing blitz
[SPEAKER_06]: there's going to be Grand Theft Auto 5 and 6 and 8 and 10 but here's your chance to branch out try some new games just because they're not beating you down with another AAA title doesn't mean there aren't super high quality games by great developers who still have jobs, knock on wood and we'll be blowing you out of the water and like I said, look to the fourth quarter because there are big names announced especially if you don't have a Sony God of War is going to be blamed a little bit better
[SPEAKER_05]: Deathwishing, we gotta let you go to close out the show but thanks a bunch and thanks for tuning in tonight we appreciate it love you
[SPEAKER_05]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love you too.
[SPEAKER_05]: We love you too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: We have last minute stories.
[SPEAKER_05]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_09]: We do have some last minute stories.
[SPEAKER_05]: I do want to make an outbound call real quick.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is an important one.
[SPEAKER_05]: We do want to do one more call.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is outbound because this is important.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to get this person on the show and unfortunately the way our Skype is set up, we have not been able to get like incoming, we just get bombarded with everybody which we love.
[SPEAKER_05]: We love the fact that so many people are trying to get through but there is somebody we wanted to talk to that couldn't get through and we want to talk to him now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Deke, are you there?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I'm here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can you guys hear me?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, not bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tired.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's 1030 here.
[SPEAKER_05]: so far yeah I've only heard maybe one little thing wrong with it and I'm pretty sure that's got to do with the database move from the old website forums to the new one and so that should be pretty easy to take care of I was honestly thinking in the back of my mind that the site would have to be reset like I was like okay we'll just have to start over with forums you know our news will probably have to start from square one and I was like ready to accept that and then when I looked at the new site today I was like holy crap he got everything migrated from the old site that was pretty impressive so props to you
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, I'm going to keep track of that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Make sure nobody kind of abuses it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I want to see cocks popping up all over the place.
[SPEAKER_05]: No cock shots!
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura on break took a picture of me eating jelly beans just randomly and uploaded them to the thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: So what should I hold up?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, how about cookies?
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's hold up cookies for this and we'll send it right to the website right now.
[SPEAKER_11]: I just posted one of myself posing next to the website a couple of minutes ago.
[SPEAKER_11]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like it.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're very excited about it and we hope to have it launched maybe next weekend even or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just as soon as we get some of our new authors on board because I know Tiara's getting ready to write some game reviews for us.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm so excited and we're going to have regular content again.
[SPEAKER_05]: I could just tinkle.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm so excited.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not in here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, Deke, thank you so much and please send our thanks along to your family as well who I know have had to put up with you working on the site.
[SPEAKER_05]: We really appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_05]: No worries.
[SPEAKER_05]: Take care, guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, that's going to do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: We are going to wrap up the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry to those that didn't get through on Skype.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know a lot of you were getting through, but I also was very happy to hear some new callers get through tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was pretty awesome, so thanks and shout out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks to the guy who ate up all the time because his system was broken because he was using it in the shower.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well done!
[SPEAKER_05]: I think the Justin TV things actually kind of helped us get some new listeners, so I'm really excited to get back on there.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think watching a radio show is that exciting, but we'll see what we can do about the TV in the future.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe we'll get a Switch box and actually play games.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know what we can do.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll figure something out.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can fix it so the audio, you can hear everything next time.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's easy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just splitter out your speaker out and then into the... They don't want to hear about the wires.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll make you
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, you know, but anyway, that's for another time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's go around and get everybody's final thought.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is going to be a three-hour show this week, but that's all right.
[SPEAKER_05]: I first off want to say, Matt, too, thank you so much for being here.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry you didn't get to say more tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: But we'll talk more about PC games in a future week.
[SPEAKER_05]: You will come back and join us again, correct?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Dan's fault, yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I had a blast.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for having me.
[SPEAKER_07]: And PC gaming is more my niche, but yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tell us, and we will do more PC gaming in the future.
[SPEAKER_05]: There hasn't been a lot this week, and we've actually got the emails.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why don't you guys talk more about PC gaming?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's why I was like, Matt 2 probably sent one of those emails.
[SPEAKER_05]: It needs to come to the show a little more often.
[SPEAKER_05]: I do want to say, though, for the folks out there who listen, who can't join us in studio, how is it different when you're listening to it on the iPod and when you're here in studio?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's actually a great way to kill, too, to
[SPEAKER_07]: 3 hours of my afternoon at work, which is quite spectacular.
[SPEAKER_07]: Quality's good, easy access.
[SPEAKER_05]: How's it different being here live?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, being here live?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's colder in the garage because my office is a balmy 72 degrees.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's definitely different.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's definitely a lot of wires around.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's actually, at times I feel like I'm a little behind the times with all the wealth of knowledge that's in here.
[SPEAKER_07]: I feel like the noob.
[SPEAKER_07]: But when we started talking about WoW updates, I felt cool again.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, yeah, Dan's pointing at me, he's about to say something profound.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll work on you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because in the world of WoW, you are the king.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sadly, possibly, but no, there are people that out DPS in the tank.
[SPEAKER_07]: In here, anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, in here?
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, cool, I'll take that title.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, sometimes I hear a term in WoW, and I'm like, I know what that means!
[SPEAKER_07]: DPS!
[SPEAKER_07]: Sweet!
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I had a blast, thanks for having me, and I look forward to next shows where you'll have room for me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dan, what can I say?
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you so much for being here and bringing your input.
[SPEAKER_05]: The chatters love you.
[SPEAKER_05]: They want you to be a regular guest on the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: Please come back again, Dan.
[SPEAKER_05]: We had a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Even if your wife is a little pissed you keep taking her microphone, maybe we'll get two mics on the couch next time or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't bet on it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I am not pissed.
[SPEAKER_10]: She's fine.
[SPEAKER_10]: You are a butt face, okay?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_05]: He told her the mic was off even though it wasn't.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, do you have any final thoughts?
[SPEAKER_05]: I had a story.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, a story.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't even ask for last minute stories.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm such an asshole.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, you are, Bob.
[SPEAKER_05]: Quickly, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_10]: There was a guy named Danny Johnson, 14, of Grapevine, Texas.
[SPEAKER_10]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_10]: who actually set a new world record in Guitar Hero at a Guinness World Records event in Manhattan.
[SPEAKER_10]: He scored 973,954 points playing Dragonforge's Through the Fire and the Flames.
[SPEAKER_10]: And from what I read otherwise, he actually broke a button while doing it.
[SPEAKER_07]: He broke his blue button and he was mad at himself that he didn't hit 100%.
[SPEAKER_07]: He only hit 99%.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll link the video in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, did you have any last minute stories?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, just some real quick stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Namco's planning on rebooting the Dead to Rights franchise.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dear God, why?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Interesting, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then some other stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Apparently some dude threatened to blow up the Bomberman devs because he had a problem with his Bomberman game, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: It sent them 11 terrorizing emails during a four-month period before the company finally decided to do something.
[SPEAKER_03]: He was unhappy with the quality of Hudson products.
[SPEAKER_06]: He was just getting into the spirit of things.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know.
[SPEAKER_10]: We have one more contribution.
[SPEAKER_03]: Telltale Games is bringing Wallace and Gromit to PC and Xbox Live Arcade this spring.
[SPEAKER_05]: I heard about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: It sounds awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then the last thing, and this is completely retarded, but PlayStation 3 apparently is going to start supporting AmbX.
[SPEAKER_05]: What the hell is that?
[SPEAKER_03]: AmbX is a stupid little thing that you plug into your... It's right now for computers.
[SPEAKER_03]: It has colored lights that change colors depending on the scenes that are in your game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then there's also fans that blow hot and cold air at you and it vibrates and craps.
[SPEAKER_06]: Think about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: That could be cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, and craps.
[SPEAKER_10]: And craps!
[SPEAKER_10]: You can say, hey, this sucks shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: That could be a feature in Excite Trucks 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now the truck's crap.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, why not?
[SPEAKER_05]: You see those guys that drive down the freeway and they have the balls hanging from their trucks?
[SPEAKER_05]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_05]: Now they can crap too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't justify that behavior, Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that's the most vile thing possible.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you have that on the back of your truck, take it off your truck and choke yourself with it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_05]: Please die.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have one quick last minute story or I'm going to get the crap kicked out of me by Travis and John over at Under Sedation Live.
[SPEAKER_05]: I believe they're down to like, I want to say like 32 games or 16.
[SPEAKER_05]: How many are they at?
2, 4, 6, 8, 10, 12, 13, 14.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're down to like the top.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: We got engaged in theory on Valentine's Day.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you know what I did on Valentine's Day?
[SPEAKER_05]: Sat home and cried and ate Lean Cuisine.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what I did.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_10]: But ours was really cool and nerdy because we were watching UHF and eating French bread with spinach dip and drinking Munchweizitz wine.
[SPEAKER_05]: I will say one of the coolest Valentine's Days I had was when the ex and I went to the Star Trek tour at Long Beach.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was a pretty nerdy-tastic Valentine's Day.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some people get married.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some people boldly go where no man has gone before.
[SPEAKER_05]: What can you do?
[SPEAKER_05]: Which kind of are the same thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Congrats to Travis.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sucker.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, actually, Jenna's the real sucker, actually, in that relationship.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, we love them.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry I missed the bachelor party.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was out.
[SPEAKER_05]: But yeah, thanks to all you guys for tuning in and listening to us, whether it be on Justin.TV or on All Games Radio or on the podcast when it gets updated, which, you know, will be sooner than usual.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see you next week.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to do it all again next week, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, now everyone knows what my home life is like.
[SPEAKER_05]: Heck yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Quickly, final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't get final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what you're doing.
[SPEAKER_05]: My final thought is Warp Core Breach.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yum.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: I need a Cage Match song.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's going to do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you guys so much for downloading and supporting independent podcasting.
[SPEAKER_05]: You guys are great.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you like what you hear here, remember we don't charge you for this or anything.
[SPEAKER_05]: We don't run ads during the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: Please leave us a nice review somewhere.
[SPEAKER_05]: Until next time, Super Weemageddon.
[SPEAKER_13]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_13]: To join us for a live show, visit www.allgames.com Sunday nights at 6pm Pacific Time.
[SPEAKER_13]: The views and opinions expressed on Orange Lounge Radio do not necessarily reflect those of the entire staff of Orange Lounge Radio or allgames.com, but we're probably right anyway.
[SPEAKER_13]: See you next week!