[SPEAKER_00]: Tonight, February 11th, 2007, Xbox Gamerscore whores might get rewarded soon, an old DC gaming franchise is said to be coming back, and we have some exclusive news on the Alice movie.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello everybody out there on the internet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: We are that podcast on the internet dedicated to video gaming and gaming culture and what you, the gamer, really want to know.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm here to help you through that.
[SPEAKER_05]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_05]: You might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_05]: Joining me as always, say hello to my lovely co-hosts.
[SPEAKER_05]: In that corner, the happiest bunny on the farm, DarkSakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_08]: Roar.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fresh off the highway.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: First off, I want to apologize for my sound tonight because A, I'm recovering from a cold, so I sound a little bit congested.
[SPEAKER_05]: I got the plague, so I guess in 2007 this will be the year of Rob getting the plague instead of Jamie getting the plague all the time, so that's entertaining.
[SPEAKER_05]: Urgent care.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_05]: That sounds like I'm talking out of a tin can, even though this microphone probably costs twice as much as Loki's microphone that he's using.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which the top is falling off of this microphone.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, that's just lovely to hear.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, then you'll have a tin can microphone soon, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: My microphone's working just fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want that, but that was donated to us.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have no idea where that microphone came from.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know who it came from.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know where it came from, but I mean, I know who donated it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know where to get them.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because we need two more like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Guitar Center.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really?
[SPEAKER_05]: Then that's where we're going.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going shopping.
[SPEAKER_05]: Any place that sells microphones.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, dude, I got this at Radio Shack.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was like, oh, Radio Shack, you know, they have like 10 different microphones.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, radio crap.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I mean, this microphone, I don't want to tell you how much it was, but I'll say it was twice as much as that one, and it has the tin can sound to it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it just takes some getting used to.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just put it up to your neck and go, hello.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was being told secrets from Jamie, so maybe we will get a shopping spree next week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait, are you saying I should do this, Loki?
[SPEAKER_05]: Eddie,
[SPEAKER_05]: Yep, that's me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Eddie, have you ever been on this show before, Eddie?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, like three or four years ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: Big, fruity, gay Eddie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Casper the gay, that's me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Casper the gay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Eddie the Friendly Gay, what kind of games are you into since you've never been on the show before?
[SPEAKER_04]: Never been on the show before.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or at least, you haven't been on here since we've been podcasting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like when you were on the show, we had like five people listening and we thought we were the shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Including us in the room.
[SPEAKER_05]: Exactly, it was like the live studio audience was it.
[SPEAKER_05]: We were live performers.
[SPEAKER_05]: But now we have this whole like internet podcast, iPod thing, it's crazy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, so what type of games are you into?
[SPEAKER_04]: Fantasy Adventure, yeah, I'm a diehard Nintendo fanboy, which everybody, I guess is not as bad anymore because Wii's pretty cool, but yep.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fantasy Adventure, kind of games like Zelda.
[SPEAKER_05]: RPGs.
[SPEAKER_05]: Was Zelda like your favorite game that came out last year, you'd say?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, Twilight Princess by far.
[SPEAKER_05]: What would you say is your favorite video game of all time?
[SPEAKER_05]: Just so we have something to go off of here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of all time?
[SPEAKER_04]: Probably like Link to the Past, something like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you're a total Link fanboy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nerd.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nerd.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nerdy nerd.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, Casper the Gay, do you follow gaming news a lot?
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you follow the gaming culture?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I log on to the IGN sometimes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: You shouldn't log on to those big money sites, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_10]: The correct answer is, I read independent blogs like Destructoid and Kotaku.
[SPEAKER_05]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whatever Rob said.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I'll go to Orange Lounge Radio for all my news and awgames.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're the shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good job, Eddie.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, good.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what I sound like.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, no.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, you know, as far as the big box... Why is Eddie Mr. Bill?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: As far as...
[SPEAKER_05]: As far as the big box sites go, IGN doesn't bug me nearly as bad as some of the others.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm reading chat room because we also have the chat room is always here to lend their perspective as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: We love our chat room.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: What do we have here?
[SPEAKER_05]: JV Mon says, Yay, Rice Princess.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dark Knight says, What is up, our home girl?
[SPEAKER_09]: You can't even say it right, Ron.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm doing very good.
[SPEAKER_09]: How about you?
[SPEAKER_05]: Good.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actdeft says, isn't every gay person friendly?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've dated some real bitches in the past.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_05]: In fact, we could name some on this program, but we're above that.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm not.
[SPEAKER_05]: All of you.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_05]: All I'm going to say, if you like to listen to the live shows on Orange Lingerie, because, you know, we don't just do this podcast.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have live shows there as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wednesday happens to be Guys on the Show, and it's our Valentine's Day special.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to be calling some of our exes on air.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_05]: And wishing them a happy Valentine's Day, so that'll be a good time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: JV Mon says, I am gay and I am far from friendly.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, I met JV Mon in person.
[SPEAKER_05]: He was just shy.
[SPEAKER_05]: He was a little quiet.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think he's gay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: TV?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know you don't watch, so that's why I'm sharing this with you.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't even have cable, Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, but okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: The extent of my cable is Court TV.
[SPEAKER_05]: Are you familiar with Lifetime, Vagina Television?
[SPEAKER_05]: Are you familiar with Lifetime?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Television?
[SPEAKER_08]: I haven't watched Lifetime in easily three years.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, Lifetime is like women's TV and like, you know, all the... That's why I don't watch it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's stupid.
[SPEAKER_05]: The movies they have on there are like the best movies ever.
[SPEAKER_05]: They have like, you know...
[SPEAKER_05]: Final Justice, the story of the woman who stood in line at Walmart for a PS3.
[SPEAKER_05]: The story of the woman who was horribly raped and murdered and had a Lifetime movie made out of her.
[SPEAKER_08]: And had ear mites.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right, I freaking love Lifetime movies.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or the most recent one.
[SPEAKER_08]: I should pick up a Lifetime movie.
[SPEAKER_05]: You should be a Lifetime movie.
[SPEAKER_08]: No way.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dark Sakura, the gamer girl of the millennia.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Fantasia Barino story was one I just recently watched.
[SPEAKER_05]: But anyway, my point is, there's commercials...
[SPEAKER_05]: for this new show they're doing, Gay, Straight, or Taken.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a dating show, and the thing is that a woman goes out on a date with a gay man, a straight man, and a guy who's already married or taken, has a girlfriend.
[SPEAKER_05]: And at the end is when she finds it.
[SPEAKER_05]: She has to pick which one's which, and if she correctly picks the straight man, then they win a fabulous date prize, like Hawaii type thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: But if she picks one of the others, then they win a prize, and she gets nothing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, because whiny straight girls have it so hard.
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: So is this something you would watch?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hell no!
[SPEAKER_05]: Is this a video game that would appeal to gamer girls?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because you know there's always that thing going around like, how do we get women into gaming?
[SPEAKER_05]: I've got two women in here.
[SPEAKER_05]: How do we get women into gaming?
[SPEAKER_05]: Do we need lifetime to bring out the video voyeur, the Susan Wilson video game?
[SPEAKER_05]: Is that what we need?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm having a terrible hair day.
[SPEAKER_08]: Video games need more violence.
[SPEAKER_05]: is that how to get women into gaming?
[SPEAKER_09]: I like to see more titties in games definitely wait a minute we need boobs and blood more guy on guy spanking wait, wait, wait I'm done with that it's all about Dead or Alive Extreme and Rumble Roses
[SPEAKER_08]: and Rule of Roses Candy.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's all about sequels to the Desperate Housewives PC game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because if there's a skill that's vastly needed in this world, it's cooking and cleaning.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, going to the chat room for some comments.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jared J says, Rob, you just crossed from respectable gay to stereotypical uber gay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whatever, girlfriend, whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: You don't know me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sit down.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, snap, girl.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is so not me.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's really not...
[SPEAKER_08]: That's so not you when you're sober.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, when I'm drunk, maybe.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Gaming Nerd says, my parents watched it one day.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was pretty creepy.
[SPEAKER_05]: JV Mon says, I hate gay straight or taken.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Padrino says, what if the taken guy is gay?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know, what if the taken guy is gay?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, there was the gay guy that was taken on the show before.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's always a straight guy that's taken.
[SPEAKER_06]: But see, here's the thing though, and even, we talked it over, like we were saying, what if, you know, we were put in that situation.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like, fuck that, just, you know, do whatever it takes to win the vacation, we'll forgive you.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like, that's, I don't know.
All you need to do is like,
[SPEAKER_09]: and I'll see you next time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, Dead or Alive?
[SPEAKER_08]: A whole crap load of it.
[SPEAKER_08]: And, oh, I also play Twilight Zone.
[SPEAKER_08]: Right now, though, we're fixing our Rocky and Bullwinkle machine, and we got an Earthshaker, which is old-school, cool pinball.
[SPEAKER_05]: How are you fitting any more pinball machines in there?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm actually going to be selling some.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: We have nine pinball machines.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, one of them's Will's.
[SPEAKER_08]: We sold him our Judge Dredd.
[SPEAKER_08]: I wanted to get rid of the Johnny Mnemonic.
[SPEAKER_08]: I told Dan that if he gets rid of the Star Trek pinball, I would murder him in his sleep.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we're probably going to sell our Guns N' Roses machine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, that's sad.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love that machine.
[SPEAKER_08]: And maybe we'll then come over and play it before we sell it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I need money for Adolfis.
[SPEAKER_05]: After the show, okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're going to charge me quarters?
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: We need to sell them so that I can use the money from Dan's pinball machines.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alpha Canogram says, Oh, snap!
[SPEAKER_05]: Rocky and Bullwinkle.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, snap.
[SPEAKER_08]: I love Rocky and Bullwinkle, but... Well, the problem with our Rocky and Bullwinkle machine is that we need a new board for it, for the ROM set.
[SPEAKER_08]: And right now the board's like, I'm going to be broken for a while.
[SPEAKER_08]: And, you know, paying for school, so I've got to decide what's more important, my education or pinball.
[SPEAKER_08]: Which is a really hard choice, but, you know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mike W. says, Don't worry, Mama will fix it.
[SPEAKER_05]: CookieMama reference, of course.
[SPEAKER_08]: Insert Ellipse here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, thanks, bye.
[SPEAKER_08]: You need to have SugarMama the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, I play that pretty often.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_06]: My gaming week was good.
[SPEAKER_06]: I played more of the Crackdown demo, again.
[SPEAKER_06]: I found the grenade launcher, which makes the game a lot more fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then, what else did I do?
[SPEAKER_06]: I played a little bit of...
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh god, what the hell is that crappy PopCap game?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, it's some crappy PopCap game that's on live.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, I'm just trying to get shooting points.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I got bored real quick, so.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then, let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Played more Resistance.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm actually playing it the second time through.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you get some more weapons, so it's like mildly fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: More fun, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: It was just so retarded, so I have to play more Driver 3 now because I forgot how crappy that game is.
[SPEAKER_06]: And probably now it's dirt cheap, so maybe pick up an actual copy of it instead of a pirated copy on my PlayStation 2 hard drive.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then play it on the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: But yeah, that's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Looking forward to playing some new stuff this week, hopefully.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jared J says, oh god, I still can't believe I paid $50 for Driver 3 back in the day.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't believe I paid $50 for a game I played a little bit this week, Fusion Frenzy 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: I picked up this game because the demo was kind of fun, and I thought, oh, well, you know, I love those little mini-games.
[SPEAKER_05]: This will be, you know, a good time.
[SPEAKER_05]: The best way I can describe this game is unpolished.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, it's just, it feels sloppy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, all these little cutscenes are bleh, and the games all look the same, and it's so bland.
[SPEAKER_05]: How could a game with 40 mini-games that's basically Think Mario Party without the big board be so freaking bland?
[SPEAKER_05]: But it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was just so...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: The graphics from F-Zero on GameCube And just like, you know, they keep looping the same animation Which is amazing because the developers are completely different Yeah, but yeah, to me it had the same look to it And it was just kind of generic And the characters are all the same, it's just they're different colors And they use the same animation loops over and over again Instead of actually having new cutscenes And it's just, yeah, I just think they rushed through it So I do not recommend Fusion Frenzy 2 Unless you want easy achievement points Go rent it because you can get through the achievements pretty easy As I understand it
[SPEAKER_05]: I racked up 75 pretty quickly just playing through it once and it wasn't anything that difficult, so yawn.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I know we're going to talk later in the show about the rewards program, but for those of you guys that are hoping to get this as a reward, you might find that they're just trying to unload the extra copies they're bound to have because this game is not fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank God that the Halo beta wasn't included with this game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Root Beer Tapper Root Beer Tapper
[SPEAKER_05]: You don't see the other player on your screen at all.
[SPEAKER_05]: All you see is their score and how they're progressing in the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it doesn't lend itself very much to a co-op.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they didn't even redo the graphics or anything.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, I mean, I guess it's good that it's only $5, which is the cheapest that Microsoft will charge any game.
[SPEAKER_05]: But expect this game to be the free toss-in on a lot of upcoming bundle stuff, like Xbox Live cards and things, because I just...
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think it's... As much as I love Root Beer Tapper, it didn't get the same treatment a lot of the other games did.
[SPEAKER_05]: Therefore, I don't think it's as good of a value.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it pains me to say that.
[SPEAKER_04]: You mentioned that it's five bucks at the cheapest.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's how it is on the Virtual Console and Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_04]: What is with that?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, to me, that's still kind of expensive for a game that came out like 20 years ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: They made their money on it, they're just selling the bits over the internet.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of weird to me.
[SPEAKER_05]: A lot of people have been making the same complaints you have.
[SPEAKER_05]: Does a game like, I don't know, Tennis, and I'm not talking Wii Sports Tennis, I'm talking old school 8-bit Tennis.
[SPEAKER_05]: Does a game like Tennis really justify the same price as a game like Super Mario Bros.?
[SPEAKER_06]: Especially when I can go buy a Nintendo for pretty cheap and buy the cartridges for like 50 cents or less.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or even if you want to go the illegal route, download the ROM, which...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh, comments from our chatroom.
[SPEAKER_05]: JeremyTodd1 says, I hate Root Beer Tapper, but of course I didn't play it a long time ago, so that nostalgia factor isn't there.
[SPEAKER_05]: But whatever, I still think the game sucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh, Brad from PodCulture says, I've been playing the hell out of Root Beer Tapper.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fun times.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, differing opinions.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess download the demo, see if it's something you like.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, there you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a chatroom brawl breaking out over Root Beer Tapper.
[SPEAKER_05]: In fact, I think some Root Beer glasses have just been shattered.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why can't it just be Tapper with the beer?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because it was Budweiser and that was sponsored.
[SPEAKER_05]: And so you got product placement in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like why you couldn't do Mike Tyson's Punch-Out now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Same type of thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, that's because he bit people's ears off.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's why... Yeah, he's a cannibal.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, actually, Nintendo is going to be re-skinning Punch-Out!!
[SPEAKER_05]: and it's going to be Mike Tyson's ear-biting and women-raping actually is going to be coming out to the Wii Virtual Console for only $5, Eddie!
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to play like Oonga Boonga.
[SPEAKER_06]: Get the Wiimote and just, like, thrust it in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: For those who don't know what Oonga Boonga is, just...
[SPEAKER_08]: It's the finger up the ass game.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, just don't research it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't look it up on Wikipedia.
[SPEAKER_08]: You should totally see it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, man, Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can address those cards and letters to Loki at orangebonusradio.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's the finger up the ass for a tickets game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why can't we have ticket games like that over here?
[SPEAKER_06]: That'd be hilarious.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's go over and check in with Rice Princess and Casper the Gay and see if there's anything they've been playing this week real quick.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've been playing Ooga Booga, but, like, on my own body with someone else.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're disgusting.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I don't dispense tickets.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm just like, ooh, awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're disgusting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Eddie, what have you been playing this week?
[SPEAKER_05]: I've been playing Hot Sex.
[SPEAKER_05]: Are you guys drunk on this program tonight?
[SPEAKER_11]: They're high on life.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're wearing hats.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know this is radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe we can take some pictures and put them on the website.
[SPEAKER_05]: But they're wearing hats.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, like...
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, Rice Princess is wearing a frickin' Shamrock hat, and it's like not even March yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Eddie, uh, Eddie, Casper the Game, what have you been playing?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, big surprise, I downloaded, uh, Link the Bass when it came out on Virtual Console, but I was kinda mad, I was like, that was $8, I was like, holy crap.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I forgot.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've been playing Super Mario World.
[SPEAKER_05]: I beat it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I beat Super Mario World because I'm awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: You beat it last night.
[SPEAKER_05]: I used Star World to get there quickly.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, Rob.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've beaten Super Mario World 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_05]: About 10 years ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kiss my ass.
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: Boonga boonga my ass?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know where that's been.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll help you out there, Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: You guys are filthy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Explicit tag.
[SPEAKER_05]: Boonk.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: because, you know, it has to do with your butt, I guess.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, my God!
[SPEAKER_08]: I like your shirt.
[SPEAKER_08]: We watched the bullshit episode about the ass last night.
[SPEAKER_05]: Video games?
[SPEAKER_05]: Anybody?
[SPEAKER_05]: Does anybody play them?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm trying to segue into video games again by commenting on your shirt.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, sure, yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a lovely shirt.
[SPEAKER_05]: I am.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm wearing a very hot Tanuki shirt.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to pose for the camera right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Look at me.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm all sexy.
[SPEAKER_05]: God damn it.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can't even see the Tanuki when you do that, Rob.
[SPEAKER_09]: Move your fucking microphone.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is great radio, by the way.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, it's not at all.
[SPEAKER_05]: I swear to god I'm not making this up.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then the woman behind the counter was like, um...
[SPEAKER_05]: Was that the Mario where you, like, killed things with your tail?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I'm not sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I've been sitting behind here all day doing nothing, and it's starting to get in my brain, because nobody shops at Radio Shack.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, more pictures.
[SPEAKER_06]: I feel like... Do you want a satellite TV?
[SPEAKER_05]: I feel like Anna Nicole Smith, only alive.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is nice.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm taking a picture of Rob's shirt.
[SPEAKER_08]: Too soon?
[SPEAKER_08]: One, two, five.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ah, thank you.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's blurry, oh well.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, anyway, let's get into... And I'm not uploading it either.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's get into some actual gaming news, because we don't really have any housekeeping tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Visit our MySpace... Oh, you have some housekeeping?
[SPEAKER_05]: What do you want to say?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, just that you need some housekeeping.
[SPEAKER_05]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, save this show with some awesome exclusives.
[SPEAKER_05]: That would be, like, the best thing ever if you could, like,
[SPEAKER_05]: Give us some video game news no one's heard yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: How about the entire lineup for Xbox 360 from Microsoft this year?
[SPEAKER_06]: That'd be great.
[SPEAKER_06]: How about that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's start off then with Blue Dragon, which has been announced now for July 11th.
[SPEAKER_06]: So look forward to that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Project Sylphid on the 360 for May 16th.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tenchu Z coming out June 12th.
[SPEAKER_06]: 2 Human, also May 16th.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mass Effect, coming out May 30th.
[SPEAKER_06]: Shadowrun, June 13th.
[SPEAKER_06]: Forza 2 is slated for May 16th as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: Man, that's going to be a pretty big day.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I know Halo 3 is around that time too.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sure some of this stuff is going to move.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then on top of all those games we have coming out, of course,
[SPEAKER_06]: They're going to be having a 4,000 point live card coming out in April.
[SPEAKER_06]: So if you didn't really want to spend $20 on live points at the store, now you can spend $40 on live points at the store.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or, I actually know that's more than $50.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was kind of wondering at first why they would be doing this, but then I think the movie rentals, you know, you can spend a lot of points really quickly on the movie rentals.
[SPEAKER_05]: So folks that are downloading the HD movies, I can see... Those cards sell well because people buy them as gifts.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I can see that.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're like iTunes cards.
[SPEAKER_06]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that's going to be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tetris Evolution is actually coming out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Remember Tetris Grandmaster was one of the launch titles in Japan.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now it's making over here the cheapest 360 game I've seen.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is a retail price point of $29.99 when it's coming out in March.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_05]: A moment of applause, please, for this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Applause, please.
[SPEAKER_06]: Low price points are awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Got some bad news though.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mario Party 8 has been delayed to June.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or not June, May.
[SPEAKER_06]: May 15th.
[SPEAKER_05]: How do you know this?
[SPEAKER_06]: This is groundbreaking news.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because us distributors talk to the publishers on a daily basis, so they will give us updates to dates all the time.
[SPEAKER_06]: And even usually before press releases go out, we get announcements for stuff that hasn't been announced yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: or maybe announced at certain retail spots but no one's paying attention.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't worry guys, you can play Fusion Frenzy 2 in the meantime and then poop on it because it's bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because you had to play Fusion Frenzy.
[SPEAKER_06]: To be honest though, most of the Wii games coming out now have party games in them.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know Sonic the Hedgehog, the brand new one, Sonic and the Secret Rings has actually party games in it as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: They look kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, Rice Princess has a question.
[SPEAKER_09]: Are the Secret Rings
[SPEAKER_06]: And finally, the remakes of Final Fantasy 1 and 2 are slated for the PSP June 13th.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's huge!
[SPEAKER_06]: So that'll be pretty nice as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow, those are some huge dates you're giving us there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good job, Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I'm just glad to see that some actual games are coming out.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not sure if Microsoft's going to be stacking that many games in May.
[SPEAKER_06]: They might try to shuffle stuff around a little bit to kind of spread out the fun, but
[SPEAKER_06]: Lots of good stuff for the summer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you just paste that picture of my shirt?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's kind of blurry.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can see my big fat stomach in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's very nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: I got a cool shirt today.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some of the perks of being in our chat room live when the show is going on Sunday at 6 o'clock.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is Captain America for President.
[SPEAKER_08]: I love Captain America.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want a shirt that says Reggie Fils-Aimé for President.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'd vote for Captain America.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, damn it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rob, I hate you, and I've hated you for years.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, thank you.
[SPEAKER_09]: I love you, too.
[SPEAKER_09]: Aw, hugs.
[SPEAKER_09]: Don't really touch me, Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: What the hell is wrong with the program tonight?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, Fireboma says Sky needs to lose a good 200 pounds.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh!
[SPEAKER_09]: In related news, Fireboma just got kicked from chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you come back in, Fireboma, I'm going to sit on you.
[SPEAKER_05]: For those who have never seen Rob, he's like the skinniest man ever.
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_08]: The only way your ass would weigh 500 pounds is if you wore a metal diaper.
[SPEAKER_08]: And you pooped in it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, God, what is wrong with this program tonight?
[SPEAKER_09]: Shit, pure shit.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, um, I was just saying that I saw a really cute shirt that was, um, Caps Lock, Cruise Control for Awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I really want that shirt a lot.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait, what is that a reference to?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't even get it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do you know what Caps Lock is?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I know what the Caps Lock is, but... It's Cruise Control for Awesome!
[SPEAKER_09]: Hello, you don't get it?
[SPEAKER_09]: And I saw this other one where the front says Ding, and on the back it says Grapp.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alice in Wonderland
[SPEAKER_05]: This would be American McGee's Alice, as you know, being made into a movie.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, I apologize to the source, because I don't think I'm supposed to name the source.
[SPEAKER_05]: But if you wanted to be named, then I apologize.
[SPEAKER_05]: But this information is coming from a very trusted source of Orange Laundry, somebody I've been working with for a while, who just happened to come across this.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't really say how, but got to read the script, the current script as it is for Alice.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, keep in mind, these things change all the time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alice, as a child, is confronted by her parents due to her uncontrollable fascination with Wonderland.
[SPEAKER_05]: Against Alice's protest that Wonderland exists, Alice's father takes down possibly anything in her room that would insinuate any thought related to Wonderland.
[SPEAKER_05]: Later that night, the house is burned down and the only survivor found is Alice, splattered with blood on her body.
[SPEAKER_05]: Forward to the future, Alice is staying in a mental institution.
[SPEAKER_05]: An MD, Dr. Hatfield, get it, is interested in Alice and transfers her to another institution, even though doctors tell Hatfield that Alice is impossible to cure.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alice then begins a new treatment at the new institution, which is looking more and more abnormal to Alice.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alice's old meds are no longer given to her, the other patients are deranged, but one sane doctor named Doyle seems to be the only sane one, and Alice pleads to him for help as she claims she's not who or what she really is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alice's treatments are getting worse and crueler, and gets wind of Hatfield's surgeries.
[SPEAKER_05]: After escaping a scuffle from getting into her first surgery, she follows a rabbit she barely saw in the middle of her struggle and follows it into you-know-where.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, apparently there were some notes on the script as well, some possible movies, because some movie names were kind of written on here, some movies that this could be influenced from.
[SPEAKER_05]: Twelve Monkeys, Seven, Perfect Storm, Pan's Labyrinth, Jacob's Ladder, What Dreams May Come, Lord of the Rings.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then some bands were written on there as well, Nine Inch Nails, Ministry, Butthole Surfers,
[SPEAKER_05]: specifically Chris Vrena of Nine Inch Nails as well, electronic industrial hip-hop music, and then this is the movie genre, psycho horror action.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, what do you think?
[SPEAKER_05]: Sounds kind of neat?
[SPEAKER_05]: Sounds true to the game?
[SPEAKER_05]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_06]: It sounds neat.
[SPEAKER_06]: I haven't played the game, but it sounds neat.
[SPEAKER_05]: I did years ago, but I don't remember it very well.
[SPEAKER_08]: I watched a speedrun of the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you?
[SPEAKER_08]: It could be okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, so it sounds like it could be interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mention a movie I saw today.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_08]: I saw Pan's Labyrinth today.
[SPEAKER_05]: JV Mon says, this sounds awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it could be very interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Padrino says, I do believe it can be real since the scripts have to make the rounds.
[SPEAKER_05]: I believe it's real too.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I think, you know, as most scripts do, it's probably going to change a bunch before we see the final product.
[SPEAKER_05]: But there you have it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Your first look into what the Alice movie has in store.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: So how about some other news circulating the Internet this week?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, there's a little bit of happiness going on.
[SPEAKER_08]: For all of us who have been...
[SPEAKER_08]: Begging and pleading for Nintendo to do a kitty kitty version of Nintendogs.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, somebody else is doing it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Crave is putting out Purr Pals for the DS.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can choose 40 breeds of kitties and pet them and love them and call them George and you can raise them, you know.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's...
[SPEAKER_08]: It's funny, this mentions modifying cat behavior.
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, cats modify your behavior.
[SPEAKER_05]: Am I the only one disappointed that they did not call this Pussy Pals?
[SPEAKER_08]: I love that this article put up a cat macro, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: It says, where is your god now?
[SPEAKER_05]: Are you going to be picking up Purr Pals?
[SPEAKER_08]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can it do Nintendogs justice?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because...
[SPEAKER_04]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_08]: Kitty.
[SPEAKER_04]: The graphical style is totally different from like a Nintendog.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not realistic cats.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like cartoony alien cats.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, then never mind.
[SPEAKER_08]: They have a video of it on IGN.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have a video of it on other sites?
[SPEAKER_08]: I usually avoid IGN like the plague, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Except I got lots of Rondo of blood.
[SPEAKER_06]: They do have a lot of videos.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, there was a Cats game that's already been out on the DS.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can do the exact same thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's called Cats, with a Z at the end, you know, because they're extreme.
[SPEAKER_06]: They did a dogs one, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, they have the dogs, horses, hamsters.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wait, do these cats, like, go base jumping and, like, extreme snowboarding and stuff?
[SPEAKER_05]: They're hardcore cats.
[SPEAKER_05]: They do crystal meth and go to raves.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: They should have it like, you know, they should have it where the cats actually start scratching the DS and you're like, what the fuck?
[SPEAKER_06]: Why is your throw up in my DS?
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, just stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: They should hack up hairballs and then poo on your, you know, your bathroom rug.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course, the chat room is all clamoring out in unison for Love Hamster, which was a game we talked about.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hamster does not have a pee in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: TheRobD says, you're just an intent pussy, Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ha ha ha ha ha!
[SPEAKER_05]: you may want to seek a better copy from Codemasters I think it would be great if there were only 31 levels so they like send it in and it's only one more level and it's like oh okay gotcha thank you wow yeah and that's the same GS68 asks the same thing in chat but can you pass level 31 don't know so what do you think guys now do we do we ease up
[SPEAKER_05]: on the folks behind Bubble Bobble for the DS and not make any more level 30 jokes?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what I think it really was?
[SPEAKER_09]: I think they just didn't finish it on time, so they purposely made it so you couldn't pass 30, and so that gave them, like, more time to create more levels and stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: And they're like, yeah, now we've fixed it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, now you can totally get past level 30.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I've read an interesting theory about that this is just a reflection of the general laziness in QA and testing, because, like, what
[SPEAKER_05]: The 360 and other next-gen systems have allowed you to do it with patching.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because companies are too spoiled now with the whole patching thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: If bugs are discovered, eh, they can go back and patch it.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the problem is, you can't really patch a DS game without doing a massive recall.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, I mean, is this maybe why this happened?
[SPEAKER_05]: Possibly.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, they obviously didn't playtest it because if, you know, oh, I can't pass level 30, I just must suck.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's okay, other people will be better than I am.
So.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, moving on into other news.
[SPEAKER_05]: Speaking of big letdowns, you might remember we even got a call on this last week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Somebody had said, hey, what do you think Konami's big announcement is?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because remember we gave the rundown on Konami Gamers Day last week, right, about the show and all the games we played.
[SPEAKER_05]: But Konami had put on their site, hey, boys and girls, stay tuned until Monday because we got some big shit, yo, that we're going to be laying down.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know what it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: What was it?
[SPEAKER_09]: I know what it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: All got me this little USB Frogger controller, and all you have to do is plug it into the USB port and it installs the game and you can play it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm here to tell you, the game sucks balls.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, that's what we wanted for you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Horrible, horrible, sloppy, wrinkly balls is what this game sucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's horrid.
Ew, that's gross.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, like, I spent more time staring at the now-loading screen than I did actually playing the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, that's half the fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Was this, like, on clearance?
[SPEAKER_09]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, yeah, meaning yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Not.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not a dollar.
[SPEAKER_05]: Was it seriously four bucks?
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: It might be worth four bucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not to make fun of Konami or anything, but... Hey, look, we gave glowing reviews of Gamers Day last week, so I think I can say this shitty little $4 thing sucks, okay?
[SPEAKER_05]: They're not going to cry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you remember the first Gamers Day we went to, and even the second, like that summer thing, that they had a whole booth set up that they'd show you how to use the USB key thing?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm like...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: And then here was, here was the big announcement.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here was this quote.
[SPEAKER_05]: Last week, Konami announced new games in its Castlevania and DDR series.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to be an incredible 2007, so stay tuned to these pages for the latest from Konami.
[SPEAKER_05]: Chirp, chirp, chirp, chirp.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, everybody was thinking, oh, it's going to be the Metal Gear Solid 4 information.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, it's going to be Silent Hill Origins.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, Silent Hill 5.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, it was, hey, our big announcement is that we already made our announcements.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: What?
[SPEAKER_09]: That's it?
[SPEAKER_05]: That was it!
[SPEAKER_09]: Not even a reach around?
[SPEAKER_05]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm bitter.
[SPEAKER_05]: Free shitty USB Frogger games for everybody!
[SPEAKER_05]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_06]: If only Barman X Zero were $4.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm tempted to wrap this up in toilet paper and give it away on the station to a lucky listener.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is there going to be poop on that toilet?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, maybe.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ew, but I don't want it.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, maybe some Hershey's Kisses or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, anyway.
[SPEAKER_11]: From your butt.
[SPEAKER_05]: What is wrong with tonight's program?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like it's, oh, I know, it's that Rice Princess and Eddie the Gay are here, but this program's like off tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you say Eddie the Gay?
[SPEAKER_05]: Eddie the Gay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Eddie Casper the Gay.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's his full name, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: I know I'm awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, who's got the next story?
[SPEAKER_05]: Is it me?
[SPEAKER_05]: Your mom.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jamie, I believe it's you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not your mom.
[SPEAKER_08]: That would be wrong.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, looks like Activision has a hair up their ass.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because they're suing their own people.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, not really their own people.
[SPEAKER_08]: But they're suing people who worked on Guitar Hero now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Remember that whole big stink they were having with the Ant Commandos for the unlicensed guitar controller?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, they're suing them again.
[SPEAKER_08]: and also including as defendants some folks that were with Red Octane previously.
[SPEAKER_08]: That would be John Tam, Corey... Wasn't John Tam the dude that went to your house?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, he is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Huh, funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: He was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, not funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry, John.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not funny, but just interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Small world.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll just sit down and shut up.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also included is Corey Fong and Jamie Yang, who actually started another company that's working in conjunction with the Ant Commandos.
[SPEAKER_05]: So in other words, these guys left Red Octane to go work with the Ant Commandos on a yet unannounced game that probably has something to do with guitars.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, Activision is accusing them of copyright infringement, trademark infringement, misappropriating trade secrets, and confidential information, breach of contract, interference with construction relations, and being stinky.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm glad they don't remember, like, before 2005.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, just, hmm.
[SPEAKER_06]: Katara freaks.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ring a bell?
[SPEAKER_06]: Anybody?
[SPEAKER_06]: No?
[SPEAKER_08]: I even brought that up in a conversation.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, well, yeah, but we're different.
[SPEAKER_05]: No you're not!
[SPEAKER_05]: To be fair, they are.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, they have five buttons.
[SPEAKER_05]: Guitar Hero, no, it's more than that.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know it.
[SPEAKER_05]: The game has a completely different look and feel than Guitar Freaks does.
[SPEAKER_05]: and it's crossed over into popularity in a way.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry, Bomani fans.
[SPEAKER_05]: Guitar freaks could never do.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: If I put Keyboard Mania and made it look like Karaoke Revolution, oh, look, I got Keyboard Hero.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's all he fucking did is they changed the way the game looks.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, great.
[SPEAKER_06]: The notes come at me instead of straight up.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what other game did the exact same thing?
[SPEAKER_05]: In the groove.
[SPEAKER_05]: How is that different from you have a game like...
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know, you have a platformer game like Mario where he jumps and hits things, and then you have another game with a hero like, I don't know, The Legend of Kage where he jumps and hits things.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know, that's really obscure.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's exactly the same.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's exactly the same.
[SPEAKER_05]: So why isn't it a problem there?
[SPEAKER_06]: Mortal Kombat Mortal Kombat
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you, that's an excellent example, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: What about King of Fighters?
[SPEAKER_05]: What about World Heroes?
[SPEAKER_05]: What about Art of Fighting?
[SPEAKER_05]: What about Street Fighter?
[SPEAKER_08]: Art of Fighting, World Heroes, and King of Fighters were all SNK, so they can get away with it.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's what I'm saying, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: But they're all Street Fighter.
[SPEAKER_08]: Finn Fury actually had multi-plane fighting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, well, here's what I'm saying.
[SPEAKER_06]: If the fucking originators of Fatal Fury came out and said, Oh, we're pissed off that people are copying our game.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, fuck them.
[SPEAKER_06]: They were second in line or third in line.
[SPEAKER_06]: They have no room to talk.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just like, you know, if the originators of In the Groove came out and said, Oh, we're pissed off that, you know, Dance Factory came out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, fuck you.
[SPEAKER_08]: You copied someone else.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sighting games were actually around well before Street Fighter.
[SPEAKER_08]: But also, let's not forget, though, remember the old... How's this for obscure?
[SPEAKER_08]: Um...
[SPEAKER_08]: Pac-Man vs. KC Crazy Chase for the Odyssey 2.
[SPEAKER_08]: That game is now so hard to find because of being sued by Williams and Midway.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it's the same thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maze games have been around in a physical form before there were... Remember the old Mousetrap games?
[SPEAKER_08]: They existed beforehand.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just think it's just a double standard right now that they really...
[SPEAKER_09]: That's what this country was founded on, double standards.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, the whole problem is that Konami didn't do anything to protect their guitar freaks, patents or whatever they had there, so now they can't really stand on that.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I still think it's retarded that they're suing over this game.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: Harmonix is working on something else right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to blow this shit away, and then whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Everyone's going to get a big boner over that, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anywho.
[SPEAKER_06]: Speaking of Guitar Hero, Activision is definitely showing their interest in the Nintendo platforms, talking about doubling their, or aggressively targeting the Wii and DS for titles such as the Spider-Man, Shrek, etc., and talking about bringing Guitar Hero to the Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: Although, what I've been reading, though, is it might not actually be Guitar Hero, it might be some other guitar game.
[SPEAKER_06]: But still, though, yeah, I guess you could do that, but
[SPEAKER_06]: The DS, I don't know about that.
[SPEAKER_06]: That'd be kind of dumb.
[SPEAKER_06]: But we'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, how exactly do you do Guitar Hero on the DS?
[SPEAKER_05]: Tap, tap, tap, tap, tap, tap, tap.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's kind of dumb.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe something with like you hold the chords with the stylet.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's kind of lame.
[SPEAKER_05]: But then that's why I don't design games, I guess.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe I'll have a thumb peripheral.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, some other Konami music game related news.
[SPEAKER_05]: I should state, by the way, we were the first website anywhere
[SPEAKER_05]: and the planet to run the official song list of DDR Universe on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: The default song list, what it's going to look like there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Our very own staffer, Mel B, did some work on that and found that.
[SPEAKER_05]: So if you want to see that, head on over to orangeontrader.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very interesting lineup, I've got to say.
[SPEAKER_05]: Cascada, you know, Every Time We Touch is in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rapper's Delight by the Sugar Hill Gang is in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's got to be fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Kylie Minogue is in it as well, so it's going to be fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hope it has an equally retarded video like it did in Pump It Up.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was hilarious.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, I wanted to say this regarding official Konami music games.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's an interesting report on Bomani Style that was run earlier this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: We received our first confirmation from Betson that Beatmania 2DX Arcade will soon be testing in the next few weeks in Illinois at Brunswick Zone in Naperville.
[SPEAKER_05]: No version has been confirmed as of yet, although it is rumored to be Beatmania 2DX Gold.
[SPEAKER_05]: So,
[SPEAKER_05]: What this is basically saying is that possibly Betson could be distributing Beatmania 2DX gold here in the States.
[SPEAKER_05]: Usually Beatmania 2DX machines have to be imported from other countries, which is why you see them so, so rarely.
[SPEAKER_05]: But very interesting that they would do this now, because Konami didn't announce a Beatmania 2 at their Gamers Day, and they came out with Beatmania 1 last year, which makes me think, I don't know if a Beatmania 2 is coming out for the home.
[SPEAKER_05]: So what would be the strategy of them trying to release one in the arcades?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: What do you think, though?
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you think they should release Beatmania 2DX over here in the arcades, or do you think it's a lost cause?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, there's been places that's had it for years anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: But they're very niche places, you know?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, and the thing is that the majority of arcades are really going to be really lazy and not want to upkeep that type of machine.
[SPEAKER_08]: So if it's going to be around, it's only going to be at major places that are guaranteed to be well kept.
[SPEAKER_08]: Other than that, they're going to be wasting however many thousand dollars a machine is on something they don't want to keep up.
[SPEAKER_05]: JV Mon says get hype through the arcades and then people would be like, hey, I want to play that at home.
[SPEAKER_05]: So maybe this is a way for them to light a fire under the Beatmania franchise at home.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I had heard the series didn't do that bad, but the fact that they didn't announce a sequel kind of makes you worry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Eh, not really, because I'm wondering if they just don't know what they're going to do with platforms.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, if you think about it, say they haven't started a Beatmania 2 yet, where's the
[SPEAKER_06]: Say in November.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, they don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's kind of a risky thing to do.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's why there weren't really any PlayStation 2 games announced at Gamers Day.
[SPEAKER_05]: Gaming Nerd says something interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: 2DX barely gets any money in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_05]: to begin with.
[SPEAKER_05]: 2DX Gold will be no different.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, you know, what if they take the Beatmania 2DX machines out of the niche arcades that have them now?
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, the arcades that are willing to import games.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they put them in your local bowling alley.
[SPEAKER_05]: Your local other arcade would stand to make more.
[SPEAKER_05]: Plus, the machines are going to be cheaper if they're done here domestically.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're going to be half as much, I think.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just guessing.
[SPEAKER_05]: But they might stand to make more profit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just a thought.
[SPEAKER_06]: Unfortunately, those machines, it's just that they have the giant plasma screen on it and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, granted, there are a lot of machines nowadays that have giant plasma screens.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, you know,
[SPEAKER_06]: I know with Golfland, for example, when you have little kids fucking breaking that shit, replacing a plasma screen isn't cheap, and that's, you know, bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: One can only hope, though, that if we're going to get it, it's going to at least be in good shape.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I have a little bit of something that will be in good shape because, well, it's brand new.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we have our UK release dates.
[SPEAKER_08]: How's that sound?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yippee!
[SPEAKER_08]: Coming out on...
[SPEAKER_08]: The 16th is a bunch of stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: We have Armed Assault.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is it Arm A, I guess?
[SPEAKER_08]: Arthur and the Invisibles, Cartoon Network Racing, Excite Truck, God Hand, Infernal, Mario Hoops 3 on 3, Over the Hedge, Hammy Goes Nuts, Sherlock Holmes, The Awakened, Supreme Commander, Toko, Race Driver 3, and Tortuga, Two Treasures.
[SPEAKER_05]: Great.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, I seem kind of short.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, it's... Yeah, I guess it's a slow month.
[SPEAKER_06]: All at the same time, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm looking at the Japanese release dates.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're not much longer, but... Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, the U.S., it's a pretty decent week, at least.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to see some new stuff for the Wii with Wii Play.
[SPEAKER_06]: So if you're, you know, short or remote and need to buy one for cheap, Wii Play is the way to go.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then, of course, if you're not in or don't have a Wii, on PlayStation 2, Ghost Rider, which is kind of a ripoff of God of War, but...
[SPEAKER_06]: God of War is not a bad game, so definitely worth checking out.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's also cheap, only $29.99.
[SPEAKER_05]: I played Ghost Rider at E3.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know how much the game's changed.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, granted, it's been six months.
[SPEAKER_05]: That game sucked ass at E3.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry, it was horrid.
[SPEAKER_05]: It looks a lot better now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, that's encouraging, because maybe they took all the negative feedback from E3 and did some retooling.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_06]: It looks pretty... All right, then.
[SPEAKER_05]: I retract my statement.
[SPEAKER_05]: A game can change a lot in six months.
[SPEAKER_06]: It looks very similar to God of War-like.
[SPEAKER_06]: Very ripped off of God of War.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyways, The Warriors is coming out on PSP, and that's pretty inexpensive as well, only $19.99.
[SPEAKER_06]: So definitely check it out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ratchet & Clank Size Matters on the PSP, if you're a Ratchet & Clank fan.
[SPEAKER_06]: Galactic Civilizations 2 Dark Avatar, the expansion pack for that game is finally coming out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Test Drive Unlimited on PC, finally making its way to the market.
[SPEAKER_06]: Guramin, A Monstrous Adventure on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_06]: Brand new Atlus game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tom Clancy's Rainbow Six Vegas on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_06]: Lots of PSP love this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Monster Kingdom Jewel Summoner.
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Stop making comments behind me!
[SPEAKER_05]: No, we're not making comments at you.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm flashing my chest at Irene.
[SPEAKER_06]: Stop getting Irene excited.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's really...
[SPEAKER_06]: Really distracting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank God we're not a TV show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dream Lords on the PC.
[SPEAKER_06]: Brand new MMO.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then finally, a GameStop exclusive, Tulip.
[SPEAKER_06]: I gotta tell you, this game looks like... Wait, it's a GameStop exclusive?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a GameStop exclusive.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, Jesus.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it looks like a piece of... Wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_05]: I played this game at E3 like two years ago when it was first... It was cute.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, it isn't... Is it 1999?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because that might be okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, um, yeah, I mean, it isn't going to win any awards, but it was cute.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, you know what you're getting into, okay?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a game called Tulip, for Christ's sake.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a kissing simulator.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it's a kissing game.
[SPEAKER_05]: You go around, you kiss people.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, man, that's going to sell really well.
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's like a sexual harassment game.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's going to sell really well amongst the nerds, because they'll need practice kissing, because they don't kiss anyone else except for their moms.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's so wrong.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, Tulip is a $30 game.
$29.99.
[SPEAKER_05]: It'll be in the bargain bin in three weeks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know it and I know it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is that it?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Japanese games coming out on February 15th on the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's not a lot, actually, across the various systems.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nothing on 360 or any of that stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: But we have on PlayStation 2, Appleseed EX is coming out from Sega.
[SPEAKER_05]: They also are putting Castlevania Curse of Darkness into Konami Best Hits.
[SPEAKER_05]: I should also mention this game, Shining Force EXA is coming out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, Soul Cradle.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sekai Okuro Mano is coming out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Shut up, Irene.
[SPEAKER_05]: I butcher it every... That's why they have me do the Japanese release dates, because I can't pronounce any of them.
[SPEAKER_05]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_09]: I hate you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Zero no Tsukaima is coming out as well from Marvelous Entertainment on the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Coming out on the Nintendo DS, Bleach DS Second is coming out.
[SPEAKER_05]: And this game sounds like it might be fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Death Note, Kira Game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_08]: I want that.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's coming out.
[SPEAKER_05]: What the hell is Death Note?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't even know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Death Note is awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: What is it?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, thanks, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's really descriptive.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, well, fuck.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to pre-order that shit right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, shut up.
[SPEAKER_08]: Death Note is a manga done by the same one who did Hikaru no Go.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's really, really, really, really, really, really, really cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: They just did a movie, and they're working on a second movie, and the anime's out right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, it's
[SPEAKER_05]: It's super awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's about a guy who finds the notebook of a death god and then starts killing people.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that's all I'm going to say because everyone should be reading it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And if that's not your cup of tea, Luminous 2 is coming out on the PSP in Japan.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not sure what songs they got different than we did, but I know they have some other songs there instead.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think we read them on a previous episode.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you'll have to go back and look, because I'm feeling too lazy.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I do want to point out, also on Sony PSP, Tales of Destiny 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you're a Tales of Destiny fan, there you have it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, Rob.
[SPEAKER_09]: Domo Arigato for that news.
[SPEAKER_09]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, actually, why don't you reserve your Domo Arigato for DarkSakura, because she is going to give you her website of the week, and it's the place on the internet that you should definitely be checking out right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not mine to give.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, well, we do...
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the gift that keeps on giving here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's someone's sick and deranged website.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, well you've found it and you're highlighting it here for us.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, arigato, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's gonna kick you, Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: Isn't that what Scott over on All Games calls you?
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_05]: Dark... DarkBallSakura?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hearts, love ya.
[SPEAKER_08]: Are you done?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura's Hardcore Website of the Week!
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_07]: We should do that from now on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Today's website of the week is davidtenant.com.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dude, I want to look up the X music again.
[SPEAKER_08]: I missed that one.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, as I said, today's website of the week is davidtenant.com because I couldn't think of anything else.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, never mind.
[SPEAKER_05]: So much for the hardcore.
[SPEAKER_08]: Meow, meow, meow.
[SPEAKER_08]: That would be david-tenant.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: He is the man who plays the 10th Doctor on Doctor Who.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I love him.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's all.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think we should just change this feature to Doctor Who site of the week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, the Doctor Who website of the week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, I haven't done a Doctor Who site in like three months.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a bite my ass in a non-literal way.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, Rice Princess has a question.
[SPEAKER_09]: I do.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can I help you?
[SPEAKER_09]: Eddie wants to know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: In any of the Link... Well, it was just, what, Ocarina of Time and... No, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: What ended up being the only village in the land of Hyrule in the Zelda games, Irene and I pronounce it differently, and we're going to start a debate.
[SPEAKER_04]: I pronounce it Kakariko Village, and Irene pronounces it...
[SPEAKER_02]: Kakariko.
[SPEAKER_02]: It would be Kakariko.
[SPEAKER_04]: And she's Asian, so she's probably right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kakapoopi is what it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kakapoopi Village.
[SPEAKER_04]: All of us whiteys back in the 90s called it Kakariko Village.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, but if you read the kana, and the Japanese has pretty much even pronunciation on every syllable, it would be Kakariko.
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't know the village had a name.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you serious?
[SPEAKER_08]: That's exactly what I was going to say.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a village that has the chickens that you beat up that all attack you.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it is the village.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's what Kakariko means.
[SPEAKER_08]: It means town of chickens.
[SPEAKER_08]: Town of avenging chickens.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, speaking of avenging chickens, we have a brand new program that's being started by Microsoft and kind of teaming up with Old Spice Deodorant to...
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, the... No, I'm sorry, this is really funny, because you know that stereotype... Because any other game would be uncivilized.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, but you know, like, the gamer that's been sitting at home all day, racking up these $10... I'm sorry, finish your story, I apologize for interrupting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Then I'll make my deodorant joke.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're basically challenging Xbox Live users, who are in America, to add at least 1,500 achievement points to their gamer score between February 12th and April 12th.
[SPEAKER_06]: And depending on what your gamer score is now, starting off, that'll depend on what prize package you win.
[SPEAKER_06]: And here are the different prize packages for you that you could possibly earn by wasting this much time.
[SPEAKER_06]: If your gamer score is 0 to 4,999, you can earn a game picture, a dashboard theme, and Contra for Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ooh, that's level 1.
[SPEAKER_06]: Level 2, which is between 5,000 and 9,999 gamer points, you receive everything from the level 1 package, as well as 100 Microsoft points and a contest t-shirt.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh my god!
[SPEAKER_06]: That's awesome!
[SPEAKER_03]: Dude!
[SPEAKER_03]: Dude, I love your shirt!
[SPEAKER_06]: Anywho, if you have over 10,000 gamer points, you will earn...
[SPEAKER_06]: The Level 1 Package, 200 Microsoft Points, a T-Shirt, and Fusion Frenzy 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh my god!
[SPEAKER_03]: A T-Shirt!
[SPEAKER_03]: Dude!
[SPEAKER_03]: Dude, I gotta get that T-Shirt!
[SPEAKER_03]: That game fucking sucks, but I gotta get the T-Shirt!
[SPEAKER_05]: And by the way, we here at Orange Launch Radio are excited to announce that there's actually some secret levels that have not yet been unveiled, but here's the deal.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you have 20,000 gamer points or more, you're in level 4 and Old Spice will actually send you free deodorant because you probably need it if your gamer score has gotten to be that high.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm not going to include it in every level because all of these stink.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're like, no, no, no, we don't care about the prizes.
[SPEAKER_09]: We really just want to get the deodorant to you and we're masking it with the prizes.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: The best prizes in level 6, they actually send someone to punch you in the gob.
[SPEAKER_06]: To enter this wonderful contest, just simply go to xbox.com slash rewards and you can enter after the 12th.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hurry up and get those 1500 achievement points so you can score that wonderful Fusion Frenzy 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hooray.
[SPEAKER_05]: Travis Donovan from our Saturday night program here at Orange Lounge says, Worst product tie-in promo ever.
[SPEAKER_05]: BlackWolf from the other Sunday Night program on the other network, AllGames.com, says Level 3 package equals 830 point value plus t-shirt plus Bill Gates' favorite game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh my god, Fusion Frenzy 2 is Bill Gates' favorite game?
[SPEAKER_06]: What a loser.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's probably the only game he's played this year.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's like, that's my favorite game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mystic Gohan says, I'm so tired of hearing, wow, you play so much, your stink is going through the mic.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks, Old Spice!
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, something else that is going to cause people to not leave the house for today.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, I should ask real quick.
[SPEAKER_05]: Are you going to participate in this, Loki?
[SPEAKER_05]: Fuck no!
[SPEAKER_05]: Fusion Frenzy 2?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, but you're not at that level.
[SPEAKER_05]: Your gamer score is not 10,000.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know, free t-shirt.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to be playing Crackdown, so if I finish Crackdown that quick, I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: DDR Universe is going to be an easy 1,000 points.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow...
[SPEAKER_05]: The Halo 3 Beta Invite
[SPEAKER_05]: Halo 3 Beta invites the picture that are included with Crackdown, like the little slip that comes in has been leaked out to the internet.
[SPEAKER_05]: And here's the catch about the Halo 3 Beta.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have to have the Crackdown disc to be able to play the Halo 3 Beta.
[SPEAKER_05]: So no buying the game, taking the slip out for the Halo 3 thing, and then selling the game back.
[SPEAKER_05]: You actually have to hang on to the game, probably past the return window, to actually play the Halo 3 Beta online.
[SPEAKER_06]: And just another thing, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Halo 3 beta might not be available right as you pick up Crackdown.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I hope nobody's expecting that.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not going to be.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hope people don't think that's what's going to happen.
[SPEAKER_05]: It just means that you're going to get into the beta whenever it's available.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is that like a subtle way for them to let people know that they're cracking down on that returning...
[SPEAKER_05]: Say goodbye to Rice Princess, everyone.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the last show.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's nice knowing you, Rice Princess.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for playing.
[SPEAKER_05]: You lose.
[SPEAKER_05]: Failed.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, in other gaming news, there is a particular little game that a lot of people were sort of obsessed of that didn't go so well in Japan called LocoRoco.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, the sequel is now playable.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can go actually onto the website and there is a downloadable version available.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you download it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Not yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Are you going to?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I haven't been home.
[SPEAKER_05]: I see.
[SPEAKER_05]: She got her hair did this weekend.
[SPEAKER_08]: I got my hair did.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, there also is, though, a little bit of a rumor stating that it could be possible this will be a PS3 version, but honestly, I'm really thinking that it should just stay PSP, because that type of game really lends itself well to the PSP, especially, you know, since you're turning the six success, you know, is not going to be as much fun as
[SPEAKER_08]: The system itself.
[SPEAKER_08]: Rocking the system itself.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I'm hoping it'll go on PSP as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because PSP, you know, actually PSP's having a little bit of a resurgence with the Castlevania and some of these other games that are coming out.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's in Portable Ops and all these Konami's support behind PSP.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's actually becoming more and more like a system people ought to be checking out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Especially if a price cut is in the future.
[SPEAKER_06]: I bought another PSP.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_06]: I bought it off of a friend.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's this, your 4th?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I only have two now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Only?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, basically, this one is going to be... I'm going to put the Dark Alex firmware on there now.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's because my friend, he mistreats his PSP, so he broke the buttons and the analog sticks, so I have to fix that.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I bought it for three bucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: By the way, if you're listening to us on a PSP, you should visit olrpsp.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki hasn't updated it in about a year, but it's still pretty.
[SPEAKER_05]: And there's a background that you can download.
[SPEAKER_06]: There will be new stuff eventually.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sure, there will.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm working on stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right after you finish the Wii website, too, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, that has to do with the PSP.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow, that's lame.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is better than OPSP, really.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, well, some cool stuff, though, that you might be able to do in the future will include Skype.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because apparently...
[SPEAKER_06]: Speaking of the new firmwares coming out, they have dissected the firmware and they have found a little line of code here in 3.11 that says, it talks about the Skype plugin.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's something that will be coming out possibly later on, but that's kind of cool though.
[SPEAKER_06]: So Skype support coming soon to your PSP.
[SPEAKER_06]: How's that going to work?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because there's no microphone on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, they have headsets for it.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can use headsets for... Whatever happened to the DS thing that was like Skype?
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember when they showed that at E3?
[SPEAKER_05]: Like they had the Wi-Fi voice thing?
[SPEAKER_06]: Voice over IP?
[SPEAKER_06]: Just like they have in Metroid Prime Hunter?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, they put it in one game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Big wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, no, they have it in the new Diddy Kong Racing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think you're missing my point.
[SPEAKER_05]: My point is where is the standalone app where I can use this to call my friends across the U.S.
[SPEAKER_05]: for free?
[SPEAKER_06]: Rob, now if they had a standalone app, that would mean that they're embracing online.
[SPEAKER_06]: They don't want to let everyone know that they're embracing online.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a secret.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, because they haven't actually embraced online.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're actually making the internet harder, is what Nintendo does.
[SPEAKER_05]: You don't understand, Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: You don't understand.
[SPEAKER_06]: We connect 24.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's connected all the time.
[SPEAKER_06]: That means it's connected to...
[SPEAKER_06]: Something out there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Something that makes my Wii glow.
[SPEAKER_06]: But when I turn it on to see what that something is, there's nothing there.
[SPEAKER_06]: But shortly after I turn it on, there's stuff there.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just it lets me know soon there will be more stuff there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wake me up when the Wii downloads my porn for me.
[SPEAKER_06]: What the fuck is... Seriously, and I hate to go on a rant about it again, but what the fuck is up with Wii Connect 24?
[SPEAKER_06]: It doesn't download my messages.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't have current weather.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't have current news.
[SPEAKER_06]: It doesn't download any updates.
[SPEAKER_06]: What the fuck is it doing?
[SPEAKER_09]: Is your Wii on?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, my Wii is on.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it's devil power making it glow.
[SPEAKER_05]: You should be a Nintendo customer service rep.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've had the total opposite experience.
[SPEAKER_04]: My Wii starts glowing, I turn it on, and there's messages right there.
[SPEAKER_04]: All the updates are downloaded without me having to do anything, so I don't know what you're doing.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, but don't you have to click in and actually do the update manually?
[SPEAKER_05]: What?! !
[SPEAKER_04]: I've never had to do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you have the news channel on your Wii right now?
[SPEAKER_04]: I do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, when there's a new server, because they're not just going to do that without you wanting to do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the messages are there, the updates of like, yeah, it'll tell you right away.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was the thing, is that Wii Connect 24 is supposed to do all that shit without you having to think about it, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Not the extra apps, though, because you have to choose what apps you want.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, I'd be kind of mad if I won, and I was like, I don't want that app, and it was on there, you know?
[SPEAKER_04]: But like, the messages, I don't have to download them.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're already there when I turn it on.
[SPEAKER_06]: What if you don't want the internet browser?
[SPEAKER_06]: Too bad!
[SPEAKER_06]: Then don't download it!
[SPEAKER_06]: The internet browser you don't have to download.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's news and weather.
[SPEAKER_06]: You need your news and weather.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh yeah, I really need that really bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would like to take a quick poll of all the Wii owners in the room.
[SPEAKER_05]: How many times have you used the news channel and the forecast channel?
[SPEAKER_05]: I will go first.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've used the forecast channel twice and the news channel three times.
[SPEAKER_05]: And once was this week because I was looking for pictures of Anna Nicole Smith.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: I used the forecast channel once today, but it had weather from midnight, which said it was still raining, yet outside it's blurring sun, so apparently that was wrong.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Loki went outside in a huge parka going, Man, fuck the week!
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, how many times have you used the news channel and the forecast channel?
[SPEAKER_06]: She's holding up a big fat zero.
[SPEAKER_06]: Eddie?
[SPEAKER_05]: One time, when I first got it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dan just used it, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, every day?
[SPEAKER_08]: I just happened to be in the living room and he had it up while I was leaving.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, so once.
[SPEAKER_08]: More than that, but I saw it once.
[SPEAKER_09]: I haven't used either before, but I use the Foreskin channel a lot.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: The PSP and the PS3 networks will be joining together.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was coming from Phil Harrison.
[SPEAKER_05]: Quote, this year we'll be adding some functionality to the PSP that will unify our approach.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we really don't know what exactly that means yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: That means I don't have to buy a PlayStation 3 to download PlayStation 1 games to my PSP.
[SPEAKER_05]: If maybe that means that they'll have the same look and feel of the store or what's going on, but we don't really know.
[SPEAKER_06]: That means that the PlayStation Portable will actually have a network store, since it doesn't right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: That would be kind of nice, because the Sony website isn't even that great on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if you've gone to it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not that great.
[SPEAKER_06]: I try not to go to it, because it's lame.
[SPEAKER_06]: Lame.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm reading comments in chat room, by the way, who's giving some feedback on the whole debate we were having in here.
[SPEAKER_05]: James Patrick says, Forecast is good here in Texas.
[SPEAKER_05]: It told me it was going to rain a couple times.
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bershaz says, Wait, we are gamers.
[SPEAKER_05]: We are in the basement.
[SPEAKER_05]: No windows.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I forgot.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: How could I forget?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yeah, because we're on the second story.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well.
[SPEAKER_08]: I actually read an article last week about an HMV UK retailer who was doing a PSP, PS3 bundle.
[SPEAKER_08]: They have retracted it now due to consumer pissed-offness.
[SPEAKER_08]: They've heard the people... Is that the legal term?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, pissed-offness.
[SPEAKER_08]: They have heard the people.
[SPEAKER_08]: They have gone back and said that for anyone who's participated in the pre-order...
[SPEAKER_08]: They did this in response to customer demand.
[SPEAKER_05]: PMS of the Masses
[SPEAKER_06]: Which is kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: You tilt the screen around, moving the mother duck to collect the baby ducks and reach the end.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that will be coming sometime soon, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then, of course, they were talking about SingStar for the PlayStation 3 and how the PlayStation Store will be supporting that as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, no, that's not a big surprise.
[SPEAKER_06]: And of course, you know, also talking about how people will be able to create their own custom user pages, including video performances of them singing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I assume that you would need the eye toy for this, or the eye of judgment, or whatever, you know.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then, of course, they were talking about Will Simon Cowell be a part of the eye of judgment?
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought it was awful.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, they will not.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think you should take a gun and shoot yourself in the face.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then finally, the PlayStation 3 online platform will continue to evolve aggressively.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, that's great, because one game, or less than one game a month, kind of sucks right now with your PlayStation online store.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know people bitch about no updates to the Xbox 360's market, but geez.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, at least Xbox 360's getting stuff, you know, on a weekly basis at least.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have yet to see some new demos come to the PlayStation 3 store.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's early, I mean, for PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, Xbox was slow in the beginning as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I remember that, but still, though, I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't want to see an update.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, there's new stuff on the PlayStation store.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a new PS1 game that you can't play on the PS3.
[SPEAKER_06]: You need to play it on your PSP.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, fuck you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Raven's Dolphin says, Loki, I think the duck is a joke I do not know.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's the duck joke?
[SPEAKER_06]: The duck they showed at every new console launch.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like the tech demo that they had.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, the rubber duckie.
[SPEAKER_08]: The way they filled the tub with the rubber ducks to do how many on-screen polygons.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was on the very first disc, the PS position demo disc.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, speaking of PlayStation, at least the portable types, they're going to get you in trouble in New York City pretty soon, but don't worry, Sony fanboys, Nintendo DS is a fair game as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is the reason
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: It's legislation.
[SPEAKER_05]: It hasn't been passed yet, but it's on the table.
[SPEAKER_05]: You could be charged a $100 fine if you're using a PSP, a Nintendo DS, an iPod, a Blackberry, or a mobile phone all while crossing the road.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dangerous to use a device and walk?
[SPEAKER_06]: What about people driving?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, it's dangerous, too!
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: It is illegal there, too, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_05]: But, well, yeah, I mean, that's already illegal in New York City, but you have to remember... It's illegal here, too, Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: Keep in mind... Well, not yet, but it almost is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_05]: But keep this in mind, is that... I switched to speakerphone anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: Back off, lady!
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_06]: Who the fuck can play a game and walk in the first place is what I want to know, but, you know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: So they're doing it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some of our New York City living friends chime in on this in the chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ranma says, Sky, some people are too stupid to pay attention.
[SPEAKER_05]: You do not turn the volume up to the point where you cannot hear a honking horn.
[SPEAKER_05]: Legend of Zaku says, looks like this guy hasn't heard about natural selection.
[SPEAKER_05]: Amen to that.
[SPEAKER_05]: What do you guys think about this law?
[SPEAKER_05]: Is this a needed law?
[SPEAKER_05]: A necessity?
[SPEAKER_08]: I think...
[SPEAKER_08]: That Darwinism should just be let work because that would cleanse the gene pool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think we have to blame Grand Theft Auto for this because in Grand Theft Auto you run over people.
[SPEAKER_06]: So therefore, Grand Theft Auto is to blame because these people are getting run over by cars.
[SPEAKER_06]: It makes perfect sense.
[SPEAKER_06]: Where is the justice with these damn M-rated games?
[SPEAKER_06]: We need to take them off the shelves because clearly it's not incompetent people that are causing deaths.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is these M-rated games.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: I was thinking they shouldn't pass that so that people can still be getting hit by cars while they're doing that.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then I can just run over and take their PSP while they're on the ground, dying.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I'm like, yes, I have a PSP now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, you're so sympathetic.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I would totally do that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, me too.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like, you're stupid.
[SPEAKER_09]: You don't deserve one of these.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I sense the angst rising in this room.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you know what happens when the angst rises?
[SPEAKER_05]: People die.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's time for the FUs of the week here, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_08]: I love the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, then start us off.
[SPEAKER_08]: A big FU to the medical industry for being more interested in selling us drugs than actually fixing the problem.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because they give you all these drugs that do nothing but, you know, treat the symptoms or suppress the symptoms that your body, you know, creates to help you heal.
[SPEAKER_08]: And making us more and more and more and more and more dependent on them.
[SPEAKER_08]: When I think, you know, it's one thing that if you, like, say, have, like, diabetes and need insulin.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's one thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's chronic condition.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, like, if you have the flu...
[SPEAKER_08]: And think, oh my god, I need to take this drug and this drug and this drug and this drug When all you have to do is drink some tea, take some vitamin C, and take some time off work and sleep You don't need to pay the whole reason that the medical field is so fucked up right now Is because people are too dependent on treating symptoms I've learned so much since going into massage therapy about how the body works
[SPEAKER_08]: And also, if you're stressed out, take some fucking time and breathe.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're dumping adrenaline and other toxins into your liver.
[SPEAKER_08]: You are making yourself fucking sick.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just stop and breathe.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: Shut up, Firebomba.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fuck you.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't give happy endings.
[SPEAKER_05]: See, if you want to join our chatroom, you too can get yelled at by DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'd like to make a nephew to the Highway Patrol in California.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not very angry today.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fuck Activision for suing people over Guitar Hero, the completely original guitar game out there.
[SPEAKER_05]: My FU of the week goes to my doctor for not being available when I need her, and to the dentist for my temporary crown falling out a second time.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's just lovely.
[SPEAKER_05]: RicePrincess, do you have any FUs?
[SPEAKER_05]: Any angst you'd like to get off your chest?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I wanted to say F you too because you're playing this version of One Man Angel when you should be playing the piano version.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jamie's choice, not mine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you can play that one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, so it would be an honor if Amy and I remember that one.
[SPEAKER_05]: I do, but nobody else does.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that's okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, then we can refresh their memories by reenacting it on their own.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think I deleted that MP3.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think I'm going to punch you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh, Eddie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Eddie.
[SPEAKER_05]: Any F yous of the week you want to give?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, I'm F youing Whiney
[SPEAKER_01]: Immature Stray Girls was the only guys for me, so ha!
[SPEAKER_03]: Me too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well... Stupid Stray Girls.
[SPEAKER_05]: Look out!
[SPEAKER_09]: That was a good comeback, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: Look out!
[SPEAKER_09]: You need a third eye for that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nobody understands that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nobody on the internet.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know, I know, because no one listens to the Wednesday show.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jerk.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, I think now's a very good time to take a break.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know about you kids, but I think now's a good break time.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we're going to take a break right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll be back with more of Orange Lounge Radio right after this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and is podcast to the world twice a week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Stay tuned to our podcast feed for the conclusion of this week's Orange Lounge Radio.