[SPEAKER_00]: Tonight, February 18th, 2007, new arcade games are revealed, including Tekken 6 and Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_00]: Someone in the know violates Microsoft's partner, NetNDA, and could rare be developing something for a Nintendo platform?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello everybody out there on the internet and welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: We are that podcast dedicated to what you, the gamer, really want to know about and a little bit of gaming culture, geek culture, pop culture types affair.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm here to help you through the next few hours of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: My name is Rob Roberts and joining me as always, say hello to Jamie Summers, Dark Sakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whoa, the angsty, loud Dark Sakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_09]: I hate people.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry to hear it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why do you hate people?
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: and what I noticed is that I was very loud, so I apologize for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I've adjusted the audio for this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's okay, we're used to it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But on the playback, because it's a lowered bitrate on the podcast, it didn't sound as bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: It didn't sound as tin canny.
[SPEAKER_04]: As usual.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I don't think it'll be so bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: The show sucked, but I was good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's surprising.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I...
[SPEAKER_04]: What the... Doing it the whole time and you're like... Have you been like snorting crack today?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I had a frappuccino.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, goody.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's another one of those shows.
[SPEAKER_11]: A crackuccino.
[SPEAKER_04]: Say hello as well to Loki.
[SPEAKER_11]: I forgot that I turned the mic off so I didn't catch that last comment.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's why I didn't call you Tech Mask to Loki tonight because apparently you forgot how to work sound equipment.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_04]: The winner is you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_04]: We hope you have enjoyed.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know how to use sound equipment.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, we have some special guests with us in studio tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're extra special.
[SPEAKER_09]: They have their own bus.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be another very interesting week here at Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: The feedback from last week is that you guys liked a little bit of the silliness we had going on last week.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we brought some of the silliest people we know to the program.
[SPEAKER_04]: Say hello to one of the Orange Launch Radio... Oh, God damn it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I get the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, no mailbag for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: and also say hello to somebody brand new.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's losing her Orange Lounge cherry tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's brand new to the program.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Marissa.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_04]: How are you, Marissa?
[SPEAKER_09]: I love it when you talk nerdy to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Marissa is the originator of Utus Braziers.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would like to point out, whatever brazier Marissa has on tonight, you know, I might be gay, but I can't help but look.
[SPEAKER_08]: Marissa, you have to do it for the listeners so that they hear the original Utus Braziers.
[SPEAKER_01]: Should I do it right now or later?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sure, why not?
[SPEAKER_04]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, the Utus Braziers thing originated because...
[SPEAKER_01]: I am a A, B, C, D, E, F, G, H, A, B, H, H, H, H, no.
[SPEAKER_01]: For all you nerds out there, I am wearing a... I'm a geek too, I'm just a music geek.
[SPEAKER_01]: I am a double G. So my sisters were complaining about the types of bras that they get to wear.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I thought this was the most ridiculous thing ever, because it is awkward changing in the, uh, in the locker room.
[SPEAKER_01]: But they have all these choices, you know, Spangly this, and Clear Strats this, and that, and, you know, Zebra Bras, and all they get to wear are UTA'S BRAZERS!
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, Nazi bras from the Third Reich!
[SPEAKER_05]: You will wear them, and you will like them!
[SPEAKER_05]: In old country, teeth did not fly free.
[SPEAKER_05]: They were disciplined!
[SPEAKER_05]: And they stood at attention like rockets!
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's where I came from.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, we have our chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: We would never have a show complete without our chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is the chat room going insane?
[SPEAKER_04]: The minute Marissa said double G's.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alpha Catagram says double G. Shadows Liar says this is the best show ever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fireboma says keep this girl alright but now because the show is about video games we need to kind of confess Marissa you're not a hardcore gamer are you?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, because I've been depressed ever since they stopped making King's Quest.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, but so you did, you used to play like the old school adventure games, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, I was obsessed with it, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was obsessed with the, yeah, all of them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have you heard about the King's Quest fan project, the Silver Lining?
[SPEAKER_04]: We host the demo on Orangelandradio.com.
[SPEAKER_01]: I hadn't heard of the brand new one, although I downloaded, I guess, Tierra as opposed to Sierra made remakes of the really, really old school ones.
[SPEAKER_04]: I downloaded those.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think I remember, yeah, hearing about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_01]: It did get a little boring.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sometimes it's tough to live up to the classics, you know, when people say, oh, there's this new game out and it's like the classics, but then you play it and it's really not, you know.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's true, but I think a lot of the appeal of the adventure games was the humor.
[SPEAKER_01]: In Siberia, I kind of lacked that.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've been eaten by a grue.
[SPEAKER_04]: I gotta say, Jared J. in chat says, she loves King's Quest?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my god, marry me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Marissa's taken, yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh yes, but for a little self-whoring, myspace.com slash Marissa Mizell, M-A-R-I-S-S-A
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm a musician.
[SPEAKER_01]: Fuck you!
[SPEAKER_01]: And that whole thing?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's cool, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, I was going to say, as a legitimate musician, what do you think about Guitar Hero?
[SPEAKER_05]: Ho, ho, ho, ho, ho.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is this a good ho, ho, ho, or a bad ho, ho, ho?
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Really quickly, so we can get to the crux of the show here.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you think of Guitar Hero?
[SPEAKER_04]: Good thing, bad thing?
[SPEAKER_01]: I've already sworn on this show.
[SPEAKER_01]: Am I allowed to again?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's on the internet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck, shit, cock, cunt, piss, whore, whatever you want.
[SPEAKER_01]: I fucking hate Guitar Hero!
[SPEAKER_01]: No!
[SPEAKER_04]: Why do you hate Guitar Hero?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, I guess it's fun, but learning to play guitar gets you laid.
[SPEAKER_01]: Playing video game guitar does not.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, no, it's only good fun, and I like that it brings attention to classic music, but the most interesting part is that musicians suck at Guitar Hero, just like real dancers suck at DDR.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's true.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have videos of guys on the Internet playing their own songs on Guitar Heroes, and they fucking suck at them.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's sad.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's really, really funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: Megzi, when she has a Guitar Hero demo set up at her GameStop, and they sit there and they ask her, so does this teach you how to play a real guitar?
[SPEAKER_06]: She goes, no, it doesn't.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, but that's what it advertises.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it doesn't.
[SPEAKER_06]: And she has to get through to people to tell them it does not teach you how to play guitar.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would like to say Jared Jay has changed his mind on Marissa.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh shit, now I hate you.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I quote, I quote, go fuck a goat.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_01]: But classic rock is good.
[SPEAKER_04]: You'll learn to embrace when the listeners tell you to go fuck things.
[SPEAKER_01]: I like go fuck a cactus.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's my favorite.
[SPEAKER_01]: Does that give me any points?
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rice Princess is going to make a cameo real quick.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, I agree.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, Marissa Rice Princess.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry, I'm introducing myself.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, Chris.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice to meet you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, what's up, Rice Princess?
[SPEAKER_04]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, I'm sick.
[SPEAKER_04]: You brought a posse with you.
[SPEAKER_04]: What is this?
[SPEAKER_04]: I brought my posse.
[SPEAKER_04]: Introduce your posse real quick.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, this is Chance.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, what's up?
[SPEAKER_04]: Real quickly, because we're not going to have time to have air bands show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Chance, what type of games do you like?
[SPEAKER_03]: PS2 games, like RPG games.
[SPEAKER_03]: RPG games?
[SPEAKER_03]: Action games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow, and World of Warcraft?
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: How about, wait, board games, like Cold Step?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't play video games, do I?
[SPEAKER_04]: He doesn't play video games.
[SPEAKER_04]: He plays WoW.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're not picking him up on the mic either.
[SPEAKER_04]: But he says he doesn't play video games.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm Chris, and I am a butt.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, video games suck.
[SPEAKER_04]: And this is Heather.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, Heather.
[SPEAKER_04]: Come up real quick.
[SPEAKER_04]: How are you, Heather?
[SPEAKER_08]: Great, how are you?
[SPEAKER_04]: Good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you play video games?
[SPEAKER_08]: Kind of.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm a button masher, sorry to say.
[SPEAKER_04]: Button masher?
[SPEAKER_04]: What type of games do you play?
[SPEAKER_04]: Get the mic a little closer to your mouth.
[SPEAKER_08]: Halo, Soul Collaborator, Burnout.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you any good at Gears of War?
[SPEAKER_08]: Never played it.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're looking for some good players for Gears of War for something I can't talk about yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: But we need to put together a team for Gears of War, and I'm very scared.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pick that one up and check it out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: And let me know how it goes.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: So what is this now, Rice Princess?
[SPEAKER_04]: Is this like one of those swelled ego things after the last show?
[SPEAKER_04]: You got like a fan letter, and now you have this swelled ego.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: I got two.
[SPEAKER_04]: She has to have an entourage everywhere she goes.
[SPEAKER_07]: I got two fan letters now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I'm taking over your show now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry, Rob.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did you know that I'm moving in?
[SPEAKER_07]: Again?
[SPEAKER_04]: This will be the last week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hope you enjoyed the program while it lasted.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: Irene was here from show one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Irene, you were here for show one, weren't you?
[SPEAKER_04]: I totally was.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was three studios ago.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, seriously.
[SPEAKER_07]: I remember.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, well, just like old times, you should go clean my kitchen.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just like old times, I should punch you in your gob.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dan repaired our whodunit, so I actually played some pinball.
[SPEAKER_04]: I brought my PS2 over here and we never played it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I heard you brought it over here for Silent Hill, but the Miglatov was like, no, my panties are bunched too tight, I can't play Silent Hill tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I also brought Crazy Taxi and we didn't play it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Crazy money.
[SPEAKER_04]: For PS2?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can only play that on Dreamcast, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I just grabbed a handful of stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: Nothing else?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's kind of slow.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's alright, that's alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're a busy girl.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can't play games all the time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_11]: My gaming week was fun.
[SPEAKER_11]: I played all... Basically, I just played only Crackdown.
[SPEAKER_11]: The full Crackdown.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, you got the retail release, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, so you're one of those bastards that got it early.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because street dates don't apply to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, well, sorry.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, yeah, I'm about two-thirds way through the game already, and it's worth it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I really cannot wait until everyone else gets it so I can play some co-op.
[SPEAKER_11]: But it's actually pretty funny, because if you watch some of the AI, like, especially the AI drivers, they're horrible.
[SPEAKER_11]: In fact, I was trying to kill this one guy, and I heard all this crashing going on below me, and there was a freeway below me.
[SPEAKER_11]: So I, you know, got on the edge and looked down, and there was this giant pileup of cars, and you can actually see cars being ejected out of the tunnel and just getting thrown into the ocean.
[SPEAKER_11]: And it was hilarious, and I had nothing to do with it.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was just the crabby AI drivers...
[SPEAKER_11]: Just crash into each other and just launch cars into the air.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some crackdown comments from our chatroom at chat.orangelaunchradio.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: OLArmyBlaze says, Okay, well, whoop-de-fucking-do, Mr. I work in distribution.
[SPEAKER_04]: But JeremyTel1 has a serious question.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, is the game too easy like I think it will be?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, are all the bosses really easy to kill once you start leveling up?
[SPEAKER_11]: It gets harder as you go on because the first, the Los Maritos bosses are, you know, pretty easy.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_11]: If you want more of a challenge, play on a harder difficulty.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I think you'll be at least... Play through the whole game, and then if you want to go back and play it harder, definitely play the more challenging difficulties.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think, as it is, it gets kind of hard, especially when you get towards the last gang, the Asian gang.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's just, they're crazy, the amount of people that they throw at you.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know, it does get harder, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything else in your gaming week besides Crackdown?
[SPEAKER_04]: Crackdown?
[SPEAKER_11]: Grand Theft Auto Vice City stories still still after all this time oh yeah we'll be playing until the next game comes out alright one other question here Jay Dorian asks Loki how does the full games world compare to the demo how much bigger does it feel well the demo it was just pretty much half of the first island it's not even the whole first island and the game feels huge I mean like
[SPEAKER_11]: I can't recognize certain areas of the game.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, you can get lost pretty easy in it.
[SPEAKER_11]: So it does feel very large.
[SPEAKER_11]: There's a ton of places to explore.
[SPEAKER_11]: I've been practically everywhere in the first two islands or whatever.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I've only found about less than a third of the secret orbs and just over half of the agility orbs.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I've already maxed out my...
[SPEAKER_11]: Strength, and I'm about to max out my explosives.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, I mean, there's just a ton of stuff to explore.
[SPEAKER_11]: I did like the achievement.
[SPEAKER_11]: There's one achievement for killing people with this globe.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's a giant globe that you find at the observatory.
[SPEAKER_11]: No.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's like a giant metal globe, and you have to kill 15 people with it, and that was fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: You bowl them over or something?
[SPEAKER_11]: Something like that.
[SPEAKER_11]: You basically kind of toss it onto them.
[SPEAKER_09]: Throw it at their head.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, throw it at their head Interesting I kill people all the time by throwing things at their head
[SPEAKER_11]: The fun part's going to be coming to, I think, the co-op gameplay, because you can just run around and do whatever the fuck you want in that game.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's going to be fun, and what's kind of neat about it, and you don't really notice this in the demo, the full game, you can actually have people jump in and out of your game while you're playing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I heard about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That sounds pretty intuitive, but is that as good as it sounds, you think?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, it's just going to be people jumping in and out, and you don't necessarily have to play with them.
[SPEAKER_11]: They can go fuck around your city or whatever.
[SPEAKER_11]: So that's going to be kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: I remember hearing a long time ago one of the first downloads that they were going to have for Crackdown was a replay editor or something like that where you can record your own gameplay.
[SPEAKER_11]: So that might be pretty fun to share that with people.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything else?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Real quickly, I haven't done a lot this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: I finally have taken a WoW character, World of Warcraft, further than I ever have before.
[SPEAKER_04]: My character...
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't have Burning Crusade yet because I don't see the point of getting it if I'm not gonna...
[SPEAKER_04]: Blood Elves are awesome, but seriously, on my server, everyone is playing Blood Elves.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everyone.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then I also play Paperboy, which is awesome, on the Xbox 360, the old game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It translates pretty well to the Xbox 360, I gotta say.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because the game itself was kind of widescreen, like a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like if you remember the old cabinet it was in, it was kind of widescreen.
[SPEAKER_04]: So they didn't have to smoosh it or anything, and the vertical bars aren't quite as big.
[SPEAKER_04]: The achievements are kind of smart.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're not like really super duper easy, but not super duper hard either like the previous games.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I think Paperboy itself was a much harder game than I remember.
[SPEAKER_04]: Paperboy is one of those like few truly original games.
[SPEAKER_04]: So definitely I recommend you guys check out the demo if you're 360 owners.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because if you never played Paperboy, at least, you know, play the first level that the demo gives you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think you'll find it's creative enough and original enough of a game to necessitate buying the full game.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they have co-op modes, and I think there's a competitive mode, I can't remember, because I haven't taken it online yet, because most of my week's been on Warcraft, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_04]: I tried to get more achievements in Fusion Frenzy 2, but honestly, I couldn't tolerate the game long enough to do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, I got so fed up, I was like, oh my god, this game sucks, I turned it off.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was like, it's not worth it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't care what achievement point challenges are going on right now, I will earn them somewhere else.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fusion Frenzy 2 is just that bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sigh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Chris, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_06]: I have become a World of Warcraft nerd.
[SPEAKER_04]: Congratulations!
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, clap for me.
[SPEAKER_06]: I need it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, yeah, I just, I'm on only two of the servers, which is, one is the noob one, which is where everyone starts out, Hydraxis, I think.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, I can't pronounce names.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I've got like ten characters on there that haven't even reached level fifteen.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right, you gotta start somewhere.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, and then I've got, but I have Burning Crusades, because if I'm gonna get it, I'm gonna get all of it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's really funny, on both the elves, because, you know, when you start off a new character, they all start with that little cinema, and they all say it with the elves, it's like, it's like the elves, like, the last of their races, everybody is a fucking elf.
[SPEAKER_06]: Everyone is a blood elf, everyone is a night elf, they're all, like, they're all over the frickin' place.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like, oh, last of my, last of the race, my ass.
[SPEAKER_06]: But the Draenei, oh my god, I don't care what anyone says, those things are hot.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love the Draenei.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Draenei girls are pretty hot.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ugh, their Russian accents make me horny.
[SPEAKER_04]: Please don't hold back.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love those things so much.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think they were supposed to be something else, but I like them being aliens.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's amusing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Every time I hear the Draenei females speak, though, I can't help but think, Boris, look, it's Musa and Drew.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, it was Musa and Drew.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not Another Age.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, I just love those things.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, if anyone wants to find me, I mean...
[SPEAKER_06]: Go to Jamie's MySpace.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm on MySpace.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're in my top eight.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm in her top eight.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're in the Orange Lounge top, actually.
[SPEAKER_06]: I am?
[SPEAKER_04]: You are.
[SPEAKER_06]: I feel so special.
[SPEAKER_06]: Send me a note.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll tell you who I am.
[SPEAKER_06]: Seriously, I suck.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know how to type in general yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: So if somebody knows, please inform me.
[SPEAKER_06]: I seriously don't.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know how to type.
[SPEAKER_04]: You type slash one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: Slash one, space, and then whatever you want to say.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, goddammit.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like interesting things pop up, and it's really funny when the horde shows up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, so I'm on the Horde side, definitely.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, of course.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've got both, but... Now that they have Blood Elves, you're starting to see a lot of the noobness on the Horde side.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Blood Elf males are the only ones that I can stand because they're not all butch.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, they're very gay.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know, I love them.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're so... It's like, can I help you?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm looking and Uni is jumping up and down going, ooh, it's slash one, type slash one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uni's being very helpful.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: She's noob friendly.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some people come up to me, you know what, that game is the most, WoW is the most frustrating fucking game in the world because there are people walking around you and I'm not used to that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not used to MMOs.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've never played them.
[SPEAKER_06]: And so somebody comes up to me, do you want to duel?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, thank you, decline.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't give me that look!
[SPEAKER_04]: God, she gives me that look every time I offer to pay for something!
[SPEAKER_04]: Shut up!
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll talk about it after the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I got that look.
[SPEAKER_04]: All you need to do is some sweet lovin'.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I'm going to go on break right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, we'll be right back, guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow, wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is the hottest episode of Orange Lounge ever.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't believe we're offering to eat pussy over World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_04]: Girls are going to eat each other out over World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_04]: Name one other place on the internet you will ever find this.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey, to quote Randall, I love the cock.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just had to defend myself here.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cock love and Marissa.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_08]: How many of us have shoes off?
[SPEAKER_04]: I have my shoes off.
[SPEAKER_05]: My half-Japanese boyfriend would kick my ass.
[SPEAKER_04]: Marissa takes off her shoes, then it's a Mississippi orgy?
[SPEAKER_04]: Mississippi orgy!
[SPEAKER_04]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_04]: Explain the Mississippi orgy thing again for anybody who's new.
[SPEAKER_09]: State law in Mississippi is that if three or more people, and at least one of them is, I think, nope, it's three or more people with one person of an opposite gender in the room, it's an orgy.
[SPEAKER_09]: With your socks and shoes off.
[SPEAKER_09]: or with your shoes off, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: We are having a Mississippi orgy on Orange Sound Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jeremy Todd 1 says, I disagree, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: The episode with the Mississippi orgy was the hottest episode ever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, here you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's why I told Marissa to take off her shoes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Return of the Mississippi orgy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now we need some shine and we're set!
[SPEAKER_01]: So yeah, that's the first gaming system where I actually went, ooh, I want it.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, this is a very profound thing we're talking about here because, you know, you read – from our perspective as hardcore gamers, you're always reading on the game blogs about Nintendo's trying to get the casual gamers back into gaming.
[SPEAKER_04]: How can we get the casual gamers back into gaming?
[SPEAKER_04]: So I ask you, what – I mean, you're saying the DS is the first system you have ever bought with your own money.
[SPEAKER_04]: What –
[SPEAKER_04]: What made you do it?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, I've always been broke, so that has something to do with the fact that I didn't have one before.
[SPEAKER_01]: But quite frankly, a lot of, I mean, no, PC gaming isn't the equivalent to an entire, you know, to a game system.
[SPEAKER_09]: She wants Link's ass.
[SPEAKER_09]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: TheRobD says, every chick I know is excited about the Wii.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know every chick.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, the gaming system, never mind.
[SPEAKER_01]: Get it?
[SPEAKER_01]: Uh-huh, uh-huh, give me that.
[SPEAKER_01]: But the DS just offered something completely new as far as the touchscreen interface, and you could play a game away in advance, which was cool, you know, double deal.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it's accessible.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, it really is for people like me who are kind of dyslexic and all the buttons and the functions, etc.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, and that's what they say sometimes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it the fact that you look at an Xbox 360 controller and you're like, too many buttons.
[SPEAKER_04]: What the fuck is that?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a spaceship.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, the original controller was a fucking spaceship.
[SPEAKER_01]: For the original Xbox, it is.
[SPEAKER_01]: But yeah, I mean, I think it could potentially get people into gaming again because it seems like...
[SPEAKER_01]: There isn't a single, I mean, I'm sure that there can be some recommendations, but there aren't a lot of mainstream ways to just completely reintroduce somebody into gaming who's used to the, you know, classic Nintendo, ah, God bless it, you know, two-button interface.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, I think that the Wii is a great, you know, I think they ultimately could become more successful with more complicated gaming, etc.
[SPEAKER_01]: But, Cooking Mama is fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, God, not another one.
[SPEAKER_01]: Cooking Mama.
[SPEAKER_01]: Don't worry, Mama will fix it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm burnt out on it, though, I will admit.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want off this show.
[SPEAKER_09]: A very special listener sent me pictures of Mama cosplay, which you'll hear about later.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can I tell the Mama cosplayer?
[SPEAKER_09]: Go outside, please.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's on my phone.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll show you the Mama Con.
[SPEAKER_04]: You also need to go outside.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: You need to bite my ass, but to quote Chris in a non-little sense.
[SPEAKER_01]: I do have to complain, though, and this is really old-school gaming, but my friend told me to try to get into RPGs to try Morrowind, and I bought a video game to play, not to read.
[SPEAKER_01]: Not to walk every fucking where.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just had to say that.
[SPEAKER_09]: However, here's a really awesome picture of me in a hat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have you ever... Actually, speaking more, have you ever played Elder Scrolls Oblivion?
[SPEAKER_04]: Ever?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, it's kind of an adventure game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's pretty as hell.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll have to show it to you someday.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I haven't.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's very pretty.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's very... It's fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, I don't have an Xbox, but Chris has an Xbox, yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's for 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: He plays black all the time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's doing that cosplay?
[SPEAKER_04]: Do we know?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's some convention.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, is that something Rama sent you from the... Oh, my bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Am I not supposed to spoil?
[SPEAKER_01]: For the record.
[SPEAKER_01]: I love that look, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stop pouting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bad Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: So cute.
[SPEAKER_09]: Bad Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, then let's keep the show moving so we can get to some news and whatever it is Jamie's keeping secret.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll show you movement, bowel movement.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, anyhow, let's get to some gaming news, thankfully.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, God, yes, we need some gaming news here on this program.
[SPEAKER_04]: So who's going to start us off tonight?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I think.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, we actually talk about games once in a while.
[SPEAKER_04]: In fact, get this.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what, Chris?
[SPEAKER_04]: We actually get some exclusives.
[SPEAKER_04]: Things you haven't heard anywhere else yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh my god, really?
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's amazing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki's going to tell us.
[SPEAKER_09]: Never mind.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why don't you all go back to whatever you were doing before?
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyways, so...
[SPEAKER_11]: Like last week how we had some exclusive dates for the Microsoft games, today we come with a brand new company, Midway.
[SPEAKER_11]: We have a whole lineup for their games.
[SPEAKER_11]: And the core subject of the change, you know, like a certain Halo 3 date, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which I still believe that that game Oh yes, I forgot to mention, the Halo 3 official teaser came out this week And there it is right there, Fall 2007 And Loki had said on this show previously, what, April or May or something?
[SPEAKER_11]: May, but Wrong!
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, here's why, okay, and I have a couple reasons why I think they're doing this One, it's a big Christmas, you know, they don't have a big Christmas game coming out
[SPEAKER_11]: 2.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think they thought that the PlayStation 3 was going to be in a better position to, you know, where there might actually be a threat.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, right now I don't see PlayStation 3s flying off the shelves, and they certainly don't have the lineup for it, so...
[SPEAKER_11]: You don't need to put the game out right now.
[SPEAKER_11]: And to be honest, I think the game will probably be done by May, but they'll just hold it until Christmas so they can capitalize on that stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: So lesson learned about the distribution dates.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, we've said it before.
[SPEAKER_04]: This isn't anything we didn't tell you when we said the Halo 3 the first time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dates are subject to change.
[SPEAKER_04]: Retailers push things back all the time.
[SPEAKER_04]: You read about this on blogs.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we can tell you how things are now, but unforeseen circumstances will push things back.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_11]: Also, we'll be getting Hour of Victory on the Xbox 360, yet another World War II first-person shooter.
[SPEAKER_11]: Also, Blacksite Area 51, also scheduled for September, September 12th, on PlayStation 3 and 360.
[SPEAKER_11]: Also, in September, Unreal Tournament 3 on the 360.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's the 19th.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then Mortal Kombat's coming out on the DS on October 17th.
[SPEAKER_11]: Why?
[SPEAKER_11]: Because they can.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, has there ever been a good handheld Mortal Kombat?
[SPEAKER_04]: Ever?
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, if you have a Nomad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, I don't.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, a Nomad's just a Genesis.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you said handheld.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's cheating.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it's not.
[SPEAKER_04]: You cheated.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyways, um... You're a cheating cheater.
[SPEAKER_11]: Also scheduled the same date, Wheelman on PlayStation 3 and 360.
[SPEAKER_11]: That brand new Vin Diesel movie slash game.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's going to be coming out.
[SPEAKER_11]: Some other interesting stuff from Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're going to have the official Nintendo headset for the DS coming out April 22nd.
[SPEAKER_11]: And a couple delays.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, actually, one delay here for you.
[SPEAKER_11]: MLB 07, the show for the PlayStation 3, has been delayed to April 24th.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Lots of dates.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well thank you very much for those dates.
[SPEAKER_04]: Looking in the chatroom, Fireboma says Mortal Kombat better be Wi-Fi.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe that's the reason to have an idea.
[SPEAKER_09]: I should take Dark Resurrection.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's a good point.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who said that?
[SPEAKER_09]: That is a good point.
[SPEAKER_11]: There was also Mortal Kombat Deceptions Unchained on the PSP that came out in November.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, so I think back to those crappy Game Boy ones.
[SPEAKER_04]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Surely you played...
[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_04]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all you have, though, is there was a little teaser poster that just said Dance Dance Revolution Supernova 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's really all we know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's coming, but that's a good sign.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you surprised?
[SPEAKER_04]: For me, yes, because it's arcade.
[SPEAKER_04]: If this was a home version, no, that's not a surprise at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: But as far as a arcade release goes, yeah, I think it is a little bit of a surprise because of the fact that DDR took such a long break, I think, to get a new game announced so quickly, despite the rumors of the 200, 300 song expansion, whatever it is, which is probably this, that, you know, I think it's great.
[SPEAKER_11]: I wonder what that says, because I can't read Japanese, obviously.
[SPEAKER_11]: So it says 2000, I wonder if it's like spring, fall, you know, summer.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let me give it a look, but I will do that after I deliver some other news to us.
[SPEAKER_11]: And why the hell does this look like, I want to say, like some crappy Pokemon logo or something.
[SPEAKER_09]: Where's the damn poster?
[SPEAKER_11]: Because Pokemon's very lame.
[SPEAKER_04]: Chris has problems with you calling Pokemon lame.
[SPEAKER_06]: Pokemon is the only game that I really, truly loved first.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, DDR Supernova 2, I think it's going to be a Jewish game if you notice there's almost like a Star of David in the background there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_09]: Our resident Jew in the room has made a face in regards to that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, Loki's married to a Jew, too, so he gets to make the jokes through proxy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's into Judaism, if you know what I mean.
[SPEAKER_06]: Marissa's boyfriend is half Japanese with a very Japanese mother, so she gets to make all the Japanese jokes, so she's okay by proxy, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do I get to make Jewish jokes because I know you?
[SPEAKER_08]: Damn it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, I do believe that that says, looking at that, that is, I want to say Winter.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm pretty sure that that's the kanji for 2007 Winter.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kyle Snyder's in chat, who's somewhat of a well-known DDR persona.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, Kyle!
[SPEAKER_04]: And he thinks the following will show up in Supernova 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: These are the official Kyle Snyder predictions.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fly Away Remix, Stargate Heaven, Future Love Mix, Flow, Jam & Reggae Mix, VJ Army, G2, and Outer Limits.
[SPEAKER_09]: I wouldn't mind if DJ Ranma showed up.
[SPEAKER_09]: That would be rad.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, you know what else is absolutely, completely, 100% rad and even more super cool than DDR?
[SPEAKER_03]: Me.
Me!
[SPEAKER_09]: Your mom is cooler than DDR.
[SPEAKER_09]: Which is true because I like your mom.
[SPEAKER_09]: Your mom's really cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: But not in a, you know... Not in a homosexual way.
[SPEAKER_09]: Not in an MILF way.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, but, uh, Silent Hill is coming to the arcade, and yes, I know, everybody already knows about it, so shut up.
[SPEAKER_04]: There is... Orange Lounge Radio, reporting the news you already know about.
[SPEAKER_09]: There is, uh, Silent Hill, um, in development for the arcade, um, not really major, too much about it out, it's just called Silent Hill the Arcade, um, supposed to be a gun game with a big curtain around it, and... Ooh, Pyramid Head.
[SPEAKER_09]: But, um...
[SPEAKER_09]: It looks really blurry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I'm thinking it's just going for the look of Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, it's probably going to be foggy and have that whole ambience to it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sorry, the PlayStation 2 looked better than that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That curtain's got to go.
[SPEAKER_04]: That curtain isn't going to last.
[SPEAKER_04]: That curtain that's on the thing, though, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Little kids at Golf Land will rip that shit off in five seconds.
[SPEAKER_09]: But my whole fear regarding this, though, is that it's going to turn and it's going to be like a House of the Dead clone and it better not be.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or I will personally go to Konami of Japan with a tank.
[SPEAKER_09]: I will tape that.
[SPEAKER_04]: If Akira Yamaoka has anything to do with this, I'm okay with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I know, I respect that man so much.
[SPEAKER_09]: If it's really cool, I will personally, I mean, hug him.
[SPEAKER_04]: Marissa, you a big Silent Hill, you a Silent Hill fan?
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm sorry, Chris, I'm not making it up to you.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't go see a lot of movies, not because I'm a hermit, because I don't like paying $8 and seeing a movie that sucks.
[SPEAKER_01]: I drive my feet stick to the floor and smell a vomit or whatever else goes on in the theater.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, I haven't seen a lot of movies.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you like scary games?
[SPEAKER_04]: You ever thought about playing a scary video game?
[SPEAKER_01]: I was the best girlfriend in the world when I bought my boyfriend, who couldn't afford anything.
[SPEAKER_01]: I bought him a... Neither could I, technically.
[SPEAKER_01]: I bought him a GameCube and... Goddammit, I'm having a total... Eternal Darkness.
[SPEAKER_01]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_04]: Resident Evil 4.
[SPEAKER_01]: I bought him Resident Evil for the GameCube and he just had a heart attack.
[SPEAKER_01]: This ain't a cutscene!
Resident Evil!
[SPEAKER_10]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: I like the suspenseful games, but sometimes they can just piss you off.
[SPEAKER_01]: And make you want to kill something, like in the game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like Trauma Center.
[SPEAKER_01]: Trauma Center is amazing.
[SPEAKER_01]: Trauma Center makes you want to kill things.
[SPEAKER_06]: Stab your knife into the patient.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love, that's my favorite thing to do when I get frustrated in Trauma Centers.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just whip out the scalpel and go...
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what I like to do in trauma center now that I'm in school to be a massage therapist?
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's begin the operation.
[SPEAKER_09]: I like tracing out their muscles because I know where they are now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Blaze says trauma center equals love.
[SPEAKER_09]: By the way, just because I'm proud of myself, I made a 92 on my anatomy test.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_04]: Back to games.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey, can I get some technical geek on?
[SPEAKER_01]: Is that a SM58?
[SPEAKER_01]: Do we have...
[SPEAKER_09]: I have no idea.
[SPEAKER_09]: I totally know how to relax the piriformis when you have sciatic pain.
[SPEAKER_04]: Speaking of Silent Hill, when does this come out?
[SPEAKER_04]: Do we know?
[SPEAKER_09]: I did know, and then I closed the article.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me down.
[SPEAKER_09]: No!
[SPEAKER_09]: No, they don't actually say.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just hope the curtain was just to protect...
[SPEAKER_04]: The Press at this arcade show because that curtain is so ugly.
[SPEAKER_09]: It would only be in America that the curtain would be in anything.
[SPEAKER_11]: The curtain was basically to give it a dark, eerie feeling.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's what the reasoning for the curtain is.
[SPEAKER_04]: The curtain gives you the feeling of playing it in a hefty bag.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what the curtain gives you the feeling of.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: If they want to really make it a thing, they should do it like how that crap-tastic Jurassic Park game is.
[SPEAKER_09]: Where you can sit down.
[SPEAKER_04]: All I want to do is...
[SPEAKER_04]: If they come out with the typing of the Silent Hill... No, it would be Silent Hill the typing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will retire from video game everything because everything I need in the world has been done.
[SPEAKER_09]: I still play Typing of the Dead.
[SPEAKER_11]: What if it were like Guitar Freaks crossed with Silent Hill?
[SPEAKER_11]: That's stupid.
[SPEAKER_09]: It would be keytar.
[SPEAKER_09]: Pyramid Head rocks out.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, you have to fight them with the power of rock.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, it would be, it would, I got it, I got it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's Guitaruman gone lame.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, it'd be, we should have SilentKitar.
[SPEAKER_09]: Cassio the Shooting!
[SPEAKER_09]: You can kill them with hollow notes, okay?
That's what you can do.
[SPEAKER_09]: Speaking of... Dude, you can kill anyone with hollow notes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Speaking of... If you really want to go for the murder, sorry.
[SPEAKER_11]: Speaking of slightly lame, let's talk about Tekken 6.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, Tekken 6 is slightly lame.
[SPEAKER_11]: Why?
[SPEAKER_11]: Because the screenshots and the trailer that they've shown of it look kind of lame.
[SPEAKER_11]: And not even really up to par to Virtua Fighter 5.
[SPEAKER_11]: But nonetheless, we'll be coming to arcades soon.
[SPEAKER_11]: And we'll be featuring also two new characters, Leo and Zafina.
[SPEAKER_11]: Both which look very generic.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, hooray.
[SPEAKER_11]: But it looks like it will have the same visual quality of Tekken 5 Dark Resurrection...
[SPEAKER_04]: and, um... Okay, um, wait, wait, what were the characters' names again?
[SPEAKER_04]: Leo?
[SPEAKER_04]: Leo and Zafina.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, now keep in mind, I've never seen pictures of these characters, I don't even know if they've leaked out, but I'm gonna make some bold predictions, okay, knowing the Tekken series.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm gonna say Leo is shirtless, and Jamina, or whatever her name, Jamigla?
[SPEAKER_04]: Zafina.
[SPEAKER_04]: Zafina?
[SPEAKER_04]: Serafina?
[SPEAKER_04]: Serafina has humongous breasts that will bounce.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: You're wrong about shirtless.
[SPEAKER_12]: Every character in Tekken is shirtless.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_12]: He's been one of the chicks, I think.
[SPEAKER_04]: Leo looks like a chick, who also looks like someone that was ripped from Final Fantasy X. No, Leo looks like one of the Bogards, a little bit.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, Leo looks like a chick.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyways, and then... That's a guy.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then...
[SPEAKER_11]: and Zafina.
[SPEAKER_11]: Zafina, well, she's your chick that's, you know, of course she has big boobs, but she's your... One out of two ain't bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Your ethnic chick.
[SPEAKER_04]: What, is she a belly dancer?
[SPEAKER_04]: What the hell is that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's wearing a sarong.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, easy access, I suppose.
[SPEAKER_11]: Either way, it looks kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're going to have... It looks like from the trailer, they're going to have different ways you can kind of build up your characters.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know, it looks okay, but do you really need to push better graphics with fighting games?
[SPEAKER_11]: Just make it fun.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm yay for that, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: Marissa says she's yay for that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Although they do need to push more boob physics with Dead or Alive 3, or Dead or Alive 5, I guess it would be.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie, you're a Tekken fan girl.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you excited about Tekken 6, or is this a little too much of one thing, or what?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm always excited over anything that has gin in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I was going to say, as long as gin's in it, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: And Asuka now, because Asuka's kind of... Wait here, I'm going to write a letter on Jamie's behalf to Namco.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dear Namco... May I?
[SPEAKER_09]: Namco Bondi.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sit down, shut up, let me speak.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, here we go.
[SPEAKER_09]: Rob, you talk too much.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dear... I know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Even our fans think so, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I know, it's fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what...
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, then here's my letter.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dear fans, suck it.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, here we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Back to Jamie's letter.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's G4.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dear Namco Bandai, Jin!
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, Jin!
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh my god, oh my god!
[SPEAKER_09]: No, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: Love, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_09]: My obsession has also carried over to Asuka.
[SPEAKER_09]: P.S.
Asuka!
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh my god, boobs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mike W says, my ears bleed.
[SPEAKER_09]: Rondo of Blood, the fighting game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fireboma says, write it in blood.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uni says, I'm going to smack Rob for not being nice to DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: I bite back.
[SPEAKER_01]: For the record, I'm so sick of how many shadows your game can fucking render if it still sucks.
[SPEAKER_01]: For the record.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's how we feel, but we don't know how to put it so eloquently to the developers.
[SPEAKER_04]: Would you like to write a letter to the developers of games?
[SPEAKER_01]: What if I went like that?
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's like, great, now you have a really shiny, highly rendered piece of shit instead of just, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: That dookie looks mighty fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I can see, like, it's obvious you ate corn.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's like, wow, she looks really lifelike.
[SPEAKER_11]: Too bad that she clips through people and is stuck in the stage or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love the Blood Elves in World of Warcraft because they, like, levitate over bridges because the clipping is so awful.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, let's
[SPEAKER_04]: In certain places they do.
[SPEAKER_04]: They do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's talk about something very sexy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Besides me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ikaruga is a shooter game.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know Ikaruga, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like the one where you... Radiant Silvergun, the sequel.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you press buttons to change the color of your shield because there's like red bullets and I think it was purple bullets and red bullets.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's like black and white, but the black is kind of purplish.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's so awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have these bullets and you change the shield color.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's such a great shooter.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh...
[SPEAKER_04]: XBOX 360 DEBUG UNIT PARTNER NET
[SPEAKER_09]: Icaruga that is just like so well I'll tell you something else though that's relatively sexy that is if you are a big collector like me and um a skew has shown up at GameCrazy which I cannot confirm for my husband's GameCrazy because he hasn't seen fit to tell me sorry for a black Xbox 360 and it has been confirmed by several GameCrazy's isn't this like the fourth week in a row there's been some type of black Xbox 360 story on the internet
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, why?
[SPEAKER_11]: The original Xbox was black.
[SPEAKER_11]: But we had the Halo one.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, but here's the thing, though, about it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think it's not really the fact that it's black.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's just that it's going to have a 128-gig hard drive, supposedly, and they think that's also going to have an HDMI out.
[SPEAKER_11]: I can tell you right now... And a bigger penis.
[SPEAKER_11]: I can tell you right now, either way, it's just going to be a disappointment.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's all it's going to be is a big disappointment for you.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, great.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're going to announce that.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're going to announce a 512 card or a memory unit or whatever, and everybody's like, Oh, yay!
[SPEAKER_11]: We can download more crap.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm sorry, I just had to weigh in on this subject because I think Nintendo, it's the stupidest thing in the world, but I think they made a big mistake with the GameCube.
[SPEAKER_01]: I actually got my ex the GameCube, but they made it purple.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because guys were afraid of having a purple GameCube.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, be glad that we didn't get the orange one.
[SPEAKER_12]: Mine was silver.
[SPEAKER_12]: It was indigo, okay?
[SPEAKER_11]: It was blue, and by the way, I had the black ones.
[SPEAKER_08]: In Japan they had orange ones.
[SPEAKER_08]: That makes you extra hetero.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tiger Claw says, Sky, you know that old saying, once you go black, you never go back.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that true, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that why you need the black Xbox 360 so bad?
[SPEAKER_09]: I want it to match my Saturn.
[SPEAKER_11]: Among other things.
[SPEAKER_11]: Here's the thing, though, about, you know, you're going to get this nice, fancy, black Xbox 360, and then, oh, wait, the controllers are white, the Xbox HD, you know, DVD player is white.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, wait, the remote's white.
[SPEAKER_09]: I really don't give two shits, maybe half of one, but, you know, it's...
[SPEAKER_09]: For people who say, you know, fine, you've got a new one, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: And for the record, the Sega Saturn did initially come out in white in Japan.
[SPEAKER_09]: Check your sources!
[SPEAKER_04]: James Patrick asks in chat, DarkSakura should sell the Halo one.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're worth a bit of money now.
[SPEAKER_09]: The fuck I will.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a Halo one as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why would I sell it?
[SPEAKER_04]: What would I play my Xbox games on?
[SPEAKER_09]: Keep in mind, if I sell my Xbox, that drops me down to 42 video game systems.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have an orange one.
[SPEAKER_04]: But 42 is the answer to everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gaming Nerd says, I'd love a nice pink 360 to match my pink PS2.
[SPEAKER_04]: In related news, Gaming Nerd is my favorite chatter ever.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, when I replace my JPS2, I'm going to get the Sakura PS2, which is sort of a purpley color.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's the Sakura one, so it's mine!
[SPEAKER_09]: Mine.
[SPEAKER_11]: Mine.
[SPEAKER_09]: I do, I have my own brand of condoms.
[SPEAKER_11]: Speaking of partner, Nat, a little bit.
[SPEAKER_11]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: Did she say that in a mic?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, I've got to tell you this.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is completely off the subject, but I've got to say it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have my own brand of condoms!
[SPEAKER_04]: What?!
[SPEAKER_04]: No, pass the mic to Chris.
[SPEAKER_06]: We were, uh, Jamie and I, when we hang out, we go down to Japan Town, and we go to, uh, Ichiban Con.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ichiban Con.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ichiban Con, thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, uh, they've got a bunch of imports from Japan, and one time we found Sakura condoms.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, Jamie, look, your condoms!
[SPEAKER_09]: And Chris said that, and I repeated what she said, only I had the mic in my hand.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, see?
[SPEAKER_09]: So that wasn't random, you just weren't paying attention.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm a bad host!
[SPEAKER_04]: Hold on, hold on.
[SPEAKER_09]: Bad host.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whatever, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Those are Sakura brand, those are not dark.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's one third of your show, too.
[SPEAKER_09]: But they were in a dark box.
[SPEAKER_11]: That does not count.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, it does.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's just like saying, okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: That would be just like saying, oh, the Whitman chocolates out there.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, they must be my brand chocolates because it's very close to my last name, White Man.
[SPEAKER_12]: Or that's like saying, go outside and look up.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's me, Sky.
[SPEAKER_09]: You could do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_09]: That also put you in the category of I invented the internet.
[SPEAKER_04]: By the way, I am everywhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, Loki, you had something you wanted to say.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you finished?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, we're finished.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_11]: So let's talk about PartnerNet.
[SPEAKER_11]: PartnerNet's been around forever, and I guess everybody forgot their NDAs regarding PartnerNet because you do not talk about PartnerNet.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's the first rule of PartnerNet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everyone I know who's ever had PartnerNet, which isn't us because we're not cool enough,
[SPEAKER_04]: They blab PartnerNet.
[SPEAKER_04]: We know enough that you don't post it on blogs and things, but oh god.
[SPEAKER_04]: People who have PartnerNet don't shut up.
[SPEAKER_11]: They think they're special.
[SPEAKER_11]: Someone took some video of it and they found out about more games coming out.
[SPEAKER_11]: None of which I'm too surprised about.
[SPEAKER_11]: Some of these have already been announced.
[SPEAKER_11]: Rare's Jetpack, a game that's coming out later on.
[SPEAKER_11]: They've already announced that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Juice 2007, already been announced.
[SPEAKER_11]: Absolute, who the hell knows what that is.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ob's Pinball, yay.
[SPEAKER_11]: Two Pinball.
[SPEAKER_11]: Tetris Online, which I think might actually be that Tetris Evolution or whatever that's coming out in March, whatever.
[SPEAKER_11]: Or maybe another downloadable game.
[SPEAKER_11]: Great, two different Tetrises.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then some Halo 2 maps that were already announced.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, yeah, very exciting.
[SPEAKER_11]: Great.
[SPEAKER_11]: More stuff coming out.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like I said, you can't talk about it, though.
[SPEAKER_11]: Although there are other websites.
[SPEAKER_11]: So I was reading some comments that they were posting about
[SPEAKER_11]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, apparently one of the bigger sites that had a movie got asked to take it down.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ooh, snap.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_04]: XBOX REWARDS CHALLENGE
[SPEAKER_04]: Xbox's little concession for this whole thing is that they have extended the Xbox reward challenge by three days.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you have three whole more days to extend your gamer score by 1,500 points.
[SPEAKER_04]: And people are bitching and complaining because they were like, dude, I took the day off of work so I could be the first to inflate my gamer score so I could make sure that I'm one of the ones that gets this game because you only said so many copies would be out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm saying if this is you, my personal opinion of you is that you need to go out and get a fucking life because seriously?
[SPEAKER_04]: If you took a day off of work to stay home and increase your gamerscore for this competition, Microsoft does not owe you anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: Microsoft made the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Microsoft made the system.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is what you bought.
[SPEAKER_04]: This whole rewards thing is like somebody giving you something for free.
[SPEAKER_04]: Microsoft did not owe you this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why are you so mad over this?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's why I refuse to get mad about this.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, yeah, it was a little frustrating because I tried to go on the site, but it's like, you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's free stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: Quit your bitching and get like one of those diamond cards for free and then go get discounts at other places.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or go get a whore and have sex and get some of that energy out of your system because seriously, if you're getting that
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure people know that Fuse and Frenzy 2 is not even worth it so I can think of no other reason why people want to do this other than to say look at my giant internet cock I got the free game in the Microsoft contest and let me be the first to tell you it's just like you got into the Halo 3 beta fucking everyone got into the Halo 3 beta who cares my girlfriend's cock is bigger than yours it is
[SPEAKER_01]: You know what, though?
[SPEAKER_01]: If I went to somebody's house and they have that on display, that's not unlike... Well, I have a friend that owns a magic card shop and they show me those player cards, you know, with the pictures of the expert magic player.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's like a guide of who not to have sex with.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm sorry, it is.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyway...
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, I think Marissa, I see Marissa speaking for, like, the girls who are, like, kind of just not really associated with video games.
[SPEAKER_06]: She's, like, from the outside, oh, okay, well, DS is cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, you know, so she comes in and sees, you know, a bunch of people freaking out over video games, and she goes, wow, I'm not fucking them.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, who gives a crap if, you know, they don't want to have, or they're not going to get, you know, laid by a girl.
[SPEAKER_11]: That cuts into precious time that they could be earning more gamerscore points.
Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_01]: One is, okay, everyone I've dated has been a nerd, okay?
[SPEAKER_01]: This is all on the record if anyone out there knows Kaylee, and that's just Kaylee, the big anime music video editor.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I've put in my time.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I'm a music nerd, okay?
[SPEAKER_01]: That's all I have to say about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's showing her creds.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's literally whipping out her...
[SPEAKER_04]: She's whipping out her cock and putting it on the table going, look.
[SPEAKER_01]: I spent every day at school lunch in the library, okay?
[SPEAKER_01]: I put in my nerd time.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have put in my time.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, anyway, that's all I have to say on the Xbox Rewards program.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry for the little rant.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, you know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: That's pretty shitty.
[SPEAKER_09]: However, speaking of Microsoft and shitty, but not in a... Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: I should say Microsoft and shitty, but, like, not shitty.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um...
[SPEAKER_09]: We've been discussing Forza 2 lately.
[SPEAKER_09]: The release date is in May in the United States.
[SPEAKER_09]: It has been confirmed that it will be released in the UK in May this year.
[SPEAKER_09]: So...
[SPEAKER_09]: Just to give a little bit of background on that, there are going to be a lot of different cars in this.
[SPEAKER_09]: There are 15 Ferraris, 2 Maseratis, 5 Lamborghinis, 13 Porsches.
[SPEAKER_09]: Pretty much a lot of good stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's actually going to have the 1987 Porsche 959 in there, so that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: So it's looking like a pretty cool racing game if you're into that sort of thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it will, again, have a May release in the UK as well as in the US.
[SPEAKER_09]: The PAL version, sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: Isn't that nice?
[SPEAKER_11]: That's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: And, of course, we're getting a lot more releases over here as well, not just
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, Forza 2, which still weighs off.
[SPEAKER_11]: This week, though, we've got some good stuff, including brand new Wii games.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sonic and the Secret Rings is going to be finally heading over to us, so hopefully that one won't suck as bad as... I don't know much about this Sonic, but will it redeem the series?
[SPEAKER_11]: It looks, to be honest, it looks just like the older Sonic games.
[SPEAKER_11]: So I think that this will actually be...
[SPEAKER_11]: Pretty decent.
[SPEAKER_11]: I haven't played it, though, so I can't say the control issues are going to still be there, even with the Wii being a brand new system and stuff and new control sets.
[SPEAKER_11]: I hope.
[SPEAKER_11]: It looks like it has some party games in it that are pretty fun, so hopefully.
[SPEAKER_11]: Other stuff coming out, though, we're going to have Virtua Fighter 5 on the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's going to be coming out this week, which is pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: On the 360, the game I've been playing, and you've got to pick it up, Crackdown, as well.
[SPEAKER_11]: Also on the 360, there's going to be NBA Street Homecourt.
[SPEAKER_11]: That one's going to be pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: on the PlayStation 2 Arena Football 2 Road to Glory, if you're into that alternative type of game.
[SPEAKER_11]: Then, of course, on the PC here, we've got, what was it, Supreme Commander.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, Supreme Commander on PC.
[SPEAKER_11]: On the PlayStation 3 download service, Flow is supposed to finally make its way on the 22nd.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_11]: On the DS, Azuna, Legend of the Unemployed Ninja, which should be pretty interesting.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then also on PC, Warfront Turning Point.
[SPEAKER_11]: And also, that's about it as far as the good stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well, moving on over to Japan, where the video games come from a lot of times.
[SPEAKER_04]: But also, you know, especially when it comes to Xbox 360, the US kind of gets them first usually.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it looks like they're doing a simultaneous release with Riot Act, which is what they're going to call Crackdown over in Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Riot Act is coming out this week over in Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tom Clancy's Splinter Cell Double Agent also gets a release on the 22nd of February this week in Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Coming out on the PlayStation 3, Spike is putting out, not the same, like Spike TV here, it's a different company.
[SPEAKER_04]: Untold Legends Dark Kingdom makes its way to Japan on the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Coming out on the Nintendo Wii Fire Emblem for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: That should be really interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, Naruto Shippuden, Gekito Ninja Taisen.
[SPEAKER_04]: That should be interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Coming out on February 22nd.
[SPEAKER_04]: Coming out on the PlayStation 2, you get a whole lot of stuff over in Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: What I thought was interesting, though, is that they're getting Destroy All Humans on the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, a game that was popular enough over here made its way over to Japan, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: Lupin the Third.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a Lupin 3 coming out in Japan.
[SPEAKER_09]: I love Lupin the Third.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a whole shitload of stuff on the PlayStation 2 this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pachislot, like if you like pachinko and that kind of stuff, you get that as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Prince of Tennis, Card Hunter.
[SPEAKER_09]: Prince of Tennis is actually kind of a fun anime.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: What about some other systems?
[SPEAKER_04]: How about on the Nintendo DS?
[SPEAKER_04]: You get Cats in Japan comes out.
[SPEAKER_04]: SimCity DS as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: and one of my favorite titles, although, oh, that's actually a US release date.
[SPEAKER_04]: You didn't name this one, though, did you?
[SPEAKER_04]: Izuna, Legend of the Unemployed Ninja.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, did you?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was out of the room for a second.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's my favorite name of the week, and it's not even a Japanese game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me check PSP.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, it's about this ninja who goes around doing, like, odd jobs and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Over on the PSP, you get the Metal Slug Complete Collection in Japan, Monster Hunter Portable, and...
[SPEAKER_04]: and Boku wa Koku Kansai-ken, Airport Hero.
[SPEAKER_08]: I am something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Airport Hero.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that if the other one was already taken by the U.S., then I'm going to name that my favorite title of the week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Airport Hero.
[SPEAKER_09]: We should just get another Densha Dego.
[SPEAKER_09]: It came with a controller so you could pilot a train.
[SPEAKER_04]: My Airport Hero is a screening line that can actually move at a steady pace.
[SPEAKER_04]: Instead of backing up, I have to wait 45 minutes to take my belt off to go through the x-ray.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_09]: Are we done with Japan?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, yeah, I'm done.
[SPEAKER_09]: We have other countries!
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm kidding, I'm kidding, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have our UK release date.
[SPEAKER_04]: I always thought Canada was the 51st state.
[SPEAKER_08]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: Puerto Rico?
[SPEAKER_04]: What's Puerto Rico?
[SPEAKER_04]: I've never heard of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, wait, that's Ricky Martin's hometown.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rob, Rob, Rob, Rob, Rob, Rob, Rob, Rob, Rob, Rob, Rob, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: UK.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, UK.
[SPEAKER_09]: On the 22nd on the PlayStation 3, we have Qbert.
[SPEAKER_09]: Which is funny because I have Qbert on the Atari 5200.
[SPEAKER_09]: And the Clique Vision.
[SPEAKER_09]: On the 23rd, 23, the number of coincidence.
[SPEAKER_09]: We have Blitz the League on Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_09]: We have Crackdown...
[SPEAKER_09]: We have Disney's Chicken Little Ace in action on the Wii Final Fantasy XII, which, shit, took forever Ghost Rider on PlayStation 2 and PSP Guilty Gear Dust Strikers on DS I love Guilty Gear Infernal on PC Tom Clancy's Rainbow Six Vegas on PSP and Hot Pixel on the 25th on PSP And that's it!
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, okay, actually, on the 27th there's also Flipper Critters and Jade Empire but that's next week
[SPEAKER_04]: Hot Pixel was that one PSP game that's kind of like WarioWare, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: It's not coming out until August here, I think.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: I was going to ask if it ever came out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, our UK friends get games first.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wow, that's a first.
[SPEAKER_11]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_11]: Good job, UK.
[SPEAKER_05]: Way to go.
[SPEAKER_11]: Too bad the game didn't look that good.
[SPEAKER_11]: Too bad the guy's kind of crazy.
[SPEAKER_11]: He's like this old dude.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah, that's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: He was talking to us, and he was kind of creepy.
[SPEAKER_11]: I got his card, but I felt like... Well, he's not going to come on the show now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just called him creepy.
[SPEAKER_11]: He has his own podcast, by the way.
[SPEAKER_04]: Does he?
[SPEAKER_04]: I bet it's creepy.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyways, so apparently in the UK there's this wonderful show called Watchdog that they investigate
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, companies and stuff like that that have, you know, either defective products or, you know, they're... It's kind of like, I want to say there was something like this on Dateline or something where they investigate different businesses to make sure that they're up to par or whatever.
[SPEAKER_11]: So they're investigating Microsoft about the Xbox 360 because apparently they're saying that they have received 248 complaints about faulty Xbox 360s.
[SPEAKER_11]: Um...
[SPEAKER_11]: and they're saying that the return rate was larger than Microsoft initially said and that the fact that the owners had to spend, or some of the owners had to spend around 80 pounds or about $156 to fix each of the units that just so happened to break after a year of purchasing the system.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, at the same time, I just...
[SPEAKER_11]: Aren't they a little late on this?
[SPEAKER_11]: Wasn't this whole Defective 360 story about a year ago?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It takes time to build these cases, though, don't forget.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it is the UK, and everything's delayed, unfortunately, with them.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyways, so Microsoft, of course, responded saying that the claims made by the show are false, that the return rate of the Xbox 360 is significantly lower than the CE industry average of 3-5%.
[SPEAKER_11]: Customer satisfaction is our highest priority, and we do everything that we can to take care of the gamers who may have problems with their consoles.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anybody having an issue with their 360 should call customer service immediately so that we can help.
[SPEAKER_11]: And, you know, to be honest, though, they did increase their warranty period for the 360, and I don't know, I think they're doing their part.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, I would say, how are these 360s being broken?
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, if it's people, you know,
[SPEAKER_11]: I still hear my customers talking about, oh yeah, this game came back scratch because there's a ring in it now because someone's jiggled their 360 while it's going and it carved a big ring into their disc.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, people are dumb.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought the X meant I shake it.
[SPEAKER_11]: What?
[SPEAKER_11]: The system's not like the Wii controller?
[SPEAKER_11]: It's not motion sensitive?
[SPEAKER_11]: Actually, to be honest, the system is motion sensitive.
[SPEAKER_11]: It will know if you're laying it flat or if you're laying it upright.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's true, it's true.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that's a little, yeah, that's a little tiny little bubble that does that probably.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, speaking of watchdog agencies, the biggest watchdog of them all is the government.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Sam Brownback is a senator, a Republican senator, and he's also somebody who is running for president in 2008.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_04]: Surprise!
[SPEAKER_04]: And he's exploring the Republican nomination for the president of the United States.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sam Brownback is also one of the minds behind the Video Game Rating Act, and it has been reintroduced.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was first introduced last September, but it is now being reintroduced for Senate.
[SPEAKER_04]: If this was made law, what would happen is that the ESRB, you may remember us talking about this back in September, the ESRB would have to play the final build of a game from the beginning until
[SPEAKER_04]: to the end until they could actually give it a rating.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I believe the way the ESRB works now, they're just filling out a questionnaire.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe they play a little bit of the game, but that's about it, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, it's the same way the MPAA works.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I don't see anyone cracking down the MPAA.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think the movies and the games should be done the exact same way.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, no, I take that back.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think movies, TV, and games should all be done the exact same way.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_04]: And I like how these... Oh, anyways, continue on with the story.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me give a quick quote, and I think Marissa wants to chime in too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Video game reviewers... Oh, this is a quote from Mr. Brownback.
[SPEAKER_04]: Video game reviewers should be required to review the entire content of a game to ensure the accuracy of the rating.
[SPEAKER_04]: The current video game rating system is not as accurate as it could be because reviewers do not see the full content of games and do not even play the games they rate.
[SPEAKER_04]: Boy, they're going to be screwed when they have to review, like, Oblivion or an MMO.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, Marissa?
[SPEAKER_01]: This issue in particular gets me really passionate.
[SPEAKER_01]: I watched a great documentary called This Movie Is Not Yet Rated the other day about the MPAA.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know if you've seen it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've heard of it and I really want to see it, but I've heard it's just like Super Size Me, like resonated with McDonald's.
[SPEAKER_04]: I heard this movie resonated with the MVAA.
[SPEAKER_01]: The government should not step in, but interestingly enough, I think there's a problem when the industry regulates itself because it creates a monopoly.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't understand, like for movies, for example, you can go to a website, kidsinmind.com, and it just lists specifically what is in the movie.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't think a rating system is a good idea because then people interject their opinion into it.
[SPEAKER_01]: If you want to say there's sex in this, there's etc.,
[SPEAKER_01]: and I know this is a really old meme, but it still amazed me that people got upset about the hot coffee mod in Grand Theft Auto, but they didn't have a problem with the fact that their five-year-old kid was killing hookers, etc.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, I like the game myself, but why is sex the problem?
[SPEAKER_11]: Perfect example, the hot coffee thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, granted, it was an interactive little minigame, whose graphics were really bad, by the way.
[SPEAKER_11]: But yeah, I don't hear anyone complaining that there's a fucking sex minigame in the original God of War and in God of War 2, which there's full fucking titties in the goddamn game.
[SPEAKER_11]: This wasn't, oh, it's not hidden.
[SPEAKER_11]: Big deal.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's an M-rated game.
[SPEAKER_11]: The difference between a 17- and 18-year-old, can you really say mindset-wise?
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, granted, okay, one's a legal adult.
[SPEAKER_11]: But mindset-wise, one's going to know about boobies as much as the other one.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's because they need to pull the corncob out of their ass and stop fucking promoting a double fucking standard.
[SPEAKER_04]: How would you feel if the video game was the exact same thing as the movie?
[SPEAKER_04]: You pick up the box and on the back it says...
[SPEAKER_04]: This game is rated R for sexuality and language.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it still says sexual content.
[SPEAKER_09]: Isn't that how they do it in Europe?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, in the UK it's the same system.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, it said it was rated M for sexual content.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was on there.
[SPEAKER_11]: It didn't specify saying, oh, it's rated because of this minigame.
[SPEAKER_11]: It said sexual content.
[SPEAKER_11]: So this is really getting... Now you're starting to get into semantics here about, oh, well, is this sexual content that made it M rated and not this sexual content?
[SPEAKER_11]: Who gives a shit?
[SPEAKER_11]: It's M. It says sexual content.
[SPEAKER_11]: Do we need to do anything else?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: People are stupid and there's a lot of... No, I'm not saying this about everybody because we have parents that listen to this program and you're probably smart because you know how to download a podcast.
[SPEAKER_04]: But there's a lot of stupid parents out there and for their benefit, you know, I'm going to give a little here.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's about the world works with compromise, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: My compromise is, okay, we will make one rating system so you don't have to think like, okay, I'm not that smart so I have to translate.
[SPEAKER_04]: An M means like an NC-17, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's use one rating system across the board.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's my compromise.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's why you stupid people don't have to memorize more than one system.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm pretty sure that's how they do it in Europe, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_09]: And that makes perfect sense.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, as actually, it's funny, sort of related to that, our good friend Rob with 2Bs, I wasn't going to cover this in the mailbag, but he sent me an article about parents pursuing MySpace for their daughter's
[SPEAKER_09]: Lying about being 18.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sue your daughter!
[SPEAKER_05]: My sister says she's 19.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm not finished.
[SPEAKER_09]: And their daughter going to meet up with this guy and then getting the hot nookie on and the parent was sued.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, as the article states, the judge was like, fuck you, it was your job to police her.
[SPEAKER_11]: That is the wrong person to be suing.
[SPEAKER_11]: They need to sue the internet.
[SPEAKER_11]: Internet is the blame.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sue Al Gore for Inventigan.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just to go ahead just a little bit into it.
[SPEAKER_09]: A 12-year-old Texas girl lied about being 18, met a 19-year-old man for dinner at a movie and had some hot nookie.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then the parents tried to sue MySpace for $30 million, accusing the site of negligence.
[SPEAKER_09]: But the judge in the case, Judge Sam Sparks, turned around and I quote, If anyone had a duty to protect Julie Doe, it was her parents, not MySpace.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, and Nestle, what's in Judge Sam Sparks?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_04]: Judge Sam Sparks is our American Citizen of the Week.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_04]: Our hats off to you for telling this parent to go fuck herself.
[SPEAKER_09]: The reason why I think it was worth noting is that, you know, and actually Rob with two Bs also mentioned it,
[SPEAKER_09]: that this might actually set a precedence now for future cases involving parental negligence.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just get really passionate on this issue for being exceptionally yappy.
[SPEAKER_01]: But, I mean, I agree with the idea of a rating system because it is unfair that children feel a lot of pressure nowadays to be hip and cool, etc., and they want the same things we do, which is a completely different rant of mine.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sex?
[SPEAKER_01]: Sex is cool, too.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's a completely different rant of mine that we need to allow children to still be children and not little adults.
[SPEAKER_01]: But anyway, my only beef with the rating system is, though, is that the G, PG, etc., that, again, is a personal opinion.
[SPEAKER_01]: And actually, though, I think it makes it easier for parents, for those who approve of more sexual content because their own opinion or approve of less violence or more violence, etc., you just say explicitly what is in the game that is different than saying, well, I believe that this, because there's 12 different kinds of rated R movies.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, there could be 12 different kinds of rated R games.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, there's a big, big difference.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, here's the other thing, too.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I hate how they always say, oh, well, we need to put more responsibility on, you know, the ESRB and rating these games.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, you have to put more responsibility on these parents who just ignore the ratings and they say, oh, I didn't know this content was in here.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, you didn't know because you didn't read and you bought it for your five-year-old because, you know, you'll do anything for your five-year-old and you won't even, you know, question it.
[SPEAKER_11]: You'll just like, okay, I'm going to buy him... Buy him a fucking porno then.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, seriously, if...
[SPEAKER_11]: If that's going to be such an issue with you... Wow.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's just... I don't understand... And I don't understand how... Okay, granted the content was hidden in the game.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, yippee, it's hidden in the game.
[SPEAKER_11]: So if I created, say, a series of GameShark codes or something like that and made a topless mod for Tomb Raider, you know, a very elaborate process I might add that would probably be...
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you know your child can do real fucking in Grand Theft Auto?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, power fucking with the X button.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, coming to Grand Theft Auto tonight on Xdrop.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, and it's like, I think parents go off of what they hear.
[SPEAKER_04]: and not what they're actually seeing.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's so much of that sensationalism that I think takes everything to the oomph degree.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't actually agree with that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm just going to say this really quick because do you remember how big that Super Bowl thing with Janet Jackson was?
[SPEAKER_06]: Her titty was on television for a half a second.
[SPEAKER_12]: But it was covered.
[SPEAKER_12]: It was covered.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was covered with a stupid nipple shield.
[SPEAKER_11]: I saw the exact same thing on fucking Girls Next Door where she has a stupid sticker over her nipple and then that was acceptable.
[SPEAKER_09]: It wasn't a sticker.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was actually a piercing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dude, my grandma came out once and didn't realize I was in the room and I didn't sue her.
Movies kill.
[SPEAKER_04]: It might have made me gay, but I didn't sue her.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't want to.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's not what made me gay.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's
[SPEAKER_04]: I firmly believe it's a biological thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, cock made me gay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ryoma in chat says, Sky, never talk about that again.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I'm serious.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, what kid didn't accidentally see a titty at some point, you know?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, or a dick, you know?
[SPEAKER_01]: Duke Nukem had boobies in it too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, pixelated 8-bit boobies.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, that's what they look like.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's hot.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, moving on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Every week we invite you to give your feedback here on our program through our mailbag, among other things.
[SPEAKER_04]: We like to be an interactive program because it's not just about us.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not just about the three of us that run this program.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not just about Marissa or Chris or any of the other folks you've heard.
[SPEAKER_04]: Chris thinks it's all about her, but it's actually not.
[SPEAKER_04]: We invite you guys to interact with us by the chat room, by the voicemail, 1-877-GAME-OLR, or through the email bag, which you can email us every week at mailbag at orangelaunchradio.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: We love getting your emails.
[SPEAKER_04]: And DarkSakura, she's the queen of the mail bag.
[SPEAKER_04]: She likes to jump in there and pull out some of her favorite emails.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's going to do that right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to pull it out.
[SPEAKER_11]: You should have said that on mic.
[SPEAKER_11]: GS68 says, and you penetrate her weak point for massive damage.
[SPEAKER_11]: Mailbag, please.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alien crab bag.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, wait.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: WTB, mail.
[SPEAKER_09]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_09]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: Four emails.
[SPEAKER_09]: The first one from...
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm not sure exactly what to say.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can we try something new tonight?
[SPEAKER_04]: When you say that we're going to do the first email, what I'd like Chris to do is to say very sexily, letter number one.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, so here we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: So can we start from the top, please?
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, here we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Say the first email.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, Chris.
[SPEAKER_09]: Letter number one.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, very good.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dear Rob, DarkSakura, and Loki, I just wanted to say hello to you all and tell you how much I enjoy your program.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've been listening for a little over a year now.
[SPEAKER_09]: I actually first found out about you guys when looking for websites that were optimized to view on my PSP.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hint, hint, hint, hint!
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway, what's the deal with Rice Princess?
[SPEAKER_09]: She has a filthy, filthy mouth and is incredibly offensive.
[SPEAKER_09]: You should have her on the show more often.
[SPEAKER_09]: Keep up the good work.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is Rice Princess still here?
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me go find Rice Princess.
[SPEAKER_04]: Talk smack about Rice Princess quick before I get her in here.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh my god, Irene is so... I'm going to skip the... I'm going to go into the next email.
[SPEAKER_09]: Email number two.
[SPEAKER_09]: You sounded like you had to go to the bathroom.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rice Princess, we just read one of your fan letters on the program.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it true that you have an offensive, filthy mouth?
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you know any dirty jokes you can tell our listeners this week?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because our emailer said they liked having you on the show because you had a very offensive mouth, so we just wanted you to say something offensive.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, poop.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's pretty offensive.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was on an offensive scale of 1 to 10.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was like a 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, how about you lick the crusty poop out of my butt, and then you lick the crusty poop off my finger?
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, I'm going to go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, that was a 9.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was a 9.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was much better.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, thank you, Rice Princess.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for your contributions.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a good thing we haven't done any more Yamama jokes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do you want me to do it again?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, you already did.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: I already did the email.
[SPEAKER_09]: This one is email number two from SpeedyF40.
[SPEAKER_09]: A year and a half ago I tuned into OLR for the first time after finding it on Podcast Alley.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was not hooked, but like a festering rash, the good kind, your show grew on me and a year and a half later I am still here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're like the good kind of festering rash.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a really good compliment.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rob, you guys are like the festering rash.
[SPEAKER_06]: We are the festering rash of my love.
[SPEAKER_04]: Could somebody who has not written a review on iTunes yet, somebody in chat, volunteer to do this.
[SPEAKER_04]: I actually haven't.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want somebody in chat to yell out, claim this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go to iTunes and give us a five-star review, which actually everyone should do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hint, hint.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't want everybody saying the show is a festering rash, so I want one person from chat to nominate themselves to go write a five-star review on iTunes and put, this show is the festering rash of gaming podcasts.
[SPEAKER_01]: The good kind.
[SPEAKER_04]: The good kind.
[SPEAKER_01]: Genital herpes is forever, and so is my love for Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, somebody can lay claim to that one, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like that one.
[SPEAKER_09]: Can I finish reading this now?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, you may.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fester, Jamie, fester.
[SPEAKER_09]: Bite my butt, but not really.
[SPEAKER_09]: and you have even used one of my calls on air.
[SPEAKER_09]: I love independent radio and I feel that your show is doing a service to the gamer community.
[SPEAKER_09]: OLR has even inspired me to do my own show.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki, you suck because you don't like Max.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, that's really not what he said.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: He didn't say that.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know some people may see you as an ass.
[SPEAKER_09]: You are, just not all the time.
[SPEAKER_09]: Most of the time I see you as an honest, down-to-earth realist.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki, you set the story straight, and your ties to the inside of the gaming world give the show a sense of added credibility.
[SPEAKER_09]: By the way, apples do suck for gaming.
[SPEAKER_09]: Buy a PC.
[SPEAKER_09]: I would say in two to four years, Apple computers will be a formidable gaming computer for the average person.
[SPEAKER_09]: Real gamers will stick with the PC, but that is a whole other thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Jamie, your alternative views on gaming and the gaming culture broaden my mind and keep ideas flowing through my head.
[SPEAKER_09]: I love how you speak your mind, even though I know we will have some political differences.
[SPEAKER_09]: I hold your opinions on issues that affect gamers in extremely high regards.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, thank you.
[SPEAKER_09]: That makes me feel warm in a special place.
[SPEAKER_01]: My ex-boyfriend actually had a good quote on that.
[SPEAKER_01]: He said, Macintosh makes the best computer out there.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know what the problem is?
[SPEAKER_01]: Nobody cares.
[SPEAKER_01]: Do you have another email, actually?
[SPEAKER_01]: There's more.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, I wanted to do the sexy announcement, because on the internet, I'm kind of geek famous for being the voice of a character on LJ Drama.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, well, the third one is to Rob.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, yay.
[SPEAKER_09]: You got a lot of balls being a gay gamer on the internet.
[SPEAKER_09]: Pun intended.
[SPEAKER_09]: When I jumped on air for my own show, I would have to say that I model...
[SPEAKER_09]: I model some of my on-air presence from yours.
[SPEAKER_09]: With me being straight guy, I come off as being very enthusiastic.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just don't get messages telling me I talk too much yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: I love OLR.
[SPEAKER_09]: It is polished and it is brilliant.
[SPEAKER_09]: From your unconventional views on gaming and gaming culture to the straight-up format of the show, I love it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I would not be who I am today on the internet and in real life if it was not for you guys.
[SPEAKER_09]: Independent Radio for the win.
[SPEAKER_09]: Speedy F40.
[SPEAKER_09]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_09]: Tell Rice Princess I have a crush on her because she sounds like a freak.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, Irene!
[SPEAKER_09]: You have a fan!
[SPEAKER_04]: That's very... Wait, didn't he say he ran his own podcast?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: What is it?
[SPEAKER_09]: I didn't say.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is this his Speedy F40?
[SPEAKER_04]: Is there like a signature or something?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's a crush.
[SPEAKER_09]: He has a crush on you because you're a freak, is what he said.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because you're a freak.
[SPEAKER_09]: SpeedyF40.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dude, if you're listening, and we're pretty sure that you are because you're amazing, send us a link to your podcast and we'll plug you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Totally.
[SPEAKER_04]: We want to pimp that podcast.
[SPEAKER_09]: We will totally plug you in the most awesome way.
[SPEAKER_04]: Seriously, not to spend too much time talking about ourselves, because I don't want to be like that, but that's truly one of the best compliments we could ever get.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, wait, it's on here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, it is?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, great.
[SPEAKER_09]: WCRadio.com 5pm Eastern Time on Saturday.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, it's part of the WCRadio, Warcraft Radio, like a huge radio thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Warcraft Radio?
[SPEAKER_09]: I think I've heard of them before.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm not sure if this is his or not, but it's in the signature, so check it out maybe?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, if you are going to spend all day playing World of Warcraft, I know the soundtrack gets old, so you might as well listen to Warcraft Radio, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: So go for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's very cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: and that's truly one of the best compliments but can I say something about the gay issue without turning the show too gay it's already gay it's actually not really been a big deal for me to be gay on this program because I give a lot of props to the gaming community and I think the youth in general is that I really don't think people seem to care and I think if they do care they're not listening so hey, all for the best this probably isn't their type of show anyway if it was something they care about they'd probably want to listen to Bigot Radio
[SPEAKER_04]: But most people that have listened to this program really don't care, and I think that speaks volumes about the gaming community, is that, you know, hey, there's nothing wrong with being gay, but it's just, you know, it's whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I don't want this to be the gay show either, because that's not all I am, and I think people get that wrong impression about me sometimes, is that, you know, I'm the gay gamer, and that's all I can think about is, like, how much cock is in my games.
[SPEAKER_06]: At least you're not the titty queen.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, we plugged the lesbian thing on me just because it's funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's for the straight men, you know.
[SPEAKER_09]: This segment is getting entirely too gay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just wanted to say it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Talk about your joystick some more.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait, wait, sexy please.
[SPEAKER_01]: Except that boobs are hot.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, I was just going to say it's not all gay radio unless you talk about your joystick too much.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, oh.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hi, it's me, Victoria.
[SPEAKER_01]: Email number three.
[SPEAKER_01]: Dude, that was hot.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was hot.
[SPEAKER_04]: I got a semi.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, OLR, I started World of Warcraft for the new year.
[SPEAKER_09]: I fell in love with WoW until I installed the Burning Crusade expansion pack.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I would not interrupt you if this was not the best thing ever.
[SPEAKER_04]: You interrupt me all the time.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I would not do this if this was not the best thing ever, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: Trust me.
[SPEAKER_04]: DJ Janai says, maybe we should rename the show to the Games and You Show.
[SPEAKER_04]: G-A-Y, Games and You.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't understand, but it wouldn't start up, so I reinstalled it like two times, and eventually I just called Blizzard.
[SPEAKER_09]: They told me that my graphics card just happened to not be compatible with World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_09]: He told me luckily I was able to play for a while, but once I installed the expansion pack, it stopped working.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have a VS3G Unichrome Pro ITG graphics card.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just to warn anyone who plays World of Warcraft or is starting, just make sure that... Excuse me.
[SPEAKER_09]: You should upgrade to a new graphics card if you have the VIAS 3G Unichrome Pro IGT graphics card.
[SPEAKER_04]: What, what, Loki?
[SPEAKER_11]: He's got an in-the-groove graphics card.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, IGT?
[SPEAKER_11]: That shoots a hole in my joke.
[SPEAKER_09]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_09]: My cousin bought Burning Crusade for my birthday, and now I can't play World of Warcraft at all.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nice birthday present, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_09]: Aw, don't cry, emo kid.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tough advice from Chris.
[SPEAKER_06]: I installed it and it was a pain in the ass, but I've got a Mac, so I don't need to upgrade anything.
[SPEAKER_06]: Next.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wait, what number?
[SPEAKER_06]: Shut up, Rosa.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is from Let's Have Tea.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wait, email what?
[SPEAKER_09]: Number four.
[SPEAKER_09]: Email number four.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think my semi went away because she sounded 17.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fuck you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Remember, it's only porn if you tape it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey there, OLR.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's have tea here.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have been a long-time listener, even though I have only actually tuned into the live show a few times, Podcast for the Win.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's not what this email is about, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: A few weeks back, you were talking about the Wii being used as a fitness weight loss tool.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was digging through Dig, and came across a few interesting articles.
[SPEAKER_09]: One article was showing how somebody lost nine pounds playing Wii Sports for 30 minutes a day for six weeks.
[SPEAKER_09]: He didn't change his normal eating habits at all.
[SPEAKER_09]: He just played the game more.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's because it's exercise.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also, it's...
[SPEAKER_09]: Activity for 30 minutes.
[SPEAKER_09]: It will raise the heart rate.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dude, I burn weight doing massage three days a week for 30 minutes.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: You do any kind of exercise for 30 minutes a day.
[SPEAKER_04]: And also, if you don't eat McDonald's during that same length of time, you'll lose twice as much.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also, I saw another article about wrist weight with the Wii logo on them.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sure, they were fan-created concept products, but there are similar products out there for similar workout activities.
[SPEAKER_09]: I am not prescribing nor recommending anything.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is not a prescription.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just to protect my ass.
[SPEAKER_09]: You do run a risk of damaging your wrists using a wrist weight with anything that you have to flick or move your wrist with.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wrist weights are actually not all that safe to use.
[SPEAKER_11]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_11]: No one wants to break their masturbating wrists.
[SPEAKER_11]: My problem is I would not want... I have a point.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you want to put more effort into it, I say stand up and do it.
[SPEAKER_09]: You burn more calories standing up.
[SPEAKER_04]: My problem is that I would not want to wear the wrist weights because I would be afraid that my wrist would hang down more than it already does.
[SPEAKER_06]: Then you'd look uber gay.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a visual there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Radio visual joke.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here, I got some advice.
[SPEAKER_06]: Get up and go to the fucking gym!
[SPEAKER_06]: I have no patience for people who sit there and say, you get a great workout playing the video game.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, you don't.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, yeah, you do if you play DDR.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's not the same thing, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, actually.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, I can give you DDR.
[SPEAKER_09]: I did get up and play.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a difference if you actually get up and move your arm as opposed to sitting on the couch and flicking your wrist.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you get up and get into the game, you actually are elevating your heart rate.
[SPEAKER_09]: You are actually burning more than you are sitting down and flicking your wrist.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, but you need to also stop eating junk food and you need to go outside in the sunshine and you need to check yourself into a gym so you don't turn fat.
[SPEAKER_04]: I see it as like steps.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_01]: It's not, I mean, I completely agree with Chris, you know, it's good to get out of the house, etc.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, I'm in complete agreement on that.
[SPEAKER_01]: I agree with that, too.
[SPEAKER_01]: But sometimes going to the gym sucks.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's face it, people go there to meet other people, people are checking each other out, and when I go in there in my fat ass, I am not interested in that.
[SPEAKER_01]: I do want to get a workout, and if I can do it at home and not be bored out of my brain because the Stairmaster goes nowhere, I feel like a hamster wheel.
[SPEAKER_01]: I feel like I'm on the hamster wheel of life.
[SPEAKER_01]: You pay $50 and you go up!
[SPEAKER_09]: Dennis Leary for the win.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, Dennis Leary.
[SPEAKER_01]: Life sucks, get a helmet!
[SPEAKER_01]: Yay, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: Another thing, though, is, you know, and this is what I'm going to do, because I used to be an utter gym junkie before I developed chronic fatigue syndrome, because I was going to the gym five days a week, I dropped something like 85 pounds in two and a half years.
[SPEAKER_09]: Which I hate you for.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um...
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie used to have a few extra pounds, but she's lost it all.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's hot.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't care saying I went from a size 22 to a size 12 in two and a half years.
[SPEAKER_09]: Going to the gym was good for me because I actually like to lift weights because I like being stronger.
[SPEAKER_09]: But cardio is fucking boring.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I'm actually, now that I have the okay to go back to the gym, I'm actually going to be taking... Okay, I've been slightly obsessed with Dancing with the Stars lately, after watching Stacey Keebler's legs.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I'm going to actually take ballroom dancing.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what they should have?
[SPEAKER_09]: They should have Wii Yoga.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wii Yoga would be amazing!
[SPEAKER_04]: They kind of have something like that on Xbox, and I think there was a version on GameCube.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know there was on PS2.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was that Think Fitness game or whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it had yoga in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: I want the entirety of our listeners to know that when I say, yeah, you can fucking go to the gym, this is from experience, okay?
[SPEAKER_09]: You can get off your ass and do it.
[SPEAKER_09]: You just have to want it bad enough.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nothing changes until you want it bad enough to make it change.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_04]: But would it be fair to say there's also alternatives?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because we have a lot of folks in chat saying gyms are expensive or folks don't like the gym environment.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like JV Mon says, gyms in the village in NYC are just big bathhouses with exercise equipment.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's called going outside and walking.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's alternatives.
[SPEAKER_04]: And maybe go outside, run.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go outside, walk.
[SPEAKER_04]: Find a walking buddy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do something to make yourself more fit.
[SPEAKER_04]: But wouldn't this be at least a little baby step in the right direction?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I granted that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I granted that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just, people annoy me.
[SPEAKER_09]: And for Ryoma, a special message for you, fuck your Yankee blue jeans.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway, there's more to that email.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, more?
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, wow.
[SPEAKER_09]: A little bit.
[SPEAKER_09]: We were at the end.
[SPEAKER_09]: Again, I love the show, and thank you so much for the many hours of entertainment and news you have provided everyone.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm a, quote, truck driver, pickup truck, haha, and have to drive a little over an hour straight every Saturday and Sunday, so your podcast really helps pass the time.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks again, and best wishes.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it also says, let's have tea rates as low as 4.65% refinance $150,000 loan for $579 a month.
[SPEAKER_04]: Amazing.
[SPEAKER_09]: And you want to know what's funny?
[SPEAKER_09]: Since I work in the mortgage industry...
[SPEAKER_09]: That actually isn't really all that great unless you have an interest-only loan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Isn't that some ad that goes on the bottom of the email automatically?
[SPEAKER_09]: I think it's hilarious.
[SPEAKER_09]: I work in the mortgage industry, so whenever I see those things, I go, is that shitty?
[SPEAKER_09]: Because I know how to read loan documents.
[SPEAKER_09]: It actually is another language.
[SPEAKER_04]: Too bad this isn't a banking show.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, but I have tomorrow off, so suck it!
[SPEAKER_04]: No, you suck it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have to work tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_09]: Suck it twice, huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: Suck it infinity.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, yeah?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, you can eat a hairy clam.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did she tell me to eat a hairy clit on?
[SPEAKER_06]: She said a hairy clam.
[SPEAKER_06]: Polish my pearl, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fucking gross.
[SPEAKER_04]: This show just got rated AO.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't believe.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think, I think, in like, what is this, episode 220?
[SPEAKER_04]: In 220 episodes of Orange House Radio, that was the foulest thing that bitch has ever said to me.
[SPEAKER_09]: I had the top Irene's crusty shit.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know, Rob.
[SPEAKER_11]: Remember, you are a douchebag.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, Rob is the official douchebag.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why are you bringing up like five-year-old drama of a guy that drives me nuts?
[SPEAKER_04]: There's this guy who drives me
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, it's like Neil's on a chalkboard.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, no, no, I'm not going to say it, because I'm not going to give attention.
[SPEAKER_08]: I will say it.
[SPEAKER_04]: He works for a major gaming blog now, and I'm just like, oh, this guy's so annoying.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, he called me a douchebag once at a DDR tournament, and my response, I was like, because Irene was with me, I was like, oh my god, Irene, I'm vinegar and water.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you hear that?
You're clean.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, at least I'm clean.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cut your hair.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, anyway, I'll
[SPEAKER_04]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't want to get into drama, because I really don't care.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm at least years old.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't even know why this person didn't like me, to be honest.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because he... I mean, I know why I don't like him, because he didn't like me.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like, you started it.
[SPEAKER_09]: He has an electrocuted corncob, but yes, it has this, but just so tight, that any time they pull it out, it bleeds.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can we please change the subject?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't want to talk about it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was just trying to talk about the years old drama.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, uh...
[SPEAKER_04]: Somebody, please, anybody.
[SPEAKER_04]: Was that the end of the mailbag?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, I told you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's close the mailbag and get back into the news, please.
[SPEAKER_09]: I blame Chris and Marissa for making me cry for the first time.
[SPEAKER_04]: We are running so long this segment.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, baby, any time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tiger Clawed is not Gaming Steve.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's Scott's issue.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't even know Gaming Steve.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyways, so speaking of idiotic, there's a brand new channel added to the Wii this week called Everybody Votes, which is not true because not everybody does vote.
[SPEAKER_11]: Should be locked out for... So, yeah, the Everybody Votes channel, and you get to vote on such wonderful topics like, what's better, dogs or cats?
[SPEAKER_11]: Woohoo!
[SPEAKER_11]: Yay, that's fun.
[SPEAKER_11]: Worth my Wii to be flashing, by the way, and it's still flashing because I have not turned it on since this stupid channel came out, but apparently you can vote on these, you find out the results, and then it gets, you know,
[SPEAKER_11]: Logged into your profile to how many you got right versus how many you got wrong.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I guess you can show people your wee penis.
[SPEAKER_11]: To be honest, I wish this channel was Everybody Poops because that would be a lot better.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be true.
[SPEAKER_04]: But should that be a question?
[SPEAKER_04]: Which do you prefer more in the bathroom, one or two?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, with two, you can read.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, one, you're... Anyway, this is disgusting.
[SPEAKER_04]: I actually think the channel is really cute.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't have a problem with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's... You know, it's not...
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the perfect kind of... Nintendo did not make any fanfare out of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is probably just something that used to be a tech demo.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, we're going to be seeing a lot of crap like this.
[SPEAKER_04]: But Nintendo did not try to sell this to anyone.
[SPEAKER_04]: They did not try to put it out like, by the week, because we had the Everyone Votes channel.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it was just like, hey, we're just going to put this up because we're bored.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to put up this Everyone Votes channel just because we have it, and here it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkDeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think it's a bad thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's cute.
[SPEAKER_01]: There aren't any kittens left because of all the masturbating.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's why.
[SPEAKER_04]: I see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did anybody else try the voting channel?
[SPEAKER_09]: I watched Extra for Do It last night.
[SPEAKER_04]: Was it cute though?
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought the channel was cute.
[SPEAKER_09]: I hate the entire world because cats are more awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, I believe it was Switzerland where cats outrank dogs.
[SPEAKER_04]: So let's all move to Switzerland.
[SPEAKER_04]: Norway.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have a Norway listener in chat tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love our Norwegian listener.
[SPEAKER_04]: So Olaf, we need to get Olaf the Viking a cat.
[SPEAKER_09]: I want pictures of, never mind, that's a Doctor Who reference.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, so go vote if you want on your Wii right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Another thing you can do on your Wii right now is download Kid Icarus.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you should know that some of the codes that you may remember from your childhood, they don't work.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you want to put in Icarus fights Medusa Angels, that code is not going to work.
[SPEAKER_04]: There is a warning before you download it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It says the original kit Icarus used allows players to use secret passwords.
[SPEAKER_04]: However, Virtual Console does not support these passwords.
[SPEAKER_04]: And at first I thought that meant passwords weren't going to work at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's not true.
[SPEAKER_04]: You still can use the old, you know, little jumble 0080C whatever type passwords.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just the secret ones won't work because apparently the original cartridge had an included module in it to process the special codes.
[SPEAKER_04]: I never realized that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But don't the emulators emulate those codes?
[SPEAKER_04]: So that seems so weird to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like if you play this on Nesticle or whatever those NES emulators are you use, can't you use those codes?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I don't get it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Uh, because they're lazy?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I don't know enough about hardware, I guess.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because they're too busy working on everybody votes to, I don't know, fix their virtual console stuff?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think, everybody votes was already done in some capacity, I think, as some type of, like, demonstration.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not, it's not that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm talking about, you know, um, this, this thing here.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, but really, maybe it was just done so that people would have to see how fucking hard Kid Icarus really was.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think a lot of y'all forgot, because you used to use those passwords to just beat the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: But Kid Icarus is fucking hard.
[SPEAKER_09]: It is, but it's awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's definitely worth your time.
[SPEAKER_09]: I love that game.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's worth five bucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: You'll never get a sequel!
[SPEAKER_04]: Never!
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck you, I hate you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, speaking of the Virtual Console, we do actually have some other news.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's a few of the Japan-only games that are going to be coming onto the US Virtual Console.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, it's actually, um, with a conversation with Nintendo of America, uh, Senior VP George Harrison, they, um, are looking into bringing some of the more successful Japanese franchises that have that cult following in the U.S., um, on the Virtual Console.
[SPEAKER_09]: Basically, those of us who are the niche gamers, they love us.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nintendo loves us!
[SPEAKER_09]: That's proof.
[SPEAKER_09]: So they're talking about, um, bringing over some of the games if they can have them translated properly.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry, but if they really loved us, they would have made the fucking thing region-free.
[SPEAKER_09]: True.
[SPEAKER_09]: However, they still haven't given me Guardian Legend!
[SPEAKER_09]: Bastards.
[SPEAKER_04]: Guardian Legend is that game we will always bitch about that we will never get on Virtual Console.
[SPEAKER_09]: Guardian Legend is the... Actually... Greatest 8-bit game ever made, that's all that needs to be said.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then it's followed by the greatest 16-bit game ever made.
[SPEAKER_04]: Run to a blood!
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, I think about, wasn't the MSX announced as one of the systems they were going to emulate in Japan on Virtual Console?
[SPEAKER_09]: I do believe so, because if we get an MSX emulator on here, do you know what that means we get?
[SPEAKER_04]: Metal fucking gear.
[SPEAKER_09]: Uh-uh.
[SPEAKER_09]: The real sequel to Metal Gear 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dude.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's it right there.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what I want.
[SPEAKER_04]: You write that right under Guardian Legend on the wish list.
[SPEAKER_09]: On MSX, there were two Guardian Legend games.
[SPEAKER_12]: That'd be on the same list of, yeah, sure, we'll implement online before we implement this shit.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fuck you, I hate you.
[SPEAKER_09]: But on the MSX, there actually were two Guardian Legend games.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's called Guardia.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've heard of Guardia.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've never played it, but that would be hot.
[SPEAKER_09]: I had a photograph of it once that my MSX emulator wouldn't run, so I was so upset.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I'm sure that everyone's going to be... Well, I don't know if anyone's really going to be interested in this, but apparently they're putting out Brunswick Pro Bowling for Nintendo Wii, the PlayStation 2, and PSP.
[SPEAKER_11]: Honestly, ask yourself.
[SPEAKER_11]: When ever...
[SPEAKER_12]: Ever, other than Wii Bowling, has there ever been a good bowling game on any console?
[SPEAKER_12]: You just said it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Wii Bowling.
[SPEAKER_12]: Other than Wii Bowling.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Tekken bowling game on Tekken.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, shush.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: For three seconds.
[SPEAKER_01]: Can I be really lame and not console-oriented and say that Elf Bowling was awesome?
[SPEAKER_04]: Wee!
[SPEAKER_04]: How about... What's the one they had at the Metreon years ago?
[SPEAKER_04]: Mega Bowling or whatever that thing was for you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Mega Touch Bowling.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, that wasn't at Metreon.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was at... Dave & Buster's has it too.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dave & Buster's with the giant screen.
[SPEAKER_04]: They had it at the Metreon too.
[SPEAKER_04]: I remember this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because we played it there.
[SPEAKER_09]: And Neo Geo Bowling, Ryoma says.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_09]: And Clubhouse Games.
[SPEAKER_09]: But...
[SPEAKER_04]: Because everybody loves Wii Bowling, somebody said, let's turn this into an actual full-fledged game.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, that's great.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's charge something that you can get, I don't know, for free.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's a pinball game called Nine Pin.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's just make another game that's exactly the same as the last one and charge you money for it.
[SPEAKER_11]: But that's okay because it runs with Pro Bowling.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I'm sure, to be honest, when it does come out, it'll be like $20.
[SPEAKER_11]: So who gives a shit?
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, it's going to be cheap.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, God crave.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: The last, what was it?
[SPEAKER_11]: The last, they had like some, I want to say, Extreme Bowling 2006 that came out last year.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was uber lame, by the way.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, hopefully, they will go with, you know, the same kind of gameplay as Wii Bowling, but somehow I think they're going to fuck it up because they always fuck it up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Comments from chat.
[SPEAKER_04]: James Patrick says, Elf Bowling, shooter.
[SPEAKER_04]: TJ and I...
[SPEAKER_04]: DJ Janai says, Elf Bowling is more fun if you're drunk.
[SPEAKER_04]: DJ Dark Knight says, Simpsons Bowling.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alpha Canogram agrees, Tekken Bowling.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gaming Nerd says, let's throw our Wiimotes directly into our TVs and break them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oops, I thought I was holding a bowling ball.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actdeft says, what I do want is a new baseball game for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Tiger Claw remembers.
[SPEAKER_04]: Guys, what about Hyper Bowling?
[SPEAKER_04]: It came with Microsoft Plus for the XP.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what it was.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was called Hyper Bowling.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you actually had a bowling ball.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because that was the version of it that they had in the arcades.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was Hyper Bowling, but with like an actual ball that you roll.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, forget it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was excited that Tigerclaw reminded me of the name of that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that it or any more stories?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: Next story is mine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whoops, my bad.
[SPEAKER_09]: Haha, fail.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it has to do with one of my very favorite countries.
[SPEAKER_04]: The only other country I've really been to.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't remember.
[SPEAKER_04]: I went to the Caribbean when I was seven, but that doesn't count.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the only other country I've really been to is Canada.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Canada, you know, even though we have a lot of Canadian listeners, things are kind of quiet gaming-wise in Canada.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, sure, you've got some of the game studios in Toronto, Vancouver, but for the most part, you don't hear a whole lot of big gaming news coming out of Canada.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, now, guess what?
[SPEAKER_04]: ESA has their sights set on Canada because apparently Canada has pirates galore.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yay, pirates!
[SPEAKER_04]: And they're saying that Canada has failed to deliver on promises of more stringent copyright laws and stepped up enforcements for laws already on the books.
[SPEAKER_04]: Quote, Canada remains far behind virtually all of its peers in the industrialized world with respect to its efforts to bring its copyright laws up to date with realities of the global digital networked environment.
[SPEAKER_04]: Indeed, even the major developing countries have progressed further and faster than Canada in meeting the challenge.
[SPEAKER_04]: Insert mandatory playing Canada joke here.
[SPEAKER_01]: Ace.
[SPEAKER_01]: I have to say from personal experience, all my Canadian friends love Warcraft, but then again, who doesn't?
[SPEAKER_01]: And pot.
[SPEAKER_01]: And preferably at the same time.
[SPEAKER_01]: Which really confused me.
[SPEAKER_01]: So what does a Canadian pirate look like?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jack Sparrow that kind of smells like maple?
[SPEAKER_09]: I have this image of a bobsled that looks like a ship with a sail on it and dogs.
[SPEAKER_09]: Arr, mush.
[SPEAKER_09]: No.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to Canada later this year.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Canada's a fun place.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I'm going to find me a Canadian pirate.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe he'll find your booty?
[SPEAKER_09]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_09]: What the fuck is a ferret?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a bad joke.
[SPEAKER_04]: Look, I'll hit myself with Kirby.
[SPEAKER_04]: Isn't
[SPEAKER_09]: DNL's Kirby?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's DNL's Kirby.
[SPEAKER_04]: She needs to come get it.
[SPEAKER_09]: DNL, you need to come get your Kirby.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I'm getting my coobies all over this Kirby that DMN brought on my nipple.
[SPEAKER_04]: Look at that.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just for you, Renee.
[SPEAKER_09]: He's sexing it up for you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I have news that's better than blaming Canada for shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, actually, it's not really all that exciting.
[SPEAKER_09]: But DirecTV has something called Game Lounge now, and it's this interactive channel for family stuff that you play through your satellite box.
[SPEAKER_09]: So it's like,
[SPEAKER_09]: Xbox Live Suck Edition.
[SPEAKER_09]: It has games that are based on kids shows like Spongebob.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it has competitive games where you can compete for prizes and money.
[SPEAKER_09]: And you should check it out, I guess, if you are into family games.
[SPEAKER_09]: I like for my games to have blood and sex.
[SPEAKER_09]: Gaming Lounge?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's called Game Lounge.
[SPEAKER_04]: Game Lounge.
[SPEAKER_04]: Was Orange Lounge taken?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I guess it was.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey guys, I have this really great idea.
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was it right there.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was the recreation.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shot down again by Jamie.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: Heart!
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've gone very long this segment.
[SPEAKER_04]: Almost two hours.
[SPEAKER_04]: Marissa, can you believe this show is only half over?
[SPEAKER_04]: If this is torture, then chain me to the wall.
[SPEAKER_11]: But the listeners like it when it's long.
[SPEAKER_04]: You guys like it long, don't you?
[SPEAKER_04]: You like it long.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, we're going to take a quick break, and we're going to come back with more of Orange Lounge Radio with Part B of our show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and is podcast to the world twice a week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stay tuned to our podcast feed for the conclusion of this week's Orange Lounge Radio.