[SPEAKER_07]: Tonight, May 24th, 2009, an OLR favor game is getting remade on the DS and Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did Sony confirm the smaller PS3 with their lawsuits?
[SPEAKER_07]: Will I soon be able to rent games on my PSP?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hello everybody out there on the internet and welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: We are that show dedicated to video games, video gaming, gaming culture, and the gamer lifestyle.
[SPEAKER_06]: And joining you every week is myself, Rob Roberts, and my awesome co-host, say hello to DarkSakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Porn!
[SPEAKER_06]: How are you doing?
[SPEAKER_02]: Porn.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I just wanted to say porn.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is the internet for porn?
[SPEAKER_03]: I wanted the first word that I said on the show tonight to be porn.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, well there you go, it was.
[SPEAKER_03]: Second word of the show, official word of the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes?
[SPEAKER_06]: Tribble.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, so are you into Tribble porn or something?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I went to see Star Trek again for the third time in the theater.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then we went back to Becky's house and watched Tribble with Tribbles and then Trial and Tribblations.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you see the new HD?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because apparently they remade a bunch of Star Trek episodes in HD.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have to tell you, everyone who goes to see the movie or goes to see it again, when they first show Scotty, look on his desk, there's a Tribble.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: OMG spoilers.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, like the Tribble.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, and the way they defeat the guy is Tribbles.
[SPEAKER_06]: So since you brought up porn, what would you say is your favorite porn?
[SPEAKER_03]: The Boneheads.
The Boneheads.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ali McFeel Bible Black
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's all good.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, look in the chat, chat.orangelonestradio.com is always there when, you know, every night, every week that we tape this show, you guys are always there to entertain us with your chat comments.
[SPEAKER_06]: And we have Tiger Claw says, Sky, the classic Star Trek series in HD is now available in Blu-ray.
[SPEAKER_06]: And yeah, I've heard about that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Plus all the old movies are available in Blu-ray too.
[SPEAKER_06]: But wake me when they have the next generation movies in Blu-ray.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love the Mesa Suma.
[SPEAKER_03]: Triple porn aren't triples born pregnant.
[SPEAKER_03]: By the way, if you pluralize something, do not use an apostrophe.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: One Night Stands in chat says, I just saw a porno called Six Fags Magic Mount Him.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to see that.
[SPEAKER_06]: That sounds funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: See, those are my favorite ones.
[SPEAKER_06]: The ones that are based off of actual movies.
[SPEAKER_03]: And no, Final Fuck X was crap.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good cosplay, really crappy porn.
[SPEAKER_06]: We talk about games sometimes on this show.
[SPEAKER_06]: But you're probably wondering, where's Loki?
[SPEAKER_06]: You haven't heard him yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: We gagged him with duct tape and tape.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not a drunk show though, it's a beer show
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura is drinking beer.
[SPEAKER_06]: I, however, due to everything I went through last year, I'm not drinking.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have vodka.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, just alcohol in general is a bad idea.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have some rubbing alcohol.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have wine once in a while.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't want wine.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have witch hazel.
[SPEAKER_06]: I got to be sober tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: I got to set a good example for the kids since you're setting a bad one.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have peroxide.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, look.
[SPEAKER_06]: Shut up and tell us about your gaming week.
[SPEAKER_03]: I played Sims.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: I've been enjoying porn and sims.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've actually found a bunch of naughty items that I just was curious to see how they worked so I downloaded them just to see.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're really horrible.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why do you think people go instantly to doing dirty porno things?
[SPEAKER_03]: It goes back to the first things that you learn in any language is how to cuss and how to talk about sex.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: The Sims Body Shop thing, where you can, you know, if you download different skins and everything, you can make your own Sims look pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, I showed Rob one that I made of a couple of characters I used to have, and I've even done one for, you know, quite a number of my old tabletop game characters are pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: I did one of me.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to do one of Rob, just because it's funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rob Sim Rob Sim
[SPEAKER_03]: The last one I built, though, is pretty damn cool, and I love it, and I would actually live in that house if I could.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I've been, you know, sort of letting out an artistic thing, you know, something that's been lagging, you know, while I've been in school.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess my artsy stuff has been focused toward...
[SPEAKER_03]: My assignments towards this theme, that theme, getting this done, getting that done.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I've really just sort of enjoyed having kind of a point-and-click kind of artistry lately.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, where I don't have to really use my brain so much.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can just pick things as I want to.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's been pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: You might need to play some Ragnarok this week, because I'm thinking about signing up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Really?
[SPEAKER_03]: I haven't played Ragnarok in about a month now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is the same girl who every week is like, oh, you should sign up on my server.
[SPEAKER_06]: You should sign up and play some Ragnarok.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you sign up and play with me, I'll play.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, because I might do that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Transitioning into my gaming week, I was playing a little bit of World of Warcraft this week, of course, as usual, but...
[SPEAKER_06]: There's theatrics going on.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll leave it at that.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's theatrics.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just kind of making me go, whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, I play games for fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know why everybody else can't do the same thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, yeah, so I'm thinking about just chilling out in another game for a little while while I can.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because life's going to get very busy with, you know, in a couple weeks being E3 and everything going on.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, you know, now's a good time to sell me on other MMOs if you want to get me to check it out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Even part of me was like, I should go back and check out Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_06]: But then I was like...
[SPEAKER_06]: No, that's really a bad idea.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a bad idea, Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: Other games in my gaming week You know, I haven't actually played an awful lot I know, it's kind of like, it's affecting both Jamie and I But I did fire up the 360 earlier this week And was still playing some Space Invaders Extreme And I finally bought Outrun Because I checked out the demo like a while back But I finally actually had some time to sit down
[SPEAKER_06]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_06]: I need to play more of the multiplayer though.
[SPEAKER_06]: I only really checked out single player this week and was trying to beat it and would come so close and can't seem to beat it because I suck at video games.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just didn't spend enough time with it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Otherwise, I've been watching some movies and just catching up on some other stuff around the house and other things going on in my personal life.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tomorrow's going to be a big video gaming day, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't have a lot of other stuff planned, so my things to do are clean and play video games and to get in a bunch of things before E3.
[SPEAKER_06]: I had a Twitter...
[SPEAKER_06]: message asking me to check out Team Fortress 2 which I'm going to try to do tomorrow also I really need to get in and play more Left 4 Dead so I might make it a PC day tomorrow but I also want to go back and visit some of my Xbox 360 RPGs like I don't know why I have this real itch to go back and do Lost Odyssey because I only really got through like maybe the first third or the first half and I really want to go and finish that so we'll see so yeah that's my plans for this upcoming week
[SPEAKER_06]: How about you guys?
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you guys have a good gaming week?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm looking at chat room.
[SPEAKER_06]: Cheeseburger says, I saw Star Trek twice already and I'm going to see it again.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got you beat.
[SPEAKER_06]: Unfolded Raptor says, I've been playing Bionic Commando all day and I'm already 63% done.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm kind of curious how fun that is.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've been hearing some mixed things on it, so I'm kind of curious what our chatters think of that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Certainly I like the old school one.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I like the redone old school one.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was a real fun one on Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um...
[SPEAKER_06]: GameGuru asks when is E3?
[SPEAKER_06]: E3 is not this upcoming week like tomorrow but it's a week after like it starts a week from Tuesday June 2nd is when it starts and I'll be going down there Monday night so we're still going to have shows actually through E3 week because DarkSakura is not going I do not believe we're going to be doing anything live from E3 but stay tuned to the Twitter and to the website you never know what surprise we might have cooked up I am going to take my video camera
[SPEAKER_06]: But as I was telling Bobby earlier, Bobby Blackwolf, who's before us here on Sunday nights on All Games Radio, I don't think there's a lot we can do that all the big websites aren't already going to do.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're not going to be the first to report on the news.
[SPEAKER_06]: We rarely are.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're not going to really be on the cutting edge of the latest and greatest E3 news.
[SPEAKER_06]: But what we can do...
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, you guys have been reading what's going on at E3.
[SPEAKER_06]: What do you want us to dig and find?
[SPEAKER_06]: We're your reporters on the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're the show where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_06]: What do you want us to find?
[SPEAKER_06]: So we'll be definitely using Twitter and the website and some other things to find out what you guys want us to dig up at E3.
[SPEAKER_06]: So look for that and our reports, be it in video form or other tweets or what have you.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we'll be looking at that.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm sure the person listens to this show because it seemed like the kind of thing where it's just to get a rise out of us.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like, dude, we do this stuff for free.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's like reading stuff like that is really disheartening.
[SPEAKER_06]: Leave five-star reviews for the shows you like.
[SPEAKER_06]: But what good is it to leave a one-star review for these other shows and people that work hard?
[SPEAKER_02]: Unless they're really crap.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would like to think we're not really crap.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what, Rob?
[SPEAKER_03]: Honestly, I don't care.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't, but it sucks because that, and I blame Apple.
[SPEAKER_06]: It affects your ranking on the whole if you go in and look at the lineups of the shows in there.
[SPEAKER_06]: We were on page one and now we dropped to page three.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's kind of disappointing.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the only thing that bugs me about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Otherwise, I don't care.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll elaborate it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_06]: How about some gaming news, shall we?
[SPEAKER_06]: About.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, kind of a follow-up to something we were talking about last week.
[SPEAKER_06]: 3D Realms.
[SPEAKER_06]: And we were talking about how 3D Realms went under, quote-unquote, and took Duke Nukem Forever with it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, this is interesting because apparently 3D Realms actually released a public statement this week after the whole development team was dissolved that was working on Duke Nukem Forever.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they said they are not closed and they are not closing.
[SPEAKER_06]: However, they are saying that Take-Two will be retaining the publishing rights to Duke Nukem forever, and they will be able to sell the game directly to the public.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I feel like there's two sides to every story, and I still can't help but think, guys, what were you producing on this game?
[SPEAKER_06]: There was not a lot of public buzz going on because they refused to release screenshots.
[SPEAKER_06]: There was no demo.
[SPEAKER_06]: They hadn't shown at E3 for years.
[SPEAKER_06]: What did they expect was going to happen?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, as much as I was excited for Duke Nukem Forever, like the last guy, tease us a little bit with something.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I understand, Take-Two probably had the open book, and they got to see everything that was going on, but still, I mean, it's a business.
[SPEAKER_06]: and if people aren't it's tough to sell a game in this day and age with you know look at Prey and how kind of disappointing that ended up being sales wise you know if there's not the buzz out there for the game it's not going to be pretty and I bet you anything now that Take-Two does have the rights to this we're going to see this game out in a year or two tops two years tops this game comes out well we can if it ever really does I mean honestly I sort of lost my expectation of it really coming out
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess that's true.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I even think at this point it might be a subpar game, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not going to write it off completely.
[SPEAKER_06]: Never write off a game until you play it.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what I'm planning to do.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here's a game that some people might get to play if they have a Dreamcast.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's coming out for Windows, Linux, and Dreamcast.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a homebrew game called Hypertension, and it is a re-imaging of Blood, which uses the Doom-based Edge engine.
[SPEAKER_03]: So yeah, it's kind of old school in that sense, but it's coming out on Dreamcast, so...
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, why not?
[SPEAKER_03]: If you got it, buy it, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm looking a little bit at the play from it, and I'm really not impressed.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, then again, it's old school.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's Doom-like.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is that not?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's got some 3D, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not pixely.
[SPEAKER_06]: It looks a little like, yeah, Doomish.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's quakey.
[SPEAKER_06]: Doomish meets, yeah, kind of in that vein, the early 90s, or I guess maybe the mid-90s.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the weapon is aerosol and a lighter.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I mean, is there really a market for these types of Dreamcast games?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Does everybody report on these games because it's like, OMG, new Dreamcast game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who would have thought?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's notable, you know, that there's being homebrewed, you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: People still love the Dreamcast, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: I do.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: And one thing I did love about the Dreamcast is that there was so much homebrew available for it.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what I play most of all on my Dreamcast?
[SPEAKER_06]: NES emulator.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, honestly, that's one of the greatest things about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: We busted out Marvel vs. Capcom 2 the other night.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you did do some gaming this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, Dan did.
[SPEAKER_06]: A little bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: We is in my household.
[SPEAKER_06]: Gotcha.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course, Metroid Prime 3 was the only one that's been released on the Wii in this country.
[SPEAKER_06]: However, Metroid Prime 1 and 2 were re-released over in Japan, kind of the whole new Wii controls.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, guess what?
[SPEAKER_06]: Nintendo announced this week that the Metroid Prime Trilogy will be coming to the U.S.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that means that Metroid Prime will be kind of repackaged.
[SPEAKER_06]: The first two games will have the new Wii controls and the whole widescreen graphics, which, you know, I bet a lot of people have mixed feelings about.
[SPEAKER_06]: But if you never really bought...
[SPEAKER_06]: One or two, you know, this might be a good way to revisit those games.
[SPEAKER_06]: The only bummer is, no news here about Metroid Prime 4.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, if you have Metroid Prime Trilogy, it kind of insinuates there may not be a Metroid Prime 4.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I do have that hope that maybe that's one of the surprises they're going to pull out of E3, but I don't know, I wouldn't bet on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: I do too, and I think a lot of people want that, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is it really something that might sell?
[SPEAKER_06]: Or something we would get not on the DS?
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_02]: Even more the Willa Blend.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think if a new 2D Metroid is going to come out, it's going to just be on the DS.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's kind of the bummer about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I like the DS and all, but I like to play the old school games on my TV as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: The big surround sound.
[SPEAKER_06]: Look at some of the games that are 2D, 3D hybrids that were on consoles that were pretty good.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, Street Fighter 4 is a perfect example, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: 2D fighter, awesome use of 3D in it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why couldn't you make a platformer in that kind of vein?
[SPEAKER_06]: or a game going back a little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Last we really got for platformers was, I think, LittleBigPlanet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, that's a great example.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was going to say Beautiful Joe, even though that's back on the GameCube.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's still a good example of 2D platformers.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Shinagogo.
[SPEAKER_06]: They can still be a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, if anything, I think that LittleBigPlanet proved that right away.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rene says in chat, Metroid Prime 4, you lost your power-ups again, moron.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess that's true.
[SPEAKER_06]: How many times can we go through the same story of, whoops, lost my power-ups.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe we can use dumb blonde as an excuse, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, just make it a prequel.
[SPEAKER_06]: Make it another prequel.
[SPEAKER_06]: TigerClaw says the next one will be called Metroid Prime 4, Electric Boogaloo.
[SPEAKER_06]: One can hope.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would only be if, that was what they should have called Metroid Prime 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: Brad from PodCulture says, Metroid Prime 4, Mission to Moscow.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_06]: If you want to join us and chat live on this Sunday evening, chat.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, this is something that I am going to have to get.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is on my must-buy Wii list.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're doing a haunted house simulator, and it is going to be Ju-on, which is The Grudge.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, as in the same movie, and probably not including Sarah Michelle Gellar.
[SPEAKER_03]: It already came out in Japan a few weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_03]: It will be localized hopefully pre-Halloween.
[SPEAKER_03]: So hopefully we'll be able to see it.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's actually being consulted on it is Shimizu Takashi who was the guy who directed actually not only the Japanese version but he directed the first American one.
[SPEAKER_03]: The second one is utter shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't go see it.
[SPEAKER_03]: but it's basically you're using the Wiimote as a flashlight on screen and you go through a warehouse a mannequin factory a hospital just basically all your usual oh my god I'm scared places but it's supposed to have a twist where you can use your second Wiimote to make in game things happen immediately
[SPEAKER_03]: In fact, the actual quote from this article, and I have to read this Rob, is to make in-game events happen immediately to make the player jump and hate you forever.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: And there's a YouTube they're promoting this with that just shows a bunch of scared people.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, I'm all for scary games that are going to make me jump out of my seat.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Grudge, you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: The first movie was cool, but.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've seen the second one, the Japanese movie.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've seen the TV movie.
[SPEAKER_06]: Jeff and I were renting movies the other night, and I saw The Grudge 3 on DVD.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I looked at that, and I was like, lol, there's a third one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Was it American?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it was American Grudge 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: It said The Grudge 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know if it was maybe the Japanese one being marketed as an American one.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, but it was there.
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: I crap you not.
[SPEAKER_03]: The second one's funny because it's about What's-Her-Face doing dirty things with the main character.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not dirty that way.
[SPEAKER_03]: She's... It's very interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's very interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, 2009, direct-to-video.
[SPEAKER_06]: It came out.
[SPEAKER_03]: That is shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: Stars Shawnee Smith from the Saw series is in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Grudge 3, I don't know when this came out.
[SPEAKER_06]: It came out 12th of May, so it just came out.
[SPEAKER_03]: It doesn't exist in my universe.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you want to hear the plot?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: A young Japanese woman who holds the key to stopping the evil spirit of Kayako travels to the haunted Chicago apartment from the sequel... I'm not going to read the rest, because you didn't really want to hear it anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just wanted to see if you recognized it from any of the Japanese ones.
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ghosts don't move from Japan to Chicago.
[SPEAKER_06]: All they have to do is just hop on an airplane.
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's someone who completely just knows crap about, you know, hauntings and anything.
[SPEAKER_03]: They usually stay localized.
[SPEAKER_06]: TigerClaw in chat says they tend to milk those movies by creating crappy direct-to-DVD sequels.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that's true.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, there's a sequel to Donnie Darko that just came out too that was direct-to-video.
[SPEAKER_06]: I haven't watched that yet either.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, that I want to see.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's been actually in writing and production for quite a while now.
[SPEAKER_03]: and I really want to see it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, Jeff rented that and he wanted to watch it but I was kind of like, I don't remember the first one well enough.
[SPEAKER_06]: I haven't seen the first one in like 10 years because seriously, they're making a sequel to a movie that's like 10 years old.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, I need to just go watch the first one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here's my copy right here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Really?
[SPEAKER_03]: I have the director's edition.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I need to watch it at some point.
[SPEAKER_03]: Donnie Darko is a fantastic movie and plus, you know, any movie that Drew Barrymore is going to produce and I love Drew Barrymore.
[SPEAKER_03]: She would be like my secret girlfriend if I could.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: So...
[SPEAKER_06]: I feel like slitting my wrist now.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm bleeding my pain on your face.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was so gothic and tragic.
[SPEAKER_06]: Quote,
[SPEAKER_06]: eBay is actually pulling the auctions on this and Amazon got a notice and takedown and all this fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good luck though getting all those mom and pop stores that still sell this but still puts a little dent in it and makes it a little bit harder to get if you are looking for these cartridges.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rini, though, in chat says, Flashcards are a waste of money.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi there, SD card slot on DSi.
[SPEAKER_06]: Goldanthro admits that Amazon is where he got his R4.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not into the hacking thing like a lot of y'all are.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't really have the patience for that stuff, so I don't really do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I know this is probably a loss to those that were looking forward to the homebrew.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you were using it for piracy, though, well, then, you know, it's hard to feel a little pity for you.
[SPEAKER_06]: But at least the homebrew, as far as all that goes, that is kind of a bummer.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, anyhow, let's move on with some more news.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, in other news, we have some Sega stuff that makes me particularly happy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Going to be coming out for DS and Wii is Jumbo Safari, actually.
[SPEAKER_03]: They are taking the old arcade title and making it pretty and more modern looking and having more stuff happen to make people happy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Animals in Need The DS version of course will work with the stylus and the Wii version will have a lasso gameplay that uses the Wiimote and you can have a 2 player and 4 player party version so there will be more
[SPEAKER_06]: OLR has friends in high places
[SPEAKER_06]: But, you know, Sega's got a pretty good track record otherwise, so I'm really excited about Jumbo Safari.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know about you, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you looking forward to this?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like to play the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I still want my freaking Planet Harrier.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you hear me, Sega?
[SPEAKER_03]: Whores.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I love you.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm trying not to speculate on... Bring me swag!
[SPEAKER_06]: That'll be worthwhile.
[SPEAKER_06]: Jake Hunter Detective Story, Memories of the Past
[SPEAKER_06]: Johnny Bravo, Datorama, a couple games with the preface of Crazy Chicken, including Star Carts, Pharaoh's Treasure, Imagine Boutique Owner comes out this week as well, as well as Space Camp, which I thought I remembered Loki reading a couple weeks ago, so I don't know if this game was pushed back or what.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sadly, no, it is not based on the great 80s movie with the same name, so don't get your hopes up.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Personal Trainer Walking, also on the DS this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: LOL what?
[SPEAKER_06]: Learn how to walk this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: On the PC, Hinterland, Orc Lords, Age of Pirate 2, City of Abandoned Ships, Dragon Sky, Sherlock Holmes vs. Jack the Ripper.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ooh, that might be kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: Damnation is another game that comes out on the PC this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Moving on to the consoles, one release on PS2 this week, it's Secret Agent Clank.
[SPEAKER_06]: and on the PlayStation 3 you also get Damnation, Infamous, Cross Edge, Trash Panic on the PSP Crimson Gems Saga and on the Wii another version of Space Camp and the Munchables and on the Xbox 360 Damnation as well as Wallace and Gromit 2, Wallace and Gromit Episode 2 The Last Resort which I believe is a Xbox Live game.
[SPEAKER_06]: That is all that's coming out in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_06]: this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's travel over to the U.K., DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_03]: For the U.K.
[SPEAKER_03]: on PS2, we have Secret Agent Clank.
[SPEAKER_03]: 28th, we have Inferno Pool and Saints Row 2 Corporate Warfare and Trash Panic, whatever that is.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have R. Tonelico, Two Melody of Metafalca, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: If I can, Falisa, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't read it.
[SPEAKER_03]: My brain doesn't work.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is trash panic what my mother does when I leave a Coke can on the table because I forgot to throw it away or what have you or got lazy and just walked away?
[SPEAKER_06]: That sounds like what it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: Trash panic.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't worry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mama will clean it.
[SPEAKER_03]: More on the 29th.
[SPEAKER_03]: Boom Blox Bash Party.
[SPEAKER_03]: Brain Exercise with Dr. Kalashima and Fuel and Virtua Tennis 2009.
[SPEAKER_03]: PDC World Championship Darts and Valhalla Nights 2 on PSP.
[SPEAKER_06]: Shinsengoku Musou 5 Empires
[SPEAKER_06]: Coming out in other places, I'm sorry, coming out on other consoles in the same place, Infamous comes out in Asian regions, but it's not quite out in Japan this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: However, Shinsengoku Musou 5 comes out as well on the PlayStation 3, and Agaresenki comes out with a price reduction this week, down to $44.90.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also a game called The Last Guy comes out from Sony Computer themselves.
[SPEAKER_06]: I am not sure, this is an action game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not sure what this is a port of, but it looks to be some type of shooter game.
[SPEAKER_06]: But what's kind of cool about it, it looks like it uses Google Earth.
[SPEAKER_06]: Seriously, doesn't the backgrounds here look like something you'd see in Google Earth?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, a bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that comes out this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: And looking on other consoles, going over to the Nintendo Wii, just one released this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ogon no Kizuna comes out this week, which is not a game I've heard of.
[SPEAKER_06]: It looks kind of similar to a Dynasty Warriors-ish type of game, but with a little more role-playing elements mixed in, so check that out.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you like, on the PlayStation 2, the Grand Theft Auto games get a price reduction this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's something to look forward to in Japan.
[SPEAKER_06]: On the Nintendo DS, Claymore, Gingan no Majo comes out this week, as well as Days of Memories 3 from SNK.
[SPEAKER_06]: Gaia Kukuten Kenji comes out as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: It has a Premium Edition release as well from Capcom.
[SPEAKER_06]: That, oh, that's, you know what that is?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's Ace Attorney Investigations, Miles Edgeworth.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what, Rob?
[SPEAKER_03]: I do have to say that your Japanese is improving greatly.
[SPEAKER_03]: At least the show's been good.
[SPEAKER_06]: This show's been good for something, huh?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also on the Nintendo DS, one more release for you from Sega, Suzumiya Haruhi no Shokuryetsu.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's the melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya.
[SPEAKER_06]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_03]: Because Haruhi is God.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, actually she is.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the premise of the story.
[SPEAKER_03]: She's God.
[SPEAKER_06]: Quickly looking at the PSP release dates.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ghost in the Shell.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, these are all movies.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't see any games this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bamboo Blade is the only game it looks to be this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: So check that out if you'd like.
[SPEAKER_06]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's it for Japanese release dates.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's go back into some gaming news and talk about some music that's been licensed for an upcoming Q Entertainment game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Kind of interesting about this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently, Tiesto and BT Songs have been licensed for this new game from Q Entertainment.
[SPEAKER_06]: The game is called QJ based on some... I guess some folks have been digging around some of the licensing information sites.
[SPEAKER_06]: The songs that were licensed.
[SPEAKER_06]: Love Comes Again from Tiesto.
[SPEAKER_06]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, I don't know much about this, but if it's Q Entertainment, then it's Mizuguchi.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, you know, I love him.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's very few games he's put out that I haven't liked.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm even counting 99 Nights.
[SPEAKER_06]: I forgave that game's shortcomings just because I'm a whore for Tetsuya Mizuguchi games.
[SPEAKER_06]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: More about this game hopefully at E3.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hopefully.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fingers crossed.
[SPEAKER_03]: Killzone 2, Bullet 4D Interactive Ad, Red Faction, Guerrilla Multiplayer, and Infamous
[SPEAKER_03]: PS3 game content Riddick, Dark Athena, Premium Multiplayer Pack We've got some more for Fear 2 Tom Clancy's Hawks, Pain Motorstorm Pacific Rift, Little Big Planet A bunch of stuff for Little Big Planet Guitar Hero World Tour, the European track Rock Band Alice Cooper Pack That's cool Rock Band Taking Back Sunday Kids Don't Follow by The Replacements For PSP games we have Fading Shadows and Creatures Raised in Space
[SPEAKER_06]: Creatures raised in space.
[SPEAKER_06]: Amazing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I actually logged into Home this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's one other game, quote-unquote, I played.
[SPEAKER_06]: Boy, Home is really expanding.
[SPEAKER_06]: Say what you will about whether Home is a game or any fun, all with quotes.
[SPEAKER_06]: But they're sure pouring a lot of expansions into it, which I guess is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: It seems like you have a lot of new stuff to explore if you haven't used it in a while.
[SPEAKER_06]: So props to them for that.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a new...
[SPEAKER_06]: Lord, no.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I unfortunately would have to say no.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's why she's in the kitchen.
[SPEAKER_06]: She's always in the kitchen and never in the bedroom.
[SPEAKER_06]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Moving on with some more news, talking about Sony.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, well, it looks like Sony is going to be threatening to sue companies that are publishing images of the PS3.
[SPEAKER_06]: Remember we were talking about this last week?
[SPEAKER_06]: We had some images leak out of the new PS3.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, apparently Sony has been demanding that these companies stop doing this.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I know this all started from, I guess, like their Taiwanese branch or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, dude, when you threaten to sue, doesn't it kind of prove that the story is true?
[SPEAKER_06]: That was my first thought, is like, well, way to give it away, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, otherwise, wouldn't they just release that good old-fashioned line of, oh, Sony will not comment on rumors and speculation at this time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Look for our E3 speech.
[SPEAKER_06]: But if you stick the lawyers on them, doesn't it kind of prove it to be true?
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe I'm crazy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, how about some, I guess, happier news?
[SPEAKER_03]: We are actually going to be getting some PlayStation 1 classic games for the PS1 Classic Store.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have been getting information from the ESRB because you know how they love to leak stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: And five games are supposed to be coming to the online service.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have...
[SPEAKER_03]: Among them, Resident Evil Director's Cut and Metal Gear Solid.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also among those rated is Special Ops Covert Assault and Ranger Elite and Tom Clancy's Rainbow Six.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: But dude, Metal Freakin' Gear and Resident Evil Director's Cut, I will have to go along with all the bad voice acting because I can quote that game, you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: What is it?
[SPEAKER_03]: I hope this is not Chris's blood.
[SPEAKER_03]: So.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe the hidden porn chat will be kind of embedded in the game somewhere.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because remember that?
[SPEAKER_06]: There's like YouTube out there where they mix and match all the dialogue into something disgusting.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to tell you this because I know how you can do it.
[SPEAKER_03]: There was a...
[SPEAKER_03]: A file reader that let you read the audio and video files off of PlayStation games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because, I don't know if you remember, back in the day, the first MP3s out for Bus to Move 2?
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, I did those.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, on my old website.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was the first person that I saw, that I noticed, that had them online, right after the game came out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um...
[SPEAKER_03]: but there's a little reader program that you can get to rip the files off and then just record them, convert them to WAV or whatever and record them or whatever so that's actually how they pulled all this off there there's also how they got the thing about Maria in Castlevania where an ending that they didn't put into the game of her actually being taken over by the succubus so you can find out, it was a lot easier to find stuff
[SPEAKER_06]: RedbookAudio.com
[SPEAKER_06]: Right, but no, I'm saying after that.
[SPEAKER_06]: We used to rip them by hooking them through the mixing board.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm surprised people didn't do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, you could still also pull them off doing the... It wasn't RA, it was like SX or SA reader or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_03]: But yeah, I used to do that back in the day.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it was really easy to do those.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, well, apparently there's a lot of rumbling going on about what's going on at E3 and possibly a new version of Metal Gear Solid apparently being rumored right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: And a lot of this has to do with the teaser graphic that showed up on Kojima Productions' website.
[SPEAKER_06]: I saw that too
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm surprised if this is Metal Gear Solid 5 because it seems kind of soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is it just me?
[SPEAKER_06]: Or does it seem like 4 hasn't really been out long enough?
[SPEAKER_06]: Am I crazy?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: But you know, between the magazine, Famitsu Magazine, E3 coming up next week with this countdown seems to be pointing to, and all this, I mean, if there's a time to make a big announcement, I suppose this would be it.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because you know how while the market is, you know, struck while the iron's hot, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_03]: I really don't want to put any speculation on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I really don't.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I build myself way too much up to be too excited about something.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to wait for something a little bit more concrete before I make my judgment.
[SPEAKER_06]: Comment from your chat room, chat.orange-radio.com Actdeft says, the countdown is a countdown for a countdown for a countdown for a countdown.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I'm getting kind of sick of that crap too.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_06]: Just announce it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Announce it or don't.
[SPEAKER_06]: One countdown to a big announcement might be okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: But counting down to another countdown is stupid.
[SPEAKER_06]: Very stupid.
[SPEAKER_06]: One Night Stands in chat says, was the five outlined a definite five or could it have been an S?
[SPEAKER_06]: Very good comment.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some people are speculating it might have been an S. So maybe it's a new like Metal Gear Solid S type game or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let me look at it for a second.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let me look at it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was kind of like, well, it's one of those like fonts where it's very like pixelated.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it could be a five or an S. Very easy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, let me have a look if it loads.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not loading.
[SPEAKER_06]: Trust me.
[SPEAKER_06]: It could be either one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Other comments.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alpha Cananogram in chat says it's just an announcement, which is true.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's only an announcement.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not something we should get too excited about.
[SPEAKER_06]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, how about something that might be worth getting excited about?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, if you don't have iTunes or an iPhone, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: PSP may be having a music download service.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sony's been thinking about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: They released a survey in January to check for consumer interest.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, it seems that they are considering on...
[SPEAKER_03]: and having other recording companies work with them.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Sony, they have their own music division, but they're just thinking about it right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: So they might have a digital music download, but maybe not.
[SPEAKER_06]: It might happen.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're thinking about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're sending their little slimy tentacles out to feel for it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm kind of surprised it's one of those things they haven't been thinking about for quite some time.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Again, I use the whole college kid thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who do PSPs sell best to?
[SPEAKER_06]: College kids.
[SPEAKER_06]: To replace iPods because they do everything else like games and the internet and all this.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it kind of seems like one of those things that I'm surprised they didn't do this a long freaking time ago.
[SPEAKER_06]: Especially when you consider the fact what else does Sony have?
[SPEAKER_06]: A big music label, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: So, why is this taking so long?
[SPEAKER_03]: Seriously, Sony's got a big, you know, they're big stinky tentacle fingers in the music industry, so why not?
[SPEAKER_03]: I just think, though, that they tend to behave a bit conservatively when they don't need to.
[SPEAKER_03]: Have you noticed that?
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess, a little bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: They'll venture out into something that they think is innovative and new, but with something that they see as tried and true.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're like, I don't wanna.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're doing it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't wanna.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alpha Catanagram in chat says, Sky, they did, it was called Connect, the ATRAC Atarak 3 store, which closed down.
[SPEAKER_06]: They were planning on doing it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hmm, interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't remember that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Was that something for just the PSP specifically?
[SPEAKER_06]: Or was that something to, you know...
[SPEAKER_06]: There were like a million people that were going to launch something to compete with iTunes.
[SPEAKER_06]: And very few of them succeeded.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, you could say that Napster somewhat succeeded because it's a different business model.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I think the biggest competition for iTunes has probably been, what, Amazon.com maybe?
[SPEAKER_06]: But, I mean, what else is out there that's successfully competed with iTunes?
[SPEAKER_06]: And when I say successfully, carries a market share even one-tenth the size of what Apple has.
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: No one.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's practically a monopoly on Apple's part.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, and that's what they're kind of saying there in chat.
[SPEAKER_06]: So is this something new that maybe is trying to launch, and Alpha Caninogram confirms, connect with Sony's iTunes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, well, a million people tried to launch something to compete with iTunes, and they all failed because none of them stood out.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was too much competition amongst each other, and iTunes already had the player to go with the store.
[SPEAKER_06]: But also, oh, I want to read this comment from Marissa Congusto in chat.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, that's right.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's Marissa.
[SPEAKER_06]: My dad thought he was doing me a big favor getting me a mini-disc player instead of an iPod ages ago.
[SPEAKER_06]: Face palm.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_06]: I feel your pain.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want a mini-disc player.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have an HD DVD player.
[SPEAKER_03]: So do I. I actually want a mini-disc player pretty badly.
[SPEAKER_03]: They do some good things with mini-discs.
[SPEAKER_03]: Really?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's still, I think, somewhat supported in Japan.
[SPEAKER_06]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_06]: Weird.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's another example where Sony's tried to go, we're going to do all this new stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, Betamax.
[SPEAKER_03]: Betamax was better.
[SPEAKER_03]: Minidisc was great.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the first thing that they've done in a long time that really caught on, I think that was Blu-ray.
[SPEAKER_06]: OneNightStands in chat asks, wasn't Zune a competitor for iTunes?
[SPEAKER_06]: Zune was a competitor for the iPod, and certainly Microsoft launched their own store to go with it, but it didn't really go... One could argue with me whether it was successful or not, but I think it's pretty clear iTunes has by far the most dominant share.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_06]: It hasn't really put a blip on the radar of what iTunes has.
[SPEAKER_06]: So whether they're still supporting that whole Microsoft marketplace or what, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: But we'll see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, how about some happy, happy, happy news?
[SPEAKER_06]: And just a moment, let me talk about this PSP rental service here real quick.
[SPEAKER_06]: There was a PSP survey that was hinting that a rental service might be on its way to the PSP, which is kind of interesting because we know that the PSP, you know, there's this new PSP coming out that nobody's confirming, but we all know it's probably happening.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to be announced at E3 this year.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a diskless PSP.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: VideoGaming, where instead of a company boohooing and yelling and bitching and screaming about blockbusters and Hollywood videos and places that rent video games and how they chip into game sales, a company deciding to, well, hell, we'll do game rentals of our own.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you can't beat them, join them.
[SPEAKER_06]: And we'll compete with them directly.
[SPEAKER_06]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: If this actually happens, that could be kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, why not?
[SPEAKER_06]: Apple has proved that it can happen with the movies on iTunes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why not rent games through a similar service?
[SPEAKER_06]: This could be big if it's true.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, it's all kind of a big grain of salt right now because a survey isn't the official word, but it could be very interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it could be.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's all I have.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I did have my happy news.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_03]: It has been confirmed!
[SPEAKER_03]: We are getting Tatsunoko vs. Capcom in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Nintendo Power Scan was true.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Capcom said on their Twitter that Tatsunoko vs. Capcom is being localized for a U.S.
[SPEAKER_03]: release.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, U.S., Canada, North America, whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: and the quote says Cat is officially out of the bag on Capcom Mystery Game number one and linked to the scan and then there was also one made by Capcom Unity on their blog but there's one more mystery game they should be having at E3 so I hope it doesn't suck
[SPEAKER_06]: and Renie in chat is yelling out with online and bug fixes.
[SPEAKER_06]: God, I hope that's true.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_06]: Especially if it's true they have to cut back a few characters.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, then, hell, let's make it better.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the characters that were listed on there aren't even in the damn game anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: We had some back and forth last week on whether those characters were really going to be there or not.
[SPEAKER_03]: The only Gatchaman characters that were in the game is Ken and June.
[SPEAKER_03]: Joe wasn't in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: If Joe was in it, I'd be screaming because I'd want him in the release.
[SPEAKER_03]: So...
[SPEAKER_06]: Rini in chat says Sky, Mystery Game number 2 is Mega Man Legends 3 on Wii God, I hope you're If you're lying to me So help me God That would be amazing though if that's the Mystery Game I would love that But it seems like it's all speculation to me
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Again, this is supposed to have a micro SD slot, SIM card tray, support for Bluetooth headphones in it, some optical digital output in there as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently it will actually work with Zunex Originals, Xbox Live and OnLive ready game streaming.
[SPEAKER_06]: There'll be a 32 gigabyte flash drive and the battery is built in and rechargeable.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it will bake scones.
[SPEAKER_06]: It just well might.
[SPEAKER_03]: And run Linux.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe there will be more info about this at E3.
[SPEAKER_03]: I dare whoever gets one of these to put Linux on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: That'll make me go squee for a little bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, this is something that probably won't make people squee.
[SPEAKER_03]: Although, to be completely honest, I don't think anyone will really freaking give a damn.
[SPEAKER_03]: Watchmen, the end is nigh.
[SPEAKER_03]: The second episode of it is not coming out for PC.
[SPEAKER_03]: And a sad trombone, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: It will come out on Xbox 360 and PS3 soon.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, of course, it's also going to be selling a special edition that has this and the first episode on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Warner is doing The Watchmen, The End is Nigh, Complete Experience.
[SPEAKER_03]: It has the PS3 versions and the director's cut of the film on Blu-ray.
[SPEAKER_03]: So maybe that'll be worth buying because the movie was freaking good, but meh, the rest of it, meh.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_03]: I can fart better games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, somebody out there might care.
[SPEAKER_06]: You don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Question in the chat room that I kind of like, and this is a very unpronounceable name, and I'm sorry, but RLBX327 asks, how would the new PSP work if a person does not have an internet connection?
[SPEAKER_06]: How would that work?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a great question, one that we'd all like to know the answer to as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm hoping we'll get some results at E3.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know if maybe you can take it into a game store and buy things that way, but I guess the assumption is everybody has an internet connection at this point.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like the DS download stations.
[SPEAKER_02]: Could be something similar?
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, there's definitely ways around it, but I think they just assume everybody has an internet connection.
[SPEAKER_06]: And even dial-up, if you have to.
[SPEAKER_06]: But who has dial-up anymore?
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess, well, I shouldn't say that, because there'll be somebody that sends me a message.
[SPEAKER_06]: Me, I have dial-up.
[SPEAKER_06]: My parents have dial-up.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, but, jeez, my iPod 3G's faster than their internet at home on dial-up.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I guess some areas still aren't wired for broadband But I guess you could still use a PSP Go on dial-up But maybe Sony is only marketing to those people that have internet connections I mean, let's face it, a vast portion of the population has an internet connection that's fast If every one of them bought a PSP Go, they would do very well So why bother catering to those that don't have an internet connection, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, this is the modern world.
[SPEAKER_03]: Everyone's supposed to be connected.
[SPEAKER_06]: SuperXLink in chat has an interesting comment.
[SPEAKER_06]: Go to a free Wi-Fi spot.
[SPEAKER_06]: Remember when... I think it was Nintendo did that at all the McDonald's?
[SPEAKER_06]: The McDonald's or something like that?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow, some more stories involving Capcom, actually, and talking about E3.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: Fully to attending the E3 They are still kind of contemplating What to do about the swine flu outbreak That's going on in Keihanshin, which is where Capcom's main office is in Japan Very interesting And what they're already saying is that because of this Dead Rising 2 is not going to be showing up at E3 Capcom has confirmed that Dead Rising 2 Not going to be there at E3 And this has to do with Japanese government restrictions And the advisory in Japan right now
[SPEAKER_06]: By the way, doesn't just end there, Square, Koei, also not attending E3 from their Japanese branches because of apparently swine flu concerns.
[SPEAKER_06]: A quote from an article on GamePolitics.com, quote, Square Enix has canceled plans for its Kingdom Hearts team to attend the show, whilst Koei has confirmed that an unspecified number of its Japanese employees will not be traveling to the event.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's sad face.
[SPEAKER_06]: Very, very sad.
[SPEAKER_03]: And also incredibly freaking stupid.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is incredibly stupid to still be concerned about the swine flu.
[SPEAKER_03]: My God.
[SPEAKER_03]: How many people contracted swine flu?
[SPEAKER_03]: Like what, 800?
[SPEAKER_03]: How many people died?
10?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, maybe 10 at most.
[SPEAKER_06]: But there was a couple, granted there was a couple thousand that got swine flu.
[SPEAKER_06]: But how many people get regular flu?
[SPEAKER_06]: All the time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fucking shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_06]: Seriously, I'm just... So the fact that stupid swine flu or H1N1 or whatever the fuck you want to call it is ruining E3.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fuck people.
[SPEAKER_06]: I say we dedicate the FUs of the week to this.
[SPEAKER_03]: My FU of the week goes to just those stupid people who are willing to believe any and everything that they see on TV, on the internet.
[SPEAKER_03]: You gullible, gullible fucking sheep.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hope you get swine flu.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just get it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hope you get swine flu of the colon.
[SPEAKER_03]: And can do nothing but shit viruses or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what I wish.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love you stupid people.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_03]: And also, I want Dick Cheney to shut up.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I just want people to shut up.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want people to shut up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Stop it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Knock it the fuck off.
[SPEAKER_06]: Can I talk?
[SPEAKER_03]: I want real news on my TV, I want real news, I want what's actually going on in the world I want to know what's going on outside of America, do you hear me CNN?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's why BBC America's news owns yours completely and utterly.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, it just does.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I like CNN.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like CNN much better than Fox News because Fox News is the shit that rats shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like the feces of slugs.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I hate slugs.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, you get more accuracy.
[SPEAKER_06]: You should have a political talk show.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have a blog whenever I post on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, I mean, seriously.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like, I think it's completely sad that to find out anything that's actually going on in America and in the world, I have to go to the BBC.
[SPEAKER_03]: It should be CNN or one of the good networks reporting our shit properly.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, big finger to our American media.
[SPEAKER_03]: A big finger to the gullible people who believe it.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know,
[SPEAKER_03]: I have a magnet on the door of my refrigerator that says listen to the effect of respect people that seek the truth doubt those who find it wow can I talk now?
[SPEAKER_06]: I actually don't have a lot so that's fine you went a little long because I don't really have anything my FU goes to drama I'm sick of it and I choose not to be around it so whatever I got better things to do
[SPEAKER_06]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Better things.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's it for the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_06]: How about something a little more pleasant?
[SPEAKER_06]: Even though this might drive us to some FUs, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently our mailbag is quite thin this week, and that's very sad.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mailbag at OrangeLaunchRadio.com is the place to send your emails.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the one and only DarkSakura will read them, as she'll do right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: What, we have like one, two maybe?
[SPEAKER_03]: One, actually, that came in while we were broadcasting from Cheeseburger.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey guys, I'm curious about your opinions on the new Star Trek movie.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've seen it three times.
[SPEAKER_03]: In a theater.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm 15, and I'm obsessed with Star Wars, but I never really saw anything in Star Trek.
[SPEAKER_03]: I saw the movie two weeks ago with no expectations, because I'd never experienced anything Star Trek before.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was blown away, and it was the first movie I'd ever gone to where everyone clapped at the end.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, all three times I saw it, people clapped.
[SPEAKER_03]: I knew I wanted to see it again as I was leaving the theater, which I did yesterday and plan to again next week.
[SPEAKER_03]: I plan on buying the old shows and movies on eBay to catch up on some of the older stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've researched some stuff about the movie and I'd like to say Red Shirt Guy dies if you know what that means.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're awesome if you don't go look it up.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not really a spoiler, just something they threw in from the old series.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dude, okay, I will give you the rule right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you're wearing a red shirt and no one knows who you are, you are going to die.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, next generation is yellow, but security officer, die, red shirt.
[SPEAKER_03]: In fact, they sell on ThinkGeek a red ringer t-shirt that says expendable on it in the Star Trek font.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will go ahead and say something, and I've said this before.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was not a Trekkie originally.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was a Whovian.
[SPEAKER_03]: I grew up watching Doctor Who on PBS and not watching Star Trek, although I've seen a number of the original episodes in almost all of Next Generation and maybe a smattering here of DS9 and Voyager, and I watched three episodes of Enterprise and decided it was shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_03]: and you know it's I actually you know I purchased something recently that was like the best four episodes of Star Trek ever the original series and they're great episodes and I want to say if you want to get a feel for the original series that will give you a decent smattering of what to expect just get this it's four episodes and among them are the one of them is Trouble with Tribbles which is supposed to be like the big favorite and I love that episode and
[SPEAKER_03]: And also, it's just fantastic.
[SPEAKER_03]: But yeah, go get some of those little samples first.
[SPEAKER_03]: See how you feel about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like Next Generation.
[SPEAKER_03]: Going back and watching a bunch of it, though, you're going to find it really dated.
[SPEAKER_03]: The old stuff will hold up because you expect it to be old, but Next Generation, we're talking about when I was early high school, 1990.
[SPEAKER_06]: Next Generation now, believe it or not, is getting to be 20 years old.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's kind of like, oh boy.
[SPEAKER_03]: But...
[SPEAKER_03]: DS9 you know I didn't watch much of it I'm actually going to be going back and watching a bunch of it just because from what I understand it's probably the best of the series Voyager has its ups and downs I've seen crap episodes I've seen great episodes and yeah I'm sorry Jerry Ryan is hot but Enterprise is like I keep expecting Scott Bakula to jump I'm sorry to leap because he was you know from Quantum Leap I do want to remind though Jerry Ryan didn't show up until season 4 no that's right so
[SPEAKER_06]: By the way, Star Trek, me personally, loved it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loved the movie, thought it was great.
[SPEAKER_06]: It definitely kind of, J.J.
[SPEAKER_06]: Abrams definitely said, I am fucking turning this car around right the fuck now and taking it in a new direction, but it needed it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It needed it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hope we get a new series out of it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, even if the series isn't related to the movie, I hope it invigorates interest in Star Trek enough that we do get the uber nerdy series in the Voyager, Next Generation, Deep Space Nine canon.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, I want to see a new show like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's not Enterprise.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, I'll tell you what.
[SPEAKER_03]: They've confirmed writing on the sequel now and got the whole cast.
[SPEAKER_06]: And don't get me wrong, I'm thrilled about that too, but where's my weekly dose?
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to see that too.
[SPEAKER_06]: That would be very exciting.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think I could watch the movie a million times in a theater like DarkSakura does.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe I'd see it one more time, but I'll just buy it on Blu-ray when it comes out.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I have to do it by season.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, original season?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, in the movie, I'm going to say right now, Scotty.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because, I'm sorry, I love Simon Pegg.
[SPEAKER_03]: Between him and Carl Urban, I'm sorry, that made the movie for me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Carl Urban's McCoy was perfect.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, oh my god.
[SPEAKER_03]: Southern guy.
[SPEAKER_03]: He just did the accent and everything just right.
[SPEAKER_03]: It made me really happy.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, Simon Pegg as Scotty was just like, Actually, he was probably my favorite in the original series, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Next Generation, it depends.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because as a kid, I was that age.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was a Wesley fangirl.
[SPEAKER_03]: But getting older, it's all about Q. All about Q. I love Q. I love every bit of Q. So I'd actually have to say Q for Voyager as well since we've had Q. And I think that Seven and the Doctor are funny together.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, the Doctor was probably my favorite in Voyager.
[SPEAKER_03]: For DS9, I'd actually have to say Jadzia or Worf.
[SPEAKER_03]: I really liked Odo, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: My favorite was Guinan.
[SPEAKER_06]: Guinan will always be my favorite.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, Whoopi.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love Whoopi.
[SPEAKER_06]: What can I say?
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're being way too... This is a video game show.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I will say this.
[SPEAKER_06]: The fact that Star Trek is being made into this MMO, please don't suck.
[SPEAKER_06]: Please don't suck.
[SPEAKER_03]: Remember, I'm still making the race the Olarians.
[SPEAKER_06]: Please, if there's God out there, do not let this game suck.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because right now, Star Trek is riding such a high, high wave.
[SPEAKER_06]: And there is so much potential.
[SPEAKER_06]: But at the same time, there is so much they could fuck up beyond all belief.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I am praying that this game doesn't suck.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I will be leaving all my other MMOs to play it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have to quote GameGuru on this, because honestly, I fully agree with this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Carl Urbans McCoy makes me wonder if reincarnation exists.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's it for the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you want to send us some emails, mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, guys, your call soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: But first, we have a little bit of gaming news for you guys and, of course, the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_06]: We haven't forgot that yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: But one more news story for you guys has to do with Forza Motorsport 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think y'all know it's coming.
[SPEAKER_06]: Y'all know it had to happen.
[SPEAKER_06]: And sure enough, the German retail version of Amazon.com called Amazon.de has listed Forza Motorsport 3, Prima's official game guide, out on September 30th.
[SPEAKER_06]: Whoops!
[SPEAKER_06]: Forza Motorsport 3 is coming at some point.
[SPEAKER_06]: Comments in chat.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why didn't you read my email?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because you sent it too late.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll read it next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll go to the email.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not the emails.
[SPEAKER_06]: We already went to the emails.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll go to the Classic Game of the Week now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Every week here on Orange Lounge Radio, DarkSakura likes to dig through the archives and find a game she thinks y'all ought to be playing.
[SPEAKER_06]: So here it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: Classic Game of the Week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Classic Game of the Week is beer pong.
[SPEAKER_03]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's actually DuckTales.
[SPEAKER_03]: Woo-hoo.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's about damn time I picked this one.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't actually put in a gameplay one up because I wanted the best music in the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's the moon music.
Sorry, moon level had the best music.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, so anyway, um, it is, um, of course, based off of the, uh, the Disney TV show, and it came out on Nintendo in 1989, and so you basically go around as Scrooge McDuck, um, who is going around to collect treasures all over the world, and the moon!
[SPEAKER_03]: It came out on Game Boy, and it has nothing to do with DuckTales Quest for Gold.
[SPEAKER_03]: So basically, this is really one of the top Capcom games from the Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_03]: It actually had Tokoro Fujiwara and Yuki-chan's papa.
[SPEAKER_03]: You gotta read the credits on some of the old Capcom games, I love it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was, you know, really tight to play.
[SPEAKER_03]: You could use Scrooge's cane as a weapon and a PocoStick and was non-linear.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, so basically you're going around and you're helping NPCs and whacking enemies with a cane and telling them to get off your lawn or whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, and you can actually play any of the levels in order, like I said, non-linear.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, you have a boss you have to fight at the end of each level, two hidden treasures, um, there's a golden ring in the African Mines and a golden mirror in the moon level, and after you've done all that, you go to Transylvania for some reason to do the boss fight.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you can keep going back and unlock different parts of levels and do different stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you've got basically your DuckTales characters.
[SPEAKER_03]: You have Scrooge, you have Kiwi, Dewey, and Lily, Webby, Gizmo, Duck, Launchpad, McQuack, Gyro, Gearloose, Ms.
[SPEAKER_03]: Beakley, Bubba, Magica, Dispel, who is in Traptopania, Flintheart, Glomgold, and the Beagle Boys.
[SPEAKER_03]: and then you also have an alternate ending in the NES version where if you finish the game with 10 million dollars and have both of the hidden treasures then you will have...
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh, the news article come up with Scrooge winning, but he has a crown on his head, and a paper stating that he has stunned the world with his discovery of two lost treasures.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, so yeah, it was by, um, Capcom.
[SPEAKER_03]: There were actually, there was actually a beta version that was out, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, and, uh, actually we were releasing the Consumer's Guide Hot Tip for, uh, coolest Nintendo's game.
[SPEAKER_03]: At different levels, there was the Jungle, Ghost House, Underground, Snow Mountain, and Moon Surface.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hamburgers were your power-ups instead of ice cream.
[SPEAKER_03]: There, the coffins in the Ghost House had, um, uh, crosses on them, the coffins, sorry, had crosses on them instead of R.E.P.,
[SPEAKER_03]: um although if you look in the NES Atlas um there are pictures of the original uh the moon music has a slower tempo music and I've actually heard it it's actually pretty good
[SPEAKER_03]: The Ghost House had a different music track, and Gizmoduck went by Roboduck.
[SPEAKER_03]: In the French version, it was called La Bande  Pichot.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's the same DuckTales thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the Famicom version was called One Paku Daku Yume Boken, which is Naughty Duck's Dream Adventure.
[SPEAKER_03]: and it didn't have all the censorship.
[SPEAKER_03]: So there was a DuckTales 2 game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was not as popular.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, it really, though, is... And by the way, Yuki-chan's papa is Yoshihiro Sakaguchi.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, yay.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's really one of the classic, classic, classics.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, like, I had to play the moon level music first.
[SPEAKER_03]: That is the identifiable stage.
[SPEAKER_03]: You play the beginning of that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And anyone who knows their gaming history will be able to point that right out.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, maybe that'll be Capcom's surprise announcement.
[SPEAKER_06]: They have a secondary surprise announcement, they're supposed to make at E3, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: How about DuckTales 3 on the Wii?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the sound you would hear across the world, fanboys shitting their pants.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, also, just to say, you know, if we want to even look at any more of Yoshihiro Sakaguchi's games, we have 1943, well, 1943 Kai.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have Final Fight, Legendary Wings, Forgotten Worlds, Mega Man, Mega Man 2 We have Street Fighter and Street Fighter 2, did sound design, Warriors of Fate So, pretty cool Very cool OneNightStands asks, hey DarkSakura, exactly why was this such a great game?
[SPEAKER_06]: I loved it as a kid, but it plays like a lot of other platformers
[SPEAKER_03]: It just really, it's all of the elements combined.
[SPEAKER_03]: Really, when you look at everything together, it's all those pieces.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I mean, yeah, there were a lot of platformers on the NES, but I think you had so many things falling into place on this one.
[SPEAKER_06]: You had a pretty good game, which is very important.
[SPEAKER_06]: You had a great license.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you go back and do your favorite levels as much as you wanted to.
[SPEAKER_06]: Right.
[SPEAKER_06]: You had, you know, it was kind of like that Mega Man mixed with...
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, like Mario style platformer and great music.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, just everything kind of fell into place with this game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think one other reason, think about all the crap movie and cartoon and TV show tie-in games you have.
[SPEAKER_02]: God, I know, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: DuckTales breaks that mold.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I think that might be one reason why people love it so much is that DuckTales was actually a pretty enjoyable game at the time it came out.
[SPEAKER_03]: I really think so.
[SPEAKER_06]: That would be my best answer.
[SPEAKER_03]: I really agree with that.
[SPEAKER_03]: That, Rob, dear friend, is a proper assessment
[SPEAKER_06]: If you have more questions you want to ask us, our Skype line is open right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can call right now and give us a call.
[SPEAKER_06]: In the meantime, I'm going to ask if there's any last minute stories.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't have anything.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think DarkSakura would have anything.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually... You never know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, gosh.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, let's go to the phones.
[SPEAKER_06]: We got a call.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, you're on... Shut that thing up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_01]: Hi, this is Spazinator.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, Spazinator.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's on your mind tonight?
[SPEAKER_01]: Not much.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was going to join the IRC chat, but unfortunately it won't work on my PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_01]: If you heard the Tale in a Bible show, I was asking about possibly buying an arcade machine.
[SPEAKER_01]: What I'm specifically looking for is a classic game from the 80s up until the mid-90s.
[SPEAKER_01]: Are you looking to buy a specific game?
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you looking to collect or are you just looking to play?
[SPEAKER_06]: I collect.
[SPEAKER_01]: I would go eBay, honestly.
[SPEAKER_03]: eBay or flea markets.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or even like Craigslist.
[SPEAKER_03]: Denios here in Roosevelt, Sacramento area, they sell old arcade cabinets.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can even check some of the entertainment companies that rent out the games and ask if they're putting anything for sale.
[SPEAKER_03]: eBay, Craigslist, Amazon, we've come to them that way.
[SPEAKER_06]: Newspapers
[SPEAKER_06]: so if you buy a game from the west coast you know you're going to have to pay an arm and a leg in shipping fees so you probably want to stick to things I mean you can certainly find your widest selection there on eBay but you would definitely want to stick to things like Craigslist and things that are going to be a little more local in your areas that you don't have to pay that obscene shipping fee you have the perk of having New York City not too too far away if you're especially willing to drive and pick something up with a pickup truck you can probably get some good deals
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, the thing is, I never drove a day in my life.
[SPEAKER_01]: I never bothered to get my license.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I don't think, well, I don't have any relatives that really live in the area that have a driver's license and have enough free time on their hands that would be willing to essentially take me out to wherever, you know,
[SPEAKER_01]: to pick up our kid gathering and drive her back to my place.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, that's fair.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, if you don't have a license yourself, it's going to be kind of harder to get around and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you may have to fork over those shipping fees, but just be prepared.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's going to be shipping fees, and sometimes they're as much as the games are themselves because you're talking about sending a gigantic cabinet, which basically has to go on the back of a truck.
[SPEAKER_06]: You are going to be spending a couple hundred dollars on shipping, so that's something you've got to prepare yourself for when shopping.
[SPEAKER_06]: But if you can afford it, if that's within your budget, go for it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, you know, if I do, you know, decide to go forward with this and get one, it'll probably be probably a few months before I get it.
[SPEAKER_01]: But, you know, I kind of figured, you know, this would probably go hand in hand with, you know, my councils.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, it would be a nice conversation piece to talk about.
[SPEAKER_01]: And not only that, but, you know, I kind of miss...
[SPEAKER_01]: The whole arcade experience that I used to have when I was a little kid, going to the pizzeria to play games.
[SPEAKER_01]: You're going to get one game.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I know there's people that would spend a lot of money to have
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I have like a top five wish list.
[SPEAKER_06]: It would be like...
[SPEAKER_01]: World of Combat 2, Super Street Fighter 2 Turbo, and then of course, Killer Instinct 2, and...
[SPEAKER_01]: and then like the Neo Geo MVS, the four-slot one.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now that, you know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: Look into that.
[SPEAKER_06]: That sounds like it might be a great option for you is those Neo Geo cabinets because of the fact you can fit like four games in there and that way you get that classic collectible thing mixed in with, hey, I have more than just one game in here.
[SPEAKER_06]: That might be a good thing to look into.
[SPEAKER_06]: But the good news is with those fighting games, they made so many of them, especially Street Fighter IIs, I'm sure you wouldn't have a hard time finding one at all.
[SPEAKER_06]: Finding a working one,
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Goodbye.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rene says Prop Cycle, the poor man's DDR
[SPEAKER_06]: Vid Power says Simpsons Arcade and let's see what else is there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Captain Yes said I would kill for a Super Scope cabinet.
[SPEAKER_06]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: We just had Skype crash.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was weird.
[SPEAKER_06]: At least it didn't crash my whole computer.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank God.
[SPEAKER_06]: Skype just crashed sadly and I was in the middle of a call when it did so so I apologize to the caller.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hopefully they will be able to get through again but I am firing Skype back up so we can take more calls and we look like we're back up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry about that.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's kind of crappy.
[SPEAKER_06]: 1-877-GAME-OLR, username on Skype.
[SPEAKER_06]: Live radio, guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sometimes Skype will crash on us as we're doing the show live.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I like what Bobby in chat is saying, talking about getting a 2DX cabinet.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, I think if I were to drop the money, I'd have to get something Mamani-related.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I think I'd get a 2DX.
[SPEAKER_03]: Honestly, I think I'd want a Happy Sky.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, we got another call.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_00]: Wow, I can't believe I got through for this.
[SPEAKER_00]: This is my first time calling.
[SPEAKER_00]: This is X-Link.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, hi, X-Link.
[SPEAKER_06]: Congratulations on making it through.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: You lucked out because some other, unfortunately, we were on the line with another call and then Skype crashed.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I really feel bad, but that's just live radio sometimes.
[SPEAKER_06]: And hey, you got through and you've never been on before.
[SPEAKER_06]: So what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, first off, I don't know exactly about the pinball games exactly.
[SPEAKER_00]: Arcade, I'm sorry, arcade games.
[SPEAKER_00]: I know a little more about pinballs than I do arcade because I used to work on them working at arcade.
[SPEAKER_00]: But yeah, the ones like Street Fighters and the use of those ones are a little more commonplace to find than you would with some of the other ones.
[SPEAKER_00]: The more newer they are, the easier to find, of course.
[SPEAKER_00]: The more harder they're to find is the more older they are, so...
[SPEAKER_00]: You really would have to search, and I know he's overseas, so that would probably be even more hard than it is over here in the US, where it's a tad bit more commonplace, maybe than, say, over here in Sweden.
[SPEAKER_06]: It really depends on all of those factors, but I do agree, the best way to find an arcade game without having to pay all the shipping, look for an arcade near you that's closing down.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, no joke.
[SPEAKER_00]: um but like I said before we closed down unfortunately my arcade we had like four and a half pages full of arcade different arcade games so I mean yeah if I want this nearly getting ready to close down you probably can pick one up for a good price well there you go hopefully uh the advice will be taken even though I think that last caller wasn't overseas they're upstate New York but I know we do have other listeners that are overseas that can take that um uh advice to heart well what else is on your mind
[SPEAKER_00]: Glee, great show, first off.
[SPEAKER_00]: But I was calling more in tone to THQ and their golden weed that they sent over to overseas there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Glee was amazing, by the way.
[SPEAKER_06]: If folks need a new TV show to watch, even though there's only the one episode, definitely reminded me of being a music geek in high school.
[SPEAKER_06]: Before we made it a short show tonight when Loki wasn't able to be here, we were going to talk about the Golden Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tell us a little bit about this and what you wanted to say about it.
[SPEAKER_00]: THQ which unfortunately lost a major amount of money over the last year which I thought that was even more ironic decided to send a golden Wii overseas to the UK to give to the Queen as a thank you
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you for what?
[SPEAKER_06]: Just being queenly?
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, it's a way to promote their new game.
[SPEAKER_00]: Gotcha.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was going to say, though, come on, I don't think the queen is really going to play this Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, you know, she's obviously a little old, and I think every time I've seen her on TV and stuff, she seems to have limited mobility.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sure some would argue with me whether that means she can't play the Wii or not, but, you know, come on.
[SPEAKER_06]: She's the freaking queen of England.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think she's got better things to do than sit there and play the Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: However, I think it's one of those things that you'll see in a museum someday, is the Wii the queen once owned, even though she never touched it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Actually, she has a, supposedly she was playing the Wii before with the prince.
[SPEAKER_00]: Supposedly there was articles about that.
[SPEAKER_00]: So that's why they sent her over one, so she could have one of her own.
[SPEAKER_06]: I stand corrected.
[SPEAKER_06]: What a great photo op that must have been.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: and if I'm wrong, then I'm wrong again.
[SPEAKER_06]: What else is new?
[SPEAKER_00]: Nah, that's pretty much about it I can think of.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm looking forward to see what comes out of E3 in a couple weeks out of all these rumors and stuff.
[SPEAKER_00]: Let's see which ones are true and which ones are false.
[SPEAKER_06]: Me too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Out of curiosity, since OLR can't compete with the commercial sites, what do you want us to bring you from E3?
[SPEAKER_00]: Whatever news is not given, I guess, because a lot of it's going to be hard because a lot of the news soon is going to break.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's going to be posted all over the web and Twitter and Facebook and all that.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's going to be harder this year.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's no Kensha Hall for everyone to ignore or do the nice fluff piece that is the one article on the entirety of Kensha Hall.
[SPEAKER_06]: From what I understand, we're not having that this year, so it's going to be difficult to really dig around, but we will try to find the Kensha in E3 for you guys.
[SPEAKER_00]: What I would like to see is maybe even what the independent people are doing.
[SPEAKER_00]: What are some of these games that are below key that should have been the major hits that are maybe not as hits?
[SPEAKER_06]: I will do my best to dig up the independent stuff for you guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that's where we're going to have to find our niche this year.
[SPEAKER_06]: I bet there's a lot of people that want to be heard and they're going to be excited to have somebody care.
[SPEAKER_06]: And certainly, you know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's find the next Braid.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's find the next Katamari Damacy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's find that next big thing that hasn't been discovered yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like that idea.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, X-Link, we've got to let you go so we can take some more calls.
[SPEAKER_06]: But thank you so much, first-time caller.
[SPEAKER_06]: No problem.
[SPEAKER_06]: Call us again sometime.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, definitely.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, later, dude.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll take some more calls.
[SPEAKER_06]: By the way, some other comments from chatroom on what they want to see from E3.
[SPEAKER_06]: RLBX327 wants to know about the iPhone games at E3.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actdeft says, King of Fighter 12 details.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, I did get an email about a pre-tournament that's going on, but it's going on, like, I think the Sunday before E3, so sadly we'll still be here.
[SPEAKER_06]: We can't go.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I know there's going to be some tournaments going on.
[SPEAKER_06]: AlphaCatanagram wants some Katamari Forever footage and a soundtrack bootleg.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know how Namco would feel about a bootleg on our site, but we'll try.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hello, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hello, welcome to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, the caller isn't there apparently.
[SPEAKER_06]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Remember, you can always test the calls before giving us a call at echo123 is the username on Skype.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's a great way to make sure that your microphone is working and all that fun stuff before you actually call us.
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course, that doesn't work with a touchtone phone.
[SPEAKER_06]: Touchtone phones are much easier though.
[SPEAKER_06]: You just pick up the phone and call.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think I've ever seen a phone not work, although I have seen them be quite...
[SPEAKER_06]: DJ Ranma S, I went to Anime Boston 2009 this weekend on Saturday
[SPEAKER_06]: Ah, and how was that?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm happy to hear that there was some OLR meetups going on, because I know somewhere in the Bay Area right now, GS68 is crying because he's the only OLR guy at Faname, which I'm very sad I didn't get to this year, but next year, next year.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, how was Anime Boston?
[SPEAKER_06]: It was good.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess it was my first convention.
[SPEAKER_05]: I really didn't know what to expect, but...
[SPEAKER_05]: It was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_05]: One of the first things I did was find DJ Ranma S. He was selling some stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: He didn't seem to have any good luck this weekend, but he said overall he had a good time, I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess he'll be calling in maybe next week to talk about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think he's getting home late.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I'm sure he will.
[SPEAKER_06]: Today's his birthday, too, if I'm not mistaken, so happy birthday to that if you're listening.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: Everybody wish him a happy birthday.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know I did.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, you know, and this crosses over into video games too, because I'll tell you, you can't walk through one of these hallways without seeing some Kingdom Hearts inspired, you know, fan art or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you see any art?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know if you looked around the art.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you see some art that really jumped out of you that you thought was awesome?
[SPEAKER_06]: And what was it?
[SPEAKER_05]: I saw a lot of stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: I saw anything from like anime stuff from like Death Note.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've seen the typical stereotypical stupid Naruto stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's just my opinion, not fact, but that's not my thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I also found video game stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like basically, what did you say you were wondering if there was there?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know there's always something Kingdom Hearts, but did anything kind of jump out at you?
[SPEAKER_06]: Kingdom Hearts, yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, let me give you an example.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let me give you an example.
[SPEAKER_06]: When I was at ASEN, I actually bought this.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought it was so rad because I bought it for my boyfriend, who I know is a big fan of this.
[SPEAKER_06]: But they actually had an art dealer table, and she had a drawing of David Bowie from Labyrinth.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I just thought that was so awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm like, how random to find something like that at an anime con.
[SPEAKER_06]: But did you see anything that jumped out at you like that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, wow, I didn't expect to see that at an art dealer table.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess pretty much everything was unexpected for me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like I said, this was my first con.
[SPEAKER_05]: I saw, I mean, they were selling a little... I also have a friend in chat called Robocon that doesn't seem to get to listen to OLR a lot, but he tries to catch the podcast.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's live in there now.
[SPEAKER_05]: We went together on Saturday and they had little buttons they were selling for $0.50 to $1.
[SPEAKER_05]: I got a little thing from The World Ends With You, that little pin that you'd get in that portable RPG game that says you're in the game thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: And yeah, The World Ends With You definitely has its fans, especially the Squeenix fans.
[SPEAKER_06]: So okay, cool, cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I also saw something interesting as a stained glass thing of various Death Note anime characters.
[SPEAKER_05]: It had the character, the Detective L, but it was like a vampire version of him with blue hair.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think they used the ballroom for the video game thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: What kind of games did you see in the room when you went there?
[SPEAKER_05]: I saw they had a Street Fighter 4 tournament going on.
[SPEAKER_05]: I finally got to play poppin' music.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was a pretty cool experience.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love poppin' music.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's why I brought that up.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the interesting thing is they did have the Rock Band 2 set up on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: The interesting thing I saw was the Nintendo Wii that they had actually was running on the Homebrew channel.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Homebrew channel which allows you to run like...
[SPEAKER_05]: Selfmade Applications, among other things.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they were using it for perfectly legitimate reasons, so I thought it was kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, I've got one more question for you before we let you go, and it actually comes from our chat room from our good buddy Bobby Blackwolf, heard before us here Sunday nights on All Games Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bobby asks, Anime Boston is in the same place as PAX Boston is going to be.
[SPEAKER_06]: How is the size of the place?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because some people are speculating it may not be big enough for an event the size of PAX.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, I think, I think that it's, well, I think there's like three floors, um, three, I think it's like a three floor place, and, uh, we were all around it, and, uh, it's pretty big, it really is, it's bigger than I thought it was gonna be.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like, there's a mall that's like attached to it, like, and we got some food there afterwards, but it's pretty big, I mean, even without that, the convention center itself, I mean...
[SPEAKER_05]: so yeah I think it could handle PAX East because I mean the attendance just keeps climbing every year on Anime Boston as it is so yeah it could probably handle that that's interesting news because I was I saw that the I was expecting it to be Memorial Day weekend the next week and it wasn't so I saw that it was like April 2nd or 4th from Anime Boston so probably somebody else like took the Memorial Day weekend it happens it happens there's a lot of big conventions Memorial Day weekend
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, well, we gotta let you go, buddy, but thanks so much for the report, and glad to hear you enjoyed your first con.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks a lot, Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe I'll see you at PAX Boston, speaking of which, since it sounds like it's in the neck of the woods.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll see what I can do.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll have to work things out, but we'll meet someday.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll see you later.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll get you next time, Gadget.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll do one more call if it comes in pretty soon here on the phones.
[SPEAKER_06]: How are you doing over there, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm doing fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm actually checking for video game sims.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh yeah?
[SPEAKER_03]: I found one of Leon Kennedy from Resident Evil 4, so that's a pretty good one.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, I still have yet to play Resident Evil 5.
[SPEAKER_06]: What the hell's wrong with me?
[SPEAKER_06]: But outside of the demo.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, well, our phones sadly are not really ringing right now, so we're going to go ahead and close up the lines.
[SPEAKER_04]: Damn it, call!
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it's too late.
[SPEAKER_06]: I closed up the lines.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're at about an hour and a half now anyway, and
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to go run out and get some food and enjoy the rest of my Memorial Day weekend as I'm sure a lot of you folks do.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we're going to go ahead and go around and start to wrap things up and get on out of here for the evening.
[SPEAKER_02]: In ribbons and bows?
[SPEAKER_06]: If we want to.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll go around and get everybody's final thought.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess we'll start with me tonight, although I don't have much of a final thought tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: My final thought is yogurt.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want yogurt.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want some too.
[SPEAKER_06]: It would be amazing right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: It would be some yogurt.
[SPEAKER_03]: It would be fantastical.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not FroGurt, but Yogurt.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because the FroGurt has potassium benzoate.
[SPEAKER_06]: Never mind.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, what's your final thought tonight?
[SPEAKER_03]: Porn.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: Again, if you like the show, please tell two people you know about the program.
[SPEAKER_06]: Help spread the good word about the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Help offset those a-holes that leave negative reviews on websites because they have nothing better to do with their sorry ass lives.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because it really helps us have the motivation to keep going when you guys say good things about us.
[SPEAKER_06]: And just knowing we have certain people that would be here every week.
[SPEAKER_03]: I also like when you send me money.
[SPEAKER_06]: Although sometimes it can be frustrating when people bitch and moan and bellyache when you go a week without a show or that the podcast was late or whatever, it does show that people care enough to complain.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I actually kind of see the good in that and thanks everybody for your passion around the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: That is very motivating, surprisingly enough.
[SPEAKER_06]: So keep us on our toes, I guess is what I'm saying.
[SPEAKER_03]: Twinkle toes.
[SPEAKER_06]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, that's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're out of here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have a great night, everybody, and tune in next week.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll be back with more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have a great night.
[SPEAKER_07]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_07]: To join us for a live show, visit www.allgames.com Sunday nights at 6pm Pacific Time.
[SPEAKER_07]: The views and opinions expressed on Orange Lounge Radio do not necessarily reflect those of the entire staff of Orange Lounge Radio or allgames.com, but we're probably right anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: See you next week!